Why do the FBI
always stick their morgues
in the most depressing basement
they can find?
Don't be such
a snob, Bones.
Okay, not everyone
gets to play
in a multi-million-
dollar lab, you know,
with skylights...
It's because,
as a society,
we feel the need
to hide death away.
The people who deal
with the dead
are viewed as freaks.
Yeah. I don't know if
it's the basement thing,
but this guy you're
about to meet-- Harry--
he's a bit twisted.
You probably think I get
some kind of rush when I work,
that I'm somehow
titillated.
Uh, choice of
words, Bones,
choice of words.
Agent Booth.
Harry Tepper,
meet Dr. Temperance Brennan
from the Jeffersonian.
Hmm, I've read her.
Hello.
She's good.
Read your novel, too.
The heroine's very aggressive.
Harry, you want to...?
Okay, everybody, meet Ted Macy.
Body was found
in a national park.
Local coroner wrote it off
as some kind
of an accidental drowning,
but you see, we have
to investigate
every death on federal land.
During my examination,
I found he had
a crushed larynx.
That didn't seem accidental.
This is a corpse
with skin.
She is good.
Why am I here?
Relax, Bones.
I didn't bring you here
to examine the body.
I want you to see what
they found in his hand.
Harry, the bone?
What is that?
It's a phalanx.
Finger bone.
Figured she'd know that.
Yeah, I'd figure
any competent medical examiner
would know not to
compromise evidence.
Is this Lysol IC?
We use it
to decontaminate remains.
Are you trying to break down
the periosteal surface
of the bone,
wreak havoc
on the marrow?
Did you even dilute this?
Bones...
What?!
You've removed particulates
and trace elements
that could potentially lead us
to his killer.
Is this your first day
on the job?
18 years next month.
She's intense.
Native American.
British Colonial.
American Revolutionary.
Hey, what are we playing?
Dr. Brennan, the destroyer
of evidence is here.
Okay, I assume that's a joke,
so nobody gets hurt.
Did Harry really mess up
that bone?
He dissolved
any traces
of ingrained particulates
on the surface,
but we were still
able to save
some valuable
attributes.
Like what?
Alternating sclerotic
and porotic areas on
subperiosteal surface
demonstrates that
whoever this was
suffered from
tertiary syphilis.
Tertiary syphilis. Whoa.
Wow, that's the worst.
It was a common ailment
in the 17th century.
Which is where
the bone dates from.
Say what?
We ran a radiocarbon
dating test.
The finger's over
300 years old.
It's a unique find
for the area.
I'm going to change
to French trapper.
You can't change yours.
Booth, where did they find
the victim?
They shipped him
over from some resort town
next to a federal
seaside reserve:
Assateague Island.
That's where the Money Pit is.
Money Pit?
Legend is,
Assateague Island is where
Blackbeard buried his treasure.
For 300 years,
people have been
trying to find it.
They've dug it
out to something
like 150 feet,
but they've found nothing.
Every time they come close,
they trigger a baffle
that floods the pit
with sea water.
Booby traps.
Cool.
The body was found
at a dig site.
This is the first
concrete evidence
that the treasure
is more than a legend.
I'll bet this is
from one of the men
who buried
the treasure.
Pure conjecture.
Pirate.
Pirate?
It's a pirate.
"You can't change yours."
Wait, so the victim
finds evidence
that the treasure exists.
Somebody else wants it all
for themselves.
That's certainly...
that's a good motive for murder.
I'll be glad to help.
That's okay. I-I can handle it.
Come on, man, share the wealth.
We're looking for answers, Jack,
not treasure.
Do you really think
that treasure exists down there?
What do you think?
Why are you guys smiling?
Pirates!
It's a guy thing, sweetie.
So, the dead guy, Macy,
ran the dig?
With his partner, Hardewicke.
They were hired
by anyone with money to burn.
What, people
would do that?
Sane people look
for treasure?
Well, isn't that what
archeologists do?
Archeologists are scientists
who use evidence
on which to base
their explorations,
not some pirate movie
they saw when they were ten.
Yeah, well, that,
uh, 300-year-old bone
that we just found
sort of, uh,
changes things now,
doesn't it there, matey?
What's going
on over there?
The mayor told me to let him in.
Branson Rose is
funding this dig?
Has been
for two years.
But I heard he was pulling out.
All right, thanks.
I'll take it from here.
Sure.
Who's Branson Rose?
The billionaire
adventurer.
You know, he
made his fortune
making aircraft
for the military.
He owns about half
the world.
He's the guy
who has that reality show
that goes
all over the world and...
Still no TV?
Why do I even bother?
You can't pull
out now, Mr. Rose.
We got a contract.
So you can sue,
but I don't think
you have the resources
to take me on.
Mr. Rose,
we just broke 200 feet!
I've been hearing that for
two years, Hardewicke.
Get off your asses
and load my gear!
Excuse me?
Mr. Rose, Macy--
he knew it.
He felt it.
This close!
Excuse me.
ROSE:
Two years, $2 million.
There's nothing
down there, Giles.
Macy died for nothing.
FBI! You're all
under arrest!
Come on, Bones,
you don't get to say that.
I'm the one with the badge.
The FBI's involved now?
Oh, yeah. You know,
murder on federal land--
we like to, uh,
poke around a little.
Murder?
Yeah, murder.
You said
it was an accident.
That's what I thought.
Oh, my God...
He found something.
Put my stuff back now!
What did Macy find
that would be worth
killing him for?
Cync by xxy
www.1000fr.com
In 1832, a team of six men
looking for the treasure
were killed when a shaft
they were digging collapsed.
Blackbeard's curse, man.
A curse?
We're scientists.
Look at this. 1902.
Two men disappeared
while digging.
Never found
their bodies.
Oh, that's very cursey.
So you believe
in pirates?
Pirates aren't Santa, Zack.
They did exist.
They did have treasures,
and they did bury it.
You know, I had an eye
patch when I was six.
Who didn't, my friend?
Who didn't?
It's not necessary to
lead me like a child.
I'd rather not have
any more evidence compromised.
You're squeezing my
arm very tightly.
Sorry.
No, no, it's okay.
You can give it
to Dr. Hodgins.
What is this?
Soil and water collected
from Ted Macy's
throat and lungs.
He was found floating
in his dry suit
at the top of the shaft.
All right,
you know what?
We need you to do
your dirt thing.
You know, match the
slime to the crime,
make sure that's
where he was killed.
I'd like to look at X rays
of the victim's skeleton.
Bossy.
Do not go there.
In the interest
of being thorough,
I need to determine
if he died at the top
or died at the bottom
and floated up.
I need silt abstracts
from both levels.
Fine. We'll get those for you.
No, no. No.
The soil looks
like an odd mixture of clay,
plagioclase feldspar,
pyroxene...
I really wouldn't trust
anyone else
to harvest the samples properly.
You just want
to look for treasure.
I am a serious scientist
merely trying to do my job
as well as possible.
That shaft is
over 200 feet deep, you know.
It requires
an experienced diver.
I am a certified cave diver,
which means I can go deeper
than 200 feet.
I dove Mayan Blue,
Dos Ojos, Tortuga...
Ever dive Naharon?
Once.
I named Naharon.
Well, then how
can you say no to me?
Okay...
but just to collect
soil samples.
Of course.
So, you dive, too?
I have the time because
I don't own a TV.
You wear a rubber
suit, then?
Accidents happen, you know.
Macy and I were prepared
for that, but murder?
Murder. Wow.
Anything I can do to help...
Okay, we'll talk about
that a little later.
Right now, I want to get
Hodgins down that shaft.
Dane McGinnis.
He-he's the best
I know.
Uh, he's worked
for us for years.
Agent Booth?
Are you Agent Booth?
You're going to have to stay
behind the yellow tape.
I'm Mayor Ney.
Your men keep pushing
our tourists
further
and further back.
Mayor? Wow.
I-I hope you didn't look
like that when they elected you.
Blackbeard's treasure
is what keeps the economy
on this little island running.
sometimes too intensely.
Hey, I'm not ashamed.
I've increased tourism 63%
since I took office,
and I can boost it a bit more
if the tourists could get
a closer look.
It's a murder scene, not a show.
Blackbeard's curse.
Macy would've wanted to give
a little back
to the town that he loved.
Frank, the police are
telling them no pictures.
Now, who is this, huh?
The Pirate Queen?
That's right.
My wife, Katie.
That's right. Great.
Listen, you just tell
the tourists
that the bad view
is part of the curse.
Will you please escort
the pirate and his wench
behind the
yellow tape?
Thank you.
I'm the mayor of this town...
So, Dane-- he's, uh,
an experienced guy?
I've worked with hundreds.
He's the best.
All right.
I hope this guy knows
what he's doing,
'cause it's tight
down there.
Avast, ye lubbers!
Whoo!
Dane, let's
get him ready.
You think it's a pirate?
It's a 300-year-old finger
from the left hand of a male.
That's all
I'm sure of so far.
Worth killing for?
I worked a case once
where a woman was killed,
dismembered and burned
because her friend thought
she'd taken her favorite pair
of slippers.
Cheery.
Maybe they're right.
Maybe this man died
burying the treasure.
Ironic... stealing all that
and never enjoying the spoils.
So you believe
there's treasure?
I believe there's greed.
That's the real curse.
All right, safety line,
air hose.
Either one
breaks,
you ain't
coming back up.
You got to work
on your bedside manner, dude.
You know, I don't want to be
responsible for some weekender
who buys it down there
because he thinks
he's better
than he is.
You want to go down, don't you?
It's my shaft, okay?
I've been working it ten years.
But the Feds-- they say
it's a crime scene,
so I can't help.
You're helping me.
BOOTH:
Why's he need
the air line?
Why can't he just
use the tank?
Because around 100 foot down,
the shaft gets a little cozy.
You ain't afraid
of a tight squeeze,
are you, Doc?
Gloves.
Just take it
slow, okay?
There's a lot
of stuff
to catch your hose on
on the way down.
Yeah, I saw the pictures
Rose took.
Rose.
He never went as far
as you're going.
No one has.
Maybe he shouldn't
try, you know?
People have died down
there, not just Macy.
I know.
My brother was one of them.
I'm going
all the way down.
What's at 200 feet?
We just hit 200
last week.
You're going to have
to tell me.
Well, I'm ready.
Okay.
Your friend better be as good
as he says he is.
You just feed
him that hose.
Hodgins, you read me?
I hear you loud and clear.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hodgins?
It's warm.
Passing the first flood trap.
We lost our first man there.
There's wood here
below the limestone.
Does he make any sense to you?
Oh, yeah.
He's passing the site
of the first pit collapse.
It's tight down here.
There's lots of debris.
Not sure I can squeeze through.
Hey, this guy swims
like a squid.
Actually, he swims
like a squint.
What?
Never mind.
Okay, I'm clear now.
DANE:
Good picture, too.
We can't get resolution
like that.
Yeah, well,
he's a geek
who works for the government.
You ever find anything
down here?
Not yet.
Ten years of finding nothing,
and you keep trying.
It's all about the search, man.
He's at 170 feet.
One-eighty.
One-ninety.
No one's ever been this deep.
He's at 200.
Touch down. I am on the bottom.
Visibility is surprisingly
good.
Wait a minute.
There's-there's something here.
Holy...
What is that?
Whoa, is that...?
Oh, my God.
Is that...?
I'm amazed
you found a complete skeleton.
C-14 dating matches
at 300 years.
Subject is male, early twenties,
approximately five feet...
six inches.
Legs are bowed,
result of visible calcium
and phosphate deficiency.
He had rickets as a child,
but his upper body is
extraordinarily well-developed.
Epiphyseal separation
in the long bones.
Sunken sternum forms
scorbutic rosary
at costochondral margin.
He suffered from scurvy,
as well as tertiary syphilis.
What's with the tertiary? Isn't
plain all syphilis bad enough?
Scurvy, syphilis.
Pirate.
There is
anthropological evidence
which supports the claim
that Blackbeard
executed his
burial crews
after they were
done digging.
Okay.
Let's say it's a pirate.
Yes!
Oh!
This would be
an extraordinary find.
And would open up
the reality
of the treasure.
It would be stupid to dismiss
anything at this point.
But we need
to discover why the ossein
isn't fully decomposed
from being waterlogged
for so long.
About 50
feet down
the shaft,
is a layer of blue putty,
consisting of silicon and clay.
It can be used
to form a watertight seal.
That would explain the condition
of the bones.
I took samples
of the same blue clay
between 200
and 207 feet.
Something is buried
down there.
And these bones were lying
on top of it.
Macy was killed
because of something
that he found.
Silt in his throat
and lungs confirms
he was killed at the top
of the shaft.
After he swam back up
with the treasure.
Special Agent Booth.
I hate
to interrupt your investigation,
Agent Booth,
but there's an angry billionaire
in my office,
and he won't go away.
It's simple.
You have something
that belongs to me,
and I'm not leaving here
without it.
A day ago, you couldn't wait
to leave.
Pull out of the island,
cut your losses.
You remember that?
A lot can change in a day.
Yeah. For Ted Macy,
a lot changed.
Look, I'm sorry about Ted,
but I'll be damned
if the federal government swoops
in here at the eleventh hour
and steals what I've been trying
to find for two years.
I fail to see
what this has to do
with the Jeffersonian.
Those bones belong to me.
They were uncovered
at my site.
I was granted a permit
to dig there and keep
what was found.
My attorneys
assure me, you have no claim
to those bones.
Sure, I mean, your attorney
wants to go to court
for the next 20 years, and
buy himself a nice vacation home
in Tuscany, but the fact is,
when Ted Macy was murdered,
your property became
our evidence.
And it's going to stay that way
until we find the killer.
I was hoping
to settle this amicably.
Really?
Because, you know,
we haven't seen that yet.
Nah.
This is going
to be a headache.
He has some very important
friends.
I don't understand
why he's so upset.
It's not like
he needs the money.
But he has partners that do.
Macy and Hardewicke were going
to split what they found.
But Macy is dead.
Exactly. Leaving Hardewicke
with a bigger
piece of the pie.
This is from our very first dig
together.
Oh, we found this-this
chest buried
under a flood drain
up in Smith's Cove
in New England.
There was no treasure,
but, you know, just
to unearth something
that was that old,
had that much history--
we were hooked.
Never looked back.
You know, I glanced
through your company history.
I mean, business
was pretty slow,
since you didn't find
any treasure out here.
You were getting fewer
and fewer clients.
Yeah, it's been difficult.
Branson Rose was almost
your last chance.
There's always somebody who
wants to look for treasure.
Really?
Yeah.
'Cause, you know,
Branson Rose, he pulls out,
and get a lot of publicity,
you could end up, you know...
sinking your business.
Yeah, but Macy found something
finally, and we're going
to share the find
with Rose-- 50% for
him, 50 for us.
Exactly.
Oh, I see.
More for me if Macy's out
of the picture, right?
You're forgetting
one thing.
Macy was like
family to me.
Really?
Look at this. See that?
I got that pulling Macy out
of a sinkhole back in '93.
He's got plenty
of scars on him
because of me, too.
Hmm. How'd you get
all those bruises
around your scar there, huh?
Oh...
The Mayor.
How does the Mayor figure
into all this?
His wife. You
saw her, right?
Well, Macy was a bit of a hound,
if you know what I mean.
He was sleeping
with the Pirate Queen?
The Mayor got suspicious,
he came around last week,
and I ended up taking
the heat for Macy,
because Macy's like my
brother, and I'll tell you,
that scrawny little
pirate-- he can kick, too.
Lucky he didn't have
time to load that
flintlock. Charlie?
No. Put that down.
Leave it there.
What are you doing?
Zack?
Zack, the bones--
what did you do with the bones?
Nothing,
Dr. Brennan.
I left them on the
table just like
you asked.
Where the hell are my bones ?
Bones don't just disappear.
I thought this was
a secure facility.
You assured me this
was a secure facility.
I could be working at
Stanford, you know.
This never would have
happened at Stanford.
We spend three quarters
of a million dollars
annually on security.
Obviously that's
not enough.
I want my bones.
Did you find my bones?!
Oh! Maybe you want just want
to, you know, chill a little?
Chill?
Yeah. You know, take a pill.
Listen, dude,
my lab was violated,
my bones were stolen,
so I think I'll remain warm
for a little while longer.
Honey, maybe you should focus
on your breathing.
Breathing.
Count to ten.
Have a shot of Jack.
Shot of Jack.
Look, we're doing
everything that
we can, okay?
I promise you,
we're going to find your bones,
but you have to allow us
to do our job.
I guess I wasn't helping
all that much, was I?
I...
I'm...
Sorry.
It's cool.
Hey, look on the bright side.
I mean, this whole
theft thing could be
good for us, right?
I mean, whoever took the bones
obviously had something to do
with the murder.
We're getting closer.
I've ordered all on-duty
security personnel
to give a minute-by-minute
account of their rounds.
I want an account of all
off-duty personnel, as well.
They didn't
get everything.
I thought all the bones
were on the table.
All the new ones.
I was still examining
the original finger bone
we found for scurvy,
so it was
in my room.
There is something they don't
want us to find on these bones.
Everyone knew Macy.
Helped Frank get elected.
So you would categorize your
relationship as just friends?
Yeah. Friends.
It's a small town.
We're all friends.
Well, whoever killed Macy
wasn't too friendly.
He wouldn't hurt
a soul-- Macy.
He was a sweet guy.
The way you're talking
about him, it seems like
you were more
than just friends.
Hardewicke told you, right?
Like he's such a saint.
How involved were
the two of you?
It was just one
of those things, you know.
I wasn't going to leave Frank
or anything.
I guess I wanted to see
what it was like
to be with a real adventurer
rather than a guy
who dresses up like one.
So, Frank went after Hardewicke
when he thought it was him.
You think Frank killed him?
You saw Frank.
Well, yeah.
You know, he's a little,
uh, a little unstable.
When he finds out somebody
made a fool of him twice, I...
Look, it's Hardewicke
and the rich guy
you should be looking at.
Macy said they were all fighting
over the money
they were spending.
Said Hardewicke didn't
appreciate all the work he did,
wanted to break up the company.
Well, we're-we're
looking into everyone.
Thanks.
Sure.
But all this coming up again.
Just try not
to ruin my marriage, okay?
I made a mistake.
But I love that stupid pirate,
and I don't want to lose him.
Well, thanks for talking to me.
I'll be in touch.
The periosteal surface
on the phalanx
doesn't have any ingrained
particulates that I can recover.
The solution that M.E. used
probably dissolved anything
that was lodged
in any surface irregularities.
Who would clean a bone
before extracting all available
information from it?
Not everyone is as thorough
as we are, Zack.
So true, so true.
I wonder if there was
gold dust on it.
Perhaps you should start working
with a parrot on your shoulder.
You're not curious?
Yes. About the facts.
There's a small hole
along the distal articular facet
of the finger.
It could be a foramen,
but it could be something else,
man-made.
A weapon?
Maybe.
See if you can find
any possible matches.
I wonder if there are any other
similar marks on Macy?
I'll find out.
And don't let that bone
out of your sight.
Dr. Brennan thought you might
have overlooked
a weapon of some kind.
He wasn't killed
by any weapon.
He was strangled.
The larynx is crushed.
It's plain.
And C2 through C4 are fractured.
That wouldn't have occurred
if he were merely strangled.
If the victim was shaken
while being strangled...
The fractures
are all left to right,
approximately 45-degree angles
on each bone.
That means the head
was jerked to the left and up,
making sure that the spinal cord
would tear.
The larynx was crushed
when his neck was broken.
I'm always open
to being corrected.
Why do you think
there might have been a weapon?
I saw a small perforation
in the finger bone,
which you decided to put
in the solvent.
Still angry.
I handled it according
to protocol:
rubber gloves
right into the solvent.
Something damaged that bone, and
it didn't happen 300 years...
Wait a minute.
I have alternatives
that could have caused the hole.
This is a disposable
acupuncture needle.
He was healed to death?
This is a filament used
for an angioplasty.
Hand me the wire.
BOOTH:
What are you doing?
Diminished fluorescence.
That only happens if the bones
have been cleaned and treated.
These bones didn't start out
in the shaft.
What?
Who has got
300-year-old bones?
I assure you everything here
is authentic, Dr. Brennan.
I curated this exhibit
for the Jeffersonian myself.
Could you please
open the case?
This is a beautiful specimen.
Found in Jamaica.
We believe he sailed
with Henry Morgan.
He's never been on a boat
in his life.
Absurd.
Oh, my God.
These bones
are artificial.
It's acrylic, not bone.
You can see the hole
where the wire
was threaded
when the bones were assembled
for display.
Then where's the rest
of my sailor?
He was planted in the shaft
in Assateague Island
to make the whole
treasure business seem real,
but somebody found out.
Who?
A murderer.
Okay, let me see
if I get this straight.
The pirate bones you recovered
came from the Jeffersonian
to start with?
Correct.
300-year-old bones stolen
from our own pirate exhibit.
And then recovered
by one of your own people...
Dr. Hodgins.
...who brought them back
to the Jeffersonian,
where they were stolen again?
Re-stolen, sir.
You have a security problem,
Dr. Goodman.
And when I find out
who did this,
you may have a murder problem.
But I'm on top of it, okay?
You didn't have to come
down here, sir.
That's what I thought,
until I got a call
from someone
at the Department of Defense.
Defense? How do they figure
into a murder investigation?
Branson Rose,
he has friends in high places,
and they don't like
it when the guy
who builds their bombers
is unhappy.
They afraid he'll bomb them?
What is that, squint humor?
Because I'm not laughing.
Defense doesn't need
a reason to go to war,
and I'm not about to be
their next target.
Well, of course not.
You're too busy
looking for your bones.
Let's not make this personal.
Rose wants to keep
playing in the mud,
and his big-shot friends
are going to see that happens,
unless we get some answers fast.
At this point, it appears as if
the stolen 300-year-old bones
are being used to, you know,
salt the shaft.
Salt the shaft?
Yeah, you know, an investor
spends a million bucks,
gets antsy when nothing happens,
and then, voil? you know,
pirate bones appear, and the
golden goose keeps, you know...
...laying those eggs.
Okay, that is
a convoluted metaphor, Booth.
It's a hoax, Dr. Brennan,
like Piltdown Man.
Oh, got it.
Why can't you be clear
like that?
Assuming the bones
were stolen...
Re-stolen?
...re-stolen so you wouldn't
find out they were bogus,
how did you?
How did I what?
From the finger.
They didn't get
the entire skeleton.
Would you like Dr. Brennan
to take you through the process?
I really, really wouldn't.
So who do you like?
I like the partner.
Giles Hardewicke.
Access, motive,
ability...
Dr. Goodman,
the FBI will provide
whatever help you need to solve
your breach of security
at the Jeffersonian.
You work the partner angle.
Well, my father
worked a fishing boat,
his dad before that.
Heck, me and
my brother,
we never knew
anything but the sea.
Hunting for treasure just sort
of grew out of that I guess.
Any regrets?
Sure. My brother.
Yeah.
That and the fact they might
shut us down.
Hey, not if we find something.
Huh?
You know, I thought you were
going to turn out
to be just another desk jockey
who'd read a few books
and was looking for something
to brighten up
his boring-ass life.
I'll tell you what,
I'd be down that shaft right now
if Big Brother didn't have
a minimum time requirement
between dives.
You deserve to be here.
You really do.
Thanks for that, man.
The bones were planted.
You don't seem surprised.
Eh, nothing surprises me
out of that ... pit anymore.
Nah.
I mean, you dig down far enough,
you'll come out in hell.
So, uh...
if you don't find anything,
are you gonna shut us down?
Hey, I'm not FBI.
I'm just a scientist.
It's a crime scene.
I'm surprised
they let you down there.
I'm an expert in silt, plants,
and insects--
that's right.
I got three doctorates.
When you got three doctorates,
and you tell the FBI
you need more samples,
who's gonna argue?
One doctorate, yeah,
maybe they argue, but three?
You want to go back down again,
don't you?
I could use your help, man.
You got the bug, man!
Hey, like I said,
I am the bug man.
Arr!
If you lost the bones,
how do you know
they're fake?
Thieves, they didn't
get everything.
Ah. Stroke of luck
for the good guys.
We will find out
how those bones were stolen
from the Jeffersonian.
You still think I
did it, don't you?
Why were you going to break up
the company?
Let me guess,
Katie Ney tell you that?
What makes you think
it was Katie?
That was a stock part
of Macy's seduction technique,
and it was very effective.
"I risk my life
down in that hole while my
partner stays safe topside."
That's how he
positioned himself
as the heroic explorer...
which he was, by the way,
when it came to the ladies.
Your partnership was intact?
Till death did us part.
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna give you guys
full access to the books.
You don't even need
a search warrant.
There's not a single way
in which my life is better off
without Macy.
Like I said, I miss the man.
The bones were
stolen twice--
the first time from
the pirate exhibit,
the second from the Bone Room
here in the Medico-Legal Lab.
The security in the lab
is tighter,
so the camera is continuous,
but the camera in the rotunda
is stop-action,
every three seconds.
I started with the lab
theft because we know
the bones were stolen
between 9:00 p.m.
and 6:00 a.m.
Okay.
Watch... here.
The bones are gone.
Notice the time-code.
What's that?
The camera was
turned off.
Camera was turned off
for one minute and 46 seconds.
It would take a lot less time
that to enter the room
and gather up the
bones and escape.
Now...
Dr. Goodman?
Yes?
Could I ask, why are we
doing this investigation
instead of Security?
We shouldn't walk too quickly;
it would arouse suspicion.
Neither would our thief.
I'm happy to help,
but we do have
actual security
professionals who...
Is there any way to tell if
those tapes have been doctored?
Yeah.
Since they're physical
magnetic tapes,
not stored digitally.
I always did
like analog better.
Now, I know why.
My point is is that I'm
only an amateur at this,
and I'm sure the Security
Department is better equipped
and trained...
Afternoon, Paul.
Best to Susan and Laura.
I hope Johnny feels better.
Okay you don't want
to talk about it.
I get it.
Sir?
Hit your stopwatch,
please, Ms. Montenegro.
35.6 seconds.
Double that for
a round-trip.
That's one minute,
ten seconds,
leaving approximately
30 seconds to bag the
bones and get back.
Get back where?
Oh... ah.
Wow, you must think
I'm an idiot.
I was grandstanding.
I can be like that.
So we find out what guards were
on duty during the two thefts
and we might have
our thief.
In stealing human remains?
After 300 years,
it's not like
he's got a family
grieving for him out there.
Think of me as a
grieving parent.
Grand theft, buddy;
you're looking at eight years.
If I don't kill you.
Come on, what's a bunch
of old bones like that worth?
Nothing.
How much you get for them?
Couple of hundred bucks.
Yeah. So this wire transfer
into your bank for ten grand,
what's that, inheritance?
Who did you
steal them for?
We didn't really do
the name-exchange thing.
Somebody approached you?
Yeah.
Let's see. Okay.
Which one was it?
Which time?
The first time.
Him...
but he looked better.
And the second time?
Um... him.
Look, guys, I'm cooperating,
all right?
I will give back the money.
I will quit my job,
all right?
How's about we just
call it even?
How's about we call
the D.A.?
You know, you need a better
screening process
down at the museum.
Ironic, given we
contract that out to the FBI.
The...
You think he's dangerous?
Grand theft, murder, yeah.
The music.
Shh. He's
down there.
That's not music,
it's bagpipes.
Whoa.
Mr. Harde...
Maybe we're looking
for someone else.
The larynx was crushed.
Is that going to be your
cause-of-death ruling?
We gonna have
another fight about this?
I'm a pretty
open guy, Harry,
but if you keep
pushing like that,
it's gonna be me who
smacks you around.
How do you know that won't
work for me
just as well?
You ruled that Macy died
from a crushed larynx.
A crushed larynx is fatal,
ergo it results in death.
You were wrong then,
and you're wrong now.
See? He likes it.
I need to see both sets
of X rays, his and Macy's.
It's not always about
being right or wrong.
It's about
the dialogue.
An intense conversation
can be the most wonderful
kind of intercourse.
Know what?
This guy is a pervert.
Damage between C-2 and C-4,
45 degree angle,
exact same pattern
of injury as Macy.
His head was wrenched around,
probably while the other hand
crushed the larynx.
That must really frustrate
you that I missed that.
That's a Special Forces move.
Take a sentry down,
crush the larynx,
so he can't scream.
You've done that
to people?
No. Our murderer
is Special Forces.
Your Internet bio
says you spent time
in Special Air Services.
Mr. Rose has led a diverse
and full life.
How did you feel
when you found out
the dig site
had been salted?
ROSE:
I was disappointed, certainly.
Just disappointed?
Look, I wasn't irked enough
to kill Ted Macy.
Now, could we get
to the point, please?
What is Special Air Services?
The S.A.S. is widely regarded
as one of the finest
and best trained special forces
units in the world.
See any active service?
Mr. Rose is not comfortable
discussing specifics.
I don't like to exploit
my role in operations
which cost good men their lives.
Now, if all you're
interested in is my history,
there's a bio on my web site.
Great.
We just want to know
if your reputation
is for real, sir.
Hey, we'll just
contact the S.A.S.
They'll tell us.
Look...
Fine.
Don't expect
a speedy response.
Whoa, Bones.
That's assault!
Would a Special Forces guy
have been able
to stop that?
I don't know,
you kind of
got the jump
on him there.
This one won't be a surprise.
You ready?
What?
This is common assault!
Charges will be laid!
No way he's Special Ops.
It's just PR crap.
All right, no
more questions.
I demand she be
arrested for assault!
Shut up, Kendall.
that I'm taking a woman
to court for
slapping me?
Come on, let's
get out of here.
You won't get into
trouble for this?
Three degrees.
I'm telling you,
salted or not,
there's something
at the bottom of that shaft.
Never got to go
all the way down.
The bones
were laying on wood.
I want to see
what's underneath.
Always thought it'd
be me who'd find it.
Yeah, they were always
pirate-y to me.
Let's do this.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Dispatch, 22705.
Last name: McGinnis; first name:
Dane; middle initial: P.
I need to know which branch
of the military he served in.
Affirmative, 22705.
Stand by.
Why Dane?
He said Hodgins
swam like a squid.
Squint.
He must have said "squint."
No, I said
"squint," okay?
Is this what they call
a Hail Mary pass?
HODGINS:
You receiving?
Loud and clear.
Man, it's muddy today.
Yeah.
Usually clears up past the first
flood channel at 12 meters.
* Yo-ho-ho
and a bottle of rum. *
Don't conjure up
any ghosts, Doc.
There's too many
down there already
waiting to claim your ass.
Ghosts.
Right.
22705, Dispatch.
McGinnis, Dane,
served in the Navy.
Rating: Chief Petty Officer,
Naval Special Warfare.
Oh, yeah. Had to be.
What?
Guy was a Navy SEAL.
So? You were a guide.
A Ranger.
I was a Ranger,
Bones, okay?
I was not a guide.
Guides, they show
you waterfalls,
they sell you cookies.
I was a Ranger.
What's he doing
at the shaft?
Oh.
Are Rangers
afraid of SEALs?
What? Come on,
Bones, no.
Rangers aren't
afraid of anybody.
All right?
SEALs are
pretty good, though.
Hey, Dane.
Hey. What's up?
We know it was you.
BOOTH:
Bones, please...
Why? You have a gun.
What's he got?
He's got somebody
in the shaft.
How far down am I?
Is that Hodgins?
I can't read my depth display.
Hey, is something going on?
Is there anybody up there?
Why don't you answer me?
CPO McGinnis, step away
from the air hose.
Yeah?
Well, I need you to toss
that gun into the shaft.
Then, toss me your keys.
Then, handcuff yourselves
to that crane.
I take your truck.
Otherwise, I am gonna
cut this hose,
and your buddy's gonna die.
Yeah, do that.
Bones.
Not gonna happen.
Feel a blast of cold water.
Either a spring or some kind
of conduit from the ocean.
It's clear, clean water,
so visibility is better.
You killed two men.
I can't just let you drive away.
Those guys...
putting fake bones in there,
making the whole thing
into a con job.
My brother died down there
looking for that treasure,
lot of good men did.
This was their life.
Those men
dishonored them.
Dane, can you hear me, man?
I am on the bottom.
You good enough
to take that shot
before I cut
this air hose, Ranger?
Pretty good.
Just pretty good?
Please, I'm working.
Looks like a sandy loam down,
maybe a little clay.
I'll get a sample.
I can see where
the shaft walls
collapsed before.
Oh, my God.
Holy...
Can you see this, Dane?
What is it?
Why don't you take a look?
Yeah.
I do, you'll shoot me.
Dane!
Can you see this, man?!
It's a gold coin.
Yeah, it's probably
something else
they stole from your museum
and threw in there.
This is real!
It's a big...!
You want to see it, you're going
to have to bring Hodgins up.
Please.
He's down there
because he believes.
He's no different than you,
no different
than your brother.
Bring him up.
Do it for your brother.
An original Breen 984
half doubloon,
designed by Ephraim Brasher,
engraved by Ephraim Brasher,
and, hold your breath,
gentlemen and ladies,
204 grains.
A real, gold, pirate coin.
How many more
are down there?
Branson Rose has agreed to have
the museum do the authentication
of the entire treasure
when they bring it up.
There won't
be any more.
What makes you
say that?
I was down there.
It's not gonna
give it up that easily.
But the treasure's
been located.
And I'm sure
it's been located before.
I'll take that.
You think he's happy
to be back home?
Well, he looks that way to me.
Hah.
He's not happy.
What do you mean?
Hodgins is right.
He'd be a lot happier
at the bottom
of that shaft.
With the other pirates.
Arr!
Arr, matey!
Arr! Arr, matey!
Cync by xxy
www.1000fr.com