We already know
what killed the bear.
Who's the vet
here, Sherman?
You are, Denise.
Who's the park ranger?
That'd be you, Sherman.
That's why I know
what killed him.
Scared camper drilled him
with a Winchester Magnum .338.
I get it-- you're afraid I'm not showing
respect to the bears spirits.
Because I have better
things to do
than wait around for you to
tell me what i alread know.
The law says I have to send in
as much information as I can.
Age, weight, what he last ate...
Ooh, yummy.
Hot dogs, refried beans...
What's that?
Beef jerky.
Beef jerky?
Yeah, he was in hyperphagia, eating everything
he could find before going into hibernation.
What?
Sherman, this is...
Oh, God.
Looks human to me.
- Sorry.
What's the deal?
Found in eastern
Washington state.
Where?
Inside a bear.
No, I mean...
Inside a bear?
An autopsy revealed more bone fragments
in the bear's stomach and intestine.
An autopsy on an animal
is called necropsy.
Yeah, you know, it's pretty crucial
we get that straight right off the bat.
Meanwhile, about the dead human being?
What do you need me for?
The bear ate somebody.
26 bone fragments in total.
The case bumped to the Seattle field office.
They bumped it to me. Check it out.
Why'd they bump it to you?
Bones, I mean, do you really care about
the inner workings of the FBI office?
They bumped it to you
because you work with me.
No, they hope that you
could help ID the body.
From a hand??
Yeah, they have
high expectations.
Definitely human, opposable thumb,
probably male, from the size.
- Uh-oh!
- What?
Kerf marks. Marks made
from a cutting tool.
Maybe when they
cut en the bear?
No, it's not
a straight edge.
Residual
cross-section striae.
Hmm, just because you say in that definitive
tone doesn't mean it means anything to me.
These marks we made from a saw.
The hand was already separated from
the rest of the person when the bear ate them.
Somebody was dismembered
and fed to a bear?
That's one possibility.
Okay, um, thanks, Bones.
Glad I could help.
But, uh... you're not done.
I'll check out the photographs and the
X rays, see if I can confirm sex and age.
Pack your bags.
We're going to Washington state.
I am not going
to Washington state.
Again, just because you say it in that definitive
tone, doesn't mean it means nothing to me.
Why Booth is the one who decides
we go to Washington state?
He gets a gun and the authority.
He's the one that people like.
Firstly, he didn't decide that you go
to Washington State. He made a request.
I am the one who decides
where you do and do not go.
And secondly?
Secondly, it's time to live a little, Temperance.
Connect with other people.
Are you suggesting that I take this opportunity
to have sex with Booth on a field trip?
Good God, where is
Dr. Freud when you need him?
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Which is precisely why I´m sending you
to the Great North Woods.
Come on, now.
You have partially-digested, dismembered
skeletal remains to examine.
That should put
a smile on your face.
The mosquitoes out there
are the size of dogs.
pack and set the perimeter
BONES
1X04: The Man in the Bear
Transcript: cfsmp3
Sync: Narkond, Roberto, Dedek0
You know, being cooped up in a crappy
hotel in the middle of nowhere
with a $50 per diem is not my idea
of a good time either, you know.
You only get $50 a day?
How can you live on that?
Okay, what do you mean?
What do you get?
I don't have a limit.
Just give them the receipts.
Oh, no, you have to have a limit. Everyone
has a limit. We work for the government.
I don't have a limit.
But it's not fair. It's not fair to the taxpayers.
You're like one of those
thousand-dollar toilet seats.
I imagine i´m a pretty differently than
you because I have an indispensable skill.
Right, indispensable... I do not need you.
Oh, so you can determine the origin of the kerf
marks as well as the sex and age of the victim?
You know, u're a smart ass,
you know that?
Objectively, I'd say I'm very smart,
although it has nothing to do with my ass.
You know, I'll tell you what. You can
take me out to dinner, hmm?
Put me on your tab.
That doesn't seem ethical.
You still want that gun,
now don't u-- hmm?
We'll start with breakfast.
You know, it's beautiful here
It feels good to be out of the city.
Yeah, where murderers
feed their victims to bears.
Small town America. Got to love it.
No, this is not a small town.
Chuntala in Guatemala, 150 people,
no running water.
That's a small town.
I said small town America,
not small town Guatemala.
And I've been there,
too, by the way.
Where are you going?
To see the sheriff.
How are you going
to do that?
It's an old FBI trick. I'm going to ask
somebody who lives here.
What took you to Guatemala?
Eco-tourism?
I went down to shoot somebody
through the heart from 1,500 feet.
I was pretty sure it was human,
but I'm a vet,
so I called Andrew, Dr. Rigby,
and he thought it was human, too.
Officially I'm the coroner here in Aurora,
but I'm just a country doctor.
I have no training
in forensics.
This is approximately 60%
of the arm of a male,
late teens, early 20s,
well muscled.
That's amazing.
You see these marks here
below the radial tuberosity?
You haven't by any chance performed
any amputations lately, have you?
Uh, a few frostbit
toes last winter,
and a thumb from a nasty
Murphy bed accident. Why?
These are saw marks.
That's not good, people getting
sawed up and ate by bears?
I'm going to send
this back to my lab.
My people there can give a better estimate
of how long ago the bear ingested the arm.
You got pretty good
equipment there, I guess.
I'm still on dial-up.
What's the fastest way
to ship a human arm
Charlie
Need a hand?
Thanks, but I'm trying
to get rid of this one.
These are human remains.
I have to ship them to the Jeffersonian
Institute in Washington, D.C.
Cool, they have Dizzy
Gillespie's trumpet there.
Yeah, I know.
Muhammad Ali's boxing gloves
Abm Lirahaoln's assaination top hat.
I know, I work there.
You ever sit in
Archie Bunker'chair?
I work in a different part of the museum.
I'm a forensic anthropologist.
- My name's Charlie.
- Yeah, I know.
Wow. What, you could tell
from my, like, skull structure?
It says it on your
shirt, Charlie.
Where can I
find the sheriff?
He's out past the
garage to the right.
Hey, Temperance Brennan.
I've been reading your book.
Gave me a few ideas if I ever want
to kill someone and get rid of he body.
Well, don't forget, Charlie, the
heroine always catches the bad guy.
Sounds good to me.
These are false start kerfs,
which suggest a hand saw.
The cut marks
on the break-away spur...
Here
it should give me the number of teeth
per inch, but... to me, it just looks broken.
I could work it up into a three-dimensional
image. See if that helps.
Dr. Brennan could
do it from this.
Not when she was a lowly
grad student, Zack.
Upload all the digital info that Brennan
sent you into my mainframe.
And lighten up, dude.
You know, somebody cut that
guy's arm off, Sheriff.
Couldn't be a local.
Somebody missing an arm,
that's something
you notice.
How many people
live in Aurora?
326 in town, another couple hundred
in the unincorporated surroundings,
maybe 1,200 on the
Indian reservation.
Tourists?
Hikers, campers...It's beautiful country,
so they don't realize how dangerous it is.
On average, we lose a couple
of pople a year. Cycle of life, eh?
Lose anyone recently?
Woman, 29,
Ann Nuyes from Olympia.
Disappeared a couple weeks ago. Her parents
say she was an "experienced" hiker.
Must have some
resident crazies.
Juvenile bush drinking, a couple of domestics,
a bar fight or two, joy riding.
The only felons we have arpoachers.
They shoot the black bears and
sell the gallbladders on the black market.
Park ranger handles that stuff.
Can I help you?
Yeah-- thanks. I'm with him.
Suddenly I wish I was FBI.
Sheriff Chris Scutter,
Dr. Temperance Brown.
My first forensic anthropologist.
Please.
We need to find
the rest of the body.
Sherman-- Ranger Rivers--
traced the bear's route back a week.
Said he didn't find anything.
What is he, like,
some kind of an Indian scout?
Sherman's a Flathead Indian, but since
the bear was wearing a GPS collar,
he didn't have to fully utilize
his native powers.
Did he check the scat?
What, do you think there's more
people parts in the bear crap?
We could maybe go out with
Sherman tomorrow, take a look.
Oh, yeah, now that you met Bones, you're
all about the inter-agency cooperation
Bones? I don't think that´s
a way to talk to a lady.
Thank you.
Do you have... dinner plans?
We're working.
Thanks for that.
All I'm saying is,
why cut somebody into pieces?
Pack them up tighter maybe,
say, in a suitcase.
How did a bear
open a suitcase?
I saw a documentary once where a bear
go in a car and drove away.
That was not a documentary,
it was a cartoon.
Hello.
I'm looking for Zack Addy.
I've got a package of human remains.
Yeah, I can sign
for that.
Where's Jimmy?
Tahiti, Fiji, who knows?
He won the lottery.
Is it too much of a line to say,
"No, we won the lottery"?
It is, yeah. You know what?
I take it back.
It's just, compared to you,
Jimmy, you know...
- The third nostril...
- That whistling sound when he sneezes.
Unfortuny, it is too soon to
ask you to have coffee.
It is?
Yes, yes. Coffee is the
third delivery capper.
So what's the first
delivery capper?
Initial contact, meet
cute, light flirting.
Then I'll catch you
in another couple of deliveries.
Ok.
Tchau.
You bogarted my package.
You panicked and froze, my man.
Thus, the package came into play.
Also incorrect use of
the verb "bogarted."
I've been looking for that female
hiker since she went missing.
But sometimes you never find a trace.
They fall in the ravine, the river...
So how do you like
the Evergreen Lodge?
Very nice. I have a beautiful view
of the mountains from my terrace.
You have a terrace?
- Yeah.
- I'm sharing a bathroom.
This is where
the bear was shot.
- How far did he get before he died?
- About a hundred yards.
How do you know
that's the right way?
Not hard to track
a wounded bear.
Ever hear of the
bone gatherers?
Collecting bones so that the dead can
make their journey to the next world?
I'm not even sure I believe
in the next world.
Doesn't matter what you believe in.
You're a bone gatherer.
That's a good thing,
helping the spirits move on.
Thank you. It's probably the best
job description I'll ever get.
Over here.
You find something?
Does a bear scat
in the woods?
I think he voided here, and he...
headed off over there.
See if you can fin
dy older samples.
She ain't the squeamish
type, is she?
I'm gonna go out on a limb here, Sherman
and guess you don't get a lot of eligible
good-looking women coming through town.
Hey. I just finished chapter 7.
- This has to go to my...
Do you do all the stuff
the girl in your book does?
I'm... suddenly uncomfortable
discussing that with you.
No, I-I'm not talking about the sex.
I'm talking about the running and the shooting.
I mean, if you... do do all that
other stuff, that's great, too, for...
you and, um... whoever you're...doing it with.
I'd like to send this
to my lab.
Yeah, more bones?
No, it's bear scat.
Oh, I can deal with that.
Brennan.
The person who belonged to the arm
died approximately a week ago
and the bear ate it between one
and three days after that.
Anything from the saw?
Angela's entering the data
into the holographic display.
I found something else I can't
categorize. Can I beam it to you?
Okay, hold on
Do you mind if I place the laptop here?
Uh, yeah! No problem.
Give me a second. I´m connecting
with the satelite.
Okay. I´m link.
...been focusing on,
Dr. Brennan.
- Who's that?
- My assistant, Zack.
Hey, Zack.
- Who's that?
- The overnight guy, Charlie.
Okay, I'm set up--
you can send me the picture.
- Hey, Zack, does your boss have a boyfriend?
- Not currently.
- Are you extremely good looking?
- Yes, I am, Zack.
Zack, these are bite marks.
You mean from the bear?
No. Black bears have premolars
that are small and peg-like.
These marks show
a doub cusp pattern.
Pigs are double cusped.
- Hey, Zack, are you extremely smart?
- Yes, I am, Charlie.
No, pigs have six incisors. These marks were made
by four incisors, like a chimp, except...
these teeth form
a continuous arch.
So what's got a continuous arch?
Humans.
We don't just have a killer on our hands,
we have a cannibal.
Zack'll have the odontologist at the Jeffersonian
take a look, but I'm right.
A canibal?
You mean
a Hannibal Lector type... deal?
I don't know what that means.
You're certain a human being
gnawed on that bone?
Bit, gnawed,
removed the flesh.
That's-that's really not good.
Are you sure, Bones? You've never see
anything like this before?
Of course I've seen this before--
I did grad work ong the Wari of the Amazon.
They have a long history of cannibalism.
I've also seen evidence of cannibalism in some
12th-century Native American sites--
it's not that big a deal.
Have you ever...?
I've never been offered
human flesh before.
But if you had?
That's an interesting question. I'd have
to measure my own social inculcation
against objective scientific inquiry.
'Kay, that's sick.
Maybe we're looking for someone
who needs to be rescued.
Maybe the young man died,
and the missing girl,
hungry and lost, came upon him
needing food, and she...
Sawed him up and...
barbecued him?
Well, there's no evidence
that the hand was cooked.
She does not look like the type
of girl who would chew on raw flesh.
You'd be surprised. When survival
instincts kick in...
If it isn't her, then we're dealing
with some psycho cannibal killer.
This is sick.
Someone eating raw human flesh
is going to get sick.
Teeth marks?
Yes, and these drag marks are where
the flesh was ripped right off the bone.
It's ike a zombie movie.
Where is my bear poop
Is it the excrement you're anxious
to look at... or the courier?
What do you think?
Somebody gnawed on this arm
like some kind of man corn?
According to that Peruvian soccer team that crashed
in the Andes, human flesh tastes like frogs' legs.
As if I need another reason
never to eat frogs.
We're gonna make a cast of these markings.
We won't get a full dental impression,
bu'll at least get something
Zack. You're needed upstairs.
Angela.
If we were a Peruvian soccer team
and crashed in the Andes,
Who you would you rather eat,
me or Zack?
What?
- I have a package for Zack Addy.
- That's me.
I thought...There was the other guy.
That was Hodgins. He zoomed you, because
you're so beautiful.
Thanks, that's sweet.
I-I'm not being sweet.
It's just a fact.
- How old are you?
- Twenty-four.
Twenty-four.
I could just eat you up.
Have you diagnosed anyone
rently with a prion disease?
A prion disease? No.
Some Alzheimer's, yes. Some brain
damage due to alcoholism
Delusions, erratic behavio
violent outbursts?
The incubation period for
a prion disease can be years.
You're thinking the cannibal might be
showing symptoms of mental deterioration?
Dr. Rigby, I never said
anything about a cannibal.
Well,it's all over town.
Charlie, the overnight guy. What do you
think our chances are of keeping this quiet?
I'd say absolutely zero.
You knew I was waiting
to see her again.
You said you were waiting
for your bear poop.
I said, "Are you excited about
the excrement or the courier?"
and you said,
"What do you think?"
And you actually thought
I was excited about excrement?
You have to be clear.
What's that?
A piece of undigested bone.
Metacarpal.
I think that goes with my hand.
Part of a tin can.
Elastin fibers. Some kind of sporocarp.
Here's something.
Hair follicles. Sebaceous glands?
There's a layer of dermis.
Pigmentation marks
in the macrophage.
A flap of skin with a tattoo.
We need a tatoo expert.
It's fairly simple. Uh, two colors,
red and black.
Some kind of native design.
She likes me more
than she likes you.
She said I
was sweet.
I made her laugh
at Jimmy's third nostril.
That's pretty good. Making a woman laugh
at a third nostril.
We have a tentative
coffee date.
She said she wanted
to eat me up.
Zack's definitely
ahead on points.
There it is.
The skin in the scat
has a sun on it.
- What is that, a haiku?
- It's a tattoo.
Hi, Booth.
Hi. I'm Angela Montenegro.
- How you doing, Angela?
- Angela, focus, please.
It's a Haida sun motif.
Good work,
very impressive.
18 to 25-year-old man,
Haida sun tattoo on his arm?
Hey, Booth, I have kind of
a thing for tattoos. You got any?
Angela!
I'm sorry, sweetie, but
what's with that town?
You getting anything going
with that hot overnight guy?
Angie, we're trying to work.
Is that town totally wasted
on you, sweetie?
Because I'd take this as a sign
from God to loosen up.
You know what they say-- "What
happens in Aurora stays in Aurora."
Hey.
I'm running a missing persons check
using the new info on the tattoo.
She seems very friendly,
your associate.
She's 3,000 miles away.
I'd send away
for a Russian bride.
Adam Langer, 22. Missing ten days from
a college in Richen
Wait, I know this kid. He used to come up
to visit Sherman. He wanted to be ranger.
Look, I've known Sherman for years.
I can't believe he had anything to do with this.
- Hey, Sheriff.
- Sherman.
Mind if we come in?
You guys here about
the cannibal?
We can´t talk about
official business.
How's about some tea?
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
What'd you do that for?
Give you a chance to look
around, get a sense of the man.
The raven spirit.
In some Native American stories
it has a cannibalistic element.
He went out back.
Give me a flashlight.
No way you'll catch
Sherman Rivers in the woods.
Just search the place.
Sherman, stop!
I don't know if
a wall of knives is evidence,
but it sure is creepy.
Hey! Stop.
Is there a saw?
Yep.
I want to take it.
See if it matches the cuts in
Adam Langer's bones.
See if this matches
the teeth marks.
You've got to be kidding me.
As Justice of the Peace, I authorize
you to open that locked freezer.
Thank you.
What kind of meat
do you think that is?
I send it a bunch of frozen
meat by overnight air
I need to know what
it is as soon as possible.
Think it's human?
Maybe, it's a funny color.
So did you catch the guy?
No, Booth lost him in the woods.
Whoa, wait a second!
I didn't lose him.
Well, you didn't catch him.
So you two have the night free.
Yes, we can't do anything until
I get a determination
on that meat,
and Booth has to wait
until it's light to look
for the guy he lost.
I didn't lose him, okay?
I... He... Tell her that
my flashlight died.
She doesn't care.
What?
Give me the phone.
It's not safe to drive and talk
on the cell phone.
Are you two figh?
Professional pride. Tell her,
please, tell her that.
Booth wants you to know that he
lost the guy because his flashlight died.
And because he's an Indian
and he's a park ranger,
and he's very, very familiar
with the territory. Tell her that.
Did you hear that?
Yeah, something about
Indian territory.
Yeah, she says she understands.
I need to know about that meat
as soon as possible.
Yeah! I´ll tell Zack.
Give me the phone.
Hold on. Plus...
What?
It wasn't even
my flashlight, okay?
It was the
sheriff's flashlight,
and his batteries,
they ran out, okay?
Good night, Angela.
Hey, you have to take
that man for a drink.
And have a little fun yourself.
Fun and a drink,
where do we find that?
So I was surprised
to see you here.
In your book you never sleep
until you get your man
Well, that's not me,
that's just a character.
In real life, you have
to wait for lab results.
I see, well, lucky for me.
I don't know, I'm afraid
I'm not a very good dancer.
Apparently I lead.
So, I'll follow.
Hey Booth, wanna a beer?
What you need sheriff?
You know, I climbed
with Adam sometimes.
I was kind of freaked-out
when I found
out it was his arm
You knew Adam Langer?
I taught him how to climb.
Man, he was strong.
No matter how
much I lift,
I could... I could
never match him.
You do have...
excellent definition
in your biceps
and triceps.
Well, thanks.
And your waist muscles
feel good, too.
Transverse abdominals.
Thank you.
So that meat we sent
back to your lab,
that wasn't more
of Adam, was it?
I can't discuss it.
Excusez-moi.
Dr. Rigby.
I thought rescue you.
I can't imagine you and Charlie
have a lot to talk about.
We were managing.
Look, um... I guess it looks
pretty bad for Sherman, huh?
I can't discuss the investigation
with you, Dr. Rigby.
Look, Sherman is
a Flathead.
The spiritual beliefs
of his tribe
don't value cannibalism,
they never have.
Well, anthropology
teaches us
that beliefs
and customs evolve.
That's why you can still find
cannibalism practiced today.
So wait, you can justify the act
of eating another human being?
I can understand it
intellectually.
I shouldn't
be talking shop.
Not with such a beautiful
woman in my arms.
You really think you can match the
bite marks on Sherman's apple
with the bite marks on
that kid's arm bone?
I don't really feel
comfortable discussing a case
on the dance floor.
Well, I'm the sheriff.
We're colleagues.
Mind if I cut in?
Thought you might
need a break.
What happened
to your shirt?
Well, we're in a bar.
It's a look.
Sorry?
For information
on the case.
Bones, they're
only pretending
to be interested
in thease.
Why?
They're hitting on you.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
You're the hottest thing
this town in a long time
Check out the competition.
Now that is someone who
wants to eat your heart.
Ooh. Very pretty.
Lovely.
It's a sporocarb
called tririgbosum,
after a week in bear poop.
Thank you for ruining
my moment.
It's a mushroom--
an Oregon white truffle.
They're a microrisal
species
that only grow in symbiosis
with Douglas fir trees.
Are Douglas fir trees very,
very rare in the woods?
No.
Then you really haven't found
anything useful, have you?
No.
Want to get something to eat?
Ah, you're expecting
a delivery tonight.
Zack is.
And you're going
to zoom him.
Like the Indy 500, baby.
You didn't come down
for breakfast, Bones.
I wasn't hungry.
Sorry you had to pay
for your own meal.
I called your room,
there was no answer.
Why the sudden interest
in my morning habits, Booth?
Well, I just thought we were
going to get something to eat.
You know? So I waited.
And my eggs got cold.
That's all. Cold eggs.
This is where
my flashlit failed
You mean
my flashlight.
And how can you be sure?
Because this is where
I was standing.
A shirt button?
And I heard him disappear
in this direction.
Leaving buttons on the trail.
Must be an old fish *** trick
You mean a snake eater.
An old snake eater trick.
Were you here all night?
Yes.
Did I miss Toni?
She asked about you.
You torpedoed me, didn't you?
No, I told her the truth.
you were sifting through
excrement.
You want a war?
Fine, because I am the warrior.
Zack?
I got the measurements for your
saw from the Angelator.
Now all you have to do
is find a match.
Say thank you with gifts.
Did you work all night?
Yes, I shaved
the truffle.
Is that anything like
spanking the monkey?
- I found boring dust.
- Is there any other kind?
Boring dust is produced
by beetles.
Which means the tree the
truffle grew on was infested.
That's not going
to impress Toni.
That's not why I did it.
I did it to serve justice and
capture a murderous cannibal.
That'll impress the hot courier.
I'm back in the game.
No way you'll catch
Sherman in the woods.
He's a park ranger
and an Indian.
Right there.
. He's doing some kind
of Indian ritual.
- He's waiting for us.
- Brennan.
The meat samples you sent us
were all Ursus americanus.
Black bear.
I didn't kill no one.
Why'd you run?
You're FBI.
Ever hear of Leonard Peltier?
Pineridge? Wounded Knee?
Indians and FBI don't mix.
He ran because
he's the poacher.
You're the poacher?
Yeah, the meat we found in
his freezer was black bear.
No wonder you never caught him.
I want a lawyer.
You should be on the lookout
for a patch of woods
that's infested with
Dendroctonus brevicomis LeCon.
Hodgins says the bear dug up the arm
in a stand of western pine beetle
infested Douglas fir.
Say you did catch
a poacher.
Say he was an Indian
who shouldn't have to follow
white man's law, anyway.
Not even a park ranger?
Say he could show you
a stand of trees like that.
Would you maybe let
that Indian go?
The saw is 300 millimeter
with 32 offset
teeth per inch,
with a wobble factor
of 1/100th of an inch.
Wait, that's a common hacksaw.
That won't help us much.
Dr. Brennan, I'm just wondering if you're
going to be sending us any more samples.
Yeah, uh, even more
of the same samples,
you know, in case we want
to double-check the data.
I'll let you know.
Do you think
she'll send more?
God in heaven, I hope so.
Japanese, right?
They pay a fortune
for that bear meat.
They think thgallbladders
fix up their pecker troubles.
Would have got
away with it,
if you hadn't kept the
meat in the freezer.
I'm not admitting nothing.
He couldn't bring himself
to waste the meat.
This patch of trees
is all infested
with beetles.
According
to the GPS,
the bear was here
seven days ago.
That fits the
timeline for the arm.
What a we looking for?
I'm guessing
we're looking
for a shallow grave
that's been disrupted
by a hungry bear.
Or maybe some kind
of satanic Stonehenge circle.
We see this kind of thing
all the time.
Kids come up
here, get baked,
do their own version of The
Blair Witch Project.
I don't know what that means.
It's a horror movie,
Bones.
Didn't make any sense.
Scary, though, with
the bloody handprints.
Ang, I'm going
to beam you some stills
of what looks like
a ritualistic Indian site--
a medicine wheel of me kind.
is thing legit?
What am I, a shaman?
Dr Goodman is an expert in
Native American anthropology.
He should be able to tell you
what it means.
Symbols, Indian site...
Sherman, you're looking
guiltier by the minute.
Oh, shut up, Chris.
You know better
than that.
Hey, you're
a poacher, man.
I sure as hell didn't see
that coming, either.
Got something?
Waxy leaves.
It means methane gas
leeching from the soil.
Like a body?
That's Adam Langer!
Uh, there's
a woman here, too.
Ann Nuyes,
the hiker.
And she´s missing her heart.
It's a perversion
of a Salish medine wheel.
This is the spirit chief,
Chichayilmaytchu.
The southern most stone
should represent strength.
The center of the wheel
should represent life force.
But this is upside down
and inside out.
We're dealing with a cannibal.
I suppose you could
interpret this as a way
of taking energy from someone
by eating their flesh.
Zoom in.
There. This is the symbol
for the strength: the arm.
This one is for spirit:
the heart.
This one for knowledge.
And this is for courage.
So we're looking for maybe
a scarecrow, tin man or a lion?
You say two bodies
were found?
Over here.
They were dug up by a bear;
one showing signs that his arm
was eaten by the cannibal,
the other missing her heart.
There should be two more bodies
to complete the ritual.
They checked
the site.
There were
only these two.
If I've analyzed this correctly,
it means there will be
two more victims.
Both victims were killed
by gunshots to the head.
These stellate patterns
at the entry wounds
indicate
a low-caliber handgun
at close range.
That remarkable.
Not really.
Based on adiposear formation,
I'm estimating the female
has been dead for about
A week?
Very good.
Thanks.
Well, her clothing matches
that of Ann Nuyes,
and the male
is Adam Langer.
My people at the Jeffersonian
tell me that the medicine wheel
suggests a perversion
of an old healing ritual.
The cannibal may have eaten
the arm for strength
and the heart for spirit.
Well, that makes sense, from a
certain point of view.
Do they think
it's an Indian?
No way to tell.
I'm no policeman, but
it doesn't make sense
that Sherman Rivers would lead you
straight to the
evidence that proves
he's a murderer
and a cannibal.
Adam was a good guy.
He wanted to be
a park ranger.
I was a...
what do you call it?
His mentor?
That's right,
his mentor.
Taking him out with me
on my rounds,
showing him the ropes
of the job.
Or maybe he had found out you´re poucher
so you made sure he wouldn't talk.
Yeah, so I ate his arm and ate
someone's heart for dessert,
because that's the type
of guy I am.
You know, he fits
the description
of someone who's
missing an arm.
Why didn't you
say anything?
Somebody says maybe
they're going to come and visit.
Maybe they do,
maybe they don't.
Maybe they go see
their climbing buddy instead.
Charlie?
The overnight guy.
Maybe sometimes
they go visit a girl.
What girl?
I'm not comfortable saying.
Well, maybe what, you know, with
the, uh, murders and cannibalism,
you, uh... you get
past that discomfort?
Adam had a thing
with the vet lady.
So did his buddy,
Charlie.
You know how jealously
white people can be
Um, in the interest
of full disclosure,
I've got to say
I see Denise
from time to time, too.
What, you find
that funny?
You know the apple we
found in Sherman's cabin?
You get a mold?
Zack?
Yeah. The mold from the apple
does not match
the teeth marks on the bone.
Thanks, Zach.
So what does that mean?
It means you aren't
the cannibal.
I already knew tt.
The point was to convince us.
What do we do now, start checking
everybody's teeth in town?
Not everybody.
We consume.
We are consumed.
We're consumed by greed,
by ambition, lust, jealousy.
Dr. Randall, if
u'd just like to...
I mean, even just regular love
is a form of cannibalism.
Could you just put the dental
medium between your teeth...
I mean, the whole
perfect idea of love
is that two people
become one.
Now, that's a kind
of consumption.
We're talking something a little
more literal, Dr. Randall.
I need you to bite it
Why didn't you
report him missing?
Because I would have had
to admit
that he and I were lovers.
Why not admit it?
Because it would have made
another guy angry.
What other guy?
Charlie.
And Sheriff Scutter.
And Andrew Rigby,
and maybe a couple others.
Well, there is not a lot to do
in a place like Aurora,
so what you do,
you do a lot.
Dr. Randall, if you... can you just
bite, please?
And if I were your cannibal,
would I have pointed out
that there we human bones
in the bear after the autopsy?
An autopsy on an animal
is called a necropsy.
Yeah, there's a reason I get
all the guys and you don't.
Uh, let me tell you,
if I ate Adam,
there wouldn't be anything left.
Here and here-- these look
like tooth marks again.
Okay.
Byt They´re too regular
That is 2.4 millimeters apart.
Teeth aren't that exact.
It has to be some kind
of a machine.
She was eaten
by a machine?
I don't know.
We got a love triangle,
quadrangle,
octangle, whatever.
Jealousy--
always a good motive.
For murdering Adam Langer,
maybe, but Ann Nuyes?
And the cannibalism?
No, we're looking for someone
who's clinically insane.
That whole rant thing
the vet lady had
about people consuming
each other?
That was wacky.
Yeah, but kind of
true, don't you think?
Hey, Angela
Sweetie, Zack wants
to beam you something.
Okay, hold on a second.
See if you can
tell what it is,
but if you're in
a public place,
you might want to
cover your screen.
What am I looking at?
Indentations
on Ann Nuyes' sternum.
Magnification?
Forty.
I can't belie both Dr.
Rigby and I miss these.
- Good job.
- What are they?
How far apart are
these indentations?
2.4 millimeters.
Okay, these marks
and the splitting
of the bone
here were made
by a sternum spreader.
There's no record of Ann Nuyes
having heart surgery.
Moments like this
are why I need a gun.
Where else
do you keep them?
Thank you.
That is for
self-defense.
Don't just go blasting
away in there.
What if I have to shoot?
What part of his body
should I hit?
The part that isn't me.
Just stay back.
The bodies are gone.
What's he going to do,
take them into the woods
for a late-night snack?
If I were him, I'd
destroy the evidence.
Step away from the incinerator,
Dr. Rigby.
You don't understand.
It's a spiritual right
to share the life force...
Look, you're nuts, okay?
We get it.
We don't need to
hear the rambling
psycho speech on why you did it.
You're an
anthropologist.
You know that
ancient civilizations
would sacrifice some
in order to preserve
the strength...
What'd you do that for?
Nobody wants to hear
that rambling psycho speech.
A bedpan?
Why do we have to
face her togher?
You want this settled
or what?
I'd definitely
like this settled.
What are you doing here?
Are you kidding?
It's like watching the Clash
of the Horny Titans.
Who'd like to sign for this?
Who wouldn't
want to sign for it?
So the idea is
whoever signs for this...
Yes, the act of signing is
an analog for choosing...
She gets it.
Oh.
That is really sweet.
Thank you.
That is so hot.
Why? Why is that hot?
It'd be hotter if
she'd choosen me
No, this is definitly
And to think I didn't want
to come here with you.
I mean, this was
a fascinating case.
You don't often find
ritual cannibalism practiced
so close to home.
Which I find a plus.
There are always those
individuals within a species
who are driven to break
the most basic taboos.
I mean, Rigby
actually ate human flesh.
Bones,
my steak and eggs.
Rigby has a prion disease,
which means he's been a cannibal
for quite some time.
Do you realize
when we go to trial,
he could use
the insanity defense?
The guy is nuts.
Yes, but is he nuts
because he got a brain disease
from eating human flesh,
or was he already nuts
the first time he ate flesh,
or did he just lick
his fingers after surgery?
I should just
become a vegetarian.
Or, as an alternative,
just don't eat people.
You know, I'm going to come
back up here this winter.
Charlie says
the skiing is great.
Oh, it's Charlie.
Yeah, the overnight guy.
Yeah, I know who he is.
I bet he's a great skier.
His hips and thighs
are perfectly developed
for strength
and mauverability.
That's it. I´m done.
What?
No good?
You want some corn flakes?
Want some.