victim stabed
upward of 30 times.
Every rib is marked--
vertebra sternal,
vertebra costal...
What kind of weapon?
Ooh, vacations in the desert.
It's like lunching at the dump.
Uh, pointed
with no cutting edge,
like a giant ice pick.
Whoa, Angela.
Or a sharpened screwdriver.
We warned her about the sun,
right?
We told her cover up,
avoid melanoma.
Who's the guy?
Her boyfriend,
Kirk.
Angela has a boyfriend?
Every year for three weeks,
Angela has a boyfriend
and a vacation.
Whoa, whoa, playing house
in a post-boho,
rustic artist cabin
in the desert
with her overpaid,
pseudo-celebrity photographer
boyfriend,
that is not a vacation.
Eight months to a year dead,
correct?
Yeah, yeah, pupal
casings, maggots,
blah, blah, blah,
eight months to a year.
Angela, we're betting.
Are you using Crisco
or butter for sunscreen?
Hey, Brennan,
could I talk to you
in private, please?
You're going to think I'm crazy.
What's up, boyfriend trouble?
No, I-I-I'd just send it to you,
but the sheriff won't let me.
Send what?
Somebody left a human skull
in a box
on the sheriff's porch.
He says it was probably a Navajo
who respects the dead,
but doesn't want to get
pulled into the whole
white justice system.
The thing is, is that Kirk
went out into the desert
five days ago
on a photo shoot,
and he hasn't come back.
Nobody can find him
or his guide.
You think the skull is Kirk's?
No. No.
Kirk's always going out
into the desert
for days at a time.
You're really sending me
mixed messages, Ange.
Yeah, well, I'm freaking out,
I guess.
I'm sorry.
Look, you know, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have called.
Pretend I didn't call.
I'll just...
I'll talk to you
when Kirk gets back.
Sorry.
You're taking a vacation
in the desert with no notice?
I don't get the attraction,
I really don't.
Snakes,
scorpions...
It should only be
for a few days.
Buzzards and snakes.
What about
the stabbing victim?
Zack identified
the weapon and the victim.
Our job is done.
MONTENEGRO:
I mean, it's not
like I actually think that
the skull is Kirk's.
But I mean,
if you could
just look at it
and just tell
me it isn't,
then I could stop worrying about
him being dead
and just be mad at him
for being a flaky artist.
You won't get
anything out here.
We're about 100 miles past
where Jesus lost
his sandals.
I assume that's a way of saying
"we're extremely isolated."
Yeah, it's why
we come out here
every year.
It's like you stand
still and the whole universe
just comes at you.
At 110 degrees.
You know, Kirk was out
with a good guide,
our friend Dani.
I mean, he said he'd be back,
he said we'd go out
for nachos and beer.
And this is a man who's serious
about his beer.
I got the Navajo police
looking between
Dona Ona Canyon
and the Otero Bluffs.
Ben, Dr. Brennan is
a forensic anthropologist
with the Jeffersonian
Institution.
I spend
most of my time
helping the FBI conduct
murder investigations.
Angie, I kind of
got my hands full
getting searchers out
to look for Dani and Kirk.
The state police said that
they would lend us a chopper,
but only if we narrowed
down the search area.
They got to be
running low on water.
I don't give them more
than a couple of days.
Ben, if you could just
show Dr. Brennan the skull.
Or point me toward
the morgue.
Welcome to
the Merville County morgue.
Prominent brow ridge indicates
the victim is male.
You mind?
Be my guest.
Oh, no, she wants the plate,
Ben, not the muffin.
Cranial shape and nasal features
suggest Caucasian.
Died in the last several days.
Critters been at it pretty good.
Pattern of basilar
suture fusion puts age
30 to 35.
Well, it doesn't look like Kirk.
Doesn't look like anyone, Angie.
Putrascine.
Early stages of decomp.
Cause of death?
A man gets caught
unawares
out in the desert, he could be
dead in a few hours.
Uh-oh.
What?
Base of the skull here
detached from the spinal cord.
See these little bevel marks?
Perimortem contact: gunshot.
It wasn't the desert who caught
this man unawares.
It was someone with a gun.
www.1000fr.com
MONTENEGRO:
You can't say that it's Kirk.
I know.
You want some tea?
I'd rather have a beer.
This woman modeling
in these pictures,
is this Dani?
Yeah.
Dani Weber.
It's Kirk's guide in the desert.
She's beautiful.
Dani has lived her whole life.
You know, Ben says
that she knows the desert
better than anybody.
Look, there's no way
that she gets lost
or she runs out of water.
There's just no way.
No.
What?
Brennan, if you hug me
and you be all caring
it's because you
think Kirk is dead.
Or because he was
sleeping with Dani.
No, it's because...
I'm sorry that
my friend is upset
because someone
she loves is missing.
( sighs )
All right.
I can buy that.
You know,
if you don't mind,
I'm just going to head to bed.
Good night.
( whistling )
( cell phone rings )
Booth.
How far are you from Dulles?
As far as your office is
from Dulles.
Why are you in my office?
I need your findings
on the Richmond case.
Listen, Zack,
he won't tell me where they are
unless you give him
permission.
There's a 9:15 flight to Denver.
Then there's an 11:35 flight
to Santa Fe.
You'll have to run to make
the connection.
Forget it.
Booth, please.
Angela's boyfriend is missing.
Maybe dead.
It took all of my charm...
just to get the sheriff
Your charm, oh boy!
to let me look at the skull.
When I asked him to let me send
the skull to the Jeffersonian,
he told me I am not a cop
and that I don't have
any jurisdiction.
Which is true.
Okay, what, look...
what do you want me to do?
I want you to get federal
on his ass.
( door bangs )
Hey. There you go.
Hey.
You know, people
in the desert
don't have
actual addresses.
What's up with that?
Booth, you made it.
Yeah.
You know, I'm touring the
hottest places in the universe.
Next stop-- here you go--
hell.
I'm not really awake yet.
Last night
before I left,
I used my FBI powers
to force the sheriff
to send the skull
back to the Jeffersonian.
I talked to him this morning.
Ooh, seems a little resentful.
What time is it?
Let's go.
Drink that on the way.
Wha-- on the way where?
You know, to go
check out the model,
guide, whatever's
place.
Dani.
Can I come with you?
No, no, we can ask
tougher questions
if you're not there.
Wait outside
while I get dressed.
No.
Uh-uh. Sun's been up
for an hour out there.
It's already the surface
of Mercury.
I can stand here
and close my eyes,
eat my doughnuts,
best I can do.
What tougher questions
can we ask
without Angela being here?
Things like, did her
boyfriend run off
with a model,
guide, whatever?
Angela and I
discussed this.
She said it couldn't happen.
Okay, no offense to
Angela, but she doesn't
really know this guy.
She's only with him, what,
three weeks out of the year.
No offense to you, but you're
a stodgy traditionalist
when it comes
to relationships, buddy.
Stodgy? Stodgy?
Okay, okay, here's the deal.
Yeah, stodgy.
Here's the deal, Bones.
We found out that the skull
isn't Kirk, we go home,
we let the locals
handle it, okay?
Yeah, of course.
BOOTH:
Yeah, you say "of course,"
but then you get all
caught up in it.
And then... What?
Oh.
What do you want?
BOOTH:
FBI.
We're looking for
Dani Weber.
Who are you?
Yeah, I'm the guy
holding the big gun.
Yeah, on a federal agent,
which I've been
very nice about so far.
Let's rush him.
He can't shoot us both.
How about I just show him
my badge, so we both
survive, all right?
See?
Name's Alex Joseph.
This is me and Dani's place.
Where's Dani Weber?
Missing...
in the desert for
almost a week.
I've been looking for her.
You point your gun
at everybody who comes by?
Maybe I'm nervous.
BOOTH:
Anything in particular
you might be nervous about?
Maybe something
Dani got caught up in.
Nothing I can think of.
Could we look
in the trailer?
Not without a warrant.
You have a problem
with law enforcement?
You could say that,
I guess.
Model runs off with
handsome photographer,
jealous boyfriend with a gun
finds them in the desert...
He's definitely twitchy
about something.
What if he's escaping
out the back door?
You don't spend a lot of time
in trailers, do you?
Whoa.
What?
That's Sheriff Dawes.
Yeah, he definitely
has a problem
with law enforcement.
( chuckles )
( music playing,
muffled through earpieces )
Dr. Brennan doesn't like
us to listen to music
while we're working.
Dr. Brennan is not here.
She thinks the work deserves
our full concentration.
I need the skull now.
Well, I'm still finding
particulates.
And since you're only
Dr. Brennan's assistant,
without her, you don't carry all
that much weight around here.
I'm telling Dr. Goodman.
( music playing )
Why didn't you mention your
relationship to Dani Weber?
BOOTH:
Dani Weber dropped you
for the photographer,
the Indian guy, or both.
Moron.
Dani's my sister.
Half sister.
Mostly I raised her.
You can check with Angie.
Okay, well,
I got that one... wrong.
I pretty much
don't like the look
of your sister's boyfriend,
Alex Joseph.
( scoffs )
Assault.
Narcotics.
He bootlegs
for the reservation.
Yeah, Dani could do better.
Any chance that
Dani got caught up in something
ugly because of him?
Until I find otherwise,
I'm assuming
that Dani and Kirk
are lost in the desert.
Alex Joseph-- is he bad enough
to hurt 'em
if he finds 'em out
in the desert together?
It's on my list of nightmares,
yeah.
( phone rings )
Brennan.
DNA results are in.
The skull is definitely
Kirk Persinger.
Poor Angela.
HODGINS ( over phone ):
Also, the hair test's
off the charts for
Lophophora williamsii-
derived mescaline.
What's that?
Peyote.
Anything on the cranial scoring?
ADDY:
I haven't really had a good
crack at the skull yet.
Hodgins hogged it.
The markings traced to
several desert dwelling
species-- it seems
a full-grown male coyote
did the most work on it,
but one with
a malformed jaw.
Very unusual bite
formations.
Ask Dr. Goodman to find
a naturalist.
Kirk Persinger?
Yes.
They found traces
of peyote.
BOOTH:
Drug-related.
Shot to the spine,
execution-style.
So, Sheriff, do you
still think this is
a simple
missing persons case?
I have to tell Angela.
Listen, Sheriff, um,
sorry for
the concern
you must be feeling
for you sister.
I will call the FBI
office in Albuquerque,
and I will officially take
over the investigation.
I won't do that.
Why?
Desert dwellers
are very insular.
Mongolians,
Bedouins of the Sahara,
the Himba of Kalana.
Good hosts but extremely
distrustful of outsiders.
Bone, this is the
United States of America.
It's not outer Mongolia.
The only reason
Sheriff Dawes talks to us at all
is because we know Angela.
Alex Joseph held a gun on us.
I'll admit, I've met
friendlier people.
If a bunch of outsiders
come in from Albuquerque
led by an outsider from D.C.,
I promise you
the people here will close ranks
and shut up
until we go away.
Then they'll take care of it
in their own way.
Okay, who are
you, Dr. Phil?
Who is Dr. Phil,
some kind of expert?
He likes to think so.
Okay, look, I'll take what
you say under advisement.
In the meantime, we
need to go find out
who supplied Kirk
with his peyote.
Well, how are we going
to do that?
Talk to his girlfriend.
BRENNAN:
I am so sorry, Angela.
We both are.
I knew it was Kirk.
That's why I called you.
We have to find out
what happened to Dani.
Angela, I'm going to have
to ask you a couple
difficult
questions, okay?
What-what can you tell me
about Kirk's drug use?
Kirk didn't do drugs.
Well, Hodgins found
peyote in his hair.
I thought...
I thought
that you meant drug drugs.
The peyote
wasn't recreational.
Kirk took part
in some Native Indian rights.
While high on drugs?
( sighs )
Did you do peyote with Kirk?
The peyote has nothing
to do with anything.
Angela,
you may have come in contact
with Kirk's killer without even
realizing it.
( sighs )
Who was his connection?
He's Kirk's friend.
I need the name.
( sighs ):
Wayne.
Wayne Kellogg.
He's an important local artist.
( sighs )
MAN:
I don't deny
having participated
in the peyote ritual
on several occasions.
Utterly spiritual experience.
You're not Indian.
Not by birth, no,
but as you can see
from my artwork,
I have a deep
spiritual connection
to the Navajo.
You sell a lot
of your work?
I sell very well overseas,
enough to keep this place
and a beach house
in Los Angeles. Why?
Why not buy Navajo art
created by actual Navajos?
BOOTH:
Peyote is only legal
if you're a member
of the Native American Church,
which means, you and Kirk
bought it illegally.
Buying illegal drugs
involves drug dealers.
I mean, you can follow my train
of thought here, can't you?
Look, I realize
Kirk's missing.
Kirk's not missing.
He's dead.
What about Dani?
Dani Weber remains
unaccounted for.
God, this is terrible.
I need the name
of your drug connection.
No.
I'm sorry.
These people trust me.
I understand the difficulty
in finding the peyote plants
miles out in the desert.
Secret places
passed on from generation
to generation.
Mr. Kellogg,
is that your vehicle?
Yes. Why?
BRENNAN:
Alex Joseph borrowed
that Humvee.
Wait. Alex Joseph
didn't go out
to the desert
to look for Dani Weber.
He went out
to look for peyote.
I never said that.
Mr. Joseph?
It's FBI again.
Like to ask you
a few more questions.
Booth?
BOOTH:
Oh, come on, Sheriff.
Come on, even out
here you know how the
drug world works, huh?
Kirk is found dead.
Joseph is beaten
to a pulp.
It's all connected.
My first priority
is to find Dani.
You find Kirk's murderer,
we probably find Dani.
Maybe Dani is the murderer.
What? I got to ask.
Dani never hurt anybody
in her life.
Except maybe herself.
BOOTH:
You know,
another thing
I have to consider--
maybe Dani, you know,
calls up her, uh,
brother the sheriff
and says, you know,
"This photographer
"raped me.
What do I do now?"
What you're proven
right now--
you don't know anything
about the people
that live around here.
Hmm. Joseph met us
with a rifle.
Maybe because
he was afraid
it was you coming around
the corner
of that house.
Alex Joseph is unconscious.
You maybe can talk to him
when he wakes up.
Me-- I'm going
to help the search parties
find my sister.
WOMAN:
Thanks to Fish and Wildlife,
most of the coyote packs
in this region have
at least one member
wearing a GPS collar.
BOOTH ( over phone ):
You can find one coyote
with a wonky
jaw in the desert?
What we do here is process
information from rangers,
amateur naturalists,
conservationists,
even school groups.
The Desert Coyote Packs Range
is not huge.
Perhaps ten square miles.
The pack is typically
three to eight animals
led by the alpha mating pair.
Wow.
BOOTH:
Why wow?
GOODMAN:
Professor Inez has found
your coyote,
but he's-he's way out
in the desert.
Three pups,
three females, two males--
including the leader
with the wonky jaw.
With eight coyotes
going at a cadaver.
Wow. You know, we're talking
needle in a haystack,
you know, finding the remains.
Mamas and the pups
feed together,
so I'd expect rib cage
and smaller bones
to be
in a concentrated area.
But the males move away
from each other
with the larger pieces.
No more than a half a mile.
Three weeks a year.
I mean, 15 weeks in total.
You think that's crazy.
Well...
it's not typical,
that's for sure.
And if he was
yours, 100% yours,
for three weeks
a year, that's...
It's more than I've ever had.
Kirk's photographs
show the world as a more
beautiful place than it is.
A-A better place.
He made me feel like
it was my real home.
That I belonged there...
with him.
He's the guy
I compare all other guys to.
Now he's gone, and I-I feel like
I can't even breathe, sweetie.
I can't even take a breath.
You think it's possible
that Dani's still out there?
Could she still be alive?
I don't know.
There's no crime scene, and...
we're not even sure where the
rest of Kirk's remains are.
Well, I want to help you
look for her tomorrow.
You sure?
Yeah. Dani was our friend.
I have to help find her.
Please?
Thank you.
( sighs )
I love the desert.
Or I used to.
Nothing looks the way it should.
Stuff that's far away
looks near, stuff that's near
looks far.
MONTENEGRO:
Yeah, well,
you can't trust your eyes
out here.
Not your eyes alone.
You know, Kirk said
that if you stood still
long enough,
that the desert would actually
speak to you.
Show you some kind of truth.
That ever happen to you?
No, but he really believed that.
Alex Joseph woke up.
Good.
You think whoever beat him up
had something to do
with Kirk Persinger's murder.
Yeah.
Nope.
How can you be so sure?
You were the one
that beat him up?
No.
Okay.
Well, uh... do you
know who did?
These guys.
Or guys just like 'em.
Why?
Peyote ritual.
These people take it seriously.
It's their religion.
A guy like Alex Joseph starts
selling it to white guys
like Kellogg and Kirk,
they don't like it.
Aren't you going
to arrest any of them?
No.
But I might deputize a couple.
You know, Sheriff,
I get how you people
handle things out here,
but I got ask you--
I mean, if they'd
beat up an Indian
for selling peyote,
what the hell
are they gonna do to Kirk
for taking it?
Nothing. Kirk's a white man.
The way they see it,
he's my responsibility.
MAN:
Hey! I got
something here!
Ange, they found
some bones over here.
It might be Kirk.
It is Kirk.
This is his camera.
Are you sure?
No, no, no.
Don't, don't.
There could be
exposed film in there.
It's cracked.
Can't let anymore light in,
it'll damage the film.
Maybe Kirk was right.
This could be a good way
for the desert to tell us
what happened to him.
Photograph of his murder.
This camera is going straight
to the State Police Crime Lab.
Angela is better
at developing film
than anyone in Santa Fe.
MONTENEGRO:
Plus I can use
Kirk's equipment.
It's top of the line.
Yeah, and we won't have
to wait
for the results, Sheriff.
BRENNAN:
With your sister maybe
still alive out in the desert,
every hour counts.
Can't do it.
Booth...
Yeah, you know,
according to Homeland Security,
Kellogg sold exactly $120,000
worth of art overseas.
What's that
got to do with anything?
BOOTH:
Well, it sure as hell doesn't
buy him a beach house
in Los Angeles, now does it?
He lied.
Let's go check him out.
What will we be looking for?
BOOTH:
You know, what we
always look for.
You know, something
that doesn't fit.
Something that, you know...
Something.
I can't believe that you
think that I am a suspect.
Angie, not to speak ill
of the dead, but, uh...
a woman like you,
you're worth
more than
three weeks a year,
you understand?
You think I murdered Kirk
because he didn't
give me enough time?
I'm just a lawman.
People are people.
Ben, Kirk wasn't the one who put
limits on our time together.
He wanted me to marry him,
and he deserved more,
and better.
Please, Ben, I want
to help find Dani.
And there could be
evidence on this film.
Just let me do what I do
better than anybody else.
Thank you.
Angie...
Maybe he deserved more,
not my place to say,
but he couldn't
have done better.
No man could.
I haven't attained
anything like the success
Kirk has,
but I do all right-- why?
You have a beach house.
I applied for a warrant
to check for your
assets, your tax returns.
I told you,
I do well in Europe,
Germany especially appreciates
Native-themed work.
Kirk Persinger's remains were
found way out in the desert.
What's that got to do with me?
Oh, because you have a vehicle
that's capable
of going out that far.
A vehicle I often loan out.
What are these?
Engraving plates.
Please don't
touch them.
The oils on your skin
will comprise
the integrity.
Why would I kill Kirk?
Maybe because, you know,
you had a little thing,
you know, for Dani.
Or maybe because you
were jealous of Kirk's
artistic success.
These aren't Native designs.
Bones, I'm working
a line of inquiry here.
BRENNAN:
All of your work
is stolen from Native designs.
These are floral.
It doesn't fit.
Not stolen.
Inspired by.
And that piece
is commissioned.
Another way I make money.
Hi, Angela.
Well, most of the film
was wrecked,
but I developed
a few usable images.
That's great.
No, no, because Ben got me
to make a couple of prints
and then he bolted with them
and all the negatives.
Sheriff Dawes took off
with the negatives.
What'd she find on them?
Did you recognize
anything?
Dani in the desert,
and that's all.
I have no idea
what he got so excited about.
Nothing that meant
anything to Angela.
We'll go take a look
for ourselves.
Talk to you again.
I wanted to show these
photographs to Alex Joseph.
I don't need your permission.
Why Joseph?
Angela says
there are only
a few partial photos of
your sister in the desert.
That's right.
The only person
that knows the desert
as good as Dani is Joseph.
This formation here,
I'm not familiar
with it.
There's nothing like
this anywhere near
where we found Kirk's remains
or the camera.
Well, he was killed
somewhere else and moved.
If we find that outcropping,
maybe we find the place
where Kirk was killed
and maybe we find my sister.
Did Joseph recognize the rock?
Yeah.
Where?
It's easier I take
you than explain.
Whoa, whoa, okay,
if Joseph is a murderer,
he's just sending you
on a wild-goose chase.
Well, then we know
he's the murderer
and all we've wasted is a tank
of gas in a goose chase.
How far out are we going?
A ways.
One week in the desert and
there's nothing but bone left.
HODGINS:
Same guy?
Looks like it.
Uh, I think
it would be better
if I went over the bones
for particulates
before you start
your thing.
I disagree, and you
can't have them
unless I release them to you.
You're gonna have to do
the "boss thing," boss.
Sir, Dr. Brennan needs
to know how this man died,
which is my territory,
more than when
and where he died.
Dr. Hodgins?
Even I can see he got shot
in the back of the head.
What Dr. Brennan needs
is the murder scene.
It's the desert.
Insects and particulates
aren't going
to narrow it down
any more than that.
We won't know that until
I look at the particulates.
Dr. Hodgins will have access
to the bones first, Mr. Addy.
That's the wrong decision.
BRENNAN:
My lungs are going to come
out through my throat.
You know, where I come from,
when you say
you're driving a ways,
you know, it means 45 minutes.
Out here,
it means four hours.
We've been driving five.
I maybe should have
said quite a ways.
There it is.
BOOTH:
Well... that it?
Yeah,
I think so.
Different time of day.
You people look for the exact
spot the pictures were taken.
I'm gonna take another
circle in the truck.
Looking for your sister?
I think we want to go
south slightly.
Maybe southwest.
You can tell from the shadows?
Yeah, and the angle
on the outcropping.
Where's he going?
He's looking for his sister.
Either of you two
bring any water?
Why?
You worried?
Yeah.
About what?
Because we are way past
where Jesus lost his sandals.
And I don't hear
the truck anymore.
No cell phone service.
No water.
How long do you think
we'll survive out here
if the sheriff
doesn't come back?
Three days, max.
Well, how far are we
from the highway?
Five days, minimum.
I don't like that math.
Wait a second.
BOOTH:
Kirk's?
It looks like it, yeah.
Yeah... distributor's smashed.
That's it.
All the wires
are pulled out.
It doesn't make sense
that the sheriff brings us
to the scene of the crime and
then leaves us to die, does it?
One godforsaken
part of the desert just as good
as another godforsaken
part of the desert.
We don't even know
if Sheriff Dawes actually
called Alex Joseph.
I mean,
for all we know,
he could have done
all this himself.
Could Dawes do that, Ange?
Well, I always thought
Ben Dawes was a good man.
It would take a lot
to change my mind.
Well, like, being
left to die in the desert?
BOOTH:
These tracks here,
they don't match the sheriff's
vehicle, they're too wide.
Humvee maybe?
This is blood, I think.
The victim
was kneeling here.
Bones.
Sorry.
He was dragged this way,
then the blood trail ends.
He was thrown
into the Humvee.
We've got to be 200 miles from
where we found Kirk's bones.
You think the murderer drove
that far to drop the body?
Where are you going?
Boo... Hey.
Yup, tracks,
they stop right here.
BRENNAN:
What here?
There's no here here.
Landing strip, huh?
I knew this was about drugs.
( Booth groans )
Mexico's about
80 miles that way.
Oh, yes.
Only Angela could get a ride
in the middle of nowhere.
Any signs of your sister?
She's been out
there a week.
She could still be alive if she
had a few canteens of water.
Humvee tracks, Sheriff.
Alex Joseph?
Catches Kirk and Dani
out here...
Sandy, this is Dawes,
do you receive me?
Loud and clear on the satellite,
Sheriff. Where are you?
Hell and gone.
Listen, Sandy, I need
a deputy down
at the clinic,
slap some cuffs on Alex Joseph.
Alex Joseph took off, Sheriff.
We got no idea where he went.
Kellogg's Humvee.
Sandy, go collect
Wayne Kellogg's
Humvee and we'll
see you in a few hours.
Any blood stains
should flare a bluish-green
when the luminol hits them.
Nothing.
Well, we know that Kirk's body
was put into the Humvee.
Tire treads match.
It's clean.
Give Kellogg
his truck back.
Tell him sorry
for the inconvenience.
Try the hood.
You think they tied Kirk's
bloody, dead body
to the hood like an elk
then drove him 200 miles
before dumping him for coyotes?
Even out here,
people might notice.
Right there.
????
Zack?
Yes, Dr. Brennan?
I need to know if Kirk's bones
show more damage than can be
explained by animal activity.
Preliminary analysis indicates
that the pubic rami
are fractured,
and the left hemipelvis
is severely displaced.
Congruent with a fall?
Yes, Dr. Brennan.
Were the remains found
at the base
of a cliff?
He wasn't driven 200 miles.
He was driven a
couple hundred yards.
Loaded his body in
the airplane...
( clucks tongue )
then tossed it.
Zack, I'm not happy
with how long
it took you to get
back to me on this.
We'll talk about it
when I get back.
Sorry, Dr. Brennan.
HODGINS:
You could have told her
it wasn't your fault.
( sighs )
I still have some work
to do here.
If they dumped Kirk's body
from a plane,
then they could have done
the same to Dani.
Yeah, well, Kirk was
dead when they
tossed him, right?
Absolutely. And I saw no
evidence of a second
murder at the site.
Which leaves me hoping either
my sister is kidnapped
by drug dealers or dying
somewhere in the desert.
Kidnapping's a
federal offense.
It's an FBI matter.
I can help you,
if you want.
( cell phone rings )
Brennan.
Dr. Brennan,
those cell phone photos
you sent me of engravings...
Kellogg said it was a
commissioned work.
I think these
are engravers' plates.
For what?
Currency.
To be exact, I believe
these are dyes
for the Venezuelan
500 bolivar bill.
Dyes? Counterfeiters' dyes?
Yes.
Did you say
"counterfeiters."
I got a warrant here
to search your client's studio
for engraving plates.
Well, as Mr. Kellogg's
attorney, I can advise you,
you're certain to find some.
I'm an engraver.
Larry, did you
tell Wayne about
how when someone dies
during the commission
of a felony,
everyone involved
in that felony
is charged with murder?
Counterfeiting is a felony.
My client will confess to
the counterfeiting charges,
in return for
immunity from the murder charge.
Not good enough.
He will also provide
the time and place
of the next pickup
out in the desert.
You'll be able to arrest
the actual murderers.
When Sheriff Dawes says
"not good enough,"
he means his sister, Larry.
My client doesn't know
anything about Dani Weber.
What does he know?
One week ago, I arranged to meet
some associates
at an airstrip in the desert
to pass on
some commissioned artwork.
He means counterfeit plates.
As the plane landed,
my associates
noticed two people
spying on them
from a vantage point
above the airstrip.
They became very agitated.
They commandeered my vehicle,
and they drove
up the hill.
I got my Humvee,
then I drove up there.
But I didn't see anything.
Like blood on the hood
of your vehicle?
Well... the fact remains
that agreeing to this deal
is the only way that
you're going to catch
the actual murderers.
You know where to find me.
Wayne, I need to know if they
loaded Dani on that plane.
I never saw Dani.
BOOTH:
Easy, Sheriff.
That's my sister. My sister!
I am truly sorry
about Dani, Ben.
Truly sorry. But I don't
think Wayne knows anything.
Come on, Dawes.
Easy.
Come on.
I guess we're gonna have
to take that deal, right?
I was trained as an Army Ranger.
That mean anything to you,
Sheriff Dawes?
I'd be more than happy
to go back out to
that crime scene,
see if there's anything
we haven't missed.
Appreciate it.
If you expect to win
arguments around here,
you will need
at least one doctorate.
I am Dr. Brennan's
grad student.
I'm aware.
Once I get my doctorate,
she will take on
another grad student.
My job here will go
to that person.
You have a first-rate mind,
Mr. Addy.
You can't assist
Dr. Brennan forever.
I really hope
this is necessary.
He's comfortable here.
He's enamored
with Dr. Brennan,
and he's stopped working
on his thesis. It's necessary.
It's just...
( sighs )
I like the guy.
So do I.
Which is why we must think of
what's best for him.
It's time for Mr. Addy
to grow up.
So, you say Dani knows
the desert pretty well?
That's right.
If it were you here
stranded, which way
would you go?
Highway's about
a five-day walk that way.
Mexico is three days
that way, and...
that way's two days to a ranch.
You might find some stock water,
but I wouldn't count on it.
And the terrain is rougher.
So, it all depends on
how much water she had.
Is there any way
to know?
All right, look, we'll
take a point off this
compass, all right?
Walk out in a straight line
for 15 minutes,
we look for tracks.
Good?
* *
You all right?
Dani went that way.
Okay.
* *
Ready to go home?
Yeah.
You're not coming
back again, are you?
No.
Never.
He loved me.
For three weeks a year.
No.
He loved me all the time.
I was the one who could only
manage three weeks a year.
Oh, I'm afraid that I...
I'm just afraid that I don't
have a generous heart.
I'm afraid
that I won't...
have the chance that I had
with Kirk ever again.
You will.
How can you be so sure?
Because nothing in this universe
happens just once, Angela.
Nothing.
Infinity goes
in both directions.
There is no unique event,
no singular moment.
I don't know what that means.
It means
you will get another chance.
You promise?
From your heart?
Better.
From my head.
And yes,
Ange, I promise...
from my heart...
you will get another chance.
* *
Well, Dawes and his deputies,
they caught the counterfeiters.
Dani gave a statement saying
that it was Kellogg
who pulled the
trigger on Kirk.
Dani knows that you saved
her life.
You pointed that helicopter
in the right direction.
Obviously, you
subconsciously
sifted through
the rational facts
of the case
and processed
the most likely scenario.
I'm sure that's it.
Yeah, what else could it be?
Well, it's the only
rational explanation.
Are you guys
making fun of me?
( sighs )
You know, let's go back home.
You know?
Where there's water, shelter
and living things.
Come on!
* *
www.1000fr.com