Come on, honey. If we don't leave now,
we don앖 get into the club.
I'm just finishing
up a few e-mails.
Oh, what?
My publisher wants to schedule a book tour
and I'm just confirming dates.
Okay, that can wait, sweetie.
The students need help identifying the cause
of a fracture on a lateral epicondyle.
TGIF. You heard of that?
Yeah. It's some kind of acronym.
But my inbox is full.
We know that's not true.
And there's a TV show that needs
research. Not that they listen.
We're going.
I really should catalogue that skull. It's in the
museum's exhibit on the French Revolution.
Yeah, Pepe LePew is more
important than booze and boys.
I don't think that's his name.
Tonight the basement club brings to you
a number one DJ around town
DJ Rulz
Feels good, doesn't it? Being with
people who are alive.
It's very stimulating,
I have to admit.
We're so going to
tear it up tonight.
- That's slang, right?
- Right.
Is my costume all right?
Sweetie, it's not a costume, it's a cute
outfit, and yes, it looks perfect.
I know, it's very,
very warm in here.
No, because it looks great.
Were so get in check up!
- I love this music!
- DJ Rulz! He is so hot!
It's so tribal.
- You don앖 say tribal, sweetie.
- Why?
Oh, because of
all the black people?
Sweetie, just for tonight, have fun,
stop dissecting  and take part.
Well, African-Americans aren't the
only ones with a tribal heritage.
You saying we're natives
in some tribe?
Anthropologically speaking,
we're all members of tribes.
You'd better shut your mouth.
I just meant hip-hop mirrors the direct visceral
connection you see in tribal communication.
What?
After the Cartesian split he 17th century,
we separated our minds from our bodies,
the numinous from
the animalistic.
Are you calling me
an animal, fool?
No fool, she압 using the Cart foilosophy
to say she's down with the music.
Now, who are you
calling a fool, fool?
Get out of my way.
We're going.
You shouldn't
have done that, bitch.
Are you sure she
can handle this?
No one in our lab knows the first thing
about dealing with a mummy.
I'd have to call her in anyway.
She assaulted two agents who were
trying to tape off the body.
They were trying
to compromise the remains.
A cloud of meth covered
the dance floor.
I think they inhale quite a lot.
Are you two high?
Only by accident,
so it doesn't count.
Wait. Why did you bring Tessa? This doesn't
seem like such a great date.
We were out to dinner when he got your call.
Your pupils are the size of saucers.
Get away from the remains!
Bones,  simmer down.
How long is this
going to take?
Who the hell wants to know?
I'm sorry. He works for me.
I'm Randall Hall. I run this place.
You run this place, Mr. Hall. Just so you know,
'cause we, uh, found some drugs on the dead...
We found them. We found them.
We found some drugs
on the dead guy.
We're going to want to know where they
came from, why he had them...
Why?
- Why he had them.
Any idea who he is?
Any idea?
The guy barely looks human. What makes
you think I'd regnize him?
Bones...
how did something like this
happen?
The Egyptians would give
the body a cedar oil enema
and then rinse it with wine and cover it with
salt. But I don't think that's what happened here.
Bones, you are totally wasted.
Zack! Zack!
Come here, come here.
n't thIs a beautiful
specimen of mummification?
What's going on?
Let's just say
your boss inhaled.
See how perfectly drie
and preserved the skin is.
You don't find something
like this every day.
Tessa, have you seen it
It's so hard to believe that
you two would be a couple.
You know, cop and lawyer.
It's very touching.
I'm going to grab a cab.
Oh, no, oh, okay,
hold on. Well, uh...Sorry.
I apologize. Here. I'm going to
make it up to you, I promise. okay?
Ice cream later.
-Take care.
- I'll talk to you later.
Talk to you later.
Can we just stick to the
business here? Thank you.
I앐 gonna need a list of
your employees, all right?
We'll find out-- run them through the system,
see if any one of them have a drug conviction.
How long before
you can ID him?
Well I앐 not all tired, so I'm sure
I can stay up all night and work.
We have to be careful removing him.
He's very dry and brittle.
My first modern mummy.
Bones 1x06
Trancript: cfsmp3
Sync: Narkond
Crystal meth is made
from cold medicine, lye,
and the strike
pads from matchbooks.
The body was not designed to
deal with that kind of assault.
So I'm finding out.
Chamomile tea?
It's very soothing.
JI just need your results.
How about a stick to pry
the monkey off your back?
Are you sure you need me here?
Payback for showing
me the good life.
Ok, so how is my man,
the Tut?
In better shape
than I am
The meth found in his lungs and nasal passages
matches the meth that juiced
Angela and the good doctor here.
Can you please
keep it clinical?
So, uh, he died
of, uh, an overdose.
Asphyxiation.
The meth coated the alveoli in his lungs,
making breathing impossible.
So, uh, he, uh, overdosed
with his meth behind the wall?
The little space was too narrow
for him to squeeze through.
He got stuck, the bag broke, and when he gasped
for air, he inhaled and died instantaneously.
The dry air convection behind the wall removed
most of the moisture from his body
How long he was, uh, in there?
Judging from the acarid mites
in his ears, I'd say six weeks.
Hey, didn't he have hands?
They're easier to work with
dismembered.
I've rehydrated them so we
can get some fingerprints.
- Off that?
- Sure.
You ever been
to Costa Rica?
I was flown down once.
They found a human skull...
12,000 years old
Why?
I'm finally getting some vacation time.
I was gonna head off on Thursday.
Heard Costa Rica was beautiful.
Yes. Fascinating wildlife,
lots of parrots.
Oh, I don't like parrots. No.
People should really, really do all the
talking, you know. Maybe I should...
Oh God! What are
you doing?
The Aztecs would flay people and then
wear their skin as a bodysuit.
I guess you won't be needing
mittens for Christmas.
Did the FBI find a match?
Yup. His name
is Roy Taylor.
Roy Taylor?
You're kidding.
It's DJ Mount!
I don't know
who that is.
Mount is one of the best DJs in DC.
He used to play at the club.
Everyone was wondering
what happened to him.
His album is really going
to take off after this.
Never knew this side
of you, Bones.
It's DJ Mount.
You're hung over. Does this make
your head explode?
I grabbed a couple hours sleep
on my couch
and showered in the lab's
decontamination room.
You really know how to live.
JmsJay, Tupac, Biggie...
Do you even know who
you're talking about?
Yeah, I've done my Googling.
Listen...
you can hear the alpha
male asserting himself.
eah, fill your ass
up... with lead?!
Always a nice lyric.
I'm heading back to the club
to meet the FBI forensics team.
I'm getting facts.
DJ Mount
was starting to break,
finally making some money.
Someone who's never had anything,
that can go to your head.
So, he gets involved
with drugs.
You didn't know who he was hanging with
or who might have been chasing him?
Dude like Mount,
he had a lot of enemies--
other artists, rivalries.
Everyone wants to be number one.
I mean, you have to know
who the rivals are, Mr. Hall. q
It affects your bottom line.
Wait for me by the elevator.
Rulz.
What rules?
That's his name. He performs at the club.
I'm trying to keep my crew
together, Agent Booth,
but I always had to run
interference between those two
Why?
Ask Rulz.
Was it fun coming to the club?
Yeah, before the drugs and the
dead body. Tilt... tilt down.
It seems so primitive, being in a
crowd of strangers, gyrating to music.
You never dance.
I've been told I look like a marionette
in a wind storm.
You would've fit
right in last night.
Really?
Footprints. In the dirt
and the termite shavings.
Someone was on the
other side of him.
Light.
This leads to the outside.
- We need to get inside that wall.
- Or take it down.
One last look?
Take them in, show them around.
- Agent Booth?
- Yeah.
Roy Taylor압 father.
Maybe you know him as DJ Mount.
- Mr. Taylor, please come in.
- Thank you for seeing me.
Please sit.
You're the one looking
into my son's murder?
Investigating his death,
yes, sir.
I'm sorry for your loss.
I have some information
you need.
- About your son's death?
- No, sir.
About his life.
I've been readingin the newspaper. how my son was
a part of the meth scene.
Now  he was killed by drugs,
behind the wall right there.
What my son did...
was graduate third
in his class from high school.
He would have graduated first...except he...
he worked
a full-time job.
Track-and-eld medals.
Baseball.
Roy never drank, and he never did drugs.
Do you understand me, sir?
Mr. Taylor...
How they are portraying my boy
in the newspapers is wrong.
If his mother was alive
it would kill her.
I taught him a relationship with Jesus.
Do you understand, sir?
A personal relationship
with Jesus.
With all due respect, sir, sometimes when kids
grow up they change.
They move away from
what they were taught.
Five years old,
he made this.
And a lady who...
who reads palms
she looked at it and she said...
she said my boy
was going to be a great man.
A good man.
He read no evil
inhat boy'hand.
I can see that now, sir.
Some iniquity killed my boy.
You know that word, Agent Booth?
It's from the Bible.
"Deliver me...
from
the workers of iniquity...
and save me from bloody men."
You know your salms.
I can trust that you will find
out what happened to my boy?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Then I'm glad
I came by.
Can we conform to as much
forensic protocol as possible?
We're better at this
than you think.
You know what those are?
Rats.
intensive scare of rats
eat the laces
right out of our boots.
Take it easy there, Willard.
Here are the footprints.
There are marks on the wall.
It's scraped.
Bloosmear... dried.
I see something. Can I retrieve?
Yes.
Apparently, there's
a rivalry between Mount
and this guy Rulz.
We saw him perform at the club
last night. Did you talk to him?
Oh, no. I don't have
enough yet.
I go in too soon,
he could run.
Wow, that's a beautiful piece.
Zirconium or diamond?
I'm more focused on the dried blood
and flesh at the moment.
You buy Tessa jewelry?
I... I really don't want
to talk about that right now.
Too much of a commitment? I just thought
because, you two were going away.
Do you have anything yet?
Given the rate of air convection, and the
degree of dehydration of the flesh,
I'd say they were there
at the same time.
Must hurt like hell to get that thing
ripped out of your belly button.
- I thought it was an earring.
- Look at the size of the stud.
I had one  of these. Before they
became totally Miami-divorcee.
Good news. I was able
to pull some particulates.
Are those, uh...?
Eyeballs? Yeah. Two types of
foreign material in the eyes--
low-density polyethylene residue
and methamphetamine crystals.
Polyethylene?
Came from the plastic bag
holding the meth.
This can be cleaned now.
Yeah! That's a real diamond.
Why don't you get her
a belly button ring?
That's not too much
of a commitment.
Yeah, that's great.
The inside of the lips was damaged by the teeth.
This was not an accidental inhalation.
The meth was pushed against his face
with force.
Someone was
to smother him.
Which would explain how the
particulates got into the eye.
So he didn't OD.
He was murdered.
So we just have to find out
who owns this belly button ring.
Look at this.
"Luv Rulz."
At least we know who to ask.
Hello.
Yeah, it's open.
Yeah, it's open. FBI.
Special Agent Booth
Is the FBI recruiting
from America's Top Model now?
I'm a forensic anthropologist
at the Jeffersonian.
She works for the FBI.
Yeah, I can live with that.
Dr. Brennan also discovered
that Roy Taylor was murdered.
So?
So, murder is wacked. See, 'cause those
are the rules... Rulz.
Maybe he had it
come to me.
Oh, so you and Roy Taylor
don't get along.
That sucker ran me down, man. Tried to slam me
on one of his tracks, and ain't nobody do that.
And, uh... what happens
when they do?
I take a piece of them.
I got in his face one night at the Bassment.
told to disappear, and I ain't seen him since.
'Cause he knew
to follow the Rulz.
And, uh, maybe your girlfriend made sure
that your...your problem just went away.
That ain't my woman no more. I kicked
her sorry ass a months ago.
What is her sorry ass name?
Eve Warren.
What was she doing
with Mount?
Take a guess. I guess it was just
his turn.
She kept your ring?
It's a diamond, man.
Why she gonna get rid of that?
Any idea where she is now?
Probably ripping somebody
else off.
That girl don't care about nobody but herself.
Even though she got a kid,
don't care about
her neither.
Let her brother shoulder that.
Bitch.
What happened to your hand?
I got shot through the wrist
a few years ago.
Shattered the lower radius
and the pisiform.
Yeah. I got some nerve damage, too.
That's impressive
Yeah! I got shot in the back and through
the leg, too. You want to see the scars?
Thanks anyway.
Let us know if you hear
from Eve Warren.
That's all I got for y'all.
I'm gonna get back to work.
Let us know
if you hear from her.
Bones?
I like this music.
Okay, how about this: DJ Mount trusted Eve
because they were sleeping together.
So she meets him in the wall,
takes the drugs,
kill him for Rulz then he takes off.
You should write fiction.
What? It's reasonable.
It압 not based on evidences
It's conjecture.
Look, I'm positing a scenario.
We've been through this before.
Yeah, and it always seems to be a waste
of time. Now, finding a marker on a bone...
ow. You know, I think I need a vacation.
I think you do, too.
I'm not the one who's snippy.
Snippy? What are you, 70?
See what I mean? I think you should find
a nice, relaxing place to go on that vacation.
Somewhere where you can get a
massage, maybe do some yoga.
I don't do yoga. Okay, push-ups, sit-ups,
pull-ups, that's what I do.
That's more cardiovascular.
Yoga deals more with...
Why exactly are
we talking aut this?
Because you're tense.
Because we're talking.
You switched my music.
- Roy Taylor?
- Yes.
Anything pop out at you
now that the bones are clean?
There's some damage to the facet joint and
foramen on C-4 on the right side of the neck.
That suggests his head
was forced that way.
One other thing. I was looking the
skull through the microscope
came across a slight depression.
Barely discernible.
Slight indentation?
Could be congenital or a bone anomaly.
Probably.
Do you ever go on vacation?
I take my vacation
when you take your vacation.
What do you do?
Go back home to Michigan.
See the family.
I have three brothers
and four sisters.
Do you enjoy that?
God, no.
I made the mistake of telling them. I work with
corpses and skeletons. They think I'm a freak.
Then why do you go?
It's my family.
They love me.
Take a closer look he anomaly under the scanning
microscope. See what made that mark.
Work it out, work it out.
That's right. Good, good, good.
Yeah, let's work,
let's work.
What do you want?
Special Agent Booth, FBI.
This is my associate
Dr. Brennan.
- What you call this?
- The Krump.
The kids-- they come her they dance.
They don't gangbang.
So what do you want?
You didn't come here
for a dance lesson.
Hi, Maya. How
you doing, baby?
Come on now. We're going to go outside
and gonna play with the rest of the kids, okay?
There you go.
We'd like to ask you a few questions
about your sister Eve.
What's she done now?
When was the last
time you saw her?
About six weeks ago
when she dropped off Maya.
Just dropped her off
and left?
Told me she needed me to watch her
for a couple days. Left me some money.
Did you, um, happen to have a, I don't know,
recent photo that we could take?
Evie said she had
cleaned herself out
She was turning her life around,
and I believed her.
And she never
came back.
So that little girl out there,
that's her daughter.
She's like a daughter
to me, too.
Didn앖 it bother you that Eve never came back?
I mean, didn't you go look for her?
I learned to let her go.
And Eve, she's had a lot of problems.
Drugs, hanging out with the wrong people.
I mean, if I track her down and
she takes Maya before she's ready...
I'm not letting nothin' happen
to that little girl.
Do you know
Roy Taylor?
Met him. DJ Mount.I like his stuff.
He's pure. Play it for the kids.
We have reason to believe that she
was with him the night was murdered.
Murdered?
You can't find Evie?
No.
She told me she loved him.
And ... she and Mount were gonna
take Maya away out of DC...
give her a better life,
one we never had.
She said she left you some cash.
Yeah.
For Maya.
I'll buy what you have,
two dollars to one.
Sure, man...
You may want the stooges the FBI...who
are experts, due to your so-called "drug war"--
to run a comparison, but I'd say
the methamphetamine on these bills
matches the meth found
with DJ Mount behind the wall.
And my guess is that Eve was with Mount
at the time that he was murdered.
How about this, huh?
DJ Mount rejects Eve because
of her questionable past.
So, uh, hey, she gets mad, she wants
to leave with some money, so, uh...
What?
Yeah, I don't really think much
about that kind of stuff.
I'm more about bugs
and minerals. Sorry.
Oh, come on, Hodgins, hey,
you're a smart guy, you're a smart guy.
Look up from your microscope, huh?
These are real people
we're trying to figure out here.
Maybe she was just using Mount, setting him up
to get his drugs and money.
Very nice, Hodgins.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Real question is,
where does she go next?
You're on fire, man.
After she left her brother's place, because
that is where she met her untimely end.
You know what? I'm gonna turn
you into an investigator yet.
No, no, no, no. Bugs and slimede,
that is where I'm happy.
The damage to his C-4 vertebra was the result
of his head being twisted so far to the right.
He was moving this way, toward Eve.
My bet is he was chasing her.
And that's based on...?
Money and meth.
She left that corridor carrying money
saturated in the same meth that killed Mount.
She was moving fast.
She didn't even stop when
her belly ring got ripped out.
Hey, money's a pretty good
reason to get chased, hm?
Only question is,
why wasn't he facing her?
It got thigh back there.
15 centimeters.
Eve ripped out
her belly button ring here,
and then left a smear of blood
until the corridor widened. Here.
What?
That just...makes me a little sick.
You pick dead bodies out of mass graves, and
yanking out a belly button ring makes you sick?
Okay, okay, moving on. All right, I've shot
a lot of people on my time
and I got to admit, that whole belly
button thing makes me nauseous, too.
Thank you
At this point, Mount must have looked
behind him but kept going.
Then the passageway narrowed, so he
couldn't turn his head back toward Eve.
Then there's no way she could've shove
the meth into his face...
Eve didn't kill him.
A third person surprised them--
that's why he turned his head to look.
Mount's body prevented this third person
from getting to Eve, so she escaped.
But he got to Mount and shoved the meth
in his face and he killed him. Ah.
But the real question is, who the hell
is this third person?
Why the hell you pick me up, man?
I think you know why
I brought you in.
Yeah, right.
I waited for you to contact me, explain your
situation, but you didn't do that.
That's not polite.
What are you, DEA?
Metro cop?
I'm Special Agent Ronald Oakes.
One of us?
My orders were not to break
deep cover for anybody.
Out of deep regard for my FBI brother...
I gave you the nod.
That's bull.
I made you. Now you're making excuses.
Got any keys
for these cuffs?
Fine. Have it your way.
You know I need more than aod, man.
I'm conducting a murder investigation.
Now, I need to know
what you know.
Been 15 months
on the task force
investigating the links between
the urban music business and gang activity.
So that's why you got next
to Randall Hall.
"Randall Hall" is a clean alias.
You ran him, right?
Yeah.
Came back clean?
Exactly. His real name
is Terence Baskin.
Now, we know... that he's
pushing meth through the club.
But we can't get enough to touch him.
Our informants disappeared.
They either get bought off
or they get killed.
What about this murder?
The night that DJ Mount disappeared, Hall got
ripped of for a mountain of meth and a ton of cash.
DJ Mount ripped of all?
Nah, doesn't scan. Mount was into
Jesus, not chalk.
Hall killed DJ Mount.
Hall has people do that
type of stuff for him.
So listen, anybody asks...
why'd you have me arrested?
Weapons beef.
- So I don't get my gun back.
- No. No.
We meet up again...
if you get an excuse, hit me.
Oh... count on it.
I've been investigated for years. Why do
you think they never got me on anything?
'Cause you're so smart?
Because Terence Baskin
is my past.
I am 100% clean now.
This is my life now.
This and my recorrd label.
Not crystal meth,
not gang-banging.
Yet much of the iconic
quality of urban music lies
in the perceived or actual rivalry
between the principal artists.
Where did you find her?
Museum.
Was the rivalry between Mount
and Mr. Rulz strong enough to...
lead to murder?
Sure, they were
both capable.
Add in the fact that Mount was
sleeping with Rulz' girlfriend Eve.
Yeah, in fact...
Yeah?
Rulz built himself a studio
around that time.
Poured cement for the pad
a day after they disappeared
So...?
I'm saying, Mount's dead,
Eve's gone missing.
You might want to consider that.
Let's go.
What do you think?
Oh, I think, uh, I think we need to find a way
to find a body buried under a slab of cement.
Well, can't you
get a warrant?
To look around the premises,
maybe, but no way to tear it up.
Well, let me make
a phone call.
Tutti's traveled the world
finding dead bodies.
Does Tutti always drool like that?
What, I'm gonna hurt
her... his feelings?
Tutti is the best cadaver dog
in the world, Agent Booth.
It's true. If you were a dead body,
you'd want Tutti looking for you.
How can it smell anything
buried under a building?
he can
Once, I saw Tutti find a dead body wraped
in plastic, under concrete, after four years.
Tutti can smell decaying blood on a tooth six
feet underground.
I mean, so what?
He drools a little.
What's up with that?
You know, your eyes are kind of
close together, but I don't comment.
I apologize.
Is he sincere?
Yeah.
All right, then,
we accept.
Good boy, Tutti.
Tutti found something.
Oh, maybe he's just lazy.
Lying down is his indicator.
Tutti found it. There's a body
under here.
You should get a warrant to bring
a jackhammer for this floor.
I'd start digging here.
Dental records confirm
that this is Eve Warren.
Insect activity confirms she died
around the same time DJ Mount did.
Where did Booth go?
I got to give him the news.
- His girlfriend brought him a change of shirt.
- They're up in the lounge.
Zack, clean the bones.
We've already got cause of death
and identity-- what am I looking for?
It might be grasping but that odd
mark we found on Mount's skull,
see if you can find anything
like it on Eve's remains.
Jamaica?
God, that's incredible.
Mm, it's a bed-and-breakfast.
There are these coral cliffs.
Snorkeling, kayaking...
you two are so ready for the
pre-shacking-up test vacation.
What do you mean?
You have keys
to each other's places.
You've done the weekend away
a couple times.
Yeah, it's time for the ten-day vacation.
You know, Jamaica's like a dry run for living
together, only with rum punch and steel drums.
Yeah, see you later.
Living together?
Silly.
Thanks, you know, for
bringing me a shirt.
Yeah, okay.
I'll talk to you later.
Yeah.
- Hi, Tessa.
- Yeah, okay, bye.
- It's Eve Warren.
- Eve Warren.
- Uh, cause of death?
- Same as Mount.
- Meth overdose.
- Pushed in the face, but there's more.
I don't think that
Rulz killed her.
- She was buried under his studio.
- But her wrist was broken.
Bone damage indicates
that was taken from behind
and smash into wall
Her skull shows damage to both the infraorbital
and supraorbital margins and the zygomatic process.
Zygo-zu...? You said
she was killed by crystal meth.
She was. She would've been hurt and stunned by the
blow but not killed, certainly not immediately.
A bag of crystal meth
was placed over her face
actually ground into wounds,
into the airway.
Rulz couldn't have smashed her
into a wall?
Her radius was separated
from the scaphoid and trapezium.
Her right wrist was twisted hard
behind her back.
There's damage to both the elbow
and the shoulder, as well.
For that to happen, Eve's attacker would've had
to twist her arm up with his right hand
while jamming the crystal meth
into her face with the other.
Both with a great deal of force.
Rulz had been shot twice in the right hand.
I got it. He had nerve damage.
There압 no way he had the
strength to kill Eve Warren
You did not murder
Eve Warren.
This is a weird kind
of interrogation, huh?
Cops telling me
what I didn't do.
Well, then, do me a favor:tell me Bones
is wrong and confess to a murder.
Hell, no, man. What you think,
I'm some type of idiot?
Well, do me a favor,
deny it.
See, you got tricks. You gonna
twist all my words around.
Better not say anything at all.
You didn't kill Eve Warren.
So you say. The Rulz says
say nothing.
- He wants us  hold him.
- Why?
Why? Because every time some raper gets murdered,
his business goes straight through the roof.
Why should DJ Mount get the bump, huh?
Maybe it's my turn.
I'll tell you what. I'll make you
a better deal.
You tell us what we need to know,
and I'll have those charges laid against you,
put you in the
Remand Center.
For how long?
Oh, that depends
on what you tell us.
Wait! Wait! You're negotiating
to put this guy in jail?
Sweeten the pot, I'll charge you
with Mount's death, too.
You hire one of those
moron lawyers,
and you'll be thrown in lock-up for what,
maybe a month.
Sweet.
Where am I...
in Backwards World?
What have you got?
Look, I can tell y'all.
But y'all have to figure out
the rest on your own.
We have to figure it out
just from motive?
Okay, look, Bones, this is, you know,
sort of my thing.
Man, Mount was going to jump.
You mean commit suicide?
Where did you find her?
The museum.
I mean labels. Jump labels.
You're saying that DJ Mount was going
to leave Bassment Records?
All he needed was the money to buy himself back.
That's why he got himself killed.
Now if Hall even finds out
that I told you all that much,
I'm going to end up
some dried-out mummy in a wall.
But what about Eve?
Eve couldn't kill nobody.
Sex 'em to death maybe,
but that's about it.
Oh, there's
one more thing...
the next day, Hall built me
a new studio.
Took it out of my money, too.
So, you gonna put me in jail?
EWell, you know, hey,
it's the least we can do, hmm?
Hey, how about this? Hall's got motive to kill
Mount. Why? Because he's jumping labels
and he's running away with some girl
who's stealing Mount's meth and money.
I'm starting to see how
this whole motive thing works.
Thank you.
It's still murky
psychological guesswork, though.
Dr. Brennan, I found a mark
on Eve Warren
here
on the manubrium.
Compare it to the mark
on Mount.
Okay, Eve tells Mount that
he wants to start a new life.
So she rips off the dope and the cash
thinking she can build a new future with it.
It's a story, Booth.You need to find
something real.
For what? I mean, it feels real
to me...I mean, Eve is a woman in love,
whs trying to escape a world
that's just crushing her.
Mount finds out how much trouble the woman
he's in love with is in,
so he gives up his own life to protect her
It's not enough.
They were hoping for a better life
and they both wind up dead.
Looks like a match.
Thanks.
Good job.
- What the hell is that?
- Not sure.
It's a bone dimple. But they both have it,
so it can't be genetic.
Something external caused it,
but I'm not sure what.
Randall Hall.
He's behind this.
Randall Hall... okay, he killed
these two people.
We know it; he did it.
We just can't touch him.
And there's no evidence linking
him to the drugs, the cash or either body.
Except f a couple
of damn bone dimples.
I'll keep looking at the remains...
maybe find the evidence we need.
I can't let it stand.
What?
You know what? I'm going to spread the pain.
Okay? That's my new motto.
Wait! I can help spread pain.
Wait!
We know you did it.
What?
Killed Mount in that wall so that he wouldn't
leave your label.
You killed Eve Warren.
Killed her and buried her
under Rulz's studio.
In the meantime,this i going to have
to remain an active crime scene.
That's harassment.
I'll sue.
Well, I'm going to harass you
every chance I get.
I'm not somebody
you want to mess with.
Did you just poke me?
Did he just poke me
with his little stick?
This is my place. I want to poke
someone, I do it.
All right, how easily
do you think I scare?
Hey, Booth?
Don't break the cane. Arrest him
and confiscate the cane as evidence.
I need the cane.
Arrest him for what? He's the guy
who pointed a gun at a federal agent.
Uttering threats or smelling bad
or anything. It's the cane we want.
Fine, here. Randal Hall
I am placing you under arrest...
for assault of a federal agent.
This will never
go to court.
Oh, let's go find out.
Oh, next time I take your
gun away from you, I'll shoot you.
Well then, I bette not
let you get my gun again.
Come on Let압 go!
Get this:
I called Tessa,
to tell her a cole of places
she should check out in Jamaica...
- she's not going.
-  What happened?
Well, she said something came up
at work, but I know the truth.
How many times do you want me
to poke Zack?
Just once, but
as hard as you can.
As hard as he can?
Why don't I hit him
as haras I can?
Because you have arms like noodles,
while I am vigorous and burly.
What truth?
That all you got, burly boy?
They got freaked out
by Stage Six.
What...
what is Stage Six?
One: Spend the Night;
Two: Spend the Weekend;
Three: Exchange Keys;
Four: Sexy Weekend Getaway;
Five: Extended Vacation;
inevitably folloby Six:
Move in Together.
I'm an anthropologist. I know the
stages of everything. You made those up.
I did not.
Yes, you did.
They got to Stage Five
and they balked.
Not Booth.
Booth did not balk.
Sweetie,
it's always the guy.
No, Booth is not
a balker.
Hey!  The mark on Mount,
the mark on Eve. They're the same.
He can't resist hitting them
with that stupid cane.
The end of the cane,
it's a fit for both marks.
Hall's the killer.
Send the cane, the photos, and the medium
to the FBI. Let them confirm the match.
What, and let them have
all the glory?
My chest hurts.
Yeah..
all the glory.
Here's what we know so far:
Evidce linking rap producer Randall Hall
with the death of rising hip-hop ar DJ Mount
led the charges being file today
by the Dtrict Attorney.
Information coming to us slowly at this point,
but as soon as details...
Getting yourself
in the mood?
Trying.
You know, this... really isn't going to be
the type of vacation I hoping for.
Oh?
Tessa's not going.
Something came up at work.
Too bad.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I like going
on vacations by myself.
Really?
Sure, nothing wrong
with being alone.
No, I mean,
you like to go on vacation?
Yeah, I go places
all the time.
You ever just, you know, sit on the beach?
Pretend there's no such thing as skeletons?
Is that in any way fun?
When was the last time
you got away?
Got away from what?
Ah, Bones, you know, 'cause
what usually happens to me...
I think
about not coming back.
Seriously?
Yeah, you know,
you go with someone,
you joke about not going back
to your real life..
the two of you laugh.
But when you're alone...
the world is full of possibilities.
See you next week.