Or asked me to stop by the archaeology section
and identify the skull as assyrian, hittite, or egyptian.
I'm in court today. I need my notes.
There's a photocopy in the file.
No, the last time I read from photocopies,
the defense lawyer told the jury I was winging it.
Ready? Chop-chop.
I can't find my original notes.
Photocopy in the file.
No, the last time the defense lawyer told the jury that...
It was a ploy, it failed; let's go.
I found glass, I found pollen. Which do you want first?...
Pollen.
Perhaps you could swing by archaeology on your way to your...
No, no swinging.
All right, her height makes no sense and her spine length is whacky.
Dr. Brennan?
Okay, calculate the height off the femur and assume the fire shrunk her spine.
I don't think you should talk so much about other cases on court day.
You might get confused.
One simple question: assyrian, hittite, or egyptian?
Dr. Brennan?... Five minutes!
Bones!
What's up?...
Buttercup, if you sign off on these tissue markers
Angela can finish the facial reconstruction.
Why did you say "buttercup"?
"What's up buttercup" is an amusing, rhyming linguistic meme.
This is the latest "Jane Doe" from limbo.
How about this for an amusing rhyming linguine: "see you later, alligator".
Please don't refer to bone storage as "limbo. "Five minutes.
There are thousands of human remains down there, waiting to be identified.
Limbo seems an appropriate name.
No sign of foul play.
If you have time for this, you have time for my hittite.
Tissue depth of the cheekbones
and along the jawline looks a little deep to me, but otherwise...
Out of limbo, back on earth, and on our way to court.
Thanks.
Oh, Temperance!
David! Hi.
What are you doing here?
She has to get to court, so...
Agent Booth, nice to see you again, especially when I'm not in custody.
Listen, I read your manuscript.
And couldn't wait to tell you how great it is.
Thank you. Really?
You read her manuscript?!
Her second novel. "Bone free".
It's kind of like "born free" except no lions.
Yuck on the title. Am I in it?
No...
Definitely.
We have to get to court.
I hope you have your original notes. Because last time...
Told you, Booth...
No! Bones! We don't have time.
All right, listen... uh... three minutes, I'll wait for you in the car.
So, are you two, uh...?...
Yeah, sort of.
Is that a problem?
Yeah.
You know, Bones is very literal, so, in the future,
no jokey advice on court day... Okay.
Is something wrong?
What's this?
Zack's Jane Doe.
He said that you okayed the tissue markers.
No, that can't be right. That can't possibly be right... you did it wrong.
It's a mistake, Angela.
All right, fine. Sweetie, I'll turn it off.
Zack, the artifact bag from your Jane Doe, do you have it?
Yes. I also have three...
three bags of soil samples from where the remains were buried.
Any of you see Bones? Okay, we're due in court, like...
Hello, now.
What?
This... totally freaked her out.
My theory? Caffeine intolerance.
Yeah, you're going to want to take dr. Brennan off the witness list today.
No, she can't make it into court.
Thanks.
All right, what's going on?
That... is Christine Brennan.
Good God.
You just found Bones' mother.
I have to miss court.
I know.
I remember this belt buckle.
I borrowed it without asking...
the first day of high school.
My father had it specially made for my mother because she loved dolphins.
Bones... I'm sorry.
I always knew that for my parents to disappear like that,
They... they had to be dead. I thought that...
When it was confirmed I'd feel relief. But...
It's still bad news.
You have the file, Zack?
Jane Doe, number 1-29-09-98.
Where was she found?
Bones, I...
What does it say?
In September of 1998,
a grave-digging crew at the sunset memory cemetery in Salisbury, Pennsylvania,
uncovered human remains in a completely advanced stage of decomposition.
Is it from a grave?
No, it appears somebody just dug a hole at the edge of the cemetery
and plopped the body in there.
Zack!...
Sorry.
The local coroner found no obvious evidence of foul play
and sent the remains, a few artifacts, and soil samples to the jeffersonian,
hoping we could identify her.
Technically, your mother's been at the jeffersonian as long as you have.
Zack!
Sorry, but they both got here in 1998.
Dr. Brennan, ms. Montenegro has volunteered to drive you home.
Temperance.
Go home.
It's after midnight.
Well, I was driving by, I saw the lights...
I thought you might like some wong foo's.
You saw my lights from the road?
That is correct.
All right.
After you gave me your parents' missing persons file,
I- I did some poking around.
You worked on it?
Well, there wasn't much I could do.
There was no evidence, no clear jurisdiction.
Listen, Bones...
finding your mother's remains means I can open an official FBI case.
I mean, for the first time, a real investigation can occur.
Three days after my parents disappeared, they found
our car at a rest stop, a thousand miles from where we lived in Chicago.
Yeah, I found it in a federal impound lot in Jersey.
I'm having it trucked to the jeffersonian.
They kept it all those years?
No... no, nobody claimed it.
Your father was a high school science teacher.
He had no trouble with anyone at work. Then...
your mother, that's a different matter.
She was a bookkeeper.
Mm, she was a witness for the prosecution...
twice... on evasion charges. That gives motive.
Then there's, uh... your brother.
Russ.
The brother who deserted me.
He's on parole.
He ran a chop shop, processing stolen cars for parts.
It figures.
He says that you blame him for your parents' disappearance.
You talked to Russ?
I called him.
Just asked him a few routine questions. He didn't give me much.
We're going to find out what happened to your mom... okay?
Adipocere and decomp residues in the bagged soil
indicate the body was buried at least five years.
That's congruent with the pH in the soil, climate, and degree of decomp.
No, seven years. It should be seven years.
I'm still going through the soil samples,
but something in there might allow me to be more specific.
She was buried near christmas,1991.
I need the room, guys.
The whole lab? For what?
It's a cop way of saying "get lost".
What?
When you first gave me the file on your parents,
I looked back into their lives three to four years before they disappeared.
Jobs, friends...
I looked back a little further and I found out that...
Christine Brennan didn't exist before 1978.
What are you telling me? That...
that this woman isn't my mother? I was born in 1976... obviously,
my mother existed.
Do you know the most common way of creating an identity?
Getting the birth certificate of
someone deceased who was born the same year you were,
and take over that identity.
I found a one Matthew Brennan, born and died, 1948.
Do you understand?
I don't know what it means. I don't know what any of it means.
It means that your parents weren't
who you thought they were.
It means that they were living under assumed identities.
Every minute this is down, I'm losing money.
You want faster work, grab yourself a coffee.
Let me alone, man.
You licensed for this job?
You're a cop.
You know who recognizes cops?
Other cops?...
And crooks.
I talked to you a couple months ago on the phone...
I'm Booth.
You gonna ask me some more questions about my childhood...?
You found my mother?
Your sister did the ID.
What about dad?
No.
What do you want?
You remember being anyone else besides, uh,
"Russ Brennan?"...
No.
You wouldn't lie to me now, would you, Russ?
Cops always think I'm lying.
Why don't you just come back to DC, and help out in this investigation?
I got a job, man.
Well, the alternative is, I just cite you for performing
unlicensed repairs on heavy equipment...
get your parole revoked. Tell you what.
You give me a call when you get into town.
Oh, you ask me, this...
this thing here is beyond hope.
Look at that. It works.
I'll see you soon.
What is it?
A clump of cellulose.
It came from the soil samples collected at Brennan's mom's burial site
from the same depth as her bones.
You said you had a giant problem.
I used the laser scanning confocal microscope.
Which one is that?
It looks like an espresso machine.
Now, it showed that this is mass-produced cardboard.
Now, electn dispersion spectroscopy indicates
that the cardboard is coated with ethylenically unsaturated monomers,
which kept it from completely deteriorating.
Hodgins, what's the giant problem?
It's a movie ticket.
A little UV analysis, some guesswork, I come up with "The Fugitive".
So what's wrong, you don't like Brennan's mom's taste in movies?
The fugitive was the third top-grossing movie of 1993.
Brennan's parents disappeared in December of 1991.
Yet mom's going to Harrison Ford movies almost two years later.
Oh, God, this is giant.
What do I do? Pretend I never found this?
Dr. Brennan?
Yes. Um...
Did you find something in the soil?
Yeah, uh, this was in the soil samples alongside your mother's remains.
A movie ticket?
Rialto theater. 9:00 P.M. Showing of the fugitive.
September 22, 1993.
Well, how did it get there?
Either your mother had it in her possession when she was buried, or
it was somehow buried with her.
Either way, it dates the burial.
No, that's... that's impossible.
My mother disappeared in 1991...
Sweetie...
It's possible mom was buried somewhere else for a year and half, then moved.
No, that- that's not possible.
Maybe it is...
We decided to tell you the truth,
and this is the truth.
You all right?
I'm pretty sure I just found cause of death. Zack?
Yes, dr. Brennan?
See the discoloration on the inside of the skull?
Left side... extending from the coronal suture,
crossing the supior and inferior temporal lines to the squamosal suture.
Subdural hematoma. Ooh! A big one.
Dr. Brennan?
Probably fatal.
There are no indications of a blow to the outer skull.
Scan the outside of the skull. Look for histological changes,
microscopic modeling.
I don't want to talk to him.
Bones. Bones. All right.
Listen, Zack, if this guy moves,
shoot him with a tranquilizer dart or something.
I don't actually have a tranquilizer gun.
Hey, Bones... come on.
My mother died of a subdural hematoma.
Bleeding in the brain.
Do you want to proceed rationally, correct?
Chances are the subdural hematoma was caused
by a blow to the head.
All right, you got the how. Now, let's...
let's get the who.
You just told me that your mother was murdered.
I mean, who better to help us than... than your brother?
Mom loved dolphins.
This was mine.
My favorite marble.
What was she doing with that?
Where did Booth find you?
It's not hard for an FBI agent to find a parolee.
I didn't ask how, I asked where.
Morehead City, North Carolina.
I call, every year, on your birthday.
You never pick up.
Take a hint.
Could I have this, please?
It's evidence.
Of what? It's a kid's marble.
It's the rules. I can't let you have it.
Same old Tempe.
Never met a rule worth breaking.
Same old Russ. On parole.
Angela, I might send Russ in to describe some people to you.
Okay. What people?
Well, some people that a seven-year-old boy might remember.
Well, that's a little vague there, Booth.
The drawing... I mean, that's important. It's more...
I trust your instincts.
When it comes to men?
When it comes to suspects.
Why do you think that
Bones asked her boyfriend,
you know, to, uh, read her book and not me?
You know, maybe- maybe because there was just
too much of me in the story.
Oh, she was embarrassed, you think, may- maybe...?
Booth.
Yeah. I'm on my way. Thanks.
Uh, the family car just arrived.
We on the lookout for anything in particular?
Treat it like a brand-new crime scene... full workup. Let's go!
But tear through the whole car, treat it, and then go through it with a fine-tooth comb.
That's our old car, all right.
The name of my school is scraped off... Woodside elementary.
They said they didn't find anything in the car.
There was a bloodstain, front seat, passenger side.
Guys! Everybody!
I need the space! Now!
What? Now?!
Yeah, now.
Take five, everybody.
Twice in two days.
I had the NCIC database check for a married couple who disappeared in 1978.
Meet Max and Ruth Keenan.
That's mom and dad, all right.
The NCIC database, that's...
that's criminals.
My parents were on a list of federal offenders?
How do you like that?
Guess a criminal nature runs in the family.
You were seven years old, Russ.
Old enough to remember. What...
what is your real name?
What is my real name?
Bones, it's right here in the file.
No! No! I want him to tell me.
What is my real name, Russ?
My name was Kyle.
Your name was Joy.
You are not my brother.
Bones...
He lied about that. What else are you lying about?
What else are you not telling us?
At first, I thought the worst thing was that they were... missing.
Except dead means no more hope.
My mother was alive for almost two years after they disappeared.
She abandoned me.
You don't know that.
Look, you finally got to slap Russ.
You've been wanting to do that for years.
I worshipped him, you know?
God, he was so cool.
Everyone knew I was Russ Brennan's little sister.
I wasn't... cool or pretty, so, being his sister...
You know that game, Marco Polo?
I'd be sitting in class,
and I'd hear out the window,"Marco!"
It'd be Russ checking in on me,
letting everyone know that I was his little sister.
Did you... "Polo"?
Yeah, sometimes it would be the only word I said all day.
Polo.
And then mom and dad disappeared, and...
Russ took off.
Suddenly, no one cared where I was.
I miss that.
Someone caring where I am all the time.
Bones? Bones, you up there?
Come on, let's go, huh? Chop-chop.
I found the agent that was assigned to your parents' case.
I was the FBI liaison on
a bank robbery task force working out of Cincinnati in the mid- to late-seventies.
Secret service, state police, ATF, all of us after a pretty bad bunch
of armed robbers working Ohio, Kentucky, Iowa.
You know, excuse me.
Am I to understand that I'm addressing the family of one of these robbers?
Max and Ruth Keenan's children.
Max and Ruth. Yeah.
They never really belonged in that crew.
Why?
They worked smart.
Specialized in safe deposit boxes. No guns.
They'd either con their way in, or
case out the place, break back in on the weekend.
Took their time. We never got a handle on the size of their scores.
Why?
Well, people keep jewelry and cash in safety deposit boxes.
And a lot of stuff they don't want to report stolen.
None of us understood why standup criminals like Max and Ruth
would join this midwest strong-arm crew.
Links to white supremacists, real dedication to firearms and violence.
Job in Dayton went really bad.
Two innocent bystanders were killed. One state trooper, seven wounded.
When was that?
July 4, 1978.
Never caught 'em?
Not us, no.
Few years later, one of them turned state's evidence for an FBI agent out of Louisville.
Sent the rest to jail.
My understanding is they're all dead.
Our parents were bank robbers
who morphed into a high school science teacher and a... bookkeeper?
Their particular brand of safety deposit break-ins stopped.
At the time, I figured the strong-arm crew killed them for their cut.
Agent Booth?
We found blood in the car.
We expected that.
Yeah, but here's the wrinkle:
We got blood from two separate individuals.
These two dna charts are from the blood in the car,
and these two are from dr. Brennan and her brother.
These three match. And this one does not.
These three people are related?
This is mom, me and Russ.
But this chart... a male, but it's definitely not your father.
Okay, so we'll just run it through CODIS
and the convicted offender index and see what pops up, all right?
So you describe someone to me,
and I draw them.
That's the drill.
Who do I describe?
I don't know yet.
Booth put us together,
so I could charm you into telling me the truth.
Trust me, I got no more truth.
You know, your sister is my best friend, so
when she says you can't be trusted, I trust her.
This is you being charming?
Does Tempe really hate me that much?
Russ... she loves you.
It'd be easier if she hated you.
Hate is a lot easier to deal with than love,
especially disappointed love.
You know what's ironic?
Tempe doesn't trust me because I kept a promise.
What promise?
Seven years old...
dad and me in the backyard. This was in Ohio.
My dad tells me,"you're not Kyle anymore.
"Forget about Kyle.
You're Russ. "
He says: "If you ever tell anyone...
the police, anyone... "you will be killing your mother and your sister.
"Swear," he says.
"You swear on your baby sister's life you won't tell. "
He makes me say my new name 100 times. Russ Brennan
He says it with me: Russ Brennan, Russ Brennan, Russ Brennan!
Around that time, when Kyle became Russ,
maybe you saw someone.
Maybe you saw someone who scared you.
Someone who scared you because you had instincts...
the instincts of a frightened kid.
Was there someone like that?
Yeah.
A man came to the house one day.
My dad said if I ever saw this guy again,
to grab my sister and hide.
Well, when you're ready,
you'll describe that man to me.
All right.
If you keep bringing chinese food in the middle of the night, we're both gonna get fat.
I know what you've been thinking.
I doubt it.
You've been thinking that your
family is made up of liars and criminals.
And that makes you feel lonely.
There's a story here we don't know yet.
Like what?
Bones, "don't know" means it's a mystery.
What were your parents like?
My parents, uh...
My dad, he, uh...
he drove thuds and phantoms in Vietnam.
Those are fighter jets.
After that, he was a barber in Philadelphia.
And my mom, she wrote jingles
for a local advertising agency.
So they didn't go out at night after you were asleep and rob banks?
Listen, Bones, you know,
parents, uh,
they have secret lives.
If they didn't, they wouldn't be parents.
It is a little late for chinese, isn't it?
Thanks for the meal. See you tomorrow.
Dr. Brennan, is it morning?
No, I couldn't sleep. Why are you still here?
We're all here. No one's leaving until we figure out what happened to your mother.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I'm failing.
I've gone over every millimeter of the skull and found no evidence of remodeling.
Which makes no sense, because
any wound that results in a subdural hematoma that big
should leave a mark on the living bone.
What if the subdural hematoma started out much smaller?
And grew over time?
Over the course of, say, a year.
That might explain the gap between the time
my mother sustained the injury and the time she was buried.
Then the blow itself might not have left a mark on the bone.
Show me the surface of the skull directly above the center of the hematoma.
100-times magnification.
Go to 500.
See here?
Microscopic fractures on the osteons.
And is that the result of bleeding into the interstitial spaces?
I can map the fractured osteons.
That might lead us to the weapon.
I'm awake.
Yeah, I can see that.
Caught a break on the DNA in the car.
You know who it is?
Not exactly. See, it's a closed file.
Whoever it is is in the witness protection.
I'll make a request, but they're pretty tight over there.
What if you had a face?
Who's that?
Somebody your father pointed out to Russ when he was seven.
Somebody he's still afraid of.
Hey, you know what? I'm gonna play hardball with witness protection.
If they don't cooperate, I'm gonna put his face in the paper.
Wouldn't you get in trouble for that?
We'll find out.
You know what? Sometimes, he is just... whew.
This is the pattern of fractured osteons.
It suggests a blow from the front that grazed the skull.
A bullet?
There would've been particulates left behind by a bullet,
especially fired from a short range.
I isolated the most fractured osteons,
and this pattern emerges.
Looks like the business end of a tire iron.
No, the size is wrong. It's too small.
The weapon was actually chasing the skull when it landed.
I believe that the victim was pulled away at the last second,
so that most of the force was lost,
leaving only the slightest impression.
Bones. I got what I need from witness protection. Let's go for a drive.
Everybody... thank you.
I... thank you.
Okay, Bones, just listen to me, okay?
This guy McVicar, he might be a pig farmer now, but
he used to be a mechanic, all right?
With ties to the strong-arm crew that your parents ran away from.
A mechanic, like Russ?
Not like Russ. Russ fixes things.
This guy, he used to kill people.
Can I help you folks?
Ye. Put your hands up.
Do it!
Booth!
Check him for a gun.
What's going on?
He's got a 45.
45. Check his ankle.
He's got a 38.
Thirty-eight. I'm always right.
I'm FBI. I know who you are.
Steve beers, pig farmer.
Vince McVicar, the pig farmer, huh?
You want to talk to Vince McVicar,
you do it through the federal marshals.
I do it through the federal marshals,
I'm gonna have to tell them about a pig farmer who carries two concealed weapons.
Three.
22 in the small of his back.
22. I'm always right.
No, you're not... Yes, I am.
Bones, will you put the gun down?
What do you want?
I'm Ruth Keenan's daughter.
Joy?
Joy Keenan?
Yeah... I can see that.
We found your blood in the car.
You hurt lots of people, Vince. You bashed in their heads.
They never proved that, or I wouldn't be in witness protection.
We know how it works, Vince.
You rat out your crew,
everybody loses interest in a few old murders.
My mother was hit on the head.
Ah, I know.
I was there.
32 stitches.
She fought back, huh?
Ruthie fought back, all right.
But not against me.
Then against whom?
Your father.
Why'd he attack you?
Think about it a second, all right?
You and my... my mother?
Me and Ruthie run off together.
Max caught us pulling into a motel outside of Champaign, Illinois.
We were nuts about each other, Ruthie and me. Crazy in love.
Let's just skip that part, okay?
Well, he hit Ruthie first.
With what?
Tire iron.
Hit my arm, caught me a roundhouse to the head.
Lights out, baby.
I came to. Ruthie and Max were gone.
Never saw neither of them again.
You ask me, Max killed Ruthie, and buried her somewhere and vanished.
Our plan, once we set up...
most likely in Florida... was to bring you down.
Your father is a hard man, Joy.
My name is Brennan.
I'm doctor...
I'm dr. Temperance Brennan.
I work at the jeffersonian institution;
I'm a forensic anthropologist; I..
specialize in identif...
...in identifying...
...in identifying people when nobody knows who they are.
My father was a science teacher, and my mother was a bookkeeper.
My brother... I have a brother.
I'm dr. Temperance Brennan.
I know who you are. Hey, I know.
It's all right. It's okay, I know. Shh, it's gonna to be all right.
No way dad killed mom. No way.
If he caught them together...
No way mom cheats on dad. No way.
A man like McVicar, he lies the way you guys take a drink of water.
He killed people and then he snitched to save his own ass.
You don't believe him?...
No. I don't believe him.
Give me one piece of evidence that doesn't back up his story.
Your school sticker on the back of your parents' car was scraped off.
What does that prove?
The only reason to do that would be to keep you guys hidden; to keep you guys safe.
From McVicar.
McVicar performed hits for the crew that your mom and dad ran out on.
What else?
Well, there's a story that tracks for me, but without evidence, it's...
it's just a story.
Tell us.
Your parents go out christmas shopping one day. They spot McVicar...
the hit man, all right? They lead him away from your home.
Scrape off the name of the school, so he can't trace it back to me and Russ.
He takes out your father.
And my mother gets away with a head wound.
She leaves the car a thousand miles away finds friends,
but she can never go back to see you guys
because the crew is still looking for her.
It's just a story.
Fits the evidence.
All right, you know what? The weapons that McVicar had on him,
they're a violation of his agreement with the witness protection program.
I'm going to take him into custody,
I'm going to get a warrant, I'm going to search his farm.
Search for what?
McVicar liked to bash in people's heads.
Maybe we'll get lucky and match the weapon he used on your mother.
It's unlikely.
In that case, we'll still ruin his day.
Tempe, that theory explains why mom never came back for you
during that year and a half before she died.
What's your excuse, Russ?
You're the one that left me.
You needed someone to blame, you chose me.
I was 15 years old!
I was 19!
My parents were gone. My sister hated my guts,
everyone's telling me that she'd be better off in foster care.
You didn't even ask me.
I tried, Temperance! You wouldn't talk to me!
You still wouldn't be talking to me if mom's bones hadn't showed up.
And I kept trying!
Every year... every year... on your birthday.
You're the one that gave up.
You turned your back on me and you made yourself a new family.
What's going on?
The FBI delivered all these tools and weapons from the pig farm guy.
We went through them to see if any of them match the mark on your mother's skull.
I got 20 hammers and a dozen hatchets...
The man loves his blunt instruments.
Seven tire irons,
none of them match the wound,
even allowing for shrinkage.
It was 15 years ago. Even if McVicar killed my mother,
what are the chances he hung on to the exact weapon?
Well, it's always like this with McVicar. All right? You know?
Some mook is found with his forehead bashed in,
the FBI goes in the basement, collects about 40 hammers...
and nothing matches.
Always the forehead?
Yeah, that's his signature kill, yeah.
Not that anyone could ever prove it.
You said guys like McVicar get comfortable with a way of killing.
Yeah.
Where did McVicar grow up?
He grew up a farm kid in Iowa. Why?
How do you slaughter a pig?
Why's he here?
He gets nervous, we know we're getting close.
Found this in the barn.
This is a spring-loaded captive-bolt stunner.
The animal is restrained,
this is pressed to the forehead...
What kind of person could use this on a human being?
What kind of person could use this on a pig?
It's the perfect dodge.
Blood, flesh...
it can all be explained.
I think I just became a vegetarian.
So what do you think?
Yeah.
Same shape as a tire iron...
but smaller.
This could be a match.
Before you decide anything, we should talk.
I'd call that nervous, wouldn't you?
There's no way to prove that that's
the exact weapon that killed your mother or anyone else.
You'd be surprised at what she can prove.
I need to speak to you alone.
Forget it.
Booth, it's all right.
It's all right.
You got two ways to look at this.
One is you score a private chat.
The second one is, you attack her, and I'll drill you through the forehead.
How could I possibly attack her?
I'll decide what is and isn't an attack, like, say, a hiccup.
Booth. Come on.
You killed my mother.
Gonna be hard to convince a jury.
I'm pretty persuasive.
I'll put you away.
Here's the thing, Joy.
Two people know what really happened that night:
Me and your father.
You killed him before you attacked my mother.
Then how did I get this scar on my head?
You got a choice, Joy.
You drop the bolt-stunner down the well,
and you'll know what happened.
You put me in front of a jury,
not only will you fail to convict, but
you'll never know the truth.
You can't live with that, Joy.
You can't live not knowing.
I found out what happened to my mother;
I will find out what happened to my father, too.
We're done.
You will never know what happened to your father.
Why are you letting me drive?
It's a reward.
For what?
Totally pissing off a hit man.
Can I read your book?
After it's come out.
Not before?
No.
Oh, but I let you drive.
Just let it go.
Where we going?
I'd like to make up for a little lost time.
I'm- I'm gonna go get a funnel cake. Okay?
I have something for you.
Thanks, Tempe.
Russ...
You were right.
You were only 19, but at the time...
I didn't understand what that meant.
Sometimes people need to...
explain things to me, I guess.
Then you have to let them talk to you.
If... you could maybe come back and stay a couple days longer?
Please?
At my place, I mean?
Marco.
Polo.
Anybody thirsty?
Is it too early for a beer?
Ah, I gotta go, you know? I'm picking up Parker for the weekend.
Yeah, I'll take one.
You have a boy?
Yeah...
Woman I'm seeing, she's got two daughters.
Nice.
Girls are nice.
To us.
Whoever the hell we are.
To what we're becoming.
New message recorded today, 3:00 P.M.
Temperance, you have to stop looking.
You have to stop looking for me right now.
This is bigger and worse than you know.
Please, sweetheart, stop now.
Who's that?
That was my father.