(Zedd)
Richard Cypher,
you are the true Seeker.
( heroic theme playing )
♪ Legend of the Seeker 2x17 ♪
Vengeance
Original Air Date on April 17, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
( wind gusting )
(Monk)
Your friendship and service
over these many years
have been a blessing to me,
Matthew.
I shall miss you.
My Lord, I fear the Keeper.
Your faith in the Creator
will protect you.
( gasping )
Farewell, old friend.
( melancholic theme playing )
My Lord, it won't be
safe here for long.
Matthew was loyal,
but not strong.
He will not withstand
the torments of the Underworld.
He will reveal our hiding place
to Darken Rahl.
We always knew that one day
we might be discovered.
And if that day is today...
let it be today.
(Rahl)
Welcome to the Underworld,
Matthew.
It's so wonderful to see you
again after all these years.
You always were
one of my father's
favorite servants.
So tell me,
where is the old man now?
You killed your father
years ago.
He must be here,
in the Underworld.
Yes, I did kill my father
years ago.
So imagine my surprise
when I myself arrived
in the Underworld
and discovered
that he was not here.
But then I remembered
that many of his retinue
fled the palace
shortly after I killed him.
I can only conclude that you
somehow revived my father
and then spirited him away.
I...
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Father once left me
in your charge. Do you remember?
It was the day
we found my pet kitten
dead in the gardens.
When you saw those maggots
squirming out of its eyes
you almost fainted.
( screams )
Now, where is my father?
( eerie theme playing )
( ominous theme playing )
Hello, Thaddicus.
What do you want?
What I want is what I believe
you want as well.
To bring death to the man
who murdered your father.
The man who murdered my father
was your father,
and you killed him years ago.
Somehow my father
cheated death,
just as he cheated everything
and everyone in life.
Now I have finally discovered
where he has hidden himself
all these years.
Unfortunately, as I am a spirit,
I myself cannot kill him again,
but I thought you might want to.
Even if I did want
to ram a dagger into
that bastard's heart,
why are you coming to me?
I'm not powerful enough to-to
kill someone like Panis Rahl.
No, but your brother is.
Well, why don't you go to him?
Because the great Zeddicus
will not listen to anything
that comes from me,
but maybe if he were
to hear it from family...
( dramatic theme playing )
(Richard)
This is the longest the compass
has ever pointed
in one direction.
Who would ever have dreamed
that the Seeker
could go 12 days
without stopping
to save helpless children
or distressed farm animals.
Perhaps it's a sign that we're
nearing the Stone of Tears.
(Cara)
And then what?
We use the Stone to close
the tear in the veil.
But how?
Hm.
My point exactly.
For three months
we've been going after
this mysterious Stone,
but none of us
has the slightest clue
what we're actually supposed
to do with it once we find it.
Richard has succeeded
at every task laid before him.
When the time comes,
I believe fate
will provide him
with the answer.
( bushes rustling )
( sighs )
Thaddicus.
Good to see you too, brother.
How did you find us?
Our old friend Sebastian
made me one of his maps.
Charged me for it too,
the scoundrel.
I need to speak with you.
Alone.
For 24 years no one's seen
hide nor hair of Panis Rahl
and now you know
precisely where he is?
Oh, of course, how could
an old fool like Thaddicus
know anything so important?
Uh, let me tell you, Zedd,
I'm a man of the world.
I travel, I trade,
I meet people, I hear things.
You've never been able
to deceive me, Thaddicus,
so don't try now.
How did you learn
about Panis?
Darken Rahl appeared to me.
( tense theme playing )
And you take that demon
at his word?
For all we know, he might
be trying to lure me away
from Richard
for some nefarious purpose.
I don't think so.
He wants Panis dead
as much as we do
and this might be our only
chance to avenge Father's death.
Even if you're right,
Richard may be close to finding
the Stone of Tears.
I can't leave his side.
Zedd, we swore an oath.
(Young Zedd)
Father?
Thaddicus?
( sobbing )
( melancholy theme playing )
Where have you been
all these months?
You were supposed to be here.
You could have protected him.
What happened?
He was murdered.
By Panis Rahl.
No.
No, that's impossible.
Are you calling me a liar?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Saw what exactly?
I came home to see you
and Father arguing.
You said it yourself.
I haven't been home.
If for once you'd listen to me
you'd understand!
You and Father were arguing.
I couldn't hear what
you were arguing about, I--
I didn't want to intrude.
And then suddenly
you drew a knife
and began stabbing Father.
What are you talking about?
I would never stab Father!
Then shut your mouth
and listen!
I should have tried to stop it.
I should have tried
to help Father.
I couldn't.
But then I saw it--
It wasn't you.
It was Panis Rahl.
Only he'd disguised
himself as you.
Father died...
thinking I killed him?
Zedd...
swear that no matter
what happens,
no mattew how far apart
life takes us,
we will never rest
until we drive this dagger
into Panis Rahl's heart.
We promised each other, Zedd.
Yes.
Yes, and we owe it to Father.
But Panis is too dangerous.
I'll go alone.
Please, Zedd.
While Father was being killed,
I just stood there
like a trembling lamb
and did nothing.
Don't make me do nothing now.
You're leaving? Why?
It's a family matter.
Zedd, I'm family.
If something's wrong,
I want to help.
Nothing's wrong that Thaddicus
and I can't manage on our own.
I'll catch up with you as soon
as we settle our business.
Business. What business?
It's nothing
to concern yourself with.
( dramatic theme playing )
( majestic theme playing )
(Thaddicus)
Sorry you had to leave Richard.
It isn't that.
Richard is well-protected
by Kahlan and Cara.
I was just thinking
that none of this
would be necessary
if only I'd listened
to Father.
( crying )
Darken Rahl,
future lord of D'Hara!
He has your eyes,
my lord.
Zedd.
You have been
such a loyal friend.
And you've already done
more for me
than any man has a right to ask,
but would you do me the great
service of teaching my son,
just as your father taught me?
I would be honored.
Now relax, my friend,
and enjoy yourself.
( ominous theme playing )
What are you doing here, Father?
The great Wizard,
Zeddicus Z'ul Zorander,
bought for the price
of a harlot.
I haven't been bought
by anybody.
Panis is my friend.
Oh, yes, Panis Rahl was a great
friend of mine as well,
until I refused
to teach him magic.
Then he set about finding
a new friend.
In your day, Father,
D'Hara was a land
of gentle farm folk.
Now it is darkened
by the smoke of war.
Magic is necessary
to protect all of us
and most especially our king.
So it's true.
You have taught Panis magic.
I'm only teaching him
to use the magic
that already runs
in his bloodline.
There is a reason why the magic
in the Rahl bloodline
has been dormant
since they assumed the throne.
Our ancestors
made sure of it.
Because no king
should ever possess
both earthly and magical powers.
Together they create
an unstoppable force
that can only produce tyranny.
Panis will not be able
to resist the temptation
to dominate everything
and everyone in this world.
But he trusts me.
I will be able
to teach him
to use his magic
wisely and justly.
Zeddicus, you know nothing
of this family,
or what it will become if you
continue to do their bidding.
So now you have the power
to see into the future?
Come home with me now,
Zeddicus.
Before it's too late.
My place is here, Father.
I'm not going anywhere.
( guests chattering )
Carracticus.
My old teacher.
I've missed you.
Oh, I know we've had
our differences in the past,
but on the occasion
of the birth of my son,
can't we put that aside and
share a drink like old friends?
You may have seduced my son
into believing your lies...
but I know
exactly what you are.
And I will do whatever it takes
to end the tyranny
of the House of Rahl.
(Zedd)
Father was right about
the future of the Rahl dynasty.
If I'd listened to him,
I would have been home
the night he was murdered.
I would have been
able to stop Panis.
You had important business
the night he died.
That's what I told you then...
but it wasn't true.
Bad news?
From my father.
What does he say?
He apologizes
for barging into the palace
and disrupting
your celebration.
Then he begs me to come home.
Says he wants to me peace.
The times have passed
your father by, Zeddicus.
He was once a great man,
but now he's just
holding you back.
Yes.
But he is still my father.
And he does love me.
If he wants to make peace,
maybe I should hear
what he has to say.
You're right.
A man should make peace
with his father.
Go to him.
Be with him.
And while you're there,
tell him I would also
like to make peace with him.
I'll return as soon as I can.
Have a safe journey.
I'll tell Princess Ariana
you can see her next time.
Princess Ariana is here?
Yes. That's what I was
coming to tell you.
Apparently, she grew quite
fond of you on her last visit.
As I did of her.
Doubly unfortunate, then,
that she's only here
for one night.
Perhaps she's worth
a short delay.
(Zedd)
My important business
was bedding a a young beauty.
I was so blinded
by lust for power,
as well as for Princess Ariana,
that I-- I didn't see
how Panis was deceiving me.
Well, brother,
you're finally going to get
a chance to pay him back.
( ominous theme playing )
(Richard)
Maybe we should
be looking for Zedd.
If Zedd doesn't want
to be found, we won't find him.
I just wish
he'd ask for our help.
Richard, whatever business
Zedd's attending to,
it's clearly private.
We have to respect that.
He'll catch up with us
when he's ready.
( wind gusting )
( magical theme playing )
( man grunting )
Help me! It's my life's work!
( grunting )
The Sword of Truth.
You're the Seeker.
Just the person
I've been looking for.
The Creator herself
must have brought us together.
Why is that?
So that I can--
I can join you on your quest.
I'm letting my enthusiasm
get the better of me.
Forgive me.
Horace Guildermayer,
scholar and antiquarian,
ready to fight and die
at your service.
(Cara)
As difficult as it will be
to succeed without you,
we'll have to find a way.
But thank you for your interest.
No, no, no. No, you-- You--
You don't understand.
After a lifetime of scholarship,
I have finally made a discovery
of vital importance.
Hidden inside
the Winding Wall of Valdaire
is an ancient scroll.
It instructs the bearer
of the Stone of Tears
how to use it
to seal the rift
to the Underworld.
Seeker, without my help,
you will never find the scroll,
your quest will fail,
and the world of the living
will come to an end.
( dramic theme playing )
Am I the only one who
finds it a little suspicious
that we were just
asking ourselves
what we should do
when we find the Stone,
and suddenly
a mysterious man shows up
saying he knows where
the instructions are?
Zedd did say,
when it was time,
fate would provide
Richard the answer.
Maybe this is how.
We appreciate your help,
but if you told us
where this wall is,
we could find the scroll
ourselves.
Well, I wish that were possible,
but it's not.
Long ago, the Order of Ulrich
was assigned to protect
the scroll.
One of the monks sealed it
inside the Winding Wall
for safekeeping.
He spelled the niche
so that it could only be opened
using a secret code.
But the key to the code
was lost,
seemingly forever.
Until now.
Using fragments
of the monk's papers,
I have painstakingly
created this lexicon.
And with this,
I have deciphered the code.
Well, then you can
teach it to me.
We haven't the time.
The Keeper's forces
grow stronger every day.
Seeker, I-I am aware of the fact
that I am now an old man,
and I do not wish
to burden you,
but you need this
and you need me.
(Thaddicus whispering ):
Let's go.
Calm down.
What do you mean,
"calm down"?
Panis is in there.
Yes, and he's guarded.
(Thaddicus)
They're just monks.
( clattering )
Armed monks who protected
the evil tyrant
all these years.
Stay close behind me.
( monks screaming )
( action theme playing )
Now, let's find Panis.
( grunts )
Did you think you could
hide forever, Panis?
( grunts )
That's for our Father.
It's not him.
What are you talking about?
He used the magic I taught him
to trick me again.
How are we going to find
Panis now?
We'll search
the monastery.
There must be some clue
as to where he was going.
(Rahl)
Let me save you
the trouble, Wizard.
After everything
you've done,
all the death and destruction
you've caused,
you think I'd listen
to a word you'd say?
For once our interests
are aligned,
yet all you can do
is dwell on the past?
Really, Zeddicus,
that's rather petty of you.
If our interests were aligned,
you wouldn't have led us here
to murder the wrong man.
Oh, I had no idea my father
was gone from this place.
As I am unable to walk
among the living,
I can only know what I am told
by the recently dead.
Fortunately, your vengeful
rampage has provided me
with a fresh supply of souls.
I've already tortured one
into telling me
where my father went.
We'll take no more
direction from you!
Then you won't want
to know that Panis
has disguised himself
as a kindly, old scholar,
and that he has gone
to find his other son,
my brother, your grandson.
( dramatic theme playing )
(Richard)
Did you ever doubt
that you would learn
the secret code to Valdaire?
No. No. My only doubt
was that I'd live
long enough to find you,
but when I last checked,
my heart was still beating.
( both chuckling )
How about you, Richard?
Do you ever have any doubts
about the success
of your own quest?
Sometimes.
You have already saved the world
from Darken Rahl.
And by doing that, I opened up
a rift to the Underworld.
And now things
are worse than before.
Richard.
You succeeded once.
You will succeed again.
I hope you're right.
Think of it this way.
How many men
get to save the world
with the woman they love
by their side twice?
Sounds like something
my father would say.
He must have been a wise man.
What about you, Horace?
Do you have a family?
Two sons.
Are they scholars too?
No, no.
No, they took
very different paths.
Do you get to see them often?
One of them is dead.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Oh, don't be.
He led a tragic life.
What about your other son?
He and I...
we're not close.
But I couldn't be
more proud of him.
Horace, wake up.
Oh. Oh, I've overslept.
I am so sorry.
I'm ready to go.
(Kahlan)
It's all right, Horace.
Have something to eat.
( horse whinnies )
( suspenseful theme playing )
It's Zedd.
( dramatic theme playing )
(Richard)
Zedd, what are you doing?!
Out of my way, Richard.
Cara, protect Horace.
( dramatic theme playing )
That's the man
who killed my father.
( dramatic theme playing )
Zedd, there must be a mistake.
This man is a scholar.
He's taking us to a place
where we can find out
what we're supposed to do
with the Stone of Tears.
He can disguise himself
however he wants.
There's no mistake.
He's Panis Rahl!
That can't be.
Zedd is telling the truth,
Richard.
I am a scholar,
but I am also Panis Rahl,
your father.
( dramatic theme swells )
Give me one reason
why I shouldn't
let Zedd kill you right now.
I know how this must appear,
but everything I have told you,
except for my name, is true.
Twenty-four years ago,
I renounced my former life.
I took the oaths
of the Order of Ulrich.
Since then,
I have led an austere life
of prayer and study.
I sought not only to uncover
the secrets of Valdaire,
but also to atone
for my many and terrible sins.
Don't listen to his lies,
Richard.
(Panis)
I am not lying.
If I had come to you
in the guise of a man
that the world only knows
the worst side of,
you'd never have
trusted me.
Forty years ago,
he charmed me into
teaching him the magic
he used to kill my father
and now he's
to trick you, Richard.
I did use the magic Zedd taught
me to kill his father.
And that was just a
terrible mistake.
I have been doing pepenance
for it ever since.
But at the time
I thought I had no choice.
Before you allow him to kill me,
and thus end all chances
of finding the scroll,
allow me tell you
what happened and why.
If you have something to say,
say it.
(Panis)
All those years ago,
there was was an awful set
that I kept from you, Zedd.
( crying )
Your son's illness
is not natural, My Lord.
The fever has been caused
by a terrible curse
cast from afar.
A curse?
Yes. And one that could only
have been sent by a Wizard.
Carracticus.
Send for Zeddicus.
He may be able to save your son.
No.
Let him die.
(Panis)
I let the disease
run its course
and the child soon expired.
But I had a Mord-Sith
revive him,
and my son was soon alive
and healthy again.
My father may have been
a difficult man,
but he was no baby-killer!
(Panis)
That's what I thought.
But who else could have done it?
I decided I would
ask him myself,
but knowing that he would
never tell me the truth,
I decided to disguise
myself as you.
Zeddicus.
Oh. I'm so glad
you've come.
Did you cast a curse upon
Panis Rahl's infant son?
Is he dead?
No. By luck, he survived.
How could you do
such a monstrous thing?
I'm sorry that I had to do it,
but I'm even sorrier
that I failed.
Have you lost your mind?
The great witch Shota
came to me with a prophecy
that Darken Rahl would grow up
to kill his own father
and become the most brutal
tyrant the world has ever known.
Now the baby's life
has been threatened.
Panis will spare no effort
to protect him.
Everything depends
on you now, Zeddicus.
You're the only one
who can get close enough.
You must go back
to the palace
and, horrible as it sounds,
you must kill Darken Rahl.
I'm not going to kill him.
I'm going to kill you!
( groaning )
Zedd...
( ominous theme playing )
(Panis)
I did what I had to do
to protect my family.
I knew you would come
looking for vengeance.
I sealed myself
in my palace with my son.
That's just a story you
made up to justify your crime.
The real reason
you killed my father
is because you feared him.
He was the only man
strong enough
to end the tyranny
of the House of Rahl.
Oh, Zedd,
if it had been about power
I would have found
some way to kill you.
But I didn't.
Why?
Because, old friend,
I loved you.
And I love you still.
Killing your father
was a terrible mistake.
He was right.
I should have killed my son.
If I had done so,
I would have spared the world
all the-the pain and the misery
and the evil that
he has brought into it.
Zedd, you know how hard it was
for me to become a father.
I could not sacrifice
my first-born son.
But I decided
I would correct my mistake
by siring a child
who would destroy Darken Rahl.
That child was you, Richard.
Now, I beg you, son,
please,
let me help you
find the scroll.
( suspenseful theme playing )
( ominous theme playing )
Lord Rahl.
Your Sisters slumber
so peacefully
while the Keeper wages war.
Say the word
and I'll rouse them.
The Mother Confessor
and the Seeker
are on their way
to the Winding Wall of Valdaire
in search of an ancient scroll.
You and your Sisters
are to get there
before they arrive.
Lie in wait,
but do not attack
until the Seeker
finds the scroll.
Once he has it,
I want you to steal it.
Why do you want this scroll?
It contains
secret instructions
for the bearer
of the Stone of Tears.
If the Seeker
has this scroll,
he will defeat the Keeper.
Then I will get the scroll
and destroy it.
No. Once you've
taken the scroll,
it is the Keeper's wish that
you protect it with your life.
When you've gotten it safely
away from the Seeker,
I will come and tell you
what to do with it next.
Oh. Yes, one more thing.
There is an aged scholar
traveling with the Seeker
I've sent the wizard Zorander
to kill him
but if for some reason
the Seeker prevents
the Wizard from killing
this old man,
I want you to make
sure that he dies.
My sisters and I
will leave no survivors.
Consider it a victory
if you manage to kill
the old man and get the scroll.
This is the right section.
( dramatic theme playing )
Now, the key is to read
every fourth symbol.
( reading ancient
language aloud )
( dramatic theme playing )
This scroll belongs
to you, my son.
I've done what I came to do.
I am ready now
to pay for the crime
of killing your father.
May the taking of my life
bring you some measure of peace.
( dramatic theme swells )
What are you doing? Zedd.
For decades, Panis and I
have been carrying
the same burden of remorse.
If either of us
had listened to Father,
none of this evil would
have ever come to pass.
Not the reign of Darken Rahl,
not the tearing of the veil.
It's time to end
the recriminations.
( women yelling in distance )
( all yelling )
( all grunting )
( action theme playing )
( Agiel whining )
Kill the old man.
( all grunting )
( action theme pying )
(Richard)
Kahlan! She has the scroll.
( dramatic theme playing )
( all grunting )
Kahlan!
( Richard grunting )
( dramatic theme playing )
( groans )
( dramatic theme swells )
Can you heal him?
I can't remove a Dacra.
It's all right, Zedd.
I have paid for my sins.
And I get to hold
my son's hand
one time before I die.
What more can
a man ask for?
You will find
the scroll again, you--
You will defeat the Keeper.
( groans )
I wish we had more time.
So do I.
But I want you to know, son.
You have been in my heart
from the moment I heard
the Prophecy of your coming.
Zedd, old friend,
I never thought you would
make your peace with me.
I am humbled by your generosity.
( Panis groaning )
It is time for me
to join my other son.
( dramatic theme playing )
( ominous theme playing )
Father.
Do your worst to me, son.
I am ready.
Rise.
I forgive you, Father.
Do you forgive me?
( ominous theme playing )
She took the scroll that way.
Home is in that direction.
I'm sorry I couldn't
go through with it.
I think Father would
have been proud of you.
Hm.
( melancholy theme playing )
( sighs )
Why didn't you ever tell me that
Panis Rahl killed your father?
Maybe because all of the evil
we've been fighting for so long
is my fault.
Because you wouldn't
listen to your father?
Because you let
Panis trick you?
It's time to let
go of that, Zedd.
Richard.
There's something else
I've never told you.
Or anyone.
The first lesson my father
ever taught me
was that a Wizard commits
his greatest crime
not when he attempts
to do the work of the Keeper.
The greatest sin of all
is when a Wizard attempts
to do the work of the Creator.
What's wrong, My Lord?
I have a problem.
Of personal nature.
Although the queen and I
have tried for years,
we have been unable to achieve
our greatest dream:
to produce an heir
to the throne of D'Hara.
As I have not fathered a child
with any of the concubines
that I have taken to my bed,
I know the failure
lies not with the queen
but with me.
If you help me with this,
Zeddicus,
I will raise you up.
I will make you
First Wizard of all D'Hara.
You will have
greater influence
than any Wizard
who has ever lived.
( suspenseful theme playing )
( speaking in ancient tongue )
( gasps )
You will beget a son.
I unleashed the greatest evil
the world has ever known.
Without me,
there'd be no Darken Rahl.
Zedd,
if you hadn't helped Panis,
I wouldn't have
been born either.
Still.
I can never forgive myself.
I know what it's like to doubt
yourself at every turn,
but I've realized that
if I stop and question
every decision I make
I'll never get anywhere.
All we can do is make
the best choices we can
and keep putting one foot
in front of the other.
( mellow theme swells )
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --