Richard Cypher,
you are the true Seeker.
♪ Legend of the Seeker 2x18 ♪
Walter
Original Air Date on April 24, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Lord Rahl.
Have you brought
what I asked for?
The Scroll of Valdaire.
Did the Seeker read it?
I took it from him
before he could break the seal.
Then he still has no idea
what to do
with the Stone of Tears
when he finds it.
And he never will.
No!
Do not destroy it.
It is the Keeper's will
that you take the scroll
to the Mord-Sith temple
at Jandralyn,
without breaking the seal.
They will deliver it into
my hands, and my hands only.
In the World of the Living, you
are nothing more than a spirit.
Into what hands
am I to deliver it?
If I were you, Marianna,
I would worry more
about making sure that
the Seeker does not kill you
and take the scroll
bere you reach Jandralyn.
Because I am quite certain
that my intrepid brother Richard
is already on your trail.
Her tracks lead that way,
but they're at least
a half a day old.
We have to pick up our pace.
Fortune has smiled upon us.
A Sister of the Dark
has escaped with the scroll,
she's hours ahead,
and you call that fortunate?
Can't you smell that?
Smell what? Pine trees?
Lamb, butter, a touch of fennel.
And there it is, on the wind,
the sound of distant laughter.
Leads me to conclude
we're fast approaching
a roadside tavern, and the balm
of all weary travelers.
We don't have time
to feed your belly.
None of us have eaten in days.
We'll all move a lot faster
once we're fortified,
and I'm certain
the good tavern keeper
will be more than happy to pack
up our victuals for the road.
Compliments of the house.
Oh, no, please,
let us pay you.
After all you and your friends
have done for the Midlands?
Let me express my gratitude
in what little way I can.
Thank you, sir.
May the Spirits watch over you.
To the Seeker!
Yes, to the Seeker.
May he burn brightly
in the fires of the Underworld.
I don't think
I heard you right, sir.
No, you heard me.
Damn the Seeker,
and all the fools who helped him
bring down Darken Rahl.
Darken Rahl
was a wicked tyrant.
Oh, I'll grant you that.
He'd conscript your sons,
violate your daughters,
lock you up
for looking at him funny.
But at least when he was around
we had order.
Nowadays, if the highwaymen
don't get you,
the banelings will.
May the Creator forgive me,
I miss the good old days.
To the good old days!
Well, there's at least one other
sensible man in this province.
I once came damnably close
to bringing back
those good old days.
To returning Darken Rahl to his
rightful place among the living.
Sounds like quite a story.
Oh, Oh, that it is, my friend.
And I'd be happy to tell it,
if, uh, ahem, my damn throat
weren't so dry.
Two tankards of your best,
barkeep.
You promised me a tale.
That I did.
But I assure you,
it is no tale, my friend.
It is the Creator's
honest truth.
It all started
in a flea-bitten backwater
by the name of Sheephaven,
back when Darken Rahl
was still in power.
One of the locals
had found a way
to profit from
the general hatred for Rahl.
Step right up,
ladies and gentleman.
Give the villain who is
the cause of all your suffering
the tribute he deserves!
Three tries
for a farthing.
Mm-hm.
D'Harans! Real ones!
Aah!
No! Please don't kill me!
I'm just some poor sod
trying to make a living,
I didn't mean any offense.
You're quite famous.
Do you know that?
Word of your unique talent
has reached the ears
of the true Lord Rahl.
He'd like to meet you
personally.
Think of it, Lord Rahl.
He could appear in your stead
at ceremonial obligations
that interfere with more
pressing affairs of state.
He could serve as a convincing
decoy to would-be assassins.
Hm.
Very impressive,
Captain Malray.
Thank you, Lord Rahl.
Very impressive indeed.
He is the very image of me.
Were I to have a belly
the size of West Granthia,
a nose trampled by a horse,
and hair the color
of mouse droppings.
Perhaps a year spent
breaking stones
in the quarries of Groth
will improve your powers
of perception.
As for him,
feed him to dogs, before my
enemies find use for him.
Lord Rahl--
We are finished here, captain.
Humbly,
respectfully, sir,
I brought this man here
not as the finished
work of art,
but as the raw clay
from which it would be sculpted.
If you would only let me show
you the wonders I can work,
you will not be disappointed.
What do you think, Egremont?
I !gree withou of course,
My Lord.
This rogue doesn't have
the slightest trace
of your natural radiance
or nobility.
But if he could be improved
upon, as Captain Malray claims,
he may be of some use.
One day, you may have the need
to convince an adversary
that you were dead.
He would at least make
a convincing enough corpse.
The man is the height
of a toadstool.
What do you intend to do,
put him on stilts?
Please!
I'm tall enough now.
I swear I am.
Thank the Spirits.
Hm.
Two finger-lengths more.
What?
Just close your eyes, Walter,
and imagine yourself
by the sea.
No.
And in time, we solved the
problem of Walter's stature
and colored that hideous hair.
But there was still a great
deal of work to be done.
Coming along. Hm?
Though I still don't see
a way around that nose.
Oh. It happened the first time
I was mistaken for Rahl.
This drunk took a swing at me
and knocked it out of joint.
When I'm entertaining,
I just shade it with
a little bit of charcoal
and the crowd
is none the wiser.
Well, that might fool
some provincial bumpkins.
But if you're going to be
of any use to Lord Rahl,
you will need to convince even
those who know him personally.
Oh, no,
I have seen wonders done
with a little plaster
of gypsum and honey
in the concealment
of unsightly features.
Mm.
There's no need for that.
Perfect.
"P-People of D'Hara,
"a-as we march proudly
into the dawn of a new era,
united by faith in our cause--"
Stop,
before my ears bleed.
If people hear that, they'll
know they're being deceived.
And if that happens, Lord Rahl
will order all of our heads
to grace the pikes
at the palace gates!
General.
Walter doesn't need to say
anything at all.
All he needs to do is stand
on the balcony, act the part,
and give the crowd
the renowned Lord Rahl wave.
Go on, Walter,
show the General how beautifully
you've mastered the wave.
Now if you really want to be
the one to interrupt
Lord Rahl's revelry to inform
him that he needs to come here
to lead those dreary devotions,
go right ahead.
Very well.
Make your appearance.
And may the Spirits
be with us all.
And in time, under my tutelage,
Walter eventually mastered
the accent as well.
We became great friends,
Walter and I.
And the gold we were paid
for our service,
well, that financed
many a debauch. Yes.
We'd come a long way
from the day I found him
on the filthy streets
of Sheephaven. Heh.
But alas, those good old days
were few in number.
And when the cursed Seeker
put an end to our patron, well,
the palace fell into ruin,
and was soon overrun
by an angry mob
hungry for loot and revenge.
Take that down.
Look! It's the tyrant,
Darken Rahl!
He's not dead after all!
Darken Rahl is dead.
And the Seeker killed him,
I'm just his double.
How do we know the one who died
wasn't a double,
and you're not the real
Darken Rahl?
Yeah!
Malray!
Bless you, old friend!
Get him!
And then the mob
swept him away.
And you never saw him again?
Oh, no, no, no.
I saw him again.
I've only told you
the beginning of the story.
Still ahead of us
lay the treasure, the blood,
the betrayals,
and most of all the women.
Well don't stop there, man.
Go on!
Ah, that, my friend, would
require another tankard of ale.
After the fall of Darken Rahl,
it was hard
for a D'Haran officer.
No more wages,
no more plunder.
No more pillage.
But I had a plan
to restore my fortunes.
But to do that required finding
my old friend Walter again.
How did you manage it?
Well, I knew he had a taste
for stout ale,
so I searched
all the taverns in D'Hara.
It seemed hopeless,
until one night,
I walked into the very
watering hole
where we are sitting
at this very moment.
Thought you could slip me
a lead farthing, did you?
No, I thought they
were copper, I swear to you.
I'm the one
who's been cheated here.
You rotten,
lying scoundrel!
The tyrant lives!
Walter.
Anyone who wants a taste of him
gets a taste of me too.
Go on.
Malray. Old friend.
It's good to see you again,
Walter.
This is the second time
you've saved my skin.
I just wish you could help me
wriggle out of it.
I wish I looked
like someone else.
Walter, it's how you look that's
going to be our salvation.
All you have to do
is convince a few Mord-Sith
that you're the true
Darken Rahl.
Mord-Sith?
Are you out of your mind?
The good sisters
at the temple of Jandralyn
are protecting
a hoard of treasure
stashed there by Darken Rahl.
Now, when their true lord
and master
orders them to return it,
we will have enough gold to last
us the rest of our lives.
Do you have any idea
what those women can do
to men with the--
The torture sticks
they carry?
They would never dream
of using those torture sticks
against their one true lord
and master.
Which I am not.
And we would have to get
close to them,
and then they would know.
Walter.
Just close your eyes
and imagine yourself
by the sea.
The last time you told me
to do that,
my shoulders were nearly
pulled from their sockets.
Yeah, but this time I mean it,
Walter.
We'll get the treasure, and
then we'll sail to Merilandria,
and we'll ljve
a life of ease
by the shimmering ocean,
strolling on
the golden sands,
a different woman every night.
I'd be happy with just one.
If she were the right girl.
Then we'll find you
the right girl.
But first,
we need the treasure.
What do you say?
Lord Rahl, it's true...
you are still alive.
Arise,
Sisters of the Agiel.
How may we serve you, My Lord?
I've come for my treasure.
At once, My Lord.
But first, Lord Rahl and I
would require a meal,
and a hot bath.
Lord Rahl is weary
from his travels,
and wishes to indulge
in those particular pleasures
which only the skills
of his Mord-Sith can provide.
Of course, Captain Malray.
Immediately.
Why are you standing there?
Are you as deaf
as you are stupid?
No, mistress.
I'll see to the bath at once.
And supper. Now.
Yes, mistress.
I don't think we should delay
our departure much longer,
Captain Malray.
After all, the future
of D'Hara is at stake.
Your devotion to duty is
admirable as always, Lord Rahl.
But I beg you for once
to think of yourself.
After the hardships
of the past months,
you deserve one night
of pleasure.
How dare a lowly slave
look directly into the eyes
of Lord Rahl.
Don't!
My Lord?
You will treat
the slave gently,
or you will feel the sting
of my wrath.
Yes, My Lord.
Are you trying
to get us killed?
The real Lord Rahl would never
show kindness to a slave.
They were being so cruel.
And how cruel are they going
to be to us if we're discovered,
you idiot?
I am the one who said
we should get out of here.
If we try and leave now,
before Lord Rahl indulges
in his famous appetites,
they'll get suspicious.
Lord Rahl,
your bedchamber is in readiness.
May I show you there personally?
Um...
I have affairs of state
to attend to.
But I command you to show
Captain Malray here
to his bedchamber.
And do not fail to extend to him
every courtesy
you would extend to me.
As you command, My Lord.
I will fetch you a robe,
captain.
Walter.
Hm?
You are the best friend
a man has ever had.
The night that Walter and I
spent in that temple
was nearly worth all the trouble
that came after.
Nearly.
I assure you, My Lord,
the treasure has gone untouched
since you entrusted it
to our care.
Good.
Load it onto the wagon.
At once.
Must you leave us so soon,
My Lord?
I have many enemies
in the Midlands.
More than we can fight
at present.
So I will sail
to the Lands of the South
where I will use the treasure
to raise a mercenary army
with which to return
to re-conquer D'Hara.
A wise plan, My Lord.
You and your sisters
will provide us with an escort
to see us safely to the port.
Our real plan was to catch
a boat to Merilandria,
but I knew we needed protection
to get us past
the marauders and the bandits
of the Iron Mountains.
And we almost made it...
Halt!
...if it hadn't been
for the meddling
of those Mord-Sith wenches.
Lord Rahl, it is your most
trusted officer,
General Egremont.
It was the one man
in the entire world
we knew
we couldn't possibly deceive.
What is he doing here?
We sent word to him,
My Lord.
You will need all the swords
you can get
if you are to restore
the glory of D'Hara.
Are you a fool?
Do you not know
that Lord Egremont is a traitor?
He tried to usurp the throne.
Yes.
I had no idea.
Please, Lord Rahl, forgive me.
Your only hope of forgiveness
from Lord Rahl
is the death of Egremont and all
his nefarious followers.
Order yours sisters to attack,
before he slaughters us all.
You heard Lord Rahl!
Destroy them!
When the life went out
of that first Mord-Sith...
I knew our troubles
had only begun.
What do you mean?
Well, she was dead, man.
Her soul was travelling down
to the Underworld.
Imagine her surprise
when she finds herself
in that fiery pit of anguish,
facing the real Lord Rahl.
And imagine his displeasure
when he's told
by his faithful Mord-Sith
that some impostor is making off
with his gold.
I fought bravely
at Walter's side,
but we were overcome.
Why did you attack us?
Lord Rahl commanded me.
Lord Rahl is dead!
So I can only conclude
that man's an imposter,
a double
once in Lord Rahl's employ.
You will beg my forgiveness for
your impertinence, Egremont.
Or you and all your men will pay
for it with your sorry lives.
Gladly.
If you can prove that you are
indeed the true Lord Rahl.
Which you can do
by telling me
what was the chief entertainment
at the fateful birthday party
of Princess Violet
of Tamarang?
A clown.
No, Walter.
It was a puppeteer.
You have been deceived.
Um... No. No, no.
You know-- Oh! Aah!
No.
Do not kill him.
My Lord,
he was impersonating you,
and stealing your gold.
Yes, so I've just been informed
by a recently dead
Sister of the Agiel.
But this charlatan
was useful to me in life,
and may one day
be useful to me in death.
Throw him
in your dungeon,
but maintain his appearance
in case I have need of his
services in the future.
Stay at the temple
with your men.
Guard him with your life,
until I appear to you again.
No, please-- Aah!
That was nearly
half a year ago.
I haven't seen
poor Walter since.
No doubt rotting in that
Mord-Sith dungeon as we speak.
Here's to you, Walter.
I don't understand it.
We should have
caught up to her by now.
Maybe we have.
Zedd.
Command me, Confessor.
Remove the dacra.
Oh. Oh, thank you, Kahlan.
The Scroll of Valdaire.
Do you know where it is?
Answer him.
Forgive me, Confessor.
I don't know anything
about a scroll.
A Sister of the Dark took
something very valuable
from the Seeker and ran off.
Where is she?
That must be Sister Marianna.
She ordered us to stay here
and attack you and the Seeker,
and at least slow you down
if we couldn't kill you.
Please, forgive me, mistress.
Which way did she go?
West.
Let's move.
General.
This woman claims Lord Rahl
ordered her to meet him here.
Sister Marianna, faithful
servant of the Keeper.
The day we have been
waiting for has finally come.
But Lord Rahl is not here.
I have the power to summon him.
Do you still have the scroll?
I wouldn't have dared to appear
before you without it.
My Lord,
I have done asou've commanded
and personally supervised the
incarceration of the prisoner.
I'm so pleased to hear that.
Because now it is time
for our old friend Walter
to die.
It's so cold down here.
Please don't tell anyone,
but I managed to steal
a few tots of rum.
It should
warm you up a bit.
Put these on. Hurry!
What's going on?
I'll explain once
we're outside. Quick.
There's nobody coming.
There will be.
Why are you helping me?
You were kind to me.
Nobody's ever been
kind to me before.
We have to keep going.
He's gone!
My sisters will get him back.
My riders will catch him faster.
Go!
Rahl?
No, no, I'm not him!
I swear I'm not.
I'm just this sod
who looks like him.
It's true.
I saw a Sister of the Dark
summon the spirit
of the real Lord Rahl.
I can't be him. See?
I'm not a spirit.
Go ahead. Touch me.
Uh, but not with that.
Nobody needs to touch you.
It's obvious you're not Rahl.
This Sister of the Dark.
Did she have a scroll with her?
Yes.
Please, help us.
They're planning
to kill Walter.
Thank you for saving us.
We'll just be
on our way now.
We don't want to be
any more trouble. Okay.
You're not going anywhere.
Oh.
The Sister of the Dark is
in that temple with the scroll.
We need to go in and get it.
We don't need extra cargo.
Think about it.
Darken Rahl keeps a look-alike
alive in his castle,
where he has summoned
a Sister of the Dark
to assist the Mord-Sith.
He has all the magical
ingredients he needs
to return to the Land
of the Living
in this man's body.
What?
We can't let him run off
and risk Rahl
recapturing him somehow.
We'll storm the temple,
get the scroll,
and then we'll decide
what to do with them.
You'd better
burn these bodies
before Rahl sends them back
as banelings.
What an unexpected pleasure
to see so many old friends
in one place.
Though I must say, Walter,
I have seen you looking better.
We know what you're planning
to do to him.
And we're not going to let
it happen.
No, something tells me you'll
do more than let it happen.
You are going to kill him
for me too.
And then your new
Sister of the Dark friend here
will summon my soul
into his body,
and Cara's lovely lips
will blow the Breath of Life
into my new lungs.
You're out of your mind.
On the contrary.
I'm thinking quite clearly.
Are you, brother?
Or do I need to remind you that
without the Scroll of Valdaire,
you will never repair the veil?
The Keeper will win,
and every living person
in this world will die.
But if you do as I ask,
I will hand you
the scroll personally.
Suddenly you want
to defeat the Keeper?
I want to live again.
You of all people must
understand that, brother.
I miss the taste
of a crisp apple.
The warm press of a woman's
flesh against my own.
But I must admit,
being a spirit
does have its advantages.
For instance,
I can appear to Sister Marianna
much faster than you
can get to the temple.
I have but to command her
to burn the scroll
and your failure is assured.
So do we have an agreement,
or don't we?
If we turn down Rahl's proposal,
the scroll will be ashes before
we get to the temple.
I never thought I'd say this,
but that devious bastard
has us firmly by our nethers.
We can't just kill Walter.
Maybe we don't have to.
How attached are you to the body
you were born with?
I'd do anything
to have a different face.
I think that can be arranged.
How?
We have the magical means
to put your spirit
into one of these bodies,
and bring you back to life.
And put Rahl's spirit
into Walter's body.
Exactly.
Take your pick,
any one you fancy. But quickly.
Uh...
You choose.
Me?
Yeah. If I'm going to have
a new body,
I want one
that pleases you.
Come.
Zedd, once we give Rahl
his new body,
we can't just trust him
to bring us the scroll back.
You could confess him.
Rahl's soul
is immune to confession.
But there is another way.
You sure this is gonna work?
Don't worry, I went through
it myself, and it worked fine.
Okay.
Oh. Is--?
Is this going to hurt?
I'll try to make it quick.
Okay.
Um! Does it really
have to be a knife?
Just sit back, okay,
and try and relax.
Take a deep breath.
That wasn't so bad,
now, was it?
Don't be afraid, Walter.
I'm right here.
Now.
Mika, it's me.
I'm back!
Ah, it's good to be back.
I knew you'd do
the right thing, brother.
Sister Tyra is going with you
to the temple.
You're going to get the scroll
and bring it straight back.
Otherwise, she'll release
the magic of the dacra,
and you'll be dead again
in a heartbeat.
This really wasn't necessary.
I would have done
exactly as I promised.
Well, I won't have to take
that on good faith now, will I?
My Lord.
How is it possible
you've returned
without the help
of Sister Marianna?
And how did you get
the prisoner's body
when my men have
yet to return with him?
I don't know
what rabbit trail
your men are following,
Egremont.
Fortunately,
their ineptitude was redeemed
by Sister Tyra here.
You flatter me, My Lord.
Not only did she recapture
and kill Walter,
she performed the ritual
of resurrection.
What Mord-Sith did you find to
administer the Breath of Life?
I was revived by Tyra,
who had the foresight
to kill a Mord-Sith
and take her han.
It appears you
and your sisters
are not as indispensable
as you think.
Now give me the scroll.
My Lord, you do seem
very much yourself,
but in light of recent
misunderstandings,
I believe you would want me
to verify the identity
of anyone who claimed to be you.
Of course.
I'm sure you could tell me,
for example,
what was the gift you gave
your sister Jennsen last year
when you were trying
to earn her trust?
A kitten.
And unless you want to share
that poor creature's
unfortunate fate,
you will hand me
the scroll right now.
Hm.
How very interesting.
You may be on your way now,
Sister.
Sisters!
You will of course want
refreshment, My Lord.
And company.
Yes, I would.
But unfortunately,
I have time for neither.
I must be on my way.
Prepare a wagon
for my treasure.
At once, My Lord.
The Mother Confessor said
nothing about treasure.
Now that I'm alive again, I have
no intention of being penniless.
I won't allow you
to displease my mistress.
Well, imagine her displeasure if
the Seeker never has a chance
to read this scroll.
Oh, you may command the magic
of the dacra to kill me,
but by then this parchment
will be nothing but cinders.
My Lord.
Your wagon is being prepared.
Shall I assume we're returning
to the People's Palace
to reclaim your throne?
You are to remain here,
Egremont.
My Lord, I am most eager to
help you resecure your domain.
The time
is not yet right.
Before I return
to the palace,
I must pay a visit
to Ravensberg.
When I'm ready, I will send
for you. Is that clear?
Yes, My Lord.
I need your best archers,
at once.
Why?
Lord Rahl was sending me
a message.
He was once ambushed at
Ravensberg and almost killed.
He's telling me
he's in danger again now.
And we're going
to get him out of it.
suspenseful theme playing )
Do you have the scroll?
I think you'll find it
interesting reading.
I know I did.
Hand it over.
Of course, brother.
But in case your plan
is to have your pet
Sister of the Dark here
kill me once I relinquish it,
you should know that I would
then be forced
to tell the Keeper
what is written on the scroll.
And then he will know exactly
where you'll be going next.
I imagine he would send an army
of banelings to greet you.
You win.
She won't release the magic.
Now give me the scroll.
Now get this thing
out of me.
I'm thinking maybe we should
leave it in.
You're much more
cooperative this way.
Lord Rahl is under
the Seeker's control.
And will be as long as
the Sister of the Dark lives.
Kill her.
Let's go. I know
a place we can be safe.
And happy.
Hyah!
For D'Hara and Lord Rahl!
Walter's getting away
with the treasure.
We have no use for it.
Let them go.
They're not the only ones
that got away.
Rahl's gone too.
We can track him.
Maybe.
We didn't come for Rahl.
We came to find out
what we're supposed to do
with the Stone of Tears.
What does it say?
"The instructions
inscribed upon this scroll
"will only appear in the glow
cast by a Night Wisp."
All this trouble and the
instructions are invisible?
Only until we find
one of Kahlan's tiny friends.
Well, I guess we know
which where we're headed.
So does Rahl.
A tankard of stout ale, barkeep.
Aha, a brother in arms!
Brings to mind
the good old days.
You know, I once came damnably
close to bringing back
those good old days.
It's quite a story,
and I'd be happy to tell it
if my, um, ahem--
If throat weren't so damn dry.
I already know that story.
In fact,
I know a part of it you don't.
The happy ending.
Oh, what's the matter, Malray?
Don't you recognize
your old friend?
Walter? How?
That's quite a story too.
Which I'll tell you
on the road.
That is of course
if you're still interested
in going to Merilandria.
Oh, I-I'm a little short
of funds, I'm afraid.
I've recently come into
a small fortune myself.
Found a girl too.
The right one.
She's outside
in a coach right now.
And I've bought passage
for three
on the next ship
out of Wynnmore.
Is-- Is this really possible?
Walter!
Just close your eyes, Malray...
And imagine yourself
by the sea.
Cheers.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --