Joyous news, Lord Rahl.
The forces you sent to Kelabra
have delivered
the second Box of Orden.
Send word to Queen Milena, tell her
that I accept all her demands,
in return for the third box.
Forgive me, Lord Rahl,
but why would we pay
such a generous price
when one division of our forces
could crush Queen Milena to dust?
Once I have all three boxes,
the magic of Orden will give me
unchallenged power over everything,
and Milena's demands
will be meaningless.
There lives Queen Milena.
Not the most beloved monarch
in the Midlands.
When she was still Princess Milena
she took command
of her father's armies
and attacked
the Kingdom of Tramontana.
Thousands were slaughtered,
because she wanted a pink sapphire
the size of a large pumpkin seed.
And she got it.
How many people did she kill
for the third Box of Orden?
She inherited it.
It's been in the treasure room
for a thousand years.
We're almost too late! The talk
in the village is that Queen Milena
has been whipping her servants,
quite literally, unfortunately,
into a frenzy over the arrival
of an emissary from Darken Rahl.
This emissary must be coming
for the third box.
- When does this emissary get here?
- Tomorrow.
Then we've got one day
to sneak into a locked room
somewhere inside
a heavily fortified castle,
steal the most valuable object
in the world, and sneak out again.
Or Darken Rahl gets the box
and rules us all.
If the roast looks too big to eat,
chop it in half.
You two delay the emissary,
- and I'll get into the castle.
- How?
"Hear ye, hear ye,
"Ten gold pieces to the entertainer
"who proves himself worthy
of performing
"at the birthday party
of Her Celestial Highness
Princess Violet of Tamarang."
Entertainer? What does
that have to do with you?
Do you know anyone more
entertaining than me?
Go on.
Swallow the hilt.
Next.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Hello, Princess Violet.
I'm Mr. Stocking.
Happy birthday.
Guards!
Throw this idiot off the grounds
before I chop off his head.
Forgive me, Your Magnificence,
for disappointing you.
Where are you going?
What do you mean?
I lost the job because of you,
you worthless, stinking rag.
First you blame me
for losing the job,
now for being stinky.
Something sure smells around here
but it isn't me.
You're hired.
Ruben Rybnik,
grand puppeteer,
at Her Majesty's service.
Sync: Kasius
1x09 - Puppeteer
For the party,
I want a puppet of me.
But better than a stocking puppet.
More lifelike. Can you do that?
The question, dear princess,
is not what can I do,
but what can't I do.
See this? Solid gold.
I got it for my fifth birthday.
Eighth birthday.
The rope is made out
of the finest silk in all the Midlands.
It took some old lady
a year to make it.
It's probably worth more than someone
like you can even imagine.
I got her last year so that
I could practice my leadership on her.
He's the puppeteer for my party.
If you don't make me too angry,
you will get to watch the show.
Excellent demonstration
of leadership, princess.
- I'm teaching her etiquette.
- But as Your Celestial Highness knows,
the threat of a blow
is often more effective
- than the blow itself.
- Maybe where you come from.
Now, show the puppeteer
what I taught you
before I hit you again.
How do you do, kind sir?
Very well, thank you.
And it is indeed a pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
May I ask your name?
Rachel.
Here's my dress.
Your Highness, you are the very soul
of understated elegance.
Now, what would truly set off
Your Majesty's beauty would be...
Your mother
would never let you wear that.
- Would never let me wear what?
- The Tramontana's famous Pink Sapphire.
I'm sure when you're a little older,
you'll be allowed to.
I'm allowed to wear any jewel
in the castle.
But surely the Pink Sapphire
of Tramontana is locked in a vault.
My mother lets me go anywhere
in the castle, even the Treasure Room.
I think I could go get it right now.
Is that really the key
to the Treasure Room of Tamarang?
I've dreamt all my life
of seeing those wonders.
Keep on dreaming. I'm the only one
allowed in the Treasure Room.
Wait right here.
If I were Rahl,
I'd send more than three soldiers
for the third Box of Orden.
If you were Rahl,
you'd send a small party
of troops ahead
to make sure the roads were safe.
You know,
if we grabbed one of the scouts,
and you confessed him,
you could ask him nicely
to send a message back,
couldn't you?
Telling Darken Rahl
that Queen Milena won't be ready
to deliver the box
for at least a week.
What did you do that for?
I had him.
It looked to me like he had you.
- This is what I was afraid of.
- That I'd save your life?
That you'd let your feelings for me
get in the way of the mission.
He was about to kill you,
and I stopped him.
We had a rare opportunity,
and we missed it because
you were being overprotective.
What's that?
A Journey Book.
It's how Darken Rahl communicates
with his commanders from far away.
He writes in his book,
and the words appear in this one.
This might tell us exactly
when the emissary is coming,
and by what route.
Rachel.
How did you come by
such a beautiful name?
I was named after my grandmother.
Where is your grandmother now?
The queen's soldiers killed her.
She didn't fall to her knees
fast enough
when the queen came
riding by in her carriage.
They killed my mother and my father
and my brother too.
You took the sting away.
I need your help
with something very important.
Have you ever been
in the Treasure Room?
And have you seen the Box of Orden?
Princess Violet hates it,
because it's the only thing
in the castle
she's not allowed to touch.
And does Violet ever take
the key off her neck?
She even sleeps with it.
- Do you sleep in the room with her?
- She makes me sleep in that box.
But sometimes
when she thinks I'm being bad,
she makes me sleep outside.
Sometimes I'm bad on purpose
because I like sleeping
outside better.
I like hearing the crickets.
I have something special
I'd like to give you.
It's called a Trouble Doll.
You tell her your troubles,
and she takes them away for you.
I can't.
Princess Violet says I'm not
allowed to have my own toys.
If I keep it,
she'll throw it in the fire.
In all my travels
I have never met
a ghastlier little monster
than Princess Violet of Tamarang.
If the princess knows you said
that she'll have you killed.
I trust you not to tell.
You remind me very much
of my own daughter.
She was brave and strong,
just like you.
Dear one,
why don't you take
the doll and hide it?
The princess doesn't need
to know. It'll be...
- I didn't say you could talk to him.
- You're sleeping outside tonight.
But first, go to the kitchen
and tell the cooks
that my roast at lunch
was dry and stringy.
Tell them that if that happens again,
they'll have to pay for it.
Go!
Your Magnificence,
if you would excuse me,
I need to make my preparations
for the festivities.
Not one lump in that icing,
or we'll both have hell to pay.
Put some more salt in that.
- Hello, sweetheart!
- Hello, Martha.
Just in time to lick the spoon.
Only lick fast,
before you-know-who gets here.
You-know-who says
I'm supposed to tell you
that if the roast is
stringy again, she'll flog you.
You tell that spoiled brat
that all the crops in Tamarang
go to feed the queen
and her rich friends.
There's not a crust of bread left
for me to feed my children with,
and if anyone
deserves flogging, it's her.
This servant has proven herself
unfit for the job
and disloyal to the crown.
Take her to the block.
And who are you?
Your Majesty,
it is the highest honor of my life
to present to you
your humble servant,
Ruben Rybnik, grand puppeteer,
graciously chosen by your daughter
for the amusement of her guests.
I applaud your alacrity
in stamping out insolence,
but if Your Majesty disposes
of such a talented cook
before the banquet,
I do hope the princess doesn't
miss her favorite dessert.
Release her.
She shall be granted a stay
of execution until the party's over.
And as for you,
your access to the castle
shall be strictly limited
to the servant's quarters
and the banquet room.
As Your Majesty wishes.
I didn't mean to get
Martha in trouble.
Why do I always make things worse?
I wish I could run away from here.
With you.
We'd go so far away
that nobody would ever find us.
Don't be sad, Rachel.
Ruben is going to take you
away with him.
But first he needs to get hold
of the Box of Orden
so that Queen Milena can never
hurt anyone ever again.
And for that, he needs your help.
And he needs you to be very, very
brave.
Well done, Rachel.
Sara told me you needed help.
You gave her a name.
I'm sure that made her very happy.
Now wait here with Sara,
and when I come back with the box,
we'll leave together,
and you'll never see
this castle again.
Where will we go?
I don't know just yet,
but I promise
I'll find you a safe place,
with people who will be overjoyed
to have a girl as wonderful
as you to care for.
Darken Rahl is coming.
- What?
- Look. Right here.
According to yesterday's orders,
Rahl is coming for the box himself.
For the first time, ever,
we know exactly
where Rahl is going to be.
I can kill him.
But he'll be surrounded
by soldiers, bodyguards...
I can drop a running deer
at 200 paces with one of these.
And Kahlan, we get to choose exactly
the spot we shoot from.
All we need to do
is send a message back,
directing Lord Rahl
to the perfect spot for an attack.
- What are you doing?
- The magic of the Journey Book
only works when the words
are written in blood.
We'll use mine.
I thought you weren't
being overprotective.
I was...
We've received word from our scouts.
The bridge on the main road
to Tamarang
has been washed out by a storm.
We're being advised to take
the road through the Iron Hills.
Through the narrow canyons
and dark woods of the Iron Hills?
Yes, My Lord.
It will delay you by a day,
but it could take weeks
to rebuild the bridge.
My key!
What are you doing in here?
Forgive me, Princess.
My curiosity overcame me.
How stupid do you think I am?
You have two seconds
to tell me what's going on
before I scream my head off
and wake up the whole castle.
You may want to look in the mirror
before you make good on that threat.
My face! My beautiful face!
What have you done to me?
Change me back right now
or I'll chop your head off!
How will you get rid of the warts
if you chop my head off?
It's called a Tattletale Curse,
Your Celestial Highness.
I can take it away.
But if you ever even
think of telling on me,
the warts will reappear.
Forever.
Whether I'm there or not.
I got the box,
and I fixed Violet for good.
By sunrise,
we'll be six leagues away.
- What about Martha?
- Who?
The one whose head the queen
is gonna chop off after the party.
We can't leave without her.
We don't have time to go
to the servant's quarters.
If Rahl gets his hands on this box,
he'll chop off more heads than there are
in the entire Kingdom of Tamarang.
I'm so sorry, but there are
too many lives at stake.
But Martha has three children.
If the queen kills her,
they'll starve.
Post 16 extra men
on the south battlements,
and 30 on the north.
Leave nothing to chance.
What, may I ask,
is my daughter's puppeteer doing
lurking about the castle
at this hour?
I awoke with a growling stomach,
went to the kitchen
for a late night snack,
and was just on my way back
to the servant's quarters.
Guards,
see to it that the puppeteer
finds his way back.
And remain stationed
outside his room,
in case he decides he needs
anything else.
- Where's Violet?
- In the banquet room
- inspecting the party decorations.
- We don't have much time.
The queen's guards
are following me everywhere,
- they're right outside the door.
- If they're following you everywhere,
how are you gonna get
the box out of the castle?
It's up to you now.
Me?
I'd give all the riches
of all kingdoms in the world
not to have to place
such a terrible burden on you.
- If there was any other way...
- Don't be sad, Ruben.
I can do it.
I want to do it.
Listen very carefully.
Go to the kitchen
and ask Martha for a loaf of bread.
Cut the loaf in half
and hollow it out.
Hide the box inside.
Tell the guards at the gate
that the princess has sent you
to sleep outside.
Go straight through the woods,
turn right at the stream
and follow it to the hill
that overlooks the castle.
You'll find friends there.
Their names are Richard and Kahlan.
What about you and...
And Martha?
The queen isn't going to let me leave
until I finish the puppet show.
When I'm done,
I promise I'll do
what I can for Martha.
You are now the most
important person in the world.
Don't worry.
It'll be easy to get out.
Everyone treats me
like I'm invisible anyway.
You have to go now.
Good luck.
Martha, may I please
have a loaf of bread?
I'm sorry little one.
All of the bread is already
in the banquet room.
I wanna lick the bowl!
Where is it?
- What are you doing in here?
- Nothing.
Do you have something
behind your back?
Show me your hands then.
It's a present.
I wanted it to be a surprise.
Happy birthday, Princess Violet.
You call this a present?
Where'd you get it?
The trash?
Why isn't my cake in the oven yet?
I...
- just need to add the cardamom.
- I hate cardamom.
It makes me sneeze.
Just put it in already.
Are you deaf?
Richard, what if this is it?
What do you mean?
I mean, what if you kill Rahl?
It would all be over.
The magic hold he has
over his forces would be gone.
Some people might fight for a while,
but most would wake up,
go back to their lives,
to their families.
So could you.
I have no family left.
You could find somebody
to start one with.
That's not him.
His hands aren't holding the reins,
they're tied to them.
Then he must know the message
didn't come from one of his own people.
So he sent a double.
If that's not him, then where is he?
So sorry to interrupt the party.
What a welcome and unexpected honor.
The honor is all mine.
How lovely you look today,
Queen Milena.
And Princess Violet, so beautiful.
The image of her mother.
If I cut between the two roses,
we can get the box out
and I can fix the damage
so nobody will notice.
Now, quickly.
What are you doing?
The queen wants the cake
in the banquet hall now.
Before we adjourn
to the Treasure Room,
won't you consider doing us
the honor of cutting the cake?
It would be my great pleasure.
Wait!
- Who is this man?
- My apologies.
He's nothing but a common entertainer
who doesn't know his place.
I'm so sorry, Your Supreme
and Magnanimous Lordship.
I only meant to say
that the princess
specifically requested
that we have the puppet show
- before the cake.
- What are you...?
Yes, I want the puppet show first.
May I present myself?
Ruben Rybnik,
grand puppeteer.
If you would grant this indulgence,
it would mean so much to my daughter.
We can discuss our business
after the party.
Unless of course the box
is of no importance to you.
Of course, Queen Milena.
Anything for the birthday girl.
Thank you, Your Lordship.
So then my pony pranced with joy
because it knew it belonged to
the prettiest princess in all the land.
When I was 3,
and too small to ride a real pony...
As charming as this is,
we do have more important
matters to attend to.
Of course, My Lord.
Finish quickly, puppeteer.
Lord Rahl has more important things
to do than watch your marionettes.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Beware, Darken Rahl,
I am the Seeker.
The time has finally come
for me to kill you
and fulfill the Prophecy.
What is the meaning of this?
Stop this at once.
No, please, continue with the show.
I'd like to see
how this little fairy-tale ends.
Come and fight me, you coward!
I came here to enjoy myself
and celebrate
the princess' birthday.
And here you are, as always,
trying to spoil the fun
for everybody.
You know, you really are
the worst Seeker ever.
I'm going to have to kill you now
and end your silly quest.
Now,
shall we cut the cake?
Wait!
The show isn't over.
Why,
it's just begun.
Still here, Rahl?
Is that the best you can do, Seeker?
Fighting with you is so dull
I'm afraid I might fall asleep.
I beg you, stay awake.
A hero as great and noble as myself
would never kill a man in his sleep.
Your vanity is even greater
than the size of your sword.
Enough talk.
It's time for you to die.
Somebody's going to die,
that's for certain.
But I rather suspect
it isn't going to be me!
Well done, puppeteer.
Forgive me, princess,
but the dull
business of state is calling.
As it is to your mother.
- Highness?
- Certainly, My Lord.
Hurry, Rachel.
They're on their way
to the Treasure Room.
Are you trying to trick me?
I'm sorry?
This box is a counterfeit.
- That's not possible.
- Isn't it?
Someone has used magic
to turn an ordinary spice box
into a look-alike Box of Orden.
But there is nobody
with magic powers in my castle.
Your stupidity is stunning!
Seal the castle.
No one gets in or out.
And...
bring me
the puppeteer.
Queen Milena tells me
that you arrived in Tamarang
two days ago.
Yes, Lord Rahl.
I heard the princess
was looking for entertainers
and this opportunity to perform
for you and for Her Majesty
has been the pinnacle of my career.
Perhaps Your Lordship
has called me here
to see more of my artistry?
That's quite all right.
I already know what a master you are
at the art of pulling
people's strings.
Bind his hands.
What's this?
A cautionary measure
meant to insure my safety
against an untimely blast
of wizard's fire.
Wizard's fire?
Puppets dancing all by themselves.
It certainly looked like
Wizard's work to me.
Lord Rahl, you flatter me too much.
I'll show you how the illusion works
if you promise not to tell a soul.
Why don't you show me
how this illusion works instead?
Only a Wizard of the First Order
could conjure a false Box of Orden.
This looks like
an ordinary spice box to me.
Don't play games with me.
Only three Wizards of the First Order
have been born in a hundred years.
One died.
One works for me.
And the third...
What was his name?
Now I remember.
His name was Zeddicus
Zu'l
Zorander.
He disappeared right around the time
I cleansed the town of Brennidon
in an attempt to save the Midlands
from the false promises of the Seeker.
But now, the Seeker is back.
And here you are.
And here I am.
But where is the box?
Halt.
No one goes in or out.
But I go in and out all the time.
Sorry, little one.
The orders came
from Lord Rahl himself.
Can I have your name?
So I can tell the princess
I tried to follow her orders
but you wouldn't let me.
She likes to chop people's heads
off who don't obey her.
Especially on her birthday.
Tell me where the box is.
Now.
I've hidden it.
Magically.
Kill me and you'll never find it.
I have no intention
of killing you, Zeddicus.
I'm sure you'll keep your secret
till your dying breath,
but I do enjoy a challenge.
I've received a report
that one of Milena's guards
has allowed someone to pass
through the south gate.
- Who?
- A little girl. The princess' playmate.
Find her.
- I think I went the wrong way.
- Sara, which way should I go?
Please help me.
There she is!
Over there!
We have to run. Come on.
Are you Richard and Kahlan?
- Yes, we are.
- Ruben told me to find you.
Is this Ruben a tall man with long
white hair? Thinks he's really funny?
He did it.
Where's Zedd?
I mean Ruben?
I think the bad man got him.
The great Darken Rahl,
master of D'Hara,
was defeated not by the Seeker
nor by the First Wizard,
but by a 10-year-old girl.
It's a puppet.
I told you I was
the grand puppeteer.
Sara, you can talk!
Where's Ruben?
Right here,
- hoping there's a bite of cake left.
- Ruben! Martha!
Martha, I was so worried about you.
I know you were, sweetheart.
You wouldn't leave the castle
without me.
I've told my boys so much about you.
They've always wanted
a little sister.
Would you like to live with us?
But Martha, what about
your own children?
How will you feed all of us?
Now, that reminds me,
where was it?
It's the Pink Sapphire
of Tramontana.
Think of it as a parting gift
from Princess Violet.
I'm sure she would want you
to have it.
How can I ever begin to apologize?
Be assured I will not rest
until the rats in my dungeon
are devouring the remains
of that thieving, lying Wizard.
Queen Milena, it's quite all right.
You couldn't have known
that we were all being deceived.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Have no fear for your daughter,
Your Highness.
She will grow up surrounded
by the most precious jewels.
As a slave in the deepest caverns
of the Mines of Athanasia.
Bring me my Journey Book.
Fascinating reading.
Lord Rahl leaves no detail
unattended to in his orders.
You were so close to him.
No matter how close I get,
only the Seeker can deal
the final blow.
No going home yet.
Lord Rahl is sending a message.
What's he saying?
Four words.
"I will find you."