Richard, he's fine.
Who?
- What are you talking about?
- You can't hide anything from me.
There's nothing to worry about.
Trust me.
Do you know where Zedd went?
He told you where he's hiding
the Box of Orden, didn't he?
I can't believe he would trust you
and not me.
I have no idea where Zedd is.
You enjoyed that, didn't you?
Come on.
Stop!
Who are you
and why are you following us?
Chase.
- What are you doing here?
- I'll explain everything,
but there's a D'Haran quad
on my tail.
I have a feeling they consider
the Seeker a bigger prize than me.
1x14 - Hartland
He's dead.
Chase, stop!
It's okay.
Better?
Now maybe you can tell us
what you're doing
in the Midlands?
I've been in a D'Haran labor camp.
You remember that dragon?
The one that tried
to kill my daughter?
Laura!
The Gar.
After the Boundary was opened,
dozens of those beasts
swarmed into Hartland.
They slaughtered livestock...
... children.
I had to do something,
so I went to see your brother.
What are you doing here, Chase?
If I'm to save this village,
I need every able-bodied man
back under my command.
You're not the captain of the Guard
anymore.
You lost that honor
when you sided with my brother.
There are monsters out there,
killing our people.
Citizens that you as First Councilor
are sworn to protect.
Now let me do my job.
This time,
your brother did the right thing.
But when we reached the Boundary,
it wasn't just Gars
we had to deal with.
A battalion of D'Harans
was coming in.
We tried to fight but they...
They killed most of my men
and clapped me in irons.
Those D'Harans...
they know
how to break a man's spirit.
I almost gave up but,
a few days ago
they brought in another prisoner,
telling tales of the Seeker.
He had heard you were nearby.
That my friend Richard Cypher
had the D'Harans on the run.
You don't know the strength
that gave me.
The hope.
Next chance I got,
I made a run for it.
But I knew
they'd send a quad after me
and I was in no shape
to stay ahead of them for long, so...
I came looking for you.
I can't thank you enough.
Now
if you can spare a horse
and some food...
Chase, what are you talking about?
You're with us now.
I gotta get back to Hartland.
I gotta find my family.
Then we're coming with you.
But Darken Rahl
is in the opposite direction.
Kahlan's right.
You have a bigger fight, my friend.
I've seen what Rahl's forces
can do to people.
If I can't protect my own village,
what kind of a Seeker am I?
Both of you are wanted men.
If we're going to do this...
you should dress appropriately.
So how do we get past them?
We have these uniforms.
Maybe we can just walk through.
If they start asking questions?
I know how we can get across.
Your orders, sir.
Do you recognize this?
Dragon Corps.
No member of the Corps
answers to a foot soldier.
Now move.
I'm sorry, sir. No one may pass
without proper documents.
By order of the viceroy.
Funny you should mention
the viceroy.
Guess who we're delivering
this little lovely to?
If you turn us away,
he's gonna demand to know
who disrupted his entertainment plans.
Let them pass!
Emma?
Emma! Laura!
No one's been here in a while.
If those bastards have done anything
to my family...
We'll go into town. We'll find someone
who knows where they are.
They are D'Harans everywhere.
They've taken over.
Anna?
Who is she?
Just someone I used to know.
I'd say she was
a little more than that.
It's Michael.
People of Hartland,
let us pray.
Master Rahl, guide us.
Master Rahl, teach us.
Master Rahl, protect us.
In your light we thrive.
In your mercy we are sheltered.
In your wisdom we are humbled.
Seek cover! Protect yourselves!
Brave soldiers,
all of Hartland thanks you
and honors you for your courage!
All hail the savior of Hartland:
Lord Rahl!
Things have really changed
around here.
It's almost as if
everyone's under the D'Harans' spell.
If there's magic at work,
we can't trust anyone.
So how do we find my family?
Hello, Michael.
Surprised to see me?
- How did you get past my...
- Quiet.
Now, we're walking out of here
together.
If you try to call for help, you be dead
before  the words get out of your mouth.
You wouldn't kill your own brother.
I seem to remember you telling me
we weren't brothers,
right after you accused me
of killing Dad.
Now move.
- Where is my family?
- The D'Harans moved them.
- Moved them where?
- I don't know. Someplace safe.
Gars were attacking people.
You expect me to believe those butchers
are interested in my family?
I don't know where they are.
I swear it.
Look at me.
He's telling the truth.
Of course I am.
The D'Harans saved Hartland.
Saved? How?
Lord Rahl sent his sorcerers
to seal the Boundary,
to protect us from the Gars
and the other magic
that was coming through.
But they couldn't close it again.
Lord Rahl sent soldiers to protect us.
The D'Harans are liars and murders.
You really believe they're here
for the good of Hartland?
The Gars
are no longer killing our people.
Our village is safe, prosperous.
And we have Lord Rahl
to thank for that.
I imagine you have a lot
to thank Lord Rahl for.
So who do you take orders from
in exchange for all this safety
and prosperity?
The viceroy.
Viceroy.
The Gar attack
has alarmed the villagers.
More are asking to be moved away
from the Boundary.
Do as they ask.
Sir, why do we coddle these people?
Hearts and minds, lieutenant.
Our army is stretched thin.
We can't subjugate every village
in the three territories by force.
So if Lord Rahl's empire is to expand,
he must be a friend to the people.
Now if that's all,
I have a personal matter to attend to.
Sorry I'm late.
- I brought you a little something.
- Anna.
Thank you.
I guess things around here have changed
more than we thought.
I invited you here for a meal,
some conversation.
I think maybe
you have the wrong impression of me.
I can't help myself
when I'm around you.
If I didn't know better, I'd say
you had put me under an enchantment.
Do clever words like those
make other girls swoon?
There are no others.
You expect me
to believe that a dashing,
brilliant man like you
has no prospects
other than a simple girl
from Hartland?
Simple is not a word
I would use to describe you.
Are we just gonna wait out here
all night?
Look, this can't be easy for you,
knowing what's probably happening.
But if we force our way in,
Anna could get hurt.
Is there any news of my brother?
I've got every available man
searching for him.
I'll find him. I promise.
I'm going to take care of you.
This isn't your home.
Someday you'll have to leave.
Is that what's bothering you?
I've requested permanent assignment
as Lord Rahl's envoy in Hartland.
I've fallen in love
with this charming village.
Just as I'm falling in love
with you.
Are you all right?
- Too much wine.
- Sit down.
We can't just stand here.
Chase? I don't believe it.
What are you doing here?
I heard...
Are you...?
We're just trying
not to be recognized.
I don't understand.
We don't have a lot of time.
We know the viceroy's in there.
Have you been spying on me?
- Richard, it's not what you think.
- You don't owe me an explanation.
But these D'Harans are dangerous.
- You can't trust that man.
- I know.
That's why
I've been trying to get close to him.
My brother's missing.
He hasn't been seen in months.
Rumors are the D'Harans
are kidnapping people,
forcing them to serve
in Darken Rahl's army.
Chase's family is missing too.
I'm sorry.
What would their army want
with my wife and children?
Anna, you should probably go.
We're going to speak to the viceroy
and it's better if you're not around.
You can't.
I sprinkled Rama leaf into his wine.
He'll be out for at least two hours.
But I do have this.
A key?
To the safe
in the viceroy's chambers.
If the D'Harans did have something
to do with all this,
the answers may be in there.
Chase will warn us if anyone comes along
but we'd better hurry.
When I came back to Hartland,
I looked for you.
They told me
you'd fallen under the spell of a witch,
killed your father,
and gone to the Midlands.
Anna, that's not true.
Do you remember when we were little
and you thought you saw
a tree goblin behind your house?
I told the constable we both saw it.
Do you know why?
Because I believed you.
Just like I'll believe you now
if you tell me what really happened.
I went to the Midlands
because of a thousand-year-old prophecy.
It says I'm destined to kill Darken Rahl
and free the world from his tyranny.
Sounds ridiculous, doesn't it?
I always had a feeling
you were meant for bigger things.
Maybe that's why I moved away.
Something told me
you were gonna leave Hartland,
so I left
before I got my heart broken.
Over here.
It's a record book.
Troop deployments, supply requests.
Transport orders.
There's a list of names.
There's your brother.
So the D'Harans did take him.
Does it say where?
Northwood Grove.
It's only a few leagues from Hartland.
He was taken there two months ago.
All of these people were sent there.
That doesn't make any sense.
There's nothing in that grove.
- What about Chase's family?
- They're not here.
Why would the D'Harans send my brother
to a grove in the middle of nowhere?
We're too late.
He's gone.
They're feeding people to the Gars.
You know, my brother was a good man
until you put him under your spell.
You may have grown up with Richard,
but you don't know
the first thing about him.
He's not under anyone's spell.
And to the people of the Midlands,
he's a hero.
Richard Cypher, a hero.
This is what your D'Haran friends
are doing to your people.
- I don't understand...
- Don't play stupid, bastard.
- Did you feed my family to the Gars?
- What are you talking about?
The D'Harans
protect us from the Gars.
That's what they want you to think.
The Gar attack in the square
when the soldiers shot it out of the sky
- I think it was staged.
- Staged?
They have Gars chained outside town.
When anyone questions
why the D'Harans are here,
they release one of the Gars.
Their soldiers kill it
in front of witnesses.
Michael declares the D'Harans
heroes,
and everyone
pledges their allegiance to Rahl.
This is your seal, isn't it?
"Office of the First Council."
You gave the D'Harans these names.
Why?
They wanted volunteers,
men to enlist in their army.
The viceroy asked me for the names
of those who didn't wanna join.
People like my brother?
So they sent him to the Grove to be fed
to the Gars along with all the others.
The viceroy told me that they would find
other ways for the people to be useful.
They found another way.
They told me Hartland had to do its part
for the D'Haran cause.
I thought I was keeping
the town safe.
I didn't know.
Didn't know, or didn't want to know?
I wanna help you stop them.
How?
Every evening,
I lead the town in prayer.
Instead,
I could tell people the truth.
I'm still First Councilor,
they will listen to me.
And they'll rise up.
There's one problem. The viceroy
stands with me during the prayer.
Once he realizes what you're doing,
he'll have you killed.
Not if I distract him.
Distract him how?
I could visit the viceroy
in his chambers,
keep him there
while Michael makes his speech.
How many more people are gonna die
if we don't stop them?
There are soldiers in the square.
- What if they try and stop the speech?
- We'll be there to assure they don't.
And if Michael points out the Seeker
to the guards instead?
We'll just have to trust him.
I admire her spirit.
She's always had a mind of her own.
How long were the two of you...?
We were always close,
since we were crawling on all fours.
After Darken Rahl is defeated,
maybe you could come back.
And you and Anna could pick up
where you left off.
Why are we talking about this?
Because you deserve a normal life.
A wife.
A family.
Wouldn't be fair to Anna.
Why not?
How could I marry her when my heart
belongs to somebody else?
Wait outside.
I didn't expect to see you.
I thought I'd surprise you.
You were gone when I woke up.
My niece was ill.
And you were so tired,
I didn't wanna wake you.
I owe you an apology.
I've been pushing you away.
The truth is,
I have feelings for you too.
I was just afraid
you were gonna leave.
But now that you're staying...
I don't wanna keep you waiting
anymore.
- I have to go.
- Please stay with me.
I can't.
But I'll be back.
Anna, what are you doing?
Guards!
- Why?
- You killed my brother!
How many people
did you feed to those monsters?
How many?!
And I actually thought
we had a future.
People of Hartland,
I have something very important
to talk about this evening.
Is there a problem?
Then begin the invocation.
People of Hartland...
... let us pray.
Master Rahl, guide us.
Master Rahl, teach us.
Master Rahl, protect us.
In your light, we thrive.
In your mercy, we are sheltered.
- Where's Anna?
- They've taken her.
Where?
Northwood Grove.
It's the Seeker!
It's all right.
Viceroy, the prisoner's been rescued
by a man
wielding the Sword of Truth.
Did you know your brother
was in Hartland?
Of course not.
Richard Cypher's a traitor to my family,
he's no brother to me.
Lord Rahl anticipated
the Seeker might return home.
You know what your orders are.
What orders?
You have to leave now.
- Leave? Why?
- They lied to me from the beginning.
They never tried to close the Boundary.
They been using magic to keep it open.
How?
The arch they built at the border,
it has magical properties.
It's kept the passage
from closing up.
The viceroy's on his way
to destroy the arch.
He says the Boundary
will then seal itself.
They'll cut off
the only route to here.
Defeating the Seeker
is more important.
They wanna trap you
on this side of the border.
Because if you can't return
to the Midlands,
you'll never be able
to defeat Darken Rahl.
Viceroy, a rider approaches.
First Councilor?
Don't do this.
Hartland needs the Boundary open.
You know very well
I have orders from Lord Rahl.
You'd be cutting off
our only trade route with the Midlands.
Think of your men.
All of you will be trapped
on this side of the Boundary.
A sacrifice we're willing to make
to defeat the Seeker.
I'm not.
Councilor, don't make the same mistake
your brother did.
One man cannot defy Lord Rahl.
You're right.
We'll get you to a healer.
It's too late.
Stay with me.
When I see our father
in the underworld...
I'll tell him
my brother
was a great hero.
You will order the Gars destroyed,
and disband all D'Haran forces
in Hartland.
Once I've left,
you will obey Anna's commands as if
they were my own, do you understand?
I will do as you bid, My Lady.
I wish I could control men
like that.
He has to tell the truth,
isn't that right?
My family were taken by your men.
Where are they?
I was ordered to gather women, children
and send them to the Keep of Edraan.
- It's in the Midlands.
- You've heard of this place?
Only in rumors.
The Keep is protected by dark
and powerful magic.
Why were they sent there?
I don't know.
We'll find your family, I promise.
Even if we do,
Rahl will keep sending soldiers
across the Boundary to kill more people.
Then I guess we're going to have to do
what he wanted.
Close the Boundary.
You'll set the charges
and destroy the arch
once Richard, Chase and I
are on the Midlands side.
After we fought so hard
to keep the D'Harans from closing it.
I'd ask you to stay,
but I know you have a bigger destiny.
And other people who need you.
There's something else very important
I need you to do.
It's an urgent message
from the high viceroy in Hartland.
What does the viceroy report?
"Lord Rahl,
I have the most glorious news."
In accordance
with your standing orders,
the Boundary has been sealed.
As for the Seeker...
- What of the Seeker?
- My Lord...
Is this message authentic?
It's in the viceroy's hand,
I'm certain of it.
My Lord, you've succeed.
The Seeker is dead.
Now there's really
no going home again.
I'm sorry about Michael.
We should get moving
before the D'Harans send troops
to inspect their handiwork.
If we run into them, got an extra pair
of hands to fight them with now.