Richard Cypher,
you are the true Seeker.
Legend of the Seeker 2x06
Fury
Original Air Date on December 12, 2009
-- Sync, corrections by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --
See how the deer
changed direction
when he heard us coming.
Can you tell me
which way he went?
I don't see why
I need to learn to hunt.
We're not in
a Mord-Sith temple.
We don't have
slaves to bring us dinner.
I'm here to protect you,
Richard,
not provide meals.
Kahlan's not above
digging up roots.
Even Zedd's been known to do
the washing now and then.
We all need to contribute.
Are you saying I'm not
doing enough for you?
Just tell me which way
the deer went.
That way.
Where the bark has rubbed
off the tree.
See, I knew you'd be
good at this.
Get me a strong one.
There's no need to harm us.
Take that girl too.
Spread out so I can get a better
look at the rest of you.
These men who attacked you,
do you know who they were?
Slave hunters.
And you didn't try
to fight them?
My people are called
the Minders.
We mind the laws
of the Creator,
who teaches us
that every life is sacred.
We love our enemies
as we love ourselves.
Love them?
I'd kill a thousand men
before I'd let one
make me his slave.
Think of all the battles
fought over the centuries,
all the blood spilled,
all the victories won,
and what has it gotten us?
Only more battles,
and more blood.
The Midlands
is a bloody place.
If you don't fight,
even to protect yourselves,
how have you survived?
We're healers.
For thousands of years
people have come to us
with their sick
and injured.
And so we were respected
and left to live in peace.
You're not at peace anymore.
No.
With the passing
of Darken Rahl,
these lands turned
to chaos.
A warlord named Caldor
came across the mountains
and captured our village.
Those of us who escaped
came together in the woods.
- And the slavers?
- Caldor's men.
When they realized
we wouldn't fight,
they came after us, to force
us to serve their master.
Your camp is too vulnerable.
We saw some caves
at the top of that ridge.
You'd be safer there.
We could escort you.
I know
you're trying to help.
But we've always been
all right on our own.
May the Spirits be
with you.
They don't want our help,
and we need to get back
to Kahlan and Zedd.
I don't like leaving
those people by themselves.
They have a right to follow
their own beliefs.
The Seeker
can't save everyone.
That's strange.
It's giving us a new bearing.
Which way
is it pointing?
Back the way we came.
To the Minders' camp.
Seeker, please, don't leave.
Caldor's men will be back.
Teach me how to fight,
so that I may defend
my people.
What about your beliefs?
My mother doesn't speak
for all of us.
Some of us think the old ways
don't make sense anymore.
When Caldor's fighters
attacked our village,
my father stood
in front of them
and he prayed
for their spirits.
But they slit
his throat anyway.
I'm sorry.
I don't want your sympathy.
I want you
to teach me to fight.
I'm not asking you to do
anything you don't choose to do.
But if you want to join Kur
and learn to fight,
we'll stay and teach you.
Kur, fighting is not the way.
We'll go to the caves.
We'll barricade ourselves.
We'll be safe there.
For how long?
Till they starve us,
burn us out.
Who will fight with me?
You'd all rather stick
to the old beliefs,
watch us get cut down
and dragged away
until there's nobody left?
I'll fight.
No, Veta.
You know the Creator's will.
And I also know
I don't want to die.
Or be a slave.
Do you?
You Lot will stay here
with me and Kahlan.
Roga, will you let Zedd and Cara go
with you to the caves,
and protect you
until these people are ready
to protect you themselves?
We need to ask you
something.
Do you know anything
about the Stone of Tears?
Of course we know of it.
It's in our prayers.
Today, the compass we're following
shifted its bearing
to your encampment.
Do you have the Stone?
No.
We thought the Stone
had been lost forever.
For all our sakes,
I hope it hasn't.
Don't we need
better weapons?
Uh, these staves will do
fine for now.
The slavers have swords
and battle-axes,
what can we do with these?
I used to be a trail guide,
on the other side
of the Boundary.
Sometimes there were
bandits in the woods,
and all I had was a staff
to fight them off with.
Nobody I guided through
the woods ever lost a farthing.
One, two, three,
strike.
You have to give it
more than that.
One, two, three, strike.
Better.
But even harder.
You're fighting for the lives
of the people you love.
One, two, three, strike.
Kur?
Kur, answer me.
I knew no good
would come of this.
I'm sorry.
What is it Zedd?
I believe these people
are under a binding spell.
A very ancient
and very powerful magic.
They were fighting
when they collapsed?
Yes.
This is the first time
they've ever raised
a weapon against
an opponent.
That may be what caused
the spell to strike them down.
I don't understand.
The Wizards of long ago
created the binding spells
as a way of reining
in the powerful forces
that burn inside us.
Lust, anger,
envy, violence.
It could be that this spell
was put on the Minders
to prevent them
from raising their weapons.
If the magic is thousands
of years old,
how could it be affecting
these people now?
Some spells don't die with
those on whom they are cast.
They're intended to be passed
down through the blood.
Which may explain your people's
aversion to fighting.
We choose not to fight
because we love
the Creator and her works,
not because of a...
A spell.
Whatever the reason,
I think I can draw
the magic into my own body.
But healing all of them
will drain me
of my powers.
It may take days
for me to recover.
And who knows what
the consequences will be.
What do you mean?
The ancient Wizards
were men of great wisdom.
They did not cast powerful
spells for no reason.
We have no way of knowing
what will happen to them,
or me, if I remove
the binding spell.
We have to risk it.
Thank the Creator.
And the Wizard.
Don't thank me yet.
It's our turn to help you,
Wizard.
I'll take you back
to the caves.
Can we fight again now?
How can you even ask?
You saw the price you paid.
But the spell has been lifted.
Kur, if you fight again
and something happens,
the Wizard won't have
the strength to heal you.
If we don't learn to fight,
we die anyway.
You'll keep teaching us,
won't you?
This is not a game.
Your enemy's not going
to just stand there
while you poke at him.
He's going to try
to kill you.
You have to try
and kill him first.
Hesitate and die.
I brought you dinner.
Quick little bastards,
but not quick enough.
Thank you,
but we never eat
anything that's been killed.
Actually, I found them
by the side of the road,
where they died a natural,
peaceful death.
Cara.
We're Roga's guests.
There's no sense to this.
It's one thing not
to kill another person,
but you have to eat.
I saw some winterberries
growing along the path,
down below the rocks.
We'll gather some.
Go after them.
They don't want our help.
As long as we're with them,
I'm not going to allow
any more of them to be killed.
Go.
Hungry?
Not particularly.
Don't you like winterberries?
Maybe stuffed inside
a crisply roasted suckling pig.
Try one.
You may be surprised.
Good,
right?
Roga!
Take a message to Caldor:
Leave the Minders alone.
I won't let you hurt him.
I'm just gonna teach him
a lesson.
Yes.
The same lesson you've
both been taught
all your lives,
that violence will help you?
Do what you want.
I'm through with you.
Go in peace.
Serve the Creator,
and she will reward you.
Good work.
We'll start again
at first light.
Come on, Seeker.
Draw your sword.
A good soldier knows
when to rest.
Caldor's men aren't resting.
I want to test myself
against a real fighter,
with a real weapon.
You're not scared of me,
are you?
Hesitate and die. That's
what you taught us, right?
You've been paying attention.
Don't go so easy on me.
Nice move.
But know when your opponent
has a better one.
Richard,
what are you doing?
What does it look like?
I'm teaching him to fight.
You almost killed him.
He'll never learn to defend
himself until he's faced
someone who's trying
to hurt him.
Richard, you just started
training him two days ago.
I know what
I'm doing, Kahlan.
Don't get in my way.
Did he hurt the boy?
Mostly just scared
the wits out of him.
But there was an anger
in Richard's eyes
I'd never seen before.
It's bitter, and harsh.
Maybe you're just upset because
Richard raised his voice at you.
You weren't there.
Had you seen what happened,
you'd know something was wrong.
The Sword was glowing.
Glowing?
Does that mean something?
The magic of the Sword
is fueled by the Seeker's anger,
and with it he's able to fight
with the strength of many men.
But the Sword only glows
when the Seeker's anger
turns to rage.
He was out of control.
Could this
have something to do
with removing the binding spell
from the Minders?
I don't know.
But I need to see him.
- You're ready.-
- For what?
I only planned to teach you
how to defend yourselves
against the slavers.
But you're better fighters
than I expected you to be.
We're going to take your
village back from Caldor.
Am I wrong about you?
Are you afraid
to take back what's yours?
No. There's nothing
we want more.
But to fight Caldor,
we need better weapons.
The Wizard can
make them for us.
You won't always have
a Wizard to help you.
We'll get them ourselves.
How?
If it weren't for Kur,
we could all be dead.
Kur didn't hesitate.
He did what had to be done.
Grab a weapon.
It's time to go.
You were raised with
the belief that no man's life
is worth more than another's,
but I tell you today,
the enemies we will face
are not men.
They are the monsters
who held your father
and forced him to watch
while they violated your mother.
They are the demons
who forced hot coal
down your brother's throat.
They are the ghouls
who dragged your sister away
and forced her to live
in slavery,
humiliation and despair.
Don't fight the rage.
Let it hold you in its grip.
Let it guide the deadly
sweep of your sword.
Because it is
the torch of rage...
...that will guide
your way to victory.
This is where he was
training the Minders.
The slavers must
have taken them.
They weren't taken.
Not with Richard
to protect them.
Then where have they gone?
This is for my father.
Follow them into the forest!
Hunt them down!
And kill them all!
Our village has been...
...desecrated.
Creator, forgive those
who did this.
Tamra!
I never thought I'd see you
again in the this world.
Spirits be thanked.
The Spirits have abandoned us.
Never, Tamra.
Never.
She was taken slave
by Caldor's men
when they attacked
our village.
You can't imagine
what I saw.
The killing,
the blood,
And it was Minders doing it.
Veta.
And Kur.
Slashing men to the ground.
My son?
Killing?
Man after man.
His clothes were soaked
with their blood.
It was the Seeker
who led them to do this.
Th isn't Richard.
There's magic
at work here.
Caldor's men
tried to run,
but the Seeker
killed them anyway.
Maybe he thought
he had to.
These men are savages,
slavers and killers.
If Richard let them go,
they may have come back.
Kahlan.
Zedd, what is it?
Inscriptions written
in an ancient Wizard's tongue,
one I learned long ago.
There are more inside
the temple.
We've never known
what they meant.
If they mean
what I think they do,
then there's no telling
what terrible things
Richard may be capable of.
Find him. Bring him back here
as quickly as you can.
Cara, if Richard is
truly out of control,
then maybe only
Mord-Sith magic can stop him
from using the Sword.
Caldor's main camp.
All those tents.
There must be a hundred men.
That's a hundred more souls
for us to send to the Keeper.
How do we fight that many?
We don't.
These are the men
who killed our fathers.
We can't let them live.
We won't.
If we're not gonna
fight them, then how?
We're going to burn them
while they sleep.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Richard.
What do you want?
You need to go back
to the village.
All of you.
We're not finished
with Caldor.
More killing only serves
the Keeper
and everything we're
fighting against.
The Minders have
their village back,
you've taught them
to defend themselves.
Isn't that enough?
No. It's not.
Let's move.
Richard.
You're not yourself.
Put down the Sword.
Not until Caldor and every one
of his men are dead.
Now,
you can stand with us,
or you can
fight against us.
I'm not gonna let
you do this.
Richard, no.
Cara.
Cara!
There's nothing
I can do for her.
I don't have my powers back yet.
You're healers.
You can help her.
Maybe I shouldn't.
What?
Did the Creator
give me the gift
of healing so I could put
a killer back in the fight,
only to kill again?
Isn't that a Mord-Sith's life,
one long killing?
You don't know
anything about Cara.
And if you can save her,
but you let her die,
isn't that the same
as killing her yourself?
Take her to my home.
How could I do it,
Zedd?
How could I raise
the Sword to Kahlan?
Nearly kill Cara?
How could I have slaughtered
all those slavers?
I have something to show you.
These writings tell the story
of a bloodthirsty warlord
who used dark magic to chain
a clan of fierce warriors
to his will
3,000 years ago.
Through the chain flowed
a storm
of bloodlust and rage,
and together the warlord
and his warriors rampaged
through the Midlands,
leaving death
and destruction in their wake.
Who was this warlord fighting?
Anyone and everyone.
He was mad
for blood and power.
Finally,
he was captured
and beheaded,
on the spot where
this temple now stands.
The greatest Wizard
of that time,
fearing that the warlord's
bloodthirsty men
would become chained
to another dark master,
put a binding spell
on them,
that would cause them
and their descendents
to sicken and die if they ever
again raised arms in violence.
Those warriors were
ancestors of the Minders.
And when you removed
the binding spell,
they were free
to fight again.
Yes.
And free to become chained
to another master.
Me.
How?
Why?
Because, Richard,
the madman that first put
the spell on them
was named Canton Rahl.
He was your ancestor.
We start with water,
the foundation of all elements.
That's you.
To the water, we add alum.
That's the Minders.
When I removed
the binding spell,
the Minders became chained
to your will,
but the water stayed calm
as long as you stayed calm.
But then you added the magic
of the Sword of Truth
to the brew,
and that...
...was the vinegar.
Three elements, Richard.
Each of them harmless
on their own,
but together,
a catastrophe.
Because now that
we're chained together
when I feel the rage,
so do the Minders.
Yes.
Then to protect the Minders
we need to break the chain.
Maybe if I got
far away from them.
I don't think
that would work.
The chain seems to be like
a Confessor's magic,
which is broken neither
by time nor distance.
So whenever
I pick up the Sword,
no matter where I am...
Every time you use the Sword,
and lose yourself to your rage,
they will too.
Then I need to learn
to control the Sword again.
I don't know
if it's possible.
The magic of the Sword
may have become too potent.
But I'll do what I can.
It seems so unlikely, Zedd.
Of all the clans
in the Midlands,
I just happen to meet one
that's magically chained
to my bloodline?
Nothing in this world
just happens, Richard.
The compass pointed us
in their direction.
Why?
The compass is supposed to
guide the Seeker's way.
Maybe that means more than just
showing us where to go.
You think there's something
I needed to do here,
- to help me find the Stone.
- Maybe.
Maybe there's something
you needed to learn.
About your ancestry,
about yourself.
Who knows?
Maybe you were brought here
to find an army
to fight with.
Caldor's men, they're
coming.
Always and again,
killing only brings
more killing.
Zedd,
have your powers returned?
Can you fight?
I couldn't incinerate a fly.
Cara's hurt. Zedd can't fight.
It's you and me,
and the Minders we trained,
against dozens of men.
Then you'll need this.
No.
Not after
what I did to Cara.
We don't know
if the Minders can fight
without the Sword's rage
fueling their courage.
Zedd, when I hold that Sword
all I feel is hatred.
What happens
if I use it in battle
and the fury takes
control of me?
I can't trust myself
with it anymore.
Not yet anyway.
Then what do we do?
My mother
and the other Minders
still have the binding spell
on them.
You know they can't fight.
They just have to look
like they can.
Halt.
The Minders want nothing more
than to remain in their village
and live in peace.
But if you force them to fight,
they'll fight to the death.
Your death.
It's your choice.
It's your fault, Seeker.
These people were clever enough
to know not to fight back.
Until you came.
Now we're here
to take blood for blood.
You've already tasted
the wrath of the Minders,
and now you're outnumbered,
four-to-one.
If I do decide
to let you live,
how do I know the moment
we turn our backs,
your peace-loving friends
won't attack us?
I'm the leader
of this clan.
You have my word.
Only a fool trusts his enemy.
I know this woman,
Lord Caldor.
She's telling you the truth.
I would stake my life on that.
I accept your assurances.
But you have my word
that if any of your clan
attack one of my men,
I'll be back with a thousand.
Every one of you will die!
We need to restrain you,
so no one gets hurt
while Richard
and I work with the Sword.
I'm sorry.
I hope you won't
have to stay here for long.
What if the magic's too strong?
What if
you can't control it?
Then I won't use
the Sword again.
How will the Seeker
complete his quest
without
the Sword of Truth?
Let the power of the magic
rise within you.
Don't resist it.
I don't want to lose control.
The rage is part of you,
Richard.
Fighting against it only
makes it stronger.
What do you feel?
Anger.
- At what?
- Everything.
That's no reason.
What are you angry at?
- Darken Rahl.
- You've killed him.
You've used that anger up.
What are you angry at?
The Keeper.
The Keeper didn't
drag you into this fight.
You released him.
What are you angry at?
Losing my father
and brother
and everything
I knew in Hartland.
Everybody has to grow up
and leave home.
That's nothing
for a man to moan about.
What are you angry at?
I can't be
with the woman I love.
Lots of people can't be
with the ones they love.
Some of us have even lost
our children,
and you don't see us
flying into rages.
What are you angry at, boy?
I'm not your boy!
What are you angry at?
Tell me, Richard!
Who dragged you into this fight?
Who are you angry at?
You.
Now we're getting somewhere.
All those years,
you knew who I was,
and you said nothing.
You lied to me
about being my grandfather.
You weren't ready
for the truth.
You took me out of Hartland.
You named me the Seeker.
You're the one who gave me
this damned Sword.
Richard, no.
No!
He has to stop himself.
I almost killed you, Zedd.
But you didn't.
You were stronger
than the rage.
This time.
But you will master it.
As long as you have the courage
to keep working at it.
It's yours, Richard.
And only yours.
If you want it.
Try again.
That's it, Richard.
Good.
Now let it go.
You've done well.
It's pointing due east.
The way we were going before
it sent us back to the Minders.
Maybe I learned
what I needed to.
I think you have.
The hardest people to break
are always the ones
who weren't afraid
to die for their beliefs.
I think you'd be
especially difficult.
Thank you fohelping
save our village.
I hope the Creator isn't
too disappointed in us.
The next time you're
about to use your Agiel,
I hope you'll remember
that we defeated a whole army
without spilling
a raindrop's worth of blood.
What are you thinking?
Just daydreaming, that's all.
You're actually trying
to lie to a Confessor?
When will I learn?
I thought I knew Richard.
I've watched him
his whole life,
and only seen
the good in him.
Until now.
There is only good in him.
It's the magic
that's the trouble.
Oh, if it were
only that simple.
Just a few weeks ago we learned
who his real father was,
a Rahl.
He wasn't raised
by a Rahl.
He was raised by George Cypher.
The Rahl bloodline carries
with it powerful magic.
And that magic
is in Richard.
I wasn't sure until now.
Magic isn't always passed
from one generation to the next.
But the only way he could have
become chained to the Minders
is through the magic
of the House of Rahl.
He's still Richard.
He's still the Seeker.
Kahlan,
there's a part
of the Minders' story
I didn't tell him.
Canton Rahl,
the man who first put
the spell on the Minders,
wasn't always bloodthirsty.
He started out as a protector
and benefactor to his people.
But then
as his powers grew,
he began to fight
and to kill,
and the more he killed,
the more the blood lust
overtook him.
He went mad with it.
And now we know
that darkness is in Richard.
But Richard learned
to control the Sword.
He mastered his rage.
Yes.
He controlled the Sword today.
But what about tomorrow?
-- Sync, corrections by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --