Teal'c and Bra'tac believe
the way to eliminate all System Lords
is to recruit Jaffa into the fifth column.
Only when their numbers are sufficient
will it be possible to destroy the Goa'uld.
Even then, Baal controls the supersoldier
army, which cannot be turned.
So even if the rebel Jaffa
can take out most of the System Lords,
there'll still be a massive war to fight.
The problem is, Ishta doesn't want to wait.
Moloc continues to order the deaths
of female Jaffa born in his domain,
and her railroad to Hak'tyl
can't save them all.
Even now, she's organising a rebellion
to overthrow Moloc.
Teal'c and Bra'tac are trying
to convince her to see the bigger picture.
- What was my question again?
- Um, "How's it going?"
It seemed so innocuous at the time.
Fellas. How was the trip?
I have been betrayed
by those I trusted most.
That good, eh?
His mood is foul indeed.
Greetings. It is good to see you both.
Bra'tac, what's wrong?
- There was a complication.
- Ishta?
She is well. And as lovely as ever, O'Neill.
- The problem, I fear, lies with Rya'c.
- Is he OK?
He is in love and plans to be married.
So when's all this supposed to happen?
Ow!
- Three days.
- Three days, huh? That's kinda quick.
Indeed.
Well, you know,
love is a strange and mysterious thing.
Ow!
Rya'c did not even consult me
before making this decision.
This girl has caused all reason
to leave Rya'c's head.
- Zero serving three.
- Serving eight.
Eight.
Oh!
So what's Ishta think of all this?
Ishta believes traditions
should persist at all costs,
especially in the face of oppression.
I see.
Rya'c is too young
to know what love is, O'Neill.
Or how it inevitably
weakens a warrior's resolve.
Look, T, I'm not gonna tell you
how to raise your kid,
but I've found sticking your fingers
in your ears and humming loudly
solves a whole slew of problems.
What good am I as a father, O'Neill,
if I cannot keep my son
from making this crucial mistake?
Unscheduled offworld activation.
Got one.
Receiving IDC, sir. It's Ishta.
Open the Iris.
Greetings.
There is an urgent matter
we must discuss.
Hak'tyl may have been compromised.
- How do you know?
- Yesterday we were to meet a contact.
A high priestess
stationed within Moloc's temple.
She failed to appear at the allotted time.
- You must evacuate immediately.
- I agree.
But we know not
of another uninhabited planet like Hak'tyl.
Hiding female warriors and children
within a populated planet in Moloc's
domain is difficult and dangerous.
I'm sure we could help you folks out.
Carter?
No problem. We have a number
of possible worlds on record,
but they should be explored more
thoroughly before you take up residence.
If Moloc is aware of our location,
every moment my people remain
on Hak'tyl puts them at greater risk.
Oh. Um...
You're welcome to stay here.
I'll go start the paperwork.
- Colonel Carter, Dr Jackson.
- Rya'c. It's good to see you again.
This is my sim'ka, Kar'yn.
Rya'c, stop using those old terms.
We are betrothed.
An honour to meet friends
of my husband-to-be.
Right back at you.
- Is she not the most beautiful thing?
- Stop it. You're embarrassing me.
I am not an object to be worshipped.
Thank you for agreeing
to host our union ceremony.
It will be an honour
to be betrothed among friends.
- You're gonna have the wedding here?
- Of course.
Ishta said it may take some time
to find a planet for our new home.
We are to be married in three days.
There is much to do.
Rya'c.
Excuse us.
They're having the wedding here.
Does Jack know about this?
I'm gonna work on finding them a planet.
Yeah.
Come in.
Bra'tac.
What's that smell?
I believe that is the horses, O'Neill.
The warriors of Hak'tyl
are grateful for your generosity.
Well,
you know me.
Always willing to help
those who need help.
You are indeed a wise and gracious
leader, O'Neill of Minnesota.
Sit down, you old coot.
What?
I am to officiate the rite of everlasting
union between Rya'c and Kar'yn.
I have consulted with Ishta on the matter,
and despite the evacuation, she wishes
the wedding to proceed as planned.
- And as scheduled.
- Meaning here?
A more suitable world
is not likely to be found in time.
Delaying the ceremony would grant
another victory to Moloc's tyranny.
You know what it took to get approval
for tailgate Tuesdays? Huh?
There'll be cake?
You have been avoiding me.
You have indicated
I am not worthy of your presence.
How so?
Your refusal to bless this union
is an insult to Kar'yn, and thus to me.
That is not what I intended.
Rya'c has pledged to help lead the Jaffa
in the battle against the Goa'uld.
As have I and my people.
A warrior is always stronger
with another at his side.
So you must believe Kar'yn's an unworthy
warrior, and I'm at fault as her teacher.
Ishta, this is not about you.
Soon enough Rya'c will have to choose
between his family and his cause,
just as I once did.
I merely believe that he is young
and has much time ahead,
and need not undertake
such decisions so soon.
In the same way
Rya'c had no say in your decision,
you have no say in his.
None of us choose oppression
at the hand of the Goa'uld,
nor what must be done
to free ourselves of it.
But we must not sacrifice
that which makes us Jaffa.
I have organised both men and women
to fight together to rise up against Moloc.
Maybe once we are free of his tyranny,
you will see we are worthy of your war.
Overthrowing Moloc alone
will ultimately prove nothing.
Were he to fall, his worlds
would be usurped by another Goa'uld.
I will not stand idly by and watch more
of my sisters slain at the hand of Moloc,
while you and the leaders
of this so-called "Jaffa rebellion",
you plot and you scheme
and you ultimately do nothing!
You have no wish to fight side by side,
only to dominate.
As my sisters have been for generations.
As you will remain
due to short-sightedness.
I will not rest until Moloc is dead.
I will not rest until all Goa'uld are dead.
- They want a what?
- A goat, sir.
You can tell them lamb is far less gamey.
They...
They want it for a ritual sacrifice.
- Tell them that's not gonna happen.
- I was hoping you'd say that.
They can have a pinata. That's always fun.
I'll suggest it, sir.
Please tell me
you're close to finding a planet.
We scouted one
Ishta seems comfortable with.
Fresh water, stable climate.
Good. When's moving day?
Ishta thinks it'll take a week
to get a camp going.
- A week?
- Yes, sir.
The wedding is still gonna happen here.
- Have you seen Teal'c?
- He's locked himself in his room.
That chicken.
Let this fire
bear witness to this ceremony.
May its flames keep warm
the souls of those who came before us.
We ask those spirits now
to bless this union
and to protect it
through each day of its existence.
And then the horn will sound.
Good. Now.
You will place the circle of fidelity
upon Kar'yn's head.
And you the totem of bravery
around Rya'c's neck.
The bride will then
kneel before her husband in respect.
- I will do no such thing.
- Kar'yn.
I kneel before no man,
not even my husband.
This action has been
part of the ceremony for...
Then he should kneel before me as well.
Or am I too weak
to have respect given to me in return?
- You disgrace my name.
- Perhaps if we took a short recess.
And if you insist on treating me
like a fragile handmaiden,
then I have chosen poorly for a husband.
Perhaps I have chosen poorly as well.
I can see
why one must rehearse these events.
Unscheduled offworld activation.
We're receiving a message. On screen.
Ishta, this concerns you.
It's from one of my contacts
among Moloc's Jaffa.
- He's requesting a summit.
- For what reason?
Our forces that are hiding among
the Jaffa of Moloc have become large.
But there are still many
who are loyal to him.
We risk being exposed.
We must send the coordinates of the
new home world to those who will attend.
Very well.
I will accompany you to this summit.
You have no say in our matters.
Perhaps there is counsel I can provide.
You will abide by my ruling.
- Can I come with you?
- You have a union to prepare for.
There will be no union.
Kar'yn, you must learn not to let
your emotions take you to such extremes.
I cannot be betrothed to Rya'c.
He is as pig-headed as his father.
Until you have fought as many battles, do
not speak of Teal'c with such disrespect.
Without him, we would not have tretonin,
and we'd still be slaves
to the Goa'uld symbiotes.
Why do you accept his affection, knowing
he doesn't support our war against Moloc
and the archaic traditions
that oppress female Jaffa?
We differ often.
But deep down, we both possess
the same hunger for freedom.
Does he not see me fit for Rya'c?
He could search a thousand worlds
and never find someone like you.
Teal'c has lost much
in the war against the Goa'uld,
and does not wish Rya'c to feel
the pain of such loss.
What about Rya'c? He does not respect
me as a warrior as Teal'c respects you.
That took some convincing, believe me.
What you must remember is that
as much as you desire Rya'c's respect,
he too burns for yours.
Your parries are too low.
Hold your staff higher.
Step into each blocking blow.
Leave me be.
As you wish.
Have I not been a dutiful son?
- Have I not brought honour to my name?
- You have indeed.
Then why will my father
not bless my union with Kar'yn?
- Then the union is still to be?
- That is not the point.
You have made a choice. You pledged
your life to fight for freedom for all Jaffa.
- You must commit to it without question.
- I know.
That is why my father
abandoned my mother and I -
because we made him weak.
- That is not true.
- He knows I forgave him for that long ago.
- I understand why it was necessary.
- Do you? Hm?
Teal'c stayed first prime of Apophis as
long as he did because he feared for you.
He committed atrocities because he
wanted you and your mother to be safe.
When he chose to leave to join the Tauri,
it was the most difficult thing
he has ever done.
It is not you that made him weak,
but his own fear and doubt.
When he realised the Goa'uld
could indeed be defeated,
that if he fought hard enough
you could one day be free,
it made him stronger.
It is the same for me with Kar'yn.
She fuels my desire to fight for freedom.
We know what we must face,
and we choose to do it together.
You still have much to learn
about yourself. About being a warrior.
Neither of you truly know what we will
all face in full-scale war with the Goa'uld.
I do not need his blessing.
No. You do not.
And he insults Kar'yn. She is a formidable
warrior who deserves his respect.
And yours.
The ranks of rebel Jaffa
are sizeable enough to win.
The time to strike is now.
Aron is right. If we wait longer,
it is only a matter of time
before our numbers grow too large
for Moloc not to discover.
We risk losing everything.
Aron is right. We must strike now.
Jaffa.
Hear me.
I know your hearts are prepared for battle,
but I have come to ask for your patience.
You have prepared well
for the demise of Moloc,
but only when all Jaffa rise up as one
can the Goa'uld be defeated.
And only then will all of our brothers
and sisters truly be free.
This is the counsel
you have come to offer?
What is it?
Down!
Argh!
Agh!
Go.
- The gate is well guarded.
- We must return to the meeting tent.
- If anyone survived, they will be tortured.
- Wait.
For what?
- Teal'c? Are you there?
- Proceed, O'Neill.
You know how I get when you don't call.
Moloc's Jaffa ambushed us. The planet
address has fallen into the wrong hands.
I am with Ishta and another rebel Jaffa
named Aron. We are cut off from the gate.
- How bad?
- Very.
- Backup?
- It would be unwise at the moment.
I'm uncertain as to the extent of forces.
I will gather intel
before deciding on a course of action.
All right. I'll check in in about an hour.
And, T...
- My head is down, O'Neill.
- Over.
Someone has betrayed you. That can be
the only explanation for Moloc's presence.
I do not have my tretonin. It was in my
pack, and in our haste I left it in the tent.
I have enough for both of us.
It must have shattered when you fell.
We must move.
A search patrol approaches.
Indeed.
- What's going on here?
- Silence!
Thank you.
Now,
Daniel, what's going on here?
Silence.
I said, "Daniel".
- As you can see, everyone's a little upset.
- We will not abandon Ishta.
- We insist a rescue mission be devised.
- We're devising.
- Teal'c has said the gate is guarded.
- Can we not journey to this planet?
- It would take at least a week to get there.
- Please, return to your quarters.
- I cannot go until...
- Please!
In time, your skills may be required,
then you must be ready.
Go.
- There are only six.
- Many more may be hiding nearby,
anticipating our approach.
We must do something.
I cannot bear this.
The Tauri have troops and weapons.
We have not determined
the size of Moloc's forces they would face.
Many more lives than our own
could be lost.
- Then what are we to do?
- For the moment... nothing.
We cannot hide forever from their patrols.
We will rest here.
They will not rest until we are found.
If your plan is to wait until they give up...
I need to gather the information that I can
concerning the forces against us.
We are severely outnumbered.
What more do you need to know?
Aron.
I need to speak to Teal'c privately.
- You do not trust my loyalty.
- I do.
This is a private matter. Please.
He could be the informant
as easily as anyone,
and be gathering knowledge
concerning the rebellion.
I know.
But he is right about one thing.
We cannot wait to act.
I am already growing weak.
You need rest.
As do you.
I will take first watch.
Teal'c.
I promised all Jaffa under Moloc's rule
they will be free from his tyranny.
It was not a foolish promise.
One day, we will all be free.
"One day" is not soon enough.
Where is Ishta?
It was her turn to take w...
Moloc is here.
- We must act.
- I am aware.
Even if Ishta cannot be saved,
we must kill Moloc.
- That is not my goal.
- It is mine.
And that of all the Jaffa
in the rebellion against him.
Without reinforcements,
we will be swarmed by Moloc's forces.
I am willing to die for my cause.
You will die for nothing
if you do not succeed.
You are weak. Your mind is clouded
with feelings for Ishta.
And you cannot be trusted.
Ishta's been captured.
Apparently Moloc is there in person.
We'll coordinate an attack to provide
a distraction for Teal'c's rescue attempt.
Moloc will kill her before surrendering.
Teal'c's more worried about what
he's going to do to her in the meantime.
Oh!
It is not too late
to repent for your sins.
Grovel before your god
and beg for my forgiveness.
Tell me of the sinners
who would betray me.
How many would renounce the privilege
of carrying the children of their god,
like you?
Tell me while their souls
may yet be saved.
You cannot be Ishta of the Hak'tyl,
wicked leader of the depraved.
I sense nothing but weakness in you.
Or maybe that is what happens when
you abandon the strength of the Goa'uld.
All that is left is this burning desire to die
at the hands
of your great and powerful god.
We're preparing a UAV
to drop tretonin for Teal'c.
He will need all his strength
if he is to rescue Ishta from Moloc.
The UAV will then
paint the targets on the gate.
Ishta did not exaggerate. The rebel Jaffa
on Moloc's worlds are a mighty force.
As we speak, they prepare for war
against those still loyal to Moloc.
- You think they can win?
- I do not know.
Even if they do, another Goa'uld
could simply take his place.
Or worse, come in and wipe them out
to prove rebellion is a bad idea.
Indeed. That is something
we asked them to consider.
And yet, such reason is beyond them now.
- UAV ready to launch, Colonel.
- Thank you.
Dial the gate.
Launching UAV in three, two,
one.
Receiving Teal'c's signal.
The UAV's been hit.
Teal'c, do you copy?
Proceed.
The UAV should be halfa click
southwest ofyour location.
- I am on my way.
- Be careful, Teal'c.
We'll dial back in 30 minutes.
- Can we not still send missiles through?
- Without a painted target they'd crash.
Argh!
Moloc. Shnee ka.
Jaffa, shel na kree.
Kree nok, Jaffa.
Shel kek nem Ron.
If you know who I am, brothers,
you know that there is no need
to sacrifice your lives for a false god.
Sho klok.
Rin nok, shol'va.
Aargh!
It would have been easier
had you left me with a weapon.
My thanks.
Is there anything else I can do
to prove my loyalty?
Indeed.
Is this what you want?
Evil serum to poison you further?
Or will it give you strength enough
to last a little longer?
Then take it.
Take it so that you may have
more precious time with your god.
My lord.
Word comes from Goranak.
An uprising has begun. An army of
two thousand is marching on your temple.
They control a garrison of gliders
and several Alkesh.
As I have foreseen.
Your fleet of Ha'tak
have gathered themselves in orbit.
They await your command
to crush this insolence.
I am done with this one.
Trivial as it may seem, this distraction
has given me a few moments of pleasure.
Use her to capture the shol'va, Teal'c.
- Then bring him to me.
- Yes, my lord.
When the gate opens again,
merely aim this at your target.
The missiles will come through
and strike where you aim.
You're certain your strength has returned?
This time I will not be there
to come to your rescue.
I assure you,
this time it will not be necessary.
Open the Chaapa-ai.
Jaffa, kree nok.
Teal'c, do you read?
Colonel, I am ready and in position.
- So we're on?
- Indeed.
Aargh!
She's weak to the point of death.
Zatting us both, even once, will kill her.
Drop your weapon.
Shoot them down.
Drop it now!
That is the sound of your false god dying.
- Gods cannot be killed.
- Teal'c...
- Not another word.
- Shoot.
Aargh!
Ooh!
There is no need. I have taken mine.
Is it true that Moloc is dead?
If you have the strength,
we can see for ourselves.
In a moment.
Kar'yn, speak of your love
and devotion to Rya'c.
Rya'c, your heart is pure
and your spirit strong.
You give me strength.
And joy.
And I will stand by your side.
Always.
- Rya'c.
- Kar'yn,
you are as beautiful as the sun.
My love for you is like the morning rays
that dawn over an endless day.
The rite is complete.
May you love and fight like warriors,
just not with each other.
A legend speaks of a place
where mountains meet the sea,
of hidden pools beneath waterfalls.
It is no legend.
I have seen it with my own eyes.
You have chosen the location
for your Shim'roa very well.
Master Bra'tac said
this is where you took my mother.
Indeed.
Rya'c.
I can think of no better mate
for you than Kar'yn,
and I am certain
your mother would have felt the same.
Thank you.
Before your departure,
there is a matter that bears discussion.
Father, I am aware of the ways
between a man and a woman.
Good. Then you are prepared
for the rite of Oronak.
- Surely it is not still expected.
- On the first eve of Shim'roa.
My advice is that the knife
be as sharp as possible.
Perhaps Kar'yn is right. Not all of
the old traditions are worth holding onto.
Indeed.
- And what of you and Ishta?
- What of us?
Well, your relationship would be much
easier if you both admit you are in love.
- For us all.
- Perhaps one day.
When I am as wise as you.
Once again, we owe you our thanks.
For your hospitality and for helping us
find yet another new home world,
where the Hak'tyl may be safe.
Think nothing of it.
You sure you got everything?
You didn't forget any kids or horses?
- May I speak with Teal'c alone?
- Sure.
It's good to see you again.
I will see you soon, Father.
Yes,
Father.
Be well.
I did not wish to spoil
the days of Shim'roa for Rya'c and Kar'yn.
- What have you discovered?
- As predicted, another Goa'uld
has claimed the domain of Moloc.
- Baal.
- Yes.
Do not wait too long to visit.
We have a war to plan,
among other things.
Visiontext Subtitles: Joanna Wilkinson
ENHOH