Previously on "Stargate SG-1".:
The replicators. They've launched
an all-out attack on the Goa'uld.
If the Goa'uld can't stop them,
they'll overrun our galaxy within weeks.
Daniel!
Unfortunately, to get what I need,
we're going to have to dig a little deeper.
We must once and for all destroy
the Goa'uld's image as gods forever.
- How?
- By capturing the temple at Dakara.
There's a way to defeat the replicators
in my memories, isn't there?
You need only to open your mind to it.
A force of rebel Jaffa have managed
to take control of the temple at Dakara.
Have the fleet disengage their battle with
the replicators. Take it back at all costs.
The ruins of an Ancient monument
on a planet now called Dakara.
Within it is the one weapon
in this galaxy capable of destroying me.
A device capable of destroying
all life in the galaxy?
- That's what he said.
- Baal said he was serving Anubis.
Not exactly.
You know those Goa'uld and their egos.
He would never admit
to being subservient.
No. He said he was biding his time,
learning what he could from Anubis.
Probably looking for a way to kill him.
We have no idea how this Ancient device
works or what the effects will be,
but since Anubis has no real corporeal
form, it's likely he would survive it.
- He'd have no one left to rule.
- For now.
Time may not be an issue
for someone like him.
He could start over, repopulate
the galaxy to his own specifications.
- That's a little ambitious.
- He has some knowledge of the Ancients.
I wouldn't put it past him.
No.
Well, let me state the obvious. We can't let
something like this get into his hands.
Or the replicators' hands.
How much time do we have
before Baal's fleet reaches Dakara?
Why?
Baal didn't say exactly
where the device was, did he?
No. He said it was hidden.
Chances are it's in the ruins,
but we can't be sure.
Short of blowing up the planet, we can't
be 100% positive we've destroyed it.
If it's protected by a shield, our biggest
naqahdah-enhanced nuke might not do it.
Fact is, to be sure
we've destroyed the weapon,
we have to find it first.
Go.
We've found no evidence of a weapon.
Thanks, guys. We'll take it from here.
But the structure was definitely
built by the Ancients.
As evidenced by the script on this wall.
Until I saw this monument, I did not know
that Dakara was a home of the Ancients.
The Ancient repository
of knowledge on P3X-439
was hidden in a monument like this.
This writing may help us
uncover the location of the weapon.
I was able to recognise the language.
Deciphering it, however,
is another matter.
I brought Daniel's notebooks.
This dialect looks
very old. It may take some time.
I will leave you to it.
We will be outnumbered by Baal's forces.
I refuse to consider a strategy
that demands the deliberate
sacrifice of Jaffa lives.
What, then, do you advocate?
Prayer, perhaps?
Jaffa. We are here
to consider the battle with our enemy.
Not battle each other.
Baal's forces approach at a speed
slower than they are capable.
Indeed. It seems he does wish to give us
time to find and destroy the weapon.
Why not just destroy it himself?
Baal is in a difficult position.
With many witnesses, it is easier to tell
Anubis the weapon was destroyed
before he could reclaim Dakara.
How, then, will he
explain his languid pace?
Regardless, he will only hesitate so long.
Five Ha'tak. Eight Alkesh.
Ten squadrons of gliders.
That is all we have.
Empty the bays. Deploy the gliders
to the far side of the planet.
Position two Ha'tak and all the Alkesh
on the other side of the moon.
Divide our forces?
Precisely.
All of our hardship, the suffering,
the sacrifices
we have made for our cause,
will end today one way or another.
This battle will decide the fate of all Jaffa.
This is madness.
So, too, at one time,
was the very thought of our freedom.
So, now what? You done?
You got what you wanted.
Don't suppose you wanna just
drop me off at the nearest Stargate?
It is true.
I learned the location of the weapon
that could be a threat
to me and my brethren.
But I also saw the extent of knowledge
your subconscious mind contains.
You have no idea, do you?
No.
No, I don't.
You've tried accessing it,
but it's always just out of reach, isn't it?
I could help you.
We could unlock the Ancients' knowledge,
the secrets of the universe, together.
I have to admit, it does sound interesting.
But on the other hand, you're
an evil killing machine, so, no. Pass.
No. Don't do this!
You had the power. You were about
to strike, but she stopped you.
No, I don't believe you.
You can make me see whatever you want.
- That's just a trick.
- You know it's true.
Destroying the weapon
that can destroy me is one thing.
A good thing, for me.
But there is more.
There is a way to kill Anubis in your mind,
and so much more.
I am not done, Daniel Jackson.
Far from it.
In fact, we have only just begun.
"Midday, the darkness is high in the sky"?
You sure about that?
- That is what it says.
- It doesn't make much sense.
Yeah, well, neither does
"the wind blows on the pillow"
or "three days to the chicken".
But that's what these phrases
apparently translate into.
Are you saying
this whole wall is nonsense?
- I don't know what I'm saying.
- Is it possible you made a mistake?
Would you care to try?
The text is quite difficult, and if there is an
organising principle to Dr Jackson's notes
- I have yet to discover it.
- Yeah. He certainly has his own system.
- Colonel Carter.
- Go ahead, Teal'c.
Have you had any success
with the translation?
We're making... some progress.
I am afraid you do not
have much more time.
Our long-range scanners
have detected Baal's fleet.
He will be here within the hour.
Understood.
It would be much easier on both of us
if you did not resist.
Why, in the whole wide world of all things
rational and sane, would I help you?
Because deep down you also
want the knowledge I seek.
Yes, but anything I learn
I won't be able to put to use,
because after I'm done, you'll kill me.
- What if I promised not to?
- Yeah.
Do you think
I am that different from Samantha Carter?
In that you're a replicator
bent on galactic domination
at the expense of all other living things...
Her thoughts, her memories,
even her emotions.
They are not meaningless to me.
I do not wish to harm you,
or destroy Earth, for that matter.
I could have done that already
if I so desired.
You're saying
you'll leave Earth untouched?
I promise you that.
And your life.
Nope, nope. Not gonna help you.
But, obviously, I can't do anything
to stop you, so give it your best shot.
What if it's a code?
That can only
be deciphered by someone
who understands the language.
Can I see that?
- You're holding it upside down.
- I know. I just noticed.
Upside down, these symbols look
like another word I've seen before.
Right side up it's "darkness".
Turn it around, and...
it translates into "sun".
"Midday, the sun is high in the sky."
That makes more sense.
Yeah, but so what?
That's not what the wall says.
- Now it does.
- It can't be that simple.
Just turn all five circles upside down?
No, I agree. It has to be
some sort of combination lock.
We just need to figure out
which circles to turn.
Your pathetic trickery
will only delay your inevitable defeat.
There is no trickery at hand.
We know that inevitably your goal
is to eradicate all free Jaffa.
We sent most of our fleet to safety
to survive to fight another day.
Surrender now, or be destroyed.
Defeat those who remain and you'll be
forced to destroy the weapon yourself.
Then you must face Anubis.
His fleet appears to be holding position.
For the moment.
Let's hope that's not a bad sign.
Nice going, Sam.
We're in business.
- It's an Ancient design, sir.
- Think our bomb will do the trick?
We'll soon see.
Give us ten minutes. Carter out.
Right.
Sam? You might wanna hold off
on that for a minute.
If I'm reading this screen right,
the weapon uses an energy wave
to reduce all matter
to its basic molecular elements.
It's not strong enough
to disintegrate an entire planet,
but it will wash away everything
on a planet's surface,
and anything in the surrounding space.
- That sounds bad.
- I know.
But it also sounds like
it does it much the same way
your disrupter technology
works on the replicators,
by separating the individual components.
They are both Ancient design. O'Neill used
Ancient knowledge to build the disrupter.
I know.
Can this weapon be modified
to work only on the replicators?
I don't know. But I'd hate to blow it up
before I was 100 per cent sure it couldn't.
- Teal'c, do you read?
- Proceed, Colonel Carter.
Dad and Selmak think this weapon may
hold the key to defeating the replicators,
and we'll need some time to find out.
Let us know when things get bad
and we'll blow it.
- Understood.
- Carter out.
Baal's fleet just began
moving into attack position.
It appears things are about to get...
bad.
I'm not getting anything.
- This may not be possible, you know.
- Come on, Sam.
It can't be any harder
than blowing up a sun.
You blow up one sun and suddenly
everyone expects you to walk on water.
There you go.
Oh. Next up, parting the Red Sea.
Shields are down 50 per cent.
We cannot take much more.
Signal the other Ha'tak. Begin retreating.
Sublight engines only. Full power.
The rebels are fleeing, my lord.
The planet is ours.
They expect us to follow so that they may
draw the fleet into battle on two fronts.
- Signal the fleet to pursue the shol'va.
- My lord?
Dakara can wait.
No battle strategy can save them now.
We will crush them,
and then take the temple.
Yes, my lord.
This output is the spectrum of the wave
the weapon uses to disintegrate matter.
That's nothing like the spectrum analysis
of the replicator disrupter wave. Look.
All we have to do is alter
the settings on the weapon console
so that the output wave matches
that of the disrupter technology.
- All we have to do?
- Yeah. The device can be set
by varying the height of these panels.
Well, I can run a program to compare
the difference between the two waves.
That's good.
Even if we can make this work,
the replicators were quickly able to adapt
to the modulation Thor made
to the original disrupter wave.
- What are you saying?
- The only way to eliminate the replicators
and not allow them to develop immunity is
to somehow hit them all at the same time.
Everywhere in the galaxy?
How are we supposed to do that?
The weapon translates through the gate.
Do you think Anubis planned to use it
to attack one planet at a time?
So, dial multiple gates simultaneously?
Not multiple gates. All of them.
Every Stargate in the galaxy at one time?
Do you know how many gates
there are in the whole galaxy?
A lot.
I have no idea how to alter
a Stargate to perform such a function.
I don't know of anyone who can.
I think I know someone.
- Are you certain, Colonel Carter?
- I don't think we have a choice.
I mean, this could be
the best chance we'll ever get.
Understood.
Opening a channel.
You have decided to surrender. A wise
decision, given you face imminent defeat.
We have no intention of surrendering.
I merely wish to inform you
that we have found
the Ancient weapon on Dakara.
Do you intend to destroy it?
That would be foolish.
The Ancient weapon may be the means
to destroy the replicators once and for all.
It's incredible,
yet you still resist me.
Are you not amazed
by what you are seeing?
I don't understand it. It's more than
any human can begin to comprehend.
- I am not human.
- Oh, believe me, I know.
There must be a limit to how much
information your mind can store.
I am sharing what I learn
with my brethren.
The extent of knowledge we can absorb
is only limited by our numbers.
As we speak, those numbers are growing
faster than you can imagine.
This chamber must be well shielded.
I could not find it using my ship's sensors.
Look, I assume Teal'c told you the plan.
What makes you think you can modify
this weapon to defeat replicators?
We're already on our way to doing that.
We need to get this weapon's wave output
to match our modified replicator disrupter
wave to within a margin of 0.76 per cent.
How did you develop this replicator
disrupter technology in the first place?
General O'Neill built it using Ancient
knowledge and an Asgard computer.
O'Neill?
The mere thought of that makes me sick.
Look, if we can do this and somehow
hit the replicators all at the same time,
we think it will work,
but we need your help.
You want me to reprogram a Stargate
to dial every gate in the galaxy
simultaneously.
I know you used
the gate's update program
to disseminate a dialling virus
to the entire gate network.
With a virus you initially planted
in my Stargate.
No one's trying to deny
that we're mortal enemies here.
Can you do it or not?
I can't believe I'm considering cooperating
with a female of the Tauri, and a Tok'ra.
This was not my idea,
believe me.
- I'll instruct my troops to land.
- No way.
You send one Jaffa down here
and the deal's off.
I cannot do what you ask
as a hologram transmission.
Sure you can. Just tell me what to do.
Unscheduled offworld activation!
- Is that Carter?
- No, sir. It's a radio signal.
Put it on speaker.
- Sergeant?
- I don't know, sir.
- What the hell is that?
- I'm not sure, sir.
I can't access the system. It looks like
something's hacked into the computer.
- Shut it down.
- I can't, sir. I'm locked out.
Damn.
This is General O'Neill.
Sir!
Evacuate the gate room! Get outta there!
Close the blast doors.
Initiate base lockdown.
Evacuation of all personnel
through alternate routes.
Self-destruct protocol on my order.
Let's go, Walter. Let's get outta here.
- Oh, man.
- Sir.
We're cut off from the self-destruct.
They were too fast.
There's a chance they've already
disabled the activation mechanism.
Those bugs cannot
get outta this mountain.
It's only a matter of time before
they override the security doors.
Make sure everybody's outta here,
then we'll toss a nuke down the silo.
- You think that'll stop 'em?
- It should slow 'em down.
You can't handle it, can you?
I can.
I just need time to process,
share it with the others.
Like the universe, it's infinite.
It's not just knowledge and information.
It's understanding
on a level that you'll never reach.
- Why do you think that?
- Because you're a machine.
So are you, just of weaker construction.
- And that's where you're wrong.
- We'll see.
The president has authorised
deployment ofa ten-kiloton nuclear bomb.
A 200-square-mile radius around
Cheyenne Mountain is being evacuated.
A helicopter is waiting on the surface
for you and the remaining personnel.
Thank you, Walter.
Colonel?
We have a problem. Six SGC personnel
are trapped on level eight.
They're cut off from
the emergency escape hatch.
- Siler?
- Siler.
Oh, Siler.
Let's go.
- You lied to me.
- What?
You promised you'd leave Earth alone.
There's replicators infiltrating the SGC.
How can you know that?
While I was in your mind,
you were inside mine.
Took a while to figure out.
You were too distracted to notice.
The Ancient knowledge helped too.
Thank you.
- You tricked me.
- You tricked me first.
- You should never have told me.
- Too late.
For you, that is.
Trying to leave? Sorry.
A little more time in Danny's world.
My brethren will not stop.
You cannot control them.
Not yet,
but I'm learning.
We've rigged the DHD to dial
on signal when the weapon's ready.
- I think it should work.
- Of course it will work.
How dare you doubt me?
- What's he still doing here?
- I can't exactly ask him to leave.
How's it going on your end?
I'm getting closer.
This one.
- How do you know?
- I am a god.
Gods are all-knowing.
Selmak can't work like this.
- Neither can I.
- Just try it.
Lucky guess.
- Siler, are you in there?
- Yes, sir.
We'll get you out.
Step away from the blast door.
Yes, sir.
Get this table over.
- Use two of those things.
- Sir?
It's a blast door.
Hang on, Siler.
Fire in the hole.
Down!
Whoa.
Siler?
- Thank you, sir.
- I expect to be put in your will.
- Already in it, sir.
- OK, that's weird.
Oh, crap.
Sensors are picking up
multiple ships exiting hyperspace.
They're firing on Baal's forces.
It is the replicators.
Now this one.
That one took us in the wrong direction.
All-knowing, huh?
- What's the matter?
- My ships are under attack.
A replicator-controlled fleet
is encroaching on the planet.
- Running low on ammo, sir.
- Fall back!
Instruct all of our vessels
to target the replicator ships.
Better to let them destroy each other.
If the replicators prevail
and gain control of the weapon on Dakara,
all that we have fought for is lost.
General, 15 minutes
to safe detonation conditions.
Yeah. You know, Walter,
right now we're having
a slightly difficult time getting outta here.
Relay this to General Hammond.
The second he can pull the trigger
on that nuke, do it.
- Do you read?
- Yes, sir.
And have that chopper
that's waiting for us leave now.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir?
You see those bugs going into that hatch?
Yes. Think getting outta the base
is their primary goal?
It's a fairly safe bet.
They're going to the surface.
Leaving the only other way
outta here accessible.
And here.
1.32. We're almost there.
My ship has lost life support on several
levels. I cannot maintain my transmission.
We've almost got it. Thanks for the help.
Good luck.
- That was just creepy.
- Keep working.
Go.
Siler, can we dial out?
- I'm working on it, sir.
- Ten minutes to detonation.
Shields down. Weapons systems offline.
Reroute power to sublight engines.
Evasive manoeuvres.
They are too fast. We cannot evade them.
- How's it going in there?
- Not well.
Same here.
Grenade!
Variable off by 0.98.
What's that?
- Hurry.
- I've almost got it. Just a little more time.
I don't think we have it.
Siler!
Sorry, sir, I'm trying.
Got you now.
Huh.
That's odd.
The replicator ship just... stopped.
Sensors are indicating that all of
the replicator ships have ceased activity.
Colonel Carter. Have you
successfully activated the weapon?
Not yet, but the replicators
down here just froze.
- Dad?
- Almost there.
There are so many, aren't there?
Too many for your mind to handle.
It's taking all of your concentration
just to control them.
Well, that was too good to last.
Dad, they're on the move again!
- 0.76.
- Do it!
Incoming wormhole?
Enemy ship is in range.
It is powering weapons.
We cannot survive another hit.
- Dad.
- I'm all right.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
- You did it.
- Well, Selmak deserves a little credit.
OK.
Most of it.
All replicator-controlled ships
are dormant.
Prepare enough squads to board them.
Reclaim them in the name of their god.
Yes, my lord.
- We are being hailed.
- On screen.
Surrender now
and you will be granted mercy.
You are hardly in any position
to be making such ridiculous demands.
- You are surrounded.
- You are incorrect.
It is, in fact, you that is
surrounded by free Jaffa.
Behold your false god.
- Any more word from Teal'c?
- Yes, sir.
Although Baal got away,
the fact he turned tail
made the victory the turning point
Teal'c and Bra'tac were hoping for.
Jaffa from all over the galaxy
are with them.
Well, vive la révolution.
A significant fleet is securing Dakara.
Hopefully, with our weapons, they can
turn the tide against Anubis' soldiers.
It looks like the Jaffa
might finally win their freedom.
- It's about time.
- Yes, sir.
- I heard from Thor.
- How's he doing?
Great. He sends us all his congratulations
and says that he will drop by for a visit
as soon as his consciousness
has been downloaded into a new body.
- That just never gets old, does it?
- Apparently not.
Carter, did you notice if the replicators
where you were happened to...
stop in the middle of everything?
- Yeah. It was really strange. They just...
- Froze.
It bought us time to calibrate the weapon.
Any idea why that happened?
You think Daniel
had something to do with it?
- I don't know.
- If he was on board that replicator ship...
Carter.
We don't know anything.
No, sir.
Anything else?
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke
ENHOH