It's Valentine's week,
when the Greendale human being
is the cupid being,
delivering your gift
to that special someone.
But remember, Cupid's face
is magic marker on nylon,
so love is not only blind but
also dizzy and a little belligerent.
I'm chaperoning tomorrow's dance.
You should come.
Maybe your study buds'll go.
What's the blonde's name,
Bitter, Butter... Beetlejuice?
She says Valentine's day
ritualizes a connection
between affection and candy so girls
can learn the ropes of prostitution.
- Translation: No date.
- I'm gonna join you at that dance.
But as a novice boyfriend,
could I get a map of the minefield
known as
women's Valentine expectations?
Every day of the year,
I want you to do what makes you happy.
I'm gonna be happy spending the night
with an insatiable statistics professor.
Jeff, it's the registrar's office.
Seems you were wrong about
paying tuition with airline miles.
We're gonna need a check...
Message deleted.
Jeff Winger.
I am calling you.
You're probably... Whatever.
So...
wassup?
It's the Cupid being.
Now it has arrows.
That's safe.
It's from the cook with the long beard
in the cafeteria.
I guess when he said,
I'm gonna git you,
He meant chocolates.
A flower from Vaughn.
He's on a vision quest.
You got something, Abed?
Another muffin basket
from another actress
- to be in my film.
- Does that work?
Meryl Streep has two Oscars
because of her baking.
That's sarcasm, but I forgot to inflect.
This sounds way more like sarcasm.
Inflection is so interesting.
That big bag, at the bottom,
is that for me?
Anything in there for Troy?
Troy Barnes?
Barnes, Troy?
Who cares about getting things?
It destroys the meaning
of Valentine's day:
- The birth of saint Valentines.
- Good.
Now it has arrows.
That's safe.
- Sorry I'm late.
- That's okay.
- You look very early.
- I'm really late.
- Yes, you are.
- Yeah, see you later.
Can I get you something?
Water, smelling salts,
alibi for Cobain's suicide?
No, but you can help yourself
to a shorter forehead,
a non-keebler nose, and shutting up.
That stings.
I mean, not the words.
The clouds of bourbon vapor
forming them.
A girlfriend from my anarchist days
was in town and we drank.
Everything.
And then you said,
"I should call Jeff."
'cause the first thing I do
when I'm having fun
is think about... Jeff Winger.
I am calling you.
You're probably...
Whatever.
So wassup?
A drunk dial.
So much subtext, so much intrigue.
So much of
what the kids are calling B.C.I.
That's... booty call implication.
- What happened to Britta?
- Justice.
Having spent the year
denying her attraction to me
just to be alternative,
Britta called me.
At 3:00 a.m.
Just to ask: "What's up?"
A drunk dial?
Was there B.C.I.?
- Booty call with a capital "B."
- This can't be good.
No biggie.
We give crap all the time.
That's the point. What crap can
she give you when you hold the cards?
You've shifted balance, like in a sitcom
when a character sees another naked.
Is that really a sitcom staple?
I have no idea what I'm talking about.
I'm Abed, I never watch TV.
- Feygnasse Team -
.:: La Fabrique ::.
1x16: Communication Studies
Now we all know that in english,
the rooster says:
En espanol...
the gallo says,
What? I'm teaching.
I knew you were holding back.
It's from the girl I'm dating.
I met her in biology.
She was looking for geology
and misread the sign.
Yeah, I said,
"we do not study countries in here."
Yeah, she's...
She's dumb, but...
- But sweet.
- Mine's from Danielle. She's a...
A lovely lady in my marketing class.
We're sleeping together.
They sound like very lucky ladies.
They're not made up.
What's going on?
My bullcrap meter's going crazy.
It's these presents
you've obviously sent to yourselves
to pretend you have girlfriends.
That's ridiculous.
This is obviously your handwriting,
Mr. Tremor.
Yours is signed, "love, Troy"?
This is the most pathetic thing
I've ever seen in the classroom.
Look at him over there.
Cutting the gristle off his steak
as ruthlessly as he cut off
Troy and Pierce's dignity.
Now he's eating the gristle.
I'm so sick of Chang.
Tearing people down,
making them feel horrible.
Somebody needs to humiliate him
like he humiliated our boys.
Moustache.
Get me a juice box.
- Now!
- And that somebody is us.
You can vomit into this food,
cause it already smells like it.
Totally.
My law firm went on a retreat
at Disney World once,
and I got so drunk
that I got into a fight
with animatronic Ben Franklin.
- Why are you telling me this?
- The point is that when I'm sober,
I don't secretly hate Ben Franklin
or even think about him.
So you drunk dialing me,
- I mean, it's not a big deal.
- You're pitying me now.
- You're acting really weird.
- I'll talk to you in class.
Leave me alone until then.
What is going on here?
My doody meter's going crazy.
Cut, cut, cut.
Leo, I'm not feeling it. I wanna believe
you're holding a doody meter.
The problem is not me.
It's you and your stupid script.
Idiot!
The anger.
Use it.
A Papa John's commercial,
and he thinks he's Christian Bale.
You were right.
Britta is totally weird around me.
Like I saw her naked.
Resident premise. Tony saw Angela naked
on opening credits of Who's The Boss?
Did Tony do something to fix that?
Don't know.
Could'nt get past the opening credits.
When Chandler saw Rachel on Friends
to get even, she saw Chandler's penis.
I'll show Britta my penis.
Don't waste my time.
I lose my Chang to cub scouts in 20 min.
So what? To even the score,
I have to drunk dial her?
Isn't that absurdly simplistic?
Would it even work?
Maybe.
No room for error.
She'd have to believe it was real.
Have you ever acted drunk before?
I can totally do it.
I'm fine.
I can drive.
I can totally drive right now.
Give me my keys.
- That's enough...
- Hold on a second.
Seriously, give me my keys.
That's a wrap, people.
Be at my place at 4:00
so we can work on this.
No, I can't do that.
Here's why.
Dumbest idea ever.
Britta's defining weakness.
She cuts and runs.
You do this half-assed and fail,
she may leave. And we lose her.
Not gonna happen on my watch.
Deal breaker. Saddle up.
Sorry I lost my cool.
I just quit smoking.
Kid's gonna be a star.
He's a young "the asian guy" from Lost.
Try it again.
Come on.
You're a big guy.
Action.
Your call got my thinkin'
and thinkin' got me drinkin'.
- That was terrible.
- What?
I can get drunk alone
if that's what helps people act.
That's your problem.
You've been acting your whole life.
Time to pass that act up,
and find the actor playing you.
They're gonna love you
in California.
Do you like Britta?
- Sure. Who doesn't?
- Over half the people that meet her.
They could be put off
by her mannequin face.
And her Jodie Foster severity.
- But you're different.
- She's no barrel of monkeys.
She wants everyone to be honest,
but she lies to herself.
She's seen the world,
but doesn't get it.
She fights more about stuff that doesn't
matter than a YouTube comment section.
She's passionate, which...
I find stupid.
- But entertaining.
- Attractive.
There was only attraction at first
'cause she bothered to play hard to get.
- I'm happy with Michelle.
- Slater is low maintenance.
- The lowest.
- Britta's irritating, impossible,
unpredictable, and didn't like you
so it felt useless to like her.
Slater likes you how you are,
expect nothing, you're safe from change.
And passion.
Watch it.
What? A phony drunk dial soaked
in phony pity that insults Britta more?
Or...
a believable performance
informed by feeling?
I am sure you're a good director,
but a horrible drinking buddy.
I can't feel things
with you studying me
like a beige praying mantis.
Right.
- I thought you never drank.
- Scorsese drank with de Niro.
Not for me.
For the audience.
All right, class.
Turn to page...
Looks like the law firm of seacrest
and slumdog's taking the day off.
Another special delivery
from Troy and Pierce's imaginary lovers?
That one's for me.
All right.
It's from Princeton.
They want to make me associate professor
of the Spanish department?
They're telling me I can name my price?
Oh, my god.
At Princeton?
Come on!
You two idiots
really thought I'd fall for this?
This is your pathetic attempt
to punish me for humiliating you.
- But we didn't do it.
- Save it!
As punishment,
because you two obviously
don't have any girlfriends,
you'll escort me
to the Valentine's dance wearing...
elegant ladies pantsuits.
Yeah, right.
You'll do it
or you'll fail my class.
- You can't do that.
- Have you met me?
I mean it.
Tonight,
you are my bitches.
Holy crap.
It's 3:00.
What happened?
The last thing I remember is...
you were dancing like that girl
in that movie...
- Kids in Detention?
- Breakfast Club.
Dear god.
- What have you done to me?
- Wait.
Did I call Britta?
- Where's my phone?
- Got it.
You made two outgoing calls.
One to Britta,
one to your girlfriend.
I don't remember.
Neither do I.
I don't remember the name of the girl
in The Breakfast Club.
Mary.
Margaret.
Molly ringworm.
You broke me.
I still can't believe i'm a size 14.
I know that 12's a little tight,
but I could have pulled it off.
You guys
really going through with this?
We have to.
He'll fail us.
We'll find out who wrote that letter.
We have leads.
It was written
on fake Princeton letterhead.
Whoever wrote it worked at Princeton,
ran out of stationary,
didn't have time to go to the store.
You guys...
What?
Women's sizes run slimmer.
I'm sure you're a 12
everywhere that it counts.
I'll take every little
victory I can get right now.
You look about ready
to marry Courtney Love.
That's the reverse
of my zinger from before.
Please stop shouting. All right.
I feel like that person in the TV show.
Do you remember
calling me last night?
Why?
Are we cool?
Have a seat, Drunky Brewster.
Let's study.
- Balance restored, I guess.
- Movie reference.
Hey, there.
Happy Valentine's day.
- I've been calling you.
- Yeah, I know.
I just let it go to voice mail
in case you had the wrong number again.
Elaborate?
You don't remember calling me
and hanging realizing I wasn't Britta?
I guess not.
I was trying to call Britain
to order you toffees.
Now that may sound dumb,
but I needed to open with it
to make the truth less ridiculous.
Two nights ago,
Britta drunk dialed me
and it embarrassed
her and made her sad.
And the only way for her
to get her power back
was for me to get believably drunk
and leave her an equally
embarrassing message.
It sure seems
like you and Britta are friends
the way my mom's pool cleaner
was my uncle.
- You had sex with her?
- Not even a little.
What doesn't make sense,
you did all this work
to put a smile on her face,
but can't pick up ice cream
for Law & Order night
cause it feels too marriage-y.
First of all, chubby hubby?
Could you pick a scarier flavor?
Let's talk about this later.
I need to chaperone...
something.
There he is...
I thought I'd be embarrassed,
now I'm just scared.
I'm seriously reconsidering how
much I want this language credit.
Remember what we said.
Never let him see us cry.
Right.
One,
two...
Wait!
Keep your coats on.
We're the ones that sent the letter.
What?
You work at Princeton?
We were mad at him
for humiliating you.
Nice fix,
tweedle dum and even tweedler dum.
We're gonna tell Chang the truth.
And we'll pay the price.
Wait.
We can't make you do that.
He's right.
First we gotta
get out of these pantsuits
so you can put em on.
Look, Pierce,
this whole thing started because...
you and I were ashamed
we didn't have ladies caring about us.
Good news is, we do.
The bad news is...
That it makes it our
manly duty to protect them tonight.
That's nice. But we really
can't let you do that...
No, he's right.
He's right.
Step aside.
Let's handle this like men.
Oh, ladies...
- They're gonna be okay, right?
- Get in my Mercedes.
Just look away, baby.
Just look away.
Looking for someone?
Slater.
Very funny.
You know, when you called me last night
and invited me to the dance,
I was shocked.
And...
thrilled.
Are you okay?
No, look.
I'm sorry.
I don't...
Don't remember asking you to the dance.
I don't remember anything.
Now Slater knows
about all the drunk dialing
and I'm in the dog house.
And if she finds out about this,
it's over.
So again, I am sorry.
I am so, so sorry.
And you are messing with me right now,
aren't you?
I knew you didn't remember anything
from that phone call last night.
You got dressed up...
just to see me sweat?
Believe me, you're worth it.
- Just chaperoning. Enjoy the dance.
- Wait.
What's left to say?
I don't know.
I do.
He said it last night.
So look,
I am really into Michelle,
I don't wanna screw it up.
She's a perfect
girlfriend.
And I want you to be as happy as me
cause you're, like,
my favorite friend.
I'm sorry.
Abed just made a turtle face.
In his defense,
Abed's turtle face is really funny.
Thanks, Britta.
Yeah, thanks.
That was the first 20 s
of a 40 min message.
Very informative.
Happy Valentine's day.
Perfect boyfriend.
Yeah. That's me.
Man, I cannot wait to get out
of these ridiculous outfits.
I know.
What you doing?
I'm parked here.
Come on.
What the hell is this?
- We're gonna get frozen yogurt.
- I'm not gay, man.
- They close in seven minutes.
- I could have driven you.
You said he hated fro-yo.
Just drive.