Previously on Nip/Tuck...
Sean McNamara, you are
the new star of Hearts'n Scalpels!
Sean McNamara is sexy and vulnerable,
so you're gonna be seeing a lot more
scenes like this Hearts'n Scalpels.
I made some fruitcake.
It's sort of a peace offering.
So tell me, what exactly does
a fluffer of your caliber do?
I got N.G.U.
That means I gave it to you.
Look me in the eyes and tell me
you're not attracted to me.
- I am attracted to you.
- I love her,
and there's nothing you can do about it.
- Ava's a man.
- Want a drink?
You got a goddamn dick.
I'm not gay! OK?! I'm not into that!
Is that a swastika on it?
I'm not a nazi, Matt, but I am a purist.
The Tech works, Matt.
You just gotta trust it.
Married?
Matt and I exchanged
our vows 3 days ago.
I never loved you, Matt.
I told you I did, but I lied.
I'm Rachel Ben Natan,
your burn rehabilitation counselor.
I'm here to assist you.
Season 5 Episode 13
August Walden
Hey, listen to this.
"Hearts'n Scalpels
has sunk to a new low.
What was once a mildly
interesting melodrama
has now replaced its sole
charismatic player, Aidan Stone,
with the Milquetoast Dr. Sean Mcnamara.
While Stone does the requisite
Hollywood star turn in rehab,
Mcnamara ruins the Rome that he built.
He's so dull as Dr. Peter Casey,
the best thing I can say
is that watching him
is a cure for insomnia,
or maybe he's the answer
to global warming,
for soon televisions
around the nation will go dark."
Oh, my God. I am so glad
that I took that
out of the lobby
before Sean got to see it.
Let me look at this thing.
"And I'm not yet speaking of
Mcnamara's abilities as an actor.
I can't get past the face,
or should I say cardboard box
on shoulders, a puddle of muddy water,
a jellyfish without the sting?
My only wish is that
he turn that scalpel on himself.
Perhaps a scar could bring
some character to that
brown paper bag Mcnamara calls a head."
- What are you reading?
- Oh, eh... Nothing.
Um, is your 10:00 here?
August Walden's review
of Hearts'n Scalpels
in Entertainment Weekly.
Guess he doesn't like me very much.
You are very handsome, Sean,
and Walden doesn't like anybody.
He said that James Gandolfini
looked like a scrotum with legs.
If you're gonna be a TV star, buddy boy,
you're gonna have to get a thick skin
about this kind of stuff.
Yeah, you're right.
- I'll see you in the consult.
- All right.
- What?
- You know what.
Oh, come on, man.
Who gives a crap what some
jealous loser wannabe says?
If it makes you feel better,
just get a good review
and read it 10 times over.
That's what I do on the
odd occasion some sexy lady
declines to do
the horizontal shuffle with me.
I fill my dance card with 10 more.
You've never had anyone tell you
your head looks like a brown paper bag.
True.
Oh, come on. You're a good-looking guy.
I'll take this consult.
You go get yourself some ice cream
or a lollipop or somethin'.
Transcript: swsub.com
Synchro:
_/Yellow Sub\_
Metalmarco::ITA-SA::
She was over at our house
the other day, you know.
Falafel face?
Yeah. She and Matt were locked
in his room for a couple of hours.
"Locked in his room" locked in his room?
Sounded like it.
I didn't hear any talking.
Oh. Hey, guys.
What are you guys doin'over there?
These are all the surgeries
we've performed on Rachel.
6 of them. Can you tell a difference?
A little.
You're bein'too generous.
We have relieved most of her pain,
given her cheekbones
some definition, and restored
about 60% of her sense of smell.
Otherwise, she looks exactly the same.
What's your point?
The point is she's never gonna
look any better than this.
- Right. And looks are all that matter.
- Of course not.
I'm just gonna say it, all right?
I don't care if she shits solid gold.
You can't underestimate the burden that
comes with dating somebody like this.
You two are unbelievable.
She nursed me through my recovery.
She made me feel I was
actually worth something.
- Are you wearing rubbers with her?
- Why?
Because you're a perfect
catch for a girl like this.
She forgets to take her pill and you're
trapped for the rest of your life.
- You guys are such assholes.
- Matt, wait.
Matt, you were vulnerable
when you met her.
You just got out of one
bad relationship.
We don't want you
getting buried in another one.
No, you just don't want your son dating
some girl who's walking proof
that you two aren't gods,
that you can't make
everyone look perfect.
You guys have been
messin'with people's faces
for so long that I don't even think
you know what ugly looks like anymore.
Miss Lowell, tell me
what you don't like about yourself.
You're sweet.
No one's ever pretended
not to notice before.
But call me Emme.
If there's one thing
I've learned in this business,
It's not to assume.
So tell me, you want a nose job?
When I first saw your picture online,
I didn't think you'd be so funny.
I like it.
Makes the plane trip out here
even more worthwhile.
So where are you from?
South carolina?
Please. I'm a Jersey girl,
born and raised.
Guess we both have the same
sense of humor, huh?
Actually, I'm from Cleveland, Georgia.
It's a tiny, little town in the
smoky mountains up north.
This is my first time travelin'away
from home, if youcan believe it.
I think I'm afraid of flying, too.
Yet you got on a plane
for the first time ever
and came all the way
out here for a consult.
Why?
You're the doctor who set up
the Hedda Grubman fund, right?
Well, I don't have a lot of money,
and when I went on Google
and typed in "free plasticsurgery,"
your name came up and said
you do cases like mine for no pay.
Well, you know, where
birth defects are involved.
Technically what you have
is called naevus flammeus.
It's where the, uh,
deep dilated capillaries, uh,
cause the skin to turn a reddish purple.
It's really more of birthmark
than a skin defect.
It's actually quite common.
One in 3,000 newborns have it.
Not like this, they don't.
The procedure involves
several laser treatments.
I know you flew all the way out here,
but I really have a very long
waiting list right now.
A waitin'list? I've waited 24 years.
I spent all I had just
To get out here, and then
the cab ride from the airport
cost almost as much as the plane.
You ever read The Scarlet Letter,
Dr. Troy?
In college, yes.
That's what my mom used to call this,
her scarlet letter,
Said it was the shame she had
to bear for havin'me
with some one-night stand.
But it's not just her.
I've never been a ccepted by anyone
my whole life because of this face.
That's the real reason
I never left home until now.
And now that I'm here,
I can't go back lookin'like this.
I won't.
You know, when August Walde
gave me my first review,
I ate an entire box of those,
even the kinds with sprinkles,
which I don't even love,
and a half a tray of sausages.
I was so bloated I couldn't
get my costume zipped
After my lunchtime coma.
It was ridiculous.
So this is what this does?
Rips people to shreds?
Yeah. Let's see. Uh,"
the dreary Kate Tinsley brings
to mind a sullen coonhound."
Uh,"her body resembles
that of a butternut squash,
and her speech pattern makes me wonder
if she hasn't yet swallowed
her breakfast kibble."
Yeah. Emblazoned on my brain forever.
I hope you've got some of your
good reviews memorized as well.
Yeah, well, the good ones, you forget.
The bad ones are forever. Ahem.
You learn to live with it, you know.
I mean, being in
the spotlight, you, um...
You're asking people to weigh in
on what you look like.
What you can avoid is choosing a lover
who looks at you with a critic's eye.
So, where does this guy live?
Who knows? Maybe one night
I'll get hammered
and show up at his door
and take him out.
Actually he always hangs out
at that coffee shop over on Riverside.
Sits there all day long
typing on his computer.
Of course no one wants to confront him.
Everyone's so scared
of his scathing tongue.
You know, you seem like
you're in a good place.
I'm sorry about everything.
I hope we can be friends.
Yeah, we're good.
On one condition. You actuallydo it.
Go to the coffee shop.
Rip the guy a new one
on behalf of actors everywhere
and record it on your cellphone
so I can watch it over and over again.
- It's not really my style.
- Really?
Milquetoast? "His face
looks like a cardboard box
on shoulders,
a," um, "puddle ofmuddy water."
Um, "jellyfish
Without the sting."
You gonna let that go?
Puddle of muddy water.
Here's your double espresso,
mr. Walden.
August Walden?
Have we met?
Not officially.
I'm the puddle of muddy water which
can only evoke yawns
from the audience.
Yes.
And a memorable appearance off-screen
as well as on.
You know,
I came here
with the intention of getting
some sort of apology from you
for the way you just attack people,
But now I get it.
Now I understand why you do it.
I do it because i am paid to advise
the general public
of what and whom is worthy
of their attention and admiration.
Just cut the shit, will you?
You're so eaten up with jealousy,
so full of self-contempt because of
your own extraordinary ugliness,
You have to make others pay.
I shouldn't be asking you
for an apology.
I should be apologizing to you for
what you have to go through every day
Looking the way you do.
If only making other people feel badly
could make you feel better.
Hey, baby, it's Christian.
Just confirming lunch today.
Thought you'd gone.
I would have.
Who was she, someone you picked up
at the carwash, the drugstore?
Gas station.
You really don't give
a shit about me at all, do you?
For years, i've fantasized
about being with you.
It's just
In my head, you were so perfect.
But in life, with all this messy
pain and illness
and goddamn regret, it's just...
It's not the same,
is it?
I'm sorry. I can't change who I am.
I tried.
Yeah, you've been in my head
for a long time, too,
always there tempting me.
Only, in my head,
you were beautiful,
deep down, you had a kind,
caring soul.
And only now do I see just
how ugly you really are.
Oh, my God.
What a mistake I've made.
I had a second chance with Olivia...
Kind, caring
in sickness and in health, you know.
And i've blown it,
wasting all my time on you.
It's not like I don't love you.
I just want us to be friends.
Friends?
You have donea lot of things
in your time, Christian,
but to do this to me now,
when I need you so much.
Maybe one day I'll be able to forgive,
but I know that I'll never forget.
Tell me what youdon't like
about yourself,
Although it's sadly obvious.
I thought it would only befair to write
a review of my appearance.
I'd like to hear it.
"In all my years, I've never met
an uglier human being"
"than August Walden."
"Though calling him human could be
construed as an insult to the phylum."
Please, continue.
"Below the mating caterpillars
Walden calls brows,"
"two extremely far sighted eyes droop"
"like a basset hound's
under the pull of gravity."
"In fact, his entire face looks
as if it's been pulled"
"and stretched by a hyperactive toddler
playing with Silly putty."
All right, look, the other day
I was may be a bit too harsh.
- If i'm the reason you're here...
- You are the reason i'm here,
I am thankful for your words.
You were right
and frankly the first person
to say it to my...
horrific face.
I have been isolating myself
for years behind this...
Halloween mask,
Scaring away everyone with
whom i come in contact,
In particular,
a young lady of whom i have grown fond,
a lithe
beauty of a barista at the cafe.
Every day, doctor, I am there
trying to connect with her,
Yet unable to hold her gaze
for more than a mere moment.
Can you help me connect
with her, dr. McNamara?
What are you doing?
I told you to stay in bed.
Since the surgery was free,
I figured i had to do something
to pay you back.
I cleaned the bathroom, too.
Someone does you a favor,
you do one back.
Well, take a break.
Sit down.
I need to see how you're healing.
Don't you think it'd be better
if you found a plastic surgeon
you didn't just trash
in your magazine?
If I did, I couldn'tcorrect
the error of my ways.
After the surgery, i will happily write
another critique
of Hearts'n Scalpels
and specifically you,
which I can assure you
you will appreciate more than the last.
Maybe my face isn't a cardboard box
on shoulders?
I was thinking more
along the lines of
"reminiscent of a young Gary Cooper."
You know what the kids used to
call me in school?
Swamp thing. Isn't that awful?
The boys wouldn't go near me
in High School 'cause of
how I looked. I never even had
a real boyfriend,
Though I did meet
this one guy online.
Somethin'wrong?
No. It's...
Come here.
Oh, my god.
There are ethical questions
to me performing your surgery,
Conflicts of interest.
If you have an opening, doctor,
I am ready to go
under the knife immediately.
We have an opening at 2:00.
I could really usesome lipstick,
couldn't i?
Emme, you're beautiful.
Hey, Mattie.
- How you doin'?
- I'm doin'all right.
Nice flowers.
Thanks. They're for my girlfriend.
She's in recovery.
Emme, this is Matt.
- Hi.
Emme just had a port stain removed
from her face.
Doesn't she look great?
Sure. Congratulations.
We're going to Neiman's to celebrate.
You should come with, we can have lunch.
Yeah, no, thanks.
I'm go **************
Fun.
Emme's new in town, so maybe
you guys should **********
and could try the sights.
- Stop it, Christian
- Stop what?
Look, Emme,
you look great,
and I'm really happy for you,
but contrary to some people opinion,
I have a girlfriend who I love very much
"Learning Hebrew."
Yeah. I take courts
at the jewish community center.
Jesus.
You'll take an of kool-aid
a girl feeds you, huh?
It was nice meeting you.
Honey?
How are you? I've been so worried.
Oh, my god. You look so sick.
I know how terrible I look.
And it's funny, you know, because
I've always relied on a certain beauty,
and it's really superficial, I know,
But without it,
I just... I don't even know who I am.
Just don't get upset, please.
I think you're the most
beautiful person I have ever known
in every single way.
I've really missed you, Julia.
I'm not gonna let anything happen
to you. You're my angel.
I've been having
an affair with Christian.
It's over, finally
and for the last time.
I feel like I've been
in a fever dream.
Well, a nightmare, really.
I just don't know
how you can forgive me,
let alone love me.
No use getting angry.
We gotta put that energy into action.
We're gonna send that hair
to a lab in Westbury, Virginia.
They've made some amazing
diagnostics for me in the past.
I have been to every doctor in L.A.,
and no one seems to know
what's wrong with me.
Western doctors.
God, they all have their narrow,
little focus.
No one's looking at the big picture.
We're gonna find out
what's wrong with you.
I promise.
Julia, would you like
honey in your tea?
No, thanks.
You know, you...
you really have been a doll, Eden.
I know we've had our differences,
but frankly,
You've been the only one
who's lifted a finger for me
since Olivia hasn't been here.
I know I act up sometimes,
but you're sick.
Kind of takes the fun out of it.
There's one more piece of fruitcake
in the fridge. You want me to get it?
Sure. It seems to be the only thing
I can keep down.
Follicle Analysis
Hydrargyria, exposure to
high dosages of mercury
FDA exposure limit: 1 PPM.
Test samples contain 6 PPM.
disease damages, nervous system,
kidney function
from ingestion of contaminated foods.
I really have to bake you
another of these.
Who knew you loved fruitcake so much?
Don't be shy.
You're the only one who eats it.
I think i'll...
take it to my room for later.
Ready for my close-up, Dr. McNamara?
Sometimes we make
miraculous improvements
with a single surgery,
and in othermore serious cases,
we hope for incremental improvements.
It may take a few more surgeries
than I anticipated.
- I'm not going to do any more.
- Why not? I thought you...
No, Matt was the one who kept
pushing and pushing, but
- my plans have changed.
- Sean, our 11:00's early.
- She's in my office.
- Dr. Troy,
in case I don't see you again, I just
wanted to thank you for all you've done.
I'm leaving, going back to Israel.
Mattie didn't mention
anything about that.
I haven't told him yet.
He's a nice boy,
but he's very confused.
I don't understand. You and Matt,
- he thinks...
- I know what he thinks.
He thinks I am the answer,
that judaism is the answer.
He goes from one thing to another.
The answer's always out there somewhere.
He needs to go inside.
That's the only place it is.
Don't you think you should
be telling Matt about this?
Tell me what?
We have a consultation.
Stick around after, and we'll talk, OK?
You look good.
What's wrong?
I'm going home, Matt,
back to Tel Aviv.
Why? I don't understand.
It is not right between us, Matt.
I just...
I don't love you.
I thought what we shared...
Was lovely, yes,
but I'm not attracted to you.
I'm so sorry, but I'm not.
You're not attracted to me?
Attraction has nothing to do
with what the person looks like.
It's an inner chemistry.
It's there, or it isn't.
I'm sorry, but...
have you looked in a mirror lately?
I know what you must think.
You think because I am not beautiful,
I have no right to be picky.
Perhaps you thought
you could avoid getting hurt
by choosing someone
too desperate to reject you.
No. You know what?
Screw you, OK? I mean,
you and all your bullshit
about how looks don't matter,
like you're some poster girl
for inner strength.
You won't find the parts of yourself
that are missing in me.
You need to look inside.
Only then will you be able
to express love instead of need.
Need? I don't need you, Rachel.
I felt sorry for you,
Because the only chemical reaction
you're gonna get from a man is pity.
Here. These are for you. Enjoy 'em.
... Dream come true.
I'm not... No, you're the one
living with regrets,
not me.
Hey, everything all right?
My mother. She can be a little,
overprotective, I guess.
Do you wanna go grab some lunch?
There was no way I thought
you could do that again.
I didn't think I could
do it again either.
Man, I have never felt a connection
like this before. It's amazing.
It's like we just fit together.
Our bodies, our skin.
It's amazing.
God, I always wanted
my first time to be special like this.
Your first time?
I just took your virginity?
You're not upset, are you?
Upset?
Are you kiddin'me? I'm honored.
I'm honored.
These last days
have just been so amazing.
Let's see. First, I met my father,
and then I got my face fixed,
- and then I met you.
- You met your father?
And I look just like him, I think.
And we have the same sense of humor.
It's amazing,
- just amazing.
- Who is he?
My plastic surgeon, Dr. Troy.
They still saved my same table
for me, dr. McNamara.
Now I'm crossing my fingers
that a certain someone
- bothers me constantly.
- Yeah. Where is she?
- She's very pretty.
- The apple of my eye.
Welcome back, Mr. Walden.
Almost didn't recognize you.
We've got a fresh batch
of pumpkin muffins today.
And by the way, thanks.
You changed my life.
Is that so?
Well, I was in an episode
of NCIS that you reviewed.
You said that you'd rather clean
cat piss out of the carpet
than watch another moment
of my acting,
that my portrayal
of a kidnapping rapist
was worse than the crime committed.
Then you're lucky
you still have this job.
You killed my dream.
Just when I was startin'to
pick up momentum,
my recurring role
on the show was dropped.
My agent left me. I don't make
enough money here to make rent.
I have to go back to Oregon
and live with my mother.
And I am to blame?
You need to take responsibility
for your lack of artistry,
not to mention insight.
I do. I take full responsibility
for my career and for this.
OK, so according to California law,
what we did was technically
not illegal and
not that crazy either, OK?
Here. Come here. Look.
What's this?
It's a blog devoted to couples
who are related.
"Like everyone else here, my brother
and I are not just having sex,"
"we are in love."
"Tom and I have been together
for two years and feel that"
"because we are related, have a stronger
bond than any other non-incest couple."
"For us, incest is the best
of all worlds."
Yeah. They go on to talk about
this scientific study that was done
showing that, you know, siblings
who are raised together develop
this innate sexual repulsion, but
you know, when they're
separated andr aised apart
like us, uh, you know,
they don't have that.
So there was no way we'd feel
like what we did was wrong.
And apparently in other
cultures around the world,
they don't have
a problem with it either.
But mother nature has a say.
You get freak babies
if you inbreed, right?
We used a condom.
It's OK. We're fine.
- I was born damaged like that.
- No.
You don't know how hard it is,
how people look at you.
- I don't want that to happen again.
- It won't. I promise.
Does that mean we have to stop?
'Cause you don't want to?
Oh, man.
This is wrong.
Look,
only if your mom's right, OK?
What if she's wrong?
What if we're not related at all?
It's all gonna be fine.
Mattie. Emme.
How long you guys been here?
About an hour.
Emme's never seen the ocean before,
so I thought this'd be
the best place to check it out.
Great.
Well, you guys are gettin'to know each
other, so, I'll get out of your way.
Actually, can I talk
to you for a second?
Of course.
- She's a great girl, huh? Huh?
- Yeah.
Look. There's somethin'that
you need to know,
and it may come as a bit of a shock.
Sure.
Emme...
Emme forgot her birth control
at her house, and...
- We need an emergency prescription.
- Of course. Of course.
I'm just glad you're being safe.
Pretty great what happened
to Walden, huh?
No. It's not pretty great.
The man suffered second
and third-degree burns.
Gonna need 4 or 5 painful operations.
His sight might be compromised forever.
Jeez. Mr. Sensitive.
What, you don't think
he deserves it just a little bit?
No. I don't.
And that kid who did it is going
to jail, So it's not a happy ending.
Hello, darlings.
May I join the wake?
You have read it, right?
Read what?
Well, I never take these things
too seriously, but...
We were just skewered
in the Los Angeles Times.
Perhaps you shouldn't see it.
Give it backwhen you're done.
And, darlings,
don't let this affect today's work.
Sean, you are not flat and monotone,
and, Kate, darling,
you are not... "A lumpy zero."
- I'll split it with you.
- Get your own.
It's the only thing
keeping me from suicide.
I see.
Thank you.
Hey, Julia.
I made some of my healing tea.
Think it's really startin'to work.
I feel like you're gettin'better.
Don't you?
You drink it.
Why would I drink it?
You're the one who's been sick.
Thanks to you.
I don't know what you mean, Julia.
Don't you?
You've been poisoning me
with all your soups
and the teas and that fruitcake.
I think whatever you have
is starting to seep into your brain.
Yes, it has.
Mercury poisoning does that to you.
It kills the organs
and destroys the brain cells.
I just got off the phone
with the toxicology lab.
I sent them
that last piece of fruitcake.
It had an 80% contamination
rate for mercury.
I have proof of
what you've been doing to me.
You made a mistake
in underestimating me, Eden.
You are going to jail.
You area sick, sick girl,
and you need to be locked up!
I've had fun.
You know,
watching you slowly
get weaker and weaker.
I couldn't wait every day
to come home and...
serve you a cup of tea,
bowl of soup.
Pouring the mercury
in was the highlight, really,
knowing it would eat you away
from the inside out.
I could not wait
to literally remove
your pathetic, whing presence
from the people that I love the most
in this world... My mother, Sean.
But I can't argue
with proof, now, can I?
You've out smarted me, Julia.
You win.
I have to pay for what I've done.
I'll go pack my bags, and we can wait
for my mother to get home,
and I... I'll confess everything
to her and to the police.
It's OK. I'm gonna confess. I'm...
I'm sorry.
You really should lock up your firearms
and not leave 'em in a bedside
table drawer, you stupid bitch.
You know, you were right
about one thing, Julia.
I made a horrible mistake.
Mercury takes too damn long.
_/Yellow Sub\_
contact@yellowsubteam.com