Previously on Nip/Tuck...
That's her.
Wow. She's like a little...
little lion cub.
We're doing this. Superior arterial
hemorrhage. He's going into shock.
That is the way you play a leading man.
He has the courage of his convictions,
yet he is classy.
He is always classy.
We've been to an internist,
a neurologist, a gastroenterologist.
Nobody thinks you're sick.
You're hiding behind these symptoms
because you're scared of us.
You finally get what you want,
and you can't handle it.
- You guys are screwing each other.
- We love each other, Sean.
Sean called.
He offered me the job of receptionist.
I thought Gina was a stroke of genius.
Not only is she not screwable,
you've got built-in childcare.
You and my ex-wife
can have more alone time.
Tell me what you don't like
about yourself.
I don't like that he's so old.
- Believe me, neither do I.
- And he looks like a woman.
- Your mother's quite hard on you.
- Ha!
Magda and I have been married
for 21 years this may.
- Congratulations.
- For what?
I wanted a real man.
Omar Sharif. Burt Reynolds.
Hell, even a roll of brawny paper towels
would have been fine.
But all I got was this hairless freak.
Back in the eighties,
hair removal was all the rage.
I partook, you know, to say the least.
Magda made me suffer through months
of excruciating electrolysis.
I followed the trends.
Well, now, magda demands it back.
She read in Newsweek that
being hirsute is en vogue again.
Chest hair, long sideburns.
I think they call it retrosexual.
Yeah. Hair transplants
to the face and the chest
are becoming quite popular.
I want a moustache on him,
and I want some fur on his ass.
His is pink like a girl's.
Well, you seem to have a healthy amount
of follicles on your head.
I don't think we'll have any problem
harvesting 2,500 to 3,000 grafts.
I agree to it only if I could get a face
freshening while I'm in here.
God knows I don't want all my
good years to be behind me.
Sure. We could do a tightening
along the jaw line
and get rid of the crow's feet
around your eyes.
What do you think, Magda?
That sound good to you?
Oh, Jesus. She didn't just...
She was up till 1:30 eating nachos and
watching Last Call with Carson Daly.
I've sold my soul to the devil,
and this devil just won't die.
When we met, I was in my early 20s,
struggling actor.
Magda's health was deteriorating fast.
I decided to marry her,
figured I'd put in a couple of years
at most, get a pretty nice payday.
Her first husband
made millions in tobacco.
No money in the world
is worth giving up your life for.
If I leave beelzebub now, her first
phone call will be to the lawyers.
I'll wind up with practically bupkis,
and then she'll keel over the next day.
It's her life.
Oh, I haven't even told you
the worst part.
Magda screws like bugs bunny.
She demands it, 6-8 times a day.
- How do you do it?
- I close my eyes.
I think of the villa I'll buy
in Portofino when she finally kicks.
How long was I out?
Damn. You're still here?
Oh, I dreamt I was screwing
a flugelhorn player.
Yes. We heard the flugelhorn.
I'm hungry. Go make me some soup.
Transcript: swsub.com
Synchro:
_/Yellow Sub\_
Metalmarco::ITA-SA::
Season 5 Episode 10
Magda & Jeff
OK, people, let's get it done.
15 blade.
Oh, my God. What happened?
- Who's that?
- It's ashley.
- So, where have you been?
- What...
This woman was crushed by an elephant
at the circus. Isn't that right, Peter?
I am performing a mandibular
reconstruction with the 13th rib.
- Just... 3 centimeters to the left.
- No, doctor, not the patient.
- You. Your eyes.
- Oh, it's nothing.
Just a little river blindness.
I caught it fixing cleft palates on the
Amazonian river this weekend.
Oh, the Yanomani children.
To see their faces, it was all worth it.
- Peter, if you could have been there...
- Doctor, should you be operating?
Yes, I should be operating.
Peter's my eyes.
Bone saw!
Here we go.
Oh, we got a bleeder!
Aidan Stone, you are a boy genius.
- Oh, my God.
- Marcus!
Freddie, Freddie, Freddie, Freddie.
Thank you. Thank you.
- It was a nice scene.
- Yeah. Thanks. You too.
- Dating a black guy now.
- That's great.
Good for you.
Who's Jose Feliciano over there?
Oh, that's marcus.
Aidan's blindness consultant.
I don't know how you guys do it.
And it's all the time, right?
- It's like 24/7.
- Well, pretty much, yeah.
Did it seem authentic, though?
I mean, I was doing some
really cool shit with my eyes.
- Were you?
- Like, back and forth, and then...
- Well, it sounded lifelike.
- It did. Yeah.
But no, what did it look like?
Did it look... 'cause I...
Mr. Mcnamara? Excuse me.
I'm Colleen Rose
of the Colleen Rose agency.
I was on the lot visiting another
client, and I thought I'd swing by
and watch you work.
What I just saw you do was sensational,
just sensational, really.
Such pathos. Strasberg, right?
Doesn't matter. You are a scene stealer.
And I hear through the grapevine
you're looking for representation.
I'm flattered, but I'm a medical
consultant, not an actor.
- I don't think i'm very good.
- I totally disagree.
You have a very naturalistic process.
And I know I can get you work...
Movies, commercials.
It would be a crime to hide
that massive talent of yours.
I've just gotten off the phone with
Aidie's agent, who's very, very upset
about yesterday's dailies. He has
a massive zit on his client's nose.
I need you tomorrow morning
6 A.M. To reshoot.
Oh, wait. Freddie, I have 2 surgeries
scheduled for that time.
- Excuse me.
- No, excuse me. I'm Freddie Prune,
executive producer and creator of
Hearts & Scalpels. How can I help you?
And I'm sean's agent.
Colleen Rose of the Colleen Rose agency.
Seanie, I didn't know you had an ag...
Sean is not going to be rescheduling
any surgeries because of some zit,
all right? Sean is a medical consultant
and a producer.
He's not one of your cattle.
He saves lives at his day job.
So listen, do what you have to.
If you have to shoot around him, fine.
Get close-ups, fix it in post...
I don't care, really, what you do,
but my client will not be here tomorrow.
You get me a strawberry frivol right now
before I kick you square in the nuts.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
In this next bit,
I think I'm going to cry.
You know? I just...
I really want to show that
blind people can cry like normal people.
- That's pretty brilliant, right?
- You know, Aidan,
blind people really do cry
like everyone else.
I know. But I'm saying that when I cry,
I can see again. Yeah.
Oh, but I can only see again when
I'm crying. I have to get, like...
I just got to get really emotional.
I don't know that river blindness
was ever cured that way, but,
well, from what I've learned,
I mean, blind people do
get their sight back.
Eden, right?
- Yes. We met at your hell party.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that was a pretty crazy night.
- Are you looking for Sean?
I think he's hanging out
with the extras somewhere.
No, actually, I took the studio tour
and snuck away.
Thought it would be more fun
to find things myself.
Or maybe you could show me around.
Well, where would you want to start?
Oh, well, I've always wondered if the
big stars have beds in their trailers.
I am big, darling.
I'm very big.
I have your results.
The tests don't rule out everything,
but your T.S.H. is in the range.
We just can't find out
what's wrong with you, Julia.
Well, um, what don't they rule out?
Certain rare cancers,
- but I really don't think...
- You don't have cancer.
Just sometimes, I think that you believe
I'm faking this whole thing.
But I know that there is
something very wrong with me.
And if Dr. Hughes
can't find out what it is,
then I will go to see
someone who can.
There is something else
we could test for.
Your symptoms could be caused
by an autoimmune disease.
When was the last time
you were tested for HIV?
Slow down. There are other
- autoimmune diseases besides HIV.
- 6 months ago.
And how many partners have you
had since then? Maybe 50?
I'm not HIV positive.
I was fine until
we started sleeping together.
Test me for HIV.
And I would like you
to get a test today, too.
Here's your afternoon pick-me-up...
double espresso with non-fat soy,
just the way you like it.
I left out the sambuca since you do
have surgery in 10 minutes.
Thank you. Oh, thanks.
Did you pick up my dry cleaning?
I got it on my lunch break.
I hung it up in your car.
Thanks.
What is this crap?
I mean, you get my coffee,
you get my messages,
you haven't called me "asshole"
in days. It's like
Gina slut-bitch died and Miss
Moneypenny's here in her place.
- What do you want?
- Nothing.
No, Christian, really.
I admit it... I'm not the same girl
that you knew back in Miami.
I guess I just... I finally realized
how lucky I am.
My viral load is so low,
it actually rivals Magic Johnson's.
I actually like my job.
I get to see Wilbur.
And I have you to thank for it.
And I know, you're kind of having
a tough time with Julia, and...
I don't want to add to your problems.
So, huh... huh. What did you hear?
That she rides you pretty hard.
That's all.
Well, you know,
she's sick and she, um...
You know, she's in bed all day.
She got nobody to talk to.
- Yeah. No, I get it.
- No, you don't get it. Jesus Christ.
It's like we're married already.
I mean...
I need a break.
What you need is a release from all the
stress that this hag is putting on you.
- I know exactly how to give it to you.
- Oh, no.
I am not going anywhere near that
saber-toothed snatch of yours.
Oh, God. No. I'm done with that
K-hole of irresponsibility.
I have a better idea.
I was thinking about letting Gina go.
You were right.
She's a distraction for both of us.
And today, she asked for a raise.
Well, I think we should
give her a raise.
I hate to admit it, but I think
she's the best receptionist
we've ever had.
You know what happened the other day?
I didn't know what to eat for lunch,
so she ordered the entire menu.
When they delivered it,
she screamed at them
for screwing things up,
so we got everything for free.
Your agent's on the phone.
Agent? I thought you weren't moving out.
She's not a real estate agent.
She's a talent agent.
Talent agent?
I thought you need talent
for a talent agent.
No panties. I likey likey!
Do you have enough time?
They'll wait.
I run this show. Matter of fact,
I run the whole goddamn network.
I thought Barbara Shapiro
ran the network.
That deaf bitch?
The only reason why they let her
in the jewish mafia is
is to fill a disability quota.
I'm going to make you
squeal like a pig.
Grab my ass.
What happened?
I'm not a premature ejaculator.
There's, like...
There's, like,
3 hours cut out of that...
video. Who edited this?
That's it?
This is bad.
Really bad.
Listen, kids.
2 million downloads
on Youtube in 8 hours.
There's got to be a way we can spin
this to our advantage, don't you think?
Barbara...
You know I was just kidding
about the whole jewish mafia thing.
- Sure he was.
- I love the jews.
You're an offensive piece of shit.
What... I'm sorry.
What did she just say?
You are an offensive piece of shit.
Am I... am I fired?
Absolutely not.
Is he?
Not yet.
You are going to go straight
to rehab,
and we will tell the press
that you're a cokehead
and a sexaholic.
And then... hey!
3 months,
you will do an interview
with Larry King,
and maybe
we will bring you back for sweeps.
Do you understand?
It's too bad you're not black.
We could have kept you
around till the end of the season.
Is this some sort of joke?
OK. First of all, Barbara,
I am the show.
There is no...
there is no show without me.
OK. Freddie is not really
that talented.
- How dare you.
- No, how dare you.
How dare you. What are you going
to do without me?
I just don't understand why I'm here.
Are you going to write
for that fat pig Kate Tinsley?
Maybe you should have
thought of this
before you stuck your little penis
in and out of mrs. Youtube
and betrayed not only me,
but the tens of thousands of people
that made you a huge television star.
Do you know why you are here?
You are here because you are
the new star of Hearts & Scalpels.
That's why you're here.
- What?
Just for 3 months, until... I just need
to keep the show going. It's OK.
- It's... we need to...
- You did good, Colleen.
Saved our ass.
Wait... wait. This was...
You're behind this, aren't you?
I'm just as surprised as you are, OK?
You said... you put that little
bitch up to it to set me up
so you would take my job.
And I thought we were friends, judas!
We're friends?
What are you doing with her, anyway?
I'll tell you one thing, buddy.
You want to dance with the devil?
You can go to hell!
You're the one who couldn't
keep his dick in his pants.
2 can play at this game, guy.
This is not over.
This is not over, freddie.
Do we have a deal?
Let's talk about the numbers.
I rember you.
You're the one who had so much promise.
So much hope.
Thank you, Dr. Troy.
This man's ready to have a do-over.
New face, new life.
Now's the time to start.
There you go. No need to let a wife
get in the way of having a good time.
As soon as I get out of here,
I'm going to leave her.
What?
No, no, no, no. You don't need
to get divorced to have fun.
You can have your cake and eat it, too.
No, no, no. No, Magda's no idiot.
She'll hire a private investigator.
If I don't just leave her
and throw the last 21 years away,
I'll never have any room to breathe.
Have you ever been
someone's caretaker, Dr. Troy?
It's suffocating.
It can drive you to madness.
Wait. Where's nurse Billy?
You shouldn't be walking
around by yourself.
He said he'd puke if he saw any blood.
I might just puke when I see your face.
Take a hike, doc.
Time to try out the new hair.
He's not ready for
any physical activity yet.
He's just going to lay there.
I don't care.
I'm going to sit on his face.
The... yeah. The... the follicles,
they're very...
They're very sensitive right now,
and so, you're going to...
you're going to have
to wait a couple of days.
OK. We'll watch a movie.
Where's your tape machine
I got weekend at Bernie's.
Not again, Magda.
Yes, again, G.I. Joe.
Now, move your hairy ass.
Make room for momma.
God, momma.
Mid-30s latino softball player
with an external appendage
protruding from the sacral region.
A human tail?
No quiero mi cola quitada!
Why don't you want it removed, sir?
I'm possessed by Satan!
Your mother sucks cocks in hell!
You know, I don't disagree with you,
but Mr. Aureilles,
you have got to calm down!
Jesus! That's fantastic!
Claude, could you see if there's any
of that split pea soup left at crafty?
Here.
Listen to me! You are not possessed.
This is a treatable medical condition.
I can't cut my tail off!
Yes, you can.
This is los angeles, people!
It's called a rolling blackout!
Sorry! Accidentally stepped
on the riser pedal.
OK. Now, listen.
Everything is going to be fine.
I'm going to remove
your devilish appendage, and you'll be
sliding into home plate by next week.
Cut!
Bravo, people. Very courageous work.
And a star is born, Freddie.
You know, Colleen,
sometimes I forget that
I gave birth to the supernova
that was Aidan Stone.
But I tell you what, I think that
Sean McNamara is sexy and
vulnerable and
so very, very modern.
And by the way, so do the blogs.
So you're going to be seeing
a lot more scenes like
this on Hearts & Scalpels,
I'll tell you that.
God. That's really good.
Thank you.
That was impressive work, Sean.
Thanks, Kate. You, too.
Though I really don't feel
like I know what I'm doing.
Hey, asshole.
No. It's more
like, "Hey, asshole."
You know, I'm sorry.
Why are you here, again?
It's postmodern sex, Christian.
This way, we both get what we want
without any consequences.
She's HIV negative,
so you get to ride her bareback,
and I get to experience sex
without exchanging any fluids.
Plus, it's kind of like watching myself.
Christian, you have to look at me.
- But I can't!
- But we have to have a connection!
I can't, all right?
It hurts my neck. All right?
This is not puppetry of the penis.
You want an acrobat? Blow a chimp.
Fine.
Jesus.
This isn't working for me.
Just put here where I can see you.
That's all.
- Kiss me.
- No.
- no!
There's no danger of
transmitting the virus unless
I've had dental surgery,
and I haven't.
Leave, Gina. You're ruining everything.
I'm not paying you to use your mouth,
you little whore.
Now, you shut up,
or you won't get a penny.
Please? Kiss me.
no.
Fine. Keep going.
Kiss me.
Please.
I will see you at work in the morning.
Conor finally fell asleep.
You're throwing up again?
I'm sorry. Even tea makes me vomit.
Have you had anything to eat?
I don't want to tell
the kids that I have aids.
Julia, you don't have aids.
I've got all the symptoms.
Well, along with 100 other
possible things.
It's extremely difficult to spread
between women,
and Christian has been
very careful ever since Gina.
Yeah. So careful that...
He's ignoring me.
I feel like
I'm going through this alone.
Well, you're not.
I'll stay with you.
No. I'm sure you have plans.
And Christian should be here any minute.
I'll stay till Christian gets here.
What is this, post-coitus cuddling?
Don't be an asshole. She's sick.
She can barely hold her head up.
Fell asleep waiting for you.
Where have you been?
There were some complications
with a patient recovery.
The transplant didn't take,
so I had to redo it.
- You could have called.
- Well, I didn't.
But I'm here now.
And you don't have a ring
on your finger anymore, so...
Time for you to go.
Rest and fluids, hmm?
He took the kids for an early dinner.
When you didn't show up,
he offered to stay until you did.
You could have called me too, you know.
I guess I had all the help I need.
You're leaving me?
I have to, Magda. I...
It's time I find my own identity.
What will that be, Jeff?
Who are you without me?
I found you on Santa Monica Boulevard
without a pot to piss in.
Everything you are
is because of what I did.
I made you a man.
Yeah, well, maybe I don't like
the man I've become.
Could have fooled me.
You seem to love having
gifts showered down on you.
Trips to Europe, cars,
a new wardrobe every season.
Don't you want that new Bentley
that's parked outside?
It was going to be
your welcome home gift.
You know, I know I'm slowing down,
and I can't keep up all the time,
so I figured
it would be great for you to have
a new car to drive around in
and show off your new face
to your friends.
And I was going to throw in
$500 more a week
walking-around money.
You know, Jeffy,
you're what keeps me alive.
But I'm not going to live forever.
You... you promise?
To us.
- Again, I'm sorry I was so late.
- Forget about it.
Forget about it!
While I was waiting,
I made friends with this bottle here.
Yeah, I see that.
Maybe you two should
take some time apart.
Oh, I'm fine, cookie. Perfect!
Well, I've got some good news,
and I've got some bad news.
The bad news is,
next week, you have
a nude scene with 2- ton Tinsley.
What? Colleen, I can't do that.
I'm not even an actor.
- It's undignified...
- The good news is,
I told that Freddie "Forget it!
My client won't do it."
"No nudie."
He agreed.
You're getting more surgeries.
Which means you get to keep
what I am sure is that
scrumptious weenie of yours under wraps.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
Uh, my steak's a little rare, but...
Excuse me.
- No, Colleen, it's fine.
- Let me do my job, Sean.
Waitress.
Oh, God. Magda, slow down.
Slow down.
You're going to hurt yourself.
Zip it. You're ruing
my Tom Selleck fantasy.
Oh, Magnum!
- Oh! Somebody's going to see us!
- Good! We'll charge admission.
Super orgasm!
Where did you go? Wake up.
Wake up!
Are you going to be OK?
Let me ask you something.
- What are you doing?
- What do you think of these?
Colleen, this is inappropriate.
- This is crossing the line.
- Go ahead. Squeeze them.
These aren't the tits of a
50ish-year-old woman, am I right?
You're drunk, OK?
Just go to bed and get some rest,
- and I'll talk to you tomorrow.
- They look fake, they're so perky.
Colleen, get out of the car.
Sorry.
Sorry, cookie.
Oh, shit, am I sorry.
- It's fine...
- No, it isn't fine. It's...
Ever since my husband left me
2 years ago for this
young Goddamn extra from
"The young and the restless"...
And then, I had these fibroid tumors
the size of grapefruits
that they cut out of me.
Sorry. It won't happen again, cookie.
Oh, shit.
I've got to go back to A.A. tomorrow.
Agents Anonymous.
Get it?
Just drink some water
and go to bed, please.
Do you have a breath mint?
No?
OK.
Oh, Jesus, God.
You have a nice day. Thank you.
McNamara/Troy. Thank you for holding.
How can I help you?
Oh, hi, Julia.
How are you feeling?
Listen, I'd love to talk. I just...
I need Christian.
I haven't seen him yet.
Did you try his cell?
He's not picking up.
You just tell him that I called.
Any message?
Will you ask him
if he's heard from Dr. Hughes?
I was just, um...
Hoping that he could rush
through some test results of mine.
I will definitely make sure
that he gets that message.
You feel better, OK?
Bye.
- Hi.
- Any messages?
Yeah.
Julia call?
No.
But there's a fresh pot
of sumatra in the kitchen.
Hi, Julia.
When I spoke to you on the phone,
I was so worried about you.
Here.
Um, thanks. God.
Can you just leave them there?
- Smells right now are making me...
- Oh! I rember that feeling
when I was first on the cocktail.
Even the slightest odor
would make me yack.
Has Dr. Hughes put you
on the cocktail already?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's not HIV tests
that you're waiting to hear about?
Julia, one of the advantages
of me answering the phones
is that I am the gatekeeper
for the entire office.
Nothing gets past me.
Now, what I can't figure out is how
you managed to put yourself at risk.
And Christian uses condoms, right?
Is Christian positive?
I'm sure everything's going to be fine.
I'm just a cynic.
Even if the worst were to occur,
you could get through this.
I can help you. Christian will help you.
When I found out that i was positive,
he was so wonderful.
He was a fount of support.
Not for me. I've barely seen him lately.
That makes sense.
What's that supposed to mean?
I hate to be the one
to bring you bad news,
but I think that we're friends,
even if your shitty managerial skills
did single-handedly destroy the spa
that I sacrificed
my entire nest egg for.
Just say what you have to say, Gina.
Christian's having an affair.
I literally walked in on them. It...
- it was degrading.
- No, no. That's not true.
Oh, don't be such a Pollyanna, Julia.
It makes me sick.
Gina, I want you to leave, please.
Right now.
OK.
Bye.
You know,
I guess all that I'm trying to say
is I think you need
to keep that dyke close.
Christian is not capable
of keeping his sword sheathed.
He's not capable of staying committed.
That's not news to you, right?
I mean, surely, you've figured that out
after all these years.
What are you doing here, Gina?
Just a little girl talk.
Oh. Julia, what I neglected to tell you
is the woman Christian's
having the affair with is me.
She's a dirty, whoring liar,
and she's been in love
with me for years.
But are you sleeping
with her, Christian?
No. She's got the gate to hell
between her legs.
Why don't you tell your precious Julia
where you were last night?
OK. Fine. I will.
At home with my tongue in his ass.
I want you to leave, Gina.
And by the way, you're fired.
Oh, yeah. I expected that.
I mean, it's a conflict of interest,
our working together now.
And feel better, Julia.
I should have known you'd never change.
You're such a damn hypocrite,
accusing me of sleeping around
when the only evidence you have
is that wingnut...
Despite the fact
that you're cheating on Olivia.
I can't talk about this now.
I'm not feeling well.
There's always something wrong with you.
At least Gina
doesn't live in denial, like you do.
You want me to just face facts
and admit that this relationship
isn't working? Is that it?
That you're never here for me?
That you don't support me?
That I'm not even sick?
You're not sick, Julia.
Or should I say, you
didn't catch anything from me?
I'm going to go heat up
some soup for you or something.
Tell me you don't like
about yourself now.
Me? I'm perfect.
It's dudley do-right here.
You got to do something about his chin.
Every time I'm riding him,
it's like I'm sitting on a butt plug.
And you really want this?
Not just her
making this decision for you?
Sure. I mean,
she just gave me a Bentley.
Magda, don't you think
it's a little soon to be getting
back in the saddle, so to speak?
Hell, no. It's now or never, guys.
I mean,
I'm pretty much knocking
at death's door,
and I don't see anyone waiting
on the other side for me.
Then out of respect for Mr. Morris.
He's had a grand mal seizure.
He's a vegetable.
He'll never live a normal life again.
Yeah, that's a damn shame.
Jeff was really great in the sack.
This one just lays there
like a bag of rocks.
But I'm teaching him.
You know, Jeff made
his own choices in life.
And I got to do the same thing.
It's time to move on.
You get nothing from the past,
and who knows what the future is.
It's the present, boys.
You got to take a bite out of that apple
and have fun while you can.
Nobody's keeping score.
Hey, cookie. Got us some jamba juices.
I've got bana berry or razzmatazz.
Which one do you want?
After the scene I made last night,
I need to replenish my fluids.
That's an apology, by the way.
Apology accepted.
I'll call you if I need you.
I was, um, thinking I'd stick around
and watch the scene.
Do you see
any other agents here, Colleen?
Every day, you have
some excuse to come visit
and hover around me
like some irritating fly.
Why don't you go back to your office
and just let me do my work?
Now, you just stop with the attitude,
Mister Fancy Pants.
We have to stick together here.
No, we don't.
I'm tired of you crossing boundaries.
I'm your client, not your friend.
And we need to keep things professional.
I don't want to see you here
unless I invite you.
Am I clear?
Thanks for the jamba juice.
Ooh, hey, uh...
How much more time
do they need to light the set?
About 25 minutes.
Can you throw this away for me?
Have we met?
No, but you're Sean McNamara, right?
Never really met a tv star before.
What is your name?
I'm Jenny. I'm just an extra here.
Well, there are no small parts, Jenny.
- Can I show you around?
- Sure.
What is this?
Well, I figured that you called
to apologize, and
I wanted to make it as easy as possible.
I didn't come to apologize.
I came to serve you
with a restraing order.
I don't want you near me, Wilbur, Julia,
or my work ever again.
That's bullshit.
I didn't do anything.
I took a page out of your book, satan...
I lied.
I told the judge that you were harassing
me and my family,
and that you were stalking Julia.
With your history,
he didn't have to think twice.
OK.
If this is it between us, then...
Well, I think we should end it
the way we began it.
I made us a meal.
I think your mouth's going to water
when you see the first course.
Just look at it.
Very cute.
But you're kidding yourself, Gina.
I know you want it, Christian.
I know you want it
'cause you're just like me.
I'm nothing like you.
You're a goddamn Medusa.
What, you're a friggin'saint?
You're always going to cheat on Julia.
You are always going to come back to me
because I'm the filthiest piece of ass
you've ever had.
I came so hard...
Watching you bang that girl.
And so did you.
I don't judge you.
This is the last time
we'll ever see each other.
You love me, asshole, in your own way.
Just like I love you.
Like I always have.
There's a difference
between love and sex.
No, there isn't.
Sex is the only way that we can feel
we're not alone in the world.
You're always
going to feel alone with Julia
'cause she's never going to give
her whole self to you.
I'm leaving.
Come on. Just one last bang.
Just for old time's sake.
No.
Just stick it in.
Just the tip. Just a little bit.
You can take all your rage out on me,
just like you always have.
Give me the condom.
This is love.
_/Yellow Sub\_
contact@yellowsubteam.com