Previously on Nip/Tuck...
Christian Troy,
Sean McNamara, right?
I was seeing
the future of medicine.
- Plastic surgery?
- The wave of the future.
Tell me what you don't
like about yourself.
- My ass.
- My eyes.
- My knees.
- Your knees?
Everything.
Your right eye is half a
millimeter higher than your left.
I'll give you Botox
here and here.
The breasts could go
one size bigger.
And finish off with
some abdominal lipo.
Would you have to fix anything?
Liposuction right here.
Now, your boobs,
lift them just a little bit.
Here... and here.
You are a model
of physical perfection.
But I can be better.
I've identified these
as my problem areas.
Diet? Is that what we tell
the 20 people a week...
who come in here?
We're in the quick fix biz.
I think you could go up
to a double "D".
- A "C"
- Can I go bigger?
I want to do whatever
it takes to be beautiful.
Beauty is symmetry,
and you don't have any.
Tell us what you don't
like about yourselves.
Is that what you still ask
all your consults?
Well done.
You remembered.
- Yeah.
- Do you remember us?
Of course.
Uh, Maureen and...
Marshall Ayres from Miami.
You first came
to see us in '02, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Real estate brokers, right?
"If you want someone who cares,
buy your home from Ayres."
Yeah, we figured
that getting dual facelifts
would help to boost
our business back then.
The housing market
was so hot, you know,
you needed to do anything
you could to compete.
Image was everything,
and projecting success
meant looking younger.
Of course. And those are
ours, too, aren't they?
Yep. Oh, and...
My calf implants.
They still look great.
Don't they?
- Yeah.
- Huh?
So what brings you
to Los Angeles?
You guys.
Ok, what were you thinking?
Maybe a feather lift,
or remove some of
the puffiness around the eyes?
We want you to, um...
Reverse everything.
You guys sold us
a bad bill of goods.
So let me get this straight.
You want us to undo
your facelifts.
And take out the implants.
- So you can look worse.
- So we can look real.
Forgive me,
but...
for your ages you both
look pretty good.
Pretty good?
I think they look great.
The real issue is not
about undoing anything,
it's about teaching you about
the techniques that we use today.
You don't get it.
It's not about
refining a procedure,
it's the whole concept.
Look, back in the 1940s,
doctors recommended cigarettes
to their patients
to calm them down.
Now look what we know
about those cancer sticks.
It's no different.
Nobody ever died from looking
too young or looking too beautiful.
If you want to take
them out, that's fine.
Do whatever you gotta , ok?
But it's not gonna cost you any less
than it did when we put them in.
We were hoping
there would be no charge.
Our business has dropped
over 50% in the last 3 years,
just because of
how we look.
We used to be the faces
you could trust.
But with this tightness,
we look like...
we're just advertising
our own self-loathing.
Would you buy a house
from someone like that?
We made the choice
to get the work done,
but we were led to believe
that society accepted it.
You know, the times
they are a-changing,
and if you guys
don't keep up,
you're gonna get
swept away just like us.
Oh, Sean.
Christian, would you
grow up, for God sakes?!
For God sakes.
Dr. Cruz?
Hi.
I'm Daniella Creighton.
- Your friendly drug dealer.
- Oh, right, right, right, right.
Very cute.
Chicken?
I think it's a turkey.
Uh, so what's
the, uh,
new groundbreaking
anesthesia I must have?
Sunedra.
Prospropofol disodium.
And it converts into propofol
once inside the body.
Ok, well, hit me.
Why is sunedra better
in 10 words or less?
Uh, eliminates
negative after-effects
of general anesthesia
89% of...
time.
You just made it.
- Was that 10?
- Yeah, that was 10.
What is it, Lizzie?
We came as soon
as we heard your shriek.
Does this belong to you?
I've never seen that
turkey before in my life.
Dr. Christian Troy.
How are you?
- Daniella Creighton.
- Great.
Penkala pharmaceuticals.
Sean McNamara.
It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you, too.
I've got some great discounts.
Two of our best clients
recently took early retirement,
so we're overstocked.
Really?
Anybody we know?
Dr. Chaiken
and Dr. Gaines.
Chuck Gaines?
Jesus, he's
younger than I am.
I think he got depressed.
He kept saying how plastic
surgery was over and
he didn't want to be the last
one to turn the lights out.
So, will you
take a look at
the clinical tests results
and get back to me?
I sure will.
Even if it's a no.
I will.
It was really nice meeting you.
- Yeah, see you.
- Ciao.
Was she really
coming on to me.
She was wearing
a wedding ring, Liz.
Yeah, so?
Married women have flirted
with me before.
I mean, you know,
it's called bi-curious.
It's called buy my stuff.
You know, I don't think
she was here just to...
sell me drugs.
I mean,
after 30 years of...
being a lesbian,
I think that I have some...
instincts about these things,
you know.
Fine.
Just be careful, ok?
You only have one
kidney left.
Oh, you Turkey.
Couples coming in to have
their plastic surgery reversed.
Doctors like Gaines
closing their doors.
This might be a trend
we're looking at.
Jesus, one couple and a retiree
and you start to panic.
I'm just saying it might be
smart to diversify,
maybe bring on a dermatologist,
do more fillers.
You ever eaten
at Lawry's?
It didn't change its menu when
the rest of the whole country
decided to change
its eating habits.
It stuck with what
it did best, right?
Meats, potatoes, salads.
Plastic surgery will die
when people begin
to look at themselves
for beauty and self-esteem.
And a herd of geese
will fly up my ass.
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 7 - Episode 7
"Christian Troy II"
Original VO: honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Original VO corrected by chamallow35
Corrections & Resynchro VO :
Sean
You're the perfect
candidate for injectibles.
- You a smoker, Sean?
- No.
- Never?
You drink, though.
Looking at your face,
I'd say you're
a 3-scotch-a-night man.
This crepey area here...
dehydration.
Nothing turns you into
an old man faster.
I can see
I need some help.
What is your plan?
Let's start with 15cc of
cosmoderm in the lip les.
Been feeling a little bitter
and judgmental lately?
Now no one will know
what you're thinking.
They'll just be drawn
to your positive,
boyish charm.
10cc of radiesse,
bye-bye, jowls.
10cc of lidocaine...
And definitely some Botox.
How amazing is that?
- Not bad.
- Stay there.
I don't do this for
everyone, but...
you are so cute.
You don't feel
the winds of change.
Plastic surgery is just
not cool anymore.
We're being called
to a higher purpose.
People just feel
wrong about...
self-mutilation
for youth and prestige.
And who has
2 weeks' recovery time?
It is so 2004.
So toxins and face fillers
are your higher purpose?
What's yours?
Dare I ask?
I haven't found it yet,
but at the moment, I just...
mutilate people
for youth and prestige.
Call me the face of 2004.
Did you have a chance to read
the results from the clinical trials?
Um... no. I'm sorry,
but I have not.
Listen, um...
Dani.
I feel very comfortable
staying
with the propofol.
I'm used to it, and, um...
I'm just gonna stay with it.
Ok, then.
Well, it was nice
to have met you.
Very nice
to meet you, too.
You wouldn't want to...
I don't know, um...
Have lunch with me
sometime, would you?
I promise,
no shop talk.
How do you think your husband's
gonna feel about that?
We're...
we're separated.
But you're right.
I'm sorry.
I just...
I have these thoughts...
Fantasies, and I never
act on them, but...
you just...
you seem so...
Available?
Beautiful.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry. I'm just...
I'm going through a phase.
I don't eat lunch.
We always have
a lot of yogurt here.
On the other hand...
I'm very partial...
to dinner.
I'm never gonna
have a facelift.
Botox maybe,
but no facelifts.
That's the reason you're only
an anesthesiologist, Lizzie,
and not a successful
surgeon like myself.
Ok? You're not willing
to go the distance.
You're dead wrong,
smartypants.
The reason I became
an anesthesiologist
is so that I could switch
my specialties whenever I wanted.
Call me in a year
when you're standing
over an empty
operating table
and I'm making bank over
the heart institute at cedars.
Oh, look who's here.
Fancypants, huh?
Oh, you look good.
Maybe too good.
Get an extra hour's sleep?
Is that why you're late?
Yeah, you look like a
different person, huh?
Well, I went to see
Jill Jacobson yesterday.
I sampled from
her injectibles menu.
Why the hell did
you go to her?
We can do anything
she does and better.
Dermatologists specialize in
that kind of treatment,
and frankly, they do
a much better job.
Fine, ok? But when
the stuff wears off,
I don't want you
going back to her.
If anybody should be
stabbing you with a needle,
it's me and
not the competition.
She's not the
competition anymore.
I hired her this morning.
You can't hire anyone
without my approval.
Don't worry,
you'll love her.
You're having dinner
with her tomorrow night.
- Christian Troy?
- That's me.
Have a seat. We're running
a little behind today.
Hey.
Are they always this busy?
No.
It's usually worse.
So you come here
quite a bit, then?
Every 6 weeks.
That must be awful.
No, it's not so bad.
It's just like
getting a haircut.
I meant wasting
your time and money
on something
that doesn't work.
I beg your pardon?
You do realize that
if you only use injectibles
you'll never be satisfied.
Sure, there's the high of looking
good when you first get it done.
But then you start seeing
the spots the doctor
missed right away.
Like these lines, here.
Of course, the doctor's only
too willing to squeeze you in.
It's more money for her.
Thank you
for seeing me again.
Good to have you back.
Just right here I noticed.
Ok.
You can't argue
with the results, though.
If you're looking for real
value and long-lasting results,
the only thing
you can rely on
is a qualified surgeon.
Take one.
Great.
Thank you.
Lois,
what happened here?
I thought
we were overbooked.
They all got a better offer.
How dare you get rid of
my patients like that.
They left of
their own free will.
Only after you Fed them
some bullshit line
about the marvels
of plastic surgery.
Actually, it was
an educated decision
based on
years of practice.
Of course,
I didn't do a one-year course
at a community college
to become a beautician.
So,
I'm sure that I missed out
on some of the finer points.
Oh, I get it.
This is some kind of test,
to see what I'm made of before
we start working together?
Oh, we're not working
together, sweet cheeks.
See, my partner needed my
approval for you to come aboard
and I came to tell you
that I don't approve.
Things are really bad,
aren't they?
- Excuse me?
- The business.
It must be.
Or you wouldn't look
like such shit.
I think you need my help.
I got a better idea.
You come to my office,
and I'll help you fill out
that cleavage of yours.
What are you,
an "a" cup?
Is that a problem for you?
That and your
pancake ass, but, um,
we could fix that, too.
And, uh...
What exactly
would you do
to my ass, Dr. Troy?
Why don't you just give us
a quick look here, huh?
This ass?
There's a lot
I could do with that.
I could definitely
take you up to a "c" cup.
Should we lock the door?
Why, huh?
All your patients are gone.
Actually, there's probably
another 10 out there right now.
See, I can book every
15 minutes for 8 hours.
But since you're part
of the old guard...
I guess you'll never
get to experience
what I really had
to offer you.
Which was a future.
Tell Sean I said thanks
for the opportunity.
I will.
And if you change your
mind about the, uh, "c" cup,
you let me know.
Shit!
Just a minute.
Butterfingers.
Come on in.
Come in.
I'd keep your shoes on.
- Ok.
- Yeah.
It's beautiful here, huh?
Oh, thank you.
So, would you like
some wine?
I... I got some white
and some red
that my husband
brought back from Napa.
Uh, he's an expert.
I, uh, think he knew
more about wine
than he knew about me.
Oh, God, I didn't even ask
if you drank.
I just... I've heard that most
lesbians are alcoholics.
Well, I must be in
the super minority.
I prefer red.
Me, too.
Isn't that wild?
Yeah.
Can I use this?
Oh God.
God coming
to the rescue.
Oh, good.
Is this your first date
with a woman?
Is it that obvious?
Look, believe me,
I'm not just experimenting.
I'm like 75% sure
that I'm gay.
75%, huh?
I've, um...
I've always been
attracted to women.
And, um...
it leaves the fact that
in all the years
with my husband,
I never once had, uh...
You know.
Well, bottoms up.
Oh, shit,
I didn't mean that.
What you doin'?
I'm taking care
of the other 25%.
It's...
it's just, um...
I've never...
And...
I just... I don't want you
to expect too much.
I don't expect anything.
Ok?
I just want you to
have a good time.
I don't care if you orgasm.
Just trust me.
It's gonna be ok.
All right?
Ok.
I trust you.
Sean, you might want to call
your little injectibles wench
and tell her she won't be
having a job here.
I'm not budging
on that one, by the way,
so don't tax you're
already overworked brain
trying to come up with
a way to talk me out of it.
Yeah, I think we're on
the same page about that.
- What happened to you?
- Too much filler.
- You went back a second time?
- And a third.
- A third?
- Yeah, laugh away, pal.
You're gonna be
doing the correction.
5cc of hyaluronidase
wherever she injected me.
So, fellas,
I just got off the phone
with a Bernie Greenstein,
who said that he's
representing the ayers,
and they are filing
a lawsuit against us,
claiming loss
of income
due to misrepresentation
and malpractice.
Oh, my God,
look at you.
- Who'd you piss off?
- Don't.
Well, he's trying to get
a court order
to see a list
of our patients,
hoping that there are
more disgruntled folks.
Bernie greendick is
an asshole. Ok?
And everything he touches
turns to tabloid, uh,
headlines, ok?
So who gives a shit?
All right, could we put the lawsuit
aside and bring the swelling down?
Please?
You're wrong, Sean.
We have plenty to worry about.
All people need to do is hear
the name McNamara and Troy
in context with a lawsuit
and we're screwed.
No, no, no, we can't
worry about that.
There's nothing
we can do.
It's all over, anyway.
The whole pursuit of
perfection is a gigantic hoax.
Nothing changes.
We need to put up
a fight, all right?
I'm gonna get a feather lift and
you're gonna give it to me,
and you're gonna show
the world what we do here.
And that would do what,
besides take you out
of surgery for a week?
You'll be the poster boy
for injectibles, ok?
I'll be the face
of the business
and the future
of plastic surgery.
All right, old man.
You sure you're
ready to do this?
Hold on.
I didn't get that.
Wait.
Can you say your line
again for me, please?
What are you doing?
It's ok.
She's filming this.
I asked her to. We're gonna
put the whole thing on Youtube.
The surgery?
Yes.
It's pioneering,
just like we used to be.
Any luck, this whole
thing will go viral
and the world will get
to see just how easy
a facelift
can be these days.
Oh, yeah,
that'll work.
We get a half a million hits,
you wait...
we'll go from being sued
to being stars again.
I know
it makes you a little
anxious to be on camera.
As a tv star guy.
So just pretend it's not there.
Ok?
Ok.
Ok. Now say your line again.
And do it good.
Uh... are you sure
you're ready to do this?
Absolu... absolutely, doc.
Let's operate.
Music.
Sweet dreams.
All right...
10... 9... 8...
Can you feel it? I mean, the
energy is just electrifying.
And just think, in a few minutes
we'll be at the end of an era,
and everybody
who is anybody
who no longer looks
the way they used to
will be here tonight.
Speaking of that, look who is here.
It's Dr. Sean McNamara.
Sean!
Don't you look dashing.
Well, Joan, when they told me
that we'd be celebrating
the demise of
plastic surgery tonight,
I knew I couldn't
show up in scrubs.
And this is your date?
Yes. This is
my new partner Curtis.
Oh. I love your outfit.
Well, thank you. My daughter
actually picked it out.
Oh, hello.
Don't tell me.
Valentino, right?
Crocodile collection?
I have the same thing
in my closet.
Well, we should get going.
We're already late as it is.
Sean, wait!
Ah! Look who's here...
the one man who
single-handedly destroyed
the fine art
of plastic surgery,
Dr. Christian Troy.
So what are you doing, doc,
trying to crash the party?
No, I have to stop...
If anyone needs to be stopped,
doctor, I think it's you.
Maybe you'll learn
from the lawsuit, huh?
What do you think
about that?
Hey, doc!
What are you wearing?
Oh. Yeah,
I got him right here.
Oh, sir.
I'm sorry.
This is a private party.
You can't come in.
Your name,
it's not even on the list.
Please step back.
Sean! Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Such a pretty pig,
isn't he?
Very pretty.
But do you think
he's done?
Only one way to find out.
A little overdone,
I'd say.
Ladies, I am so sorry that
you don't like your meal.
But he just refused to
let me tenderize him first.
Look... heh heh...
we're starving.
Now, there has to be
something that we can do.
Let's ask the man
himself, shall we?
Good idea.
Tell us what you don't
like about yourself.
Everything.
How can you say that?
- Look at me.
I'm on the wrong
side of 40. I got a...
fake tit from a
one-in-a-million cancer.
I can't lose the pounds
like I used to.
My hair keeps falling out.
My entire livelihood
is becoming
the enron
of surgical procedures.
And now my
closest friend, my...
Biggest supporter
is leaving me.
Oh, quit being so negative.
You sound like Sean.
When you show no fear,
you project confidence
and your life will always
have the appearance
of success.
And image is everything.
Is it not?
So...
what can you do
for me, then?
Have you thought
about injectibles?
They really are the future.
This is bullshit.
I'll get Sean
to do the surgery.
Thanks so much for doing this.
Are you kidding?
I've been waiting 20 years
to highlight all your flaws.
Why, do I have a lot?
Well,
for starters, you're
pompous, self-centered,
almost sociopathic
in your complete disregard
for anyone besides yourself.
You have almost no talent
in the operating room.
But you've managed
to make an entire career
riding on my coattails,
all the while insisting
that you're the one
who is the real star.
For the longest time
I actually admired you
for how easily life seemed
to bend to your will,
how women fell
at your feet.
And then I grew to hate you
for how careless
and single-minded
you could be.
Now I just think it's sad,
because for someone
who's so desperate
to succeed and
get recognition,
I see just how lonely
you really are.
When I'm gone,
you'll have no one
left in your life
who cares for you.
And...
You will die alone.
Am I really this ugly?
Don't be upset.
Let your shortcomings and
your flaws fuel you.
Let them push you further
than you ever
thought you could go.
When you stop
striving for perfection,
you might as well
be dead, buddy boy.
I'm so sorry
about what happened.
Don't be.
I'm not dead.
I have so much silicone in me,
I stayed afloat for days.
Don't worry about it.
It's ok.
Come on.
I've had
a really long day.
I missed you so much.
Prove it.
You couldn't save me, honey.
Nobody could.
Goodbye, Christian.
Don't worry,
I'll never leave you.
Who are you?
You don't see
the family resemblance?
Come
give your dad a hug.
Get out of my house.
You're not my father,
you're a monster.
You can try and deny
where you came from
as much as you want,
but you'll always be
daddy's little boy.
Are you trying
to rearrange my face,
just like you're
doing to your own
on the surgery table
right now?
Stop fighting
who you are.
My darkness is
a part of you.
You have my DNA,
Christian.
You have my DNA.
Although I have
to admit, you did
a lot of the heavy lifting
on your own.
Stop.
Sean, please,
don't hurt me.
Oh, it'll be over
before you know it.
Did you know
that getting a facelift is
the physiological equivalent
of going through a windshield
at 60 miles an hour?
Please, don't.
Please.
I can bring him out now.
We're done.
Turn that thing off.
Never let me give a patient
a hard time about pain again.
You know, under normal
circumstances, I'd rub it in.
But because you did it
for the business,
I'm gonna increase
your morphine regime
and say thank you.
What do you think?
I thought you
looked good already.
You didn't do this
because of a lawsuit
or because you took
one for the team.
You did it because
you wanted a facelift.
I noticed it
while I was shaving
a couple of months ago.
Nothing anybody else would
see, but I do this for a living.
Everyone gets older,
Christian.
You know, and you're
one of those lucky ones.
You're only gonna
get better looking.
You know why I have
relationships that never last?
Or why I trade in my car
every 6 months?
A.d.d.?
A complete
lack of a soul?
No.
I hate change.
Terrified by it.
I don't like it
when things end.
I like to end them
myself,
on my own terms.
It keeps you from
getting hurt, huh?
It also keeps me alone.
I just can't accept it
when things are over.
When things are perfect,
- you know.
- Life is not perfect.
Life is messy.
Sometimes life
is very messy.
- We still talking about me?
- I'm talking about life.
You know, and wanting
things to be perfect
and getting disappointed
over and over and over
because
it's never gonna be.
Then what happens?
You end up being alone.
Depressing.
I slept with Daniella.
She's great.
Ok.
She's absolutely great
and she's gorgeous
and she's funny and...
gorgeous.
You know,
I think, ok,
I've waited and
this is my reward, right?
We were making love
and, uh,
she's having this
orgasm that's just...
I know.
And then she, uh...
She what?
I can't even say it.
I can't say it.
Ejaculated?
Like a fire hose.
- Are you serious?
- I almost drowned.
- It's not funny.
- It's pretty funny.
I mean,
I told her, I said,
"It's ok. I don't mind it,
I think of it as a compliment."
But the truth is...
the truth is
you're just like me.
You want life
to be easy
and clean.
That's a damn shame.
- Who is it?
- It's me, Liz.
Can I come in?
I don't think so.
Please?
Look,
I know I didn't call you,
and it's only because...
you were repulsed
and disgusted.
No.
Shocked.
Thanks.
Only because
it was unexpected.
And it freaked me out,
and I got scared.
It's not you.
I thought that women
who could, you know,
you know...
- Squirt.
- Yeah, squirt.
I thought they
only existed in...
lesbian porn.
But you are so real.
And I don't want
to give up on someone
who I feel so
connected to
because of my ignorance.
You are wonderful.
And I am so sorry.
Hey, hon.
Who is it?
Um, it's
Dr. Elizabeth Cruz
from McNamara/Troy.
She's a client of mine,
and we discovered that
we're neighbors, so...
I told her that if there was
any sample she wanted,
she could just...
she could stop by.
This is my husband Edward.
Hi. Nice to meet you,
Dr. Cruz.
Nice to meet you.
Whatever
she's selling,
can't go wrong.
Right.
How about
I walk you out?
Sure.
I'll be right back,
sweetie.
Ok, sure.
Are you going back
to your husband?
I can't do it, Liz.
I can't.
I can't be gay.
You are gay.
Maybe.
But...
at least with him
I'm normal.
I don't do that.
You're gonna miss out
on a lot of joy.
Being like that
doesn't bring me joy.
It's just not how
I see myself. It's just not...
not how I want
to see myself.
I'm...
I'm so sorry.
Me, too.
That's the kind of call
you like to get from your lawyer.
I told you the Ayers
didn't have a case.
The only thing they had is
balls for trying to sue us
in the first place.
Too bad. They could have gotten
a feather lift for half off instead.
You know, I think you getting
that surgery helped our case.
So you're saying that that inflated
ego of mine could have
helped us for a change?
I'm just saying
you really put your money
where your mouth was.
I admire that.
Good.
To our continued success.
- Cheers.
- Yes, cheers.
You're not drinking?
It's bad luck.
No, no, no.
I'm still recovering.
You know,
I don't want to
get all swelled up,
look like I came
from Jill Jacobson's office.
That wouldn't be good.
Hey, fellas,
have you seen this?
Your surgery is one of the
featured videos on Youtube.
You're kidding.
It's already a quarter
of a million hits.
Oh, look,
it's over 300,000 now.
See that?
I told you it would be a hit.
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
Over 40,000 comments.
I think people are trying
to get in contact with us.
Is there anyway we can get our
phone number on this website?
This is like free advertising.
I told you that lawsuit
would be the best thing
that happened
to this business.
Oh, you know,
I'm not sure everybody
else is as enthused
about this as you are.
"What a barbaric thing
to do to someone."
"Does anyone really think
plastic surgery
makes sense anymore?"
"This is disgusting."
"Facelifts are so 2004."
Oh, come on.
It can't be all of them.
Give me this thing.
Maybe I need to post
a follow-up
now that I'm fully healed.
What do you guys think?
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com