Previously on nip tuck...
This is really bad.
How come I don't feel guilty?
We need to stop doing this.
You're not goin' back to him,
are you?
- He's my husband, Sean.
- You deserve better.
You'll never make me happy.
I can never love you enough.
We've hit a rough patch.
You don't break up because of it.
He's done with me now.
Good. He's doin' you
a favor, Kimber.
It's a gift.
Kimber fell off
a boat last night.
She's missing.
Oh, my goodness
these are so good.
Here. I'll go get you
some food, ok?
Weather report says it should
be clear through the weekend.
That'll help.
It's been 2 days, Sean.
If the coast guard's not givin' up,
then we can't either.
You want some noodles?
Jesus,
what are you doing, Matt,
feeding the kid Thai food?
It's too spicy.
What's your problem?
Take it easy.
Wanna get pissed at
someone, be mad at Hamoui.
If the police didn't charge
him with anything,
what the hell am I gonna do?
Hello.
Hi, Brandie.
No, you're
at the right place.
Ok.
See you in a minute.
It's Kimber's mom.
Have you really
never met her?
Kimber kicked her out of
her life a long time ago,
didn't invite her
to the wedding, so...
What happened
between them?
"Unresolved issues"
is what I heard.
Christian.
You made it.
- Heh. Hi.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too. Hi.
Hey, didn't you, uh,
say you were bringing
someone with you...
Les is coming tomorrow.
He's got business, so...
I'm here.
Ok.
Come in.
Wow, this is right
on the water.
- Brandie, I'm Sean.
- Hello, Sean.
Hi. I'm a friend of
Christian's and your daughter.
Hi.
Hey. I'm, uh...
I'm Matt.
You're Matt.
So this must be Jenna.
Yeah.
Wow. This is
a lot to take in...
son-in-law, a granddaughter,
an ex-son-in-law.
I wish it could be under
different circumstances.
Well, the important part is
we're all here now.
That's right.
Hey,
little one,
you wanna go back
and finish coloring? Ok.
I was just thinking
on the way here that
when Kimmy
was a little girl,
I taught her how to swim
in the lake that
was near our house, and...
she just loved the water
so much, you know?
She was such
a good swimmer. Just...
I just hope that everything
is gonna be all right.
And she's tough.
Yeah, she is.
That was the coast guard.
They're...
callin' off the search.
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 7 - Episode 4
"Sheila Carlton"
Original VO: honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Original VO corrected by chamallow35
Corrections & Resynchro VO :
Sean
Nous recherchons un ou deux
traducteurs pour la VF
Intéressé ? Contactez-nous
sur le topic de cet épisode
sur le site
www.seriessub.com
Jenna, sweetheart,
it's time to go.
Go?
Don't you think it's a little
soon to be uprooting her?
Uprooting her?
I'm her father.
Yeah, but come on.
Please, act like an adult
for once in your life.
What, you gonna take her
to your shithole?
Who's gonna take care of her
when you're lookin' for a job?
Well, my shithole is a sunny
studio is a great old deco building,
and I'm actually
working right now.
Yes, it's as a barista at the coffee mill
on hyperion, but it's a job.
And FYI.,
I'm dating the manager.
Her name's Ramona.
She comes from a huge family,
and they all absolutely
love my daughter.
So when are we gonna
meet this Ramona, then?
Jenna, honey,
Ramona's waiting.
She made us some meatball soup.
You wanna go?
Come on and give me
a big, big, big one.
And a kiss.
I love you.
I love you, too.
- You be a good girl, ok?
- I will.
- Ok.
- I will see you soon.
See you soon.
Let's go.
Brandie?
Sorry.
Um, should I...
No, no, no.
It's not a problem.
I was just checkin'
if you're ok.
I'm ok.
I just...
I just wish that somehow
we could have worked out
our differences.
She was always
so mad at me.
I mean, we were more
like sisters in a way,
because I had her
when I was so young.
I just didn't...
I didn't have a clue.
And I tried to reach out to her,
but she...
didn't want me to be
a part of her big, fancy life.
Yeah,
you can't let...
the guilt take over.
I know it's hard,
but...
this isn't about us.
It's about Kimber.
We need to celebrate her
and her life.
Yeah.
You're right.
Tell me what you don't like
about yourself, Mrs...
Carlton,
Sheila Carlton.
Course,
I call her Shu-Shu,
but that's because I've been
calling her Shu-Shu
since we met
in middle school,
or was it in high school?
I don't even remember.
It seems like the years
have flown by,
and I keep calling her
Shu-Shu.
Well, it says here that the injuries
to your face were caused by...
me.
It was because of me.
That's why she's here,
because I almost
killed her.
It wasn't your fault, Jane.
Stop blaming yourself.
It was Wayne.
He's the one
who did this to me.
He's an animal.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Wayne is your husband?
Her monkey.
Chimpanzee.
He weighed over
200 pounds.
He had a big appetite.
Well, I'm gonna have to do
a complete workup
and talk to the surgeons who
treated you after the attack,
but I would recommend
that you do
the reconstructive surgeries
in stages.
Your body's already been
through enough trauma.
And it's my fault.
Can you imagine
being the one
to cause your oldest friend
such agony?
Reminds me of that
awful tragedy with Travis
in Connecticut
a few years back.
Jane, please.
I shouldn't have let him
out of his cage.
He seemed unsettled
that morning,
and I...
I should have just...
you saved my life, Jane.
Now stop it.
How did you?
I hit him with a frying pan.
And when he wouldn't
release her,
I stabbed him repeatedly
with a kitchen knife.
I don't know how
you can ever forgive me.
Why don't I have a nurse
escort you to the exam room.
You can change, and
we can do a thorough exam.
I want you to make her
as beautiful as she was.
I don't care
what it costs.
- Jane, it's never going to be...
- He owes you this.
Wayne did some work
in movies, uh,
television shows.
He had such star appeal.
He was such
a little performer.
I never spent a dime of his money.
I was saving it for his old age.
But I'm spending it now,
every cent.
And everything
I have as well, if I have to.
Where is she?
- Um, she...
- Les.
Come here, baby.
It's ok.
I'm here now.
I can't believe it's true.
- When'd you hear for sure?
- Last night.
Is that why you didn't
pick me up at the airport?
'Cause that's what we
originally planned.
Les ?
I'm, uh, Christian Troy,
Kimber's husband.
- The plastic surgeon.
- Yes.
My deepest condolences.
Thank you.
Please, uh,
forgive me.
Was that your Maserati
out there?
Yeah.
Wow. For somebody so
concerned about appearances,
to drive a foreign car. Pfft.
Excuse me?
American economy
needs our support.
Les, this...
I own the largest domestic
dealership in Wisconsin.
All makes.
Great deals.
You'd be surprised what
your money can buy nowadays.
- We ship anywhere.
- You tryin' to sell me a car?
I don't sell cars.
I make people happy.
Ready to get back to the hotel?
Christian invited us
to stay here.
We were talking about
the memorial service...
I... I already booked the room
for a week, remember, on points.
Gotta try that jacuzzi, huh?
You don't wanna see her
before she puts her face
on in the morning anyway.
Listen, is there
a bathroom around here?
I had a couple beers on
the plane, and my bladder's...
Just back there.
Charming. So how long
you guys been together?
6 years.
We break up.
We get back together.
We break up again.
He can be a lot to handle,
but I love him.
We have a connection.
Well, Kimber and I,
we sure had our fair share
of ups and downs, you know.
I understand exactly
what you're talking about.
I guess it runs
in the family, then.
That is such great soap
you got in there. I love it.
You ready?
We'll call you, ok?
And don't forget to tell me
where you got that soap. Love it.
I am so sorry to hear that.
Yeah, they were married
about a year ago.
Christian's taking it
pretty hard.
Well, well, please,
give him my condolences.
I just can't imagine what
it would be like to lose Sarah.
And suicide, jeez.
That's difficult.
I guess you just...
you can't ever know
what's goin' on in someone's head,
even if you're married to 'em. Right?
I think, in a way,
we all feel responsible.
Aw, how can you not?
You know,
it's probably not
the best time for you
to be joining me
in Africa, right?
Probably not, Curtis.
I'm sorry.
Ah, I understand.
Life gets
in the way sometimes.
You know,
we all have responsibilities.
And you can't leave
Christian right now.
You get back from this
trip in, what, 3 weeks?
Tell me about the next trip
after that.
Well, we'll be, uh, building
a new hospital in Basra this spring.
- I'm in.
- What?
I've heard that before,
you know.
No, no, no.
It's firm this time. I am in.
I'll get the ball rolling
while you're in Africa.
I won't let this be
another Harvard.
Cheers.
I'll hold you
to this one, buddy.
Your blood pressure's
on the high side.
Are you under
a lot of stress lately?
You could say that.
You need to control it.
Iraq isn't really relaxing.
It's beautiful, yes, but...
their work there
is really intense.
I think it's gonna be
very good for me, actually.
It's exactly the kind of change
I need in my life right now.
Well, you couldn't have picked
a better organization to work with,
help change your life.
The savior center is
a great place to work.
Curtis often says it saves us
who work here
at least as much
as it saves our patients.
It's so nice to meet you,
Dr. McNamara.
I've heard so many good things.
Thank you, Mallory.
Dr. Kwinda.
I'm sorry to say
I haven't heard
as much about you.
That's just as well.
We keep very busy
around here.
Eyes on the prize,
so to speak.
Are you gonna be helping
build the hospital in Basra?
I'm afraid not. I'll be here
in San Diego with Nsolo,
spending most of my time
fundraising, unfortunately.
Breathe deep, please.
Heart rate's a little elevated.
But we'll chalk that up
to the excitement of a new job.
We're all excited about it,
frankly.
You'll be our first reconstructive
surgeon on staff, Dr. McNamara.
Often our patients
with deformities
are ostracized from their villages
and their communities.
Your work will give them
a chance at normalcy again.
Would you like
your prostate examined?
Excuse me?
You're 45.
You need to check it every year.
Better safe than sorry.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's all right.
We should at least be
on a first-name basis before we...
I know yours, Sean.
I'm surprised my husband
didn't at least tell you mine.
Oh, you're married to Nsolo.
No.
Curtis is my husband.
I'm Sarah.
Am I disturbing you?
Not at all.
What are you doing
in this neck of the woods?
Well, Les took me shopping
at neiman Marcus,
and he bought me
a dress for the memorial,
and I was wondering
if you would take a look at it
to see if you think
Kimber would approve.
Wow. That Les, he's got
an eye, doesn't he?
Managed to pick
the one dress in the world
that would make you
look like a whore.
That's not very nice.
I'm sorry,
but the guy's a tool,
and I don't like the way
he talks to you.
He takes care of me,
you know, Christian.
I thought women liked
a little class. Kimber did.
Well, I'm not Kimber.
And Kimber was a star
even before she became one.
I'm just a midwestern nobody.
What am I gonna do?
I really wanted to make
my baby girl proud.
I have an idea.
I have this laser machine
that, uh,
tightens the skin
through soft-cell coagulation,
and there's absolutely
no healing time.
It's like a high-tech facial.
I'd like to talk to Les first.
Oh, no, no, no.
Trust me.
It's exactly what Kimmy
would want you to do.
- Really?
- Yes.
Is this gonna hurt?
I told you. It's like, uh...
it's like getting a facial.
I've never had a facial.
Never could afford one.
Sad, right?
So Les always tells me
that my skin is dry.
Is this gonna
help with that?
It should.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Ok, take a look
over here for me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just a sec.
I, uh, forgot...
I'm sorry I was never
good enough for you either.
Something wrong?
Yeah.
It's me.
You don't need this,
Brandie.
You look beautiful
just the way you are.
Wow. Les doesn't say
that to me anymore.
I haven't heard that
in a long time.
I missed it.
Thank you.
How do you get through
something like that
and not suffer posttraumatic stress
for the rest of your life?
What about her friend?
Knowing that she was responsible
for something like this.
It's not like she trained it
to be an attack monkey.
It's what she's doing
that counts,
helping her friend
deal with it,
seeing her through
all these surgeries.
Maybe, but she's still
gonna have to find
a way to live with
the guilt. I don't envy her.
That's great.
Yes.
Here he is.
It's Curtis.
Yes, of course I will.
You, too, darling.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Curtis sends his regards.
What are you doing here,
Dr. Kwinda?
I gave a talk at USC med,
and I thought that
rather than face the horrible
traffic back to San Diego,
I'd see if you were
free for dinner.
Sure. I... I guess
I'm available, yeah.
Great.
I'd love to hear your ideas
on facial reconstruction
for patients with
neurofibromatosis.
Hey.
How'd you get
in my house?
Cleaning lady.
Just came to grab
Brandie's makeup bag.
Guess, uh, she left it
in your bathroom the other day.
Is that what you're watchin'?
Ok.
Confession time.
Look, I only found out
about Kimber's career
from Brandie recently.
Being somewhat of an aficionado,
I couldn't help myself.
So you went snoopin'
through my shit.
I know. I could have
gone on the Internet,
but the hotel
doesn't have wi-fi.
You wanna know
somethin' weird?
Brandie and Kimber
both make that same face
when they're
takin' it from behind.
Buddy,
you're talkin' about...
you're talkin'
about my wife.
I... I meant no disrespect.
She gave me a chubby.
That's the ultimate
show of respect, I think.
You're lucky I don't
throw you off the balcony.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I'm sorry.
You gotta admit it's the one thing
these Henry girls are good at.
Figured it'd be a way
for us to bond.
Please get out of my house.
Ah. Got it.
You are being
too overprotective.
Now, friends don't let other
friends' wives drive drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I'm just...
relaxed.
Bathroom.
Right back here.
This?
Yes, right in there,
my dear.
There.
Just listing a little
starboard there, Matey.
Believe me,
this isn't drunk.
That night in Thailand when
I had my fifth scorpion whiskey,
now, that was drunk.
Yeah, the sheets on the bed
are actually fresh,
as of this morning,
so you're in luck.
- And where do you sleep?
- On the couch.
Here.
Let me.
I had an easier time bivouacking
on the side of Mount Kilimanjaro.
Towels are in this chest.
Aspirin's in the bathroom.
The water in the
kitchen is filtered.
- I don't...
- Ah, ah, ah. Stop.
I'm gonna go to bed
before you tell me
about the time you boiled
parasitic water from the Ganges.
- Good night, Sarah.
- Good night, Sean.
Sleep tight.
What... what the hell?
Hey. Wha...
Feel me, Sean.
That's right.
That's what you do to me.
Don't.
Please, just don't.
I know you want me.
The way you looked at me.
And now I have
tangible proof in my hand.
I can't, Sarah.
I mean it.
I can't.
What about Curtis?
I love Curtis,
but...
these long separations
in our marriage
have forced me
to be more...
Polyamorous.
You have an arrangement or
open marriage or something?
No. I mean I have no idea
what Curtis does when he is away.
I can only assume that since
our sexual encounters are at best...
sporadic, he finds some
other way of satisfying his needs.
Don't ask.
Don't tell.
He won't ask,
and I'll never tell.
Sarah,
you are a beautiful woman,
and I am attracted to you,
but I can't do this to Curtis.
I never expected you
to be such a boy scout.
I'm... I'm not.
It's just that I've been there,
I've done that before,
slept with my best friend's wife,
and believe me,
no amount of pleasure
can make up for the guilt.
She's gonna be fine,
you know.
I managed to reconstruct
the floor of the orbit,
the orbital rim,
rebuild her ear,
nasal cavity.
There's gonna be
some swelling,
but we can deal
with that later.
I keep seeing it
over and over.
Give me something
to help me sleep, please.
I can if you want,
but...
you might wanna
talk to someone.
Your friend has forgiven you.
Might be time
to forgive yourself.
How can I?
Every time I try to sleep,
I see it...
The knife plunging
into his back
and the eyes
staring at me,
pleading with me,
"Why, mommy?
Why are you hurting me?"
Did you know
that 98% of their DNA
is the same as ours?
They can give us blood
transfusions and vice versa.
He would comb my hair
ever so gently,
and he'd make
these little Clay statues
while he sat
in front of the tv,
so expressive.
I could see God
in those statues.
I couldn't have loved him
more if he'd been my own.
Sheila never approved.
He could sense that.
Maybe she was afraid.
In light of what happened,
her instincts proved
to be correct.
She didn't respect him.
She should have known
showing up
in that new garish makeup
would disorient him.
And teasing him
with that toy?
You don't torment
an innocent animal.
Innocent?
He practically ripped
her face off.
He couldn't help it.
He didn't know
what he was doing.
She was the one
who was a grown-up.
She should have
acted like one.
But it was my fault,
and I told him that.
After they shot him
and he just...
lay there in all that blood,
I told him I was sorry,
he was still my good boy,
and I would love him forever.
Someday, maybe
she'll forgive me.
I don't know,
and frankly who cares?
I'll never be able
to forgive myself.
Hey,
I was lookin' for you.
Everything ok?
Yeah. Yeah,
I, um...
I was thinkin' how...
good Kimber looked in
this one black dress she has.
So...
beautiful,
you know.
Big tits,
teeny little waist.
I'm such an asshole.
She really did love you,
you know.
Yeah, well, that was probably
her biggest mistake.
Listen,
there's something that, uh,
- I need to tell you.
- Shoot.
I need to take some time off.
I mean,
maybe we both do.
Maybe we should just shut down
the business for a little while
and take a vacation.
Where would we go?
Well,
I think we should...
go our separate ways
for a little while.
I mean, you and I have
been together for...
20 years
practically nonstop.
You're gonna
work with Curtis.
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
I'm gonna help the savior
center build a hospital.
That's what I wanna do.
I don't wanna let another
opportunity like this pass me by.
Then go.
But you go for a month,
you go forever.
Come on. Heh.
Does it fit?
Heh. Well, you flatter me
with a size 2, Christian.
Yeah, it fits.
Oh, yeah.
It's perfect.
Did you buy this on rodeo?
Here.
Try this.
It's beautiful.
Wanna try it on?
Yeah.
Of course.
May I?
What do you think?
I think you look just
as amazing as she did.
Did I do something wrong?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I just...
We can go shopping
for a new dress.
I don't know what
I was thinking. I just...
No, no, no, no, no.
It's good. It's good.
It's all good.
You've been so good
to me, really. Really.
I can't thank you enough.
It's just a little strange,
but it's good.
Just having you here's been
a great comfort for me, so...
She loved you very much.
Yeah, maybe so, but
something of which I'm not
entirely worthy.
No, don't say that.
That's not true.
My mother?
My mother.
She's a lovely woman.
She's lonely.
She...
she lost a daughter.
Come on,
Christian.
What kind of woman sleeps
with her daughter's husband?
And really, that...
that's even
a new low for you.
We were giving each other
comfort in a time of need. It's...
human.
It's normal.
Well, it's a good thing
I'm dead
so this isn't the final
knife in my heart.
Everything's a knife
in your heart.
So what are you gonna
do now, Christian?
You gonna take care of her?
I mean, give me a break.
You don't care about my mother.
You're just using her
like you do everybody.
I am who I am, all right?
You don't have a say in it.
- You killed yourself.
- You destroyed me.
What is it?
I really miss her.
I know.
Dr. McNamara.
Nsolo.
How are you?
Good.
What are you doing here?
Well, I know we don't
leave for a few weeks,
but since it's a Saturday,
I thought I'd come down and
volunteer for the day.
We can always use
an extra hand.
We're helping the W.H.O.
with an airdrop into Kenya
on Thursday to help the people
who suffered from the flooding.
We have over 1,100 units
still to pack.
Show me where.
Curtis.
I'll catch up with you.
I didn't think
you'd be back yet.
Ah, something more pressing
came up here.
Can I help?
I've already told Christian,
so...
I'm officially yours
in a couple weeks.
You know,
you and Christian,
you guys are a lot more
alike than I ever thought.
I mean, you come in here
all eager like a puppy, and then
you piss all over
the carpet.
Curtis, what's going on?
I don't...
Sarah told me,
you asshole.
And when I got the call,
I was holding
a 3-month-old little girl
severely malnourished,
chances of survival
practically nil.
Her mother died of aids
20 minutes earlier than that.
You know, one less doctor there
means many less lives saved,
but I came home
to save my marriage.
Curtis, I don't know what
she said, but nothing...
I mean...
Nothing happened.
Don't believe you.
No, I mean,
we went to dinner.
She... she got really drunk,
and... we both were,
but we both went
right to sleep.
Nothing...
nothing happened.
Nothing.
I wouldn't do that to you.
I wouldn't do that to us.
Why would my wife lie about screwing
an old friend from college?!
I have no idea, but you...
you gotta believe me.
No, I don't.
And as executive director,
it's gonna be impossible for you
to work at the savior center or
any of its affiliate missions,
so just get out of here, ok?
Go back to Christian.
You two...
you two are obviously
meant to be together.
Curtis, you gotta let...
Ok.
Here we go.
Dr. McNamara
is gonna be in today,
and then we can schedule
your follow-ups,
ok?
May I?
Oh, absolutely you may.
You know that Jane
has paid all your bills.
You know that.
You know, a lot of the
swelling has not gone down,
and when it does, we will
then know how to proceed.
It was never going to be
what it was.
He told me that.
But still,
we hope.
I suppose I should
take some comfort
in becoming a poster child.
If anyone had any doubts
about the state passing
that ordinance requiring owners
to cage their exotic pets,
they only have
to look at me.
Knock-knock.
Oh, my.
Look at you.
You look beautiful.
Well,
you will look beautiful.
Of course you're still swollen
and bruised, but that's not surprising.
I just knew
they were the best.
I knew we picked
the right doctors to come to.
You know,
I was just telling her
that she's gonna
have to take it easy
when you leave
here tomorrow.
I'll make sure of that.
I've got the guest room
all made up.
It'll be like staying
at a 5-star resort.
And I've got a surprise.
Oh, dear. That's not
very relaxing, is it?
Something to cheer you up.
There.
That's much better.
Wait'll you meet Gunther.
He's hilarious.
Your favorite.
A little comedian in fur.
Gunther?
Jesus, Jane, you didn't.
He's just a baby,
Shu-Shu.
He's nothing like Wayne.
He's just the most adorable
thing you ever saw.
He's already using
a fork and knife.
You got another monkey?
Chimp.
Look at me.
Look at me!
Look at what that
animal did to me!
Look at what you did to me.
Shu-shu...
you get rid of that ape, Jane.
Stop showering all your
affection on these animals.
That's why
you can't find love.
There's no room
for anything human.
If you value our friendship,
the 30 years we've
known each other,
you have to choose
the monkey or me.
That monkey loved me
unconditionally.
He never judged me,
and he forgave me, even when
I took his life to save yours.
You think your heart will
ever be that big?
- Hey.
You mind if
I have one of those?
Sure.
Where's Brandie?
Wisconsin.
It's for the best.
She reminded me
too much of Kimber.
Aren't you supposed to be getting
dysentery shots or something?
I'm not going to Africa.
Where's Saint Curtis
taking you?
Nowhere.
Turns out he's kind
of an asshole.
Well, you never were
too good at picking partners.
He accused me
of sleeping with his wife.
- Did you?
- No.
Well, that's good, because
sleeping with your friend's wife
is very tough on
the relationship.
I'm stayin'.
That's good.
Thinkin' 'bout sellin'
this place,
gettin' a place up
in the hills, you know,
view of the city lights or...
Well, you can't beat
this view.
I used to love it,
but now it's just like
looking at a graveyard.
It'll pass.
It's good to have you back.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com