Previously on nip/tuck...
Kimber's missing.
Coast guard thinks
she's dead.
I don't know what to do.
If you do the surgery
I'll pay you $300,000
Senor Perez.
Let's schedule.
I'm Escobar Gallardo,
the former boss
of Silvio Perez.
Silvio stole
my daughter's innocence.
Your brother said he was
with the boss' girl.
- How old was she?
- She was 6.
Tell me what you don't...
Honey,
how old are you?
15.
All right.
That's what I thought.
I'm sorry, but any surgical
procedure would require
a parent present on a minor.
Will your mother be
joining us today?
Not unless you can
bring back the dead.
Sorry.
You're exactly as
my father described you.
- And your father is?
- In hell.
With her.
If there's any truth to what the nuns
taught me in catholic school.
They say I look like him.
I'm Aurelia Gallardo.
Escobar Gallardo's daughter.
The devil's child.
Monsters never consider
the shame they leave their children.
It becomes part
of their identity.
Are you sure you're only... 15?
15.
Old enough to understand
all the suffering
my family has inflicted on
so many innocent people.
Aurelia, I really don't know
how we can help you.
You can help me
figure out who I am.
- I don't think that that...
- Silvio Perez.
He was one of my father's
business associates.
I also seem to recall he was
a patient of yours at one time.
Am I correct?
- Well, he, uh...
- I'm sorry.
That name doesn't
ring any bells.
Well, it was
a long time ago.
I was 8 when uncle
Silvio disappeared.
I started therapy
a few years ago.
Thought it might help
with the nightmares.
Of course, it's not surprising
I had nightmares
considering my life
was one.
I remember something
about a surgery Silvio had
when you practiced
in Florida.
Sorry.
Unfortunately,
I remember your father,
but Silvio Perez?
Sean?
Uh, no.
It doesn't sound familiar.
Funny.
There's so much violence
I can't forget,
no matter
how hard I try.
Yet the truth of who I am,
why I feel the way I feel,
that's still a mystery.
I wish I could help you,
but I can't.
I understand.
Maybe it's right
that I never know.
I suppose it's only just that
I suffer for the sins of my father.
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 7 - Episode 5
"Virginia Hayes"
Original VO: degroote
www.addic7ed.com
Original VO corrected by chamallow35
Corrections & Resynchro VO :
Sean
Are you insane?
I thought you'd be
more sympathetic.
You know what it's like
to be abused at a young age,
to want answers
and closure.
You're gonna get us
closure in a jail cell.
Oh, stop being so dramatic.
Stop using my past to manipulate
me into agreeing with you.
What are you two guys
arguing about today?
You tell her.
Our morning consult turned out
to be Escobar's daughter.
But don't worry,
she's just a kid.
He's dead, Gala's dead,
and she's all alone.
In Roman times, your enemies
would kill your children
after they killed you to make sure
there was no one left
to grow up to take revenge.
Anyone who shares the blood
of that animal is not to be trusted.
She doesn't want revenge.
She wants to know what happened
to the man who molested her.
Oh, and you're
considering telling her?
Look,
I know in theory
telling her what happened
could somehow
implicate us in a crime,
but...
A number of crimes.
Cessory to murder,
obstruction of justice.
I mean, hell, they could
nail us on an EPA violation
for feeding alligators.
But there's isn't any
evidence of any of that.
- And no one's ever gonna find it.
- Screw the evidence.
All right, it's done.
We got away with it.
It's like winning the lottery.
You don't screw
with that kind of luck.
Ok, no. We're not even
gonna discuss it.
I'm not gonna let you bring
even a little piece of that man
back into our lives to relive
some kind of Irish catholic guilt
that all of a sudden
you're feeling.
- Liz.
- No! No. No.
No.
2 against 1, buddy boy.
You lose.
Tell me what you don't like
about yourself, Ms. Hayes.
This town, Dr. Troy,
is an impossible place
for a girl to be herself.
Don't tell me
you're an actress.
Like everybody else
you meet on the street, right?
Chicks like me are a dime
a dozen in Hollywood.
Back in Michigan,
where I'm from, I was hot shit.
I'd go to the clubs and
the bouncers would say,
"Right this way, ten."
Right this way, ten.
Really?
Is that what they'd say?
I'm not a ten, am I?
Out here I barely register
as a six, maybe a seven.
Out here,
that makes me a nobody.
You shouldn't be
so rough on yourself.
You're a very
pretty girl.
You really think so?
Yes, I do.
Would you bang me?
On that desk.
Right now.
Unfortunately, that's not
much of a barometer.
I'm a horny devil.
Then let's do it.
Just hold on a second.
Playing hide the tree trunk
with me might, uh,
boost your ego
for a little while,
but then eventually you have
to go back to your real life as a six.
- Maybe a seven.
You know, it's not as easy
to sleep your way to the top
as it used to be.
Sexual harassment
ruined everything.
I'm sorry.
I just...
don't know how to get
people to notice me.
I'm actually not that bad of
an actress, you know.
Not that acting has anything
to do with getting roles here.
Then why stay?
Why put yourself through
constant humiliation
when you could go back
to your hometown and
be homecoming queen again?
Be a ten.
Because I told
everybody back home
I was gonna make
something of myself.
That some day they'd
be able to say
"I knew her when."
If I return now,
I return a failure.
Then let's try this again,
shall we?
Tell me what you don't like
about yourself, Ms. Hayes.
I am so happy that
we are doing a simple
mammoplasty today,
and nothing's
gonna go wrong.
Right, Christian?
Why would it?
I don't know.
Maybe because
our surgical suite is
directly over
the gates of hell.
I promise you, nothing
will go wrong today.
Oh, that sounds so good.
We're just gonna
listen to the music,
do our job,
go home.
- Sounds good, right?
- Sounds good to me.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
She looks a lot like Kimber
under the mask, doesn't she?
She's definitely not as hot,
but she's got the same color hair,
same color of skin tone.
Same breast implants.
You remember?
I gave Kimmy little Cs
for her first surgery.
- They're our top seller.
- Yeah.
There are a lot of girls
in the world
who have bad
self-image problems, huh?
Ten blade.
Some serious shit
right here, Dr. Sean.
What the hell am I
supposed to do with this?
Kill the wabbit,
asshole.
I mean, you could try
to shoot me but...
I'm already dead.
Come on, Sean, kill it.
Goddamn it,
you're still such a pussy.
50 years of school and
you still don't get it.
I dropped out in the second
grade, and I even know.
- This thing is a metaphor.
- For what?
For that prick Christian
and all that shit
he made you do.
Silvio Perez,
his brother, me.
And that's just the big
ticket items, man.
You've been feeding him
little bites of your soul
every day since the day you
met him, and then asking him,
"would you like
seconds, please?"
I knew what I was doing.
I made my choices.
Oh, like choosing
to keep your mouth shut
when a poor little girl
needs a daddy to talk to?
Come on, man.
Shoot him!
Kill the douchebag
once and for all.
Be a man for once
in your waste of a life.
Ok, doctor man,
let's cut this bad boy open
and see what's
inside of him.
Have you seen Peter pan?
That's you, dude.
Taking people to Neverland
so they never grow old.
Hey, didn't he get eaten
by an alligator, too?
Will you shut up?
- It's Silvio's.
- Maybe.
My daughter has no one, Sean.
Her whole family is gone.
But she has the guts
to come to you,
look you in the eyes,
ask you for the truth.
An innocent.
She needs your help.
You're the one who
got her into this.
You and my partner.
Alligator boy?
You're right,
we did.
We got both of you into it.
You are both innocents.
And now I'm all taken care of,
but what are you going
to do about him?
What am I supposed to do?
He's my best friend.
You've got 2 choices.
Eat
or be eaten.
Hey. I'm looking
for Virginia Hayes.
I'm Dr. Troy, Ms. Hayes'
surgeon. Can I help you?
Is she still here?
Where do you keep them,
down here?
I'm sorry, are you
a family member?
Could be. Not sure exactly.
I'll tell you when I see her.
No, no, no. Why don't you
just tell me right now?
I'm the one getting
all of her bills.
What the hell
does that mean?
I'm Virginia Hayes.
The woman you gave
new tits to stole my identity.
I'm sure it's just some kind
of misunderstanding.
She tried to bang you,
didn't she?
What?
No.
The last time
I got this close,
the watch salesman had
screwed her on his Rolex display,
so of course
he took her side.
Must be a pretty good lay.
Virginia, dear,
you have a visitor.
Where are you?
She can't have gone
too far, trust me.
Linda, get your ass
in here.
Dammit.
Thought I had her this time.
Don't worry, Ms. Hayes.
I'm sure that the credit card company
won't stick you with the bill.
No, but they will
stick you with it.
You know, the merchant's
the one who pays in fraud.
Not the victim
and not the creditor.
Her Lexus,
it's not in the structure.
She drives
a Lexus.
A $600 a month Lexus
while I drive
a piece of shit '87 Corolla.
How did you find out
she had the operation?
Oh, I got a guy.
A private dick.
He's been searching for her
for 3 years now.
I mean, that is how long
I have known about this bitch.
And you don't know
her real name?
No. No, no, no.
No, she's that good.
No, she just uses my name
every once in a while.
So it's almost like
I forget about her,
and then something
pops up again.
3 weeks ago
I get my first bill from
that Lexus dealer,
so I call my P.I.,
he starts keeping an eye
out for everything
with my social
security number on it,
calls me this morning,
and says
she got a new card and
it was used here yesterday.
Can't you just cancel your
credit cards and move on?
No.
You can't just
go on with your life.
My life is totally screwed.
I can't get a job, ok,
because she got caught
shoplifting 2 years ago
and she used my name.
Me and my husband divorced
so we could keep
his assets separate,
then the asshole realizes
he's got a free pass
to screwing around.
So now he's gone.
Not that I blame him
because I'm in this
pissy mood all the time
because I spend
most of my time on hold
trying to clear my name
with one credit bureau or another.
Well, Ms. Hayes,
I don't know how we can help,
but if there's anything...
anything we can do.
You can stop
being enamored
with every little ingenue
that walks
through your doors.
Ok, I have heard her story.
She plays the victim
and guys fall at her feet.
So here's what
you can do, Dr. Troy.
Stop being
such a chump.
My daughter used
to love to swing.
The higher I'd push her,
the more she'd beg me
not to stop.
My father and I could
never play outside.
Too dangerous.
It was years before I realized
he was worried about his safety,
not mine.
Thank you, Dr. McNamara,
for calling me.
I was surprised, actually,
to hear from you.
Your visit took us
a bit by surprise, too.
Your instinct was right
about your uncle.
He did...
He molested you
when you were young.
How young?
6.
Silvio offered us a lot money
to do a facial reconstruction.
We had no idea
why he wanted it, what...
So you did his surgery?
Yeah.
And then he wanted
another one.
Your father
tracked him down.
He wanted vengeance for
what Silvio had done to you.
So he killed this man?
One monster killed another?
No.
Actually, no.
He would have,
but Silvio's brother
Alejandro got there first.
He broke into
our surgical suite
and he held him down
while he turned up
the anesthesia.
They were enemies?
No, I think Alejandro
loved his brother, but
he was frightened.
He knew what Silvio
had done to you and
when he found out his wife was
about to have a baby girl,
he didn't want
to take any chances.
By the time
your father got there,
Silvio was dead.
And you never
went to the police?
He died on our table.
If we'd have reported it,
we would have lost
our medical license.
We had no choice but
to dispose of Silvio's body.
You had a choice.
You made it.
Yeah.
Alejandro
followed us to the swamp
where we dumped it and
soon after your father
killed him.
To get rid of the evidence
for our sake, he said.
Thank you,
Dr. McNamara,
for telling me the truth.
I was born into the world
of Escobar Gallardo.
Evil and violence
was all I knew.
Maybe now
I caput it behind me,
start fresh.
Me, too.
That's some kid.
Takes after the old man,
don't she, Sean?
Thank you.
I got you!
That's taking
a really long time.
It takes longer
if you keep interrupting.
Look,
I am in a lot of pain.
Is there anything
you can do to
hurry it up?
Try these.
They should ease the pain.
At least until
the cops get here.
Thanks, Mort.
How did you find me?
I called every pharmacy
in the area.
I asked them to contact me
if a new c-cup tried
to fill up
the prescription I wrote.
I'm serious
about the pills.
Who knows what
they'll give you in jail.
Please,
don't call the police.
Why?
You have
a check for me?
I don't have
anything anymore.
I'm really sorry.
I... I never imagined
that this would happen.
You stole that woman's
social security, her credit cards,
skipped out
on a $5,000 procedure.
What did you think
would happen?
I meant
I never imagined that...
my life could end up
to be such a failure.
What do you think,
Mort, huh?
Surprised she doesn't
get more jobs.
She's one hell of an actress.
Wait.
I'm not an actress.
Look,
it was all a lie.
I'm just Marcy Hamels
from des moines.
I came out here to get
my real estate license,
but I failed the exam.
I have dyslexia.
And then I had this problem
with my job where
I got these headaches
and I couldn't focus.
And the temp agency fired me.
And everything just
went to shit.
I didn't know
what else to do.
You didn't know
what else to do,
so you decided to get
breast implants, huh?
Yes.
I thought a new body
might get me a new life.
And everyone out here
who's anyone has them.
I was just trying to fit in.
You do realize what you did
to the real Virginia, don't you?
I feel horrible.
I always told myself that
I'd find a way to pay her back.
You don't have to do that.
No. No,
I want to.
No, I mean,
you don't have to do that
because you don't have
to pay for the procedure.
If you had told me your story,
we could have
worked something out.
- Really?
- Of course.
Matter of fact,
if you come back in,
I'll lipo away
a few pounds for free.
Why would you do that?
I became a surgeon to...
change people's lives.
And well...
You look like
you could use a little help.
What are you doing?
I thought she was having lipo.
So did she.
Thank God she's lonely
and desperate enough
to fall for the grade-a bullshit
I fed her in the pharmacy, huh?
She actually thought
that I cared about her.
These C-cups right here, they're
the property of McNamara/Troy.
I'm repossessing them.
You can't foreclose implants.
Watch me.
Why don't you just go
to the police?
What, and lose all
the personal satisfaction?
I'm tired of being taken
advantage of.
This bitch is just the last
in a long line of gold diggers
who have tried
to milk me dry.
You don't know what it's like
to be taken advantage of, ok.
I feel like a goddamn
Chinese buffet.
I get it.
I do, I get it.
You dealt with the pain of
Kimber's death with her mother,
but you haven't dealt
with your rage.
And it's normal to be angry.
Especially when
you didn't get a warning,
you didn't get a note.
You had no closure.
But I'm telling you right now,
this is not gonna
give you closure.
I don't give a damn
why I'm doing it.
All I know is that
I feel much better.
Linda, close this bitch up
for me, would you?
Looking for these?
- You took them out?
- I took them back.
But, you told me that
you wanted to help.
You lied to me.
That makes us even
then, doesn't it?
How could you be so cruel?
Cruel would be
calling the police.
Let's face it, you'd be
qualified for social security
by the time
you got out of jail.
Given the grief and
the financial hardship
you cause me
in the routh Virginia.
what I did was generous.
You should feel lucky.
You're welcome to stay
the recommended 48 hours
for recovery, I'll make sure
you're treated well.
Not any pain.
But live what happend,
nothing is fair.
You're right.
I also got you some pamphlets
for some woman's shelters.
You're welcome to use
the phone here if you'd like.
They'll help you
get back on your feet...
In an honest way.
In the meantime,
if you feel any pain at all,
just go ahead and
press that button.
Be careful, it's morphine,
so don't overdo it.
Hang in there.
Dr. Troy?
Could I ask you
for one more favor?
Are you kidding me?
Could you give me
Virginia's number?
I want to call her myself.
Tell her I'm sorry.
She's only gonna
call the police.
Well,
if that's what she does.
There's probably already
a warrant for my arrest.
Right?
And...
if I'm gonna start
a new life,
I can't stay on the run.
Who knows, maybe
she'll be nice like you were
and we'll
work something out.
I'll leave her number
right here.
Get some rest first,
though.
You look like
you need it.
Christian,
this is special agent
Reynolds and agent Ryan
from the FBI.
What are the feds doing here?
We're not pressing any charges
against Ms. Hamels.
I'm sorry?
There must be some
sort of confusion.
We're here to talk to you
about Silvio Perez.
She's an interesting girl,
wise beyond her years.
Makes sense growing up
in a family like that.
Did she say anything about why
she would make up a story like this?
Said she wanted
to change her identity.
Said she was raised by killers,
surrounded by evil.
Kid's full of guilt.
She kept going on
about how her braces
were paid for with
the blood of innocents.
She said she couldn't be
a good person
and let a bad deed
go unpunished.
We were gonna ask you
the same question, though.
Oh, I have no idea.
She came in for a consult
the other day,
asked us about
this Silvio Perez.
We told her we didn't know
anything, and she left.
The kid's loco.
We're plastic surgeons.
Who do have a number of
connections to Escobar Gallardo.
Let's not forget that he was
last seen in your offices
and that he left a trail
of dead peace officers
as payment
for services rendered.
Which is probably why
she's fixated on us.
We were very transparent
in our dealings with Escobar.
What about Silvio Perez?
First time we hard
the name was
when she mentioned it
in the consult.
That true for all of you?
Yes, it is.
Well,
we're sorry to have
taken up your time.
You should know we've
started an active investigation.
Probably won't go
anywhere, but
anything related to the war on drugs
gives our bosses hard-ons.
We'd like copies of all your records
from the time in question.
Oh, that's ok.
I mean, it'll take a few days
because, you know,
things got mixed up when
we moved here from Miami.
Well, just
call my office.
We'll send a courier.
We'll be sure
to keep this quiet.
Thanks.
And remember, we offer
a 20% off to law enforcement.
Am I dreaming?
Would someone tell me
if I'm dreaming?
I never thought
she'd go to the police.
Are you out of
your goddamn mind?
I mean, how could you
be so stupid?
I'm gonna check on the files
and see if there's anything in there.
Lizzie, you get that
shredder humming.
And remember, when
in doubt, Chuck it out.
I'm sorry, Christian.
I honestly thought
that girl deserves someone
in her life who is willing
to tell her the truth.
Don't you apologize to him.
You don't owe him Jack shit.
Well, Mr. Holier-than-thou,
I don't intend to spend
the rest of my life in prison,
so shut your mouth or
have your moral crisis
at some other point
in time.
Do you hear the way he talks to you?
It's only going to get worse.
He has absolutely
no respect for you, Sean.
I never wanted anything
to do with that Perez case,
if you recall.
You think your shit doesn't
stink as bad as mine?
After all these years,
I'm sure it does.
I don't know how much longer
I can live with it.
That's a start.
Now get up in his face.
Say, "I ain't gonna pay
for your shit, Christian.
Your ass is the only one
that's gonna fry.
I'm the bad ass now,
and I'm gonna
take care of Sean.
And there ain't nothing
you can do about it, lizardman."
Now all you have to do
is drop a dime
on him, baby.
You know it's his fault.
Your word against his.
Who do you think
they're gonna believe?
We're gonna get through this.
It's her word against ours.
Who do you think
they're gonna believe?
You need to find a better way
to deal with your stinky shit.
Hello, Marcy.
Virginia?
I finally found you.
You got my message.
I didn't realize
you'd be
stopping by tonight.
Yeah.
I had to.
I mean,
things like this just
can't be done
over the phone.
You're right.
And I'm glad you're here.
I hope you can find
some way to forgive me.
Never!
You hear me?
Knock knock.
You, uh,
sleep ok last night?
Yeah, well, me neither.
Not to make excuses,
but I've had a really
tough couple
of weeks lately.
I lost somebody
very close to me. And, um,
well, look, the point is,
I haven't been myself.
You were right.
I was cruel,
and I'm sorry. I just...
right or wrong,
you're
just trying to make
yourself feel better. And I...
understand that impulse.
You're lucky we never backed
up our files online in Miami.
All we have are these hard copies,
and they're incomplete.
We have a problem.
I doubt it.
I don't think Silvio Perez
even put his name
on the patient...
It's not Silvio,
it's Marcy Hamels.
The i.d. Thief?
Yeah, she's dead
in the recovery suite.
She what?
She's dead
in the recovery room.
I tricked her into going
under so that I could
repossess her breasts.
Are you insane?
Maybe she had an adverse
reaction to the anesthesia
or O.D'd on
the morphine drip.
Or maybe she was struck
by a bolt of lightning.
It doesn't matter.
She's dead in our offices.
And when the police
come to investigate,
they're gonna find out
you operated on her
against her will.
Why do the police
have to know?
No way, Christian.
We're not going down
that road again.
This time we do it
by the book.
We have a code blue.
Marcy Hamels flat-lined
in recovery.
We know.
Well, why aren't you guys
doing anything? Let's go.
What's going on in here?
What happened to Marcy?
Maybe her numbers were off.
Are you trying
to pin this on me?
Did you know he was operating
on this woman against her will?
No, I did not know.
I did not know at first.
No, but it's not
like you tried
to bring her out once
you found out, right?
What are you saying?
What I'm saying is that
we're all in this together.
Together?
What did I do?
You?
You're McNamara/Troy.
Ok, every little piece
of every little thing
is gonna have
your name on it as well.
You try rebuilding your business
after that kind of press.
And that's if
we don't go to jail.
What are you suggesting?
I'm suggesting
that we take care
of this ourselves.
We've done it before.
I mean, who is
this Marcy Hamels anyway?
Nobody knows her.
She's got no family, no friends.
No, not again.
We've had Silvio Perez
on our backs for 10 years.
- We don't have a choice.
- You don't have a choice, I do!
And I can do
the right thing here.
Call them.
Be a big man.
I'm sure you'll make
your kids proud,
especially when you can't afford
to pay for their education anymore.
I mean, Conor,
he's so young,
he'll only remember you
as the unemployed asshole
you're about to become,
but you would have done
the right thing. That's good.
Fix this.
This is your mess. We should
have brought your car.
Oh, yeah,
that's a great idea.
Nobody would notice a Bordeaux
Pontevecchio-colored Maserati
out in the middle
of the desert.
Yeah, that wouldn't
draw any attention.
All right, it's deep enough.
Let's get it over with.
Come on.
Put these on.
Maybe it'll keep us
from going to the chair.
All right, I got it.
Ready? 1, 2, 3.
All right.
Come on, we can't
waste any time.
Come on.
Let's do it.
Man, I love this shit.
They just don't make them
like they used to.
Do they, Sean?
Man, I love this shit.
They don't make them
like they used to.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com