Previously on nip/tuck...
Why are you with me,
Christian?
You think I'm stupid.
You hate yourself like I do.
I always go back to you
because you hate me the best.
Will you marry me?
Christian loves you,
and he is faithful to you.
I don't know who he is.
I don't know who I am.
We're bad.
Like, this is really bad.
Heck if I don't feel guilty.
Curtis?
I got to tell you,
I was a little shocked
when I heard you won
the Poland award.
We're lucky, though,
you know, Sean?
Most poor bastards,
they never get to find out
what their true
purpose in life is.
Usually, we ask our new clients
what they don't like about themselves,
but in this case,
I think we can figure it out.
What happened?
- Car accident?
- Physics.
170 pound man
falls 245 feet,
quickly reaching a maximum
velocity of 86 miles an hour
before he hits the water
4 seconds later...
which, I know, doesn't
sound like a long time.
But it's a frickin' eternity.
And was this
a suicide attempt?
Yeah, at the most cliched
spot on the planet...
the golden Gate bridge.
And you survived the fall.
You...
must be one in a million.
Close. About 1,200 people
have jumped from the bridge.
Conservative estimate...
the current's so strong there,
they assume more than that
have jumped
without being seen,
have been swept out to sea
or taken by sharks.
Only about 40 of us
have lived to tell the tale.
Why'd you do it?
Uh, what my partner means is,
we're going to need
a complete psychological picture
before we can agree to operate on you.
I don't mind talking about it.
I'm as sane as the next guy.
My psychiatrist agrees.
You ever try and kill yourself?
No.
Uh, what about you,
Dr. Troy?
You know,
I've had, uh,
rough patches, but I guess
I've always been able to...
find pleasure
in my life somehow.
Well, that's lucky.
I guess I'm just
kind of a naturally
depressive personality.
I guess, obvious.
Just...
life's just been...
kind of hard for a while.
My son died...
of leukemia.
He was 14 years old.
You know, marriages don't
survive that kind of thing.
I just felt this kind of...
darkness building up
inside me.
The edges of it disappeared,
and...
it felt like it kind of
swallowed me up.
Wasn't even painful anymore.
Everything just was so hard.
Except jumping.
Jumping was easy.
I remember, I didn't want anybody
to see me go over the rail...
like I didn't want to get
in trouble somehow.
And I went over the rail,
and there's a lip,
and I stood there,
and then, I just stepped...
I mean, the way, you
know, you step out of...
bed in the morning,
I stepped.
And I thought to my self,
"no, not this. Go back.
Stop. Go back!"
By second 2,
I knew I wanted to live.
I've never been so sure
of anything in my life.
What did you do?
Well, most of the people who've
survived landed feet first. So...
I somehow managed
to flip myself over and hit...
the water like
a blade of grass.
And it still felt like a cinderblock
to the balls, though.
Broke 2 vertebrae
in my pelvis
and, you know, obviously,
the reason I'm here.
Broke all 14 bones in your face,
but your jaw is remarkably intact.
Uh, Mr. Seabrook,
we may not be able to make you
look the way you looked before.
I don't care about that.
I just want to look normal.
Jumping gave me a second
chance to live my life,
to follow my dreams.
I want to go back to school,
maybe...
become a therapist,
start dating again.
You know, maybe, uh...
Maybe have another kid.
You must be
in a lot of pain.
You know how they say
when you die, your life
flashes before your eyes?
It's not true.
You don't see all the things
you've done. You see...
all the things you're never
going to get a chance to do,
all the opportunities
you're going to lose.
I didn't jump to my death.
I jumped to my life.
I just need you
to help me to live it.
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 7 - Episode 3
"Joel Seabrook"
Original VO: honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Corrections & Resynchro VO :
Sean
Nous recherchons un ou deux
traducteurs pour la VF
Intéressé ? Contactez-nous
sur le topic de cet épisode
sur le site
www.seriessub.com
Baby, that feels so good
Ok.
Come inside me.
Well...
Aren't you...
No. I mean, no.
I'm good.
I don't need to.
You do it.
Oh! Oh, oh,
my gosh, Sean!
Oh! Oh, my God.
Oh. Oh, my God.
That was insane.
That was weird.
Why?
I'm not used
to you not coming.
I don't always
need to come.
Well...
I do.
Honey, we're married.
We have, like, a lifetime
of orgasms ahead of us.
We're good.
It's good.
Why stay with him?
Are you suggesting
that you and I...
No.
I want to know.
Why stay with him,
if it makes you so unhappy?
I don't know.
The same reason
you do, I guess.
Kind of feel sorry
for the guy, huh?
Unlucky bastard.
He survived a fall from
the golden Gate bridge.
How is that unlucky?
He went from being
depressed and suicidal
to completely delusional
in 700 feet.
He really thinks he's going
to change his life now.
And you don't believe him.
How many times have you
sworn off drinking
and then wake up
with a hangover?
Same thing, right?
Having a hangover and attempting
suicide are not the same thing.
You would know,
I guess.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm just saying that people
don't change just because
they think they're going to die
and then get a second chance.
You had cancer.
You thought
you were going to die.
You're saying that
didn't give you
the courage to look
at life a little differently?
For about a week, yeah,
maybe. All right?
I think there's no way you can't
change after something like that.
So tell me,
how is your life so different
since you swam out to the buoy?
At a certain age, you just
accept who you are
and stop thinking there's
something better out there.
You're right.
You haven't changed at all.
You married Kimber,
and you still screw around
every chance you get.
Which reminds me, I was having
lunch at shutters the other day,
picked up these 2 hot sisters who
both want to go up 2 cup sizes.
They're coming in on Thursday.
Unbelievably hot, trust me.
I told them that'd be cool.
Is that cool with you?
Why don't you finish
up here? I forgot.
I have a meeting
I need to get to.
We have a consult after this.
Tell me what you don't like
about yourself, Mr. Wise.
Uh, don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't trying to kill myself.
Mr. Wise, the gash
around your neck
was clearly made by a belt,
probably spiked,
from the sharp indentations left
at perfectly spaced intervals.
The skin's been ripped
and twisted.
Not a surprising consequence
when you try to hang yourself.
Kudos, Sherlock.
Spiked belt it was,
although you haven't
solved the case just yet.
I wasn't trying
to commit suicide.
I was masturbating.
Autoerotic asphyxiation.
Gone awry.
My bad.
I just...
need you to fix this
so that I can
stop wearing scarves
and turtlenecks when
it's 18 degrees outside.
I liked you better when
I thought you tried to kill yourself.
You risk dying
for an orgasm?
It wasn't just an orgasm,
it was the orgasm
of a lifetime.
You have no idea.
Cutting off the blood
supply to the brain
provides an amazing high.
I do have an idea.
It's better than any drug
you've ever had...
I've ever had.
Includes quite an extensive list,
I can tell you.
Don't knock it
if you ain't tried it, doc.
Thanks, but,
you know,
I can usually find
someone to help me out.
Call it the perks
of being married.
Right.
Been there.
Divorced now.
Look, all I'm saying is,
you cut off the flow of blood
and oxygen to the brain,
your dick gets
unbelievably hard.
That's why these guys
who are hung get
these huge, stonking boners
and ejaculate when they die.
It's called induced...
induced cerebral anoxia.
I know.
That's right.
You get this euphoria.
It's like having
one foot in heaven.
So, I take it you're going to continue
with this practice even after I, uh,
repair the damage
to your neck?
Don't worry, doc.
I'll stick to silk ties
from now on.
Same high without
the ring around the collar.
Look, I'm asking you to fix this,
not how I choose to come.
Judge not,
right?
- Excuse me.
- May I help you?
Yeah. I'm looking
for Dr. Ryerson.
Is he expecting you?
We spoke earlier on the phone.
I'm Sean McNamara.
Oh! Dr. Mcnamara.
Yes. I'm Nsolo.
Curtis told me
you were coming by.
You and your partner
were the other recipients of
the other Poland award this year.
Congratulations.
Follow me, please.
Hey! Sean,
thanks for coming.
Hey,
how was your drive?
- Just fine.
- Good.
Let me know if there's anything
you need while in San Diego,
anything at all.
Thanks.
Nsolo stepped on
a land mine in Angola.
He was a beggar at the airport
when we met him, and now he...
practically runs the entire center
when I'm on the road,
which is about 10 months
out of the year.
Well, I'm glad
you were in town.
I've been wanting to see your
operation since we talked in Miami.
Well, here it is,
in all its glamour.
Not exactly
Beverly Hills, but...
That's a good thing.
So, uh...
What's going on
with Christian?
Oh, he's still sucking the
champagne and caviar out of life.
After the ceremony,
you guys took off so quickly,
- I thought maybe...
- Sorry about that, Curtis.
I had to jump
on the next flight.
There was an emergency
back at the office. So...
I cannot tell you how many trips
I've had to cut short and hop on a plane.
I remember once,
crop duster came and
picked us up on the serengeti
on the way to a malaria
outbreak in darfur.
An angry herd of wildebeests
chases us down the runway,
I kid you not.
Barely got out of there
with our necks.
The closest I've come
to anything like that
would be bumper-to-bumper
on the 405 with Christian,
who's in a bad mood 'cause
he's late for his massage.
That's why I called you.
I'm here because...
I want to help.
So what can I do?
Well, we are flying a 12-year-old
girl in from Jakarta on Thursday.
Her husband cut her
in the face with a machete
when she fought off
his rape attempt.
What we need
is a surgeon
and an O.R.
Consider it done.
You sure about this?
I mean, maybe think about it,
talk to Christian.
No, I don't need
to talk to Christian.
Just something
I want to do,
something I probably should
have done a long time ago.
All right. Well,
I'll set it up for Thursday.
Great.
This is really going
to make a difference, Sean.
What are you doing?
I want to make
my baby happy.
If my baby's not happy,
then I'm not happy.
- I'm half asleep...
- Look,
just tell me
what you want.
Anything.
I want you...
don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
You don't seem fine to me.
Come on.
Yeah.
Get it, baby.
What are you doing?
Oh, trust me. Trust me.
Trust me. Trust me, baby.
You got to trust me, ok?
You're going to have the come
of your life, I promise. Ok.
Trust me.
Look at me.
You got to trust me.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
That's my baby.
Next time,
you do me, baby.
Sorry, partner.
I was performing
a slipindicktomy.
Are we in high school?
You have to brag about
having sex with your wife?
We are not talking
about sex, partner.
I gave Kimmie the orgasm
of her lifetime, ok?
I mean, Kimmie's toes curled up
like the wicked witch of the east,
and it's all because
of Mr. Wise in there.
Seriously. I mean, we were
having marital problems.
The sex was all,
you know, whatever.
Anyway, I took his advice
and tried erotic asphyxiation.
You choked your wife?
Ok, come on. It's not like
I'm O.J. or something, all right?
I know how to deal
with the pressure. I'm a doctor.
Oh, you're right.
That's very romantic.
Trust me.
Kimber loved it.
Not as much
as you did, though.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Everything is about
power for you.
You're not satisfied...
unless you're
dominating your partner.
You do live with your
hand on her throat,
might as well screw her
that way, too, right?
Jeez, what's up
your ass today, huh?
Kimber deserves
better than this.
You know,
if you're having problems,
why don't you try
talking about it?
Ok, Mr. Marriage counselor guy.
Ok. You're giving me advice, right?
Last time I checked,
you've been divorced...
how many times?
Same as me, right?
And since when do you care
about Kimber so much?
Guys,
are you clean enough?
The guy's been under
for 6 minutes.
Hey.
Sean... Sean...
No, no, no, no.
No... don't talk.
Don't talk.
Isn't that what you like now?
No.
Sean. Sean!
Ugh! Sean, stop it!
Jesus.
Kimber...
Hey, look. I know about
the choking. He told me.
I just want to know
if you're ok.
It's fine.
It's not as bad as it looks.
You should get somebody
to look at that, you know?
Sean,
stop it.
I really... I really don't want you
to touch me right now, ok?
I came here because
we need to stop doing this.
Ok.
Ok?
Just ok?
What do you want me to say?
"Stay, we can work it out"?
Well, I would have thought maybe
you'd have a little bit more feeling than
that, or for me.
It's never what this was about.
You know that.
Ok.
Then I guess that's it.
You're not going back to him,
are you?
He's my husband, Sean.
You deserve better.
I know.
And the only reason why
I haven't been able to get it
it is because I'm fooling around
with his best friend,
and I am just as much to blame
for my own unhappiness as anybody.
And if I'm going to get
what I deserve,
I need to take
a little bit of responsibility,
refocus on my marriage...
even if that means being
completely honest with him.
How long you been going behind
my back, you cheating bastard?
I come in this morning
expecting to be
waist-deep in double Ds.
Instead, I find my 2 bimbos out
in the lobby trying to reschedule.
Oh, cool your jets.
We'll fit your bimbos in.
And I promise, this operation
won't cost you a Penny.
Good to see you,
Christian.
I don't give a shit
about the money.
If you're operating on somebody
who needs it, that's fine.
There's a first.
And... and what about him?
I mean, where did
he come from, huh?
Last time we saw each other,
you were too embarrassed
to say good-bye,
and now you're working
together in our surgical suite.
Curtis said he needed some help,
and I jumped at the opportunity.
And you just
forgot to tell me.
Frankly,
I didn't think you'd care.
Bullshit.
You knew exactly
what you were doing.
Why don't you scrub in? You can
help us with these grafts here.
No, thank you, Curtis. I have
no desire to be around Sean
when he's got his tongue
so far up your ass.
Sorry about that.
Guess you never got
around to telling him
you're going to be gone
to Africa for a month, huh?
Sorry to interrupt.
We really do need to get
a "do not disturb" sign on that door.
You know, nurse Linda's
come in a couple of times.
She needs
to take your vitals.
That's fine.
I'm through.
You know, maybe you should
go finish off in the bathroom.
Really,
it's not worth the effort.
I've had farts that
were more exciting.
Why don't we take a look, huh?
How's it look?
Looks pretty good.
Very good, in fact.
How's the patient doing?
Depressed.
That's just the anesthesia
wearing off.
You'll be fine
in a couple of days.
Bullshit.
I've been rubbing myself raw,
fantasizing my ass off.
Sex without asphyxiation is
about as exciting as...
a day without sunshine?
Right.
I forgot.
You liked me better suicidal.
Oh, no, no, no. I don't.
I mean, I did, but...
I don't.
I've been having some trouble
in my marriage, and...
I think you might
have just...
helped it.
She was a little scared at first.
Thought I was trying to choke her
to death or something.
- And?
- It worked.
It worked.
Probably the greatest orgasm
I've ever seen. I mean...
And how was it when she did you?
Blow your mind or what?
No, no, no.
I'm better at giving
than receiving.
Well, it depends
what you're receiving.
Believe me,
if you want to discover your
capacity for limitless ecstasy,
go beyond what you
ever thought possible,
get her to return the favor.
Your marriage will last forever.
Well, I think the neck's
coming along fine.
As long as you stay off the windpipe
for a couple of months,
maybe forever,
you'll be good.
You know what it's like?
To have experienced heaven,
and now be denied entry?
You know, I think I'll get you a couple
of girl-on-girl action videos,
so I'll talk to my anesthesiologist,
get a recommendation.
Hey, handsome.
Hey, honey.
I'm just going to
jump on the treadmill
before I get some dinner.
What?
Come over here.
Sit.
What are you doing?
You look like
a bitch in heat, Kimmie.
- Do i?
- Yeah.
Well,
I'm actually a tigress,
and you are a tortoise.
A tortoise?
That's exciting.
I've been reading
the kama sutra book.
You're not
the only creative lover.
I like creative, huh?
Why don't you get me off
like I got you off?
Well,
I'm not really into
that sort of thing.
Come on.
No?
But I want you to lay back.
Right here.
Spread your legs.
Give me your hands.
Come on.
You're the tigress.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, Christian.
Oh, that's so good.
What are you doing?
What?
You don't come
like that with me. That's...
but I'm having an orgasm.
You faked that.
- No, I did not.
- Yes, you did. Bullshit.
- Filthy old porn trash.
- Oh, thanks.
I'm sorry.
This is the only time
I've done it, ok?
I've never done it before.
I promise.
And why should
I believe that, huh?
Well, because I'm not really
into the choking thing.
- It freaks me out.
- Well, why didn't you just tell me?
- Because I feel guilty.
- Guilty? What the hell for?
I think that you have
made the right decision.
There's not much choice.
It's...
peach or blueberry.
I overheard Ryerson
on his cell
after you 2 worked on
that girl the other day.
You're going
with him to Africa.
I just want you to know,
I think it's really great.
I mean,
I do hate you for leaving,
but I do understand.
And by the way, when the hell
were you going to tell me?
I mean, should I
update my resume?
It hasn't sunk in yet.
What did Christian say?
Haven't told him.
Yet.
Don't say anything, ok?
You know,
it's funny.
After all these years of you
changing people,
and you being the one
who needed it.
Shithead was right.
Feels like an orgasm
everywhere...
in my feet,
shoulders.
Oh, God.
Going to come.
Get up and
take the belt off.
Shit. I can't move.
There's not enough...
I can't feel...
I can't breathe.
Stand up and take
the goddamn belt off.
Get up.
Get up!
Christian?
Jesus Christ
Christian!
No.
Are you ok?
Are you sure you don't
want them to come?
Did you try
and kill yourself?
What is it,
the choking thing?
Honey, if it is,
I don't care.
I'll do it.
I'll do whatever you want.
I'll be a slave,
if you want.
I don't want a slave.
I didn't mean it like that.
That's not what I meant.
Yes, it is.
I had this...
Moment of clarity
before I lost consciousness.
You'll never
make me happy.
I...
Can never
love you enough.
Oh, baby.
You are not...
thinking clearly.
You don't have enough
oxygen in your brain.
You don't know
what you're saying.
I've never felt so clear.
Christian, we've hit
a rough patch.
You don't break up
because of it.
We said "for better or worse",
remember?
Yeah.
I can't that part.
Ok, look.
This is my fault.
It's my fault.
I've been a bad wife,
and I've done
really bad things.
But I'm so sorry, and
I'll make it up to you.
And I know that
you'll love me again.
Can you hear
what you're saying?
I'm not good for you.
I'm meant to be alone.
He kicked me out.
That's it. It's over.
He's done with me now.
You've heard that before...
How many hundreds of times?
No, it's different this time.
You should have seen
the look at his face.
We're like 2 strangers. I mean,
the guy doesn't even like me.
Good.
He's doing you
a favor, Kimber.
It's a gift.
But I don't want
that kind of gift.
I want one that includes him,
one for us.
I mean,
he's where I belong.
Not anymore.
Maybe you never did, right?
Maybe it was just your fear
of not belonging anywhere
that made you so stuck.
Doesn't matter now.
All that matters now is,
what are you going to do?
This is your opportunity,
Kimber.
Jump.
Take the leap.
Find out who you are without him
telling you you're not good enough,
pretty enough,
smart enough.
Do it before you get too old
and you can't.
I'm not like you, Sean.
I don't hate Christian.
And I certainly don't
want to be him, either.
Hey.
What's the with bad mood?
Well, I don't really enjoy
hanging out with a bunch
of Hollywood skanks.
Oh, come on.
They're nice girls, Kimber.
You said we were
going to be alone.
You'll get your turn.
There's more than enough
Mike to go around.
Ok. Just give me a second.
I'll be right there.
I believe April is next.
Excuse me.
I thought I was the one you wanted
to spend the rest of your life with.
So did I.
Wow.
Crazy times, huh?
I'll tell you what.
It's a good thing you kicked
my ass to the curb that final time.
I mean,
it's taken a shitload
of curbs, but...
I think I finally
got the message.
I'm sorry about that.
It was shitty.
And...
I don't have an excuse
other than I was...
obsessed with Christian.
But I don't feel that way.
And you're so good to me,
and we're good together,
and I just... I really,
in my heart,
feel that 2 people
that are right for each other
need to spend the rest
of their lives together.
Honey, I've got more bumps
and bruises than a rodeo clown.
I can handle the pain, but...
after a while, you just
get tired of being laughed at.
Listen...
do me a favor,
will you, Kimber?
I've got a Chateau Mouton
Rothschild 1986 over at the bar.
Why don't you be a sweetie
and go get it?
And bring a corkscrew.
Kimber?
The wine?
Not yet.
I plan to take him to
his favorite strip club and...
drop the bomb there,
let naked women soften the blow.
Uh, no.
Not anymore.
He kicked his wife out.
Listen, Curtis,
I was thinking
we could author an article
together based on this trip.
I have an idea for
a new procedure
on patients with
neurofibromatosis.
Great.
Ok.
Yeah.
Well, we'll talk about it
when I see you in a few days.
Ah. I got to go.
Ok. Bye.
What?
Kimber fell off a boat
last night. She's, uh...
She's missing.
What?
Whose boat?
Mike
coast guard thinks she, uh...
thinks she's dead.
Wait. I... don't understand
what happened. She...
She slipped and
fell off the boat?
I think she jumped.
Jumped?
Yeah.
Suicide?
Well, but the coast guard
is still searching,
so they could still find her.
Impossible.
12 hours?
Can't survive in the water
that long, you know.
I kicked her out last night.
I told her I wanted her
out of my life.
I shouldn't have...
I should have...
I don't know what to do.
There you are.
Hey, Dr. Mcnamara,
I wanted to thank you
and Dr. Troy
for the excellent care
I've received here.
Is he around?
No. He's...
You look like you're
healing well, Mr. Seabrook.
I feel great.
Today really is the first day
of the rest of my life,
and I'm not going to let
another day pass
doing things I don't want to do
or feeling ways I don't want to feel.
Good for you.
I wish you luck
with everything.
Hope the same for you,
Dr. Mcnamara.
Goodbye.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com