Previously, on nip/Tuck...
You're one of the most respected
psychologists in the country.
It's just a good thing
I didn't sacrifice my career
so my daughter
could have one.
It's Kimber.
I'm in love with her.
What?
You seen Kimber?
It's cute, huh?
I got shot.
You got shot?
How?
I was desperate. I started robbing
convenience stores.
I'm taking the kids
to a hotel.
You can't just take them
away from me.
One day, you'll see
that this is for the best.
Tell me what you don't like
about yourself.
Erica,
Don't psychoanalyze me.
Just get me out of here.
I'm required to submit
an evaluation.
There must be an awful
lot you don't like
about yourself for you
to attempt suicide.
I wasn't attempting suicide.
I just--
I swam out too far.
Naked.
In the middle of the night,
1 1/2 miles from the shore,
clinging to a buoy.
That's a hell of a miscalculation.
I went for a night swim.
It was cold,
beautiful.
Just me and the water.
Felt like I was one
with the ocean, like...
I was inside it and...
it was inside me.
If my son were in jail
and my ex-wife
were a lesbian,
my daughter dined on hair
and my newly married,
just murdered wife
turned out to be
Lucretia Borgia,
I'd take the plunge myself.
I'd be crazy not to.
Sean, don't bullshit
a bullshitter.
I can't get you out of the psych ward
if you don't level with me.
The idea
that someone like Teddy
could be in love with me
was so overwhelming,
I was blind to who she really was,
And I, uh, I wound up
putting my kids at risk.
It's hard to forgive yourself
for something like that.
Go on.
I was gonna swim
until my arms fell off.
And then, about a mile out,
I, uh, had a...
change of heart.
Something inside of me
opened up and I...
I thought about how much
I love my family.
So, I fought.
I fought to stay alive.
Thank you, Sean.
So, did you drive?
- Yes.
- Oh, good.
So, you can give me
a ride back to malibu.
Oh, no, Sean, I can't.
The policy is very clear.
You attempted to commit suicide
within the last 48 hours.
I can't authorize your release.
It would be
professionally irresponsible.
Take care.
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 6 - Episode 6
"Alexis Stone"
Original VO: honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Correction & Resynchro VO : Sean
Hey, Bud.
You got a sec?
I wanna get your opinion
on something.
Hey, uh, I'm really sorry
to hear about Sean.
God, you think you know
someone, and then...
What do you want, Mike?
What do you think, huh?
Is it big enough?
5 carats.
Cost a quarter of a mill.
Yeah, she's gonna
go crazy for it.
Don't you think it's a little soon to be
asking Kimber to marry you? Hmm?
You've been dating for what?
3 months?
Well, when you know,
you know.
Kimber and I are soul mates.
You think this is
some kind of competition.
Not really.
She's mine.
Why don't you get
the hell out of here,
Drop your key off
at reception.
I'm popping your surgery pod
like a whitehead.
No problem.
You know what, christian?
You're an asshole.
But I really do hope
Sean gets better soon.
I'll tell you what's crazy.
Julia calling her mother and
thinking that bitch...
would ever lift a finger
to help me.
Now, just relax, all right?
It's over. You're out.
What'd you tell them, anyway?
That I tried to discourage you
from training at night
without a certified escort boat,
but nothing could stop you from
pursuing your...
dream of, one day,
swimming the English channel.
They believed I was
a competitive swimmer?
And they thought
you were delusional,
but they can't keep you
for longer than 24 hours.
Why are we stopping here?
While you were in the can
with all the other nut cases,
Mike proposed to Kimber.
So, I have a hankering
for a cold scotch
and a hot sandwich.
- She say "yes?"
- Who gives a shit? Just have a drink with me.
You just got out of the snake pit yourself.
Don't tell me you don't need one.
You know what?
Some other time.
I have a few things I need
to talk over with Julia.
Just how far were you
planning on swimming?
Changed my mind.
That's all that matters now.
I suddenly thought,
What if there are
other possibilities?
We consult each other
on everything.
Right?
What you did was
stupid and selfish.
If you ever do it again,
I'll kill you.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- All right.
- Can I get another drink, please?
- Sure.
I just need your cell phone
and car keys.
I'm an expert at reading people,
And you're about 5 minutes
from calling her or just driving over,
and either way,
someone's gonna get hurt.
You know, if you're trying
to make me feel better, it's not working.
I thought that was
the vodka's job, not mine.
So, you're a real bitch, huh?
Yep.
And you strike me as
the kind of guy
who attracts that sort of thing.
What's your name, handsome?
My name is christian.
Christian.
I'm Alexis.
I tell you what.
This one's on the house if...
you promise not to do
anything stupid,
and in return, you have to give me
all the gritty details.
Or if you'd rather
wallow in self-pity,
I'll put that on your tab.
Her name is Kimber.
We've known each other
for a very long time,
what seems like a lifetime.
Started off as a one night stand
and just...
never stopped.
The sex was that good, huh?
It was unbelievable.
And I don't even like her.
But you love her
and that's what's killing you.
I'm sorry.
I know what that's like.
But as I always say,
the best way of getting
over someone...
is to get on top
of someone else.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- What'd I do?
Oh, nothing.
You taste like honey.
And your body's like...
David
How could anyone let you go?
I'm a plastic surgeon.
Oh, my god.
Now you're really
blowing my mind.
Well...
It's time to return the favor.
I've got a better idea.
I've never had someone ask
for that on a first date before.
You have to go.
Why?
Do I have to spell it out?
I want you to leave.
You had your fun.
I don't wanna spoon.
Good-bye.
This beats the hell outta
the meatloaf I had last night.
I still don't know
what they put in it.
Thank you, Sean.
It's good to know that
my cooking's better than
the mental institution's.
- I was just trying to break the ice.
- Don't.
I like the ice.
I want to keep the frozen
right where it is.
Hey, beautiful.
Hey, sweetie, um,...
Daddy and I have some things
we want to discuss with grandma.
Can you give us some privacy?
Thanks. Mwah.
See you...
So, Sean,
how are you feeling?
Just how long would you have
kept me in that place?
Well, let's not go there.
Oh, no.
I want to answer his question.
I think you should still be
under psychiatric supervision.
Make you feel powerful, Erica?
Have control over me?
God knows, you manipulated
your daughter her whole life.
Julia,
your decision to placate
this unstable man and...
endanger the children,
is quite frankly, baffling.
Well, this unstable man
happens to be their father.
Father who's willing to leave
his children fatherless.
He's a father only
in the biological sense.
I'm petitioning for custody
of the children.
You'd really do that?
You'd take... my children from me?
You vengeful bitch.
I'd like to see you try.
Now, don't pay attention to her.
She's just doing what
she enjoys most...
causing you pain.
Um, you know what?
I'll...
take the kids back to New York
if Sean can have supervised visits.
Why are you letting her
intimidate you like this?
Because she's one of
the best child advocates
in the country, Sean.
If Erica Noughton says
a home is unsuitable...
Oh, my god, how could
you have been so stupid?
Well, in all fairness, Julia,
you haven't exactly
been June Cleaver.
Come on, Julia.
She's never gonna get the kids.
I mean, look at her.
Don't let appearance
deceive you.
Like they say,
you're as young as you feel.
And I have been feeling
remarkably youthful these days.
Whatever happens
to you in this place,
you mustn't be ashamed.
It's just the way things are.
Really? So, you know
the way things are in here?
I know that you have neither
the muscle mass
nor the gang affiliations
to be a predator,
and it's not your nature to be
a nilly queen, so,
If you don't want to be passed
around like a box of chocolates,
you had better find a protector.
You want me to become
somebody's bitch?
Cleaning a man's cell?
Doing his laundry?
Small price to pay
for your life.
You're wrong.
One is all it takes.
After you get turned out,
you lose your status as a man
and you can never
get that back.
Status?
Among savages?
It's survival of the fittest.
If you don't adapt,
you won't make it.
How's mom and dad?
They haven't come here
to see you?
No, dad came once.
He was having
a really hard time.
Then mom...
I don't want her
to see me this way.
She tried to come,
but I wouldn't see her.
So, once again,
it's about their feelings?
Matt, your parents are
totally self-absorbed.
They should be here
supporting you.
You are the one in hell.
You're not the one
that let them down.
It's the other way around.
Don't you see that?
Well, yeah, I suppose they could
have been there more. Sure.
They were too busy
acting out on each other
to instill a sense
of self in you.
And they're doing the same thing
to Connor and Annie.
If you want to be a real man,
stand up for your brother
and sister. Protect them.
How am I supposed to do that?
You can help me get custody.
You would know better than
anyone what it will cost them
if they stay with
their mother and Sean.
No offense, but...
Aren't you a little old
to be a mom?
Well...
It wasn't part
of my retirement plan.
But I can't sit out and
watch them sink
deeper into dysfunction.
Will you be my witness, Matt?
Hey.
What do you think about these?
Why not have fresh flowers
delivered, huh?
They brighten everything up,
don't they?
Oh.
What the hell?
It's expired. What?
Right.
That's all it is.
Sour yogurt.
You want to talk about it?
I mean, look.
If we're gonna work together,
then I think that we should be able
to talk to each other like we used to.
Talk to me.
I'm afraid I might hurt your feelings
and I don't want to do that anymore.
You're not going to hurt
my feelings.
As a matter of fact,
I think it might make us feel,
You know, like...
like we're getting
back to normal.
I met this woman yesterday.
Gorgeous.
I mean, hot body, hot ass.
Went back to her place
and nailed her like a...
I mean, incredible sex.
I mean raw, nasty, mean...
but in a good way... sex.
You know?
Then she asked me to...
take her in the back door,
which was great.
Anyway, we finished and, uh,
She kicked me out.
So, what's that about?
You know what?
You should have trusted
your first instinct.
Next time, don't tell me.
Hey, how's everything
going with Erica?
Well, I just got a letter
from her lawyer.
She's started
custody proceedings.
Sean, the whole thing
is ridiculous.
There's no way she's gonna get
custody of those kids, all right?
Julia's gonna stay out here
so we can fight this together.
We got an attorney, but
I'm gonna have to spend
as much time with my kids as I can
until this gets resolved.
Can you get Mike
to cover for me?
That's gonna be a problem,
because I just fired him.
I just saw him
in the exam room.
Yeah, he's cleaning
his stuff out.
We're just getting back
on our feet here.
Without his help,
we're screwed.
You need to get him
to stay, christian.
We need as much support
as we can get
if I'm gonna be able
to keep my kids.
Just leave everything
where it is.
It's my stuff. I told you
I was taking out what I brought in.
You don't have to.
Leave, that is.
I went through the contract we signed
when you first came on board,
and since there's some surgeries
on the books,
I'm holding you accountable.
So, you're trying
to get me to stay now?
No, I'd rather you go, but,
you know, it's a legal issue.
So, sue me.
- Look, I'm sorry.
- No, you look.
I'm happy to go.
And now that I've built up
my client list,
my fiancee and I
are looking forward
to starting my new practice
in Beverly hills.
- Your fiancee?
- Yeah, that's right.
Kimber accepted.
Wept tears of joy.
Happiest day of her life.
Now that it's official,
we're only gonna get better.
Alexis.
What a surprise.
What do you think
she's afraid of?
Hmm. Well, I think
we're all afraid of something.
That's what I like about it.
And if you stick around for an hour,
we can go out for a drink.
I have to be at work
in an hour.
Oh.
And, truthfully,
I'm here
for professional reasons.
Not personal.
This about your breasts?
'cause I...
I didn't want to say anything,
but you could definitely go...
a cup bigger.
I want you to give me
a sex change operation.
I want to be a man.
I was that bad, huh?
I'm a little, uh, confused. Um,
I... I thought we had a good time.
We did.
There's no reason
why we can't again.
I'll still have the same lips,
The same hot ass.
Let's get this clear.
I'm not into men.
I'm into women.
Beautiful women, like you.
Actually, I was born a man.
I had sexual reassignment
surgery when I was 23.
As a boy,
I was always so pretty.
My hand gestures were
feminine and...
it always seemed like
I was so much...
more of a girl
than a guy.
In high school,
I wasn't attracted to girls. I just...
wanted to hang out
with them.
I had crushes on all
the same guys they did.
And, finally, it was clear.
I was a girl living...
in a male body.
So, why the change of heart?
Forget to take your hormones?
I still love men.
I still love glamour,
And I'd rather hang out
with women, but...
I've come to
the understanding that...
I'm not a woman.
I--I'm a gay man.
So you, uh, you tricked me.
You've lied to me and pretended
that you're a woman.
I am a woman.
I prefer to be a man.
Haven't you ever had
a change of heart?
It's not the same as changing
one's mind.
Sometimes, we don't have
the choice about what we feel.
Oh, come on. That's the biggest line
of tranny bullshit I've ever heard.
I mean, think about
what you're saying.
You're asking the guy who, uh,...
a straight man
who you...
who you just asked to...
to give you a sex change.
So, in your mind, if I become
Alex, you become a fag?
What if I stay Alexis?
You're just some straight guy
that got duped?
No, in my mind, If you're Alex,
you'd have a bloody nose right now.
Can you please just
leave my office?
I asked you to leave.
Oh, well, this is a surprise.
Can we come in?
That depends.
Are you unarmed?
This is just a rental
while I look around
for something with a yard.
Please, mother.
You've made your point.
So, um,...
Sean and I have been so wrapped up
in our own divorce drama that, um,...
we failed to see the effect
it was having on the kids.
Anyway, I have decided
to move to L.A.
so that they can have
the benefit of both parents...
living in the same city.
And we found a really great
therapist for Annie.
- She's agreed to go twice a week.
- Annie's going to therapy.
Yes.
So, you can, uh, drop all this
bullshit about custody.
Oh, but Annie's not the one
who tried to kill herself.
Annie's not the one that wanders
from one confused relationship
to another,
Changing her self image
as frequently as she changes
her panties.
It's you two
who need counseling.
If you can't see that,
Then you're more out of touch
with reality than I thought.
Reality? Mother,
you're in your sixties.
I mean, what if
something happened?
You had a stroke.
Or die.
Renaldo will be down
in a moment.
Who?
Renaldo Panatieri.
Sean and Julia McNamara.
But not as beautiful
as your mama.
Mother,
who is this man?
Renaldo is my husband.
Julia, he'll be such
a wonderful father.
He always wanted children.
- Hey.
Look at you, huh?
We're gonna have so much fun
together, you and me.
Yes.
There you go.
Here's your monkey.
- Bye-bye.
- Thank you, Maria.
Bye.
Ok, there are 2 changes
of clothes in here for her.
Ok.
And please don't forget
her strawberry allergy.
No, no, no.
Daddy knows all about her.
Just enjoy your evening out
with Mr. Joe 6 pack.
You mean fiancee.
What?
Wow! I didn't know that...
target was, uh, selling
engagement rings. That's cool.
Thanks.
No, I'm sorry.
I just...
I'm in a bit of a funk.
I'm happy for you.
You? In a funk? Why?
Desperate encounters with people
who turn out to be freaks is...
just not working
for me anymore.
Are we talking
about the tranny?
He, she, um,
ran into Mike in the hallway
after your unfortunate encounter,
So, Mike agreed to do
the surgery for her.
Fine.
Let him.
That he-bitch is lucky that
I didn't rip her... his... face off.
Christian,
you, of all people, should have
a little more compassion.
Anytime anything good
happens to you,
whether it's a good woman
or an opportunity
to do something good,
you always turn it around
and you make it about you.
Why don't you try...
to get over that petty,
male ego of yours
and do something good because
it's good for someone else?
What about if
I gave you a ring?
What?
Better than the one
before, you know?
With the same kind
of sentiment and...
emotion?
Christian, ahem,
You don't give a shit
about me, honey.
You just hate seeing
another man with me.
No, no.
That's not true.
And I can't see you with that...
bimboy, but...
Well,...
I like my ring,
and it came from Mike's heart,
which is really good,
and it's true and it's kind.
And I don't think
you really have one.
It's kinda buried in there.
But I do have one,
and it belongs to you.
Always has.
Ahem, make sure you put Jenna
in the purple and white dolce and...
feed her protein, not sugar,
for her breakfast, ok?
I wasn't expecting you.
Mother, could you
close your robe, please?
For heaven sake,
you're a lesbian, aren't you?
You must be used
to the sight of a naked woman.
Now.
Why did you come here uninvited
and without a phone call to say?
It's been a long time
since I've seen you.
Without your clothes, I mean.
You've really aged.
Nevertheless,...
Renaldo and I are fornicating like
two sex-starved teenagers.
I guess love must be blind.
Well, there's nothing wrong
with Renaldo's eyes.
Did you see the way
he looked at me?
I thought he was
giving me a physical.
God sake.
Julia, what do you want?
Uh.
I'm here to save your marriage.
Sean has promised me that
he can take 20 years off
your appearance, head to toe,
and you know he can do it, too.
Mm-hmm.
You're here to strike
a deal, aren't you?
My lost youth
for your lost children.
That's what this is
all about, isn't it?
Your lost youth.
From the day that men
began to notice me,
you have been filled with rage.
You know, suddenly,
I had everything you'd lost.
Beauty, power,
sexual supremacy.
Now, I'm sorry I forced you
to face your age
and you have never
forgiven me.
Now, if only I could force you
to face yours.
I remember...
driving an intelligent, confident
young woman to college.
Now, she's indulging
in a prolonged adolescence
at her children's expense.
You can't steal my life
and pretend that it's yours.
See yourself out, won't you?
Mother, don't you want
a second chance?
You could look 50 again.
No, I don't think I'll be
having any more plastic surgery.
That's the wonderful thing
about raising children.
They keep you young.
Vodka soda, right?
You remembered.
I guess it must be a little
surprising, seeing me here
after everything
I said to you earlier.
I was a little harsh,
and that's why I,...
I came to apologize.
I guess I can't blame you.
Not even my gynecologist knows.
Well, if your surgeon did
such a great job,
why don't you just go back
to get the reversal?
He said that he couldn't possibly
undo all the hard work that he'd done.
It'd be like Michelangelo repainting
the sistine chapel.
Please.
My body is my Temple.
I can repaint it any way I want.
And how can you
afford all this?
The surgeries cost a fortune,
not to mention recovery period.
Trust fund.
Daddy owned hotels.
I just work here to keep busy.
Money aside, are you
aware of the risks involved?
I'm already off hormones.
I mean, just...
take out my implants.
I'll cut my hair.
I know you more than anybody
else should understand
the complications of
this kind of surgery,
but to reverse a vaginalplasty
and to rebuild a penis is...
is very complicated.
Ok? It's gonna take
a year, at least.
Do you understand the...
the microsurgery procedures involved?
No.
Well, can I explain it
to you?
Ok.
First, we sketch out the size
and shape of your new penis
over your latissimus dorsi muscle.
After raising that flap off
your ribcage,
we roll it up
and create your new penis.
Complications, however,
I mean, could include
hematoma,
vascular thrombosis,
partial, or even complete
necrosis of the flap.
But after performing microsurgery
on the blood vessels and the nerves,
We would reattach the member
in the pelvic region.
Now, I'm assuming that
you'd like to be able
to pee standing up?
I guess.
Well, in that case,
we'll have to take, uh,
a graft from the inside
of your mouth.
You'll need to wear
a catheter for 5 to 7 days.
Go to an after care facility
for up to 5 days.
The recovery period would be
3 to 6 months, at least.
And I wouldn't go through any other
procedures until we got through that.
I'm not scared and
I don't care about the risks.
It's nothing compared to a lifetime
of living in a body that...
doesn't feel like
mine anymore.
Well, in that case,
you definitely don't want
Mike Hamoui performing
this kind of surgery.
He's never even attempted
this type of thing before.
He seemed so sincere.
I know, but that's because
he's trying to rebuild
his practice
after I fired him.
What you need is a... a surgeon
who completely understands
this type of procedure.
Ok.
- Thanks for meeting with me.
- You were supposed to bring my kids.
Actually, I'm sorry.
I lied about that.
I thought you and I
needed to talk, man to man.
Well, I've got nothing
to say to you.
Well, I got something
to say to you, then.
I want you to know that
we'd never try to stop you
from being their father.
You couldn't stop me from being
their father in a million years.
But when I'm done,
I will stop you from coming
within 10 miles of those kids.
- This thing isn't over, asshole.
- Sean.
It looks like it is over.
Who do you think
you are, anyway?
- You're just some greaseball punk.
- No, I just...
What are you doing with a woman
old enough to be your grandmother, huh?
What is your angle?
All I want is to be a good
father to Annie and Conner.
That's all.
Give them something
they never had before.
A chance to be happy.
Look, man, watch out.
Don't do anything you
might regret.
I'll never regret that.
Look, man. Watch out.
Don't do anything you
might regret.
Classic borderline behavior.
That's enough.
You missed the part,
Renaldo's lying on the ground
and Sean actually spits on him.
Well, mother,
it's gonna take more than
this little video sting to get custody.
You're quite right.
Child endangerment must be
substantiated by a witness
who can prove that the parents
failed to prevent their child
from becoming
a neglected child,
an abused child,
or a juvenile delinquent.
Matt...
testified against us?
Yes.
He loves you, Julia.
Just doesn't want what happened
to him to happen to Conner and Annie.
Someday, Julia, you will
understand that what I did was
for the good of everyone.
And are you, um, videotaping
this conversation now?
No, of course not.
Good.
Be sure to have the children ready
and their things packed by friday.
You like that, baby?
Yeah.
We are gonna be
so happy together.
I...
am the luckiest guy
in the world.
And FYI...
I'm not gonna be like one of
those men who doesn't like
to wear his wedding ring.
Just so you know.
You can do whatever you want,
it really doesn't matter to me.
No, you deserve it, Kimber.
When we're not together,
I want you to feel safe.
And loved.
What do you want
to do today, huh?
I have the whole day free.
What about if you and Jenna
and I, we go for a picnic?
You want to go for a picnic?
Yeah.
Ha, you mean like with, um,
mosquitoes and ants?
Honey, that's really sweet,
but actually, saturdays are
more of a me day.
I kinda like to do my facials,
my manicures and my pedicures, ok?
How do you not know
my schedule by now?
Ok. I can...
Look after Jenna, for you.
You know, my precious
little step-daughter...
Ok, ok, Mike, I really need
you to stop kissing my ass, ok?
It's not the way
to make me happy, ok?
I just need you
to back up, and...
Just let me come to you, ok?
So you want me
to back up, like...
like how far?
Like all the way
to taking my ring back?
Well, no! Come on.
I just need a little
bit of space, ok?
And this has been a whirlwind.
Well, why don't I just call you
in like a week? Is that ok?
I'll call you.
Tie's a little crooked.
That's what you were
thinking about
when you were staring
at me over there?
You're right.
I was thinking...
you shouldn't be out of bed
so soon after surgery.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't wait to see myself in
a suit, it's been so long.
And I didn't want you to see me
for the first time, again,
in some awful paper gown.
- Not too flattering.
- No.
Can you undo
those pants for me?
Looks good.
What little there is.
Statistically speaking,
it's a little below average, but, um...
I did the best I could.
I know. I was never
a size queen anyways.
And if there's anything
this experience has taught me, it's...
that the penis does not
make the man.
It's what's in here.
Ah, Jesus.
You're gonna be sore
for a while.
What about next week?
I want to take you to dinner
and thank you.
No.
You don't need to do that.
If there's a better way
I can get you to my place,
let me know.
You're not interested.
There's a lot of things I've had
a change of heart about in my life,
but being with a guy,
definitely not one of them.
Christian?
Yeah.
Do you have a minute?
I need a little work done,
surgically speaking.
And you came to me, huh?
How about that asshole
fiance of yours, huh?
Why don't you hit him up?
Because,
I need a tattoo removed.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com