I woke up I didn't know
where I was.
Didn't know who I was.
Couldn't believe I'd slept
through most of my life.
I'd been unconscious
for 22 years.
Since 1989.
I was 18.
And the accident happened
at a construction site, is that right?
Yes, it was a summer job.
I was installing a church steeple.
A crane collapsed.
I don't even remember it
hitting me.
One second, it was
a beautiful day, the next,
lights out.
And what exactly is it
that brought you here? What...
don't you like
about yourself?
Jesus, man,
look at me.
I'm ancient!
Even though my body
was alive for 40 years,
I was only awake for 18.
And you want to look like
an 18 year old again?
I am an 18 year old!
I had plans before
I went in the coma.
I was gonna go to college.
I was gonna...
meet a girl,
have a family.
Have a career.
Mr. Kenny...
See, that's...
I'm a mister.
I'm a mister now.
I look in the mirror
and I see this old man looking
back at me. And I'm like...
"who are you?
Who put me in your body?"
I need you to make
the outside match the inside.
You can give me a chance
to live all those years that I lost
for the first time,
fully awake.
You can give me back my life.
Nip/Subs Team
presents
Season 7 - Episode 2
"Willow Banks"
Original VO: honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Original VO corrected by chamallow35
Corrections & Resynchro VO :
Sean
Why aren't you getting ready?
Ready?
For what?
I have a meet and greet
at the pacific design center tonight.
I told you this a week ago,
you don't remember?
Christian, this is really important.
I need to make contacts tonight,
and I had all of these
business cards made.
"Over 15 years experience."
In what?
Well, I had a life before
you and I met.
I designed all
my own movie sets.
Oh. Ok.
Well, you haven't exactly thanked me
for what I've done here.
Can't imagine how that
slipped my mind.
Look, I know it takes
a little bit of getting used to,
but in the overcrowded
markets in L.A.,
you need to make
bold style choices.
And speaking of style,
could you please get up off
the couch and go get dressed?
This is the third time you tried
to drag me out this week, all right?
I didn't get married so that
you could get me in a suit
and have me rub elbows
with the great unwashed.
All right.
Look, I got the house,
the job, the beautiful wife.
Just let me relax
and enjoy my life.
Ok.
Awesome ballgame last night.
You get to catch it?
- Is that you?
- Huh?
You stink.
And you look like shit.
Thank you.
You know how long it took me
to get ready this morning?
3 minutes.
Got to catch sportscenter
for the first time in months,
didn't cut myself shaving,
didn't have to swing by the dry
cleaners on my way to the office.
Yeah, maybe you should have.
I am done getting up at 6:00
every day, getting ready for work.
Shower, shave,
do the hair, press the suit.
All that bullshit's hard on a man.
Why are you looking
at that thing, by the way?
Trying to find a bed.
Only have a mattress
on the floor right now.
A man over thirty should never buy
anything that he has to put together,
particularly
from the swedes.
Julia used to buy
our furniture.
Never really had
to do this before.
Never had my own
place until now.
Ha, call my wife.
She apparently is
an interior designer now.
- Kimber?
- Matter of fact...
You'd be doing me
a huge favor.
She's being a real pain
in the ass.
Do you mind
giving her a buzz? Huh?
Excuse me. I've been
waiting for a half hour.
Should I reschedule?
I told you already, we'll be
with you as soon as we can.
- Hi.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
Mrs., um...
- Banks.
- Willow Banks.
- Willow Banks. Wow.
Beautiful.
Dr. Christian Troy.
You a model?
- I was.
- Great.
I'd like to apologize
for the receptionist.
She can be a real
bitch sometimes.
- Dr. Troy...
- Do it again, you're fired.
Shall we?
Yeah.
Please don't fire her
on my account.
Women always seem
to treat me like that.
Maybe I'll give her a raise.
Maybe I should bang the shit
out of you right here on this desk.
Dr. Troy?
Excuse me?
Yes.
So...
What can I do for you,
Ms. Banks?
I'd ask you what you
don't like about yourself,
but you look
pretty good to me.
Well,
that's exactly the problem.
Right.
I'm tired of all the attention I get
because of the way I look.
I'm tired of every guy I meet either
being too intimidated to talk to me,
or think that he can just
stroll up and ask me out.
I can't tell you how many
times a guy has tried...
some cheesy pick-up line or
howled like a dog as I walk by.
I mean, is it too much to ask
for just a little conversation
before telling me that
you're envisioning me naked?
And I'm tired of not
having any girlfriends
because they think
I make them look bad.
I just...
I can't be perfect anymore.
I want to be unperfect.
Unperfect?
Yeah.
Well, that's the stupidest thing
I ever heard.
People come in here every day
asking for what you have.
- They want your face.
- Well, I don't.
Not any longer.
It's just too much pressure,
Dr. Troy.
I feel like I'm onstage
all the time.
I even quit modeling,
and that hasn't helped.
Look, for once in my life,
I just want to be able to...
walk down the street
and be ignored.
I want to be normal looking.
I want to be average.
What about putting on
a couple of pounds?
A double cheeseburger,
something like that.
- I don't eat red meat.
- Ice cream.
- I'm lactose intolerant.
- Jesus.
You know what
I'm talking about. Just...
Just take worse care
of yourself. Like some nuts?
- No, thanks.
- Come on, you might enjoy it.
Look, I said I wanted to be
unbeautiful, not unhealthy.
Ok.
And I have tried to make
superficial changes.
I'm not wearing any make-up,
I haven't washed my hair
in like a week.
I mean, look at what I'm
wearing, for Christ sakes.
And still, your parking valet
gave me his phone number.
Well,
you'll just have
to try a little harder,
because looking
the way you look,
I would never touch you
with a scalpel.
And good luck finding
a doctor who would.
- Hey.
Oh, hello. Do you want
me to come back?
No, no, no.
Come in, come in.
- You sure?
- I just got a little carried away.
- Working out?
- Yeah.
It's kind of a metaphor
for my life these days.
- You want some water?
- Oh, no, thanks. I'm good.
I just keep
running and running
without a clue
where I'm going.
Well, at least you care about
your health and your body.
Christian's at home laying
on the couch drinking beer
like a fat slob.
Seems he's given up.
Well, maybe that's his way
of saying he's happy.
Or maybe it's his way of telling me
he doesn't care what I think.
Well, he is proud of you,
Kimber.
I suppose.
Well, ok. I hope you like
what I put together.
- Do you mind?
- No, no. Yeah, yeah.
First one.
Oh.
Now, see,...
this is a little more Christian
than me, don't you think?
All right.
Well,
what are your tastes?
Like, how would you
describe Sean McNamara?
Well, how would I know?
I'm just a doctor.
Well, you're more than that.
What about like an artsy,
intellectual, mid-century type of guy?
Or you could do kind of a homey,
kick-back, country French look?
Look, do I need
to go to therapy
just to get some furniture
for this place?
That's why I hired you.
No, it's just,
in design school, they really
emphasize on listening to the client.
You know, like your likes,
dislikes, colors.
Yeah, well, this particular
client has no self.
It seems he's arrived
in his 45th year
with no opinions
or taste of his own.
He spent too much time in
everyone else's shadow.
Kimber, just...
do your thing.
You know,
whatever you think.
Let your imagination go,
you have my permission.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Ok. Well, I think I can do
something in here.
Thank you.
I promise you,
I'm going to blow you
away with this place, ok?
I have total faith in you.
Thanks.
I'll see you later.
- Ok.
- Bye.
Bye.
- See ya.
It really is a miracle.
Oh, absolutely.
99% of comas
that last more than
three years are permanent.
No, I mean because he can
steal $40,000 from us just...
lying on this table.
It's... it's miraculous.
This is not a typical
pro-Bono case.
The wear and tear on his face
is completely out of the norm
because of his prone position.
Ok, we're doing a rhytidectomy
with an SMAS asplication.
You're right.
We can now corner the market
on rip van winkles.
Very impressive.
Made up a lot
of new expenses.
You know, I'm just trying
to be responsible.
At this point in my life,
I'm not compromising
on work I find...
interesting and rewarding
so you can have new toys.
I don't know why
you're worried about money.
I just got Kimber's first bill.
Well, unlike Mr. Kenny,
you're not a charity case, ok?
Did you think she was going
to work for free?
There's a difference between
pro-bono and bleeding me dry.
I'm her first client, and I only
hired her as a favor to you.
You know, if I had have known
you'd be such a pain in the ass,
I never would have suggested it
in the first place.
You know what?
Why don't you just leave?
I'd like to finish this
on my own.
Are you serious?
I'm tired of the witty banter
and the back and forth
and you telling me all the ways
I'm making your life more difficult.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to spend some time
focusing on my work.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Fine.
Jesus!
Wait a second, don't push it.
It's gonna get dirty.
Don't tell me you're redoing
the living room again.
No, no, this is for Sean.
I have to go there
later and finish.
I thought we were
going to stay home
and watch some
television together.
Honey, I told you,
I have a client deadline.
Client?
He's not a client,
he's Sean.
The only reason
he gave you the job
was because I asked him to
in the first place.
Well, that's not
what he told me.
Damn it, I can't find
the swatches.
Christian, why do you have
to ruin everything for me?
Look, I told Sean to call you
before you got booked up,
that's all, all right?
This is exactly what I was
worried about, by the way.
I mean, you working again was
supposed to make you feel happy,
not miserable.
Now you feel miserable
and I feel miserable, and...
It's not good.
Maybe we should spend
more time together or something.
And how are we going to
spend time together...
with that giant gut of
yours in between us?
What?
I have a gut?
And that stubble
you've got going on?
You think I like that
rubbing in between my legs?
I thought you liked
the beard.
I'm not talking about
your beard, Christian.
I'm talking about your balls.
You used to shave them for me.
Now I'm lucky...
if you even run a comb
through your hair
before you leave the house.
This whole new
Christian look...
isn't exactly
working for me.
So maybe if you could
rediscover a brush, or,
I don't know,
maybe a razor...
Until then, you're not
doing me either, ok?
Oh, don't wait up for me,
'cause I'm gonna be late.
You look good.
Sorry.
I, uh...
Linda gave me this,
and...
I used to think
the walkman was cool.
Have a seat.
I want a last little look,
send you on your way
with a clean bill of health.
My mom started crying
when she looked at me.
She said looking at me made
her feel 20 years younger.
Well,
I don't know about 20.
But we definitely
chopped off at least 10.
So,
what's next
on your agenda?
It's all pretty weird.
All my friends have grown and
have families and careers, and...
a lot of them have
moved away.
So... I really want to meet
someone my own age.
Early twenties, maybe.
I don't want to aim too high.
But I figured I'd go
to the clubs and...
see if I was any better
of a dancer than I used to be.
Any suggestions?
No, not really.
I travel in a slightly
older circle.
- Best of luck, though.
- Thank  you.
I feel like a freak.
I have no idea
what girls like today.
You know, texting,
cell phones, Google.
It's all pretty...
Nerve wracking.
Well, it's kind of like riding a bike.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Except I've never
ridden a bike.
So to speak.
- So you're...
- Yeah.
A 40-year-old virgin.
Could have been worse.
Could have died one.
I know a place
that you might like.
They even let
old guys like me in.
- Oh. Hi.
- Hi.
Did you come find me
to tell me that you changed
your mind about my surgery, or...
No, actually,
I came...
to change your mind
about the surgery.
That won't happen.
I already have
two more appointments
with plastic surgeons
next week, Dr. Troy. So...
You can call me Christian.
I'm not here
as your doctor.
You do like wine,
don't you?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Well, this is, uh...
really nice. Goes perfectly
with the colonel's
special recipe.
I've already eaten,
but thank you.
Oh, ok. Well,
that's more for me.
What are you doing?
You know, it's
Saturday night.
How do you know
I'm not going out?
You don't like
aggressive men, and...
there's more aggressive
and drunk men out...
on a Saturday night than
any other night of the week.
So why don't you do us both
a favor, just quit your yappin',
grab a couple of glasses
and a corkscrew,
and come sit your little ass
down on the couch.
Seems like I don't have to go
out to find an aggressive man.
Ok.
Come to papa.
I don't think I've had fried chicken
since I was in, like, high school.
But at least you're
removing the skin.
- That's where all the fat is.
- That's where all the taste is.
Ok.
Are you sure you don't want
to try some of this?
Yeah, no.
Ok.
Give me one of those.
The music's pretty cool.
Who is this?
To tell you the truth,
I think the last time I bought
a cd, you were still awake.
I'm mostly into pop music
from the late eighties.
You know,
Phil Collins,
Richard Marx.
There was an innocence to it.
It sucked.
The girls dress
a lot better now, though.
Yeah.
You woke up
at just the right time.
This is the slut generation.
Most of these girls,
their role models are famous
for having sex tapes.
My partner's really
the expert in these places.
Well,
what would you do now?
Hi.
I'm Dr. Sean McNamara.
I'm a plastic surgeon.
Are you guys narcs?
What do we do now?
Now we get drunk.
Tequila.
Best you have.
Tomorrow, I'm introducing you
to a triple stuft burrito with sour cream.
I think we should buy
a KFC franchise together.
Settle down
somewhere like... Fresno.
And never be heard
from again.
Sounds good.
Fat and happy ever after.
Fat and happy.
And ugly.
Wait a second.
I have an idea.
You better not be puking
your guts out in there.
You don't have
anything sweet, do you?
So what do you think?
Holy shit.
Yeah.
I can't believe I did it.
But I did it.
It worked.
I'm ugly, right?
You're, um,
impulsive.
Which is very hot.
This place is awesome!
Hey, how are you doing?
Hey.
I gotta...
I gotta get out of here.
You stay,
I'm gonna go.
What the hell...
Oh, hey.
Oh, I didn't know
you'd still be here.
Oh, well, it took a lot longer
than I thought it was going to.
Actually,
the movers just left.
So what do you think?
Oh, you hate it.
This is how you see me?
Well, old-fashioned gentleman
with a hint of...
old-world glamour,
yeah.
Old-fashioned.
Old world. Old...
pretty much says it,
right?
Sean...
Think of Clark Gable.
Or Rudolph Valentino.
If those guys had
a bachelor pad,
they'd totally decorate it
like this.
All right, you hate it.
I'm sorry if it's not
what you wanted.
I just wanted
to make you feel...
special.
Kimber...
So caught up in myself,
I wasn't thinking.
You know,
now that I'm really looking at it,
it is pretty great.
You got me,
or somebody
I'd like to be.
Yeah, now
you're just saying that.
No, no, no.
Hey.
It's completely different from anything
I could have imagined. But...
strangely...
right.
I think I'll like
coming home to this.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, Sean, thank you.
My God, you have no idea
how hard I have worked on this.
Well, you are talented,
Kimber.
Well, tell that to Christian.
He hates how I redid the house.
Our house, whatever.
Well, he can be tough.
I'm terrified of making
mistakes, right?
Like, I completely
lose my instincts.
I don't know who he is.
I don't know who I am, or...
Us as a couple.
It's just so frustrating.
But thanks for being sweet and
making me feel confident.
Doesn't take much.
A little sunshine,
a little watering.
Look what you did.
Well...
You know,
I did the library back there,
and it has this beautiful,
dark carved wood...
Show me the bedroom first.
I came here to tell you that
we can't do this again!
Oh, yeah, we can't do this
anymore, you're right.
I mean, like, we're bad.
Like, this is really bad.
I know.
And the worst.
How come
I don't feel guilty?
Is that him?
Is that Christian?
Yeah. We're only
separated by this wall.
Oh, I like it.
Not even fast food?
You gotta eat.
No I need to go surgery.
I'll have you back in a flash.
A flash?
Come on.
Big old burrito smothered
in guacamole and sour cream.
- Ok.
- Yeah?
Pull the car out front.
Meet you downstairs.
Sean, who the hell you
banging in there?
Oh, just your wife,
sweetheart.
Hey, what's up?
What the hell
are you doing here?
Well, she's doing such
a good job on the apartment,
I wanted to ask her advice
on a new desk.
Tired of glass.
I want to warm it up in here.
Why was it locked?
Um, oh, I had just
mentioned to Sean
about the new brush
nickel door hardware,
and so I must have just,
you know, hit the button.
Brush nickel?
Look, no changes
without me, ok?
I gotta go uh...
take care of something I forgot
to take care of before. And...
if I'm not back in time,
just start surgery without me, ok?
No changes
without my ok?
What kind of ego trip
is he on?
Well, it's always gotta be
the Christian Troy show,
even my office.
You were very cool, my dear.
Mmm, well, it's all
my years of acting.
Ok, so, Sean, um,
I'll get you some tear sheets
on the wood desks.
For this stuff,
you need to be YOB.
I don't drink beer,
remember.
I mean bring
your own beano.
Eating like a pig is one thing.
Smelling like them is another, ok?
Stinky women are
a real turn off.
I'll keep that in mind.
All right.
We got everything.
When do you have
to be back at work?
Whenever.
It's not like my partner has
anywhere else to go.
Then let's hit a matinee.
We'll waste
the whole afternoon.
You know, a movie theater is
the only place I can really relax.
Because you sit in the dark
and nobody bothers you, or...
Maybe.
Maybe I just like juju fruits.
.. Alien nation!
That's right! Aye!
Hey, have a little respect,
buddy boy.
Go! Go!
You know, uh,
you can slow down now.
We can't do anything
to change myself.
I'm so sick of this face.
Jesus! What are you doing,
you crazy bitch?!
If you want to kill yourself, fine,
all right, but just let me out of the car!
Sorry, Christian.
That's the only thing left
for me to do!
Stop the car,
please stop the car!
Jesus, Jesus!
Stop!
Those guys at the E.R.
were awesome, by the way.
She's lucky she's alive.
What a crazy bitch.
You're driving me
bat shit, Sean.
Don't move.
Oh, Jesus.
Like waiting to get a shot,
the anticipation is worse
than the actual needle.
Just go ahead and say it,
all right?
I think with my dick.
I am a dick. Ok, say it.
It's none of my business.
Since when is me screwing up
none of your business, huh?
You thrive on it.
That should heal
without a scar.
I know you. You can
pretend you don't care.
But I know you do.
That may have been
true once.
Come on, you can't tell me
you don't want to know what happened.
I think I'll leave that
for Kimber to ask.
She's your wife.
She's the one who
might be curious.
She's the one who pushed me
out of the goddamn door.
So tell me...
Is there anything about me
that you still like?
I don't think so.
You're a self-righteous
little prick, you know that?
Did it ever occur to you
that maybe it's you
who needs me to
be angry at you?
Quite frankly, it never
occurred to me.
Good, 'cause I'm done being
a substitute for your conscience.
I know you can't change.
So we met at the club.
It was love at first sight.
But then when he told me
his story, oh, my God,
imagine how much fun it will be
to teach him all about the last 20 years.
Obama and Britney.
All that stuff.
Well, I don't understand,
Rupert.
You don't need my consent
to have a girlfriend.
Oh, fiancée.
We're engaged.
Well,
engaged to be engaged.
I want to get McKenzie
breast implants.
A diamond is
more traditional.
My right one's
a little smaller,
and it's sort of has that
pancake thing going on.
It's been a struggle
her whole life.
Rupert, can I speak to you
alone for a moment?
She's awesome, isn't she?
She's using you.
Dude, you're wrong.
We've been doing it nonstop
for like two days straight.
Sex is not love, ok?
It's usually not even
an expression of love.
Sometimes women and men use it
for less than innocent purposes.
You're just a kid. You've
been asleep for 20 years.
You don't understand
how women work.
Oh, you do? I saw your moves
on the dance floor,
it was pretty mediocre.
- I was married for 20 years.
- How'd that turn out?
Look, I've slept
with plenty of women.
The good ones don't ask you
to buy them new breasts
on the first date.
Well, look, thank you for caring,
but I'm going to do this.
So do you want
my business or what?
Ok. I'll just go get
a couple of samples.
I assume she wants Ds?
Yeah!
How'd you know that?
They always want Ds.
Something's wrong with him!
I didn't touch him, I swear.
I just wanted new tits,
I didn't touch him!
He slipped back
into a coma.
Well, when is he
going to wake up?
Oh, my God! Baby,
what happened to you?
Your face!
I'm fine.
Your arm...
Seriously, I just...
a few scrapes,
I was in an accident.
I tried calling you.
You didn't pick up your phone.
I was...
I'm sorry...
Why didn't you
pick up your phone?
You always pick up
your phone when I call you.
- I'm sorry, I don't...
- You ignoring me?
- No.
- I get it.
I've been such
an asshole lately.
Especially with that
thing with Sean.
What thing with Sean?
He's your first real client,
and I...
I should...
I should be supporting you,
and I'm not, and I'm sorry.
Oh, honey.
You don't have to apologize.
No, I do.
I'm sorry, ok?
Well...
Please.
Um, ok.
Where's your car?
Is it totaled?
No, it wasn't my car.
I was a passenger in
somebody else's car.
Well, are they ok?
Who was it?
They're fine. I mean,
I think, you know.
It was a client,
Willow Banks.
The model?
Yeah.
You were in a...
car with Willow Banks
during the day,
and you were supposed
to be at work?
Good news is that I didn't have
any lunch, so, ha.
I think I lost about 5 pounds.
Maybe I should go
take a shower.
Maybe you should
make it a cold one.
I guess it worked
after all, huh?
I wanted people
to stop looking.
And now after they do,
they turn away.
Just like you did.
With their eyes full
of pity and disgust.
They still don't see me.
Well,
I guess going through
a windshield at 110 miles an hour
was the answer all along, huh?
Who knew?
I need to talk to you.
Please.
My parents sent me to this really
exclusive all-girls' prep school.
The rich kids would always
dress like they were poor.
Slummin' it.
It was fun for
them you know?
Cool to reject the values
you'd grown up with.
Are you coming to
a point any time soon?
When you have money,
it's easy to romanticize
not having any.
And when you're beautiful,
well, it's easy wanting
to give that up, too.
The romance of ugliness...
All I wanted was to know that
when someone looked at me,
they were actually seeing me.
Not just some image they could
place on their mantelpiece or
show off to their friends or
brag about having screwed.
You need to get help,
Willow.
Serious help.
I told you that,
I'm not the one
you should be coming to.
But you understand me.
- You're just like me!
- Bullshit!
I'm not trying to carve up my face
or endanger other people.
Then why were you
with me, huh?
You wanted to destroy
yourself, too.
In your own little passive
aggressive way.
'Cause you're pissed.
You know that all
the success you've ever had...
wasn't because of what
you did or who you were.
It's always been
about the way you look.
Just make me beautiful again.
Fix me.
Give it back to me.
I...
I can't live
looking like this.
Willow.
You need to listen to me.
There's no doctor alive
who can make you
beautiful again.
Where's my treadmill?
I had it moved to
the Malibu house.
Your apartment's
too small for it.
And I was hoping
Christian might take a hint.
I gotta get going.
No, no, no, hey,
just go back to sleep.
Come on.
Christian's going
to start to worry.
No, he won't.
Just a few more minutes.
Ok.
Will you wake me up
in 15 minutes?
Promise me you're not
going to fall asleep.
Don't worry,
I'm wide awake.
Nip/Subs Team
Seriessub.com