Previously on Nip/Tuck...
My dad just gave us
a lot of money for
the baby's education fund.
Her name is Kate. She happens to be
pretty special.
I had gastric bypass and...
I lost 100 pounds, this is the result.
I don't give a shit
if she was once fat.
Julia met someone. You met someone.
Ollie. Sounds very upper crust.
Is Ollie rich?
Yes, very.
And it's Olivia.
No.
Come on. Let them out.
They'll suffocate.
Trust me. I'm a famous TV surgeon.
Right, which is exactly
why you should be careful
because the tabloids
would kill for a photo op.
Of us naked in the hot tub?
- Sean, I got to go.
- Oh, no, you don't.
- No, I do. I got a cramp.
- OK, OK.
I promise we don't have to get naked.
Wait, Sean. Oh, God.
I, uh, I drained it.
I put enough disinfectant in there
to kill an outbreak of Ebola, so
Honey, come on.
Don't. Don't touch me.
I can't even look at you.
I'm a doctor.
Besides, this was nothing.
- Once you've seen your children born--
- Wait, wait. Hey, whoa.
Are you comparing the birth of your
children to me shitting in a hot tub?
Maybe you've got a bug or a stomach flu.
Did you eat something--
Yeah, yeah. I did. I ate something, OK?
I felt awful after doing
the scene with Aidan, and
I tried shoving the entire
catering truck down my throat.
When that didn't
make me feel any better,
I went over to the craft service table,
and I hoovered up all the sugar cookies.
At least when you do a play, you can
go to the ladies' room
and vomit between acts, but, no, this is
TV. The next shot was close on my face,
so I had to resort to plan "B."
|- You took a laxative?
- Yeah, 3.
You're never going to be able
to have sex with me again, are you?
Oh, for God's sake,
I mean, I am a little concerned
that you'd resort to pills.
It was a catch-22, OK?
I'm so dissatisfied
with everything-- work, my body--
So I eat.
I'm just scared.
I'm scared that I'm not gonna
that I'm not gonna be satisfied
till I drive away
the one thing that is working--
you.
I'm not here because you're perfect.
I'm here because you're you--
Human, beautiful--
and I'm satisfied with you.
Tiger. You should probably
replenish your liquids.
OK. Fill her up.
How about I satisfy you right now?
Transcript: swsub.com
Synchro:
_/Yellow Sub\_
Metalmarco ::ITA-SA::
Season 5 Episode 03
Everett Poe
Mr. Poe, how long have you
been a plastic surgery addict?
Well, I'm hardly what you
would call an addict.
Really?
Let's see. You've had two rhinoplasties
to reshape the nostrils and
straighten out the bone, right,
a chin augmentation,
two blepharoplasties,
a canthoplasty
to tighten up the bottom lid and
give you that catlike appearance there,
a brow lift, two otoplasties...
Am I missing anything?
- Chin reduction, not augmentation.
- My bad.
No. It's actually Dr. Woodman's bad.
I asked for a cleft.
Do you see a cleft on me?
No. That's the one thing
on your face I don't see.
It would've delineated the symmetry
that I've been trying
so hard to achieve.
Now, that hardly makes me
an addict, does it?
I mean, a perfectionist, perhaps,
but in our business, that sort of
- goes with the territory, doesn't it?
- Our business?
Yes. I own one of the top salons
in Beverly Hills-- Paragonia.
Oh, I've heard of it,
home of the $800 haircut.
Farmers get haircuts.
My clientele are
limited to the|very rich and famous.
They don't come to me for haircuts.
They come to me because they know
that I understand
beauty is an olympic ideal.
I face a mirror all day.
Every time I look up, there I am.
Now, if I'm striving to make my clients
pictures of perfection, then
don't I owe
the same obligation to myself?
And this cleft chin,
it's gonna fulfill some kind of ideal?
Dr. Troy,
when an A-list celebrity is thinking
about getting a little work done,
to whom do they turn,
their maid
or to someone like me
who has dedicated himself body and soul
to a universal standard of beauty?
So, to whom do I send my $800 haircuts?
I truly am at a loss.
OK. So, this cleft-- Are we talking
Michael or Kirk Douglas?
My migraines had just gotten so bad
that actually, it was my
mother, of all people,
that suggested I got acupuncture.
I put two needles in her,
and, bingo, she starts to sob.
And she let me stay
until I'd stopped, and then
I invited her
out to dinner to thank her.
And you're still thanking
each other, huh?
So, how did Annie deal
with the new situation? Did she freak?
Well, you know
how she adores her aunt Liz,
- so I just told her--
- You outted me to Annie?
Why? Is that something to be ashamed of?
No. It's just that I wanted
to be able to tell her myself...
Like when she's 60.
Ladies, this is the 21st century.
You can take off your corsets.
Oh, I'm sorry. No. It's just,
Olivia said I should get used to PDA's--
- Public Displays of--
- Of affection. I know.
So, how did Annie deal with it?
she's fine. I mean,
she sees how happy I am,
that I'm more complete, that
there's no missing part of me.
- You know how it is.
- Well, actually, no.
Yeah. What's up with that?
You're this beautiful, brilliant doctor,
and no one has grabbed you up yet?
- Hard to believe, huh?
- Honey, look in the mirror,
OK? you're one hot mama.
You've got sexy spilling out
of every pore, doesn't she?
I'm surprised you two never went for it.
Oh, Liz is like family.
It'd be like going out with your sister.
Well, call me stupid.
You're married with kids.
I sort of assumed
that you were straight.
Lesbian lesson number one--
Never assume.
Time's up.
Do you have an appointment?
I'll give you a lift.
Lesson two-- hotel sex:hottest kind.
We've got this incredible suite
overlooking Hollywood.
I always stay there
when I come out on business
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Let's go take advantage
of the kids not being around.
- I can't wait to do you on the balcony.
- Come on. Stop it.
And you hang in, OK?
She's out there.
You just have to have a little faith.
- Thar she blows, laddy!
- Damn it, Christian. She got sick.
Oh, come on. It's no big deal.
There are plenty of women out there.
- Some are even potty trained.
- Well, I'm not like you, OK?
You see the slightest imperfection
in a woman, and, poof, you're gone.
Well, news flash-- the only kind
of woman who doesn't fart
and cry and look like crap in the
morning is either inflatable or dead.
Sean, you're not gonna
start dating the shitter.
Stop saying that.
Come on. How can you look at her naked
body and not think,"rubber sheets"?
I got some leftover sloppy Joe's.
Any takers?
No, thank you, Liz. Asshole.
Was it something I said?
I tell you, man, that guy is
the job of the dating world.
First, julia moves to Lesbaynia.
Then bachelorette number two--
Julia is just a tourist.
She hasn't taken up residency,
and I don't think she plans to.
I thought she had the hots
for that Olly chick.
Gay, straight, who wouldn't be?
Olly is incredibly beautiful.
So she's just bi-curious?
Right now, Olivia is
something dangerous and new,
more satisfying than what she had
with Sean, but this isn't it for her.
You can see that
every time Olivia touches her.
Poor sean.
I tell you, that Julia
keeps you guessing, don't she?
At least she doesn't shit
in the hot tub.
They told me to come right in,
so at's what I did.
And you are...
Weston, Eden,
like in "The garden of."
No. I meant, you are...
How old?
Old enough. I just turned 18.
Is your mother or father
going to be present?
I don't perform surgical procedures
on anyone under
21 without parental approval.
My father is not really in
the picture anymore,
and...
I'd be too embarrassed to talk
about it in front of my mother.
What is it you want me to do?
Surgically, I mean.
My hymen broke while I was riding
my stupid horse at school.
I could feel it rip deep inside.
I want you to reconstruct it.
Why don't we call your mother and
just talk to her about your problem?
I'm still a virgin, ok, and I want to
decide who to give it to.
I don't want some damn horse
deciding it for me.
I mean, blow jobs don't count.
That's just like kissing someone,
you know,
and anal is cool.
I mean, guys don't mind as long as
they get to stick it in somewhere,
but your virginity,
that's a sacred hole.
It's a gift you give to someone
you care about.
You know, I'm not
comfortable having this conversation
without a parent present.
Is that why you're squirming
around like that, because you're
not comfortable,
or are you hard?
You need to leave.
You know, I could make
that erection go away for you.
I'd let you put it in my mouth, my ass.
2 out of 3 is not bad, right?
Maybe another time.
It was nice meeting you.
You're even hotter than you are on tv.
- Who is it?
- Dykes on bikes.
We're having a "Welcome to L.A."
weenie roast with real weenies.
What are you doing here?
Can't an old friend come by
and see how an old friend is doing?
Look at you.
I love this place.
I wish you'd called because
i'm meeting olivia, and
I have to get ready.
Just slam on a pair of jeans
and some birkenstocks, and
you're good to go, right?
What's this that you're reading,
"Lesbians at mid-life"?
You need a how-to book.
I thought this kind of stuff
just came naturally.
- This is very interesting.
- Collected writing, literary work.
You mean like
"The vagina monologues"?
Do you have a problem
with my sexuality?
I've always had a problem
with your sexuality,
and you've always
had a problem with mine.
That may have been true once,
but not any more.
Why, because you're a lesbian?
- Because I'm in love with Olivia.
- Bullshit.
For the first, time we have
the opportunity to tell each other
how we feel, and you pull
this lesbian crap.
Unbelievable.
You think I'm with
a woman because of you?
I think you're with a woman
because deep down, you realized
that you can't fall in love
with another man.
Your ego is so huge, it's a wonder
your head doesn't explode.
It's the only thing bigger than my cock,
if you recall.
Or do men disgust you now?
You know what?
I am gay, Christian.
I feel like I'm being authentic
for the first time in my life.
So, what we had wasn't authentic?
What we had was
exciting and illicit
and full of fantasy.
This has nothing to do with you.
It's just that...
women have a greater level
of sensitivity.
Sensitivity, my ass.
Remember how this felt, huh?
You know what that feels like?
Puzzle pieces fit, baby. Admit it.
Let me make love to you.
What's the worst that can happen
that I'm right,
- that we stop running?
- Damn it, Christian!
You want honesty?
You can't stand the fact that
I am happy without you,
that I'm in love with someone else.
You keep lying to yourself,
sweetie pie.
One day, the novelty will wear off,
and you'll realize you missed
your one chance at true happiness.
Olivia is a nice piece of ass,
but she can never get
inside you the way that I can.
So, this is nice, huh?
Kind of like being back in Florida.
How's school going?
Mom says it's a little
bit of an adjustment
just because everything is new,
which is totally understandable.
I want to come live with you.
Sweetie, it takes time.
You don't know any of the kids yet,
It's not the school. It's mom.
Her being gay?
It's pretty new for her,
too, you know?
I just want to live here with you.
Can i, daddy?
How about I talk it over with
your mom, and then we'll see.
sometimes when things are different,
you just have to get used to them.
Then they're not so bad, you know?
Hey, Annie.
That's cute suit,
but lay off the carbs, pudge.
Annie's fanny is starting
to look like a blubber butt.
- How do you know that girl?
- Eden? She's Olivia's daughter.
Want some?
My mom likes to loosen her girls up
before she nails them.
Julia is quite the screamer, by the way.
Why didn't you tell me
you were Olivia's daughter?
You mean use my real name?
Would've spoiled all the fun.
You know, if Julia is my new mommy,
that practically makes you my daddy.
Don't you want to be my daddy?
What I want is for you
to stay away from my daughter.
You mean my little sister?
She's so sweet and impressionable.
I have so much to teach her.
You're a real little bitch, aren't you?
What did you just call my daughter?
Your lovely daughter showed up
at my office
requesting a hymen reconstruction.
I don't care
if she asks for a third tit.
You're never to use that word
in reference to her again.
What's going on?
Hi, Julia.
I didn't know you were here.
It was so quiet.
What's the matter, mom,
have an off day?
Sweetheart, don't think that
by going on the offensive,
we'll forget that
you're the one in trouble.
So, who popped your cherry?
Charles. He's black.
And that should make a difference?
He was too big for me.
It hurt when
I rode him.
You thought you couldn't come to
your mother because
I was in the way?
No, Julia. You're not in the way.
You aren't even here. God.
Don't talk to her that way.
I won't allow it.
I bet you don't even know
the first thing about
who this Charles is,
where he comes from.
I told you, Charles is
a goddamn black stallion,
you racist piece of shit.
Even if that's true,
I'm sure it wasn't her first horse.
Your daughter came to me
to have her hymen redone. Doesn't that
make you a little bit uncomfortable?
Julia is always talking about
how you're one of the top
surgeons in the country,
so I assume she went to you
because you were the best.
Maybe the discomfort is subjective,
doctor.
Can I talk to you
for a minute outside?
- What is wrong with you?
- It's about Annie.
I don't think this is a good arrangement
with you and Olivia.
For her or for you?
If you're worried about Annie
seeing her mother with
another woman, don't.
She seems perfectly fine.
That's not what she told me.
What did she say?
She says she wants to live with me,
that she's not comfortable
with everything that's going on.
I don't believe that.
She never mentioned anything.
She loves you.
She doesn't want to hurt you.
She's not happy.
She's my baby, Sean.
I don't want to lose her.
- You're late. We started without you.
- Sorry.
I got a little hung up at Julia's.
Pass me the roto-osteotome,
would you?
Unless, of course,
you want to do the honors.
There you go.
how'd everything go with Julia?
Julia is fine. It's Annie.
She's uncomfortable
with the whole Julia gay thing.
She wants to live out here with me.
I can talk to her, Sean.
At that age, it's all about fitting in.
Maybe she's right.
Maybe I'm the one
who's having trouble with it.
Maybe.
Maybe I don't want to see her with
someone else, male or female.
Maybe Annie is picking up
on something from me.
You know what I think you should do?
You should take Kate on one of
those romantic california weekends,
you know, like shutters down
in Santa Monica
or something like that.
Forget about julia.
You're suggesting
I take the shitter to shutters?
Look. I was wrong.
You were right. We're all human.
Everybody poops.
Julia doesn't need you to take care
of her problems anymore, Sean.
You're a free agent.
You should just go for it.
Eden is rebelling.
Rember how you always wanted
to shock your parents?
Well, most kids go through
that stage, but
when your mother is a lesbian,
it's a tough act to follow.
She's giving it a hell of a try. Look.
Gay or straight, as parents,
we need to set limits.
I think she could use a few more.
Her story about the horse was true.
I checked with her riding instructor.
After a particularly difficult hurdle,
she had blood on her uniform.
Look.
She's been through a lot.
Being different, having me for a mom
isn't easy on a kid,
and if, for once in her life,
she wants to be like the other girls
in her class, I want her to have that.
I'm signing the consent form.
I'm not comfortable doing this.
Julia would never approve.
Oh, she already has.
She says medically, you're the best,
and as far as your ethics are concerned,
she trusts you completely.
I'd have to see
how extensive the tear is.
What if you can't repair it?
We'll have to use a dermal
regenerative template.
I'd shape it to an exact fit,
replicating the natural fenestrations
that would allow normal secretions.
I want your hands on me any way I can.
I'm sorry you don't agree
with my decision.
I'm just doing the best job I can,
and I know you will, too.
What's the matter?
Matt, what--
I've left kimber, dad.
I've taken the baby.
I really need your help.
She's beautiful, Matt,
but you can't just take her
and disappear.
- It's kidnapping.
- No. Kimber knows she's with me.
She doesn't care. She can't handle
being a mother right now,
and she doesn't want anything
to do with me.
I've been declared a suppressive person.
- What the hell is that?
- It's this whole campaign
they wage against people
who leave, you know?
I mean, they take your property.
They take your kids.
There was no way I was gonna let them
get their hooks into Jenna.
All right. Just relax, all right?
Here you go.
Take a seat.
Ok. Nothing is going to happen
to you now. You're with us.
- Does your mother know?
- No, and I don't want her to.
She's going through enough right now
coming out to everybody.
I don't know. I was thinking maybe
I could give it a try out here,
you know, start over.
If I can make a few thousand bucks,
find a place to live,
- maybe check into school, I think--
- You've got 250 grand, Matt.
I can't think of a better time
to dip into it.
The money is gone.
She gave it to the church.
All of it?
- Jesus, Matt, that was our house.
- I didn't know she was doing it.
That's my house,
everything I worked for.
How could you have entrusted her
with that kind of money?
He loved her, Sean.
He didn't know the bitch
was gonna to rip him off.
Look. Here's
a few hundred bucks to tide you over.
I'll pay the first
couple month's rent
when you find a place.
Thanks.
Great. You be the good father
and watch him take
everything you ever did for him
and flush it down the toilet.
Dad, look.
I'm sorry, ok? I screwed up.
It's unforgivable,
you know, and I wish there were
do-overs in life like when you're a kid.
I have to change her.
Come on. Cut the kid some slack.
He can't help it if he was born
with his brains in his dick.
He's just like his daddy.
I'm having a great time.
- I wish you were here.
- Sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm just--
- I'm just off.
- Off or off me?
- Beginning to question my technique.
- No. Don't.
You have a very good technique.
You have a great technique.
I'm just, oh, I don't know. I'm just--
I'm just distracted, you know,
with Sean and Annie and--
That Christian is a piece of work,
isn't he?
Mm, yeah. Yeah.
- You know what I think we should do?
- What?
I think we should get married.
We could drive to Boston
when we get home.
The girls can be maids of honor.
Oh, God, Olivia, I--
I just don't think I'm up for this.
You know, I don't think
Annie is up for it.
You know, I don't know that I am.
I am.
I love you...
Orgasm or no orgasm.
Sooner or later, I just--
I just want the world to know it.
Oh, sweetheart, wait.
I just have to go to the bathroom.
I'm sorry. It's not you.
It's me. I'm just distracted.
My daughter is going
through a tough time.
Ride me, baby.
Ride me.
Yes! Full gallop.
Harder, harder.
These sheets are real soft.
The blood supply seems healthy.
The risk of rejection is what
we mostly worry about
with the majority of allografts.
It feels very tender.
It will for a couple of days.
There's some slight swelling, nothing
unusual.
It's real sensitive
all along here.
Whenever I touch it,
it seems so--
I don't know.
Once the sutures are removed,
the extreme sensitivity
should lessen.
Not too much, I hope.
That'd be a drag.
Do I have to worry about tearing
my new hymen
when I touch myself like this?
I'll recommend another practice
for your follow-ups.
I don't want to see
you in here again ever.
I couldn't leave L. A.
without seeing the pacific ocean.
I was driving around,
and I just kept thinking,
"what if he's right?"
"What if I'm running away from
the only thing that I have ever wanted?"
Listen.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It's the world's oldest song.
May I have this dance?
I should be the one to tell Sean,
unless, of course, you want to.
No.
Then I'll tell him.
He'll be upset at first,
but he'll come around.
He loves us both.
I'm sure he wants us to be happy.
He'll find someone, you know?
Did he tell you what happened with
that tv actress that he's been seeing?
Oh, my God, that guy sure can pick them,
present company excluded, of course.
He's going to have to learn
how to live without you, you know?
I've been doing it for years.
Now it's his turn.
Is that what gave you an orgasm,
imagining the look on Sean's face
when you told him we were together?
That's ridiculous.
I love you.
How can you love
what you can't even see?
Where you going?
Home.
Olivia said that the only way
I'd get you out
of my system was to sleep with you.
I guess she was right.
Mattie?
Do you know when Christian
is gonna get back?
I wanted to ask him if he could--
You know what? Never mind.
It's not important. I'm sorry.
You need some money?
What did Christian give you,
a couple of hundred?
Here.
No. No. It's ok, dad.
You made your stance on that
real clear. I got it.
I was wrong.
I overreacted.
Let me help you out.
I'll make it out to cash.
- Um, why the sudden change?
- We all make mistakes, right?
We all just keep trying to do better,
be better people,
overcome our weaknesses.
It took guts to do what you did.
Take it.
Leave Kimber, start fresh.
I'm proud of you.
Did you get it?
I got $300 worth,
courtesy of my two dads.
Daddy Mac gave me a big fat check
to help me get me back on my feet.
Next week, it's mommy's turn to save me.
- Hey, I think she's hungry.
- She's fine, Matt.
Will you help me with this, please?
Patron Silver, please.
Thank you.
Well, Helen didn't exaggerate.
She said you would be over
6 feet tall and gorgeous,
although she said you'd be sitting
at the other end of the bar.
Do I pay for the drinks now,
or should I put it on my hotel bill?
- And you are...
- Valerie Farell.
I probably shouldn't have used
my real name.
Oh, well. Too late.
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
I'm afraid I've never done this before--
paid for someone.
Tell me,
does your husband
know how you spend
his hard-earned money?
Only if there's life after death.
Sorry.
Don't be.
He's much better off to me that way.
My husband owned most of the city
of Santa Clarita, California.
He was a very powerful man
in every way but one.
Well, as they say, money
can't buy you everything.
As long as it can buy you.
Campbell, isn't it?
I think that's what Helen said.
- Is it enough?
- Depends on what you're thinking.
3 or 4 years ago, we had one of the
worst droughts in California history.
The fruit just withered on the vine,
and then it rained,
and it all came back.
It's been a long dry season.
Wwell, I hope you brought an umbrella
because they're predicting
thunder storms.
I know Matt is an adult
and i'm not supposed to worry, but
when was the last time
you heard from him?
Oh, you know how it is with a new baby.
Yeah. I guess with Kimber
and the church, he's got his hands full.
So, what did you decide about Annie?
You said you figured something out.
Actually, it was her idea.
He was so checking you out.
Here. Let me have those.
So, did mommy tell you? Isn't it great?
Annie wants to go to preston,
the school where Eden goes.
It's right outside of Santa Barbara.
Isn't it wonderful?
I'll be able to look out for her 27/7
Like a real big sister,
and it's only an hour away, so
daddy can come visit
whenever he wants to.
_/Yellow Sub\_
contact@yellowsubteam.com