Here you are, Mr. Rebhun.
Another scotch and soda.
[ Chuckles ]
The only way to fly.
I used to be just like you.
Used to hate flying.
I mean, the moment
I got on the plane,
I'd be gripping those armrests
like my teeth were being drilled.
Truth is, statistically,
you could fly every day...
forthenext26,000years
before you'd have an accident.
Do you believe that?
[ Unbuckles Seat Belt ]
[Explosion]
- [passengers Chattering]
- Ooh, baby! Settle down.
- [ Chattering Continues ]
- What the hell is this?
[Shouting, Screaming]
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Chattering ]
##Happy birthday to you##
# Happy birthday to you #
# Happy birthday
dear Dana #
#Agent Scully#
# Happy birthday to you #
I didn't know it was
your birthday, Scully.
[ Cheering, Whooping ]
Mulder, you have never
remembered my birthday...
in the four years
I've known you.
That's the way I like to celebrate 'em,
is every four years.
- It's like dog years that way.
- Dog years? Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, I got something for you.
Oh, you've got
to be kidding me.
-It's something that reminded me of you.
-What, an alien implant?
Two, actually.
I made 'em into earrings.
Mmm. "Apollo 11."
Read the back.
"Commemorating Apollo 11 and the
mission to the moon. July, 1969."
- I'm touched.
- It's, um--
Excuse me.
Are you Scully and Mulder?
Oh, promise me this isn't leading
to something really embarrassing.
My name is Sharon Grafia.
I'm sorry to approach you
like this, but I followed you.
- I was asked to find you
if something happened.
- Excuse me?
You have no good reason
to believe me, but my brother,
who I believe you know, he said
you'd understand what to do.
- About what?
- If he didn't make it.
- Excuse me. Who are you talking about?
- Max. Max Fennig.
He was on his way here
to deliver something that
made him fear for his life.
Something he said
the government would kill for.
But his plane,
it went down two hours ago.
What we know right now is that the
plane designated as flight 549...
Lost radio contact tonight
at 1 900 hours EDT,
and subsequently crashed
into a wooded area...
approximately 30 miles
from Albany, New York.
Local law enforcement and EMTs
have been on the scene...
for just under two hours,
but initial reports are they've
found no survivors yet...
of the 1 34 passengers and crew
listed on the manifest.
I wish I could tell you that we had
more information about the crash site,
but darkness and the terrain are gonna
make it pretty slow going until morning.
We have a tape
of the last radio exchange...
before 549 went down,
which we're gonna play.
But I want to stress
the need to keep everything...
you know or learn
within the go team...
so that all information
to the press...
comes from the I.I.C.
- You cued up, John?
- [Man]Ready.
[pilot On Tape]Copy, Tower. please
advise. Do you see a need to adjust?
[ Tower Controller] Negative, 549.
Steady air speed of two-niner-six knots.
Maintain heading one-zero-zero
at two-niner thousand feet.
Go ahead, 549.
- [ Beeping On Tape ]
- [ Pilot ] What the hell is this?
[ Tower Controller]
549, do you read?
[ Pilot ]
We've got something-- some intercept.
My God! My God!
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
And that's all she wrote.
Controllers tried to raise 549
on all available frequencies,
but the pilots did not respond.
Okay, we've got an FAA
charter leaving in one hour.
- Accommodations--
- Excuse me, sir.
I'm Agent Mulder with the FBI.
Is there any indication
or suspicion that flight 549
may have been forced down?
- Forced down?
- You can hear the pilot say
"intercept" on the recording.
We have absolutely
no data to support that.
No confirmation of other
aircraft in the area.
- Unless you have something.
- No. No.
But there was a passenger
on that plane...
who was well-known to our
government as an alien abductee.
[ Murmuring ]
- An alien abductee?
- A man named Max Fennig.
A multiple-abduction victim.
What's known as a repeater.
- [ Murmuring Continues ]
- Hold on a second. Please.
Can I have some quiet.
He predicted the accident.
From the sound on the tape, the
plane may have been forced down.
- Forced down by who, or what?
- I'm hesitant to speculate.
- Mulder-- Your name's Mulder?
- Yes, sir.
Let me tell you something.
I’ve been doing this for 18years.
I thought I'd heard everything.
I'm looking through the manifest
here, and there was no one
named Max Fannigon flight549.
Fennig. And there may be people
who want to cover up this evidence.
Agent Mulder, is this
an official FBI position?
No, sir.
Because what you're suggesting
trivializes this tragedy...
and casts these fine people
and the work they have to do...
in a light that I think
you'd be well-advised to avoid.
I think we all share
the same goal here, sir,
and that's to find out
what caused that plane to crash.
And if any of the capable
men and women in this room...
- find Dr. Spock's phaser
or any green alien goo,
- [Murmuring, Chuckling]
we'll be sure to give you
all the credit.
- [ Chuckles ]
- All right then.
You sure know how to make a girl
feel special on her birthday.
[Indistinct Radio Chatter]
[ Indistinct Chattering ]
Have you ever seen
anything like this?
Where's the plane?
They think it hit the ground
at over 300 miles an hour
on an almost vertical descent.
Meteorological data
is being collected and analyzed,
and so far they are attributing
the crash to weather phenomena,
to a rapid depressurization
caused by a lightning strike...
or by something called a wind rotor
coming off the Adirondacks.
But not to Max Fennig.
Even if he was on this flight, looking
at this, he'd be in a hundred pieces.
They're gonna be lucky if they can
I.D. half the bodies they find here.
He was on this flight, Scully.
I'm sure of that.
Well, say we do find him.
What's that gonna prove?
I don't know.
Maybe that one man's life
was worth sacrificing 1 33 others.
[Helicopter Approaching]
Is that a hand?
- Is that a watch?
- Yeah.
What does it read?
- 8:01 .
- So does this one.
What are they listing
as the time of the crash?
Uh, 7:52 p.m.
-Just nine minutes' difference.
- It's gotta be a mistake.
Nine minutes. Do you remember the last
time you were missing nine minutes?
[ Sighs ] Mulder, no one
even reported the plane on radar.
These guys are just going
off of estimates until they
can recover the data recorder.
Yeah. Something
just occurred to me.
- What?
- I don't think we’re gonna find
Max Fennig after all.
Just a few minutes ago,
you were absolutely certain
he was on this flight.
Yeah, but I'm beginning to doubt
whether he finished this flight
with the rest of the passengers.
[Man Shouting]
Hey! Get me a medic over here!
This man's alive!
Get me a medic over here!
Somebody!
[Man]
Right there! Let's go, let's go!
We need an airlift to a burn unit
as soon as possible!
This man needs oxygen
and a saline I.V.!
Sir, can you hear me?
Sir?
I've got
what you asked for.
- All of those are from Max?
- Every letter he ever wrote me.
You said to bring everything I had.
I'm still not sure why.
Sharon, we believe that there are
things that you haven't told us.
- We need to know
everything that you know.
- About what?
About Max. About where he's been.
About where he's traveled.
About exactly what it was
he was carrying on that flight.
- Did you find Max?
- No. But we found a passenger...
with severe burns,
severe cellular damage.
Burns that we wouldn't see
unless the victim was exposed
to a high level of radiation.
- Something Max was carrying?
- We need to know what that was, Sharon.
If you’re withholding any information,
there could be severe consequences.
Mulder?
Man's name
was Larold Rebhun.
The manifest has him
listed in seat 1 3-D,
which is the aisle seat
right here.
My guess is that Max Fennig
was in 1 3-F, window seat.
But the manifest has a passenger
in that seat as a--
Paul Gidney. It's an alias
Max Fennig used in his letters
when he went underground.
He had many aliases, in fact,
one of which he used to get a job...
at the Rocky Flats Environmental
Energy Site in Colorado...
where they handle and store uranium 235
and weapons-grade plutonium.
Do you think Max
was carrying plutonium?
Mulder, the burns on that passenger's
face were deep-tissue radiation burns.
I don't know how else
he might have gotten them.
- What would Max be doing with that?
- I don't know.
He wrote hundreds, maybe even a thousand
letters describing his abductions,
but beginning in January, he started
making vague references to a theft.
Now, it seems to me from reading
it that he started to get the idea...
that he'd come on to something
that was very dangerous.
So what caused this crash?
If he was carrying
fissile plutonium, Mulder,
and it became exposed
in the cabin,
it very conceivably
could have caused the crash.
You want to know
what I think, Scully?
- I'm gonna tell you.
- [Instrument Clicking]
I think Max was abducted,
sucked right out of this door
at 29,000 feet,
and the burns we're seeing
are a result of that abduction.
- Mulder--
- And all the evidence
will point to this conclusion,
but it will be dismissed because of
its improbability, its unthinkability.
- Mulder--
- The crash of flight 549 will
go unsolved unless we prove it.
When Max is returned, he's going
to tell us the same story unless
someone gets to him first.
Mulder, Max is returned.
I found out a few minutes ago.
They found his body a short way
from the wreckage earlier today.
You're positive of this?
Traveling under the name
Paul Gidney, seat 1 3-F,
with the same burns
as his seat mate.
There's still no explanation
for this crash.
[ Investigators Chattering ]
[Rumbling]
[Electrical Crackling]
[ Gasping, Whimpering ]
[ Screaming ]
[Unzipping Bag]
[ Sobbing ]
But you guys are willing to make
a determination as to whether
there was an explosion....
pre-impact or as we can see--
[ Continues, indistinct ]
But the data only points
to an explosion...
after the aircraft--
[ Continues, indistinct ]
Did you make a positive
I.D. on Max Fennig?
Well, they've located
the cockpit voice recorder...
and the flight data
recorder.
- And?
- And the I.I.C. is making
a statement to the press...
saying that there was a complete
systems malfunction on the plane.
In other words,
there's still no explanation for
what brought this plane down.
No, not yet, but they are taking a
careful look at the emergency exit door.
And while they cannot
explain the radiation readings,
they are not ready to attribute it
as the direct cause.
They're not able to,
or they're not willing to?
- Why can't you just accept the facts?
- Because there are no facts.
What they're telling you,
what they're gonna report,
they're the opposite of facts.
A claim to ignorance
of the facts.
Claimed steadfastly, ignorance
becomes as acceptable as the truth.
What would you like them
to report?
That there is not one wristwatch
on any of those bagged bodies.
The watches have been stolen.
- Are you accusing these men
of covering evidence?
- These men? No.
These men are trained to identify
moving parts-- hydraulics, electronics.
They're trained to reconstruct
those parts in the past
and arrive at the present.
But they can't do that because
somebody has stolen the past from them.
Nine minutes of it.
Nine minutes that became a lifetime...
for those passengers
and now for their families.
Someone has got to figure out
what happened in those nine minutes.
Somehow, we've
got to get that back.
- Louis Frish?
- Yes, sir.
I just got the call from the C.O. Said
you were coming out with some questions.
I'm Agent Mulder.
This is Agent Scully.
If you’re here about the crash
the other night, I already told
the NTSB guys what I know.
- They were already out here?
- Yes, ma'am. Night of the crash.
Were you in the tower
that night?
Yes, sir. Me and
Sergeant Armando Gonzales.
- Did flight 549 show up on your radar?
- Yes, sir, it did.
- Did you establish
radio contact with them?
- No, sir.
We would have no reason
to contact a civilian airliner...
unless it crossed
into military airspace.
Would there be a record
of549 on your log?
Yes, sir.
I know it by heart.
At 1 9:52, flight 549 dropped
from an altitude of29,000 feet.
About 45 seconds later, we got
an altitude reading of triple-X.
I've never seen anything like it.
Hope to never again.
- Then what did you do?
- We called 549 and got no response.
Then we called A.T.C.
in Albany.
- And what was their response?
- We just gave them the information,
Last we'd heard.
Is there something else
you're looking for?
About nine minutes.
We've been traveling
a long way.
Wasn't the initial report that there
was no radar confirmation of the crash?
Yeah. That must have come
after our briefing.
What did you tell them?
What I was supposed to say.
Somebody's gonna figure out
what's going on.
I don't ask. I don't know.
I don't want to know.
If they find out the truth, do you think
anybody's gonna take the heat for us?
[ Sighs ]
I'm not the only liar here.
If they come back here
to talk to me, I'm tellin' the truth.
I'm not gonna have
no blood on me.
Then you make me the liar.
Roger.
[police Radio, indistinct]
- I don’t want any trouble.
Did they find her?
- No, ma'am.
- We need some answers.
The place is a mess.
- We'll do our best, ma'am.
Hey, you're gonna
have to take care of this.
- You're gonna have to pay.
- Excuse me?
The room you rented for the woman?
Well, she trashed it and split.
- Sharon Grafia?
- It was under your name.
- Yeah.
- Look at this!
And I don't know what kind
of game she was playin' in here.
She blew the door
right out of the jamb.
[Sighs]
I doubt insurance will cover it.
Does your policy cover
the acts of extraterrestrials?
- We'll take care of it.
- Great.
Okay, Scully,
hit me with your best shot.
- What do you think happened here?
- I haven't a clue.
It looks an awful lot to me like
this place fell from 29,000 feet.
- You think Max's sister--
- Was abducted, just like Max.
Maybe it runs in the family.
- What happened here?
- You're the experts.
Why don’t you bring your team
down here and work it out?
- They've got their hands full.
- Yeah, coming up with all
that inconclusive evidence.
I've come to tell you we've
found some evidence. Good evidence.
- About what caused the crash?
- Possibly. But I'm not ready
to make an announcement.
Why not?
I'm afraid I'd sound
as crazy as you.
Is there someplace
I can show you these?
Someplace with a door?
These lines you see here
running outward from center--
Those are what we call fatigue cracks,
caused by cyclic stress on the fuselage.
- From what?
- Wear and tear.
Most commercial planes have an
average 20, 30,000 hours' flight time.
Except 549 was a new plane.
549 had no wear and tear.
- Then what caused that?
- I can't tell you that.
But I can tell you this.
The way all these cracks
radiate from a central point...
Looks like the door's been shaken and
blown outward, straight off its frame.
If it hadn't been for you, we
wouldn't have known what to look for.
Sounds like what you’re describing
is physically impossible.
In normal operation, it could
never happen. Not this way.
But it did.
[ Indistinct Radio Chatter]
Hey, man, how ya doin'?
Sorry about before.
It's, uh--
I was way out of line.
I just--
[ Sighs ]
I’ve just been letting
this thing get to me, I guess.
Hey, Gonzales?
- Did you find him, Sergeant?
- He's not up there.
[ Tower Controller On Tape ]
Thirty five thousand feet.
It's negligible.
Nothing to be concerned about.
[ Pilot ] Copy, Tower. Please advise.
Do you see a need to adjust?
[Tower Controller]Negative, 549.
Steady air speed at two-niner-six knots.
Maintain heading one-zero-zero
at two-niner thousand feet.
Go ahead, 549.
[ Pilot ]
What the hell is this?
[ Tower Controller]
549, do you read?
[ Pilot ]
We got something-- some intercept.
My God! My God!
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
[ Line Ringing ]
- Scully.
- Scully, it's me.
I just realized something.
The voice of the air traffic
controller-- I've heard it before.
- We've been up for 36 hours.
Can it wait till morning?
- No, I know, I know.
I just need you to come over here
and listen to this right now, okay?
I'm on my way.
- [ Gasps ]
- Don't scream. Just listen to me.
Listen to me.
I'm the man responsible.
I'm the one that caused
that plane crash.
[Investigators Chattering]
Uh, give me a second.
You said you had someone
who had some information?
This is Louis Frish.
Sergeant Frish.
He's the air traffic controller
you heard on the recording...
that you played for us
the other night.
That was from
Albany Control Center.
- It was the voice of a civilian
air traffic controller.
- No, sir.
There seems to be more
than a little discrepancy.
What you’ve been told, what
you've been led to believe...
was built upon a lie that
Sergeant Frish was asked to perpetuate.
Along with Sergeant Gonzales,
who is now dead.
I was asked to lie. I was ordered to
lie about what happened to flight549.
- By whom?
- My C.O.
Flight 549 appeared
on my radar at 1 900 hours...
when we were asked to give its
coordinates at 1 5-second intervals.
About two minutes
past 30 degrees north,
we saw a second aircraft enter 549's
airspace in an intercept pattern.
It shadowed 549
for another ten minutes...
before we were asked to give
a new set of coordinates.
A few seconds later,
there was an explosion,
and 549 disappeared
from my radar screen.
I don't believe this man.
There's not one speck of
forensic detail to support it.
No sign of an explosion, no flashing,
no residues, no oxidation, nothing.
I'm telling you what I saw. We shot down
a civilian jet, knowingly and willingly.
I'm gonna tell you two
something.
- I have a responsibility
to the truth here.
- So do we.
This man can't testify to this story,
not without evidence.
- The military's working
to cover up that evidence.
- The story makes no sense.
Unless the aircraft that was fired on
never appeared on his radar screen--
a third, unidentified aircraft
then engaged the civilian jet,
which the sergeant never saw.
A stealth aircraft?
Shot down by the intercept
aircraft, which in turn may have
caused the crash of flight 549,
which means that the cause
of this crash is not here...
but is out there somewhere
at a second crash site.
- Somebody would’ve spotted it.
- No, they didn't know
about a second aircraft.
Except the military. Which means
that this man's life is in danger...
because he can put
the pieces together.
Then somebody has to get him
someplace safe.
If there’s a second crash site,
Let’s find it.
Mulder.
Hold on.
Mulder?
- Louis, help me out.
- Don't take your foot off the gas.
- Is he gonna see us?
- No. We gotta get under him.
We're not gonna make it.
[Rumbling]
[Sobbing]
Somebody help me! please!
Who's there?
[ Sobbing Continues ]
Oh, don't-- Don't let them
take me again!
Louis! Louis!
I want to ask you something.
This is where
flight 549 went down.
As far as you know, there's been no
substantiation of a second crash site?
- Right.
- What if that’s because
there is no second crash site?
Because that second aircraft
never fell to the ground.
It came down
somewhere around here.
- In Great Sacandaga Lake?
- Yeah.
Traveling north to south,
1 5 degrees.
It's a shallow intercept.
Yeah, that's very possible.
Possible?
Are you okay taking
Sergeant Frish back to D.C.?
- By myself?
- Yeah.
- You just let me know
what's going on, Mulder.
- As soon as I know.
- I saw the sign. Are you Bearfeld?
- Yeah.
I stopped by your place.
Nobody was home.
- Who are you?
- Fox Mulder. I'm with the FBI.
You got anything to do
with what's going on out there?
What's going on out there?
Some kind of search-and-rescue
operation...
or some damn thing.
I don't know.
- Where?
- Out over at Democrat Point.
Some kind of hovering lights,
just there and then gone.
Can you show me?
No, no, no. I need you
to take me there.
- I'm just gonna get some things.
- Where then?
[ Sighs ] I'm gonna ask for
some kind of protective arrangement.
I need to talk to my agent in charge
to get a feel for how to go on this,
but I think it's pretty clear you’re
gonna want to talk to the right people.
- Do you think I'll be prosecuted?
- For what?
I gave the coordinates.
You didn't bring
that plane down, Louis.
I lied. I misled
a federal investigator.
I misled you.
A hundred and thirty-four people,
Sergeant Gonzales-- they're all dead.
- It wasn’t your fault.
- But I'm gonna have to live with it.
I watched that plane
fall out of the sky.
It was just a dot on the screen,
just a set of numbers.
But that wreckage--
I can't get that out of my mind.
How those people died.
How easy it is to lie.
Just to say it was
a dot on the screen.
Until you see it.
Look, I can't tell you
how to feel, Louis.
But I can tell you that
I will do everything I can...
to make sure you tell your story to
somebody who will do the right thing.
Yeah. Thank you.
Do you think it's safe
to make a phone call?
I'd like to tell my girlfriend
that I'm... whatever.
Yeah. Um, just
tell her you're okay.
[ Mulder]
Over there.
- How deep is it here?
- Fifty. Sixty, maybe.
Have you worked
at this depth before?
Not exactly.
What exactly
is your experience?
Once l, uh, I got a quarter off
of the deep end at the "Y" pool.
Last call, folks.
Cocktail?
- No.
- No, thanks.
[ Chattering ]
We're being met here
by a federal marshal.
You're probably gonna end up
sleepin' in somebody's office.
You want a drink?
You need a drink. Yes.
-[Bartender] There you are.
- [Woman] Yeah. Thank you.
- Hey! Birthday girl!
- Agent Pendrill. How are you doing?
I have something for you.
Where have you been?
- I've been, uh, gone.
- Oh. Uh, can I buy you a drink?
No, you know, it's okay.
I've, uh-- I'm with somebody.
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
Let me buy him a drink too.
- No. You know what? It's okay.
- No, no. I insist.
- Bartender? Bartender?
- Yeah?
Set me up with a couple
of birthday girl drinks here.
Can I have a couple
of your finest--
[ Chattering Continues ]
Get down!
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Screaming, Shouting ]
- [ Gasping ]
- You've gotta keep breathing, Pendrill.
Do you hear me?
Subrip by drEAmEr(C)