[Crickets Chirping]
[ Gasps ]
[ Exhales ]
[Wind Whistling]
[Woman]
Here. Try this screen.
Concentrate on this area
over here. Right there.
Mulder.
What's going on ?
I'm not sure
I can explain.
You called for a forensic excavation
at 5:00 a.m. on a Sunday ?
- What are you looking for ?
-Just give me a minute, okay ?
What are you doing
out here ?
I keep having this dream.
It's about a little blond girl.
Are you saying you're out here because
of something you saw in a dream ?
Sir.
[ Gasps ]
[Woman]
Carefully remove all that. Easy.
Tell me about this dream.
I've had flashes of it
three nights in a row,
and last night it went on
long enough to lead me right to her.
- I need the chest exposed.
- Yes, sir. It just takes a little time.
[Bird Cawing]
Sir ?
Let us do that.
Sir.
If you destroy evidence, we may
never find out what happened here.
I know what happened.
She was strangled.
He used an eight-gauge
electrical cord.
He took something from the body
postmortem-- a trophy,
a piece off a bric cut from her clothes
in the shape of a heart.
- You got all these details
from your dream ?
- No. I know this M.O.
- Whose M.O. ?
-John Lee Roche.
He killed 1 3
eight- to ten-year-old girls.
This makes 1 4.
It was a difficult case.
He was extremely hard to catch.
By 1 990, ten victims
had been found,
scattered across
the eastern seaboard.
The earliest
dated back to 1 979.
VICAP named the case " Paper Hearts"
because of the trophies the killer took.
All the victims
were abducted from their homes.
Reggie purdue brought me onto
the case because he thought...
- I could get inside the killer's head.
- Did you ?
I concluded that we were
probably looking for a salesman,
someone who
traveled around a lot,
who could gain people's
confidence, someone ordinary.
Turns out Roche was
a vacuum cleaner salesman.
His job took him
allover the Northeast.
He'd be in someone's home,
demonstrating his vacuum cleaner.
All the while he'd be
checking out their kids.
He'd choose a victim and then
come back for her months later.
But it was your profile
that caught him.
What about the trophies
he took, the cloth hearts ?
We never found them, but we
didn't need them to make the case.
We had him on 1 3 counts of murder.
He admitted to 1 3.
The polygraph said he was telling
the truth, but that always bugged me.
I always wanted to find
those hearts and count them,
see if they
really added up to 1 3.
I guess they didn't.
If nothing else,
I think I can at least
help explain your dream.
I don’t think you ever stopped
thinking about this case.
I believe that you may have
solved it in your sleep.
So you think that I've somehow
had this information about
a 1 4th victim all the time...
and I've been processing it
unconsciously ?
You said it yourself once.
You said that a...
a dream is an answer to a question
we haven't learned how to ask.
You did good work, Mulder.
Let's identify this girl
so we can put her to rest.
[Door Opens]
I believe her name
is Addie Sparks.
She went missing from her home
in King of Prussia, Pennsylvania,
in June of 1 975.
I contacted the Center for Missing
and Exploited Children,
-ran a search through the database.
- 1 975's too early.
I think the match
is right.
The height is right;
the description of the sleeper is right.
That would mean Roche started
way before we thought he did.
Mulder, we're gonna have
to verify this.
Are you up for that ?
[Children Chattering,
Shouting]
[Dog Barking]
- Frank Sparks ?
- Can I help you ?
Yes. I'm Agent Scully.
This is Agent Mulder.
We're with the Federal Bureau of
investigation. May we speak with you ?
You've found Addie.
This was for
the tooth fairy.
When Addie was asleep at night, I'd come
and put a quarter in this pocket.
Her mother’s sewn it.
Where is your wife, sir ?
She passed away
last summer.
So you, uh--
you're saying the, uh-- the man
that did this is already in prison ?
Yes, sir,
and he won't get out.
You do this full-time, telling people...
this kind of news ?
No, sir, not full-time.
- It's not a good job.
- No.
I used to think...
that missing was worse
than dead because--
[ Clears Throat ]
you never knew what happened.
But now that I know,
I'm glad my wife's not here.
[Sniffles]
She got luckier.
How many more people,
uh... like me...
-are you gonna visit today ?
- Sir ?
Were there other victims
you didn't know about ?
Roche's car.
Roche drove a white EI Camino.
- I saw it in my dream.
- What are you saying that means ?
The cloth hearts he collected-- he would
have wanted to keep them close to him.
For a traveling salesman,
that means inside the car, right ?
Maybe. You're saying the hearts
might still be in his car ?
He doesn't have them in prison.
His cell is searched regularly.
His mail is examined.
His car was sold at auction
in 1992, put beyond his reach.
It's worth a look. We got to find
those hearts in order to count them.
[ Sighs ]
Don’t you think the car might have
been searched at least once already ?
Not by me.
Here it is.
I've been, you know, detailing it.
Dropped the bedshell and did
the decals, stuff like that.
- Thank you.
- Honest-to-God serial killer
owned my car ? For real ?
I'm helping him detail.
- Something's wrong here, Scully.
- Maybe it's underneath.
Mad hat.
[Trunk Opening]
Hey, Scully,
the camper shell.
The kid said he took
the camper shell off.
" Mad Hat."
Mad Hatter.
Eight, nine, ten,
eleven, twelve,
thirteen, fourteen--
[ Gasps ]
Addie Sparks.
[Scully]
Fifteen,
sixteen.
He killed
two more victims.
[Door Buzzing]
[Bali Bouncing]
[Buzzing]
Mulder.
Long time no see.
You got
a new partner.
Agent Scully.
- So what's up ?
- We found Addie Sparks, John.
Congratulations, I guess.
We also found
your cloth hearts,
-all 16ofthem.
- Huh.
Sixteen victims, John.
How come you said
there were only 1 3 ?
I don't know. Thirteen sounds
more magical, you know ?
Why don’t you tell us
about the last two victims.
You're inhere for life.
You've got nothing to lose.
- I got nothing' to gain.
- You can gain one moment
of decency in your life.
You can finally let those families
put their daughters to rest.
I understand you take this
very personally, Mulder.
How about this ?
Sink one from there,
and I'll tell you.
You'd trust
a child molester ?
You bring my hearts
and give them back tome,
I'll tell you everything
you wanna know.
- Coming out.
-[Door Opens]
[ Sniffles ]
[TV Audio, indistinct]
[Male Newscaster]
...president Nixon and H.R. Haldeman...
while transcribing
the subpoenaed tape.
Woods testified that she erased only
about five minutes of the conversation,
- but the tape contained--
- Fox, it's your move.
Under investigation
from Senator Howard Baker,
H.R. Haldeman reiterated
the White House explanation that--
- Samantha.
- Are you gonna move or not ?
- Do we have to watch this ?
- ...accidentally hitting
the record button.
It would be very difficult to reach
the conclusion it was an accident.
The Magician
comes on at 9:00.
Mom and Dad said I could watch
the movie, butt munch.
They're next door at the Gal brands'.
They left me in charge.
- [Loud Click]
- No.
[Rumbling]
Not again.
[Car Engine Revs,
Loud Hum]
Samantha, run !
[Samantha Whimpers, pants]
- [Glass Shatters]
- [Samantha]Fox! Fox !
Samantha !
[Door Buzzing]
[Door Closes]
Did you bring me
my hearts ?
Yesterday, you said something
about me taking it personally.
Why did you
say that tome ?
Where were you in 1 973 ?
- What, the whole year ?
- November. The27th of November.
Do you know
what I'm getting at ?
I was selling
vacuum cleaners in 1 973.
I made a sales trip to Martha's Vineyard
that year, and...
I sold a vacuum cleaner
to your dad.
He bought it for your mom.
I believe it was a, um...
Electro Vac Duchess,
or the princess model,
and your dad and I talked about it
at great length.
He-- He had
a really hard time choosing.
What do you know
about my sister ?
You bring me my hearts,
and maybe I'll tell you more.
[ Chokes, Grunts ]
This man--
This man hit me.
I didn't see it.
[ Knocking ]
[Door Buzzing]
I did.
[Door Closes]
He was there, Scully.
He was in the house. He took Samantha.
In your dream, Mulder. It was a dream.
Your mind made it up.
And a dream is an answer to a question
we haven’t yet figured out how to ask,
something buried
in your subconscious.
You heard him in there.
He knew something.
He mentioned being on Martha's Vineyard.
Is it a state secret that you lived
in Martha's Vineyard ?
- How would he find out about that ?
- Through the prison library.
The inmates have access
to computers and the internet.
- I checked.
Roche logged on just yesterday.
- Looking for what ?
The server records don't show,
but on the 'Net he can find out
practically anything about you.
He is playing with you.
He is committing emotional blackmail,
and you are letting him.
You walked into that room
with your heart on your sleeve.
He saw vulnerability,
and he took advantage of it.
You had a dream,
a nightmare,
and you had it because of
all the emotions that this case
is stirring up for you, but...
it was nothing
but a dream.
My last dream came true.
Do you believe tha tmy sister Samantha
was abducted by aliens ?
Have you ever
believed that ? No.
So what do you think
happened to her ?
What are you saying
you believe now ?
I don't know. I don't know what
happened. I don't know what to believe.
I just know
I have to find out now.
[ Sighs ]
- Fox ?
- Mom. I'm in the basement.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you up.
I'm sorry. How’re you feeling ?
Good, Fox. I'm fine. What are you doing
down here in the middle of the night ?
[paper Rustling]
Do you recognize... these fabrics ?
Either one of them ?
- What am I looking at ?
-Just look closely.
Do they seem familiar to you ?
- Familiar how ?
-Just familiar.
Have you seen them before ?
[ Sighs ]
I don't know what you want me to say.
You know my memory isn't as good as it
used to be ever since I had the stroke.
I just don't know what--
- It's all right.
- Oh, Fox.
Dad never bought you
a vacuum cleaner, did he ?
Yeah, a long time ago.
I don't use it anymore.
- Where is it ?
- Well, it's here under the stairs
in the storage.
Fox, what is going on ?
Sir? I’ve been denied further
access to John Lee Roche.
I'm told that order
comes down from you.
Could you tell me why you saw it fit to
strike a prisoner in federal custody ?
Agent Scully didn’t report that tome,
though she should have.
The whole thing was videotaped
as per prison policy. I saw it.
- You're lucky I don't have
your ass in a sling !
- Sir--
You've gotten too close to this.
You've let this man get to you.
I have reason to believe he can tell
us what happened to my sister Samantha.
It is looking
possible, sir.
John Lee Roche apparently spent
most of 1 973 in Boston.
He did take one sales trip to Martha's
Vineyard in October of that year.
- The timing is right.
- I need to know.
I just need to speak to him
one more time.
- This just makes it
even less of a good idea.
-Sir, the fact remains...
that we still have two more victims
that we need to find and identify.
No one has more insight into Roche than
Mulder, and this is still Mulder's case.
[ Sighs ]
You tread very lightly.
You see that he does.
I'm not talking to you
if you’re gonna hit me again.
No ! You don't get
to touch 'em.
They stay in the bag.
- Name 'em.
- Well, I think you know
one of them already.
Prove it.
Watergate was on TV.
You and your sister...
were sitting
in front of it...
playing a board game, uh,
with little red and, uh,
blue plastic pieces.
Anyway, you wanted
to watch a TV show,
the one
with Bill Bixby.
What the heck
was the name of that thing ?
How could you know
what I said ?
I was watching... from the window.
I was very careful.
If that’s true,
tell me where my sister is.
- Pick her out.
- What ?
You choose the one that was your sister,
and I'll tell you where she is.
Hey, come on.
It's a 50-50 chance.
Either way,
I'm giving you a victim.
That one.
You sure you want that one ?
No, just kidding.
It's-- It's a good choice.
Mulder ?
Let's get a team out here.
- Let somebody else do this.
- Help me, Scully.
[Scull Sighs]
[ Exhales ]
[ Sighs ]
Mulder ?
It's not her, Scully.
Am I right ?
Samantha broke her collarbone when she
was six. It was her left collarbone.
We had a rope swing
in the backyard.
-It's not broken, is it ?
-You're right, Mulder. It's not a match.
- [ Exhales ]
- It's not her.
It's somebody, though.
Like I said,
it wasa50-50 chance.
Tell us the name
of that girl.
It was
Karen Ann Philiponte.
She lived in a green rancher
in East Amherst, New York.
Mint grew outside her window.
I-- I stood outside her window...
atop sprigs of mint.
- It smelled wonderful.
- What year ?
July 1 974.
I had her mother on the hook
for a Electro Vac Argosy,
but at the last minute
she said thanks, but no thanks.
Oh, well.
It's your sister.
- If that’s true, tell me where.
- You want to know a lot more
than that, don’t you ?
You want to know everything, right ?
The big mystery revealed ?
- Drop the mind games.
- I can’t just tell you.
I mean, I know
you don't believe me yet.
You need me to show you. You need me
to lead you through it, because...
after all these years,
anything less than that's
not gonna satisfy you, right ?
You just want
to get out of here.
You're damn right I do.
If only for a day or two.
I'm realistic.
[ Sniffles ]
I mean,
more than that, l--
I can't wait
to see your face.
[Scully Whispers]
Oh, God.
You're gonna see the inside of your
cell instead. You're gonna rot there.
[Door Buzzes, Opens]
Are you okay ?
The last thing we should do is
give this man his way on this.
If we do, he could
string us along forever.
I know
you appreciate that.
There has to be another way
to come to the truth.
[Door Buzzes, Opens]
[Touch Tone Dialing]
[ Line Ringing ]
- [ Woman ] Clerk's office.
- This is Special Agent Fox Mulder
with the F.B.I.,
badge number
J-T-T-0-4-7-1-0-1-1-1-1.
I need a removal order
for a federal prisoner.
-[Woman]Do you see any houses ?
-[Girl] Yeah, lots of them.
[Woman Chuckles]
Yeah ?
Can I use the lavatory ?
Keep your hands
in your lap.
-[Woman, Girl Chattering]
- Something to drink ?
[ Mulder]
Excuse me.
- First flight ?
- Yeah.
-She's really excited.
- You having fun ?
- Mm-hmm.
- What's your name ?
Caitlin.
What the hell do you mean
he checked out Roche ?
Agent Mulder convinced the judge
that it was an emergency situation.
- And where were you ?
- I had left Agent Mulder for the day.
I suggested
that he get some sleep.
I have a clear idea of where he might
have gone, and I can catch up with him.
- I'll be the one to catch up with him.
Where's he headed ?
- Martha's Vineyard.
I would hope that you’d appreciate
the uniqueness of this situation...
and its effect
on Agent Mulder.
I fully understand
the effect it has on him.
That was the sum and total of my
last words to you on the subject.
You let me down.
Let's clean up this mess before
it gets completely out of hand.
[Door Closes]
No one home ?
I sat on this couch.
You know, your dad
bought the vacuum.
You ready ?
- Go.
- November27, 1973.
I watched the house for hours.
I parked across the way, out overthere.
I was just casing. I wasn't
planning for this to be the night.
But then, all of a sudden,
your parents leave, and I figure--
Where'd they go ?
House next door... to play pinochle.
I don't know.
- Whatever it was people did back then.
- Go on.
After they're gone, I get out
of my car, and I move closer,
and I watched you
and your sister...
playing that board game.
A little after 8:00,
I'm about ready.
So I move
to the junction box.
I cut the power,
and the lights go off.
And then I moved around
to the front door,
and I was ready
to kick the door in.
It was unlocked.
It was 1 973.
It was a different world back then.
- And then what did you do ?
- Well, you remember that.
I-- I came in the front door, and you
tried to get to your father's gun.
I give you credit for that.
But then you sort of froze, and then...
-[Mulder panting]
- I took your sister
away from all this...
- to a happier place.
- That's exactly how it happened ?
- Right here in this room ?
- Yeah.
Wrong house.
My father bought this house
after he and my mother divorced.
This house is in West Tisbury.
The house that Samantha was
abducted from is in Chilmark.
That's six miles from here !
You screwed up. You were never here.
You didn't take Samantha.
- Wishful thinking.
- No. No, but I think
I know what happened.
- Somehow you got inside my dreams.
- Come again ?
I profiled you. I got inside your head.
Maybe you got inside mine.
Maybe some nexus or connection
was formed between us.
And through that, you got access
to my memories of my sister Samantha,
- and you used them against me for this.
- You’re just resisting me.
And you're in the wrong house,
you stupid son of a bitch !
You were never here, you liar !
It's geography, man.
It was 23 years ago.
That was geography we’re talking about.
Yeah, but you remember all
the other details so vividly.
That's because you
watched it through my eyes,
through my dreams.
[ Chuckling ]
I hear things about you, Mulder.
You know what I heard ?
I heard you go after aliens...
from space.
It's like your world will be okay
as long as you can believe in,
Like, flying saucers.
[ Imitating Flying Saucer Whirring ]
But I'm telling you
the God's honest truth.
And I can see you’re not as
open-minded as you think you are.
You must have been
one hell of a salesman, Roche.
First flight’s
at 6:;00a.m.
Enjoy your last few hours of freedom.
Come on.
[Distant Cry]
[Girl]
Fox !
Fox! Help !
Unlock me! Help !
Help me!
Fox, help me !
- Unlock me! Fox !
-[Engine Revving]
Fox ! Fox, help me !
Unlock me !
- Fox !
-[Revving Continues]
[Engine Revs]
[pounding On Door]
[Scully]
Mulder?
[Skinner]
Mulder, open the door!
- You let Roche go ?
- I must've done it in my sleep.
I had another dream.
[ Sighs ] Why don’t you check
to see if anybody saw him leave.
He took
the last cloth heart.
-He also took your badge and your phone.
-Where's your gun ?
How do you explain
yourself?
- I don't.
- You don't.
A predator is loose because of you.
God only knows
how many hours lead he's got.
Any idea where
he might be headed ?
- Yeah.
- Where ?
- Where's your phone ?
- [ Sighs ]
- There was a small child on the plane.
- What child ?
[ Woman ]
Seaboard Air.
- Please put me through
to your supervisor.
- What child ?
- [ Indistinct Chatter]
- This is Special Agent Fox Mulder
with the F.B.I.
I'd like a passenger manifest
for flight 1 650...
from Washington National to Boston,
8:;50p.m. lastnight.
- My badge numberis J-T-T--
- I'm sorry. Agent Mulder called.
[ Indistinct Chatter]
- You said he was a white male ?
- Yeah.
- About how tall was he ?
- Um, he was about 6'5" or something.
[ Sobbing ]
He said his name
was Mulder.
He had a badge.
He said he was official.
- Oh, my God, what have I done ?
- We sent a unit over
to pick up the girl's mother.
- She's on her way down.
- Okay.
What am I going to tell her ?
It's all my fault.
It's not all your fault.
It's my fault.
[Chatter On police Radio]
I'm sorry. You were right.
He was playing me the whole time.
You don't think
he took Samantha ?
None of that really matters
now, does it ?
Where do you think
he'd take this girl ?
Would he follow his M. O.
and drive her out of state ?
There's no reason for that.
He knows we're gonna catch him.
He just needs it to be later
rather than sooner.
He's gonna stay in the Boston area.
He'll be somewhere nearby.
How much of a creature of habit is he ?
Do you think he'd take her
someplace familiar ?
Try to relive some past glories ?
I don't know, maybe. What ?
He lived in Boston
in the early '70s, right ?
- What’ve you got ?
- Roche's old address in the area.
- Revere. 9809 Alice Road,
apartment number 6.
- He's there.
- How do you know ?
- Alice. Alice in Wonderland.
He's the Mad Hatter.
- That's thin.
- That's where he got the idea
in the first place.
- All right, let's go ! [ Whistles ]
-[Ignition Starting]
Check the other rooms !
I don't think
he brought her here.
He never brought
anyone here.
[ Male Agent ]
No one, sir !
[ Panting ]
[Skinner]All right, spread out!
Find the entrance!
[Man Shouting]
[Shouting]
[Girl Screaming]
[ Creaking ]
I'm beginning to believe we do
share that... nexus you spoke of.
You always seem
to find me.
Are you okay, Caitlin ?
Good. My name is Fox.
I'm gonna take you home.
I have your gun, Fox.
Caitlin, can you do me a favor ?
Can you count to 20 ? Can you do that ?
Will you close your eyes and count
to 20 out loud quietly and slowly ?
- [ With Mulder] One, two,
-[Cocking Hammer]
three,
- I will shoot.
- four,
- Don't make this end badly.
- five,
six,
seven,
- You're not giving me very much choice.
- eight,
-nine--
- I really don't want
to go back to prison.
- Put the gun down, Roche !
- ...eleven, twelve,
- You have one left.
- thirteen,
-How are you gonna find her without me ?
-fourteen,
- How sure are you it's not Samantha ?
- fifteen,
- Huh ?
-sixteen, seventeen,
- How do you know ?
- eighteen,
- nineteen--
- [Gunshot]
[ Screaming ]
-[Scully]it’s okay. I got you.
-[Skinner]Call an ambulance.
[Knock At Door]
I got back
some lab results.
The dye analysis determined that
the fabric of the last heart...
was manufactured
between 1 969 and 1 974,
but beyond that,
there's nothing more they can tell us.
Mulder, it's not Samantha.
And whoever that little girl really is,
we'll find her.
How ?
I don't know,
but I do know you.
Why don't you go on home
and get some sleep.
Subrip by drEAmEr(C)