[ Scully's Voice ]
From space, it seems an abstraction,
a magician's trick
on a darkened stage.
And from this distance
one might never imagine...
that it is alive.
It first appeared in the sea
almost four billion years ago...
in the form of
single-celled life.
In an explosion of life
spanning millions of years,
nature's first multicellular
organisms began to multiply.
And then it stopped.
Four hundred and forty
million years ago,
a great mass extinction
would kill off...
nearly every species
on the planet,
leaving the vast oceans
decimated and empty.
Slowly, plants began
to evolve,
then insects,
only to be wiped out in the second
great mass extinction upon the Earth.
The cycle repeated
again and again.
Reptiles emerging independent
of the sea,
only to be killed off.
Then dinosaurs
struggling to life...
along with the first birds,
fish and flowering plants.
Their decimations-- Earth's
fourth and fifth great extinctions.
Only a hundred
thousand years ago...
Homo sapiens appear--man.
From cave paintings
to the Bible...
to Columbus and Apollo 1 1 ,
we have been a tireless force...
upon the earth and off,
cataloging the natural world
as it unfolds to us,
rising to a world population
of over five billion people...
all descended from
that original single cell,
that first spark of life.
But for all our knowledge,
what no one can say for certain...
is what or who
ignited that original spark.
Is there a plan, a purpose
or a reason to our existence?
Will we pass, as those before us,
into oblivion...
into the sixth extinction that
scientists warn is already in progress?
[ Speaking Native Language ]
Or will the mystery
be revealed...
through a sign?
A symbol?
A revelation?
[ Man ]
Professor! Professor! Professor!
[ Native ]
Two more!
[ Dialing Rotary Phone ]
Yes, get me the international operator,
please.
I need to place a call
to the United States.
Excuse me. I'm looking for the biology
department for a Professor Sandoz.
[ Chittering ]
Dr. Sandoz? Professor Sandoz,
I'm Solomon Merkmallen.
Dr. Merkmallen. My God, I thought
something had happened to you.
Oh? Did you not get my message?
We were delayed in Frankfurt.
- Look, the important thing is
you're here now and you're safe.
- Yes.
Now, you brought me something,
this discovery of yours.
- Yes.
- I'm quite anxious to see it.
I was concerned I might be
relieved of it in customs.
There was some trouble
with the X-ray machine in Germany.
- What kind of trouble did you have?
- I told you of its power.
Yes, of course.
My credentials were
the only thing that prevented me
from being further detained.
[ Monkeys Screeching ]
I can't explain how it is,
but the two pieces
have become one.
I was hoping they'd match
the piece that you found...
so that you might see
for yourself its magic.
Have you had any luck
reading it?
You're not Dr. Sandoz, are you?
-[ Grunts ]
-[ Scuffling ]
[ Screeching Continues ]
[ Gasps ]
A case like this, I, of course,
thought of your obvious interest,
Dr. Merkmallen's views
and theories being what they were.
I believe Agent Mulder
is familiar with his work.
Dr. Solomon Merkmallen,
professor of biology,
University of Ivory Coast.
[ Skinner ]
He flew in yesterday from Africa.
Two hours later, he was apparently
murdered at American University.
His body is missing,
but there was enough blood found
to make a fair assumption.
A couple of students also confirmed
that they spoke to him...
when he asked for directions
to find Dr. Steven Sandoz,
also a professor of biology.
Both men espouse a fringe theory
called panspermia.
- It's the belief that life originated--
- Elsewhere in this universe.
- You've heard of this?
- Yeah. It's the idea that
Mars or other planets...
were habitable
long before Earth...
and that cosmic collisions
on these planets...
blasted microbes into our
solar system, some of which
landed and flourished here.
You'd accept that as plausible?
Well, almost any scientist
would... theoretically.
It's just a theory.
That's about it though.
You don't think this has anything
to do with his death, do you?
Dr. Merkmallen found
an artifact in his country.
This is a rubbing of that artifact.
He claimed it contained a message,
not only of his Mars theories...
but the very meaning
of human existence.
- Much less plausible.
- Dr. Sandoz, the man he'd come to meet,
made a similar claim
in a science journal.
He said he'd found an artifact
almost identical to that
with similar writings on it.
And what was it
supposed to say?
We'd have to ask Dr. Sandoz that.
- Well, why don't we?
- We can't. He's missing.
[ Chattering ]
What are we doing, Mulder?
This is a police matter at best.
Skinner wants us on the case.
Are you gonna try to convince me you
have no personal interest in this case?
I am just a hired gun for the F.B.I.
- Oh, come on.
- I wonder if there's something to this.
Two men suggesting
that we're all Martians.
Why would they possibly
come into foul play?
That's what we're being asked
to figure out.
I can't believe you'd stand here and--
[ Fades ]
[ Ringing, Indistinct Voices Echoing ]
There has to be some limit--
I mean, this endless pursuit
of the truth, Mulder,
it just doesn't make
any sense to me now.
Mulder?
Did you hear a word
of what I just said?
- No.
Well, maybe you didn't
want to hear it.
No, I--
I couldn't hear it.
Mulder--
Look, after all you've done,
after all you've uncovered--
A conspiracy of men
doing human experiments?
Men who are all now dead.
You exposed their secrets.
I mean, you've won.
What more could you
possibly hope to do or to find?
My sister.
[ Officers Chattering ]
I guess I was right about this
being a police matter.
- Detective.
- [ Man ] Can I help you?
Agents Mulder and Scully with the F.B.I.
What do you have here?
Probable weapon. Blood and hair on it.
Looks like prints too.
- Any word on this Dr. Sandoz?
- No.
But we're being told
the prints are likely his.
- Told by whom?
- The man your partner's speaking with.
-I'm Fox Mulder with the F.B.I.
-I'm Dr. Barnes, head of the department.
They've asked me to suspend classes and
organize interviews with the faculty.
Any ideas yourself
about what happened here?
- There's plenty of speculation.
- About the missing Dr. Sandoz?
Apart from his laughable ideas,
my colleague was capable...
of almost anything to advance
his rather questionable reputation.
Capable of murder?
Dr. Sandoz's notes are full
of talk about an artifact
coming over from West Africa.
But like the man who was bringing it,
that artifact has yet to be located.
Are you speaking of this?
[ Ringing, Voices Echoing ]
Mulder?
You know, Dr. Sandoz believes
this writing was from aliens.
He's a trivial man. They have no
patience for the scientific process.
They're happy to read
their names in the tabloids.
Pseudoscientists.
Beyond embarrassment.
- What is it, Mulder?
- I don't know.
This, uh, hollow noise.
The same thing that happened to me
at work in the elevator this morning.
- Do you have a fever?
- No.
This sounds weird,
but I think it's that thing.
You're not kidding.
It's just a piece of paper.
Well, I recognize
the ideography.
[ Scully ]
You're late.
I'm sorry.
I thought this was my office.
- Fox!
- I called Chuck...
'cause I knew you would
for authentication,
and to get his professional opinion
on how you say it's affecting you.
- Fascinating, Mulder.
- You don't believe it, Chuck?
No, no. You know me. This is right up
my twisted little alley.
So, uh, what exactly
are you experiencing?
Noise, aural dissonance.
It comes and it goes.
- Is it happening right now?
- No, but it was a few minutes ago.
And it's only affecting you?
Triggered by the rubbing.
Wow. That blows me away.
- Why?
- Because the rubbing is a fake.
And I'm not the first one to say so.
The writing is Cree,
phonetic Navajo,
but no literal interpretation
makes any sense.
The fact it was found in Africa makes it
more suspicious as a fabrication.
- Suspicious of what?
- Do you know what a magic square is?
Yeah, it has to do
with the occult.
Right. Very cool. They first appear
in the ninth century in history.
But, uh...
as the story goes, God himself
instructed Adam in their use,
and then handed down the secret to all
his saints and prophets and wise men...
as a way of trapping and storing
potential power...
to the person whose name or numerical
correlative exercises that power.
- That's what this thing is?
- That's what someone would
have you to believe this is.
- How do you know that?
- As it turns out,
neither of us had to go
very far to find out.
Barnes documented
Sandoz's fakery once before.
If he was blunt about his
colleague when we met him,
in here he is downright brutal.
- Does he back any of that up?
- Well, it's quite scholarly, actually.
Barnes has made
something of a career...
exposing science
and religious fraud.
Name your wonder of the world,
he's been there, debunked that.
Yeah, but wouldn't it be
in his great interest...
to hide something that he couldn't
disprove with his scholarship?
Mulder, if it were real, then why would
an American Indian artifact...
be fused in rock on the West Coast
of the African continent?
In 1 996, a rock from Mars
was found in Antarctica.
- How did it get there?
- It was from outer space.
Begs the question, doesn't it?
Why produce a fraud
with Navajo writing...
in Africa?
[ Ringing ]
[ Scully ]
Mulder?
- Hey.
- No, no, no.
Step outside.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
You're in pain.
No, no, it's going away.
Mulder, whatever's causing this,
I think it needs immediate attention.
-I'm gonna schedule you an imaging scan.
-No, I'm okay. I really am.
You're not okay. If nothing else,
you should be at home in bed.
I'm not going home to bed, Scully.
I think I know what's causing this.
I know what happened to those
two professors and that artifact.
I had a sense of it yesterday
when I met that man Barnes.
- You had a sense of it?
- Yes.
This man Solomon Merkmallen is dead.
Barnes knows it.
He killed him-- killed him in that lab.
I hope you're not going to
suggest we arrest him on that
rather baseless assumption.
No, I'm not. Not until after
I show you what he did with the body.
I've been all through the place.
You know what you're looking for?
- We'll let you know if we find it.
- Ah.
Cops have been here, too, you know.
They couldn't find nothin' either.
[ Scoffs ]
- I'll come get you--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whatever happened to Dr. Sandoz,
he certainly liked to fly south
for the winter... a lot.
Gallup, New Mexico.
Navajo country.
I think I know who
he was going to see.
- That's Albert Holsteen.
- A World War II code talker.
Maybe he was using him to read
the symbols on the artifact.
Or write them.
Mulder, you also said
that we'd find a body.
Care to make good
on that prediction?
- Scully, you packing any latex?
- No. Why?
Doesn't it smell like somebody
forgot to take out the garbage?
-[ Insects Buzzing ]
- Ooh!
- Oh, God! Phew!
Oh!
- This.
- A genuine artifact.
One of several pieces
of an unknown hull.
Dr. Barnes has one now too.
That's why he killed Solomon Merkmallen.
- But the way his body was disposed of--
- Was to incriminate Sandoz,
to make him
look like the killer.
It's also to hide something that
no one would think to look for.
Scully, could you please tell...
what your medical exam found
in the lab report?
Parts of his body were missing--
his arms, his hands, uh,
parts of his vital organs
and his thyroid.
All of which would retain
telltale traces of radiation.
- Radiation from what?
- The artifact.
On Agent Mulder's urging,
I ran tissue samples...
through what's called a charged
particle directional spectrometer.
There were traces of a kind
of radiation called C.G.R.
[ Mulder ]
Cosmic galactic radiation.
It's a type of radiation that's found
only outside our solar system.
Agent Scully?
I don't know how to explain it,
but I feel that we can make an arrest.
Oh, forget the arrest.
We've got to find these artifacts.
-[ Ringing ]
- Agent Mulder?
- Is there someone else
on this case, sir?
- Excuse me?
There's someone else on this case
you're not telling me.
- What the hell is he talking about?
- I hear it in my head.
Mulder, let's go.
[ Voices Echoing ]
- Mulder, you're losing it.
- No, I'm not.
Listen to me.
He's not telling the truth.
I'm hearing people.
He's spying on us.
Mulder, you need
to see a doctor.
- I need to find those artifacts.
- I'll find the artifacts.
You need to go home
right now.
Mulder?
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Approaching Footsteps ]
[ Chattering ]
Is there something
you're looking for?
Yes, I was looking to speak
to Mr. Holsteen.
Mr. Holsteen cannot accept
any visitors at this time.
I understand. I saw him wheeled
out of here in an emergency.
What's wrong with him?
I'm not allowed to give out
that kind of information.
I know him.
He's helped me in the past.
I'm sure that he wouldn't
mind you telling me.
Albert has cancer.
He's suffering from its effects.
He's dying.
[ Chattering ]
[ Man Shouts, Indistinct ]
[ Monkeys Chittering ]
[ Ringing, Indistinct Voices ]
[ Ringing, Voices Continue ]
[ Scully ]
Hey!
[ Alarm Ringing, Faint ]
[ Alarm Continues ]
[ Panting ]
Look, I need answers from you.
[ Door Opens ]
You the man who called?
Dr. Barnes.
Yes?
Dr. Barnes,
you and I are...
destined to be great friends.
[ Sandoz ]
Albert was the only translator
who didn't dismiss me out of hand.
When I showed him
the original artifact...
he sensed immediately
its power and importance.
The trouble was
it was only one fragment.
- Not enough to read.
- But then other pieces surfaced.
Dr. Merkmallen found two more in the
tidal shallows. He sent me a rubbing.
Suddenly, Albert was able
to make a real translation.
A passage from the Bible on an artifact
that you're saying is extraterrestrial.
And, uh, how did
the aliens get it?
They gave it to us.
The text came from them.
I can prove it. It's written here.
I'm sure of it.
Albert was working to translate
another section when his health turned.
And, uh...
this was going to tell us what?
I don't know yet. Albert said
it just seemed to be random letters.
- [ Phone Ringing ]
- [ Woman ] Hello?
Hello. Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm trying to reach Fox Mulder.
Hold on, please.
Fox.
Hello?
- Mulder, where are you?
- I'm here. I'm resting.
Where?
Who answered the phone?
I'm home. It's okay.
Where are you?
I'm in New Mexico
with Dr. Sandoz.
- Does he have the artifact?
- Oh, God--
Mulder, this, uh, artifact,
- if I'm to believe
what I'm being told about it--
- What?
It has a passage on it
from Genesis.
- Scully, that artifact is extraterrestrial.
- Mulder, it can't be.
- Did you know what that would mean?
- It would mean nothing.
It would mean that
our progenitors were alien,
that our genesis was alien,
that we're here because of them,
that they put us here.
That is science fiction.
It doesn't hold a drop of water.
You're wrong.
It holds everything. Don't you see?
All the mysteries of science, everything
we can't understand or won't explain,
every human behaviorism, cosmology,
psychology, everything in the X-Files.
It all owes to them.
It's from them.
I will not accept that.
It is just not possible.
Well, then, you go ahead
and prove me wrong, Scully.
[ Receiver Clicks ]
[ Line Ringing ]
Yes, it's Diana Fowley
calling for him.
I received a call
from Agent Mulder this evening.
He was in a particular
state of distress.
I don't know why,
but I'm staying here until I find out.
[ Receiver Clicks ]
[ Man ] You'll find preparations
for mass destruction on a scale...
that can only be imagined.
- What can we do to stop them?
- There appears to be nothing
we can do to prevent it.
It becomes a question
of managing the crisis.
Otherwise, we're facing
annihilation ourselves.
[ Scully's Voice ] It began
with an act of supreme violence--
a big bang expanding ever outward,
cosmos born of matter and gas--
matter and gas--
ten billion years ago.
Whose idea was this?
Who had the audacity
for such invention?
And the reason?
Were we part of that plan
ten billion years ago?
Are we born only to die?
To be fruitful and multiply
and replenish the Earth...
before giving way
to our generations?
If there is a beginning,
must there be an end?
We burn like fires
in our time,
only to be extinguished.
To surrender to
the elements'eternal reclaim...
of matter and gas.
Will this all end one day?
Life no longer
passing to life.
The Earth left barren
like the stars above--
like the cosmos.
Will the hand that lit the flame
let it burn down,
let it burn out?
Could we, too,
become extinct?
Or if this fire of life living inside us
is meant to go on, who decides?
Who tends the flames?
Can he reignite the spark
even as it grows cold and weak?
The healing ceremony has begun
if you want to go inside.
No, I don't think that's right.
I don't share in their faith.
The medical doctors say
they've done everything they could.
I know.
I think they have.
-[ Cell Phone Rings ]
- I'm sorry.
- Scully.
- It's Skinner. Where are you?
- I'm with Dr. Sandoz.
- Where?
In Gallup, New Mexico.
Where are you?
The hospital in Georgetown.
I'm calling with bad news.
Mulder's in serious condition.
- What happened to him?
- Nobody knows.
You should do whatever you can
to get here as soon as possible.
I have to go.
I have to leave.
Please, don't let anyone know
where I am... until we know for sure.
[ Approaching Footsteps ]
They just told me he's in
the special psychiatric unit.
- I told you on the phone--
- No, you said there was bad news.
You didn't tell me
what was wrong.
I'm sorry. It just took me
three flights to get here.
I don't know what to do.
No one else does either.
I knew you'd want to be here to see him,
to talk to the doctors.
What? What is it?
[ Mulder, Indistinct ]
[ Door Opens ]
Thank you for coming.
He was asking for you
last night.
- You shouldn't be in here.
- What's wrong with him?
This man, Fox Mulder.
[ Screaming ]
I'm not sure what's wrong with him,
and we don't know what to do for him.
He's got extremely
abnormal brain function,
but there's no signs of stroke.
- We're waiting to run more tests.
- Waiting for what?
He's extremely violent.
With what we've given him,
he should be in a barbiturate coma.
But there's brain activity
in areas we've never seen before.
- I wanna talk to him.
- No, he's a danger to anyone.
- Not to me.
- Can we speak in the hall?
About what?
Agent Scully?
Scully!
When did all this start?
When we took this case,
when Skinner gave it to us.
- What kind of case is it?
- Investigation into a murder.
- Of whom?
- The case has nothing to do
with what's happened to him.
Agent Scully says it does.
You know my background,
my previous work on the X-Files.
- If I can help on this case--
- The X-File here is a fraud.
Scully has ample proof of that.
Evidence authenticated
by a scholar and authority.
I never sent you that report.
Anyway, the case is being resolved.
[ Diana ]
Not as far as it affects Agent Mulder.
If you know what's happening,
why won't you tell me?
Why were you
with him last night?
He called me. I found him
in a university stairwell.
He could barely speak.
He said I was the only one who'd
believe him about an artifact.
You're a liar.
Scully.
You're both liars.
-[ Departing Footsteps ]
-[ Door Closes ]
[ Chanting In Native Language ]
[ Ringing ]
Hello.
Agent Scully. Dr. Sandoz. I'm sorry,
I didn't know how else to reach you.
- There's something--
- Dr. Sandoz, I-I don't know
if this is a secure line.
Yes. All right.
But I realized something.
The letters Albert translated
on the artifact? I know what they are.
-What they are?
-Yes. They're coordinates, Agent Scully.
- For what?
- For genes.
They're symbols for gene clusters.
The human genome.
- Are you there?
- Yeah.
I think it's all here--
the map to our human genetic makeup--
every gene on every chromosome.
Proof of what I've been saying.
If only we could find more pieces.
[ Whinnying ]
Dr. Sandoz?
- Hello?
- [ Gunshot ]
Dr. Sandoz?
[ Native ]
It's the same.
I'll take you, but they are afraid.
[ Child ]
I made this!