[ Man Narrating ]
One upon a time, there was a guy...
with the improbable name
of Fox Mulder.
He started out life happily enough,
as these things go.
He had parents who loved him,
a cute kid sister.
He had a roof over his head,
got all his flu shots,
had all his fingers and toes.
And aside from being stuck
with the name Fox,
which probably
taught him how to fight--
or not--
he pretty much led a normal life.
But the worst thing by far--
the biggest kick in the slats
this kid Fox ever got--
was what happened to his sister.
One day, she just disappeared.
Now, Fox buckled down
and worked his butt off.
Graduated top of his class
at Oxford,
then top of his class
at the F.B.I. Academy.
None of that hard work
made up for his sister, though.
It was just a way
of putting her out of his mind.
Finally, the way I figure it,
he went out of his mind,
and he's been that way ever since.
Fox Mulder pissed away
a brilliant career,
lost the respect
of supervisors and friends...
and now lives his life
shaking his fist at the sky...
and muttering about conspiracies
to anyone who'll listen.
If you ask me, he's one step away
from pushing a baby carriage...
filled with tin cans
down the street.
But now, all that's gonna change.
Tell them the truth,
you lying son of a bitch!
He's not me, Scully!
Scully!
Scully, he's not me!
[ Vehicle Departs ]
You hate me now, right?
Dana, I'm sorry I narc'd
on you to Kersh, but I--
I was scared you were
gonna lose your job.
You did the right thing, Mulder.
I did?
I've been telling you for years you
should play more by the book, haven't I?
Hey, it's the new me.
Hey. Hey, fellas. Take--
What about these?
Come on, fellas.
[ Chuckling ]
You ain't going nowhere, Mibby.
[ Chuckles ]
You and me have had our asses
officially disappear.
Looks like we're up Fudge Creek.
- Who are you?
- Call sign's Maverick.
Not like I'm gonna be
hot-sticking it anytime soon.
Are you all right, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Kiss my ass, you desk monkey.
[ Morris ]
Oh! No, no, no, no, no! Uh, uh--
Whew!
- [ Golf Ball Falls In Cup ]
- I am Tiger Woods.
So, what did Kersh say?
He said that I was willful,
insubordinate and not a team player.
And the F.B.I. didn't need agents
that weren't team players.
What a jerk. Then what?
Two-week suspension without pay.
You're not serious!
Who does he think he is?
See you in two weeks.
Dana?
Do you suppose a home-cooked meal
might ease the pain a little?
Say, my place, 8:00?
I think she likes me, Tiger.
[ McDonough ] So there I am with this
wet-behind-the-ears Rio flying backseat.
And I'm thinking, ""Hell, man,
I'm gonna give this cherry
the ride of his life.''
So I'm putting the spurs
to her,you know?
And I'm doing a little hassling
with my wingman, Buzz Saw.
- Buzz Saw--
- Would you mind?
- Hold up.
Buzz Saw gets on my zero.
He's right on my zero.
- And when Buzz Saw gets on your zero,
- Maverick?
- he's like a damn dog tick.
- Maverick.
You ain't shaking
that son of a gun.
Hey, Grandma Top Gun,
will you shut the hell up?
You're my bitch now, pencil-neck.
[ Laughing ]
General Wegman wants to see you.
Son,you got a set on you.
- I'll say that much.
- [ Man ] You had us fooled.
Why didn't you tell us
what you were doing from the start?
Meaning?
It's the wrong one.
You replaced the flight data recorder.
This one's from--
[ Man ]
A scrapped F-1 1 1, sir. It's junk.
You gave the F.B.I. the wrong
flight data recorder. Why?
Morry, if you were running a scam on the
F.B.I., why didn't you let us in on it?
I didn't know
if I could trust you.
We have a security leak, gentlemen,
and for all I knew it was one of you.
That's why I decided
I should approach Agent Scully alone...
to find out who her contact is.
Unfortunately, her partner,
Agent Mulder, screwed everything up.
Why didn't you tell us
this afterward?
I knew you wouldn't believe it
till you figured it out for yourself.
So the real flight data recorder
is safe?
Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
- And you will bring it back?
- [ Laughing ] Of course!
By God,you do got a set on you.
I wish I could say the same
about some of your colleagues.
About those who proffer
rumor and innuendo,
those who make
dangerous accusations.
Sir, Morris's behavior
seemed to--
You can explain yourself
to the review panel in Washington.
I've already wired them
recommending censure for your actions.
You're lucky I didn't
throw you in the stockade.
Uh-huh.
A little mood lighting
for the bedroom.
No bedroom.
This guy hasn't been laid
in ten years.
Hey, Chris. Hey, I like the, uh--
the, uh, nose--
Ouch!
As if!.
Terry. Buddy. Hey.
Terence, sorry.
How's it going?
Mom says she's taking out
a restraining order on you.
[ Car Drives Away ]
- What are you doing back?
-Joanne.
Your stuff is all outside.
Take it and get out.
Listen to me.
There's something I've got to tell you.
I've heard enough from you
for one lifetime, Morris.
Go tell it to that tramp
of yours, that Scully what's-her-name.
Dana Scully.
Special Agent Dana Scully.
- Special Tramp Dana Scully.
- She's my partner,Joanne.
- I'm supposed to be your partner.
- My name is not Morris Fletcher.
It's Fox Mulder, Special Agent
Fox Mulder with the F.B.I.
Dana Scully is
my F.B.I. partner.
I'm not your husband. We are not
married. We are complete strangers,
and I have a whole other life that
I am desperately trying to get back to.
You know, Morris, most men,
when they have a midlife crisis,
they go out and buy
themselves a sports car.
They don't run around
calling themselves ""Fox.''
I-I want you to look out the window.
Just look out the window with me
for a second.
See that car down there?
See the two men in it?
They're surveilling me.
They're spying on me.
I don't know if your husband told you,
but he has a very dangerous job,
and those two men in that car,
like you, think that I'm him.
Only they don't trust me.
So one false move, and I'm history.
This means that your husband
will also be history,
because I won't be able to get back
and set things the way
they're supposed to be.
Do you understand
what I'm saying to you?
Morris, if you don't like the man you've
become, I don't blame you one bit.
But this flight from reality
isn't the answer.
Accept who you are,
however repulsive that may be.
Perfect timing.
Welcome.
Wow. Mulder.
You like, huh?
Yeah, I thought it was time
I stopped living like a frat boy.
Come on, see the rest
of the place.
There.
I didn't even know
you had a bedroom.
Oh, yeah.
Got to have someplace to lounge around,
read the Sunday New York Times.
Uh, no, that's okay.
Thanks.
Seriously,just check it out.
Seriously.
- [ Waterbed Sloshes ]
- Oh! Oh! Whoop.
- Oh!
- Uh-oh.
- Mulder!
- Maybe I like to read
the New York Times backwards.
Do you hate it?
No, I don't hate it.
Well, all right, then.
Uh, don't go away.
& Let's get it on &
& Let's get it on
Let's get it on &
& Tonight is the night &&
[ Laughing ]
You know what would really be fun?
What?
Oh, yeah.
- Me first?
- You first.
My first time.
Now what?
- You're not Mulder.
- What?
- Baby--
- ""Baby'' me and you'll be
peeing through a catheter.
Your name is
Morris Fletcher.
It was Mulder who was
arrested in the desert.
He was telling
the truth about you.
Now, how do we get things
back to normal?
How should I know?
I wouldn't do it even if I could.
You saw my wife.
You think I want to go back to that?
Two kids who'd probably kill me
in my sleep for the insurance money.
A $400,000 mortgage on a house
that just appraised at 226.
And my job--
Ye, gods.
You think being a man in black
is all voodoo mind control?
You should see the paperwork.
Are you through?
As far as I'm concerned,
this thing is a gift from heaven.
Besides, no one's gonna believe you,
so get used to me being here.
Or I just shoot you, baby.
I'm telling you, I have no idea
how to change things back!
What about Mulder's source, the man
he was supposed to meet in the desert?
Do you know how to get
in touch with him?
I don't know
anything about that.
- Sorry. You're out of luck.
- [ Phone Ringing ]
[ Morris On Answering Machine ]
Hello, hello. I'm very busy
entertaining a special guest.
- Leave a message,
and I'll get back to you.
-[ Beeps ]
[ Man ] Agent Mulder,
I'm trying you one last time.
Are you or are you not interested
in the classified information I have?
Please pick up the phone
if you're there.
- Mulder.
- Agent Mulder, listen very carefully.
[ Door Closes ]
Well, I guess we've given
the neighbors enough to talk about.
For God's sakes, Morris. At first
you couldn't wait to get away from me,
and now you won't
leave the house.
Where can we go?
- What do you mean?
- You're right.
We should get out of the house,
go someplace with a lot of people.
Someplace with a lot of people?
- In Rachel, Nevada?
- What do you say?
All right.
Let's run through this one more time.
I'll go in there alone,
just like you told me to.
He'll be wearing a blue
Buffalo Bills cap.
And?
And, if I try and slip out
the back door, da-da-da, dee-dee-dee.
Get going.
Can't we start over? You know,
do that thing with the handcuffs?
- [ Trigger Cocks ]
- Probably not your scene.
&I have waited for what seems &
&Like a light-year &
&Just to see your face &
& Once again, my dear &
&Shining bright like moonlight &
&Sunlight, starlight &
&And big, dark eyes
that send me out of sight &
&Now, I'm staring at the stars &
- Are you expecting someone?
- No, I'm not expecting someone.
Because if you're here expecting someone
and not to buy me a drink,
tell me now so I can divorce you
and take the house.
Joanne, have another white wine.
&Staring at the stars &
& Wondering where you are &
You're the guy?
Sit down.
[ Sighs ]
Well, I'll be damned.
Whoa. Uh, ooh, God.
That beer went right through me.
I got-- I'll be right back.
- You sabotaged a U.F.O.?
- Keep your voice down.
I didn't intend for it
to crash, Agent Mulder.
I just meant to disable
the stealth module so you could see it.
- Scully.
- Mulder?
Is that really you?
What are you doing here?
I'm trying to figure out
a way to help you.
&Now I'm staring at the stars &
- What are you, disgruntled?
- You make me sound like
some postal clerk.
What you came for
is on the floor by your feet.
&Starlight, star bright &
Morris?
&In my memory you are moonlight &
&Starlight &
& With big, dark eyes
that send me &
& Out of sight &
&Now I'm staring at the stars &
& Wondering where you are &
& Wondering if I'll ever &
&See your face again &
&Now I'm staring at the stars &
& Wondering where you are &
Joanne?
Hey, how's it going?
Listen, have you seen Morry?
[Joanne ]
You bet I've seen him.
Hey, hey.
Whoa, whoa, guys, guys.
- What the hell was that, Morry?
- I guess I make a lousy husband.
I'll talk to her.
[ Exhales ]
So you're the guy
that wants my life.
I assume that includes
all the ass-kickings.
Oh, no.
You don't want to do this.
- Yeah, I do.
-Jeff's outside.
- So what?
- If he sees us together,
we're both dead!
Especially when he sees this.
You take that
to Scully right now!
You must have some sort
of waxy buildup.
I said Jeff's here!
No way am I going out there
until he leaves.
You sneak it past him.
You're his buddy.
His buddy? He doesn't trust me as far
as he can throw me. You saw to that.
Oh,jeez.
Hey.
&As long as the sun would shine &
& You would love me &
&&[ Continues, Indistinct ]
-Jeff.
- General Wegman.
You men, come with me.
Sir, what are we--
Uh--
There.
Detain that man.
Morris! Stop!
Hey, guys.
What's in the bag, Morris?
It's, uh, beer.
You're sure it's not
a flight data recorder?
No, it's beer.
[ Chuckling ]
Suckers.
Mmm.
More huevos rancheros.
Mas huevos rancheros.
Por favor.
-[ Door Buzzer Buzzing ]
-[ Scully ] Open up!
[ Frohike ] Mulder, if I'd known you
were coming, I'd have made more salsa.
-[ Scully ] We need your help right now.
-Who crashed?
Who, what, why.
I need to know everything
that's on that data recorder.
It's similar in size
and shape to the F.D.R.s on the SR-7 1 .
That's definitely not
standard issue.
- Where did you get this?
- Groom Lake, outside Area 51 .
- Dreamland.
- The Aurora spy plane.
- What's that?
- Black World.
Top, top secret.
A skunkworks special.
Aurora is a hypersonic
reconnaissance aircraft...
fueled with slush hydrogen.
- Or methylcyclohexane.
- [ Snickering ]
- What's with him?
- You guys like the name?
I'm going to go with either
""Aurora'' or ""Borealis.''
- What the hell's he talking about?
- Mulder--
- He's not Mulder.
- Huh?
We think the crash
of this particular aircraft--
whatever it was--
resulted in a, uh--
[ Sighs ]
My name is Morris Fletcher.
I work inside Area 51 .
I assumed Mulder's identity through
a warp in the space-time continuum.
Trust me, little man.
I ain't him.
Oh, I love you guys.
I really do.
You're the Lone Gunmen, aren't you?
You guys are my heroes.
- Look at this crap you print.
- We uncover the truth.
Oh, the truth. That's what's
so great about you monkeys.
Not only do you believe this horse pucky
we create, you broadcast it as well.
I mean, look at this.
There is no Saddam Hussein.
This guy's name is John Gillnitz. We
found him doing dinner theater in Tulsa.
Did a mean King and I.
Plays good ethnics.
You're trying to say that
Saddam Hussein's a government plant?
I'm saying I invented the guy.
We set him up in '7 9.
He rattles his saber
whenever we need a good distraction.
If you boys only knew how many of your
stories I dreamed up while sitting on the pot.
- What stories?
- I'm sorry, Melvin. That's classified.
The name's Frohike, you punk-ass.
What the hell'd you do with Mulder?
Shut up, all of you.
If you guys want Mulder back,
get me these results.
[ Knock At Door ]
- Who is it?
- Morris Fletcher.
Come in.
We shouldn't be seen together.
Not after last night.
Fletcher, Mulder,
whoever you are.
I'm hoping this will be
our last meeting.
Agent Scully's flying back with the
analysis of that flight data recorder.
- It'll be too late to save me.
- I know.
The real Morris Fletcher
knows you're the leak.
Once you get back,
if you get back,
he'll have me arrested,
disappeared.
Even if he doesn't, his colleagues
will figure out soon enough...
I sabotaged that craft.
- Why'd you do it?
- I didn't mean for it to crash.
I just wanted you to see it.
Well, why?
There comes a time
when you look back...
instead of forward,
see the sum of your life.
My entire career has been spent hiding
the truth from the American people,
destroying, in a way,
that which was most precious to me.
What is the truth?
You mean, you don't know?
- Don't know what?
- The truth.
What is going on here at Area 51 .
What are these
black-budget projects?
We just fly these birds.
They don't tell us what makes them go.
They engineer them all up in Utah.
If you don't know,
why'd you call me?
I've seen your file.
You've chased flying saucers
for years.
Do aliens really exist, Agent Mulder?
-[ Frohike ] Something's coming up.
-[ Byers ] Got it.
- What is it?
- We broke the encryption.
This baby records
the telemetry of 28 systems,
including airspeed,
fuselage torque and Delta-V.
Yeah. All the usual readouts,
but what are these?
[ Byers ] Tachyon flux,
gravitational displacement.
Aurora, my ass. What have you guys
been flying out there?
I want you guys
to analyze that data.
- Morris--
- This is one of mine.
- Get your butt in gear.
- You're gonna miss me when I'm gone.
- Yeah, fat chance, laughing boy.
- Back off, Sneezy.
Enough.
Call me when you guys
have some answers.
Far out!
The black mailbox.
[ Man ]
Dude, that's a white mailbox.
No, they painted it white
to hide it.
This is the black mailbox.
The best place
to see Freedom Mountain...
and the U.F.O.s
over Dreamland, man.
I know a guy who saw
five in one night.
He said they danced in the sky.
-[ Low Rumbling ]
- You guys hear that?
What the hell?
[ Loud Rumbling, Whooshing ]
Cool.
Did you guys see that?
[ Muffled Shouts ]
You don't look too happy.
Don't tell me I'm gonna have to
put two kids through school.
That is you in there, Mulder,
isn't it?
I, uh--
I just got off the phone
with Frohike.
They were able to download
and analyze the crash data,
and yes, there was an
anomalous event that night.
And how do I get back?
Well, that's just it.
It's all about
random moments in time,
about a series of variables
approaching an event horizon.
And even if we could
recreate that moment,
if we could sabotage
another craft--
Mulder, if we were--
if we were off--
If the event were off
by even one millisecond--
I might wind up
with my head in a rock.
Something like that, yeah.
What about him?
I mean me, whatever.
Whoever he is.
Agent Mulder has become
A.D. Kersh's new golden boy.
He's been tasked with returning
the flight data recorder...
that he and I stole.
The son of a bitch confesses to Kersh
even more than I do to my priest.
I'm just tagging along
for the ride.
What do you mean,
""just tagging along''?
I'm out of the bureau.
- I've been censured
and relieved of my position.
- No.
You can explain it to them
like you explained it to me.
You have the data.
You can make them understand.
You can get your job back.
I'd kiss you if you weren't
so damn ugly.
[ Car Horn Honks ]
Take a picture.
It'll last longer.
If I shoot him,
is that murder or suicide?
Neither, if I do it first.
Hey, Scully.
[ Car Engine Starts ]
[ Car Door Shuts ]
[ Car Departs ]
Stop! Stop!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
You got to help me!
Open the window, please.
Open your window. I need to talk
to you. I need somebody to help me.
It's this thing--
It was like-like a wave,
like all squiggly and everything.
And-- And their faces,
they stuck together.
And-And her arm,
it was coming through his chest!
Sam, man, where you been?
Who's the dude?
I swear, man,
they were messed up.
I believe you.
[ Morris ]
So the motel guy wants cash. Won't take
credit card. You believe that?
So then it hits me. I flash him
my badge-- ""Fox Mulder, F.B.I.''
I tell him we're investigating
crappy motels in the southwest.
He better watch his behind.
So guess what?
The guy gives me the room for free and
throws in a six-pack of brews to boot.
I love this job!
Listen, Dana, after we return
this flight recorder,
what do you say I have a word
with the big man?
See if I can get you
yourjob back.
We could have lots of fun together
once you got to know me.
- You know that, Danes?
- I still got my gun.
- All right, already.
- Wait. Hold on.
- Back up. Back up!
- What is it?
Can I help you, ma'am?
I don't understand.
This place was burnt to the ground.
[ Man ]
I don't think so.
Yeah.
This place, two nights ago.
I think I'd remember that.
[ Chanting In Native Dialect ]
- What's going on?
- [ Lock Clicks ]
- What are you doing here?
- I need to talk to you.
Something's happened.
[Joanne ]
Morris, don't forget your stupid chair!
You and it should be
very happy together!
Terence, get back inside.
You got a lot of gall
coming back here, sister!
Joanne, I told you,
I'm not your husband. This man is.
You come here to watch my family fall
apart? You get a big kick out of that?
I have to talk to you alone.
Homewrecker!
- Careful. You're gonna bust a lung.
- Leave me alone!
Joanne,
what he said about
me being your husband--
It's true.
Get the hell off my porch!
We got married
on June 1 3, 1 97 8.
It rained that day.
You got mad at the reception
'cause I said I couldn't see
the cake behind your fat ass.
Remember our first apartment?
That dump in Pentagon City?
You'd turn the air conditioner on
and the lights would go out.
Or when you were pregnant, how I'd
tickle your kneecaps to make you laugh?
Remember? Remember the night
Chrissy was born?
And I held her in my arms
all red-faced and screaming?
That's the only time
I ever saw you cry.
Oh, my God.
Morris?
Is that you?
[ Mulder ]
Come on, Morris. Let's go.
What do you mean, "go''?
Where are you taking him?
We have reason to believe
that whatever event...
caused this to happen
may be in the process of reversing.
[ Mulder ] We got to get back to
the exact spot where this all began.
It may be our only chance.
[ Vehicle Approaching ]
Sorry, Morris.
A traitor's a traitor.
- This isn't what it looks like.
- Got it.
Sir.
- What are you doing?
- I'm cleaning up a mess.
- What are you talking about?
- About an hour ago,
I put Captain McDonough and Mrs. Chee
back where they belong.
- Now it's their turn.
- The warp that started this...
is snapping back
like a rubber band.
Only we have to be
in its path when it happens.
Why are you doing this?
Till now, I had a spotless
career record. I want that back.
So this is time snapping back?
It'll be like
the last few days never happened.
You won't remember any of this.
Oh, well, in that case,
Dana, it's been real.
Come on, Mulder.
Let's go.
[ Car Door Closes, Engine Starts ]
[ Car Engine Starting ]
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
- Mulder.
- [ Scully ] Mulder, it's me.
I just wanted to let you know
that we slipped under Kersh's radar.
Our little field trip
to Nevada went unnoticed.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mulder,
I'm sorry that your confidential
source didn't pan out.
I guess you were right, Scully.
Just another crackpot
who watches too much Star Trek.
- Good night.
- Hey, Scully.
I, uh, know it's not your normal life,
but thanks for coming out there with me.
You're welcome.
[ Child ]
I made this!