[ Machinery Beeping,
Metal Clattering ]
[ Beeping Continues ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Instrument Whirring ]
Dr. Openshaw, congratulations.
Your work-- it's completed.
You should see her.
Twenty-five years.
She must seem
like an old friend.
Yes.
We're, uh, going out
to celebrate.
- If you'd like to come--
- No.
You go on ahead.
[ Gasping ]
[ Screaming ]
Oh, God!
-[ Men Screaming ]
-[ Man ] No!
[ Grunts, Groans ]
This is the end.
I never thought I'd hear myself say
those words after all these years.
When you put your life
into something,
build it, protect it,
the end is as unimaginable
as your own death...
or the death of your children.
I could never have scripted
the events that led us to this.
None of us could.
All the brilliant men,
the secret
that we kept so well.
It happened simply, like this.
We had a perfect conspiracy...
with an alien race--
aliens who were coming
to reclaim this planet...
and to destroy all human life.
Our job was to secretly
prepare the way...
for their invasion,
to create for them a slave race
of human/alien hybrids.
They were good plans,
right plans,
kept secret for over 50 years,
ever since the crash at Roswell,
kept secret from men
like Fox Mulder.
Plans that would have worked...
had not a rebel alien race
come to destroy them,
had not my own son
chosen betrayal...
or chosen to betray more wisely.
A.D. Skinner, I-- I didn't hear
the elevator. I was working here.
Working on what, Agent Spender?
[ Clears Throat ]
Progress report on the X-Files.
- Progress report to who?
-Just a file.
I wasn't aware that
you'd made any progress.
In the months since your assignment,
I've received but one memorandum.
Are you planning
to hit me all at once?
Uh, it's been slow going.
The truth is, your purpose is not
to make any progress, isn't it?
The truth is, you have
no interest in the X-Files...
beyond a certain personal case.
- Your mother's abduction.
- Alleged abduction.
That's what I'm here about.
[ Fire Extinguisher Spraying ]
- What happened here?
-[ Skinner ] No one knows yet.
A group of people
were burned alive here.
And a man's on life support.
- Only your mother survived.
- Where is she?
- They've got her outside.
Mom.
It's me,Jeffrey.
Mom, what happened to you?
You've been gone so long,
I thought I'd never see you again.
Oh, don't cry, honey.
Where have you been?
What did they do to you?
- I need to talk to someone.
- You can tell me.
I need to speak to Agent Mulder.
- I don't want him talking with her.
- Why?
He's forbidden from the X-Files.
He's to stay out of this.
- She's asking for him.
- She's my mother.
What are you afraid of?
Mulder filling her head
with alien-abduction nonsense.
Are you afraid of the truth?
I want to know who did this to her
and why. That's all I want.
Then why not use every resource
available to you?
I'll send you
a progress report.
My son refused to believe that
his mother had been abducted,
though it had been
going on for years.
Even after I schemed to put him
in charge of the X-Files,
where Fox Mulder had amassed
so much evidence of our secret plans,
he still couldn't bring himself to
accept the possibility of alien life.
When he did come to believe,
when the facts became so glaring,
he turned not to me, his father,
but to the man I'd ruined,
the man I'd chosen
for him to replace.
Hey, milk, let's play ball.
Yo, homestyle,
cough up the rock.
[ Man ]
Wanna rotate in?
[ Man Yells ]
Yeah.
- Game.
- Oh, nah. It don't work like that.
Hey, homegirl. Word up.
Mulder, it's my distinct impression
that you just cheated...
and that you're not
coming in again today.
Scully, I got game.
You got so much game, I'm wondering
if you have any work left in you.
No, I'm ready toJ-O-B,just not
on some jagoff shoeshine tip.
No jagoff shoeshine tip?
No background checking
jagoff shoeshine tip.
About yourJ-O-B, Mulder,
somebody's been trying very hard
to reach you by phone,
somebody who wants you back
at the F.B.I. A.S.A.P.
- About what?
- About an X-File.
[ Phone Rings ]
You looking for work, Agent Spender?
'Cause if you are,
I got a whole pile in that middle drawer
I'd love to shove down someone's throat.
I was writing you a note.
You know why I'm here.
They found your mother.
She wants to talk to you.
I didn't hear the magic word.
- I'm not gonna get down on my knees.
- Are you asking me?
My mother's been gone
for almost a year.
She turns up in a train car...
where she's been operated on
by doctors who were burned alive.
I just want the truth.
Well, the truth is out there,
Agent Spender.
Maybe you should
find it for yourself.
[ Machinery Beeping ]
[ Air Hissing ]
I expected you sooner.
I've been at the train yard.
I'm trying to tidy things up.
The overkill will be hard
to divert attention from,
but not as hard
as from Cassandra.
You have no idea, do you?
Cassandra is a success.
No.
She can't be.
Not now.
I had prepared a syringe
for her, as agreed.
But the rebels came.
They saved her to expose us.
She's the key to everything.
I won't let her
out of our hands.
They will run
medical tests on her.
It's only a matter of time.
Cassandra must be terminated.
They will come and question me.
I know.
I'm sorry.
[ Air Hissing ]
[ Beeping Faster ]
A man should never live
long enough to see his children--
or his work-- destroyed.
[ Fast Beeping Continues ]
[ Beeping Faster ]
[ Phone Ringing ]
Hello.
[ Cigarette-Smoking Man ]
Have you heard the news?
- No.
- The rebels have struck.
- Where?
- In Virginia...
during one of our
medical procedures.
They killed the project doctors,
burned them.
- All of them?
- Yes.
Dr. Openshaw died in the hyperbaric
chamber this evening.
My God.
I've called an emergency
meeting of the syndicate.
Only the future rides
on our response.
I'll be on a plane.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
- Dr. Openshaw.
- I've come to see you.
[ Grunting ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Keyboard Clicking ]
- Didn't expect to find you here.
- Where'd you expect to find me?
I thought Agent Spender
offered you an X-File assignment.
It wasn't exactly an offer.
But isn't it just the opportunity
you've been waiting for?
It is an opportunity made to order
for the powers that be.
You think it's a setup?
This is exactly the kind of
mistake they've been waiting for...
to come down on me full force.
But Agent Spender asked you.
Like I said, not exactly.
We've seen this before.
Bodies set aflame with no
conclusive cause of combustion.
Mulder.
I know.
I was with Cassandra Spender
when she disappeared.
You sat with me while I
was under hypnosis...
when I spoke of just
these sorts of details.
I have no doubt that
what Cassandra would tell us...
would expose more than
just what happened to her.
I was taken to one of those train cars.
I was tested just like Cassandra.
What if what she tells us
could-could expose...
who did this to me?
Mulder, Agent Spender
doesn't have to know.
[ Door Opens ]
Oh, my God.
- My God. [ Chuckling ]
- Cassandra.
Oh, Dana. Oh, my God.
It's so good to see you.
We're old friends.
If, if I can get ahold of a wheelchair,
you want to go out for some fresh air?
I don't need a wheelchair.
But I am dying for a cigarette.
It feels so good to walk.
The doctors don't know
what to say.
I told them they wouldn't believe
how it happened, and they wouldn't.
No, I'm not gonna
tell anybody this time,
because nobody
believes you anyway.
They want to hear it,
but they just think you're crazy.
Guess I wouldn't
believe it either...
except that it happened to me.
No, I'm only gonna
tell somebody I can trust...
and who can do something
about it.
I was hoping, when I saw you,
that Agent Mulder...
was going to be coming
in the door behind you.
I've got a surprise
for you, Cassandra.
- Agent Mulder?
- Shh! Shh, shh, shh!
Oh! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! I think
I'm going to pee the floor.
- Don't-- Don't do that.
- [ Laughing ]
- Look at you.
- I told you about their power.
You said you didn't believe it.
Well, I had reasons for doubt
when I met you, Cassandra.
You just doubted yourself.
You were just doubting you'd
ever see her again, weren't you?
Your sister.
Agent Mulder told me he believed
he saw his sister last year.
That wasn't her, Agent Mulder.
- Then where is she?
- Out there, with them.
The aliens.
[ Striking Match ]
Cassandra, you were found
in a train car.
You'd been operated on by doctors.
Yes, that's right.
- These are the doctors who cured you?
- No, the aliens cured me.
The doctors were working
with the aliens.
- That's what I wanted to tell you.
- What?
I told you that the aliens
were here to do good...
and that I was being used as
an oracle to spread the word.
Only now I know what the aliens
are here for, and it isn't good.
What are they here for?
To wipe us off the planet.
They're taking over the universe.
They're infecting
all other life-forms...
with a black substance
called Purity.
It's their life force.
It's what they're made of.
It's the virus, the black oil.
But, Cassandra, the doctors
weren't infected. They were burned.
By another race of aliens.
A rebel force that are
mutilating their faces...
so that they won't be infected.
This is what I couldn't
tell my son Jeffrey.
- Why couldn't you tellJeffrey?
- Because he doesn't believe me.
Even though his life is in danger
by these same rebel aliens.
Spender's life's in danger?
He's in with the men that have been
working with the alien colonists...
for 50 years.
Working to do what?
Whatever it is they did to me...
and to you, Dana.
And you know who these men are?
Oh, sure.
One of them's my ex-husband,
Jeffrey's father.
Cassandra was beginning to realize her
role in the greatest science project...
that man had ever known.
She was the center
of 50 years of work,
the key to all of our plans--
something even my colleagues
didn't realize yet.
I killed to keep them unknowing.
I killed Dr. Openshaw
so they wouldn't discover her...
when it's Cassandra
I should have killed,
Cassandra who needed to die.
I couldn't do it.
With all the blood on my hands,
I couldn't kill
the mother of my own son,
a woman I never even loved.
My colleagues never knew,
focused as they were
on the new threat--
the faceless alien rebels
who'd burned our doctors alive.
But my colleagues
had become old men,
blind to the fact
that the faceless rebels...
already held the upper hand,
that they'd used their powers
of disguise to infiltrate our group.
[ Krycek ] Rebels have attacked
and burned project facilities...
in New Mexico and the southwest.
The medical staff at our Arizona
research facility's been slain.
The train-car deaths cost us.
Work on the human/alien hybrids
will suffer the death of Dr. Openshaw.
What do they want?
To expose our enterprise,
everything we've worked for.
Well, some hotshot reporter's
gonna put the pieces together,
not to mention law enforcement.
We have our control
on the federal agencies.
Our new man at the F.B.I.'s
very capable of diverting attention.
Why not side with the rebels?
Join their alien resistance.
It's an option.
It's an option
you declined long ago.
Resistance was futile then.
Why would it be any less so now?
That's why you voted against it,
against men like Bill Mulder.
Collaboration has allowed you
to prepare, to stall colonization.
How close are you to developing
a human/alien hybrid?
That alone ensures your survival.
As slave laborers for the aliens.
What about your vaccine?
By collaborating,
you bought yourself time...
to secretly develop a way to combat
the aliens, to fight the future.
Alex, enough!
For 50 years we've
worked on this project.
Fifty years since Roswell.
We can't sacrifice ourselves
for every new threat,
can we now?
Why risk getting caught here?
They're gonna be monitoring
any work on our machines, in or out.
We need access to files
on a name that'll raise flags.
[ Beeping ]
Maybe she was making it all up.
[ Computer Beeps ]
Smokey's got a name.
[ Typing ]
[ Beeps ]
Get up from the desk.
Get up, turn the computer off,
grab whatever you took
or printed out and give it to me.
Let's go, Agents.
They're coming.
- Who?
-Just go.
Assistant Director.
I'll assume you came down to apprehend
these agents for unauthorized entry...
into my office.
I'll make sure it's duly noted
in the report of their dismissal.
I've done as you've asked. Mulder's
been brought up to his superiors.
He and his partner will be
processed out of the F.B.I.
I've done as you've asked.
Now, I would like you to do for me.
Do for you?
- I think I'm entitled.
- To?
The truth.
The truth about my mother.
She won't tell me.
Because you won't believe her.
Maybe you won't believe me.
- Maybe it's better not to know.
- Look, I need to know.
Show me that you're capable
of handling the responsibility...
that comes with this knowledge.
Don't try me, old man!
I gave you responsibility.
I gave you a position.
I gave you the things that you couldn't
get yourself, and you can't do the job.
Keeping Fox Mulder down is not a job!
It's your dirty work.
You pale to Fox Mulder.
Bet you're curious about C.G.B.
What's that?
C.G.B. Spender. His name--
cigarette-smoking man.
What's it stand for?
-[ Ball Swishes Through Net ]
- It's an alias, as far as I can figure.
One of hundreds.
Scully, wanna go one-on-one?
We got nothing but time now that
we're on administrative leave.
Aren't you curious
what I've got in the box?
Everything I could find on him.
Nothing you could ever find
would be accurate or credible.
Maybe.
But there's a picture
you're gonna want to see.
That's C.G.B. Spender...
and my father.
It was taken in 1 973.
I traced the connection to something
they worked on together for 25 years...
at the State Department--
a highly classified project.
There's more, if you're ready.
Cassandra Spender is, indeed,
the mother of AgentJeffrey Spender...
and the ex-wife
of C.G.B. Spender.
But there's something that you're
gonna be surprised to find out.
She was first abducted in 1 973...
on the night of November 27.
That's the same night
as my sister.
And there are other names connected
to C.G.B. Spender and your father--
PhDs, doctors,
one a Nobel winner
for early works in genetics,
a Dr. Eugene Openshaw.
He was the doctor that was found
amongst the burn victims...
clinging to life
beside Cassandra Spender.
He died the next day
in the hospital...
before he was questioned.
- The project is still going on.
- Yeah.
If Mulder hadn't known of
his father's history with me,
he was fueled now with names
and dates and... certainties.
I couldn't stop him any longer--
stop him from learning our sins,
his father's and my own.
The truth was out there...
fatally exposed.
I had one last hope,
one chance to preserve my legacy.
- I waited, like you asked.
- Good.
I'm pleased.
I was doubtful
after our last meeting.
You have a new job for me?
Yes.
I may have been unduly harsh.
You deserve a fighting chance...
to prove your father wrong.
- What is it?
- A weapon.
A man has infiltrated
the group that I work with.
- That's to kill him.
- I don't understand.
He's pretending to be
a member of our group,
disguising himself as a man
he's already killed.
You will greet him as that man.
Engage him in conversation,
then put that
in the back of his neck.
You can do it,Jeffrey.
-[ Door Lock Locking ]
- Watch where you point that.
[ Doorbell Ringing ]
Sir, my name is Jeffrey Spender.
My father sent me to see you.
I have a message from the group.
- They've changed their minds?
- That's what I'm here about.
Sit, please.
- What have you to tell me?
- Something I've been entrusted with.
It's, uh--
It's a name, actually,
one that will have
meaning for you.
I'm sorry.
[ Grunting ]
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Panting ]
Thanks for coming.
I know it's late.
You've been forbidden
to have any contact with us.
Sir.
You say Cassandra Spender's
life is in danger.
Her life's been in danger going on
30 years,just not the way it is now.
In danger from who?
Men who have conducted
medical experiments...
in what began as a secret
government project,
but what is now the most
private global enterprise.
Enterprising to do what?
To develop alien/human hybrids that
will survive the viral apocalypse...
when aliens colonize the Earth.
And I suppose you
have proof of this?
Files that Agent Scully dug up...
that make the right connections
to Dr. Eugene Openshaw,
to my sister, to my father,
to Agent Spender's father.
- Agent Spender's father?
- The smoking man.
- What?
- It's true.
We have documented evidence.
Then you believe this, Agent Scully?
This whole account?
I know that Agent Scully has her doubts
about the purposes of these experiments.
I also know that she believes she was
a test subject when she was abducted.
If Cassandra Spender's life
is in danger, why not Scully's?
I believe Cassandra Spender represents
the final stages of these experiments--
that she may very well be the first
successful alien/human hybrid.
What I don't understand is if she was
a success, why is her life threatened?
Because...
the men who created her
would rather kill her...
than let her expose
the enterprise.
She's under 2 4-hour guard.
Assigned by Agent Spender?
You've never seen one
before, have you?
It's shocking at first--
the acceptance of the idea.
It's something you thought
only children...
and fools believed in.
It undermines your beliefs...
in yourself, in the world.
- But then you come to understand.
- Understand what?
The responsibility that this knowledge
demands by the men who have it.
The great sacrifice...
by great men
like... your father.
What sacrifice?
The sacrifice of your mother.
What do you know about that?
Just that she's been the subject
of an experiment for 25 years.
My father's involved in that?
- Is he?
- Your father directs the experiments.
So I'm protecting her now
so the experiments can continue?
That's why he put you
on the X-Files.
That's why your father
sent you here tonight.
You're protecting
the project,Jeffrey,
making the sacrifices...
so that you can be a great man too.
I'll be my own great man.
I've trusted no one.
Treachery is the inevitable result
of all affairs.
Every man believes
he has his own good reason.
I have little doubt
of my son's disloyalty to me.
Certainly he led
Mulder and Scully to us.
His mother must know by now
her central role in the grand plan,
that she's as much alien as human.
Do you wonder why I've chosen you?
You've never betrayed me.
Now I need someone to trust.
I'll help you.
It's not too late.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
Cassandra?
Ms. Spender?
- Where's my mother?
- You tell me, Agent Spender.
Where's the guard?
I-I had a guard posted here.
I got here, and she was gone.
- He took her.
- Who?
-[ Dialing ]
- Agent Spender?
[ Frantic Knocking ]
- [ Panting ]
- Cassandra.
- I can't believe I found you.
- How did you find us?
Cassandra?
How did you get here?
How'd you get out of your room?
- Where'd you get your clothes?
-[ Knocking ]
Agent Scully, Agent Mulder,
you cannot let them find me.
[ Knocking Continues ]
- Stop it. Let go!
- You cannot let them have me.
You have got to kill me now!
If you don't kill me,
it all starts!
There won't be any stopping it.
-[ Frantic Knocking ]
- I am the one!
You have to shoot me, please!
[ Knocking Continues ]
Mulder, what are you doing?
- Stand away, Scully.
- Mulder!
-[ Knocking Continues ]
- Mulder, we have to protect her.
[ Harsh Pounding On Door ]
- Mulder. Mulder!
-[ Pounding Continues ]
[ Child ]
I made this!