Freddy, get going.
But stay in the area.
- We'll call when we need.
- Got it.
Tell me we're good
for battery and drive space
Yeah, we're good. I'm just
cleaning the coffee off the lens...
- Oh, today!
- Okay, yeah. Yeah, we're good.
- Okay, let's go, let's go.
- All right.
What about the stuff in the van?
We can't edit without...
We need to travel light.
This is happening now.
Cops haven't even had time
to set up a perimeter yet.
- See what I mean?
- Yeah... Yeah, I do.
Maybe there's a reason
why the cops are coming down here.
Like the fact that something
dangerous is going on?
- You said some people died, right?
- Right, which means something very cool
and newsworthy is going on,
and whoever gets the exclusive on this
is gonna be in the driver's seat
for a network job.
Okay, that's really cool,
it's just, you know...
you're a weather girl.
Meteorologist,
Bill O'reilly started as a weatherman.
Dan Rather was a sportscaster.
All you need is one big break.
This, my friend, is mine.
- Yeah, but wasn't O'reilly out of...
- Come on!
Amy Saunders,
Channel 13 Eyewitness News.
- Can you tell us what happened?
- We don't know anything.
- We'll brief you once we know more.
- Rumor is that three people are dead,
and there have been sightings of a wild
animal of some kind loose in the area.
Can you tell us what happened?
Is the public in danger?
- Is this a zoological crisis?
- Look, you'll know when we know, okay?
Now, back off, both of you. This area
is off-limits effective immediately.
Keep the camera rolling.
- I don't want to miss anything.
- I'm getting everything. Don't worry.
How do you know
there's another way into this place?
Crap.
So... okay.
I don't know about this, Amy.
This is...
Oh, sweet bike.
These warehouses are all interconnected
by a rail system.
All we need to do is to get into one
before the cops cordon them all off.
Like so.
- And hello, Pulitzer.
- I don't know, Amy.
Look, I'm just saying
if there's a wild animal in here,
shouldn't we wait till we know
more about the situation?
By the time the cops get their act
in gear, the story will be over.
We get the jump on this,
we could make the 11:00 broadcast.
But what if it's a hostage situation,
or like, or something like that,
or, like, a mad bomber or something,
and like, the cops are just using
the wild animal story as a cover?
Maybe dudes from homeland security are
coming, because this is a terrorist...
Would you relax?
I've been monitoring the police band
since the first 911 call.
Witnesses said some kind
of lizard or something
escaped from a cargo ship
and attacked some people.
So we get the exclusive footage
on the recapture,
I get a promotion, you get a raise.
I don't want a raise, Amy!
I want to live!
Seriously, Zach, just man up, okay?
We'll be fine.
Holy...
Holy crap!
- This is...
- Just keep recording.
- Are you...
- Keep recording.
I'm going to keep recording.
There's dead people.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god...
That guy's totally...
Amy, he's...
Holy...
Oh, my god!
What was that?
Amy, that was not
a zoo creature, or...
I don't know what that was.
That was something different.
- What was it?
- I know, I know, I don't know.
- What the hell was that?
- I don't know, but it knows we're here.
The Team Projet-SG
presents:
Sanctuary - Season 1 Episode 11
Instinct (v. 1.00)
Timing by: Arrow,
nitrogenc, Salomon
http://projet-sg.net
We're going to leave now, right?
I don't need a science degree
to figure out that the thing that we saw
is what killed those people.
Zach, just calm down.
We don't know what we saw.
Yes, we do. We saw
three extremely dead dudes
and something
that looked like a giant...
I don't know what, like,
an insect or something!
Look, whatever is going on here,
it's bigger than we first thought.
The higher the body count,
the better chance whatever we file
will get picked up nationally,
so just grow a pair, will you?
Shut up!
Both of you, shut up!
- How did you get in here?
- It was her idea.
We're with Channel 13.
Please don't hurt me.
You're both gonna die
if you don't get out right now.
- There's something in here.
- I know, I know, we saw it.
What the hell is it?
I don't know, but it killed
three of us before, he didn't blink.
It got three of my buddies, too,
who tried to stop it.
Okay, seriously,
we are so out of here.
I've been watching it.
It can only focus on
one target at a time.
Now, the only chance you have
is if I give it something to chase
instead, do you understand?
- No, we're not leaving.
- Yes, yes, we are, thank you.
- You see that door over there?
- Yeah.
You go for it like a bat out of hell
when I give it the distraction, okay?
Wait for my mark.
Ready?
Go, go, go!
Hey, over here!
- Oh, my god!
- Zach, tell me you got that.
Amy, come on!
Get off me!
Oh, my god!
- Are you okay?
- Are you insane?
- Clear! Henry!
- I'm on it.
- Are you two all right?
- No!
I'm not sure if it was a direct hit,
but it's gone for now. Ashley's...
- What is this? What's with the camera?
- What did you do to it?
A short-wave sonic weapon.
I haven't met a creature
that likes getting hit with it...
when it works.
Who are you two?
Journalists?
We're with Channel 13.
- I'm...
- Amy Saunders.
"Weekend Weather Watch with
the fabulous Amy." I love your show.
I mean, I watch it, when I can.
- You're a weather girl?
- Meteorologist.
Almost. You're actually short
a few credits, so...
Sorry.
Where are we going?
Still no sign of it,
except for three more KIAs.
Do you mind getting that camera
out of my face?
Yeah, sure, sorry.
- Who the hell are these guys?
- Who the hell are you guys?
I mean, I've never heard of
a sonic super... whatever.
What are you, Federal law enforcement?
Military intelligence?
- Magnus, they can't...
- Listen, you two can't stay here.
- It's an extremely unstable situation.
- I told you!
- Why? What's going on?
- For God's sake, stop filming us!
- You don't understand what's going on.
- I'm a journalist,
and he will stop filming
when I say so, not you.
- People have a right to know the truth.
- Not this truth.
If you guys stick around,
it'll get messy, trust me.
Look, we can't baby-sit them.
It's too dangerous.
We tranq 'em, stuff 'em in a crate.
Wake them when we're done.
- I'm right here. I can hear you.
- We can't do that.
We'd leave them vulnerable
if we leave them on their own.
Excuse me, Men in Black, you can't
drug us, and you can't kick us out.
Okay, whatever you people are up to,
we want in.
Why? So it can end up
on the 11:00 news?
- You want to catch this thing, right?
- Yeah.
We just want to document it, okay?
We will give you all the footage
when this thing is over, I promise,
but don't cut us out of the plan.
You film what I tell you to film,
nothing more.
Fail to play by my rules,
and you will be left on your own.
- Understood?
- I'm down with that.
- Hold on a second, we can't just...
- We don't have a choice.
Escorting them out wastes precious time,
plus I don't think they'd go quietly.
- Definitely not.
- This is crazy. It's crazy.
Henry, do we have a fix?
Yeah, hold still, everyone.
I'm scanning.
Okay, I have movement.
It's moving out of range fast.
Southwest corner.
- You guys know what this thing is.
- Just let us do our jobs, please.
- Henry, how long do you need to set up?
- I don't know.
There's so many places in here
I could set up a shock-web.
Henry... Just tell us what you need
and a time frame.
Here. Here, by this crane.
Just give me two minutes to set it up,
then you send it running in here,
it's game over.
Cool.
Two minutes coming up.
Motion sensor.
Thank you.
Who are you guys?
Amy, we'll explain what we can.
We're a private research facility.
What are... What are those for?
That's super cool stuff, though.
Those little, like...
blow-uppie things or something?
Cool...
Is that...
Is that what you guys do, though?
You hunt things, like that thing?
Because that is some seriously
hardcore equipment you guys got.
You're just mapping out
where the bombs are going to go?
Could you maybe go film something else
while I do this, please?
Thank you.
It's my first real mission, you see?
I want to get out in the field
since I got this job, and, truthfully,
I just don't want to blow it.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I know what you mean, dude.
That's cool. I'm just saying,
whatever your job is, you can...
I can't tell you that, bro.
Excuse me.
I don't even...
This is insane.
Okay, doc, we're ready to go.
Shock-web is hot.
Let's hope this works.
I don't know how much time we have
- before the police begin investigating.
- Three dead that they know of.
Once they trace the killings here,
they'll cordon off the area,
and bring in SWAT
to secure the building.
I'd say we have 20,
maybe 30 minutes, tops
before the window
of opportunity closes.
Opportunity for what?
Capturing it alive.
- What?
- Let's take cover.
Ready, Zach?
Ashley, we're ready.
Send it our way.
Making it happen.
Okay, it is pissed!
Are you sure?
Holy crap!
- Zach, you good?
- Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
What happened? Did you get it?
Not exactly.
I can't believe that thing
shook off 100,000 volts.
So it didn't work.
What does that mean?
It means this creature's far more
powerful than we thought.
Oh, yeah?
So, what's plan B?
We're working on it.
Zach, come here.
Sit down.
- Can you give me my stuff?
- Yeah, okay, just hold on.
I just gotta get this...
- Here.
- Thank you.
Listen to me.
We got some really
cool footage, okay?
Probably enough to get us
a promotion and all that,
but can we just get the
hell out of here now?
Oh, Zach... Zachie.
These people are far more
than research scientists.
Oh, god...
- Zach...
- What?
This is another man's blood
- on my face.
- Yeah, I know. It's disgusting.
It makes me want to throw up.
Anyway...
They knew this thing was in here,
- and they came prepared.
- Not really.
That shock thing totally blew up,
and it got away.
Yeah, well, the point is they...
are part of the story now too,
not just the creature.
We need to learn
as much about them as we can.
Yeah, but you said you were going to
give the footage back to Dr. Magnus.
Yeah, I told her that just so
she wouldn't toss us out of here.
Oh, great. So,
now you're totally playing her?
Look...
We get footage of them
bagging this thing,
and sell it to the highest bidder,
this is brangelina money, okay?
- This is way bigger than we thought.
- You've got to be kidding me.
Look,
government black ops, military,
private security firm,
whatever these people do for a living,
they want to keep it a secret.
Well, maybe they're playing us,
you think of that?
And they're going to kill us after we're
done recording their little documentary?
- You should be rolling on this.
- Yeah, I know. Okay.
- Zoom in!
- This is just... This is too crazy.
Well, we have plenty of firepower.
We can always fall back on that.
It's definitely larger and faster
than I'd anticipated.
Yeah, and more dangerous,
but I'm guessing
you still want to take it alive.
It's incredibly valuable intact.
If we can do it without more collateral
damage, I think we should try.
And if not?
People are dead.
If we have to, we kill it.
Okay, good,
we have a plan B. I feel better.
Okay, so how do you want
to bag this thing in one piece?
I mean, I'd amp up the shock-web again,
but the thing's totally fried.
And the sonic's broken.
Again.
Dude, I told you
it needed better shielding.
Yeah, which messes with
the weight balance ratio.
- Ash, we've...
- Don't move! It's right behind you!
Where it is? Where?
Tell me where?
Please don't eavesdrop
like that again.
Yeah, sorry. I didn't mean to.
I hate you!
Go with tranq rounds only.
Everyone's armed. You too, Will.
We hit it enough times,
we should bring it down.
Failing that, the gloves come off,
and we switch to live ammo.
Two teams. Ashley and Henry
take the journalist,
- Will and I will take the cameraman.
- Who will keep taping.
Absolutely.
If we do have to kill it,
I want as much detailed footage
of its anatomy as possible.
Thorax and mandible, preferably.
Also images of its pincers
and anterior skeletal protrusions
would be very helpful.
Yeah, mandibles.
What... What's a... a pincer?
Dude, got a 9000-pound camera here.
Just...
It looks like a giant
cockroach or something.
Gorgeous, isn't it?
The theoretical name is
Blattella Asahinai Sapien,
an extremely rare species
found on islands
off the coast of Japan and Korea.
Supposed to possess
physiological attributes
dating back to the paleozoic era.
What, like dinosaurs?
Try 150 million years earlier.
Its biological makeup
could offer new insights
into our genetic building blocks.
Yeah, but it killed,
like, five people.
Well, taken from
their natural surroundings,
even the most docile creatures
become aggressive,
especially when they're trapped.
Battery warning light.
Just give me a second, guys.
So how did it get from
some island in Japan to here?
We don't know.
We got just word that someone
was trying to smuggle
- a rare abnormal into the country.
- A what?
Creature.
By the time we got here, it had already
broken loose and attacked people.
Who managed to capture one?
Those are totally vicious aliens,
like in the movies,
which I used to think were awesome.
Not anymore, though.
It's freezing in here.
Careful.
It's not in there.
Yeah, yeah, I'm getting this.
Cool.
Looks like it made a nest in here.
A chrysalis of some kind.
Likely to keep itself safe
while it traveled,
but why wait until the journey's over
to break out?
Maybe whoever captured it,
drugged it.
It wakes up here,
gets mad and busts out
before anyone can take
possession of the cargo.
But it had time to build
a safe traveling environment.
- It's odd.
- Yeah, totally.
It's kind of cool, though.
Looks like that stuff from ghostbusters.
Mom?
Go, Ashley.
Henry's been monitoring
police chatter.
The area's secured,
and SWAT is 15 minutes away.
- Window's closing.
- We gotta go.
Meet us back in engine repair.
I've something for Henry
- to run through the mobile lab.
- Copy that.
So, like,
choppers are coming in,
and that's it, we're done, right?
With the choppers coming?
You should, like, team up with...
Hey! Quit it with the yabbering.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Sorry. Sorry.
They have a full tactical unit inbound.
Building will be the first they sweep.
Once they arrive, how long
before they breach our perimeter?
10 minutes, tops.
We don't have time to screw around.
- Go, Zach.
- Don't plan to.
What does that mean?
I think the battery's
loose on this...
- What?
- Come here.
- What did you find out?
It made a nest, and it's supposedly
older than a dinosaur or something,
and it's from Japan.
About them.
I don't know. They're cool,
and they're smart,
- and the blonde one is totally hot.
- Zach, you are completely useless.
Amy, I'm a camera tech,
not a war correspondent, okay?
Why not cut me a little slack,
because, under the circumstances,
I'm doing a pretty good job
of holding this all...
I'm sorry. You're great.
Just calm down.
I'm calmed down.
Follow me.
I will show you how it is done.
Let's see.
Hey, Early, how is it going?
- It's Henry.
- Right.
Is this really your first mission?
Because you seem awfully
calm and confident,
and look at all this amazing
technology you've designed...
Okay, so I know what you're doing,
because you know I'm a big fanboy, and
you're using your feminine wiles so that
I tell you things I can't tell you, but
I can't tell you.
- That obvious, huh?
- Just a tad.
Look, this is a big
opportunity for me.
So...
Lot of... bullets.
You're the tech support guy
for the team?
Pretty much.
Tied to a lab, watching
everyone else get the glory.
Look, I just want to prove
that I can do this, that's all.
That's all I'm trying to do, too.
Do you honestly think I want to be
"Weather watch with fabulous Amy"
for the rest of my life?
I want to be taken seriously
as a journalist,
and...
that's why I took this chance.
And if all that happens to this footage
is that it ends up in a drawer
somewhere in your lab, then, fine,
but at least I know that it exists,
and that I had the guts
to follow my instincts,
you know?
So I'm analyzing the organic compound
found in the creature's nest,
see if I can find a chemical signature
so that we can trace it
a little more accurately.
Cool, so, when you catch it...
Is your facility
or your headquarters far away?
I mean, are you guys local?
I really do like your show.
I watch it all the time.
Do you mind?
That was you showing
me how it was done.
Mom...
He's alive, but he's not well.
- That's the guy from before!
- You know him?
Yeah, when we were first in here.
He helped us.
- We thought he was...
- He's lost a lot of blood.
There could be spinal damage.
We can't move him until I know more.
- How long until the scanner's ready?
- Two minutes. Almost done calibrating.
Non-fatal wounds
to the shoulder and knee.
Why would it leave him alive?
Maybe it didn't want to kill,
just disable what it viewed as a threat.
Let's stop playing games.
Let's take this thing down.
- Don't move, you're safe.
- You're okay, you're okay.
He isn't.
Sorry, it's just,
why lie to the guy?
Is it... Is it still in here?
For now it's keeping its distance.
We may have frightened it into hiding.
You won't stop it.
It moves too fast.
Did it attack you for any reason?
Did you provoke it?
Run, hide,
fight, it doesn't matter, man.
It doesn't make any difference.
It's not hiding from us.
No, it's...
It's watching us right now.
It's learning.
I don't see it!
Ashley, stay with him.
Zach, come on.
- Rolling?
- Amy, I'm rolling. Don't worry.
Chemical signatures
all over the place.
The chrysalis it made is preventing
a clear lock. Plus it could have left
- more residue in places around here.
- Can you refine the signal?
Not on the fly, no.
You can't find it?
I thought you knew
what you were doing.
We do. It's a matter of being prepared
for the unexpected.
- See what I mean?
- What the hell just happened?
You think the cops
turned off the power?
They have no reason to. As far as
they know, this isn't a hostage crisis.
Turn on your on-board light.
Will, get them out of the way!
Henry, covering fire!
All right, come on. Let's go!
- Let's go, now, come on.
- All right, all right.
- Are you okay?
- Did you see that thing?
- It was right on top of us!
- Are you injured?
No, I think...
I think I'm all right.
It's okay. You're okay.
It's just waiting for us!
Look at me, look at me.
You're okay.
It was just...
- It was just waiting for us.
- I know. It's going to be okay.
It's going to be okay.
- Did you... Did you get any footage?
- Are you kidding me?
I almost dropped a deuce on myself
when the lights went off.
- That was interesting.
- Good shooting, Henry.
- What happened?
- We winged it with a couple of tranqs.
Do you think it's unconscious?
To be honest,
I think we just made it angrier.
It definitely wasn't the cops
who cut the lights.
It's an insect. It can't know
how to work an electrical panel. Can it?
Even if they can,
why kill the power?
Because it sees better in the dark.
Dammit.
Sorry.
I've stabilized him for now,
but we need to get him to the Sanctuary
as soon as possible.
- None of this is going how we planned.
- No kidding.
Can you can
the commentary for a while?
I'm just saying, this thing's owned
our asses so far, man.
As much as we'd love to blow its ass
to kingdom come, it's not cooperating.
I'm just trying
to find a logic pattern.
Somebody brings this thing here,
it gets free, and kills,
what, six people?
And it's remarkably intelligent.
And none of the perimeter alarms have
been tripped since we set them up.
Why not escape?
It's not exactly like
we're holding the line.
- It's not trying to leave.
- Exactly.
Which makes me wonder,
why this warehouse?
- Why make this its turf?
- Yeah, why not go tearing through town
on some huge killing spree
or something?
There was a shipping tag on
the container it made its chrysalis in.
If we can find out who brought it,
we might be able to find out
- how they captured it.
- Warehouse manifest.
Should be in one of those offices
on the other side of the building.
All right, you three go.
Find out what you can.
I need to get this man
ready for transport.
I can take him in the van.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah,
you guys need to finish this.
I've had my fun.
We got to get this dude out of here.
Thank you, Henry.
You sure you want to stay?
You need the footage,
and a reporter never abandons
her cameraman.
We're just going to go to the control
office, or whatever, right?
Like, not find more nests.
Yeah, that's the plan.
Let's do it.
Be careful.
- What...
- Check inside there.
What are we looking for?
We are looking for something that might
tell us how to stop that thing.
Right, cool.
Is there anything?
I don't know.
You keep asking me questions.
Sorry.
I know this is probably the worst timing
in the history of the world,
but, you know, is there any way
that you and I could go out, you know,
for something to eat, or a drink,
or, like, a matcha or
something like that?
Tea?
I'm flattered...
Zach, right.
I don't...
I don't go out on dates...
much.
I know, me neither.
I'm not trying to put you on the spot.
It's just the possibility
of me dying, just...
It always just brings out
the desperado in me.
Right. Raincheck?
Yeah, great. Great, so...
You're not a vegetarian, are you?
Why, what are you...
What are you thinking?
I was thinking, like... You know, maybe
like some Kobe beef or something.
- Steaks.
- Yeah.
Or...
- I think I got something here.
- Oh, good. You found something.
The crate we found
the chrysalis in was
one of two items registered
to the Japanese Vessel Miyazaki,
out of Hokkaido.
The other is a container
full of medical supplies.
No export company
or local receiver listed.
Location?
Section 12?
Peachy.
This way.
Sorry.
Scratched.
I guess we're not the only ones
who are curious about what's in here.
Wild.
You want to use your special
lock-picking skills?
Stand back.
Cover Zach.
Zach, stay back.
- Back.
- All right, all right. I'll stand back.
- Ears.
- Ready?
That's...
That's a gun.
Nicely done.
What...
is that?
Maybe it's a bomb.
I don't think we can move this.
Then let's open it.
I can peg that.
Round 2.
- Ears.
- Okay. Sure.
- Take my flashlight?
- Sure, yeah.
Two, three...
What? Flashlight.
That's wild...
I guess now we know
why it doesn't want to escape.
It's protecting its young.
Oh, my camera's...
No, don't!
What are those things?
- Insect embryos.
- Size large.
No wonder it's pissed.
So they're like tiny scary insect
creatures waiting to be born?
That's just so gnarly...
So someone finds the creature's eggs,
steals them and bags the mom.
Who else would know about this?
This is an extremely rare species.
- The Cabal.
- Who?
They'd smuggle something like this
into the country for their own research.
Which would not be
for the common good.
This is just so 007.
Seriously, do you have
any more openings in your office,
'cause I am totally down with this.
Serious.
I'm guessing that creature
wasn't captured at all.
It stowed away on that ship.
It followed these here out of pure...
Maternal instinct, yeah.
I guess the lucky thing is it's still
pretty early in the development cycle.
I doubt
they're anywhere near maturity.
Unless their cycle is super fast.
I'm sure this is probably
a really cool find, or whatever,
but if that thing wants to
protect its kids so bad,
shouldn't we get the hell
out of here right now?
Magnus has to see this.
She'll light up like
it's Christmas morning.
Your mom is weird.
No, like, cool, like,
"Whoa, so cool" weird...
- Sorry.
- Ashley!
- What's up?
- Get back here immediately.
Let's go, guys.
Stay close, stay close!
- He's having a seizure!
- Henry, sedative!
- Just hang on.
- Oh, come on! Come on!
Quick, quick.
Oh, my God...
Oh, my God.
His vitals were stable.
We were just about to move him.
He suddenly went
into anaphylactic shock.
Come on!
He was attacked by the creature.
It probably caused more than external
trauma. Look at the symptoms.
A neurotoxic venom.
Oh, that's great.
It's not just a bug, it's a...
giant poisonous bug!
That's great, that's just great.
He just...
That thing could do that
to all of us.
I'm sorry.
Did you think
this was some kind of game?
That you could just come here and film
some wild event, and then, what,
enjoy cocktails
at some award ceremony?
I've never seen anyone die before.
This is what you came for.
This is crazy.
Okay, forget about capturing it alive.
How do we kill it?
Actually, capturing it alive
is exactly what we're going to do.
- Come on.
- Mom, come on,
I know you want this badly,
but really...
It's time to bring
the hammer down, big time.
We don't have to.
It wants to protect its young.
I say we let it.
- We leave the embryos exposed.
- Draw mom into the kids club.
Lock the door on it.
Presto, we got built-in
secure transport.
Exactly.
Yes! This is so freaking cool.
Nothing.
- You're getting this, right?
- Yeah, yeah,
don't worry,
I got a perfect view from here.
I'm glad you like my show.
Yeah, it's good.
You should be proud.
So should you.
Is this thing coming, or what?
Just give it time.
Once I had this mouse in my apartment,
so I set a bunch of traps for it,
but I never caught it, 'cause it was,
like, this super genius mouse...
- Zach, please.
- Sorry, Dr. Magnus,
- it's just, what is this thing?
- Dude,
- just chill out.
- I'm sorry, dude.
I'm just a little stressed out
right now. There's a monster.
Mom, we have a problem.
Police chatter says we're out of time.
SWAT is starting their sweep right now.
Dammit.
Go, go!
Get it! Get it...
Push!
Come on.
You wanted it alive...
- You got it alive!
- Well done, Henry.
- Not bad for your first mission, buddy!
- Way to go, team!
That'll be the police.
Good timing, as usual.
- Them we can handle.
- Hypocrisy.
- What the hell?
- What are they shooting at?
Let's go!
Go?
What do you mean, let's go?
What is going on here?
What's going...
I just wanna...
This is just insane. I don't know.
What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
What the hell?
But it couldn't have done this.
We just caught it.
Unless there's more
than one of them.
Guys...
Two of them.
You have got to be kidding me!
I can't get a fix!
- I think we just locked up its mate.
- Oh, that's not good.
That's not good.
Oh, where is it?
Where is it?
Oh, come on, where is it?
Hey, are you okay?
I think so.
I just... I don't know.
- What happened?
- This one's angrier than the first one.
Thanks for saving my ass again.
You're worth it.
Really?
You weren't just placating me
with a raincheck?
Like, I totally thought
you were back there.
I wasn't, really. I'm...
- I'm going to call you.
- Really? You'd go out with me?
That's to...
Considering everything,
it was incredibly brave of you
to contact us.
I changed my mind
about a dozen times
before I picked up the phone,
believe me.
And we do.
Look, I know you had to confiscate
the hard drive,
but technically that footage
belongs to Channel 13 News,
and my bosses know that something went
down in that warehouse, and that we...
That Zach shot a lot of footage
before he...
- They want to know what happened.
- A lot of questions are being asked.
And I figure the best way
to deflect them
is to put something together that
doesn't show anything incriminating,
that keeps
you guys and that...
- thing out of it.
- That's everything on there.
I can re-edit it to look like
a community square dance
if you give me enough time.
It won't go to air.
I promise.
Look, I know you guys think
I am a...
pushy, ambitious cold-hearted bitch,
but I came to you
because...
Because Zach shouldn't have...
What you guys do,
protecting people,
learning from the creatures.
Your work,
it's important.
So why not
show the world and further your career
in the process?
Because I thought
I should do the right thing,
and help you keep your secret,
so that maybe, at some point
in the future, you would help me,
and let me in on something
I can take to my superiors.
If you're looking for a deal
or a guarantee,
you won't get it.
All we ask is that you do
as your conscience dictates.
If at all possible.
We really need this to die down.
The rumor mill at the precinct
is in overdrive.
- Make us look...
- Like we were never there.
And that nothing ever happened.
Thank you.
I loved your last show. The one
about gore-tex and umbrellas?
Killer stuff.
Really.
Call me.
I'm just sayin',
chicks love dudes
who go on missions.
That's awesome!
I have it.
Yeah, book me an edit suite
right away,
and start laying pipe with New York.
This is...
This is going to blow their minds.
They'll want it first up
for tomorrow night's broadcast,
for sure.
Nice try.
You know, the shame of it all is that
you'll make a hell of a good reporter...
Someday.
Have a good career.