Previously on Sanctuary...
We were a part of something,
something we called "the Five,"
a small group dedicated to expanding
our knowledge of the physical world.
Your mother was able to procure
a very rare sample
of ancient untainted vampire blood,
blood that supposedly possessed
miraculous properties.
After each of us was injected,
we received unique gifts
as a result.
Griffin's molecules
became photosensitive.
Watson's mind grew to new heights,
and Tesla's reaction
was the most dramatic.
Your name is Gregory Magnus,
and you're my father.
You were the leading
scientific light of your day.
The Cabal are a powerful
shadow organization bent on
controlling all abnormal life
on the planet.
They threaten
everything we stand for.
Roy...
You scared the living crap
out of me.
Did Jack swing by
and return your boat?
He should've been back by now.
What's going on?
Are you feeling all right?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
What are you doing?
Roy...
It's me. George.
The Team Projet-SG
presents:
Sanctuary - Season 1 Episode 12
Revelations - Part 1 (v. 1.00)
Timing by: Kujathemas,
nitrogenc, Salomon.
http://projet-sg.net
We thought these reports of sudden,
unexplained violent behavior
among abnormals,
were isolated incidents,
but Henry's data analysis
clearly tells us otherwise.
It's getting hairy.
Those yellow clusters,
63 incidents in the last five days,
almost all of them against humans.
There's 20 dead so far.
These aren't exactly
high-population centers.
- The Yukon-Alaskan border?
- What's particularly troubling
is the pattern of distribution,
starting in the north at Mount Logan
and then following the upper airstream.
How could this abnormal-on-normal
violence be following the wind?
- Unless it's something in the air.
- My worry is what happens
when it reaches population centers.
Abnormals surfacing
in significant numbers
will undoubtedly trigger reprisals.
You think it could be insect-borne?
Given the cold climate,
it seems unlikely,
but certainly
a pathogen could be involved.
Viruses have been known
to cause mass psychosis.
What we need to find out is whether this
was a naturally occurring phenomenon,
or something
that was intentionally released.
Not often I use a front door.
Quite the novelty.
You're not welcome here, Druitt.
You know that.
I bring critical information,
my hirsute friend,
about the troubles in the north.
Forgive my skepticism, John,
but your history of altruism
is just behind a scorpion's.
Had I not dispatched Tesla, your reign
over the Sanctuary may well have ended.
- Why is he here?
- Please. I am your father.
Then you should start acting like one,
and that does not mean kidnapping me
- when you spend some quality time.
- That is part of why I'm here.
I'm guessing it's not about
visitation rights.
You have frostbite.
It's certainly no reflection
on your hospitality.
- Perhaps you can guess where I've been.
- The Yukon.
I saw the carnage first-hand.
Traced the epidemic...
To its origins.
Mount Logan.
Not to worry.
It's all been sealed to proper
BSL-3 protocols. Et cetera, et cetera.
I wasn't aware that epidemiology
was one of your specialties.
Well, that's why I've come to you.
I found these fragments
at ground zero,
and I believe you, Mr. Foss,
will find these of particular interest.
These look like fragments
from a dispersal mechanism.
Henry, prepare a level-three
residential cell for introduction
- of a possible bio-hazard.
- Better than some I've been called.
What's the point?
He will teleport out of there.
- I give you my assurances I will not.
- Let me back up those assurances
with an EM-shield.
You teleport, you die.
Are we supposed to believe that
you came here to fight the outbreak?
The war has begun.
Humans versus abnormals,
and I will not stand idly by
while the Cabal imposes its chaos.
Well, John was right
about one thing.
His body shows no presence
of any viral or bacterial anomaly.
Fortunately, neither do any of ours.
- You want to take him out of isolation?
- I think we should wait for a bit.
There might be a latency factor
that we should allow for.
I'm prepping the machine
for a full work-up.
There's only so much I can tell
from the fragments.
It's way sophisticated.
This is stuff they tested
at Fort Dietrich
when they were researching
biological weapons for...
"defensive" purposes.
Your biosafe room
is scrubbed and ready.
- Thanks. I'll let you know what I get.
- Thank you.
Something the Cabal
could have built.
Well, we know their access
to technology is unrivaled.
Yeah, and I just got schooled
on their willingness to experiment
- on humans as well as abnormals.
- Telegram.
Telegram?
What is this, 1890?
Our Dr. Watson tends only to trust
the more established forms
of communication.
Dr. Watson?
Not as in James Watson,
who's a member of the Five?
Yeah, and head of the UK Sanctuary.
"Helen, a matter
of the utmost urgency.
"Will be arriving at the Sanctuary
tomorrow.
"Will be bringing everything we need
to get to the bottom of this new menace.
"Your trusted colleague, JW."
Do you have an update, doctor?
The field test is going very,
very well.
Better even
than our models suggested.
Abnormals in the path of the agent are
showing rapid onset of clinical paranoia
and extreme aggression.
How far is this dispersal
expected to spread?
We put sustainability at four days
before it wanes of its own accord.
The reaction to the abnormal uprising
is exactly what we hoped for.
Anger, scapegoating, retribution.
That's your real vector
of transmission.
What about the Sanctuary?
Two of the five, Druitt and Watson,
have already made contact with Magnus.
I want hourly updates.
Every communication in and out.
We really can't take
anything for granted.
You said that we were dealing with
the most brilliant minds on the planet.
Brilliant, yes, but they have no idea
what they're facing.
I have some good news.
James...
It's so good to see you.
You haven't changed a bit.
- Since last fall in London?
- No, since spring of 1886.
Coming from such a keen observer,
I'll take that as a compliment.
Now, I will need help.
I have a driver and a truck
at the loading dock.
- I brought some things.
- Things?
Corpses, Helen.
You didn't expect me to arrive
without a gift, did you?
Dr. James Watson,
Ashley and Henry
you know, of course.
Lovely to see you again, my dear.
Henry, the new servers
are working perfectly.
- Oh, thanks, doc. I try.
- And my new colleague,
- Dr. Will Zimmerman.
- Hello.
The protégé.
Yes, I've heard quite a bit
about you.
- All good, I hope.
- Some.
Profiler, right?
Yes.
Yes, Dr. Magnus told you?
No, actually, I was
watching you looking at me.
- Really?
- A profiler looks, listens,
gauges, senses,
calculates, compares.
Am I really a doctor?
Am I really who I say I am?
The tells, the giveaways.
The twitch of an eye,
the odd unnatural pause...
You have dirt under a single fingernail.
Did you scratch at something?
- Did I?
- I think so.
Something green.
Verdigris...
Oxidized bronze.
The door knocker.
To test its age.
Reproductions are rampant.
I would have been so disappointed.
- From that, you got "profiler"?
- More your immediate threat assessment.
Is that a bomb on his chest?
Is the accent authentic? Is he casing
the room? That said "profiler".
- I'm impressed.
- Yes, of course you are.
And people tell me
I sound like Sherlock Holmes.
Actually, Will,
that's exactly who he is.
So you don't mean that your
Dr. Watson really is Sherlock Holmes?
Not the literary figure,
of course, but yes,
Conan Doyle did model the character
after James' brilliant deductive mind.
So why did he get relegated to
the sidekick in the stories?
At Watson's insistence.
He preferred to let
Holmes take center stage
while he played the fawning
acolyte in the wings.
His genius...
Was exponentially increased
when he became one of the Five.
What about the bodies
he brought here?
They're being prepared for an autopsy
in a biosafe environment.
You know, if this disease really does
turn abnormals into psychotic killers,
then in theory, you, Henry, the big guy,
are all potentially susceptible.
Ashley, too, in theory.
Anyone with that DNA could suddenly
be stricken with psychotic aggression.
I've done that dance with you once
a half a mile under the ocean.
- I'm not anxious to do it again.
- Nor am I, Will.
Body is that of a male abnormal,
Odobenus Rosmarus Sapien.
A genetic melange
of human and walrus.
Koo-koo-ka-choo.
Cause of death,
multiple gunshot wounds
suffered during a reported
fire-fight
after the subject allegedly slaughtered
three out of four family members.
What you mean is,
the abbie went psycho
and then got shot to bloody hell.
You always did have
the gift for brevity.
It's not the ballistics
we're interested in.
We'll need samples of every organ.
The scalpel is yours, doctor.
Thank you.
You know, James, you really are
a walking medical miracle.
I think "walking"
is a bit of an exaggeration.
Without these exoskeletal
powered braces,
I fear I would be confined
to a wheelchair.
Nothing to be ashamed of at 160.
Anyway, if I am a miracle,
what does that make you?
My gift was longevity.
Yours was far more profound.
Care to switch?
How's the serum transaminase going?
Inconclusive levels.
The fact that behavioral changes
are the first clinical presentation
make this diagnosis very prickly.
Well, John was unaffected despite
being exposed to ground zero,
which suggests that the special
qualities of the Five
might well provide
an immunity factor.
Until the tests come back,
I'll be looking at my own blood
- to combat the disease.
- I'll tell you the results,
- or would you rather be surprised?
- A man-made pathogen.
A psychosis-inducing agent that affects
only abnormals has to be by design.
John believes
the Cabal is behind it.
Well, John draws his insights
from an affinity with evil.
I have great faith in his analysis.
I've released him from isolation.
Now if you could
only release yourself.
I'm sorry?
Our contacts are too seldom,
too brief,
considering I'm the leader of
your largest satellite operation.
It's out of respect for your autonomy
as much as anything else.
Most people go back to their oldest
contacts for solace, Helen.
You defy that convention,
but then, you always have.
We're together now, aren't we?
If only the circumstances
were more agreeable.
So, what is that?
A necessary component
for my survival.
There's not much we can do till
the results come in in the morning...
Not that I think Helen
will sleep very much.
Tell me, young man,
what is it like to work for a woman?
A woman like Dr. Magnus?
It's a privilege.
What Watson means is,
what's it like for someone
who hasn't been dragged
by his scruff into the 21st century?
And the century before that.
Most men's failures
haunt them for a lifetime.
Mine have haunted me for two.
What failure?
The Ripper case.
It confounded me like no other.
You came close, James.
You don't know how close.
Night after night,
I poured my insights out to you,
never knowing that the target of
my manhunt was the man
who dissected my suppositions.
I was in the grip of something
I couldn't control. You know that.
The fact remains,
you gave the lie to all my bravado.
You shattered my belief that I could see
beyond what a mere mortal could.
A little sensitivity here.
We're in the presence of a mere mortal.
Young Will here has the makings of
a decent detective.
Perhaps he would have seen
what I could not.
I'm sorry.
It's just, it's amazing to me.
Sherlock Holmes, Jack the Ripper...
The fact that you two
can sit here together...
Time is a great healer.
Redemption,
that requires a little more.
You ooze judgment, doctor,
like a weeping sore.
In a life devoted to justice, sir,
it is a constant burr on my backside
that you have avoided it.
Justice is meted out in many ways.
You're not the only one haunted.
You've got to believe that fate has
brought you two together for a reason.
Yes, why are you here, Druitt?
To save the world as we know it,
and, time allowing,
reassert my superiority
in our battle of wits.
It's really hard to know
how this sucker worked.
So much chop and so little suey.
But you think cryo was involved.
Well, it looks like the bio-agent was
cooled way down before being vaporized.
The latest data suggests that
the rate of infection is slowing.
That's a good thing?
This first dispersal was a test,
a dry run. I'm certain.
To measure the effectiveness of what
I think is some sort of neurotoxin.
A dispersal device of sufficient size
could well blanket the globe.
We need to find out
what their capabilities are.
Our intelligence has
the Cabal's weapons laboratories
in several far-flung places.
Including one very close to home.
Like just outside of New City,
if I remember right.
Hang on a second.
- I think I got somethin' here.
- What is it?
Looks like one of the microcapsules
survived detonation.
It's a pure sample of the agent.
Put it in a biosafe
container, Henry.
Just be very, very careful.
You know those little mechanical arms
that pick up stuffed toys at arcades?
Four-time state champion.
We're looking at one of
the most dangerous pathogens
the abnormal world has ever seen.
It functions very much
like a prion on steroids.
The rogue protein
found in mad cow disease.
It replicates inside the abnormal's
brain, causing pathological aggression.
And eventually a very painful death.
According to the tests,
we can say with certainty that the mode
of transmission is not person-to-person.
It's not communicable.
That's the good news.
But the susceptibility
to antivirals is nil.
The fact is, prion disease
is largely incurable.
I still think our best hope is
to find something in our own blood,
possibly an antigen
that could inhibit the disease.
That would explain
why we are apparently immune.
Because you all injected
the source blood.
That's pretty powerful stuff.
Even if we can't find something
in our individual blood
that could stop the disease,
it may well be
that the source blood could,
in the form of
a synthesized antitoxin.
Except that the ancient blood
was used up over 120 years ago.
Not all of it.
What?
My father wanted to destroy
what was left.
Eventually he agreed to set aside
the unused portion of the vial
only to be tapped
in the most dire of emergencies,
and he made sure that only the five of
us acting in concert could retrieve it.
Which is a bit of a problem if,
in fact, I have killed Tesla.
Even if Nicola managed to survive,
the last of the Five, Nigel Griffin,
could not possibly be enlisted.
Because?
Because Griffin died
half a century ago.
The situation may not be
as hopeless as you think.
You have the power to revive the dead?
Now, that would impress me.
Before he died, in the early '60s,
Griffin wrote me a letter
declaring that his legacy
had been passed on.
He has a daughter, Anna.
Now, with any luck,
we could track her down
and convince her to take on
her father's role in our mission.
Hold on a second.
You said that only the Five acting
together could retrieve the blood.
The powers of the Five,
to be more accurate.
So, what's Griffin's power?
Nigel Griffin?
He was the invisible man.
I don't understand.
If the epidemic stopped in its tracks,
how did he get the disease?
Well, Watson and Druitt may have
come back clean in their blood work,
but that doesn't rule out
the microorganism being brought in on
their clothing
or their personal items.
So it's only a matter of time
before every abnormal in the Sanctuary
comes down with it.
Including me.
I could offer you assurances, Henry,
but they'd be hollow.
What's his prognosis, doc?
Well, I suspect every species
of abnormal reacts differently,
but if the reports
are any indication,
he'll become increasingly
irrational and violent,
then turn against human beings,
and eventually,
he'll die.
We appear to have been successful
in getting the toxin into the Sanctuary.
By now I'm quite sure our friends there
will have correctly concluded
that the biologic wildfire we started
has all but burned itself out.
I wouldn't sound so cavalier.
Remember the problems
we encountered with her father.
Gregory Magnus helped us engineer
the consummate soldier for our army.
Yes, but his information
on the whereabouts of the source
proved utterly erroneous.
Perhaps what Gregory didn't disclose,
the Five will.
I've checked with every source I have.
Every contact in the abnormal community.
They're all saying the same thing.
The Yukon test was a dry run.
A popgun compared to what happens
three days from now.
A big bang that'll blanket
the entire planet.
Three days? Why three days?
Why not launch the biowar right now?
Changing weather patterns, wind shear,
patterns of the trade winds.
Telling you, there's something wrong.
It doesn't fit. It doesn't make sense.
Yeah, well, genocide rarely does.
You told me the lengths
the Cabal went through
to build the perfect soldier
for the ethnic cleansing.
My father became an unwitting
accomplice to those ends.
Why engineer an army of abnormals if
your real line is an invisible pathogen?
Perhaps to fend off any re-emergence of
abnormals once the decimation complete.
Who's to say that your own army
won't be susceptible?
You've got to believe that they've built
an immunity into their design.
They knew it would be possible
to immunize after the fact.
The source blood is the key.
Even if we do find this Anna Griffin,
we still don't have Tesla.
What's the point if you don't have
the last member of the Five?
I know how my father thought.
Now, if he'd anticipated that one
or more of the Five might have died,
he may well have built in
some sort of safety mechanism
- so we could still crack the code.
- Same old Helen.
"I'm just going to jump off this cliff
and hope that I sprout wings."
Where did Gregory hide the vial?
In one of the most inaccessible places
on the planet.
The lost city of Bhalasamm
in the Indian Himalayas.
The seat of the original culture
of ancient vampires.
So, not Transylvania?
Its unique topography
keeps everything well-hidden.
Trust me, Will,
this makes the other wonders
of the ancient world pale.
- He what, hid it like a pirate's chest?
- There's a labyrinth beneath the city.
My father placed
five keys within it,
each impossible to release without
the properties acquired by the blood.
And what's your power,
just showing up for the meeting
after 135 years?
Like to see you do it.
Okay, so I did a full cavity search
on the Internet for this Anna Griffin.
She went by a different name,
so that slowed me down,
but then I tracked her
to Baton Rouge.
- 3 years ago, she drops off the earth.
- Could she simply have died?
If you believe the obit, she did,
but it didn't pass the sniff test.
The certificate of death
was an outright forgery.
Somebody wanted us
to think she'd kicked.
Like it was, like,
a witness protection or something.
So I was lucky to find a few
fragments that they missed.
I found an address. So,
somebody better wake up Druitt, 'cause
we ain't got time to take no fast train.
- "We"?
- You can't send Druitt alone.
He's all hearts and flowers one day,
next, he's turning a girl into a canoe!
Despite his goodwill as of late,
there are definitely
warring sides to his personality.
- Keep Druitt company.
- What?
Why me? I'm supposed to tell
Jack the Ripper to fetch?
Just remember...
His sharpest implement is his mind.
Can I help you guys?
Yeah, as a matter of fact.
We're looking for Anna Thayer Griffin.
Who's asking?
We're friends of the family.
Then I'm surprised
you don't know she's dead.
Is she?
Yes, she is.
I went to her funeral.
She died three years ago.
Where's she buried?
We'd like to pay our respects.
Whispering Pines.
Thanks.
Just give me a second...
Every experiment where I tried to create
an anti-toxin from one of us has failed.
We've no choice but to go
to the source.
You do have a choice, mom.
We find a way to stop
that bioweapon from going off,
- you don't need the damn source.
- You want me to send you into the heart
of the Cabal's weapons factory
and do it all on your own.
Henry said he'll go with me.
No offense, but you don't graduate from
Eagle Scout to James Bond overnight.
- I was green as Gumby, too.
- I can do this.
What, Gumby?
I'm Gumby now?
Odds are, the device will be triggered
from their network of weapons labs.
Which is why we need to break in there
and find a way to stop the detonation.
Just like that?
- I didn't say it'd be easy.
- I didn't say you could go.
Mom, we don't have a lot of time.
We can do this.
Get in.
Get what you need, and get out.
No unnecessary risks.
- Let's go, Gumby.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
- Ashley...
- Yeah?
Someone's been visiting the grave,
empty or not.
If the gift was passed on
to the daughter,
why not an offspring?
She went that way.
- How could her clothes be invisible?
- She's not wearing any.
I thought so.
You're Anna's daughter, aren't you?
Clara.
She was afraid she'd be called.
You're the people she was
worried about, aren't you?
Yeah, well, she's off the hook.
We'd like you to take her place.
I don't know about the Sanctuary,
and I don't know who you guys are.
You just said your mother was afraid
she'd be called on.
She obviously talked to you about
your grandfather. His unusual past.
I have to go.
Why did you follow us
out here, Clara?
Before she went into hiding,
she must have told you that
the responsibility would fall to you,
- that you'd have to use your gift.
- I do use it.
I can reach into any till I want.
- That's not what it was made for.
- Why did she fake her death?
Because she was sick
and tired of running,
living in fear.
She wanted to disappear for good,
so she made everyone believe she died.
The irony is,
is two years later, she did die,
and she was the only one who understood
what it was like for me,
and now there's no one.
I never wanted it,
what you guys call a gift.
But you have it,
and right now, you could be
the only person that could help us
stop something terrible
from happening.
Let me out!
Let me out now!
Helen... Helen...
Don't let me out.
Pitting humans against abnormals,
decided who lives and who dies...
The Cabal has to be stopped.
It's why I started this mission
more than a century ago.
I just didn't know it.
Well, you have four of the Five,
but I don't think Clara can do
what we need her to do.
- You said you saw her go invisible.
- Yeah, but...
Look, she talks a tough game,
but she's afraid of her own shadow,
when she has one,
and she thinks we're a cult.
I just don't think
she has it in her.
Well, you have till mid-day
tomorrow to convince her.
And what if she can't pull it off?
What if we can't find Tesla's key?
What if my father gave up
the source to the Cabal
when they had him
under their thrall?
You can't answer
every "what if", Will.
I just know that we only have days
to stop the destruction
of every abnormal on earth.
Prisoner visiting hours
are 10:00 till 2:00.
You're not a prisoner.
Oh, so, I can leave, then?
When we go, you can go with us.
You got a real trophy,
didn't you, Dr. Z?
That's not what's happening here.
Invisible girl?
Come on...
Tell me your band of creature hunters
scores like that every week.
Clara, I need you to understand
the stakes here.
- I know it could cost me my life.
- I don't think it will come to that.
You don't think?
I don't want to sugarcoat it.
This mission is going to
be dangerous as hell,
and you're gonna have to use your power
in a way that's never been used before,
and if you fail, if we fail,
then thousands if not millions
of lives will be affected.
You finished?
Except to say that...
- I believe that you can do it.
- Oh, please.
You don't know who the hell I am.
I don't think you know
who the hell you are.
I mean, you've spent
half your life hiding.
You have no idea
what it's like to disappear.
People look into your eyes,
and they don't see anything.
You're a... a phantom,
a mirage.
You don't matter,
and you don't exist.
Yeah, but you can do something.
I mean, you can do something
that maybe nobody on earth can do.
You sound like my mother.
So she did talk to you
about your destiny.
Yeah, she...
said the power was passed on
for a reason.
First to her, and then to me.
I've never wrapped
my head around it.
I don't know, Will.
I have never done
anything like this before.
I don't think any of us have.
How long before
the sedation wears off?
Three, four hours.
I've managed to increase
the antigen levels in our blood samples
by a factor of two.
We need a factor of 100.
If I draw his blood and inject myself,
my levels would spike that high.
- You'll most likely kill yourself.
- My blood will protect me,
- I'll bet my life on it.
- That's what you'd be doing.
If we don't find the source,
we need to find some way
to fight this disease.
Helen, for God's sake,
you have no protection!
Are you mad?
Just desperate.
I warned you.
It's me, Helen.
There's no need to harm me.
Okay, so if this isn't the back entrance
to an evil lair, I don't know what is.
Okay, the barbed wire's easy.
- How do we get rid of the lasers?
- I blind them, with this.
- What would boys do without their toys?
- Can you stop with the boy thing?
If we're gonna do this,
I need a modicum of...
Respect.
Henry, you're Indiana Jones
with cooler toys.
Thank you. See?
Was that so hard?
John will teleport us two at a time
to a wooded area just below
the rim of the outlook.
We make the modest descent
to the ridge
and enter the lost city
via the eastern approach.
Can't you just teleport us
into this labyrinth thing?
My powers are formidable,
I'll allow,
but as I haven't seen
what's down there...
Rematerializing inside a granite boulder
would not be a comfortable way to die.
No, true.
Absolutely.
I prefer to walk.
Once inside
the subterranean passages,
we'll each be responsible
for securing our designated keys.
Does no one else see
the madness in all this?
You believe
I can't accomplish Nicola's task.
He had the powers of a vampire.
And, he fell asleep in Edison's
electric chair at full current.
I don't see your skill sets
overlapping.
My father always said
no problem has a single solution.
There are always alternatives.
All right, then, in the unlikely event
that we find all five keys...
We'll be led to an inner sanctum
where our keys will be inserted,
and the vial containing the source
will be released.
You know, it's not
the mission, Helen.
What worries me
is that gleam in your eye.
Suck it up, Jimmy.
We're going to India.
Kind of quiet.
That's good.
We don't have a lot of time.
We need to get in, get what we need,
and get out.
Okay, they're leaving.
Let's move.
Come on...
- Freeze!
- Don't move!
This is my father's worst nightmare.
That we would try
and retrieve the source.
You going to tell him?
If I find out where he's holed up,
and if the time is right...
No.
Who the hell are you?
Relax, Mr. Foss.
I'm your doctor.
Hello, Ashley.
It's good to finally meet you.
- Go to hell.
- I apologize for this,
but your reputation
does precede you,
and I have yet to meet
an intelligent being
that doesn't respond
to the proper stimulation.
What did you do to me?
Taming wild creatures
is what we do best.
We haven't even touched on
me getting wild yet.
- I think you'll like it.
- My name is Dana Whitcomb,
director of logistics
and operations here.
Nice job title.
Long hours?
You and your colleague, Mr. Foss,
came here with the intent
of trying to stop the release
of a bioweapon, codename Lazarus.
Very ambitious, not to mention
incredibly brave of you.
It was also incredibly foolish.
Well, foolish is
kind of how we roll.
Well, despite your efforts,
Lazarus will be released.
Its effects will be a thousand times
more devastating than phase one.
When the dust settles,
it will bring a new day for humans,
and what's left of abnormals.
Yeah, well, we'll see, won't we?
Your mother and her colleagues
will no doubt try to stop us.
I promise you they'll fail.
They'll fail because...
You're going to help us
complete our plan.
We're about to see the ninth wonder
of the ancient world,
- and I didn't even bring a camera.
- You brought your mind, didn't you?
Damn, you know,
I knew I forgot something.
Dear god.
It's all been destroyed.
There has to be a way down there.
There has to be a way
into the labyrinth.
It's over.
No access, no source.
No source, no vaccine.
No vaccine, no way to stop the Cabal
from taking over human evolution.