It's all clear up here.
Yeah, same here.
Ditto.
Copy that, I'm arriving now.
- It's me, Magnus.
- Over here.
- It's good to see you.
- You too, Helen.
- I love the hair.
- Thank you.
- Any problems?
- No, package is safe and sound.
Although I'll be very happy
to be rid of this one.
Little warmer than I'm used to.
That's what you get for transporting
a Tunisian fire elemental.
I have a cryo-container in the van.
We got company.
Two cars headed your way.
I got 'em.
All right, fan out.
They can't be far.
Eight scary-looking dudes.
They're searching the area.
- The Duke.
- Who?
Head of the abnormal mob
back in Chicago.
Damn.
He hired me
to bring him the elemental.
You stole this from a mob boss?
I wasn't about to let it
fall into his hands.
- How did he find us?
- You tell me.
- Your organization sprung a leak.
- No. Impossible.
Henry, we need a diversion.
I'm on it.
This way.
Let's go!
- Get in!
- Go!
Protect the package!
Go!
Please go!
They're on the move, headed north!
Okay, I'm on it.
Henry, Will, Kate's got Jimmy.
Meet at the rendezvous.
Hell, yeah. Copy that.
Nice work.
I think we lost them.
Where are we headed?
Why are we slowing down?
Crap.
The Team Projet-SG
presents:
Sanctuary - Season 2 Episode 9
Penance (v. 1.00)
Timing by: Arrow, Salomon
http://projet-sg.net
- Any sign of them?
- Not yet.
- Maybe they got turned around.
- It's been too long.
Kate, come in.
- Do you read?
- Maybe she dumped her walkie.
Try her cell phone.
I'll call the Big Guy,
see if she showed up at the Sanctuary.
- Who were those guys?
- Abnormals from Chicago.
- James stole the elemental from them.
- That's wonderful.
How were they able to track us?
- We told no one about this meeting.
- Maybe they followed him.
I've worked with James before.
He knows better than to let this happen.
She's not at the Sanctuary either.
All right, go back
and check with our contacts.
Find out if anyone's seen them,
and, Henry,
I want to know
how this Duke found us.
All right.
Easy!
I'm just looking at the wound.
We're gonna have to get
that bullet out.
We should get back to the Sanctuary.
No, we'd never make it.
There's a bunch of guys out there
trying to kill us.
Call Magnus, she'll pick us up.
No can do, your walkie's toast.
Besides, we don't know
how those guys found us.
They could be monitoring
our communications.
If you think Magnus tipped them off,
then you're crazy.
Not her, but there is a leak.
Until we find out where it is,
we can't risk
getting in touch with anyone.
I need you...
to stay still.
Are you nuts?
Come on! If I don't get the bullet out,
you are going to bleed to death.
Is that what you want?
You do me a favor. You take this,
you point this at the door.
Anyone comes through,
you blow them away, okay?
Try not to move too much.
It was a gray Sedan.
They shot out a couple of the windows.
If she went to the rendezvous,
she would've turned left
at the first opportunity.
Unless she were going to the Sanctuary,
she would've kept going straight.
Why were they shooting at him anyway?
Dangerous way to bring in an abnormal.
It's the container.
He doesn't have to be alive
for them to collect it.
Magnus, come in.
- How's it going, Henry?
- I put the word out about Kate,
but nothing yet.
Big Guy's checking to see
if anything got caught on videos.
- What about the system scan?
- Still processing, but in the meantime,
I did some research
into this abnormal mob.
Turns out their leader's a Diukon.
What's a Diukon?
Highly aggressive humanoid offshoot.
They suffer
from uncontrollable bouts of rage
so powerful they literally
can't contain it.
What do you mean,
they can't contain it?
Diukons have special glands
in their hands
that secrete radiation
when they get angry.
If they grab hold of you,
it's very unpleasant.
They cook you from the inside out
like a microwave...
Or so I've heard.
How is it possible
that a Diukon is leading a street gang?
There's no known suppressant
for their anger.
I have no idea,
but somebody's giving this guy
some serious happy pills.
Six months ago he was pit-fighting
other abnormals for cash.
Now he's the boss.
How'd it go?
We lost him.
He got away
with a member of the Sanctuary,
Kate Freelander,
but word is that they never made it
back to the Sanctuary.
So where are they now?
- We don't know.
- What about our monitoring capability?
It's still in place, but we have no way
to locate Freelander specifically.
Her radio signal went dead.
Boss, we'll find him.
Don't worry.
I'm not the one that needs to worry.
Duke...
Get him out of here.
Looks like those rage parameters
need a tweak.
I think I lost control for a second.
I'll run a diagnostic.
And keep monitoring
the Sanctuary frequency.
As long as Freelander's out there,
I want to keep tabs on them.
I'm gonna need a new one of these.
This is gonna hurt.
Come on...
You've got to stay still.
You got any morphine?
Please, I wish.
I could use some.
Here.
Hell of a first date, huh?
I've had worse.
I'm Jimmy, by the way.
"Hi, Jimmy, I'm... "
Where you from, Kate?
I grew up in Chicago.
Chicago, no kidding? Me too.
What part?
West Side.
Cal City.
Cal City?
That's not Chicago.
Says who?
Anyone actually from Chicago.
I'm sorry.
It's in kind of deep.
God... It's still not Chicago.
Want to continue on foot?
If what you say is true,
and Kate really has gone into hiding,
we'll never find her from the car.
Any particular direction
you have an affinity for?
You go east, I'll go west.
Proceed one block at a time.
Stay in radio contact.
All right.
Easy, I almost got it!
There!
You can save this one
for your collection.
Come on, West Side,
don't give up on me.
- Go ahead, Henry.
- Destroy your walkie right now.
- Now, tell me why I just did that.
- We got hit with a remote hack.
They're using our radio
frequencies to track us.
- Where's Will?
- He's not with me.
- He's not answering his cell.
- Dammit.
Easy...
Easy, easy...
What happened?
Nothing much.
You... stopped breathing,
so I...
took the opportunity
to make out with you.
Thanks.
Come on,
what are casual acquaintances for?
I'm sorry, doc.
- You had no way of knowing.
- Whoever did this is sophisticated.
I'm gonna have to re-encrypt
all the com frequencies.
Understood.
I'll see you soon.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Except for this 1,200-degree
abnormal inside of me,
I'm fine.
Why don't you take it out?
We need a cryo-container
to put it into.
See, this pocket of mine,
it acts like a sealed container.
Without it,
the vessel would breach
in 20 minutes or so.
Even with him inside there,
we got six hours, eight hours
at the most before I'm gonna have
to get it out of there again.
That's very reassuring.
What do those guys
want with it, anyway?
You kidding?
This thing represents
a virtually unlimited source of energy.
Makes weapons-grade plutonium
look like lamp oil.
The Duke's got this guy...
Ellison, a former Cabal geek,
who figured out a way
to harness the energy and weaponize it.
They were planning on selling it
to the highest bidder.
You should go.
You have a better shot at making it
to the Sanctuary on your own.
Yeah, and what?
Just leave you here?
Look, I don't want to be responsible
for that thing getting used
for some crazy weapon.
That's very noble, Kate,
but there's got to be
50 guys out there by now.
I wouldn't make it
out the front door.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
We'll wait until dark.
You know, hopefully
things will have cooled off by then.
No pun intended.
Name's Zimmerman.
And the others?
The signal went dead
after we grabbed him.
I know what you guys
are looking for.
I can't help you.
Come on...
Don't sell yourself short.
Everyone out there
is looking for Jimmy,
and the first one to find him,
they're gonna have a big advantage.
That's why I need you.
You're my insurance policy.
Put him in the room.
Put more men on the street
and widen the net.
There.
The com system's clean.
Any word on Will?
We tried to track his cell,
but they must have ditched it.
What are we gonna do?
We have no choice
but to continue looking for James.
We have no leverage at the moment,
which is why we need to find him
before they do.
Besides, the canister he's carrying
has to come out soon or...
Of course.
Henry, thermographic scanners.
We use them to detect the canister.
I thought his pouch was shielded
to prevent that detection.
It is, but after prolonged exposure,
even a sealed chamber
succumbs to the effects of radiant heat.
See if you can calibrate
our scanners.
Yeah, all right, I'm on it.
See you at the van in five?
- Actually, you go ahead.
- Why? What are you gonna do?
Stall.
Come on.
None of that.
Here.
This will perk you up.
So, Cubs or Sox?
Really?
This is what we're gonna talk about?
No matter how tough things get,
there is always time for baseball.
Come on, Cubs or Sox?
If I wanted to see fat guys
running around, I'd watch reality TV.
And you say you're from Chicago.
Next you'll be telling me
you don't like pizza.
My dad was a Cubs fan.
So I guess that makes me one too.
I knew I should have
left that bullet in.
- I take it you're a Sox fan?
- Oh, yeah.
My dad used to take me
to the games on Sundays.
He died when I was 12.
Mine died when I was eight.
No kidding?
What happened?
Who are you, Dr. Phil?
He died, okay?
Okay, I was just, you know...
This stuff tastes like crap.
We're shut out
of Sanctuary communications.
What happened?
They neutralized the initial hack
as expected.
- What about the back-up plan?
- Still in play.
Good.
Who the hell is this?
Let me make one thing
perfectly clear.
If you have touched so much as one hair
on Will Zimmerman's head,
there is not enough real estate
on this earth to keep you safe from me.
That's awfully tough talk
for someone in your position.
Is it?
- I guess you haven't heard.
- Heard what?
I have Jimmy.
- You're lying.
- My team picked him up moments ago.
- They're on their way back here.
- They have cell phones, don't they?
Put him on the phone.
Let me talk to him.
He's been injured.
He's in no condition to talk.
I will call you once he's stable.
Until then,
get your men off my streets
and keep your hands off my people.
Do you think
she's telling the truth?
Find out.
Is this thing gonna work?
Absolutely.
Detecting the heat signature's easy.
Problem is the range,
because we've got to be
within 35 feet.
35 feet?
You know I never have enough time
with these things.
- I guess I'll be walking, then.
- It's good for the heart.
I'll go this way.
Stay sharp.
- So who was she?
- What?
Only one reason
to get a tattoo removed.
That, or you found out
the Chinese character you picked
means "stupid white guy".
I used to run with some guys
back in the day.
The Kingtown gang.
You ever hear of them?
Sounds familiar.
I fell in with them when I was 16,
after my dad died.
Took me years to find my way out.
I know the feeling.
See, I was an easy target
because of old Mr. Happy here.
Started out innocent enough...
Drugs across the border,
stuff like that,
and then someone need a gun
for a robbery,
for a murder...
Yeah, pretty soon I was carrying
just about anything that fit in there.
I did some things I'm not proud of.
When'd you get out?
10 years ago.
They got me to make
a drop on the L
at rush hour.
A peridax.
- You know what that is?
- No.
It's this cute thing. It's a cross
between a guinea pig and a koala,
but anyway...
They said it was to create a diversion
for a robbery they're pulling.
Fine, so I'm...
I'm on the platform at Lake station,
I'm waiting for the red line,
and this woman comes up to me.
Dr. Magnus.
And somehow she knew
everything about me.
Who I was, what I was about to do,
and she tells me the gang lied.
That when a peridax gets scared,
it releases a spray like a skunk,
really toxic in close quarters,
you know?
I mean, I was that close
to killing...
hundreds of people.
She stopped me.
What?
Nothing.
Sorry.
You look really familiar.
Sorry...
Enjoy your meal.
Tell the Duke Magnus' people are still
out here looking for something.
I think your boss is lying to me...
Which is very, very bad news
for you.
What are you doing?
Ingenious, aren't they?
Built by my second-in-command,
Ellison.
Without 'em,
I'm nothing but an animal,
but at half power,
I find it to be
a very effective interrogation tool.
Okay, just hold on a second.
This is a very bad idea.
I disagree.
Where the hell is Jimmy?
Come on, come on...
Don't try to get up.
Seriously.
If you die, no one's gonna believe
that I saved you.
I can't stand this.
I need to do something.
We're sitting ducks.
Just relax.
It'll be dark in a few hours,
and we'll move then.
- So why'd you leave Chicago?
- Nothing to tell. I left, end of story.
Come on, I had my show and tell.
I think it's your turn.
You know I'm just gonna be annoying
and keep asking, right?
I left after my father died.
He was a lock-pick.
Could crack a safe
in four minutes flat.
He was hired to pull a bank job
by a group of heavy-hitters,
and they were impressed, and pretty soon
he was running with them.
Sound familiar?
What happened?
He was pinched.
When I was eight.
I remember because my mom
was pregnant at the time.
We were on our way to post bail.
He died...
Along with a dozen policemen
and three civilians.
The shock sent my mom into labor.
We nearly lost my brother too.
We left Chicago a few years later.
Moved around until my mom decided
to go back to Mumbai.
I headed to Montreal.
That's quite a story.
What's wrong?
What?
I'm just looking out the window.
You're acting all fidgety.
No, it's the elemental.
It's making me uncomfortable.
What the...
- What is it?
- Are you doing anything on the system?
No. Why?
Something's wrong. It's too slow.
Oh, man.
- I don't believe this.
- What?
They embedded a sleeper worm
that could only be activated
in the event I re-encrypted
the com frequencies.
They knew that we would find the virus.
They had a back-up plan in place.
Wait a minute.
They're monitoring our system right now?
I'm on my way.
I'll take care of it.
If they're so interested
in what we're up to,
I say let them see.
Where did Freelander take him?
How would Magnus
get in touch with them?
I don't know anything.
Then you're no good to me.
No, don't do this.
Why did you do that?
We just got confirmation.
The Sanctuary does have Jimmy.
What?
We were able to access
their intake files.
Jimmy's there.
Injured,
just like she said.
It's the Duke.
You think he bought it?
Let's hope so.
I thought I told you
to wait for my call.
I've waited long enough.
Besides,
your friend isn't doing too good.
I've transmitted my location.
If you have Jimmy
like you say you do,
you have 30 minutes
to deliver him to me.
Otherwise...
Pretty boy dies.
What the hell are we gonna do?
Did you notice that device
on his temple?
- What was that?
- It looked like some sort of electrode.
So he's a Diukon, remember?
- That's what's suppressing his anger?
- It makes sense.
A device that taps directly
into the limbic system
would have the desired effect
of keeping his aggression in check.
All right, that's all great,
but how does that help us?
Diukons' brain chemistry is vastly
different than that of a human.
If indeed his rage center
has been suppressed,
it's likely that other parts
of his brain are open to manipulation.
- What other parts?
- The visual cortex, for one.
Come on, I have an idea.
What was the name
of the gang you ran with?
Kingtown?
I think I remember
where I heard of them.
Yeah, that's good for you.
Guy by the name of Ernesto Ripelli
used to run with them.
They charged him
with the bombing
that killed my father.
That was before my time.
He got off
because they couldn't explain
how he got past the metal detectors.
That's what made the explosion
so shocking.
No one had any idea
how that bomb was planted.
It was you, wasn't it?
Kate, you got to understand.
It was my first big job.
I didn't think I had a choice.
You know how it works.
Once you're in...
You're in.
So that's it?
That's all you've got to say?
I can't change what I've done.
So my dad was just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Is that it?
Kate, what are you talking about?
Your dad was the target.
He was trying to cut a deal
with the DA.
That's why the gang
wanted him killed.
Shut up!
Shut up! You're lying!
I don't wanna be the bearer
of bad news here,
but your dad was turning on the guys
he was running with. He knew the risks.
Well, it doesn't change the fact
that he's dead.
No, it doesn't.
Get down.
Get down on your knees.
Anything else you want to say?
Just that I don't blame you.
And go, White Sox.
We have to go.
Not now.
Magnus needs our help.
Where's Jimmy?
I wanted to make certain
Will was still alive.
Now you are.
Where's Jimmy?
I don't take kindly to strangers
coming into my town
making bull-headed demands.
You'll get James
once you've released Will.
You've got me now.
You don't need both of us.
This is not a negotiation.
I was prepared to cut you some slack
because of your considerable reputation,
but now you're just trying
my patience.
So one last time.
Where's Jimmy?
Fair enough.
Easy.
Easy!
Magnus, don't do it!
Well, now, you've given me some grief
over the last few days, haven't you?
Are we square?
Get out of here.
- Boss, what are you...
- Let him go.
Come on.
Let me see the container.
- When did you turn into David Blaine?
- Just keep moving.
It's working, Sally.
Keep concentrating.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I said, let me see it.
There's no one there.
Who you talking to?
Let me see the container.
Now!
Stop them!
I suppose that was your idea
of a joke!
Stop!
You're looking for me?
Let them go.
I'll come quietly,
but you've got to release them first.
How do I know
you have the container?
Why don't you reach in
and see for yourself?
Well, it looks like
we have a deal after all.
- You don't have to do this.
- Yes, I do.
I'm sorry.
It's all I can say.
You go. Hurry.
All right, come on, come on,
get in the car.
Tell the others
we'll meet 'em in Chicago.
Glad you finally came
to your senses.
Me too.
Let's see the goods.
Sure.
What's this doing here?
I don't know.
Here you go.
I admit, it was a calculated risk.
That's what you call it?
Did you even know it was gonna work?
Not positively, no,
but I was sure that if Henry were able
to boost Sally's telepathic signal,
she could tap
into the Duke's visual cortex.
- And see something that wasn't there.
- Exactly.
That's why I'm glad we had a recent
photo of James for her to focus on.
Yeah, about James...
I'm sorry.
He did what he felt he had to do.
He'd been living with the guilt
for so many years,
I suspect it was a relief.
I'm off to see Sally.
What kind of gift
do you get for a mermaid?
She likes it if you swim with her.
- I'll get my suit.
- No suit.
May I come in?
How's the shoulder?
Looks like my tennis days are over.
I wanted you to know
that I had no idea
about your family's prior history
with James, otherwise I would...
Never would have put me
in that position.
I know. It's okay.
Actually, it's not.
I run a very thorough background check
on everyone I work with,
and somehow I missed this.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's not the kind of thing
you put at the top of your resume.
Well, I appreciate
your understanding.
I'm not sure I'd be as forgiving
if I were in your position.
It's funny.
I always wondered what I would do
if I ever figured out who killed my dad.
Turns out it's not as black and white
as I thought.
Life rarely is.
I could have been Jimmy.
I've done things I'm not proud of.
How are we so different?
I've been blaming
the way my life turned out
on that one moment
20 years ago.
But the truth is,
I made my life the way it is.
And your life is still unfolding.
I'll let you rest.