- Good morning, Officer.
- Sir, can you turn the music down?
Down means off.
You know why I pulled
you over this morning?
Well...
I'm pretty sure I wasn't speeding.
I've been using the cruise control,
so I...
No, sir. Your windshield.
License and registration, please.
Right.
This was from Wayfarer 515.
My house was in the debris field.
And that's
what shattered my windshield...
some piece of wreckage
from the plane.
I understand.
You know of Flight 515, the plane crash?
You're wearing the ribbon.
Yes, sir.
I'm quite aware of Wayfarer 515.
I was one of the first responders
on the scene that day.
Then what are you doing?
Citing you, sir.
You don't believe me?
Regardless of how
that windshield was damaged,
this car is unsafe to drive
in this condition.
Stay in the car, please.
Wait just a minute.
Just one minute.
I asked you to stay in the vehicle.
- I can get out of my own car.
- Sir, listen...
No. You listen to me.
It's time for you to listen to me.
Calm down and get back in that car.
This is America. I have rights.
Do you understand that?
At least have the common decency
to hear me out.
- Step back right now.
- Did you even hear what I said?
Now you're giving me a ticket?
I told you
that my house
was in the debris field.
Do you have the remotest
inkling of what that means?
- Sir, calm down.
- Hellfire rained down on my house
where my children sleep!
There were body parts in my yard!
- Sir, this is your last warning.
- You gotta be kidding me!
I'm gonna pepper spray you.
You're gonna pepper spray?
Perfect!
That is just perfect!
Pepper spray the man
who's expressing his opinion
under the First Amendment!
Subtitles:
Breys
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
Lastly, a little something
from down El Paso way.
Border Patrol came across
multiple homicides
just this side of the border.
Truck turn out to be a chicken run
out of Juarez and Laredo.
Border Patrol's been playing
hide-and-seek with these polleros
for two years.
But this time,
as soon as they made it across,
someone hit them.
Hit them hard.
We're talking a driver
and nine illegals.
No sign of the shooters.
This truck was carrying
more than just people.
What are we looking at?
Weed, coke, or meth?
Doesn't look like
they were transporting narcotics.
Why did the Border Patrol
kick this to us?
They didn't. I pulled it.
You ask me,
this high-end cartel work.
Los Zetas, maybe.
Question is,
why do we have Juarez-style action
on our side of the DMZ?
They sending a message
or clearing a path?
Or was this about
stopping one particular border-hopper?
Maybe one of those extra-crispies
knew something he shouldn't.
Anyway, keep your eyes open.
All right. That's it.
Slow news day.
Add one more to the countdown.
What's that, Gomie?
We're waiting
on that famous blue meth of yours.
29 days since we saw it last.
It's still out there. Don't worry.
Local PD. I gotta take this.
Gomie, go beat your pinata.
Rest of you jokers...
too damn quiet in here.
Go catch some bad guys.
What's up, Paul?
Hey, Dad.
- So you're fixing up the house?
- Doing a little work, yeah.
I'll bounce. It's cool.
You doing okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
I just happened to be driving by
and saw the sign.
So, you're selling the place.
In this market.
Can you believe it?
I see you moved the garage.
That's bold.
Your mother's idea.
It's quite an operation.
We did, all new stucco,
all the master suite,
sandblasted,
fumigated the basement...
Right on.
Fixing up the place
totally increases resale value.
I read that in...
I want to say, like,
Time magazine.
So, what'd you do
with the upstairs bathroom?
All redone. New tiles
in the bathrooms and kitchens,
granite countertops, new appliances...
all top of the line.
Damn.
That's great, Dad.
Think... I can get a tour?
These guys are trying to finish up.
Maybe we'd better
stay out of their way.
There are pictures on the Web site,
if you wanna take a look.
You're looking healthy.
I'll tell your mother.
She'll be happy.
Thanks.
You know, I could come by
sometime for... dinner or something.
Sometime.
Later, Dad.
You know, look,
he's a high school
teacher over at Wynne.
Never been in trouble
a day of his life.
Found out he's got lung cancer,
and now his wife kicks
the poor bastard
out of his own house.
I mean, look, guys,
if anybody rates a little slack,
here's the guy.
You remember Officer Cavanaugh?
Officer, I'm very sorry
that I lost my temper.
There's no excuse for my behavior.
It was disrespectful.
She's divorcing me.
I don't know
what to tell you, buddy.
It is what it is.
She doesn't want me to see the kids.
She said that?
You don't write? You don't call?
It's a disaster.
It is not a disaster.
It's not a disaster, all right?
She's not going to the cops.
She's not gonna tell a living soul.
You wanna know why?
One word:
"blowback".
If she blabs,
it'll be a disaster...
for her.
That DEA brother-in-law?
Screwed.
You were right under his nose.
He'll be lucky if they let
him bust glue-sniffers
at the hobby shop.
The kids...
Paging Dr. Phil.
My daddy's a drug dealer,
and my mommy turned him in.
And the house... gone.
The feds will come and RICO her
and the kids out on the street.
Good luck arguing with them on that.
No. It's not gonna happen.
She's bluffing,
and she knows it.
Her going to the police
is not the point, Saul.
She's out of my life.
Do you understand?
I've lost my family,
everything that I care about.
Buddy,
it's bad.
It's a calamity,
but we live to fight another day.
And after a decent interval of time,
well,
there are other fish in the sea.
You've been out of circulation
for a while.
I mean, you'll be just amazed
at what's out there.
Thailand, the Czech Republic...
Those women are so grateful
to even be here.
In the meantime,
idle hands
are the devil's playthings,
so you should get back on the horse
and do what you do best.
First step:
talk to our friend and get cooking.
I can't be the bad guy.
You know, we'll...
We'll revisit.
Promise me you won't hang yourself
in the closet.
Pop-pop, the ice-cream man!
Don't tell your mom.
- Yeah.
- It's me.
We may have a wife problem.
Look, I need eyes on it.
You got an address?
Dinner's gonna be late.
Uncle Hank and Aunt Marie
are bringing takeout. But...
if you're hungry,
I could rustle something up.
Pass the ketchup, will you?
I've had enough trans fat
for one lifetime.
A two-day drive from the nearest ocean,
and you're eating raw fish.
That's all I'm saying.
Been a while since that minnow
been swimming. Right, buddy?
You know... Flynn, here,
is looking for a part-time job, so...
I don't know. If you...
- know of anything, you might wanna...
- My name's Walter Junior.
Like... What, you...
You can't even say his name?
If you've changed your mind
about being called Flynn,
all you need to do is just tell me
that you don't want
to be called Flynn.
Dad didn't even show
up till fourth period,
and his eyes were all red
like he'd been crying or something.
But you...
you don't even care.
And now,
he won't even drive me home.
He won't say why,
but I know
it's because you told him not to.
- Honey, I...
- What?
I don't know what your problem is.
You may not love him anymore,
but I do.
I mean, why you gotta be...
Why you gotta be such a... a bitch?
You don't talk to your mom that way.
It's... It's all right.
Skyler, I know
that you must have your reasons
for... all of this.
I know it's none of my business,
but...
keeping Walt from the kids...
You're right, Hank.
It's none of your business.
Oh, my God.
After all of that, please tell me
that you are still not curious.
- There's nothing to be curious about.
- Please.
The day I heard
there was a second cell phone, I knew.
Believe me.
I've seen it a hundred times.
So, what?
Stop dancing around it.
What is it exactly
that you have seen a hundred times?
Please, enlighten me.
Look, a guy like Walt...
a nice guy, decent, smart?
Let's face it... underachiever,
dead-end life, okay?
He gets cancer. Time's running out.
Midlife crisis.
He acts up. Steps out.
Then the wife... she catches him.
I mean, it's a story as old as time.
Look, do the math, Marie.
Only comes out one way.
Knowing Walt, he...
felt so guilty,
he probably told her himself.
I don't know. I think...
if he cheated on her,
that she would've told me by now.
It just feels like...
something more.
24-7 coverage. Need you ask?
How much is this gonna run me?
Jesus. I'm in the wrong business.
Yeah. I'll call you.
Return of the prodigal.
- Welcome back. How you feeling?
- I'm good.
Of course you are.
The world's your oyster. Am I right?
Unencumbered young man with...
stacks of cash.
I'm jealous.
Hand to God, I'm jealous.
Yeah, speaking of cash,
you know what's giving me
heartburn lately?
Your former partner. This guy...
He works like a bastard, right?
Builds a business, single-handed.
Finally, the big money shows up,
and what does he do? He walks out.
Talent like that,
and he just flushes
it down the crapper.
It's like Michelangelo won't paint.
Look, I know you're out of it
and all, but you...
you wouldn't talk to him, would you?
Help him pull his head
out of his ass?
Scratch that.
He won't listen to me,
he's not gonna listen to you,
all due respect.
You want a job?
A job?
Who's got a job for me?
I do.
Thought I'd...
- well, visit, if you don't mind.
- No, of course not. You don't...
- You don't need the room, do you?
- No.
I just needed some more space
to spread out.
Just wanted to say hello
to little Holly here. Hey, girl.
She is a beauty. Look at her.
Thanks for being so flexible
on me coming in.
I just wish we had you back
full time.
You do brighten up the place.
Listen, believe me, this is...
I don't wanna bring this up,
but I... I can't sign off
sign off on these quarterlies.
I'm sorry.
I just can't.
Is that right?
If you're gonna do this,
you can't be so glaring about it.
Glaring.
That does sound bad.
Show me what's bothering you.
Keller.
Again...
God, I'm sorry.
I know how you feel about this.
Revenue with no backup.
Here, here, and here.
I don't even know what to say.
This is fixable, right?
How about if I just push... 28,800,
out of this into next quarter?
Would you sign it then?
I'm just saying
I can't sign it
as it currently exists.
Fair enough.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you for the heads-up.
You won't have to deal
with this again, I swear.
What if your kids found out?
If my kids found out?
This... what you're doing.
Someday,
they're gonna be old enough.
How would you explain it to them?
Put me on the spot, why don't you?
I guess maybe I'd...
I'd say that...
I might have feet of clay that...
But that whatever I did,
I did thinking of them.
You know? Trying to provide.
And I'd ask them
to try to take the time
to understand...
You know what? Truth is,
I haven't thought that far ahead.
I'm just trying to keep
my head above water, so...
I better get back to it.
Hi, Walt.
Listen. I can't talk.
I'm at work right now.
Louis dropped him off.
He was here when I got home.
No. Of course.
No. He's not staying.
He understands that.
I'll bring him anywhere you want.
Dad...
It is rush hour. I could fight traffic
and bring him down to Beneke now,
but wouldn't it be easier if we...
Right. Okay. Good.
So we'll meet you at the house.
Why are you doing this?
She's just trying
to keep me from seeing you,
and you're helping her.
No. No, son. I mean, your...
your mother... she has her reasons.
What reasons?
They're...
Well, they're just a little
difficult to delineate, but...
I mean, yes,
there are two sides to every story.
Always. But...
she...
This is just how it has to be.
For now.
And, look, your home is your home,
and that is where you belong, okay?
But it's where you belong.
Dad, it's your house.
Uncle Hank, Aunt Marie...
everybody knows
that you haven't done anything wrong.
Everybody is on your side.
It's not about taking sides, though.
How can you let
her treat you like this?
Now, come on.
- How can you just... just take it?
- Just listen to me, okay?
No matter what,
all of this has nothing to do
with how we feel about you, okay?
We both love you very,
very much, okay?
You and your sister
will come first, always.
Now, come on.
Let's try to see this
in a positive light, okay?
Both of us.
Let's just buck up.
Then I'll take you home.
Let me first just
hit the old bathroom here.
Good afternoon. Nice to meet you.
Saul Goodman. Nice to meet you.
You're not that lawyer
on late-night television, are you?
Better call Saul!
I get it all the time.
We're here to discuss the sale
of the property at 9809 Margo.
I get it. Flat-fee clients.
Am I right?
Well, folks, today's your lucky day.
I represent a client
who shall remain nameless.
However, for our purposes,
you might just as well
visualize a large bag of money.
This individual wants to buy
your house today, for cash.
- Cash?
- Cash. I know. In this economy.
In fact, the money is already burning
a hole in my client's account.
You can ask Mr. Gardiner. I've shown him
all the pertinent financials.
It's the only reason
we're sitting here.
Fair enough.
We... get a few papers signed
and notarized,
we can take care of this right now.
In fact, I can wire you your money
this very afternoon.
There's just one
little hair in the soup...
the price.
We feel 875 is very fair.
But I suppose there's always a little...
wiggle room.
You wiggle us on down to 400
and you got yourselves a deal.
400,000? What is that, a joke?
No, that's my offer.
That's less than half price.
We put almost that much
into the renovations alone.
Why don't we just cut the clown act
and you tell us
what you're willing to come up to?
400,000. That's my final offer.
This is a waste of time.
How could you possibly imagine
that we would entertain this?
I thought some allowance was in order
once I heard about the meth lab...
that used to be in the basement.
I looked over your signed
disclosure statements,
and I don't see any mention
of a meth lab.
You got your termite inspection.
That's good. But no
... meth lab.
Now, some would call that fraud
in service of concealing a felony.
I, myself, am more open-minded.
But it is tricky.
Don't get me wrong.
I applaud your cojones.
I mean,
good try in sneaking a meth-contaminated
property past the buyer.
Could've been a good deal for you.
Too bad.
Now, I could...
file a suit and encumber
this property indefinitely,
or I could start
some criminal proceedings.
But I don't think
any of us want that now, do we?
How about it, counselor?
Do you concur?
Here you go.
Come on. It's not Devil's Island.
- Brought pizza.
- Well, I'm making dinner.
I'll just... put it in the fridge.
It's even better the next day.
Hi, honey.
Sorry.
Honey, what...
What kind of example
do we want to set here?
Right? I mean,
can't we at least just sit down
and eat a piece of pizza together?
Just to hash things out like adults?
We have...
discussed everything
we need to discuss.
I thought I made myself very clear.
I got dipping sticks.
You've reached Walt's temporary number.
Please leave a message.
When I went out this morning
to get the newspaper,
I saw a pizza on our roof.
Would you know anything about that?
Listen to me, Walt.
You need to control yourself.
Calm down, accept the situation,
and keep your distance.
If you can't manage that,
I will get a restraining order.
I got your restraining order
right here!
Restrain this!
Breaking even's not so bad.
In this economy, a lot of people
would kill to break even.
Poor Jake. He had his heart set
on going to space camp.
Oh, God, this is all we need.
Hey, Mom, Dad.
How's it going?
It's really not a good time.
Jesse, the house has been sold.
The new owners
are expected at any moment.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Inside.
I bought the place.
Be back by 7, okay?
I love you.
Bye.
It's me. There's something
you should know about.
Hold on.