Previously on Stargate Atlantis.
I'd like to report for duty, ma'am.
Lieutenant!
What do you think you're doing here?
- Just give me something to do.
- I don't think so.
Don't push me around!
Where's the rest of the enzyme?
Lt Ford might have been your friend,
but he's not anymore.
We are only here searching for a friend.
You guys all think I'm crazy or something.
No, no-one thinks that.
We think we can help him,
if we can find him.
This drug is messing with your head!
I'm not just fine.
I'm better than fine.
Lieutenant!
Don't!
Ford!
This is ridiculous.
Well, keep complaining about it
and we may get there faster.
Well, couldn't we have met these people on a tropical
beach planet, populated by tall, blonde women?
Whoever wants to speak with us,
obviously values their privacy.
Yes, well I value my time and this is a waste of it.
What's a waste of time, is listening to you, Rodney.
This is a mission.
Yeah well, it strikes me that this is a mission better
suited to one of the... lower echelon teams.
Lower echelon?
He means to say, less important.
Got a tip from one of Teyla's contacts.
We're following it up.
And this is like what? The umpteenth tip
we've followed up in search of a ZedPM?
- Rodney?
Look, I just want to make it clear
that every second I am out of my lab
is a second the galaxy goes
without another ground-breaking...
We have to get them through the Gate
before their people realise they are missing.
You guys OK?
Oh yeah, fine.
Seems like a whole lot of trouble to go through,
just to get us to dinner.
Not a talkative bunch, are you.
We'll release you from your bindings
if you promise not to attack us.
Sure.
Yeah. We promise.
Before we untie them,
they had to know that they are among friends.
Ford?
Thought I was dead, didn't you Sheppard?
Season 2 - Episode 10
The lost boys (part 1)
Transcript: Scifigate.net
Sous-titres: Team SG-66 - www.seriestele.net
Guys.
Guys please.
Eat!
Eat.
Well men,
this used to be my team.
Not this one.
But I think he's OK, too.
What is all this?
Some local vegetables.
A sorta alligator thingy.
Tastes like salted meat. It's good. Try.
I'm not talking about the food.
What the hell is going on?
Who are these men?
Why bring us here like this?
That's a lot of questions.
Pick one.
That's good.
Where did you find him, Sheppard?
Maybe you should start with how you managed
to escape being caught by the Wraith Dart?
What? I get nervous, I get hungry.
OK, the Dart.
Ford!
You're not getting off this planet!
I have no idea how long I was in the Dart.
Next thing I knew, I was on a Cruiser
and I was awake.
It's the enzyme.
Makes you almost immune to a Wraith stunner, so
when you're dematerialized from the Wraith Dart,
you were awake as opposed to...
As opposed to dead!
I cut open it's enzyme pouch.
Took my fill.
Made my way off the ship.
You can get around pretty easy on a Wraith ship.
They're not used to people making it aboard,
so there's next to no security.
I walked off with enough enzyme
to last me a little while.
Tracked down the stargate.
Dialled the first friendly address I could remember.
I need a place to stay and a hot meal.
And what do you got to trade?
What'll that get me?
No weapons.
So?
What'll that get me?
I still don't really understand.
Look at me. I got shot.
I healed.
I can see farther. Clearer than I ever saw before.
I told them about the enzyme.
How it makes you stronger and more aware.
More resilient.
How to give us a fighting chance against the Wraith.
I mean, look at me.
Look at me!
I walked off a Wraith Cruiser!
It works.
I wanna try it.
Wait a second.
All your people here.
All your men.
They're on the enzyme?
Of course.
No!
We don't do it like that anymore.
Let's get him back home.
As our numbers kept growing,
we needed more and more of the enzyme.
Nice work.
Thank you.
This should give us a steady stream of the enzyme.
Time to focus on some bigger issues.
Aiden.
Do you mean to tell us that there are
live Wraith here in this cave?
That's right.
The Wraith can communicate
with each other over a distance.
But not between stars.
They'd have to be in this solar system.
You taught me that.
Yes well, good for me.
It doesn't matter.
They can't communicate if they're unconscious.
Why'd you jump us?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
It was the only way to get you here.
Why didn't you just tell us where you were?
You know we would have come.
Yeah, you and a special ops team.
No, no!
I know you think I'm crazy.
I brought you all here to show you that you're wrong.
I mean, do I look crazy?
Do I seem out of control?
Are we speaking in relative terms, or...
Look. Jace here has really fine tuned the enzyme.
We know how to administer it now and to regulate it.
Refine with it.
We've gotten so good we can even lace food with it.
Excuse me?
Congratulations.
You've just had your first dose.
What?
I thought long and hard about how
to show you that the enzyme was safe.
To convince you that it was the first step
to defeating the Wraith.
So you could convince Weir.
- Convince the military.
- Are you out of your mind?
- Hey! Settle down, McKay!
- No I will not settle down!
I have been drugged against my will,
you little punk!
You should not have done this Aiden!
Be as mad as you want.
Couple of days, you'll be thanking me.
We'll all have a good laugh about this.
Now eat up.
I'm itchy. I'm itchy all over.
This is exactly what happened
when I toked pot once in college.
Everyone stay put.
Let him go.
Ford!
Look.
I know what you're trying to do. I get it, I do.
But you're going about his all wrong.
Weir isn't going to listen to us
if we're all hopped up on the enzyme.
Your food was clean.
Why?
Why me?
You're gonna be the witness.
You're gonna be the one to tell Weir,
that her most trusted team has taken
the enzyme and is better because of it.
Look buddy.
Why don't you come back with us.
Have Beckett look you over?
- That's the best proof.
- No.
No, I've thought this through.
This is the plan.
- Look, I don't know what you're thinking...
- You're free to roam around as much as you want.
You're all a part of the team, now.
OK.
So why aren't these guys watching us?
Ronon is right.
They went to great trouble to get us here.
Why would they allow us to leave?
Just waiting for the other shoe to drop.
Oh, that little bastard!
- There it goes.
- See, this is what I was afraid of.
What'd he do?
He's taken all the necessary control crystals.
Something I showed him how to do on a mission,
I might add!
Well, that's not good.
That is the understatement of the year.
Alright! See what you can do!
OK, why don't we just take them?
All we gotta do is get our hands on one stunner.
I can take them all.
Yeah, maybe, but if we mess it up, whatever trust
we might have been given, will disappear.
You wanna make them trust us?
We play it cool, we let 'em get comfortable.
They're bound to make a mistake.
And in the meantime?
We play along.
How are you guys feeling?
I didn't eat that much.
I feel fine.
Perhaps if we were able to fast, they would be
unable to administer the enzyme.
I doubt that.
I don't think they'd have a problem forcing us.
This thing is useless and I ate my face off.
And I can tell you, I can feel it working!
There's a good possibility that everything
you're feeling right now might be
- psychosomatic.
- Oh, is that right, Professor Science?
Is that your expert opinion?
Yes it is.
Well I can tell you, when they up the dosage,
the side effects will be very real
and very unpredictable.
You're back early.
Janev's kind of a closed society.
Very polite, very courteous, but completely
uninterested in having anything to do with us.
Well better that than hostile, I suppose.
Colonel Sheppard's team.
Three hours overdue.
It wouldn't be the first time.
Any radio contact?
None since they left.
Well, you know those guys.
What do I know about those guys?
Just that they tend to get all caught up
in whatever it is they're doing
and sometimes they don't check in.
They forget how much you worry.
We worry.
- Collectively, I mean.
- Yes we do.
Yeah, we do.
OK guys, looks like we're heading back out.
Thank you Major.
You're welcome.
Seriously! I'm getting... I'm getting... chills,
hot flashes, chills and hot flashes again and again.
None of you are feeling that?
The enzyme side effects are gonna be
the least of his concerns if he keeps this up.
I know. Just be patient.
Historically,
that hasn't been a strength for me.
I know!
Sheppard, Teyla!
Kanayo's running a mission offworld.
I want you to go with him.
Why?
We're running an op.
Time you might wanna see the men in action.
Sure!
Wherever you need us.
Just give us some weapons and...
Nice try.
No, you're gonna hang back and watch with Kanayo.
Don't worry, you won't be in any danger.
That's a load off my mind.
Good.
What about us?
Jace'll give you the grand tour.
Show you what we've done with the place.
How's that sound?
Oh, it sounds delightful.
Good, good. Then if Sheppard tries anything offworld,
you'll be nice and close for me to kill you both.
Can't think of a better way of spending the afternoon.
Move!
Looks like he's asking you to go.
Are those guards Genii?
Yes.
What exactly are we doing here?
The Genii have spies all over the galaxy.
For whatever reason, if one of them can't
make it back to the Genii homeworld,
their leaders have established safehouses.
When they need a place to unload on
gear or a place to hide, they come here.
That's useful.
Yeah, we've found it to be an excellent
source of information and supplies.
How did you find them in the first place?
I was a Genii spy.
If you're one of them,
why don't you just walk in there.
Well I used to, but eventually
they realised that I'd betrayed them.
I can see how they would.
We rely on raids now.
Why? What more do you guys want?
We don't have all the pieces we need for the Lt's plan.
Right. And which plan would that be, again?
All will be revealed when the time is right.
Well, good. I hate for things to be revealed too early.
How are you powering these Genii computers?
We stole a Talnoran generator.
They're a pain to keep serviced, but they do the job.
Actually, we just got
our hands on some Palation solar cells,
but I haven't been able to figure out how to
interface them yet. Have you used them before?
Can't say that I have.
What do you, what do you do here?
We study the Wraith.
Oh yeah? How's that going?
Some of our discoveries,
have been quite exciting, actually.
Like what?
Well for one, they seem to be territorial.
Very much so, it turns out.
They're not a united foe, like we once believed.
Really.
Yes, in fact I believe
they're fractioning even further.
Now, my understanding of
their language is fairly limited,
but they seem to be trying to establish a system
that would restrict intership communications.
What? Why would they stop
sharing information with each other.
Ford thinks it might have to do
with your friend's ability to read their minds.
If she taps into them, only one ship
would be compromised, not the whole fleet.
What, all this because of Teyla?
Well for one, she may not be
the only one that possesses that ability.
Fair enough.
And two. I think that the lack
of food in the galaxy has created
some deep divisions within the Wraith cells.
And you got all that from...
this?
Yes.
To be honest, I could use some help.
How's your Wraith, Doctor?
It's OK. Let me see what you got.
That's better.
You guys still need to work together.
We're stronger as a team.
You wanna spar a little?
We're cool, right?
You're not holding a grudge or anything.
I did save your life.
I remember.
You know, it's funny.
If you ask a dozen people who they thought
would win in a fight between you and me,
people would choose you, hands down.
Hell, I'd choose you.
But we went toe to toe.
Yeah, we did.
Till Sheppard showed up.
So I guess it's still undecided.
Look, all I'm saying is,
why do you think I was able to fight you like that?
It's the enzyme.
Look what it did for me.
Imagine what it could do for you.
I'm not the bad guy here, Ronon.
I'm just trying to help.
You'll come around.
I know you will.
We've just finished our scans, Ma'am.
They're not here.
Do you think they've headed to another planet?
It's possible, but as you know,
it's standard procedure to check in and tell us first.
They didn't do that, so...
They might have been taken offworld against their will.
Yeah.
Alright. Can you get me
the last few addresses dialled from that DHD?
Maybe somebody can,
but that's a little out of my skill set.
I'll send Zelenka.
Good call. Lorne out.
So, what's the plan?
We take them by force.
That's some ground-breaking strategy there.
I think the Colonel is interested
in the type of attack.
We plan to overpower them.
I think it's best if we just watch.
Now.
What kind of plan is that?
One that works.
One of your men got hit.
Well it should be safe for us now.
This guy's dead.
So you see, you are not invincible.
We're close enough.
There are skills to the art of war, Kanayo.
Don't you tell me how to run my missions.
You're just here to watch.
Look familiar?
It's our C4.
We're stealing it back.
For what purpose?
For the Hive.
As in hive ship?
Yeah. That's the Lt's plan.
You're gonna help us destroy a Wraith hive ship.
One of the added bonuses
of killing the Wraith is,
every now and again you get
your hands on a couple of these.
Now thanks to Jace and some of the
computers that we borrowed from the Genii,
we've been able to figure out the
exact flight path of one of their hive ships.
It's decimating all inhabited worlds in it's path.
It has to be stopped.
I've been able to calculate that in the next several
days it'll be forced to make a hyperspace pause,
very near an unihabited planet.
that happens to have a stargate.
We gate to that planet, get on a hive ship,
plant the C4 in the Dart Bay and get out.
We could save thousands, if not,
hundreds of thousands of lives.
So?
You heard me.
Let me see if I can couch what Colonel Sheppard
means by wow, in more explicit terms.
That is a terrible plan.
Rodney.
Made all the more frightening by the
fact that you think it's a good plan.
What's wrong with it?
What's right with it?
Look, let's just for a second,
give in to reckless abandon and assume
it would be possible to plant a single charge,
large enough to destroy an entire hive ship.
We're planning on secondary explosions in the Dart Bay.
Regardless!
The hive ship will be on a hyperspace pause, yes,
but it will not enter the planet's atmosphere.
Nor will it take up any sort of stable orbit.
It will be flying through space.
Which means, that unless your enzyme allows you
to jump higher than you've let on...
We've a space ship.
Oh yeah? Really.
And what's it made out of? Bark?
No, it's real, McKay.
In fact, it's the only ship I'd feel
comfortable using on a mission like this.
OK, where'd you get it?
Does it matter?
None of us has had much success flying it.
Banged it up pretty bad in the last couple of landings.
It's in need of some repairs.
And a real pilot.
This is why you brought us here.
It's the reason I've waited till now, yes.
- Assuming this guy can get it working again.
- He can.
These people are the best at what they do.
Look, you fly, you scoop us up, you
take us to the Hive, you drop us off.
All we need, is time to lay the charge.
We'll be in and out of there before the
Wraith have any idea what's going on.
It's perfect.
It is far from perfect!
But, it is possible.
Colonel.
What? Are you honestly considering this?
It's on it's way to a culling, Rodney.
Yeah and I am sorry about that,
but this is insane!
Maybe not!
Jace has been trying to get it working,
but he's not you, McKay.
Can you fix it?
Probably not.
That usually means yes.
Aren't you the one, not taking the enzyme?
You're supposed to be the clear
voice of reason here.
Look, can you fix it?
Even if I could, I wouldn't. I'm sorry,
drug me all you want, I'm not doing this!
Let me talk to him. He'll come around
OK.
Rodney!
Look, maybe you are on the enzyme,
maybe Ford lied, because no rational
person would think that was a good plan.
Look, a million things could go wrong,
I know that, but just...
Look stop! Shut up and listen.
You fix that Dart, we all get outta here. I know
it's risky, but Ford's not thinking straight, so...
What are you talking about?
I'll insist you're all on the away team.
I'll scoop you up and instead of flying out
to the hive ship, we fly out to Atlantis.
How?
That Dart's gotta have it's own DHD, right?
Of course.
Well, you get that thing flight worthy, we all go home!
Right, of course!
You see, I would have thought of that myself,
before I became a drug addict.
I'm sure you would have.
I'm sorry.
Alright. OK.
Damn it, this just doesn't work.
That good?
These things are not designed to store Gate addresses.
What can you give us?
Well, every time the gate is dialled,
it's like a residual imprint
is left on the control crystals.
Which means?
Well, I've managed to mine
about fifty addresses, but
no idea if they're correct or
what order they were dialled in.
Fifty? That's a lot of planets to check.
Yes, And that's assuming that they're correct.
OK, so long story short?
It's going to be next to impossible
to find Colonel Sheppard and his team,
based on what I can get from this DHD.
Great. OK, pack it up. Let's take what you've got.
We'll go over it on Atlantis.
Weir's not gonna be happy about this.
How'd that go?
Well, he'll do it, but we need some conditions.
What?
Dial back McKay's enzyme doses.
No!
Look! We're under some time constraints here.
I'm not saying the enzyme wouldn't help.
I'm saying, we need him standing still and
thinking, not running laps because it feels good.
Ronon and Teyla?
Stick to the plan.
Fine, what else?
I'll fly it, that's obvious, but I want
McKay, Teyla and Ronon on the strike team.
It's not a good mission for McKay.
- It could get rough in there.
- Look,
suddenly we need a door opened, or a
computer hacked. McKay should be there to do it.
That's why he's on my team in the first place.
Is that it?
No.
No. You fire it up now, it'll only explode.
OK.
We're close.
It's a good plan.
I couldn't have done it without you, Sir.
Well, I'm glad you trust me enough to bring me here.
What's wrong?
I wanna go home.
Let's go.
Give McKay the DHD
crystals and let's get outta here.
I can have you back on Earth within an hour.
No.
We have to do this first.
I have to prove to them that we can do this.
You don't have to prove anything to anyone, Lieutenant.
I saw your cousin and your Grandparents,
when I was back to Earth.
They miss you.
A lot!
This whole MIA thing is killing them.
They're strong.
They can wait.
If anyone's ever going
to take me seriously ever again,
we have to do this.
Listen, Aiden...
No.
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna talk about this.
Well, part of me thinks he brought us
here cos he knew we'd bring him back.
I think subconsciously, he knows what
are plan is and he's fine with it.
Give it back!
Or what?
Come on guys. Guys! Stop!
What the hell's gotten into you two?
Oh, right. Never mind.
We need to talk about this?
About what?
The enzyme works.
No-one's saying it,
but we're all thinking it.
It works.
I must admit, I have noticed
an increased amount of strength.
Maybe Ford is right.
Maybe it's worth looking into seeing
what this stuff can do.
They were an hour late in delivering
our doses yesterday and I felt awful.
It frightens me how reliant my body has become
on the enzyme always being in my system.
What would happen if we
suddenly could not receive it?
The only negative is that
you gotta keep taking it.
I'd wanna stay on it.
How about you?
The fact that I'm even
considering it, makes me feel...
So?
It's ready.
OK, now... Could you move?
Look, this is probably gonna
make you a little uneasy, but
when the canopy forms, it's perfectly opaque.
Then, how am I gonna fly this thing?
The whole thing is one giant heads up display. It'll
show you all the pertinent information that you need.
Yeah, you mean in Wraith!
Which is why I've installed an interface
to translate a lot of the readouts.
And by a lot, you mean all? Because
my Wraith's not all that good.
Enough to get you by.
I knew you could do it.
Right on time.
Kanayo's gonna get you suited up.
You should get ready.
Right.
Seems a little nervous.
You know McKay. He'll be fine.
You know how to dial the DHD on this thing?
The address is memorised.
Good.
Listen, I should probably tell you,
there's been a slight change of plans.
Oh yeah?
Kanayo!
Don't even think about it!
What the hell you doing?
McKay's going to stay here,
while we do the op.
Take him!
This wasn't part of the plan.
Neither was you heading back to Atlantis.
You didn't really buy the whole
'I wanna go home' speech, did you?
Always underestimating me Sheppard.
You need to stop doing that.
Complete the mission and McKay lives.
We can't complete the mission, Ford.
It's a bad plan!
You said it was a great plan.
You didn't buy the whole
'It's a great plan' speech, did you?
Get this Dart in the air and come scoop us up.
And the Dart DHD only dials to the
planet we're going to and back here.
Just in case McKay's life isn't enough
to get you to do the right thing.
Aiden.
What are you doing?
Just making sure you guys
hold up your end of the bargain.
It's OK, give them back their weapons.
Are you sure?
Yeah. If we're gonna do this,
we all gotta work together.
Good luck to us all.
Stand by for pick-up
If they were OK, they would have radioed in by now.
I understand that, ma'am.
I want everyone who is cleared for offworld
activity, to help with the search.
The Daedalus is on its way from Earth and they'll be
able to help, but until they get here, it's up to us.
And I know that, but I need you to understand
that it is gonna take a very long time to
search all the planets on our list.
It could take months.
We can't afford months. Major.
And I know that, too.
Good.
This is gonna take some getting used to.
Come on! And we were getting along so well.
Auto Pilot. NO!
R2, I need you to turn
the auto pilot off!
Now!
Worth a try.
Jace!
We have to go after them!
No-one would have survived that fall.
We have to get out of the open.
You guys OK?
No, we're not OK!
You beamed half
of us off the edge of the platform.
Teyla and Ronon?
Is that all you care about?
You murdered my men!
I've lost all control of the Dart.
I had to release you blind.
Maintain radio silence until we lay the charge.
Negative! We need to stay in contact.
Their ship...
You should leave that radio on, Aiden.
Don't tell me what to do.
Ford.
Ford?
Ford!
Damnit!
I'd prefer not to.
Oh boy!
Would you mind checking tomorrow?
This is not good.
What is that?
It's an alarm.
That shouldn't happen.
No it shouldn't.
Sheppard, you there?
I think I might have set the alarm off.
You guys be careful,
cos there's probably some guards on the way.
Too late.
If you wanna live, stay behind me.
You want some?
No, I'm good, thanks.
- You sure?
- Yeah, pretty sure.
Look, don't you
think that they should be back by now?
I mean, how long does it take to
fly there and fly back, you know? I mean
I say it's a minute from here to the gate.
Ten, tops from their gate to the hive ship.
Twenty to get in and lay a charge and and what,
ten more to get back out and home, right? So...
Worrying really isn't going to do anything.
Yeah well, I subscribe to a
different school of thought.
- They're fine!
- You can't possibly know that!
- I got a gut feeling.
- Yeah, well I have a different gut...
feeling.
Ford!
What's your position?
Ah, dammit!
Keep fighting!
And thanks to several modifications,
the specifics of which are encrypted in this databurst,
we believe we can streamline
our power consumption a further 30%.
Also at the time of this transmission,
Colonel Sheppard's team is still missing and is
is presumed...
Colonel Sheppard's team is still missing.
End transmission.
Are you alright?
I'm in a holding cell?
Yes.
On a hive ship.
Well then, no, I'm not doing so good!
I can't believe you screwed up!
I did what?
You set off the alarm.
You ruined the mission.
The Dart went on auto-pilot,
the second I got close to the hive.
You're lucky I was able to get you out!
Why would it do that?
Why would it go on auto-pilot?
That's what Jumpers do
when they gate to Atlantis.
Well, why didn't you say something?
Why didn't I say something?
You want me to fail.
- You want me to look bad.
- That's right, you snot nosed brat!
I put my team's life on the line,
just to prove you wrong!
We got company.
Move away.
What do you want?
The one who flew the ship.
Why don't you start with me?
Wait!
You want me.
It's alright.
There's always a way out.
If he dies,
you die.