-Previously on The O. C. :
-Rebecca is gone.
-What did you say to her?
-I asked her if she was in love with you.
And she said she was.
-I tried to tell Summer, and I couldn't.
-So you' re here to break up with me?
-Then I told her.
-I believe in taking every precaution.
-Caleb's gonna ask for a DNA test.
-You can't let him adopt you.
-What are you talking about?
-He might not be your dad.
When we were about to...
-...there was this voice in my head.
-Seth?
Have a great time in ltaly.
I'm cool with it.
I'm over you.
Well, I cannot believe I'm saying this,
but it's raining in the O. C.
I know, it's crazy.
I gotta tell you...
... traffic is a nightmare.
The 405 is jammed.
The 5, the 7 10, they 're all gridlocked.
Stay safe, stay dry,
and let 's all pray for sunshine again.
Hey, I kind of need to talk to you...
-...so you coming over for breakfast?
-Need to clean. Swing by the pool house.
Look out the window.
It's the sequence...
-...from Day After Tomorrow.
-It's just rain.
-I'll be here if you need to talk.
-Dude, come on.
I'm a child of Southern California.
I can't go out in this. I'll melt.
-You wanna do it over the phone?
-Works for me.
So does this weather.
It's very reflective
of my current emotional state.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
So I'm gonna lose her, man.
Summer's leaving for ltaly tomorrow.
It'll be nothing...
...but cannolis and canoodling
with Zach.
Haven't talked to Lindsay
since she ran out of Caleb's.
-You should talk to her.
-She won't talk to anyone.
I don't know. Maybe it'll
all work out for the best.
Yeah, maybe.
You don't think that's God trying
to tell us anything, do you?
Not gonna take that chance.
I've gotta talk to Lindsay.
You think we should stick together?
Kind of two by two, like Noah did.
He's very wise, Ryan. He had a beard.
It's just rain. It can't hurt us.
Not worse than our women can.
It's 1 0:00.
Are you gonna stay in bed all day?
Maybe.
I like it here.
Oh, I feel like-- Like we've
become like strangers.
Well, I was taught never
to talk to strangers.
Funny.
Not trying to be.
-Well, I'm sorry you're upset.
-Really?
Because the last time I checked,
everything was my fault.
-I never said that.
-Not in those exact words.
-Hello.
-Sandy.
-Rebecca.
-Now I'm up.
I wanted to run, Sandy. I...
...got on a bus. I was on my way.
But I realized I couldn't leave
without saying goodbye.
As long as you don't flee...
...we have a chance with your case.
Please, stay where you are.
-Hey.
-Good morning, Marissa.
Oh, I didn't know you
had a friend over last night.
-I'm Julie Cooper-Nichol.
-Alex.
Oh, so you're the feisty young lady
Caleb mentioned.
I was just making bagels.
If the Cohens can do it, why can't we?
None for me, thanks.
I don't eat breakfast.
That's very punk of you.
I used to like the punk in my day.
-Mom.
-You're right, Marissa. It still is my day.
I was just being modest.
We'll be keeping kosher in no time.
So how about this weather, huh?
-It's unbelievable.
-Yeah.
I think I have to go.
But very nice to meet you.
Rock on.
She seems nice.
No problem if you want
a friend to stay over.
-lf you could let me know beforehand--
-You didn't get the memo?
Marissa, I don't think it's too much
to ask to know what's going on...
...underneath my roof. That's all.
You want to know what's going on
with me? I'm gonna tell you the truth.
No screaming. No crying.
Just the truth.
You have no idea how happy
it makes me to hear that.
Hold that thought.
Alex is my girlfriend.
I know. I'm happy that
you've made a friend.
-Though I hope we keep seeing Summer.
-No, Mom.
Not my friend who's a girl.
My girlfriend.
Yeah.
-What are you doing?
-You wouldn't open the door.
-Because I don't want to see anyone.
-Please let me in.
I rode my bike here.
Bicycle, monsoon...
...seriously flawed plan. I'm freezing.
Come on.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, no.
All right. Hold on.
Okay. Come here.
Well, you could've opened the door
for me a half-hour ago.
I thought you were Caleb, showing up
to drive me to my DNA test.
He scheduled you a DNA test?
It was either that or the pony.
-So you're not going?
-No way.
But you're going somewhere.
Yeah, I was gonna pack up
to move in with my dad.
But since he might not be my dad...
...I was thinking
about packing up for...
...well, maybe...
...I don't know, Chicago.
"l don't know, Chicago"?
Yeah. We have family there.
Actual, no-doubt-about-it family.
And my mom is thinking that
it getting out about her and Caleb...
...that maybe the best thing
would be...
...to start over.
And you'd go with her.
Well, if Caleb's not my dad,
what else can I do?
Except you don't know
he's not your dad.
I don't know that I want to know.
That's not gonna stop
until you know the truth.
And besides, if you are his daughter...
...at least you'll have a reason to stay.
I mean, the other reason.
I don't know, Ryan.
A DNA test just sounds so sci-fi scary.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Who looks good in this much yellow?
Zach?
Oh, thank God. Look, I really
don't know about this dress.
Hi. It's just your friendly
neighborhood Seth Cohen.
-Okay. What?
-Well, I look stupid in hats.
And I don't have a raincoat...
...so Spider-Man is the only
protective waterproof headgear I own.
T oo bad you weren't wearing
protective headgear...
...when you were dropped
on your head as a child.
Zing. So listen...
...I know that my visits to your bedroom
are probably getting a little bit repetitive.
-You are helping me miss you less.
-That's great.
So....
-You're really going, huh?
-Yeah. Of course I'm going.
How could I not be?
I am in his sister's wedding.
-You are?
-Why do you think...
...I look like lemon meringue?
Bridesmaid's dress.
You're a bridesmaid?
That's really....
-Guess you and Zach are serious.
-Cohen, are we gonna do this again?
Or did you, like, actually come here
to advance the plot.
You're, like, part of his family.
Okay.
The reason I came by is to tell you...
...you need to take a special plug
for the outlets there.
For your hair dryer. Don't want you
to brownout Western Europe.
Goodbye, again.
And you have a safe flight.
-Thanks for coming.
-Oh, it wasn't easy.
It rains in Southern California,
all of a sudden, nobody can drive.
You're shaking.
I don't wanna run anymore.
-Come back with me.
-And do what? Sit in jail?
Destroy your marriage?
My marriage has
nothing to do with your case.
Come back with me. We'll explore
amnesty or some kind of plea bargain.
I think we can make this right.
-I told her.
-You told who what?
My mom, about us.
I can't believe it, but I did.
You-- You told her.
Well, I thought you'd be happy.
No, l-- It just depends.
Did you tell her to piss her off?
Hey, look. I told her
so this could be real.
For us.
So, what happens now?
She's probably having
a meltdown. I can't go home.
-So stay here.
-You sure?
Yeah.
But first, let's get you
out of these wet clothes.
Thanks for coming with me.
What's more romantic
than a DNA test?
Yeah. Maybe we can donate
kidneys one Saturday night.
Now we're talking.
So if, in 24 hours,
it turns out Caleb is my dad....
You talking dirty to me?
Sorry.
Well, if the tests come back positive,
then he'll adopt you, right?
Right.
Except, I don't know
if I want him to adopt me.
Well, you're not going to Chicago.
Let's just forget about that option.
No, l--
I know that.
I couldn't handle the cold...
-...and the wind.
-lt is the Windy City.
I'm not a big fan of deep-dish pizza.
Thin crust, only way to go.
And I couldn't be without you.
So I come in right below pizza.
That's good to know.
Yeah, well, a girl's gotta eat.
What are you doing here
late on a Saturday?
Oh, hey, Julie. I'm just trying
to distract myself and failing.
-What about you?
-Same.
How long is this weather
supposed to last?
News says 24 hours.
-I don't think my hair can take it.
-I don't know if my marriage can.
Gossip?
You have no idea.
Want to break into
Caleb's liquor cabinet, dish some dirt?
-I'd like to use this on Caleb sometimes.
-I know what you mean.
-More Scotch?
-Sure, why not?
Nothing like a rainy day to reflect
on what a mess your life is, huh?
I mean, not yours, per se.
It was, you know, the universal "you. "
My life is a pretty big mess.
I may even beat you on that one.
Oh, I don't think so, honey,
but go ahead.
Well, my husband is currently
transporting a fugitive...
...who used to be his ex-girlfriend.
Well, I'll see your fugitive former flame
and raise you a lesbian daughter.
Marissa?
Well, I'm sure it's just a phase.
It was for me.
And it is for you too.
You guys will work it out.
-I'm not so sure.
-No...
...Kirsten, seriously,
you have to work it out.
I couldn't handle it if you didn't. You
two are the moral center of the universe.
You're Sandy and Kirsten.
Yeah, well, now we're
Sandy and Kirsten and Rebecca.
-Oh, no, police.
-Take it easy. We're fine.
The road's
completely washed out ahead.
We need you to turn around. We should
have the road open by morning.
-Not till morning?
-Yes, sir.
There's lodging a few miles back.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
You're listening to Boyz ll Men?
I can think of no sadder song
in the whole world.
So I'm guessing it didn't go well.
Unless I can think of one last grand
romantic gesture, Summer's gone.
I remember when I first heard
about Summer.
We were sailing. You said
you named your boat after her...
...which I thought weird.
You'd never talked to her.
Eureka, Ryan. Can't believe I just
said "eureka. " That's okay. That's it.
-What's it?
-Thing to win her back.
The grand romantic gesture that's
gonna put Zachary's Euro-trip to shame.
I shall take her on a sailing adventure
aboard the Summer Breeze.
-Except you sold the boat for bus fare.
-I did. Damn it.
Eureka, Ryan. I shall buy back
the Summer Breeze.
-Yes.
-Except with what money?
If I wanted my parade rained on,
I'd step outside. Let me ask you.
-Do you like the shape of the idea even?
-Definitely.
So all I need is money. Hang on.
Yes. Got the answer.
But before I say "eureka" again...
...do you see any other potential flaws,
holes in my plan?
-No.
-Then, eureka, Ryan. Eu-freaking-reka.
Turn this music off.
It's depressing me.
Come in.
-Hey. Hey, Zach.
-Hi.
You're listening to Boyz ll Men?
This song is so sad.
Yeah, I was waiting
for "Motownphilly. "
Oh, right.
-Thanks.
-Oh, my God.
You're taking all that?
Well, yeah. I don't want the ltalians
to think I have bad style.
I am representing America.
Oh, that's very patriotic of you. I just--
We're gonna be backpacking.
You know, going
from hostel to hostel.
You haven't seen hostile
till you put me in one.
No, it'll be fun. An adventure.
Don't you think it's a little much I'm in
your sister's wedding? I've met her once.
No, I told you. She doesn't have many
friends. She's very alienating and severe.
-Do you not want to come?
-No, l--
Well, no-- Yes, I just--
I have to get a special plug
for my hair dryer.
I already got you one.
Of course you did.
Seth. You here to fight crime?
No, actually.
I'm here to get my job back.
No. No, no, no. What, you were like the
flakiest employee in Bait Shop history.
That's an easy accomplishment?
And Homer, the beer guy?
How long would you be
keeping your job this time?
Until I can make $500,
so however long that is.
Please. Alex, Alex, Alex. Please.
I don't know, Seth. "With great power
comes great responsibility. "
Yes. Oh, thank you. Listen to me,
it's gonna be like no one...
...ever peed in the bathrooms.
The only other thing...
...is I kind of need an advance.
Well, you're lucky today was payday.
Hey, Alex. Should I be getting dressed,
or are we going back to...
...bed?
-Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Let me get this straight.
You broke up with me for Marissa?
-Want your money?
-Who better...
...than a superhero
understands secret identity?
-Okay.
-Now, hold on.
I just want to make sure
I have the visual.
Okay, I got it. Great. Thank you.
Hey, listen, Alex, thank you. Both
of you, for everything. I mean, keep...
-...doing what you're doing. I like it.
-Okay.
So, what will it be?
Ding Dongs or cheese sticks?
Well, this is a dessert wine,
so I'd say Ding Dongs, of course.
Oh, really?
Well, this is one classy picnic.
We got...
...washed-out road...
...rain storm...
...cheap motel.
Cheap wine. Has all the makings
of a great slasher movie.
-Getting stuck here overnight.
-Well, that's El Niño for you.
Or fate.
Here we are, all alone.
No one knows where we are.
It's like nothing else exists.
Tomorrow we head back to reality.
But, for now...
...it's just us.
Except it's not just us.
It hasn't been just us for 20 years.
I gotta call Kirsten, say good night.
I appreciate you
selling me my boat back.
When I sold it I was
in desperate straits.
Low blood sugar, no snacks.
Listen, just a heads-up.
I made some modifications to her.
Modifications. Terrific.
That's very Melville of you.
Referring to the boat as a she.
Dear God. She's a slut.
-Hello?
-Hey, honey.
Hi.
I tried you last night.
I got your messages.
I passed out early.
It was a long day at the office.
I was hoping the rain
would've stopped by now...
...then they said they'd have
the road opened up.
Right. The conveniently
washed-out road.
Believe me when I tell you...
... I' m walking home if I have to.
Just get home.
One way or the other.
I'll see you soon.
-You got a minute?
-Not really.
I would like to talk to you
about your friend Alex.
-I'm sure you would, Mom.
-Look, Marissa...
...I experimented
when I was your age.
Albeit it involved a little Mötley Crüe
and a lot of Jäger.
-Way too much information.
-I'm just saying...
...I understand that
this is a phase. But...
...I won't make a big deal
if you don't.
Right, this way you avoid
any public embarrassment.
Where are you going?
-I'm moving out.
-What?
You have my cell if Caleb kicks
and you need help counting your cash.
-What's the plan here?
-We get the boat in the pool.
I get Summer to come over, voilà.
You take Summer for a
spin in the pool in the Gimmie Sex?
It's a symbolic gesture, Ryan.
One that'll get Summer
to fall back in love with me, okay?
-Okay.
-Oh, by the way, our exes...
...are dating each other now.
Marissa and Alex, no longer
welcome in the red states.
That I wouldn't have predicted.
-Think it's for real?
-God, I hope so. I just want them to....
I'm not gonna ask why there's
a boat in the living room.
It's an objective correlative, Mother.
I'm getting Summer back.
Lindsay called. The tests are back.
She wants us to go with her.
This is it? There's not another room
full of Samsonites somewhere?
I promise. Thank you.
You know what? I forgot Princess
Sparkle. I can't go without her. Here.
As long as you leave her stable.
I'll meet you in the car.
-Hello?
-Hey, Summer, it's me.
-Why am I not surprised?
-So, what are you doing?
Don't know, leaving
for the airport to go to ltaly.
Listen, Summer, I have
something to show you.
-Okay? And not in a creepy way.
-What you're selling I ain't buying.
Okay, Summer, before
you get on that plane...
...I need you to give me
one last shot, okay?
You had your shot.
Remember when we were dating
and you sailed away?
-That's what I wanna talk about.
-You have no right to do this.
-Not now, okay? I'm hanging up.
-Okay, then just tell me this:
I mean, when you're with him, is it...?
Is it like what we had?
You know, I can't remember
that far back.
Clearly, Cohen, what we had, it wasn't
as awesome as what you had with Ryan.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have left.
So now I'm leaving you.
Okay, Summer, would you please--?
Someone please say something.
There's a lot of rain.
-Yeah, nice to see you, Kirsten.
-Yeah, nice to see you too.
Yeah, I feel much more relaxed.
Lindsay, no matter what happens
you'll always be a part of the family.
I couldn't have said it better myself.
Hello. Thank you for waiting.
Our results demonstrate...
...we have a match.
Caleb Nichol is the father
of Lindsay Wheeler-Gardner.
I knew you were my daughter.
Boyz ll Men, huh?
Guess it didn't go well.
I just hope they get
the sex over with early.
Join the mile-high club
over the Atlantic or something.
Oh, I'm sorry, man.
-What happened with Lindsay?
-Caleb's daughter.
Hey, that's great.
Wait, I don't know. Is it?
She's moving in with him.
She went home to talk with her mom.
Wanna help move her?
-Get your mind off Summer.
-The schlepping of heavy things.
Comfort for the weary soul. I'll pass.
-You can't sit here and mope.
-I've got a plan, got the satellite fired up.
Showing a marathon
of Sherman Oaks: The Real Valley, so--
-What's that?
-Apparently, The Valley...
... has its own reality-show knockoff.
And, you know, why watch angst...
...of fictional characters when you can
watch real people in contrived situations.
Could you turn the music up
on your way out, please? Thanks.
Oh, lay off your brakes.
Can't anyone drive in this weather?
Sandy, relax. Please.
-Can we talk about last night?
-No. We've got nothing to talk about...
...other than your case
and this traffic.
-So, what we had meant nothing?
-lt meant everything to me then.
That was then. Now I've got a family
that I love. I'm not throwing that away.
I gotta get back to Newport,
make sure they know.
Sandy!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I think.
Hey.
-You guys all right?
-A little bruised and battered...
-...but we're okay.
-I already called 91 1.
Cops are on their way
with a tow truck, ambulance.
-All right, thank you.
-All right.
-What are you doing?
-I can't do this.
I gotta go.
The cops are coming.
They're gonna arrest me.
-Maybe arrest you.
-So we'll talk to them.
I'm gonna chalk last night up to fate.
I gotta do the same here.
You can't run again.
What choice do I have?
Now my father's gone, and you--
l-- You're right.
What we had was a long time ago.
Gotta let it go. Let you go.
See you, Sandy Cohen.
So your father's flight
doesn't leave D.C. until 1 1.
He's lucky he doesn't
have to fly in this weather.
Oh, sorry.
Well, I'm really excited that I finally get
to meet your dad. He sounds really cool.
Did Dad make reservations
at the Uffizi?
He sure did. I can't wait
to see the Botticelli.
The Birth of Venus
is amazing in person.
-Are you a fan of Botticelli?
-Yes, yes, I am...
...although I prefer his earlier work.
You know, the comedies.
I'm gonna go get a magazine.
Would you like People, Us Weekly...
-...In Touch? Anything?
-Oh, I could take an Economist.
I could use a Xanax.
Okay. Okay.
You have one new message.
Hey, it's me. Look, perhaps
you 're screening. Perhaps you 're...
... being screened by security. I just--
I just wanted to say...
...sorry to leave things like that, okay?
I hope you have a good trip. I really do.
And somebody else here
wants to say something.
Captain Oats is a horse of few words,
but he said he 'd like you to travel safe.
And he said we 'll miss you. So okay.
Okay, bye.
-There's no more closet space.
-No.
I know. I' m sorry.
It's okay. I can learn to live
with less shoes.
I've got to get to work. Wanna
walk me? I love walking in the rain.
-Sure.
-Cool. Oh, garbage day's tomorrow.
Do you mind taking out the cans? And
rent is due the first day of the month.
-Okay. Rent.
-I know, it's really real, huh?
-No turning back.
-It's real.
Bet you never did anything
this crazy before.
I'm gonna grab my jacket.
-Hi.
-Hey.
All packed?
-Getting there.
-Call Caleb?
Let him know you were coming?
No.
Because I'm not.
-Okay.
-Ryan...
...I talked it over with my mom.
And I want to go with her...
...to Chicago.
But I thought....
Do I really want to be
Caleb Nichol's daughter?
That's not the life I want.
As hard as it is to leave you,
I can't leave my mom.
She's the only family
I've ever really had.
I get it.
Here we go, buddy.
Hours of mind-numbing escapism.
The satellite's out?
I refuse to be denied
this one small pleasure.
This I can fix.
I need you. The flight's been delayed
because of the weather.
My sister is having an anxiety attack.
-What's the matter?
-She's superstitious and thinks...
...this is a sign she shouldn't marry
Rodolfo. I don't know...
...maybe a girl's point of view?
-Sure. Yeah. Okay.
-Okay, good.
Are you coming?
I can't do it.
-Okay, I'll talk to her myself.
-No.
I mean, I can't go. I can't do this.
The truth be told, I didn't think
you'd make it past security.
I'm really sorry.
Can't fight fate.
-You took the bus.
-I told you.
Nothing was keeping me from you.
Is it over?
I promise you, it never started.
Help. Anyone?
Mom?
Thanks for walking me.
Sure you don't want to come in?
-The band is really good.
-Oh, no, I should get back.
-Dishes aren't gonna wash themselves.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Hey.
Hi.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Cohen.
-Cohen.
-Help.
Someone.
Anyone.
-Cohen?
-Summer?
Oh, my--
What are you doing here?
What do you think, Cohen?