Previously on The O. C.:
Caleb is gonna be indicted.
I don't know when.
Oh, my God, the yard guy?
-Yeah, I know.
-Marissa!
Was I supposed to wait for you?
You weren't coming back.
I wanted the truth.
-Who's your favorite writer?
-Bendis.
-Well, hot damn, welcome to the club.
-Thanks.
-Dude, I love that guy.
-You're not the only one.
You had me three months ago,
and you left.
-I wanna make it up to you.
-lt has nothing to do with me.
It is about you,
and it is always about you.
Put your hands behind your head.
Don't say anything. I'll follow you
to the station. I'm his lawyer.
Do you think I did the right thing
cutting my hair?
I don't believe this.
Your grandfather's in big trouble.
Yeah, I know.
Up the creek and then no paddle.
Damn Oregonian barbers, man,
making my head too small for my body.
-How do you work with this mirror?
-Grandpa. Front page. Jail.
I know. I got cut out of that photo
because of my hair.
Sorry to see you're so upset.
-I'll survive. It'll grow out.
-I'm talking about Caleb.
Looks like some of us
were way off base.
Accusing you
of making everything about you.
-My God, she is right.
-I'm just kidding.
No, dude, here I am going on and on
about my haircut.
My grandfather's in the cooler.
I'm like a monster. I'm all I think about,
and not in a good way.
-There's a good way?
-Talk to me about anything...
-...other than me. Go. Give me anything.
-Here it is.
First day of AP physics.
Kind of nervous.
Could you quit fretting over
your nerd gear for five seconds?
We have a real crisis on our hands
unless Summer's wrong...
...and I'm not completely insufferable.
-Why didn't you just tell me?
-lt was kind of hard getting a word in.
-You're a good talker, but--
-Summer's right.
Dude, I have to change.
I have to be, like, a better person.
-Better how?
-Less selfish.
More selfless. Less take, more give.
Less pitching, more catching.
Look, don't change for me.
-I'm not changing for you.
-For Summer?
No, no.
I think, for the greater good of man.
No hidden agenda here,
like getting Summer back?
Dude, I don't even want
Summer back...
...unless that is what she wants.
In which case, that's not about me.
That's about me supporting her,
and her wanting of--
Whatever she--
That's what she wants, okay.
Admit you want her back.
No. No, I don't.
It's the new me, Ryan. It is.
Wrap your head
around the new Seth Cohen.
You're talking about yourself
in the third person.
How is Seth's hair right now?
You can thank me later.
Thank you? For letting me
sleep the night in jail.
It was the most vile,
most inhuman night of my life.
Coming from the guy
who married Julie Cooper...
...that's saying something.
So aside from coming up with
your hilarious one-liners...
...what's our next move?
My next move
is to meet with the partners...
...make sure they agree
to my taking you on as a client.
-Why wouldn't they?
-Well, you're not exactly the ideal client.
What? Rich, powerful....
Guilty.
You missed the turn.
I'm not taking you to the office.
Kirsten's meeting us at the house.
-I have a business to run.
-Who are you kidding?
We both know, with the exception
of the underhanded stuff...
...Kirsten does everything anyway.
Step down. Put Kirsten in charge.
That's your next move.
Excuse me.
I'm new. Is it all right to park here?
Sure. If you're not embarrassed.
Ryan, what would you like?
-You buying?
-No, but I'm letting you order first.
I may be selfless, but I'm stingy.
In that case, let's see.
Can I have a...?
What have you got?
Large coffee.
I just didn't wanna keep him waiting.
That'd be selfish.
Iced coffee for me, please. Thanks.
What?
There's a new club
that the Walkmen are playing at.
-You know who loves the Walkmen?
-You.
Yeah, and?
-Summer.
-Summer, who's going out with Zach?
Yeah. So maybe I'll buy
her and Zach tickets.
-Why?
-Out of friendship...
-...and selflessness.
-And to get her back.
-I can't hear you.
-Seth, your coffee.
Thanks a lot. I'll get you next time.
God, I am so sorry.
-That was refreshing.
-Here, let me....
I am so sorry.
-You okay?
-Yeah, I have to get a rhinoplasty...
...but now I'll look
just like all the other girls here.
It's okay, really.
You can leave my tampons
where they are. Thanks.
Is there anything I can do?
I guess you could dislocate my shoulder
or shave off my eyebrows.
Is this how you treat your new students,
or is today my lucky day?
-Can I buy you a coffee?
-No, no, no. Please, please, don't.
I've had plenty, thanks,
and I'm guessing you have too. So....
I'm just gonna wring out my shirt
and stuff toilet paper up my nose...
...and I'm sure
I'll have no trouble fitting in now.
So thanks.
We have to think
about the future here.
The only way a company
is gonna survive a crisis like this...
...is for the CEO to step down.
Face it, Caleb.
It's time to get your Martha Stewart on.
There's more police, more reporters...
...or angry stockholders.
Julie.
Caleb.
As soon as I saw the paper...
...I walked right out of my seaweed
wrap, and I came right here.
-That's heartwarming.
-A weekend at the Montage...
...was exactly what I needed
to remind me what's important.
I know I haven't been there for you...
...but you haven't been exactly
honest with me.
We're gonna....
It's just getting good.
All right.
Honey...
...when Jimmy went down,
our marriage fell apart.
I do not want that to happen to us.
We're partners,
which means we share everything...
...so put me to work.
What can I do?
Talk to the press, make some calls?
Kirsten's taking care of that.
She can't do everything.
Surely there's something I can do.
There is one thing, but--
-Name it.
-Food.
Since I'm working from home,
we need water...
...some coffee, some of those
pumpkin muffins I like so much.
Thanks, Juju.
Kirsten, Sandy, back to business.
Is it just me or is Zach perfect?
He's good-looking, but not into himself...
...smart, but not a show-off...
...athletic, but sensitive...
...a politician's son.
Hey, he's like Newport's Price William.
Yeah, the kind of guy parents love.
Hey, did I tell you how stoked my dad is
that I'm dating a congressman's son?
He is dying to go
have lunch with Zach.
-So are you gonna do it?
-No way.
Do you remember what a disaster
that was with Cohen?
Yeah, but Zach's not Seth.
-Believe me, I know.
-So then what's the problem?
You afraid
he might actually like Zach...
...that you two
will live happily ever after...
-...with nothing standing in your way?
-No, l-- No.
So then you're not over Seth.
I am. I've divested myself
of all Seth's material possessions.
I'm vibrating at
an extremely Cohen-less frequency.
Okay. So then
you don't really like Zach.
No. I mean, yes.
I don't-- Shut up.
Hey, Summer. Marissa.
Hey, come sit down.
Marissa, I was sorry to read
about your stepdad in the paper today.
You read the paper?
Just the L.A. Times,
The New York Times...
... The Orange County Register
and The Wall Street Journal.
This relationship
is probably over now, right?
-I'll just go.
-No, no, no. Stay.
Actually, we were just talking, and....
What are you doing this weekend?
-You gotta be kidding me.
-I know.
I know. I'm sorry,
but it's the only seat left.
Don't worry.
I promise I'll keep my hands to myself.
Well, it's your elbow
I'm worried about.
Dude.
Why do you hate me so much?
-I don't.
-What did I do?
-lt was an accident.
-lt was, like, four accidents.
Six, if you count each tampon.
-I'm sorry. I don't know what else to say.
-Nothing.
We don't need to speak
to each other again.
That's too bad. I was enjoying it.
-I wasn't.
-I was being sarcastic.
I wasn't.
Morning, guys...
...your favorite physics teacher here,
Ari Greenburg...
...with new lab partner assignments.
We've got Adriana Albergetti
with Philip Raskin.
Ryan Atwood with Lindsay Gardner.
Jennifer Anderson with Jamie Barber.
-Ryan Atwood?
-Lindsay Gardner.
Bait Shop.
Could be our very own CBGBs.
-What?
-Come on.
The only music in Chino is
the sounds of gunshots and helicopters?
Let's get the tickets.
Hello?
Hello.
Okay.
Hi. Excuse me.
We're here about tickets.
She's got headphones on.
Yeah, I can see that. Thanks.
Excuse me, ma'am?
-Touch me again, I'll hurt you.
-Okay, fine. What do you call this?
-Thanks.
-What do you want?
-Tickets for Friday's show.
-Sold out, sorry.
That's the last one.
-All set, Alex.
-Awesome. Thank you so much.
Here are your tickets,
and I threw in a couple extras.
Cool, thanks.
-Why does he get tickets?
-He works here.
-lf I work here, could I get tickets?
-You don't work here.
What's that?
-You.... You wouldn't want that job.
-No, sure I would. Sign me up.
-Seth--
-You don't wanna know the pay...
-...hours, job description?
-No, I'm good.
Minimum wage. Long.
Taking tickets, cleaning toilets
and the preparation of fried foods.
I'll be sure and wash my hands
between the last two.
I have to ask Nat, the owner,
but he's never here, so--
-Perfect.
-Okay. I'm Alex.
You can start right now.
If I don't fire you by the end of tonight,
then come back tomorrow.
I have a mop, Ryan.
You got a mop, bro. So.
-You're doing all this for Summer?
-Yeah, for her friendship.
-You really are changing.
-I am. Changing urinal cakes.
That's how committed Seth Cohen is
to the new Seth Cohen.
Okay. Now you're talking about yourself
in the fourth person.
It's a whole new dimension
of selflessness, Ryan.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm off to the urinals.
I don't know where they are.
Check out the new Ryan Atwood
studying at the breakfast table.
-How are classes going?
-T ough. Physics.
Physics is tough.
It's not the work, it's the students.
A student, to be exact.
God, my back.
Personal growth is so painful.
My son doing manual labor.
I never thought I'd live to see the day.
Hey, Mom.
Check out this ironic twist of events.
Ryan is now a science nerd.
I'm working a blue-collar job.
That's nice, honey.
Mom?
Seth, don't worry. Your grandfather's
situation is very serious...
-...but your father and I are handling it.
-Right.
To tell you the truth, I haven't even...
...slept well the past couple nights, so
concerned have I been for his well-being.
-But everything's gonna be okay?
-Right.
-Right?
If Grandpa did have to go to some
white-collar prison with tennis and TiVo--
Don't worry.
It won't affect you.
-He wouldn't lose the company?
-No.
-Or the house?
-Son.
That's crazy talk.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I don't want you to worry, sweetie.
I'm not.
Because it's not gonna be like it was
with your father.
I'm going to hold this family together.
Fine.
Marissa, listen to me.
I know that there's a lot of uncertainty
in our lives right now.
But I want you to believe me when I say
that Caleb is not going to jail.
Oh, well, that's a shame.
Because if Caleb did go to jail...
...then you'd be on the street,
and I could go back to living with Dad.
So should we maybe
exchange numbers or something?
For what?
To work on our lab report.
No. I already turned it in.
I put both our names on it.
You'll get an A.
-Funny. I thought we were supposed to--
-Yeah, I know, but here's the thing.
The only reason I transferred to Harbor
was so I could load up on AP courses...
...get into Y ale early and never
have to see a cheerleader...
...or water-polo player ever again.
No offense.
Okay, I think you got
the wrong idea about me.
You think I'm stupid.
God doesn't give with both hands.
So take the A.
Enjoy it. It's my treat.
Where are you going?
-Mr. Greenburg?
-Yes?
That lab report Lindsay handed in,
I'm not quite finished with it yet.
Well, it looks perfect to me.
Nice work.
You guys make a great team.
I didn't contribute
a whole lot to that report and...
...by a whole lot, I mean anything.
Is this true?
Lindsay?
Look, guys.
Good science requires teamwork.
Part of the assignment
is working together.
-Maybe if we had different partners.
-No.
I'm keeping you together and
giving you an additional assignment...
...which you'll do together.
Or fail. Together.
Oh, yeah. You're not stupid at all.
A little help here?
I think I'm gonna have a hernia.
I had a hernia when I was little.
-I had to have an operation.
-Seth! Can you...?
Sorry, sorry.
Okay.
My legs just went numb.
My legs went numb,
but we're cool.
-That's normal, right?
-You are so out of your element.
-No, I'm not.
-What are you doing here?
-I need tickets.
-What are you, like, a huge fan?
Yeah. Of a prickly brunette
named after my least-favorite season.
-This is for a girl?
-T o be clear, I'm actually...
...getting the tickets
for her and her boyf--
Her boy--
Her friend that's a boy.
I'm showing her that I'm capable of
thinking of somebody other than myself.
-That's sweet. It's pathetic, but sweet.
-That's my niche. Pathetic and sweet.
What? No. Mom.
I don't know, maybe.
Okay. I love you too.
And say hi to Daddy.
-What?
-How old are you?
-Seventeen.
-What?
-Really? You don't go to school?
-I used to.
I got kicked out...
...of Corona, Mater Dei
and even Newport Union.
After that, my parents had enough.
Said go away, get a job, move out,
which I did.
I got my own studio and I work here,
and I've never been happier.
Yeah. This is you happy?
-Look, you barely earned these, but....
-Hey.
Right on. Thanks.
All right.
Summer's gonna be very stoked.
On the band.
I think the best thing for our
friendship is, like, a good live band.
Yeah. As a girl,
I feel I should probably warn you...
...that this whole little game
you're planning....
She's gonna see right through it.
Mr. Brubaker,
I assure you that my father is innocent.
I--
No, he's not in the office, but--
I'll have him call you.
I am so happy to see you.
Guess who no longer works for
Partridge, Savage and Kahn.
-You quit?
-Or got fired.
Quit/got fired.
A lot of things were said.
-None of them good.
-What happened?
Your father.
They said as long as I was representing
him, I wasn't working for them.
I love April. I do.
She's, like, the most awesome girl ever.
- You know, Mrs. Robard--
-Call me Sara.
It's Thursday night.
No knocking until 9 p. m.
-Sara. You 're a woman.
-I'm April's mother.
Cohen.
How did you get in here?
Your stepmom,
who's in unusually good spirits.
-It's the Klonopin.
-That explained that eye twitch.
-I won't stay long--
-You can't stay. The Valley's on...
-...so you should....
-No. I have something for you.
Unless it's a plutonium car
to take me to last year...
...so I can never date you, no.
It's tickets to
the Walkmen tomorrow.
-I'm not going to a concert with you.
-I'm not going.
Well, I am. Actually, I'm going.
But I'm not gonna go with you.
These are for you and Zach.
-Me and Zach?
-Yeah.
-ls this a trick?
-Nope.
Just, you know, wanted to do something
nice for someone else for a change.
So hopefully, I don't know,
we can all hang out. We can be friends.
Friends?
If you want.
Anyways, enjoy the show.
You want this closed or...?
-Yeah.
-I think I'm pregnant...
... with his baby.
Thanks for letting me stay over.
And thanks for breakfast. You finally
learned how to make French toast.
Anytime. Happy to have the company.
-I know what you mean.
-Yeah?
What do you know about being lonely?
Well, let's see.
My stepfather blackmailed me
into living with my mom.
My mom shipped my little sister
off to boarding school.
My boyfriend
spent the summer with a girl...
...who may have been pregnant
with his child...
...and now he still won't talk to me,
thanks to DJ.
Who's DJ?
Doesn't even matter,
since he's not talking to me either.
Mariss? Honey?
-You ready to go?
-I'm gonna go get my stuff.
Back to the gulag.
She knows I heard that.
It's a little game we play.
-So how's Caleb?
-Fantastic. Never better.
Facing prison.
We could lose everything.
You gonna divorce him
and take his kids?
No.
You'd think he'd be
just a little bit grateful...
...show some appreciation
for my personal growth.
He only listens to Kirsten and Sandy.
Well, the woman I married
wouldn't stand for that.
Nobody puts Julie Cooper in the corner.
I don't know
how this is happening again.
Maybe because
you keep marrying for money.
I did not marry for money.
I didn't marry you for money.
No, you married me
because you were pregnant.
You married me
because I was pregnant.
I married you because I loved you.
-Bye, Dad.
-Bye, sweetheart.
-Love you.
-I love you too.
Back to the gulag.
Okay. E equals
one-half MV squared.
So if gravity is the constant,
and we plug in these velocities....
Ryan. What are you doing?
I'm trying to do the assignment.
-Except you've already finished it.
-I'm sorry.
But if you flunk out,
you can spend your life...
...floating in your parents'
infinity pool, okay?
I'm here on
academic scholarship, so....
What makes you think
my parents have an infinity pool?
I mean, they do,
but they're not my parents.
I transferred in from Chino.
I was just like you.
Really? You were assaulted
by the captain of the water-polo team?
Okay, first of all, I've never even seen
a water-polo game.
Match. Whatever. Second of all, yeah.
Yeah, I was.
Then I got to know the guy,
and he turned out to be a good friend.
Well, I'm not here to make friends.
Yeah, well, mission accomplished.
-Look, clearly this isn't working.
-Clearly.
So let's just....
You do the first half, then
I'll go over it before I put it with mine.
-And I'll go over yours.
-Fine.
I guess we'll get together
this weekend and go over it together.
Sounds like a perfect way
to spend the weekend. See you.
The Bait Shop.
Where is that exactly?
I don't know.
So where'd you get these from, then?
You know. Cohen.
He gave them to you?
To us.
Why'd he do that?
Well, he said he wants to be friends,
that he's trying to change...
...to be less Cohen-y
and more like, well, a person.
You think he might be
trying to win you back?
No!
-I mean, no.
-Okay.
Let's just say, hypothetically,
Seth really is changing.
Would that mean you'd want
to get back together with him?
Well, hypothetically....
You know what?
Don't answer.
-Just go to the concert alone.
-Zach--
See Seth. No bickering.
No bantering. Just talk.
As much as I like you, Summer,
you need to figure this out with him.
I need you to figure this out.
Holy mack.
You are, like, such an adult.
I mean, you're not insecure.
You're not jealous.
Are you a robot?
We had a great time over break, right?
But if that's all it was supposed to be,
and we've taken this as far as possible...
...just let me know. Okay?
Okay.
Do you think champagne
is really necessary?
Absolutely. We need to toast to
quitting/getting fired. T o independence.
-You mean unemployment.
-Dad.
Think how much time Sandy'll have
to spend on your case.
Padding around the house
in his black socks and robe. I can't wait.
-Cal, don't you have a toast to make?
-No.
It's all right.
Too much champagne, I get giggly.
-When have you ever been giggly?
-Dad? What is it?
Julie and I have been talking,
and I've come to a decision.
Tomorrow morning, I'm calling a press
conference to announce that I'll be...
...stepping down from the Newport
Group and appointing a new CEO.
I'm glad you listened to reason.
Dad, wow.
As of tomorrow morning, Julie will be
the new chief executive officer...
...of the Newport Group.
Who needs more champagne?
Thanks.
-Hey. Thanks.
-Yep.
Any Summer sightings?
No, not yet.
What if she doesn't show?
What if, after all this...
...she never knows the blood and sweat
and other people's pee...
...that went into getting her tickets
because Zach took her to see lncubus?
You'd be happy for her...
-...because you're her friend, right?
-Totally.
Hey, you came.
Where's Zach?
He couldn't make it.
That's real-- That's too bad.
Let me show you
to your very VlP seating.
It's this way.
Hey.
I wasn't planning
on coming here tonight.
I'm here for Team Summer.
I'm here for Team Seth.
So, what do you think?
Seth and Summer, star-crossed lovers?
Or better off just friends?
Destined to be together?
Or just too dysfunctional together
to make it work.
I guess only time will tell.
Yep, I guess.
You wanna go in? Watch the band?
The last time we went to a concert,
it didn't turn out too well.
Things are different now.
Well, then, come on.
You like this band?
I like Journey.
Julie's waiting in the car.
You are I are gonna talk later, yes?
-I'm not sure I wanna talk to you.
-Sandy.
Kirsten is the one good thing
in your life.
How could you do this to her?
After all she's done for you.
I have to think of my marriage.
What does Julie know about being the
CEO of a multimillion-dollar company?
It's a figurehead position.
You said so yourself.
-Kirsten will continue to run the show.
-And work for Julie?
Why the hell
would she wanna do that?
What do you suggest I do?
I suggest you find a way
to make it up to Kirsten. Now.
Unless you want Julie
to be your lawyer too.
Can you see okay?
Yeah, I can see fine.
There's no obstructed views, right?
-Right.
-Okay.
I know sometimes you can't see so well
because the tall people are standing--
Y eah, right, you know, but now
I'm just having a hard time hearing.
-But thanks for getting me a seat.
-No problem.
Look, Cohen,
I think we need to really talk.
There you are. Some guy
just puked all over an amplifier--
I'm on it.
Why was that tattooed girl
telling you about vomit?
She's my boss.
I actually work here now.
-What?
-Yeah.
It was the only way
I could get those tickets.
But why?
Well, I needed the tickets
to show you that I could be selfless...
...and to get you
to stop hating me...
...and I needed you to stop hating me
so that we could be friends.
Cohen, that was really sweet.
Pathetic and sweet?
No, just sweet.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Oh, God.
Come on, I'm--
Summer, wait a second.
You are unbelievable.
Not in a good way, right?
-I thought you just wanted to be friends.
-I do.
-Well, then, what was that kiss?
-I didn't mean for it to happen.
Really? So this whole night
wasn't just a plan to get me back?
No, absolutely not.
Unless maybe it's what you want.
-Cohen.
-What? Come on.
I believed you, that you were changing
and just wanted to be friends.
I do. That's--
Maybe I just--
I can't be just friends with you.
Well, then, I guess maybe
this is it for us.
I'm so tired right now.
I didn't even sleep at all.
Oh, dude. The only thing
holding my head up is my lungs.
I'm sorry, man.
I handled that Summer situation
so wrong. I just....
-I should've never returned her calls.
-She never called you.
-I should've dated other girls.
-What girls?
Maybe if I played her hot and cold
and messed with her mind...
...then it potentially could've worked.
Look, man, I'm sorry. Really, I am.
And I would love to rehash the evening,
second by second, one more time...
...but I'm late.
-Late for what?
-I'm meeting my lab partner.
-I got this physics assignment.
-On a Saturday?
The geek routine
was really amusing at first...
...but I think you're going too far.
-This chick's going down.
-I need to talk about me...
...for several more hours.
-I thought you didn't do that anymore.
-That was the new Seth.
I'm back, Cohen classic.
Red, white and me.
Hang in there. I won't be gone long.
Did the light of dawn
make any of this a little easier to take?
Harder, actually.
So, what are you gonna do?
I'll tell you this:
I'm not going back to the office.
I may tolerate Julie
as my stepmother...
...but I will not suffer the indignity
of her being my boss.
Which means as of Monday,
we're both unemployed.
-There's a concept.
-Come on.
You and me, bathrobes,
some black socks.
The thought of that is so....
-Liberating.
-Scary.
Forget the black socks.
Barefoot, baby, barefoot.
I can't be unemployed.
I can't even take a vacation for more
than a week without freaking out.
A vacation with you is no vacation,
with the itineraries and sightseeing.
I can't have worked this hard
and not have something to show for it.
I don't know.
Can't quit.
Can't go back there.
I don't know either.
But what I do know is...
...I'm not the one
you should be telling this to.
-Hey.
Seth.
-You're in my room.
-Yeah.
How'd you get in here?
Took a left at the grotto,
then I hopped the funicular...
...to the dumbwaiter.
This is a nice place.
So, what are you doing in here?
Well, when I have a problem, Marissa,
I like to talk about it incessantly.
Yeah, no. That's it.
I just think I burned out anyone else
who will listen, so....
Is now a bad time?
I'm game.
So...
...I think I really messed things up
with Summer last night.
Hurt her pretty bad.
-Yeah, you did.
-You're not gonna sugarcoat this one?
Not for you.
Look, if you really
wanna be her friend...
...then maybe you should
think about just apologizing.
-You know, say you were sorry.
-Y eah, no, I know.
Sounds so simple when you say it.
I think that's a good place to start.
Okay, do you happen to know
where Summer is right now?
I just have this thing to tell her.
-She's at the club with her dad.
-Oh, yeah, the father.
Cool. I'm just gonna, you know--
Whoa, Seth. You know what? Don't go
there now. Just give her some space.
-Yeah, space. Totally. I know.
-Hey, do you know where Ryan is?
Because we had fun last night,
and I just thought--
Ryan's actually at school,
doing his physics homework.
School?
Y eah, I don't know. He's kind of
a dork now. Thanks.
She's agreed to supervised visitation.
Twenty minutes, max.
She's my daughter, Sandy.
I don't need to be supervised.
I'm supervising her.
I'm afraid she might kill you.
I'm sorry...
...about yesterday.
So that's it? No second thoughts?
-You're not gonna change your mind?
-It's what I have to do, Kiki...
...for Julie, to save our marriage.
Who's gonna save the company?
You.
That's why I'm appointing you
Newport Group's chief financial officer.
Because we all know whoever controls
the money controls the company.
Really? Does Julie know that?
She'll find out.
-I don't know.
-Come on, Kiki.
The company needs you.
The family needs you.
I need you.
Julie will get bored
after a day anyway...
...want to go to Cardio Barre,
Fashion lsland....
Do I get a raise?
So...
...I appreciate
what you're trying to do--
Lindsay. Lindsay, I'm reading here.
Take your time.
I just wanted to let you know
that you didn't do a bad job.
Your work isn't terrible either.
A little rushed, maybe.
So I've been thinking.
I owe you an apology.
Well, several, actually.
You have to actually say the words.
That's kind of how it works.
I would like to extend to you...
...a formal acknowledgement that l...
...may have unintentionally....
-I'm sorry.
-Me too. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about the coffee
and the black eye and the tampons.
You can see why I thought
you were intellectually challenged, right?
I'm just....
I'm really glad that you're not.
Your penmanship, however--
Hey, what's wrong with it?
Nothing, just....
Next time don't hold the pen
between your toes.
Well, next time
don't spell "canceling" with two L's.
Yeah, that's wrong.
You wanna fix it?
I was using the Canadian spelling.
You're using
the Canadian spelling, eh?
Hi. I'm looking for Roberts,
table for two.
-We've got Roberts for three.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Hey.
If someone would've told me
last year...
...that you and I'd be
the two loneliest people in Newport...
...I wouldn't have believed them.
Well...
...at least not the "you" part.