-Previously on The O. C.:
-He's totally checking you out.
It's the first time since Julie left me
I don't feel completely alone.
DA comes
to see me at the beginning of summer...
...tells me the sky is falling,
and he hasn't done a damn thing since.
You're not charging that
on the company card, are you?
Acknowledge me now
or lose me forever.
I can't believe this.
-So you and Summer....
-Not so good, actually.
She'll probably
never speak to me again.
-Do you guys still talk?
-Not really. We used to...
...but it just sort of
made everything harder.
-We can not go.
-We can't not go.
We can so not go. We missed
registration. No one's expecting us.
-Your mom called the school.
-Did my mom call the--?
You're the bad boy.
You're the outsider.
Lead me into temptation,
not homeroom.
It's just the first day of school.
Exactly. An entire day
of Ashton Kutchers knuckle-knocking...
...and going on and on about summer.
Their summer, not my....
You know, the season, not the person.
-At this point, how would I even know?
-You haven't called her?
Remind me to explain the difference
between Plastic Man and Elongated Man.
-That's a no?
-When did I have time to call?
I just got back. I have three months
of back issues to bag and board.
And on top of that, apparently,
I have to go to school.
-Could've called her from Portland.
-I did, every day. I got her voicemail.
Until she picked up, and said if I ever
call again, her dad will have me killed.
-So Summer has no idea you're back.
-Killed, Ryan, as in dead.
Well, that was months ago.
She's probably moved on by now.
I'm sorry.
Moved on?
Gotten over it.
Gotten over it? Why?
Because I just--?
I meant nothing to her?
I'm gonna brood silently, over here.
-She's gonna have me killed.
-She's not.
You're right. She'll ignore me.
That's worse.
So? She's been ignoring you for years.
That was before I was not ignored.
Why should I have to go back to that?
Why?
Because you left for three months
without telling her.
-So it's my fault?
-You left.
-Because of you.
-So it's my fault?
You think she'll buy that?
-Just talk to her.
-And say what exactly?
-I don't know. "I'm sorry," maybe?
-Really. "I'm sorry. "
Is that what you said to Marissa?
No, but I'm going to.
Oh. Okay, then.
So it turns out, what do you know,
I'm not the only coward in the room.
No, I'm just gonna see her at school.
I know that.
You're gonna walk up to her
in front of everyone...
...and be all, "Hey,"
and hope she "Heys" you back?
Yeah, we're not going to school.
Okay, listen,
whatever happens today at school...
...the important thing is that
the Ryan-Seth team's back in action.
Together, we can face anything.
I'm moving to Portland.
-Good morning, men. Sleep well?
-No.
-Ready for your first day of school?
-There's bagels.
-Coffee.
-I'd love some, thanks.
-And then there's Archie.
Will you explain to me
this remodeling thing again?
Your mother got bored.
Your father complained about having
no place for his surfing memorabilia.
Oh. So it is my fault.
-We'll finish the kitchen today.
-The rest of the house?
-ls that the phone?
-Sandy.
-Honey, I'm mid-schmeer.
-I am late for work.
Well, if I could find it,
maybe I'd answer it.
Hello?
-Hung up.
-I hate when they do that.
I called the school,
so you're registered.
You just have to go by the office.
-Your dad will go with you just in case.
-All right.
I thought you were gonna take them.
-I have a meeting.
If it's too much trouble,
maybe we should stay home.
I have to go.
-Hello?
-I'm really glad that you guys are home.
-Maybe we should raise our allowances?
-He's where?
You don't know?
It's the office.
All right, I'll find him. Thank you.
-I have to go.
You want me to take them?
Not an auspicious way
to start the school year.
Thanks, Archie. Don't worry.
I'm sure nobody saw.
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God. Ryan!
-Hey!
-Hey.
-All right, wish me luck.
-Yeah.
-Summer.
-What are you doing here?
I'm back. I'm back at the Cohens',
back at Harbor. I'm.... I'm back.
But how?
I mean, what about Theresa?
It's kind of a long story.
I wanna hear it
if you wanna tell me.
Yeah, sure. After school?
After school. It's a date.
Summer!
-Aren't you even going to talk to me?
-Nope.
Sorry. Maybe I'll write a letter.
You can read it over and over...
...trying to figure out
what I was thinking all summer.
-Wait a second.
-I am done waiting for you, Cohen.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go meet my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
I can't believe this is happening.
Well, how much are they offering?
Wow. So when do we
have to be there?
I can't. It's too soon.
I still haven't told Jimmy yet.
-Because I don't wanna hurt him.
-Hey.
There you are, to be sure.
Jimmy's up. I gotta go.
I will, I promise. Bye.
-Susie says hi.
-Susie...
-...calls too early.
-It's almost 9.
Whoa. Time for a mimosa.
Are you trying to get me drunk?
I am trying to keep you drunk.
Last night was pretty awesome.
The whole summer's been awesome.
The beach, the yacht, you.
No, you.
You're the one.
Listen, I've got a really good idea...
...and I want you to
really concentrate on it, okay?
We should keep the boat
for another month...
...and we go down to Cabo.
-Jimmy, we can't.
-Why can't we?
Come on, it's not like either of us
have jobs that we have to go back to.
Come on, look,
I'll manage my portfolio online...
...and, you know, this way
the summer never has to end.
-You know? Right? Am I right?
-Right.
-Right?
-Right, right.
I put this schedule together for you,
which you'll probably hate...
-...which is fine.
-I'm sure it's okay.
I based it on the schedule
from last year.
-Nice GPA, by the way.
-Really? Thanks.
So is there anything missing?
Favorite subject? Favorite teacher?
Electives? Anything?
Honestly, l' m just happy not to be
working construction right now, so....
You know, Ryan, it's not too early
to start thinking about colleges.
Thanks, but I can't afford college,
and I won't let the Cohens pay for it.
Ryan, you have great test scores...
...a solid GPA, and if you work
your ass off when you get out of here...
...you can do whatever you want.
The question is, what do you want?
How do you mean?
Well, what do you like?
What are you interested in?
I don't know.
Seriously, I don't know.
Okay.
I have an assignment for you.
Go to your classes and write down
everything you like about them...
...and everything you don't like,
and most importantly, why.
T omorrow, we'll go over it
and make sure you get what you want.
-I'm sure this schedule is fine, really.
-You'll find out and let me know.
-All right, I'll see you tomorrow.
-Yep.
Love letter to Marissa?
No, no. It's....
Did Miss Fisher
give you an assignment?
No, but I didn't get a warm cinematic
hug from anyone when I got here either.
-Cute. Did you guys talk?
-Yeah, we sure did.
Long enough
to hear she has a boyfriend.
-Buddy, I'm sorry.
-It's all right, man. You know why?
I had a whole life at this school
before Summer.
-Sure.
-An outcast's life, maybe...
...but I was a vital part
of the Harbor club scene.
-There's a Harbor club scene?
-Sure.
Sailing Club, Film Club,
and, wait for it...
...wait for it.
The Comic Book Club.
Check it out. Huh?
-Who's this guy?
-That's me with powers.
The power to be handsome.
This may have something to do
with the outcast thing.
No, it doesn't. Listen, Spider-Man 2?
You know how much money that made?
We're not outcasts anymore, okay?
We' re edgy. We're like trailblazers.
-We?
-Yeah, dude, listen.
Miss Fisher says get involved?
Well, I need you to get involved.
Get involved. Get onboard.
You, me, Comic Book Club...
...and hopefully others.
I need you to pass those out.
Hey, guys.
Comic Book League. Check it out.
We're gonna get into the issues.
Stuff that matters.
T oday's topic,
"Capes: Fey or Kind of Cool? "
Ryan, you better pass those out.
Thanks for the ride to my car.
Anything to get away from Cohen.
Do you wanna go get lunch after this?
I should probably
get back to school.
Back to Ryan, you mean?
So tell me, is he taking you
to the Kickoff Carnival?
You gonna go for another spin
on the Ferris wheel?
-He said we'd talk after school.
-About getting back together?
No. I don't know.
Would that be so bad?
No, I mean.... Well, it's just....
Him and Cohen can't think
they can walk in and out of our lives...
...whenever they want, you know?
I-- Whose truck is that?
The yard guy's,
and he's blocking my car again.
-Hey, hey!
-Hey, DJ, you're blocking my car!
Do not honk at DJ. He's hot.
He's the yard guy.
He can park his truck
in my driveway anytime.
I'll see you back at school.
-What are you doing in here?
-I work here.
I have to go.
So go.
Will I still see you today after school?
I.... I can't. I'm sorry.
-It's just--
-It's okay.
Don't worry.
I may still be here when you get back.
Hey.
-What are we drinking?
-Sum, wait.
What are you drinking?
Did you spike your latte?
-It's been a weird day.
-Marissa, we're at school.
Yeah. Exactly.
What is going on with you?
-Did something happen with Ryan?
-What am I supposed to say to him?
About?
About DJ.
DJ? Who in the hell is--?
Oh, my God, the yard guy?
-Yeah, I know.
-Marissa!
-Since when?
-Since-- I don't know. All summer?
And you didn't tell me?
Summer, I couldn't tell anyone.
No one can find out about this.
Okay.
God, that is so hot.
No, it's not, believe me.
Really? But he's so ripped.
No, he's great, it's just....
He's the yard guy.
Now Ryan's back,
and I don't know what to do.
Well, just explain it to him.
He left...
...and suddenly, there was a hot, hot
yard guy in the yard, who was hot.
You didn't do anything wrong.
If I didn't do anything wrong,
why should I tell him?
Well, if it really is over with DJ,
then I guess you don't.
Let's go get you some coffee
with actual coffee in it.
-Two coffees, please. Black.
-Yes, sir.
You're gonna lose that hand.
Since when is Scotch
part of your nutritious brunch?
Since the DA's office finally decided
they had enough to indict me.
So, what did they decide
to charge you with?
Bribing certain city officials
to obtain building permits.
That's a new one.
-ls there any truth in it?
-Please.
Why I would I need to bribe anyone?
-I own this town.
-Sure you do. You bought it.
All right, I admit that I have done
some things that I'm not too proud of...
...but I did not do
what they are accusing me of.
Well, then, they'll have no case.
What they do have, however,
are documents.
Bank statements showing
large sums of money transferred...
...from the Newport Group
to the city councilmen's office.
Well, how is that possible?
I don't know.
Will you help me?
How?
I was hoping you could tell me that.
-Hey.
-Okay. Sorry I'm late.
No, no. You're right on time.
We're just getting started.
Ryan, would you please
take the minutes?
-Seth, it's just us.
-Yeah. Write that down.
I now call to order this year's first Harbor
School Comic Book League meeting.
Members include Seth Cohen.
Present. Ryan Atwood.
-Seth, if it's just--
-Ryan Atwood?
Present. If it's just you and me,
can we do this at home?
-There'd be no yearbook picture.
-Maybe not a bad thing.
Maybe you couldn't undermine me
in front of the League?
Hey, I'm here for
the Comic Book Club.
-You are?
Yeah. Why wouldn't I be?
Because you're on
the water polo team?
What's that supposed to mean?
Okay.
You wanna talk comics?
Let's talk comics.
-What day do new comics come out?
-Wednesday.
-Wonder Woman's secret identity?
-Doesn't have one.
True, which I think is a mistake.
-I know. Me too.
-Who's your favorite superhero?
Depends who's writing him,
but I'd have to say Superman.
Superman. This guy.
He's too perfect, guy.
No. He seems perfect, but he's not.
I mean, if you think about it,
he's actually kind of messed-up.
He lost his parents, lost his whole
planet. He's, like, totally alone.
He could take over the world
if he wanted, but he doesn't.
He just keeps helping people.
Why do that?
Unless he was trying
to make a connection.
Trying to, like, find his way home.
-Who's your favorite writer?
-Bendis.
-Well, hot damn, welcome to the club.
-Thanks.
This is gonna be good.
Today's topics, we have some. The Hulk.
He gets bigger,
all his clothes rip off except...
...his pants. Why is that?
-We'll meet every Wednesday.
-Yes.
Hit the comic store
and then hang out.
-Awesome. I'm psyched.
-Great.
-I'll hit you those Green Lantern jpegs.
-Yeah, definitely do that.
Dude, I love that guy.
Whoa. You're not the only one.
No, she cannot be dating him.
That's not even possible.
How is that possible?
-A second ago, you wanted to date him.
-Because he's me.
See what she's doing? She's dating
the WASP version of me. It's so stupid.
-What, you think Zach--?
-Yeah, I do. Look at him.
He's like, what, the conventionally
attractive, athletic, confident...
...just, completely non-neurotic...
...WASP version of me.
So there it is. The haunted mansion.
Damn. I am definitely
not in Chino anymore.
So have you talked to Theresa at all
since you--?
Since we lost the baby? No, no.
But we didn't really talk a whole lot
while I was there either.
So you weren't really a couple?
-I mean, you never--?
-No. No.
It wasn't really like that at all.
So, what about you?
You dating anybody?
No. I'm not dating anybody.
Okay, so, if you're not
dating anyone...
...maybe you'd wanna go to
the Kickoff Carnival with me tomorrow?
I don't know.
Can we go on the Ferris wheel?
My last boyfriend
was afraid of heights.
Poor guy.
He didn't know what he was missing.
Come on. I can't wait
for you to see the house...
...and the look on my mom's face
when she sees you in it.
-You got a job?
-No, it's not just a job.
It's a whole new career.
-ln fashion.
-Hailey.
-ln sales.
-ln Japan.
-Oy!
-How's Jimmy doing with that?
-He's great.
-He doesn't know.
-Hailey....
I tried to tell him, but he just seems
so happy all the time.
He's making so much on the market,
all he wants to do...
...is drink and sail and go to Cabo.
You poor thing.
I'm too young for early retirement.
-You're too old for running away.
-I'm not running this time.
I have a shot
to make a real future out of this.
Jimmy just seems kind of...
...stuck.
He loves you.
-I love him too.
-Then you have to tell him.
-I can walk on my own, you know.
-Yeah, when you're not drunk.
-I'm not.
-Oh, no, you're all right.
-You're fine.
-Oh, my God, Cal?
I spoke too soon.
What's the matter with him?
Is he all right?
Did he have a stroke?
I'm fine.
-He had a bottle of Scotch.
-You got him drunk?
No, I took him to lunch
to get him sober.
I am not drunk.
Somebody tell me what's going on.
-Cal?
-I'm going to bed.
The pleasure is all yours, Sanford.
Enjoy.
-You may wanna sit down.
-You may wanna just tell me.
Caleb is gonna be indicted.
I don't know when...
...but the DA's office
has been investigating him for....
For a while now.
For how long?
How long have they been
investigating him, Sandy?
Since before the wedding?
Son of a bitch.
Well, you know,
he didn't wanna worry you.
Is he going to jail?
They're accusing him of bribing city
officials, and apparently they have proof.
-I wish there was something I could do.
-No, you don't.
You despise him. You despise me.
You'd love nothing more than to see us
get exactly what we deserve.
-No. Julie, no.
-Let me tell you something.
If Caleb's going down,
Kirsten's going with him.
So you better come up
with something...
...or it won't be just my kids
who lose everything.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go take care of my husband.
-Hey. How's it going?
-Let me help you with that.
How was your first day at school?
It was all right, actually.
How'd it go with Miss Fisher?
Is that your assignment?
-She told you about that?
-Y eah.
She called to tell me
she wants us all to sit down...
...and start talking about
colleges for you.
-That's fantastic--
-Where the hell are you going?
-You're paying me to work, aren't you?
-I thought I was.
-Ryan, did you tell her?
-No, but--
Ryan figured out why there's no wall
in our family room.
-There's no wall--
-He misread the blueprints...
...and ordered the wrong I Beam,
hoping we wouldn't notice...
...while he bills us
for the time it'll take to replace.
-We're doing other things.
-Yeah, eating our bagels.
Taking your kids to school.
I ordered the right beam.
-The wrong one got delivered.
-I get that...
...but can I ask you something?
If you just moved the new wall
out about 1 0 inches...
...couldn't you just use
the I Beam you've got?
-You an architect?
-No, I worked construction--
-Don't tell me how to do my job.
-Don't talk to him like that.
There are still couches in my kitchen.
What, looking for another free meal?
Want us gone? We're gone.
Get your little construction worker
to finish up.
-Archie, don't go. Please.
-No, no, no. Thanks for the coffee.
Sandy, apologize.
I have nothing to apologize to him for.
Nothing.
And I am sick of putting myself
on the line for this family...
...and getting nothing.
If you wanna apologize, apologize.
I'm done.
I'll call Archie and apologize.
No.
You're right.
He should have told us about the beams.
I'll call a new contractor
in the morning.
I know I wasn't the easiest person
to live with this summer.
I was just really upset
about the boys being gone...
...and I took it out on you.
I'm sorry.
You know...
...what I said in there...
-...it wasn't about you.
-Thank God.
-Because you were scary.
-Really? I was scary?
Yeah.
I've never seen you go off on anyone
like that except for my dad, and....
Oh, no. What did he do now?
-Hey.
-You all right?
-Yeah, I'm just tired.
You missed all the drama.
It's all right.
I think I got my quota for the day.
How'd it go with you and Marissa?
She's gonna go to the carnival with me.
You wanna come with?
Hang out with you and Marissa
and Summer and Zach?
Is that how it's gonna be
from now on?
-Probably. I don't know.
-Great. I can't hang out with you again.
Doesn't mean we can't be friends.
You really think Summer will wanna
be friends with me after what I did?
Especially now she has Zach?
The guy's like Superman.
-He's not Superman.
-He's like a thoroughbred.
I'm a monkey, with cymbals.
So, what are you gonna do?
Spend a whole year with Captain Oats?
Not like I have a choice.
Of course you do. Just call her.
Look, be her friend.
I can't, man. It's too late.
She's not gonna wanna hear
anything I have to say.
Okay. So, what happened was...
...Susie and l
were roommates in Santa Cruz...
...until we dropped out of college
to start our own fashion line.
You had your own fashion line?
No, because we took all
my dad's money, moved to Paris...
...and partied till I had to move back.
Now, that is the American dream.
But Susie stayed in Paris.
She got a job at Chanel...
...and just sold her first collection
to a company in Japan.
Here's to Susie.
To Susie, who asked me to be
her sales rep and move to Japan.
More wine?
She asked you to move to Japan?
-I know, right?
-So...
...what did you say?
I said I'd talk to you about it.
You're asking me to move to Japan?
No.
You've got your kids.
You have a whole life here...
...and being with you has
made me realize I want all that.
I want a job. I want a future.
I don't wanna run away anymore.
Then don't.
You can have all that here.
I can't. The money's in Japan.
So? I'll back you.
No, I can't take your money.
It wouldn't be my money.
It would be our money.
-Marry me.
-What?
I've had and lost
enough jobs to know...
...the only thing important in life
are the people in it.
And I want you in my life, Hailey.
I wanna marry you.
Happy, high vibrations attract happy,
high-vibrational circumstances.
Yucky, low vibrations attract yucky--
I' m doing my homework!
It's the same principle
as a tuning fork.
If I fail lntro to Pre-Calc this semester,
it's all because of you.
Ryan? I....
Sorry. I thought you were
the evil step-monster.
She let me in. She seems nice.
Well, she just switched antidepressants.
Give it a day.
-Can I come in?
-Sure. Wait.
-Did Cohen send you?
-No. He has no idea I'm here.
-So.
You just in the neighborhood?
No.
I owe you an apology.
It's my fault Seth took off last summer.
Ryan, stop. It is so not.
If I hadn't left, you'd be together.
That is not true. He would've found
some Cohen-y way to break us up.
He can't help it. He's Cohen.
Come. Sit.
Okay.
Look, I know
you have a boyfriend now--
Whoa. No. Who told you that?
-I thought you told Seth that.
-Yeah, to torture him.
See, Zach and l, we're just hanging out.
He is not my boyfriend.
I do not want a boyfriend, okay?
I had a boyfriend. He sailed away.
Which was wrong, but....
But he cares about you so much...
...and if you could just
give him another chance...
...and maybe we could all go back
to the way that we were?
How?
You guys just left. For three months.
You moved on. I moved on.
Marissa moved on.
What?
I mean the way we were
wasn't always so great.
You guys had to deal with
Marissa's mom, Luke, Oliver, Theresa...
...and Cohen and l
never should have hooked up.
Look, just trust me on this.
Things are the way they are
for a reason.
You should go talk to Marissa.
You can't keep calling me, DJ.
You shouldn't even be here.
We're eating dinner.
Who is he?
He was my boyfriend.
So you're back together now?
-I'm sorry.
-Didn't look sorry when you were kissing.
-That's not fair.
-Don't talk to me about fair.
What were we doing
all summer?
I know, but he's my boyfriend.
-And I'm the yard guy, right?
-DJ, come on.
-I hear the way you talk about me.
-We agreed not to tell anyone.
-Because I'm the yard guy!
-Because you'd get fired!
Know what? I quit.
Have fun explaining that to your mom.
DJ, wait.
I'm not like that!
You know I'm not like that.
Please.
Hey, don't cry.
Please, don't cry.
I pull in the driveway,
Marissa's making out...
...with some guy
I've never seen before.
-What did you do?
-Nothing. I drove off.
I guess you should have called first.
She said she wasn't dating anyone.
Maybe she's not.
Maybe they just hook up for sex.
I'm sorry. I'm distracted.
Listen, man, I cannot believe
you talked to Summer for me.
Dude, thank you.
That is just above and beyond you.
-Now you have to help me get her back.
-Seth.
She said she wants to try again.
-Y eah, as friends.
-Come on.
Why go to the trouble of telling you
that Zach is not her boyfriend...
...if she just wanted to be friends?
Why would she tell you she just
wants to be friends if she doesn't?
Because she's hurt and scared
and she's hiding behind walls.
Y eah, and I will bring those walls down
with one single grand gesture.
-No. No grand gestures.
-I'm afraid it is time...
...to stand on that proverbial coffee cart
and declare my love for her.
Maybe at the carnival.
Maybe it'll be a hot-dog stand.
Okay, all right, all right.
What do I do about Marissa?
I don't know.
I mean, what do you wanna do?
You sound like Miss Fisher.
-I forgot to finish the assignment.
-Hey.
See where this is going? This is good.
Marissa's distracting you from school.
Summer and I will get back together.
The thing is,
by the end of Kickoff Carnival...
...the four of us, we're gonna be
exactly the way we were.
Dad. What are you doing here?
-He's having breakfast.
-Julie's not talking to me.
She left a note saying she checked into
the Montage for a $3000 spa weekend.
But you get the Sandy Cohen
lox scramble with rye toast.
So are you here to see Sandy
so he can bail you out again?
No, I'm not dragging Sandy
into anything.
Before serving me these eggs...
...he was the closest thing I had
to a friend in this town.
I came to apologize, Kiki.
And to ask you to remember that
whatever happens in that courtroom...
...I did what I did for this family.
I should go.
-Where to?
-lnterviewing lawyers all day...
...then I imagine I'll be home tonight,
shredding documents.
Don't do that.
Have dinner with us instead.
I won't cook, I promise. Although...
...if Kirsten's mad enough at you,
she might.
I don't wanna be any trouble.
We'll order in.
So the thing is, I'm not really a writer.
At all.
Words are kind of not my thing.
Obviously.
So maybe if I had some more time--
What is this?
What I did when I should've done
what you asked me to.
Yeah, but what is it?
It's the Cohens' new family room.
Actually, that's....
That's what it should have looked like...
...but the contractor didn't know
what he was doing.
Can I see your schedule, please?
Yeah.
Because we're gonna need to get you
into advanced math and science classes.
Some calculus, physics--
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Why?
You'll need them
if you want to become an architect.
Isn't that what you want?
-You taking off?
-Yeah. Dad's coming for dinner tonight.
I left a message on Hailey's cell inviting
you guys, but I never heard back.
Well, that's because she's probably
halfway to Japan by now.
-Did she at least tell you, or--?
-Yeah, no. She told me. Yeah.
I just didn't listen.
I asked her to marry me instead.
Oh, Jimmy.
No, it's good. It's good. It's....
You know, I'm happy for her.
You know,
it's what she always wanted, so....
What do you want?
I don't know. I thought I wanted
to spend the rest of my life with Hailey.
-lt was fun.
-I'm sure.
Living on a yacht, drinking all day,
sailing off to Cabo.
How come when you say it,
it sounds bad?
Listen to me. You can do
whatever you want with your life...
...but you're not gonna waste it.
I won't let you.
Hailey's made her move.
What's yours?
-We can just not go.
-We can't not go. We're here.
Look at them. Oblivious, having fun.
To them it's all funnel cakes
and fried Snickers.
Just a chance to mingle
with the carny folk...
-...and win an awesome stuffed monkey.
-For us?
But for us, Kickoff Carnival determines
the course of our romantic lives...
-...for the entire year.
-No pressure.
We did good last year. We did okay.
You kissed Marissa
on the Ferris wheel...
...Summer threw up on my shoes....
I think I know how she felt.
I'm gonna go find a hot-dog stand
to climb. Good luck.
I was gonna tell you.
No, you weren't.
I asked you point-blank and you lied.
-I didn't lie.
-Marissa.
Was I supposed to wait for you?
You weren't coming back.
I wanted you to tell me the truth.
His name's DJ.
He works for my parents, so we had
to keep it a secret from everyone.
We're not seeing each other anymore.
After last night
when he found out about me, right?
Look, I'm sorry.
For right now, we should....
We should just be friends.
Friends?
Ryan, we're not friends.
We were never just friends.
I guess that was the problem then.
See you.
So, what'll it be?
Funnel cake or a fried Snickers?
Bottled water.
What? You can't come to a carnival
and just have bottled water.
No, I meant with the funnel cake
and the Snickers.
What?
Cohen. What are you doing?
Nothing. Why?
Looks like you're humping
the hot-dog stand.
No, actually, Summer,
I'm not even humping anything.
You know how I love to stand
on countertops in public places.
You know,
hot-dog stands, coffee carts--
-Oh, no--
-Because, Summer Roberts...
-Cohen, do not!
-...I love you.
-What?
-Hey, Zach. How's it going?
Don't listen to him.
He's crazy. He reads comic books.
-I know. So do l.
-You do?
Zach, listen. I really hope
this doesn't affect the League.
-Summer and I have a history.
-But no future. We are leaving.
Wait. Hang on. Just hear me out.
-Cohen, back off! I mean it.
-Fine! Just one second.
Seth. She said back off.
Please?
-You all right?
-No, but I have not yet begun to fight...
...or grovel, should it come to that.
Oh, my God.
Cohen?
Oh, my God! Are you okay?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
-Good!
What do you think you're doing?
This isn't a game!
-You could've gotten hurt!
-Good thing I didn't.
What do you want from me, Cohen?
I just want you.
No, you don't.
You had me.
You had me at Chrismukkah
in a freaking Wonder Woman costume...
...and you chose Anna.
You had me three months ago,
and you left.
-I wanna make that up to you.
-lt has nothing to do with me.
It is about you,
and it is always about you.
What you need,
and what you want, you know.
It seems that you only want me
when you can't have me.
You like the chase, and that's all.
So you know what? You can have it.
I'm going home.
All right, man. Let's go home.
Hey, guys. You're home early.
You hungry?
There's some Moo Shu left.
Do you want some?
-Grandpa, you eating on the floor?
-Yes, it has come to this.
Unfortunately, the family room
is still stuck inside the kitchen.
-How was school?
-Really good. I'm never going back.
Just what a father likes to hear.
-Ryan broke up with Marissa.
-Summer broke up with Seth.
-Zach will never talk to us again.
-Who?
New guy. But on the plus side...
...Ryan's taking AP physics, AP math,
and this Moo Shu looks delicious.
-It's really good.
-Caleb Nichol?
Sir, you're under arrest.
Gentlemen.
-What took you so long?
-You have a right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be
used against you in a court of law.
You have a right to an attorney
during questioning.
-What's going on?
-Your father will explain.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
You have absolutely nothing
to apologize for.
-Do you understand?
-Yeah.
Put your hands behind your head.
Don't say anything. I'll follow you
to the station. I'm his lawyer.