-Previously on The O. C. :
-Carter Buckley. What's he done?
He published a magazine
called Revolution.
I read it. I'd love to meet him.
-Where'd you find this?
-My husband.
Well, I'll have to meet him.
This is not the moment when you want
your reputation undone.
You got three days...
...or everyone is gonna see
a lot more than your face.
-I can't do it. I'm really sorry.
-You can't fight fate.
You and I are back together, maybe
Marissa and Ryan might get it together.
-So who are you?
-Whoever you want me to be.
All right, dinnertime!
How do you feel about chicken parm?
That is simply unacceptable.
Hey, don't look at me.
I'm the one who wanted Thai.
Carter, I am gonna
have to call you back.
Okay.
I barely recognize you without a wire
coming out of your ear.
Honey, I'm sorry. It's just that we're
unveiling the magazine to advertisers...
...in 67 hours. At which point, I will
have some semblance of a life back.
Well, here's hoping.
And every time I do that,
you pause it.
Oh, yes.
I thought I smelled Al Forno's.
-Thank you. I'm starving.
-Thanks. Nice.
-See you later.
-Whoa, no, no. Sorry.
This is a family dinner.
No. The sneak-attack family dinner.
-We walked right into it.
-I have to work.
Ryan and I are in the middle
of a very crucial PlayStation game.
-It's like our Super Bowl.
-I don't care.
Nobody here eats unless we sit down
and eat as a family.
No excuses. Tonight and together.
Now sit down. Everybody. Come on.
Great.
You too.
Family time's always best
when it's forced.
You're not gonna be invited
on the family trip I'm planning.
Ryan, you ever seen Mount Rushmore?
-Could be work.
-Summer gets mad if I'm not available.
-Marissa's supposed to call me.
-I'll get the phone.
Nobody's taking any calls.
It is dinnertime.
Hello?
Just a second.
It's for you.
What? Ryan gets to talk on the phone
during dinner...
...and I can't play PlayStation?
Hello?
Hey.
Really? When?
Yeah. No. All right.
Yeah.
See you then.
That was Trey.
-Your brother?
-Yeah.
He's getting out of jail tomorrow.
-He wants me to pick him up in Chino.
-There's that family trip you wanted.
Hey, what are you doing in here?
There's bagels and cream cheese
in the kitchen.
-Yeah, I'm coming.
-And yet you're sitting.
I guess I just needed a second
to brace myself for today.
Yeah.
Picking up your brother from prison.
That is not not intense.
Have you talked to him
at all, since--?
Last Thanksgiving when he tried
to get me to steal a car? No.
I kind of thought he was
out of my life for good.
Do you want him out of your life?
I don't know. Maybe.
He's my brother, but....
-The guy is trouble.
-lf you want my advice....
I mean, l....
Who am I kidding?
I'm totally out of my league.
I will say this, though.
As your brother...
...your other brother who's less related
to you, I officially have your back.
-Thanks, man.
-All right. Let's go. Put your shoes on.
-The bagels are waiting.
-Yes.
I know Trey is the only family
that Ryan has...
...and I think we should help him....
But you're scared I'm gonna want
to adopt him? Honey, don't worry.
Trey is 20 years old and an ex-con.
I don't think he wants to be adopted.
-Don't you think we gotta help?
-We don't know what effect...
...this will have on Ryan.
He's been doing so well.
Morning. You might wanna switch
to a more neutral topic.
-I was just about to get you. You ready?
-Sure.
Look, I appreciate you driving me
down to Chino...
...but this shouldn't
have to be your problem.
Hey, if it's a Ryan problem,
it's a Cohen problem.
-Here you go. For the road.
-Thanks.
Dad, I think I should head down
to prison with you guys...
...and take the day off school.
We all know I've had some,
well, behavioral issues this year...
...and I think prison might be
just the thing to scare me straight.
Nice try. Get to school.
Seth just said that Ryan went
to go pick up Trey from jail.
I wish I could've known.
So you could've gone? The last time
you two went to jail, it didn't go well.
Well, at least I could be there for him.
Coop, you sound extremely
girlfriend-y right now.
I'm just trying to be his friend, which is
the part we skipped over last time.
Besides, Ryan and Trey have
a very complicated relationship.
Speaking of which....
Zach? Oh, my God.
I'm having a panic spiral.
-That's Zach on the Vespa?
-Yeah.
He was in ltaly for so long...
...I assumed he bought a villa
and opened an espresso bar.
-Are you gonna say hello?
-I can't.
I ditched him at the airport
in front of his family.
-Say something. He's coming.
-I'm about to get bitch-slapped.
-Hi, Zach. Welcome back.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-Or, wait:
-How was ltaly?
-Oh, it was amazing.
Probably the best vacation
of my life.
Oh, I'm gonna be late.
Listen, great to see you guys.
Catch up with me at lunch.
I got some awesome pictures.
-Okay.
-Okay. All right.
-Later.
-Cool. Bye.
Somebody totally spiked
that guy's gelato.
I guess you don't have to worry.
He seems pretty okay.
Yeah, a little too okay.
I'm not buying it.
He's hiding something.
Flashback?
-A little bit.
-lt feels like 1 00 years...
...since I got you out of juvie,
doesn't it?
And he's been in here the whole time.
What would you say
if Trey stayed with us?
At least for a little while.
I don't know.
If no one helps him, statistics say
he's back in jail within a year.
Trey's old enough to take care
of himself.
Little brother.
Good to see you, man.
-I'm Sandy Cohen.
-Nice to finally meet you.
-You hungry?
-Starving.
All right. Let's go.
So I think we hold on this shot of
the coast just a bit longer, just until....
-See, into this shot.
-What are you two doing?
Cutting a video for the showcase:
"An lntroduction to Newport Living. "
Your magazine?
The one with you on the cover.
Right, right. I'm sorry. I'm just....
I'm a little distracted.
Kirsten, could I talk to you
for a moment in private?
I'm going to get some air.
I made a mistake, Kiki.
-A naked mistake.
-Excuse me?
A hundred years ago,
a boyfriend convinced me...
...to let him film me in the act.
I was young, living on ramen,
I needed the money.
I told him he could never show it
to anyone or release it...
...which he didn't, until now.
-Unless I give him half a million dollars.
-Did you talk to a lawyer?
Sandy was able to negotiate the rights
from him, but we still need the money.
Well, if Sandy can't help you,
you're gonna have to tell my dad.
This is it.
-Who are you staying with?
-My buddy, Rick.
I think it's his brother's house,
but they said it's cool if I stay there.
Good to see you.
-Take care of yourself.
-Yeah.
-Thanks for lunch again, Mr. Cohen.
-Take care.
I'll call you.
What do you say we give it a try?
Just for a few days.
Hey, Trey!
Wanna come with us?
Hey, man, you came back.
-People never leave and come back.
-Long time no see.
-How you been?
-Good. Dude, things are really good.
Listen, about what happened
with you and me and Summer--
No, no, don't worry about it.
You two belong together.
I should've clued into that a while ago.
Actually, I did clue into that
a while ago.
-Whatever, man. I'm fine with it.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-You seem different.
-You seem like--
-Like I'm vibrating at a high frequency?
-Sure.
-lf I tell you something...
-...do you promise not to tell Summer?
-Yeah, okay.
My track record with secret-keeping
hasn't been that good...
-...but it's gotta turn around sometime.
-Look, man, when I was in ltaly...
...I met someone.
Her name's Francesca.
-Yeah? What's she like?
-Tall. Blond. Gorgeous.
Doesn't speak English,
but she's learning.
When we met, it was, like,
we just clicked.
Are you guys still clicking?
Across the globe?
We've got webcam. We got e-mail.
We got instant-message date.
-Long-distance dating is so hot.
-Do me a favor, all right?
Don't tell Summer. It might hurt her
that I moved on quickly.
Y eah, yeah. My lips are sealed.
-Cool. Great.
-Okay.
Bye.
Well, this is the crib.
You gotta be kidding me.
If it's any consolation, I felt
the same way the first time I saw it.
Bet you get used to it, huh?
Trey, why don't you stay
in the pool house.
-Ryan, you take the guest room.
-Y eah, okay.
Wait. Did he just say pool house?
This is where you've been living?
You got hooked up.
Yeah.
Towels are in the linen closet. You can
borrow whatever shower stuff you need.
Thanks.
And sorry I'm kicking you out
of your little cabana mansion here.
It's only for a few days.
Don't worry.
I won't get too comfortable.
-I'm sorry. I didn't mean--
-I know I'm crashing your party here.
But you got a good thing
going on here...
...and I'm not gonna screw it up.
I promise.
Okay.
-See you later.
Hey, man, I want some details.
Does Trey seem different to you?
I mean, has he found Jesus?
Does he have a Chinese tattoo?
Did he shave his head?
-Oh for 3.
-Oh, hi.
-You're not Ryan.
-Nope. Trey.
Yeah, well, I was close.
You're still an Atwood.
Only a slightly more edgy...
...darker version, I think.
But some people think
Ryan's gotten a little softer--
-Ryan said you talk a lot.
-Yeah, it's a problem.
But hopefully one you'll come
to find endearing.
So how does it, you know,
feel to be...
...Iike, out?
-Good.
-Yeah. Cool.
Monosyllables run in the family.
That's awesome. Hey!
Oh, good. You two have met.
Trey's gonna be staying with us.
Just until I can find my own place.
You might need to go shopping.
This is just to get started.
For clothing, toiletries....
You know, all the basics.
-You sure?
-Of course.
-You can show Trey where to go, right?
-Yeah.
Want me to come? I got a knack for
picking out the post-prison wardrobe.
-You coming?
-Yeah.
Call Marissa. Have her meet us.
-It's a better job for Cosmo Girl.
-Yeah.
Not like you to drop in for lunch.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
With all the hustle and bustle
of this showcase, I've barely seen you.
It's crawfish, your favorite.
I thought we should check in.
Have a state of the union.
Well, sounds fair enough.
What's on the agenda?
We ought to replace the showerhead
in the one guest bathroom upstairs.
Oh, and you really have to fire
that new gardener.
Those are some sorry-looking
hydrangeas out front.
Fine.
Was there anything else?
I made an adult film
in the '80s with an ex-boyfriend...
...who's threatening to release it
unless I pay half a million dollars.
And I really would like
to redo the kitchen.
-Are you saying you did porn?
-lt was erotica. T asteful, at times.
You're in quite a bind.
See, I knew it. I knew that you would
react this way. Absolutely no sympathy.
And this from a man who
kept an illegitimate child hidden--
It's all right. I'll pay the money.
-You will?
-Well, your dignity's at stake.
I'd say that's worth
half a million dollars.
Oh, thank God.
You have no idea how much damage
this could've caused the magazine...
-...and Marissa, me.
-I'll call my financial advisor.
-You should go back to work.
-Right.
Because I have a magazine to launch.
Cal...
...thank you.
-How can Zach act so normal?
-And here we are again.
I ditched him at the airport. It's not what
you'd call letting him down easy.
I'm not certain on this,
but I thought you and I were dating.
I know. I just didn't expect him
to get over me so fast.
Well, Zach's resilient.
Under all that floppy hair and goofy
smile, there's, like, a layer of steel.
You talked to him today, right?
Did he say anything?
Any footnotes
to the whole "l love ltaly" story?
-No. I mean....
-Spill it, Cohen.
He made me promise
to keep it a secret, okay?
-Have you ever kept one?
-He has a girlfriend.
Already? He's only been back,
like, one day.
He met her in ltaly.
Her name's Francesca.
She's tall and beautiful,
and he's way into her, okay? Great.
I say we get burgers
and two vanilla milk shakes and fries.
She's tall?
Two hundred dollars for this watch.
Do you believe that?
-These stores are pricey.
-Yeah.
I bet you got a closet full of this stuff.
Shirts with alligators, topsiders...
...the whole deal.
We should go. You won't find
anything you need here.
You kidding? I got cash to spend.
I'm not going anywhere.
-Hey, I found you.
-Hey, Marissa.
-Trey.
-Hey, Trey.
We've met before. Marissa Cooper.
Oh, yeah. You're Ry's girlfriend.
-Well, no. Well, not anymore.
-Yeah, we're just friends.
Not just friends. But friends. Right?
Right. I heard Ryan was taking you
shopping, so I figured you needed help.
Why don't you try this,
and I'll grab you some more stuff.
-Seth said you might need some backup.
-Yeah. Thanks for coming.
Look at this. Yeah.
This has you written all over it.
Yeah, that looks really adorable
on you. Because you're so cute.
I thought ugly hats were your thing.
It looks really good on you, honestly.
Really?
Yes.
So to my utter shock...
...he agreed to pay in full.
Crisis averted.
Oh, well, I guess my dad's softening
in his old age.
That, or he has a porn tape
buried in his past too.
I'm speaking metaphorically, of course.
Hello? Kiki?
-I'm talking about erotica.
-Oh, I'm sorry. What were you saying?
-You like Carter.
-Excuse me?
You have a thing for Carter.
Kirsten Cohen crushes Carter.
-That's ridiculous.
-I've been so preoccupied...
...with my sex scandal,
I hadn't noticed.
-That's enough.
-Sandy's off in strange motels...
...with that fugitive ex-girlfriend,
so you turn up the heat at the office?
Julie, stop it.
I do not have feelings for--
-Sandy.
-Surprise.
Julie and I were just going over
some magazine stuff.
Launch fever.
Well, I'll let you two talk.
So, what's up?
-I invited Trey to stay for a few days.
-Okay, sounds good.
Sounds good? I thought you were
gonna have a five-alarm freak-out.
Well, I trust you.
I mean, you were right about Ryan,
after all.
I'll see you tonight.
Hey, now where's this famous
Carter Buckley? I'd love to meet him.
Oh, tonight....
It's-- It's not a good time.
He's up....
Up to his ears in the launch.
All right, well, some other time then.
I'll see you tonight.
Man, am I tired.
That's shopper's fatigue. Shop enough,
and you'll become immune. Trust me.
If anyone should know.
-Excuse me.
-That's funny.
Can I check your bag?
Why? I didn't do anything wrong.
-I saw you handling that watch before.
-I didn't take your damn watch.
We have the right to look.
Hand it over.
I don't see you giving
other people a hard time.
-He didn't take anything.
-Let him check.
Hey, man, I'll handle this.
-Get out of my face.
-Send someone to the front entrance.
Yeah? You know what?
Don't bother.
Because I paid for all of this!
If we hadn't gotten Trey out of the
store, he would've taken the guy out.
So he's got rage issues like....
-Like Summer, or--?
-He's just got a lot of pride, you know.
When something sets him off,
it's like he can't control himself.
Well, it's comforting
to have him staying here.
-Have you told my parents?
-No, I can't.
I know I should, but....
Oh, hey, Ryan.
I finally met your brother.
-He seems to be adjusting well.
-Y eah, smooth sailing.
Well, here's one.
A barista at a local coffee joint.
-Barista?
-That's a fancy word...
-...for a guy who makes coffee.
-That I can do.
We were just checking out
the classifieds.
Yeah. The job hunt begins today.
-Feel like coming with me?
-I'll pass, thanks.
Seth, why don't you come out and clear
the patio furniture with me for the party.
I believe, son, that's code
for "let's get out of here. "
If I help set up for the party,
will you let me skip it?
That would be a no.
I'm sorry about yesterday. I just didn't
like the way the guy was looking at me.
So you trashed the store.
Look, my old ways aren't
gonna work here. I need to change.
Do it soon.
-Zach.
-Hey.
I brought over some of your stuff.
-Things you left at my house.
-Post-breakup stuff exchange.
I won this for you
at the Kickoff Carnival. It was a gift.
I'll always remember how you owned
that Whack-a-Mole.
I don't feel like it's a good idea
to have reminders of you around.
I get that you've moved on,
but do you have to totally erase me?
What do you mean, moved on?
-Cohen.
-He let it slip, okay?
I just didn't want you to know,
in case it hurt your feelings.
Why would it hurt me?
Just because 20 minutes
after we broke up...
...you were scootering around ltaly
with a 6-foot-2 Euro-chick?
-Hey, you left me.
-I know. I know that, but....
The cast of The Valley are guest VJs on
Music Video Nation. I have to see that.
-I'll drop off your stuff soon.
-Wait!
Well, how do you like this?
Caleb Nichol showing up
in my lowly hotel room.
Let's get this over with.
Thank you.
The video's right here. It's all yours
if the money's in that case.
Five hundred thousand. As requested.
I'm assured this is the only copy?
This is it.
So...
...how's it feel to get a little glimpse
into your wife's past?
I didn't get where I am today
by being a fool.
I knew what I was getting
into when I married Julie.
You expect me to believe
she told you?
Because Julie keeps her past
pretty tight to the vest.
I have some very thorough
and talented Pls on my staff.
I'd venture to say there's nothing Julie's
ever done that I don't know about.
Allow me.
-What the hell is this?
-Some friends of mine...
-...who want to get to know you.
-You son of a bitch.
That's your cue to hand me
the briefcase.
Lance.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Thanks for the tape.
I'd like those flowers delivered by 5.
Thank you.
What do you think for tonight?
I want Donatella-Versace-meets-
Martha-Stewart-before-the-scandal.
Don't look now.
Boyfriend, 2 o'clock.
Hey. I brought you something.
Pinot Noir. Russian River Valley.
-Hi. The one you said you loved.
-Hey.
-Thank you. How thoughtful.
-I thought we'd pop the top...
...have a few glasses
before the madness.
We have a lot riding on this.
I think it would be unprofessional
to drink wine beforehand.
Are you kidding? We average a bottle
a night around here.
You can celebrate at the party tonight.
Okay. Y eah, okay. I'll....
I'll see you later.
Completely focused and totally sober.
Kirsten and Carter
Sitting in a tree
I' m just kidding. Unless l' m not.
K-I-S-S-I-N-G
Summer. I thought we'd seen
the last of you.
-ls Zach home?
-He's at water polo practice.
-He'll be home in a few minutes.
-Can I leave this with you?
He left it at my house
when we were dating.
So it's really over
between the two of you?
Mrs. Stevens, I am so sorry about
what happened at the airport.
You should be.
But at least something good
came out of it. Right?
-I mean, Zach met Francesca.
-Who?
You know, 6-foot-2 ltalian supermodel.
Zach's new girlfriend.
And when would this have happened?
While he was sulking over you?
He never left the hotel room, Summer.
Hey.
How'd the job hunt go today?
Not so good.
I tried five or six places...
...all turned me down on the spot.
That sucks.
You hungry? We could grab a bite.
Catch up.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Cool.
We should head by the pier. You'll like it.
They've got, you know, boats and stuff.
After you clean this place up.
Jeez, man. We do have closets,
you know.
Yeah, who's funny?
-This is from that store.
-I went back and bought it.
Don't lie to me.
I'm not.
You're never gonna change.
This family is taking a chance
on you, Trey.
You know what?
It makes no difference what I say.
You'll believe the worst,
no matter what I do.
-You blame me?
-I guess I don't.
Why don't I do us both a favor
and take off?
Fine!
Oh, and I bought it as a gift for you.
To thank you for helping me out. And
before you go calling the cops on me...
...here's the receipt.
Well, the party's starting soon.
Are you hiding out in here?
-Yeah, good guess.
-Where's Trey?
Oh, I see. Well...
-...we knew it was gonna be bumpy.
-Yeah.
-This is harder than I thought it'd be.
-ls there anything I can do?
Hey, can I borrow the car?
Be careful.
Zach. Hey.
I realized, I forgot to give
your sweatshirt back. I was going to--
-I know you talked to my mom today.
-Brief conversation. Brief.
And I know she told you
about Francesca. Or lack thereof.
-You don't need to explain.
-No, I do.
When I came home, I knew that
I was going to see you and Cohen.
And I didn't want things
to be tense between us.
And I figured the only way to do that
was if I was with someone too.
Zach, I'm sorry.
And you told Cohen because...
-...you knew it would get back to me.
-Within minutes.
God, that is so typical of Cohen.
-He knew it would make me jealous.
-Summer, remember, she's a fake.
Yeah, but still. Cohen could not wait
to tell me...
-...about your smoking new girlfriend--
-This is between you and Cohen.
Which has nothing to do with me...
...finally.
Look, Zach...
...I am so sorry that
I made a mess of everything.
As for Francesca,
unlike some loudmouth geeks...
...I can keep a secret.
-Hey, Ryan, where you going?
-T o get Trey. He took off.
Well, I'll go with you.
Remember the last time
you came to Chino?
Yeah, I saved your ass. Come on.
Do you realize that in a couple of days,
your face will be...
...on every coffee table in this town?
Frankly, I'm surprised
we even got it off the ground.
-Well, I'm not surprised at all.
-Hi, Dad.
I know this magazine is going to be
an enormous success.
-Absolutely.
-I take it everything went smoothly?
Everything's taken care of, Juju.
Hey, you made it. I was starting
to get worried. Thank you.
Well, I came for Newport Living.
I do live in Newport.
Is that what this party's for?
I didn't....
-What's the deal? Is it something I said?
-Something you weren't supposed to say.
Right. I guess I did something wrong...
-...so I should probably just apologize.
-Well, yeah, if you mean it.
That's hard if I don't know what it is.
It's hard to forgive you
if you don't mean it...
...because you don't know
why you're apologizing.
I'll wait in your room for 20 minutes. If
you can't figure it out by then, I'm gone.
-Hello, everybody. Julie, congratulations.
-Thank you.
-May I speak with you for a moment?
-Sure.
-What is it?
-Have I said something to you?
Have I done something wrong?
Because all day,
you have seemed angry at me.
Look, whatever it is,
I hope you can talk to me about it.
We are liable to be working together
for a long time. So I don't want to--
On second thought,
let's just focus on the presentation.
I hope it goes without a hitch.
-Excuse me. Is that chardonnay?
-Yes, ma'am, it is.
Thank you.
We used to hang out
at this place all the time.
There he is.
Yeah. I'll be back in a second.
What the hell are you doing here, man?
-I came to find you.
-I'm not looking to be found.
-Trey, listen--
-Beat it, little brother.
-I just want to talk to you, all right?
-Why? You're in your pool house and....
-And I'm here.
-I'm sorry, all right.
Why are we kidding ourselves here, Ry?
You knew it couldn't work.
We are who we are.
I'm not going back
to Newport without you.
Fine.
Stay here. See how well you fit in
after being away two years.
I'm gonna go out and get some air.
Okay, I thought about it.
I thought about why you're angry.
-And?
-I have nothing.
I do not know what I did wrong.
But listen, I am totally willing
to apologize. Extremely sincerely.
Why did you tell me about Francesca?
Because you begged me to.
That is not why. I have begged you
to do plenty of stuff.
Like give up comics, stop mumbling.
You don't do any of that.
Are you actually angry with me for being
jealous of you being jealous of Zach?
No.
-You were jealous?
-Gee, why would that be, Summer?
Hearing you go on and on
about Zach's new woman.
-Because you told me about her.
-Yeah, I did.
I saw the high road there, and I did
not take it. You wanna know why?
I was a little bit worried.
Here we had this big, great kiss in
the rain upside down, and I don't know.
I thought maybe, what if after that
everything was a letdown for you.
You had buyer's remorse or something.
Cohen...
-...you are so neurotic.
-Exactly.
Unlike Zach, who's anxiety-free,
with his big smile...
...and natural athleticism.
-That guy makes me feel very Jewish.
-I know Zach looks great on paper.
Son of a congressman,
sweet, selfless....
-Hey, and even, well, boring.
-Yeah, he's a touch bland.
And you, with all your little flaws
and your little quirks...
...somehow you keep
drawing me back in.
Yeah? So, what you're saying
to me is then...
...that the more neurotic
and insecure I am...
...the more you're attracted to me.
Well, then. Do I look fat in these pants?
Hello, everyone. I'm Carter Buckley,
managing editor.
And on behalf of everyone
at Newport Living...
... I'd like to thank you all
for coming tonight.
Now I would like to introduce the woman
who has made all of this possible.
Julie Cooper-Nichol.
Thank you, Carter.
I can't believe this night is finally here.
Well, what is Newport Living?
-Wow, so that's Carter Buckley.
-You haven't met him yet?
No. He's been more of a phantom
presence. I thought he'd look...
-...more like Jerry Garcia.
-Who?
But if you really want to know
what Newport Living is all about...
...take a look at this.
If I've never had sex before...
... why do I feel so horny?
- You 're turning me on.
-Dear God.
-Oh, my God.
-Give me the remote.
Come over here, pizza boy.
Give me that.
-You son of a bitch.
-Sorry about that, everyone.
T echnical difficulties.
Please, everyone help themselves
to a drink or two.
Lord knows, I'm going to.
Don't worry, Juju.
It'll all blow over.
I don't understand. I mean,
you gave him his damn money.
It just goes to show,
it doesn't pay to give in to these people.
You meet their every demand,
and they ruin you anyway.
Well, ruin's the wrong word.
You can go on with your life, Cal,
but I am never leaving this room.
My Howard Hughes phase starts now.
We could go to Europe.
Paris, Vienna, anywhere you like.
By the time we get back...
...something else will have exploded
to make this whole thing look silly.
I guess you can always count on
this town for a new scandal.
Paris?
Carter. Sandy Cohen.
You throw a hell of a party.
-It's great to finally meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry I haven't introduced
you two.
Oh, no problem. You sound like
you have a wonderful family.
I do. Including my mother-in-law,
the porn star.
If it makes you feel better,
I think it livened things up.
Here's hoping everyone
was drunk enough...
...they black out and
don't remember anything tomorrow.
Here's hoping.
Can I get you two anything?
-Thanks. I'm good.
-No, thanks, I'm fine.
All right.
Listen. About before...
-...I have to apologize.
-You do?
Yeah, you know, we have been working
together for a few weeks now...
...and I just want you to know...
...that if there has been a tension
between us....
I don't know
what you're talking about.
If there's been a vibe between us...
...it's me, okay. And I'm sorry.
-Carter--
-Let's just leave it at that, all right?
Ryan, I don't think he's coming back.
All right. Let's go.
We should go find him.
Hey, feel like playing some pool?
-No, thanks.
-Then let me buy you a drink.
-I don't think she wants anything.
-Was I talking to you?
We should get out of here.
I want to buy you a drink.
Why you being rude?
-I don't want anything.
-Leave her alone.
Listen, rich boy.
I ain't buying the act, all right?
-Let's get out of here.
-Hey, hey! Let go of her.
Come on, you want some more?
Stop it, please!
Can I help you? Let's dance!
-Tell them to let go of my brother.
-Take it easy.
Let him go.
-Wild kid!
-I haven't done that in a while.
-You looked good.
-Thanks for coming back for us.
Yeah, well, I was gonna say
the same thing to you guys.
You want a ride?
-Yeah, sure.
-Well, where are we dropping you?
Just come home with us, man.
-Thought you didn't want me over there.
-Yeah, well, people change.
All right.
-But I get to drive.
-Oh, no, no.
I've seen you drive. Back seat.
I'll drive.
-Hey.
You guys were gone a while.
Everything okay?
-Fine.
-Yeah, nothing to report.
-How was the party?
-Good.
Uneventful.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-Great party, okay?
-Well...
...if you're hungry, we got leftovers.
Look, Dad, we're all having
a family dinner.
Well, how about that? Look at that.
Now, this is not so painful.
-Gotta tell you, it seems pretty great.
-Y eah...
...wait till the novelty wears off,
right, Ryan?
You know what? It still works for me.
That's very obli--
-Come on, young man.
-These ones are really good.