Previously on "The Shield"...
Teenage resident Lloyd Denton...
he's our shooter.
There's speculation bundy's first murders
were committed in his early teens.
Are you saying
this kid's a serial killer?
This guy's all I've got.
I'm targeting Cruz Pezuela.
Aceveda's one-man
campaign bankroll?
He's buying up Farmington
with cartel money.
Blackmail... that's how Pezuela's getting
everyone on board the train to cartel town.
Where's our blackmail box?
I am in possession of the box
until the time to turn
it over to justice.
What about the files?
The armenians are making a hard
play for your barrio sand box.
This piece of shit Rezian has taken
something that belongs to me.
You want to give me a clue
what all this is about?
The mexis are using to blackmail
their way up to the top.
And you made it look like this
prick sold out to the armos.
Which lit the fuse for
the blood feud we're stirring up
between Rezian and the Mexicans.
We need a quick Armenian political win.
Give me the name,
I'll put it in play.
The city controller...
Robert Martin.
He's in the blackmail box?
Robert, oh, my God!
I need a medic!
Their march turns
into a goddamn killing.
That was never part
of the plan.
Martin was my colleague, Vic.
I did not sign up for this!
Detective Mackey,
amando rios.
Amando will speak for me.
Give me a name,
and I'll run with it.
Rios isn't just some beaner.
He's got a face
only a cartel could love.
If rios gets spooked, we lose
our best shot at Pezuela.
Never heard of him.
David Aceveda,
federal agent Olivia Murray.
That fed in the Clubhouse...
I thought I'd seen her name
somewhere before.
She's in the blackmail box?
Pezuela got her
in his pocket.
How much have
you told her?
Enough to get us
both killed.
www.1000fr.com presents...
You look like shit.
I'm supposed to get
a minute's sleep
knowing Olivia could have
ratted us out to Pezuela???
Just because Olivia has been
Pezuela's eyes and ears
doesn't mean she's been
passing along the intel
we've been feeding her.
Do you think
she's holding on to it,
maybe use it
against Pezuela herself?
She's up to her manhole
in shit lake.
That's what I'ddo.
Dangerous part for us, though,
is not knowing.
You two work closely.
Did he have enemies downtown?
A city this size with the money
and powerat stake?
But at the end of the day,
Robert was a glorified accountant...
not a very sexy target.
And your people
didn't see anything?
Heard shots, and then
it was complete chaos.
Why was your team deployed
there in the first place?
Detective Vendrell has been
working with an Armenian C.I.
Who's given us a couple
of wins recently.
We've been hearing
some chatter
that there's been some, uh,
Armenian-Mexican friction.
So your assessment... this is organized-
crime syndicates squaring off?
Martin was clearly the target,
and there's not a banger out therewith
a merit badge for marksmanship.
Have to wonder if those shots
weren't meant for Mr. Aceveda...
you being a mayoral
candidate now.
Uh, Vic, do you...
do you have any change?
This kouf guy's becoming a real
rock Star in the department.
With him leading the investigation now
and our involvement,
this could all blow back on us.
Take a deep,
cleansing breath.
Neither one of us had anything
to do with that shooting,
by word or deed.
We damn sure know
who's responsible.
- When you've got a minute...
- sure.
And the slightest whisper
of impropriety
is a political career ender.
Do you know how much
she's told Pezuela?
I'll handle her...
but it's got to be gently.
Your problem is, you're trying
to have it both ways.
You want to take down Pezuela,
win a landslide as a reformer,
but not until he pays
all your bills.
Oh, sorry.
I only got 50 cents,
and you're about a dollar.
What's up, buttercup?
Got a situation I could use
a little help on.
Ask, and you shall.
I need to run it by your captain first,
make sure it's kosher.
Then I'll hit you
with the details.
Uh, anything come back
on the intel I gave you?
Nothing so far.
Hope it wasn't
a bum steer.
Not like you to be
off the money.
Okay, well,
give me a shout...
it gets you
to that bigger fish.
You'll be the first to know,
believe me.
I got to go.
Olivia needs us to backstop
her on something.
I'm waiting on the details.
Am I, uh...
am I missing something?
Olivia's carrying water
for Pezuela.
She's in the box of sins.
What?
Her brother got jammed up
with some mob bookies.
Pezuela got wind somehow,
got proof.
Could explain why she's become a fact of life
around here all of a sudden.
This prick owns a federal agent
who's up our ass, collecting intel.
You boys gonna let me
in on this?
I just found out myself.
We're still not sure about
the size of Pezuela's hook.
Well, it's pretty goddamn clear
what we need to do.
We'll give the box to Rezian so that
the armenians can return it to Pezuela,
and he lays off.
Not yet.
Are you not understanding
that this master plan of yours is backfiring?
Rezian still has our families
in the crosshairs.
Now Pezuela has sicced
a fed on us.
I understand the situation.
Return the box and get credit
for brokering a peace deal.
Our money train debt
is paid in full.
Now, explain to me how that is not
in all of our best interests.
Another time.
King rat's gaytan echevarria...
cuban, Miami-based.
He's visiting I.a.
Doing what?
He's meeting Martin blez,
number-two denim manufacturer
in the world.
Echevarria's looking to clean
his drug benjamins
by plowing them into
a legit biz... blue jeans.
So, how does the
strike team fit in?
Echevarria's daughter, noelle...
freshman at s.c.
She got carjacked this morning
at 8th and hoover.
Three black males
ordered her boyfriend
out of the car at gunpoint,
drove off with the girl.
Our surveillance picked up the boyfriend
telling her old man what happened.
That neighborhood,
it's probably gang-related.
Hence the strike team.
With his daughter missing,
echevarria's not focused
on business.
Bad guys love
their kids, too.
This meeting with blez
is our one opportunity
to take down
the whole network.
It doesn't make,
a high-dollar 18-month investigation
goes out the window.
So you need the strike team
to find the missing girl
so daddy will get back
to the dirty business.
Without tipping echevarria
the police are involved.
He hasn't reported
the kidnapping.
Our surveillance intel has got him using
his own muscle to find her.
Taking matters
into his own hands...
could get a lot
of people hurt.
He knows law enforcement's involved
and he didn't drop the dime,
he'll figure out
he's being watched.
Description of
the echevarria girl's car.
Not like we can put out
an apb
if we need to keep this
on the down low.
My best recommend is start
with the local chop shops.
See if anyone's trying
to unload her nissan.
Let's pull all the files on car thefts
for the last six months...
suspects, arrest records,
similar m.o.s.
Got it.
Your surveillance come up
with any intel
on the kind of muscle
echevarria's traveling with?
Four guys... cuban and jamaican,
armed, long list of crimes.
When's this meet with denim dude
supposed to go down?
Blez's jet gets
into Van nuys around 6:00,
assuming our cuban
doesn't cancel the meet.
That doesn't give us
a lot of time.
Let me say it again...
echevarria gets a whiff
of police anywhere near this,
he will get spooked
and bolt.
Understood.
You drop the bomb that Olivia
is in Pezuela's blackmail box.
Now she's walking us
into a sketchy case
with out-of-town players.
You think
she's setting us up?
We got to assume she's gonna
give Pezuela a heads-up.
Maybe he decides
to strike first.
Or maybe you're just
being paranoid
and this is exactly
what she says it is...
a random street crime that could possibly
wreck a high-profile I.c.E. Collar.
Either way,
we got to watch our backs.
I pulled the most
recent 10851s.
Chop shop on manzanita specializes
in stolen parts for Japanese street racers.
We'll start there.
Ride with me.
We didn't get a chance to finish
our earlier conversation.
You were about to explain
what's more important
than keeping
our families safe.
Nothing.
Settle this beef between
the armos and the mexis.
Just let Pezuela have
whatever it is that he wants.
Just get us off
the hook already.
I can't do that.
If you think you're gonna
use this box
to squeeze your way into keeping
some detective career...
Iook, I-I don't have to remind
you of all the bad shit
we've been responsible for.
You're the one
who wrote it all down.
Well, that was
"bad shit volume I."
The next installment has Ronnie
doing Zadofian's murder.
Since we're being honest
about things,
it means we're all
blood brothers now.
Pezuela's a scorpion.
He can and will
unleash a level of violence
and corruption in Farmington
that'll turn this place
into little Mexico city.
I can't let that happen.
I don't trust anyone else
to stop him,
- including robbery-homicide.
- If it's not Pezuela shitting on the streets,
it's going to be
some other asshole!
Putting Pezuela away
is a down payment
on me being able to live
with myself.
Now, if you can't
understand that,
at least respect it.
Sync: Vine
Dutch,
I got a call from beth insardi
wanting to know
if I was deliberately
ducking the subpoenas
on the Kleavon Gardner trial,
subpoenas which you
have been intercepting.
I want to know why.
- Captain, you've been busy...
- it was my fault.
Uh, Danny was just following
my instructions.
Give us a minute.
Apparently, Kleavon is defending
himself prose in his murder trial.
And I-I just didn't think
you need the stress
of being drawn
into that circus.
Because of my illness?
Your last encounter with him
landed you facedown
on the stairs and in the hospital.
Does Danny know why you had her
running interference for me?
Of course not.
Cops duck subpoenas
all the time.
As far as she's concerned,
we were sparing you some
unnecessary aggravation.
I can handle my own affairs.
This guy's had it in for you
from the beginning.
He killed a woman
who looked like you
just to make his point.
I want this prick to get
the justice he deserves,
and if it means
giving a deposition...
Kleavon is a confessed serial killer
facing the death penalty.
What better way to spend
his final days
than lobbing shitballs
at you?
Let's not humor him.
He's coming in this afternoon.
I'll get it over with.
Fine.
See if this guy's
part of the chop shop.
Yo!
We got a rabbit.
Watch it!
Ronnie, get in front of him.
We're moving to intercept.
Get out of the car!
Let me see your hands!
- Get out!
- Get down!
Get down!
Don't move.
"Llewellyn wang"?
Farmington grand prix
means you know why we're here.
I had nothing to do
with it, man.
I ain't never even heard
of this missing chick.
Where's the girl?
I don't know.
And neither did
those dead homies,
but those gusanos
kacked them, anyway!
You lost me.
We was kicking it.
I went out back
to take a leak,
and that's when the shit
jumped off.
What kind of shit?
Four caribbean dudes
showed up,
started sweating everybody
about some cuban girl they're looking for.
My friends were like, "what
the hell you talking about?!"
Dudes went at 'em
with knives and shit!
You're gonna take us to where
this gangster party went down.
They're back there.
Vic.
Zorro wannabe?
From this angle,
I'm reading an "n."
Missing girl's name
was noelle.
They weren't wishing him
an early merry Christmas.
We're on the record
in the matter of people
vs. Kleavon kwame Gardner.
The witness
has been sworn in.
All parties present
have been advised
that this deposition
is being videotaped.
Please state your name.
Claudette Wyms.
Would you describe your
relationship to the defendant?
I investigated the murders
you committed
and arrested you for them.
When you say I committed
these murders,
what you are expressing
is a personal,
very biased opinion.
Enjoy this charade
while you can,
because you are gonna be
sentenced to death
for the murders
of pauline walker,
Mary simpson, lana gregory,
and all those women you killed
back in texas.
Did you interrogate
any other suspects besi...
I didn't have to.
So you made up your mind
from the jump,
which means that this so-called
investigation
is really just an exercise
in closed-mindedness.
Mr. Gardner,
the purpose of a deposition
is to ask questions,
not put words in the witness's mouth.
I'm just trying to see
how she developed this theory,
accusing a black man,
when everybody knows
that serial murder
is a white man's crime.
Shade's got nothing to do
with it.
The evidence pointed overwhelmingly
to you and only you,
and let's not forget,
you confessed...
we've got it on videotape.
Are you currently taking
any prescribed medication?
Don't answer.
That's completely irrelevant.
Have you ever seen
this before?
Let the record show I'm holding
a prescription bottle
recovered from a trash barrel
at miss Wyms' home.
Label reads...
"corticosteroid,
"60 milligrams, 3 refills.
Patient's name...
Claudette Wyms."
You son of a bitch.
Echevarria's crew...
conducting a q&a about
his missing little girl.
What's the next move?
Ronnie and Julien
are out
talking to the local shot
callers on the d. I...
Los mags, One-Niners,
spook street.
There's a "get out
of jail free" card
for anyone who dimes
the missing car.
I just hollered at a buddy
in robbery-homicide...
third carjacking in a month
involving sexual assault.
So, m.o. Is,
they steal a fresh whip,
take it and mommy
for a joyride.
Every boy's dream twofer.
I.c.E. Surveillance capture
any of this on videotape?
They're focused
on echevarria.
All you should be thinking about
right now is finding this girl.
Hey, darling,
I don't need you or anybody else
managing my thought process.
Uh, think maybe we should have
a talk with Deena?
Doesn't feel like her stilo.
No, but grand theft auto...
she knows all the players,
and we need all the information
we can get.
We'll be in touch.
Deena!
Put the gun down!
Drop the gun!
Drop the gun,
God damn it!
You stupid bitch!
God damn it, Deena!
Sorry.
Were you taking
this steroid medication
at the time
of my interrogation?
You are way over the line.
Goes to her
state of mind.
My reading of the law books
says that this is relevant.
Were you on drugs
at the time
of this alleged confession
you mentioned?
Please keep in mind,
you are under oath.
I need a bathroom break.
Hmm, not surprising.
Frequent urination is one
of the less dangerous side effects.
Claudette?
Okay, okay.
You need to shut this down
right now.
He's entitled
to conduct discovery.
What is she on meds for?
You need to talk toher
about that.
How serious?
She doesn't need
her medical history
to become an issue
for the department.
I could get the judge
to seal the transcripts.
They'll be unsealed
when this goes to trial,
used to attack her credibility
in all cases.
And that's our system,
isn't it?
Who is this guy?
Just a guy I've been
working with lately.
Accomplice,
in other words.
I came back from a run,
and I found him like that.
Busted out the shotgun
when I heard you rolling up.
I did say sorry, right?
The people responsible are
looking for a silver nissan 300.
You know anybody who traffics
in a load like that?
Could have been anyone.
There's a lot of
demand for Jap cars.
The jackers have been
targeting females.
They grab the car,
help themselves to the cooch.
You know anyone who rolls
like that?
Ghost town piru's been boosting
for initiation lately.
So has hollis lane.
I liked him.
He could have been
the one.
We were talking about getting
out of the game.
I'd think about sticking
to that plan, even without him.
You became quite ill during
my interrogation,
as I recall... disoriented,
unsteady on your feet.
It was not serious.
Well, you started bleeding
heavily from your nose.
Had to leave the room.
I saw you fall down
a flight of stairs,
or don't you
remember that?
60 milligrams...
that's a high dosage
of a very powerful drug.
You're not
a medical expert.
Well, I'm not a lawyer,
either,
but the court says I'm competent
enough to argue my case.
Are you aware some
of the side effects
of long-term
steroid use include
confusion, hallucination,
paranoia, psychosis?
Do you suffer from any
of these side effects?
No.
Just before you had
taken ill,
before the blood started
pouring out of your nose,
you had told me
that my sister Fatima...
I'm reading
from the transcript here...
was found "strangled and dumped
in an alley."
But that wasn't the case,
was it?
It's a standard
interview tactic
used to mislead a suspect
with disinformation
in order to get the truth.
Was that a tactic,
or were you
having a hallucination?
Because I saw Fatima downstairs
a little while later.
What you're doing is more
prejudicial than probative.
I don't know
what that means.
It means that you're gonna stop
this irresponsible line of questioning.
I was told by this woman
that my sister had been murdered.
I was overcome with grief.
I might have said some things
I didn't mean
because I wasn't
in my right mind.
Now, if my emotional distress
was caused
by a mentally disturbed person
on drugs,
that's something the jury
needs to know.
You attack my credibility
all you want.
It still won't get you off,
not with all the other evidence
we got against you.
Evidence collected by a heavily
medicated police detective in a station...
now under the command
of that same paranoid,
delusional psychotic who's now
been promoted tocaptain.
You've got to ask yourself
how credible that evidence really is.
Can we go off the record?
You are putting on
quite a show.
Thank you.
You think you're gonna get
acquitted?
Think again.
You're gonna go down for
those murders, no matter what!
Might as well take some folks
down with me... or not.
- It all depends.
- On what?
I want the death penalty
off the table.
You drag me through the mud
all you want.
I'm gonna live
to watch you die.
If word of your unstable
mental condition gets loose,
they'll have you
out the door faster
than you can say
"Mark fuhrman."
Job you're in...
it's all about credibility.
You deserve the same fate
as all those women
you put in the ground.
I'm a different man now,
fallen in love with a woman
that I've been in correspondence
with since my incarceration.
I'm looking forward to spending the rest
of my natural life with her.
Even more reason to put you down
like a sick animal
now that you got
something to lose.
Another potty break?
You're not gonna cave in
to this stunt!
The slightest whiff
of doubt,
juries back off of capital
punishment in a heartbeat.
- There is no doubt.
- He's got a story.
- That's all that matters.
- Don't do this, beth.
It's not your call to make.
I got to use your phone,
run this past the bosses.
Lyor chotzen
left a message.
He'll meet you
at Los perditos.
Thanks.
Chotzen...
the FBI profiler that worked the
Kleavon Gardner case for you?
Yeah.
With Kleavon
back in the house,
got me thinking
I should talk to chotzen
about the Lloyd denton
shooting.
We already went
at that brat once.
You keep hauling him
in here,
his mom's gonna figure out
you suspect him
as Jack the ripper Jr.
That's where you're wrong.
I'm not trying to arrest
the kid.
I'm just trying
to help him.
You want to beat a dead horse,
do your thing.
I got enough paperwork
to wipe my ass for a year.
Vic, did you sign
that document for me?
The, uh, quit claim
on paternity for Lee.
Oh, I haven't had a chance
to read it.
Could you make the time?
My lawyer wants to file it
by the end of the week.
What's the rush?
I just want to get
it done, okay?
What now?
Cassidy's been suspended
from school.
I give up.
Suspended? For what?
She and her friends were
at some "pimps 'n ho's" party.
All the girls had
to wear lingerie.
Pimps 'n ho's?
Yeah, some kid posted
their pictures on the internet.
These girls were dressed
in their underwear,
traipsing around
in front of the boys.
- It was revolting.
- Where's cass now?
Home.
There were drugs involved.
Jesus Christ.
She wouldn't even
have admitted it to me
if I didn't threaten to drag
her here for a urine test.
What kind of drugs?
Ecstasy.
She claims it was
her first time.
Who gave them to her?
She won't tell me.
I just don't know
what else to do.
I sure as hell do.
Who organized this party?
I'm not sure, but I spoke to one
of the other mothers,
and she said it was at this boy
mickey dightman's house.
There are pictures of him
on the same website,
and he's smoking a joint.
All right, listen,
I got this.
I'll call you later, okay?
Intentional or not, that was live ammo
Deena directed our way.
There's no way Olivia
could have orchestrated that.
So if Deena would have blown
our brains out,
that would have just
been dumb luck?
This cuban's
one-day body count
is gonna cut our car-theft
numbers in half,
but I want him in custody
or on a plane back to Miami.
You need to decide
how much collateral damage
you're willing to accept
to preserve this I.c.E. Investigation.
Well, the sooner we get
the missing girl,
the sooner the streets
settle down.
Ticktock.
Hey, Vic, unis
just took a statement
from a domestic victim
up in observation.
We should follow up.
Uh, couples counseling isn't
on my to-do list right now.
Her boyfriend is a gangbanger...
priors for car theft.
And he was bragging to someone
about running a train on some latina.
What set's
the b.f. Claiming?
Ghost town piru.
I can take a beat-down,
about as tough as any bitch.
But I'm done!
This nigger came home
smelling like badussy.
I ask him,
"what's up with that?"
He talking about
imust be on crack.
Only then I hear him
loud talking to his boy
about how they was running
the old alabama anaconda
up in ol' girl
all day long.
Happen to mention
if "ol' girl" was cuban?
Cuban, Mexican...
it's all reggaeton to me.
I told him, "you think a sister
gonna be 'bout it, 'bout it"
when he got taco stank up
on his black ass?
Think again.
Gave me the fist.
Girl's got to draw
the line somewhere.
Any idea where he is
right now?
He's probably at his job.
He work around the way,
you know, stealing cars.
I've been dreaming about tacos
for the last two weeks...
hard to come by
in beijing.
You over there on vacation?
Paid consultant
to the people's republic of.
37 dead females
autopsied premortem.
Chinese law enforcement
is strangely proud
to finally have one of their own
up on the world stage,
alongside John wayne gacy
and andrei chikatilo.
What's the profile?
Organized killer,
male, 20s.
With a billion Chinese,
you're looking for a needle dick
in a haystack.
What about you?
I got a suspect...
kid, shot an intruder.
You wouldn't be talking
to me
if you thought it was
a one-time thing.
It's not something I want
to be wrong about.
He's 16, no obvious
killer symptoms.
What about the obvious
precursors?
No arson,
cruelty to animals,
or bed-wetting
that I know about.
What's got your antennae
twitching?
I think he killed him
just to kill,
and if he can do that at 16,
what's he gonna be doing at 25?
Want me to talk to him?
Prove me right,
prove me wrong...
I just need to know
what I'm dealing with.
Don't let him know
you're a cop.
I need him to think that I've moved off
the criminal investigation.
You bet.
So, what, are you gonna show me
those ink-blotch things...
ask me what I see?
If you want.
Mostly, I'm here to listen.
I sat in this room
for like 97 hours,
answering the same questions
over and over and over again.
I'm... I'm pretty
talked out.
That was
a police investigation.
This is an opportunity
for you
to conduct one of your own...
into your feelings.
I'm gonna give you some room,
keep your mom company.
Can I, uh, get you anything
to drink... water, tea?
Oh, no, thank you.
I wonder if I should be
up there with him.
Uh, this kind of
therapy works best
when you're talking
to a stranger.
It's easier to vent
those feelings
to a blank screen
rather than to someone
who knows everything
about you.
Makes sense. I don't know the first
thing about psychiatrists.
How's, uh, how's Lloyd been
doing since all this happened?
Surprisingly well,
under the circumstances.
Not acting out,
anger, depressed?
Oh, no.
Has he wet his bed...
anything like that?
No, my son is 16.
The only reason I ask is,
sometimes,
the body wants to rid
negative feelings
the same way it does
other waste products.
Well, no, Lloyd's never had
that problem.
How long is he going
to be up there?
All these shrinks seem to think
an hour's 50 minutes long, so...
well, maybe I will
have that tea.
Silver nissan 300
parked inside.
Three guys downstairs,
one guy up in a loft,
poking on something.
I'm guessing that's our girl.
All right, Ronnie, nice work.
Come on down.
Kick down the door,
go in guns drawn, badges out,
noelle's gonna know it was
the police to the rescue.
And so will her big pa.
That's why we got to make it
look like a robbery
by a rival gang... choreograph
it so the girl escapes.
No disrespect, but the only set
you guys can claim is aryan nation.
No, I got an idea...
only I'm gonna need you
to sell it to Claudette.
Coming from any of us,
it'll be a no-go.
Done.
It's questionable tactics,
high risk to my personnel
andcivilians.
The fresh hell
you're proposing
must have come
from the mind of Mackey.
This operation's got a high
degree of difficulty.
We are running out of time,
and I don't have a better idea.
I sign off on this insanity,
- here are my terms.
- Bring the pain.
Echevarria's hit squad gets charged here
in Farmington ahead of any federal case.
I need a win after the shit rain
these bastards caused today.
Okay.
And any blowback
from Vic Mackey's
voodoo law enforcement is on you.
How I'm supposed to trust you after the
shit you pulled with my escalade?
You want to feel those fine leather
seats on your ass again or not?
No one's gonna see
your face.
You won't have to wear
your own colors.
No one except the people
in this room
will know
you were involved.
It's bad enough we down
with one time,
but taking flight
on a band of brothers...
spare me
the pan-Africa bullshit.
You guys are out there killing
each other all day, every day.
You get a little taste
of black pussy...
now you're an expert
on Africa?
Streets is watching, homey.
We're supposed to be
strapped, right?
You can take your own heaters,
but just for show... no ammo.
Officer Lowe will be embedded
with you, and he'll be armed.
The rest of us will cover you
from the perimeter.
Our targets have been
on the bong all day.
You go in fast and hard,
they won't know what hit 'em...
no one gets hurt.
I mean, now that we're
undercover brothers now,
don't you think we need
to be deputized?
You know,
make this shit official.
All right.
Raise your right hands.
Now do this while you do this.
Sure, she's like supermom.
I mean, she's like a mom
and dad rolled all into one.
I feel like I let her down.
See how he's shifting the focus
away from him to his mother?
- Consciousness of guilt?
- Possibly.
Maybe I should have, like,
dove headfirst
through the window
to get away.
I'd like you to close
your eyes.
I gave him a guided image
transference exercise here.
Now, watch what he does.
Tell him what you were feeling
when you pulled the trigger.
This is on you,
you stupid shit.
And this is all your fault,
only I'm the one messed up
over it,
- and I don't even know you.
- Blaming the victim to generate sympathy.
But he's also speaking
to his own shadow self...
could be interpreted
as an admission of guilt.
Anything else
you'd like to say to him?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm just...
I'm really sorry.
Affect and emotional responses
are consistent with
post-traumatic stress...
remorse, grief,
guilt, anger.
What if it's all an act?
Then we're dealing
with a sociopath
with a well-constructed mask
of sanity,
but the stats
are against it.
Most serial killers
don't come online
until they're in their 20s
or 30s.
You think I'm pissing
in the wind here?
There's something off
with this kid.
I just can't tell you
what it is.
Death penalty's
off the table,
contingent on you
pleading guilty to all charges
and stipulating
to life without parole.
I can live with that.
If there's a God in heaven,
you'll catch a shank
to the throat,
choke to death
on your own blood,
miserable and alone.
When I get back
to my cell,
I'm gonna call my girl...
pop the question.
We all understand
what we're doing here?
Look, ain't no thing.
This is how we ride 24-7, my nig.
Throw it out... now.
Just trying to cover up
the smell of bacon.
Hey, do what he says,
homey.
I need your mind right
on this one,
and I'm trying to hang on
to this car.
Okay, Vic,
we're all in position.
All right,
let's get this done.
Wes, wes, y'all.
Hey, hey, my man,
how you doing?
Look, how much I got to drop
if I want to floss the load
with some sprewells on dubs?
Burnout, Burnout.
Don't move!
Get down!
Hey, come on!
Where the scrilla
and the cush at?
My man asked you
a question!
Hey, load up them rims!
Load them up!
Get dressed, bitch.
Yo, look at what I found.
Oh, sugar walls
found us a new bbc!
Let me see what I'm working
with here.
You dented the rims!
Let me hit that, dog!
That's money, nigger!
That's money over there!
Let me crank that bitch!
Come on, man!
- Help me, please!
- You okay?
Go, go, go!
Danny's got the girl.
All right, move in. Move in.
Hands in the air!
Head down on the ground!
Stay where you're at right now!
Stay where you're at!
Counselor,
moment of your time.
I understand
you're an attorney now.
Not sure if that's a step up or
a step down from doing murder.
You got jokes.
I was wondering if you'd be willing
to help me out on another matter.
What's in it for me?
Spoken like a true lawyer.
It's a 16-year-old kid. He's
got himself into a situation.
I could use your expertise,
help me figure out
what I'm dealing with.
Or I could just ship you back
to county in time for dinner.
I'm just...
I'm really sorry.
Anybody reached out to you
when you were his age,
with an arsenal of help
and understanding,
do you think you might have channeled
your energies in a different direction?
Don't get it twisted, man.
Everybody is born into this world
with their own set of gifts.
You grow up, you find out
what you're good at,
and you roll with it.
That's why you're a cop,
and I took a different path.
We all got to ride or die with what
the good lord meant for us to do...
you, me, and him.
So you're saying, if killing's
this kid's shot in life,
there's no stopping it.
There's stopping it.
Y'all stopped me, didn't you?
All it takes is a pair of cuffs
and a cage to throw him in.
But, yeah, he's got the look.
I seen it before.
Where?
In the mirror.
Which one of you fine young men
is mickey dightman?
What do you want?
Hands behind your back,
mickey.
Hey, what's going on?
I'm taking you in
for questioning.
Stroll!
What did I do?
That's what you're gonna tell
me, big pimpin',
and you better not
leave out a thing.
You can't arrest me
for smoking.
The picture doesn't prove
anything.
I can arrest you for scratching
your tiny little nuggets.
By the time you're done
with booking,
fingerprints, mug shots,
transport to juvie,
it'll be 18 hours before they release you
to your mommy and daddy.
And they're gonna love being in
and out of courtrooms
for the next year, trying
to clear their baby boy.
So, who supplied the drugs?
L- I brought one joint
with me.
Where'd you get it?
There's a weed patch
behind the school.
It grows wild.
What about the ecstasy?
I don't do "x."
That's not what I asked you.
Who brought it to the party?
I need a name!
- What?
- Kid's father's here.
Can you give me a second?
Vic, he's a juvenile.
He has to have a parent present.
Go ahead.
What's going on here?
Are you okay?
Your son is involved
in a drug investigation.
I had to make sure he was
in a secure environment
for his own safety
before I could notify you.
You are involved
with drugs?!
Marijuana and ecstasy.
If you can get him
to cooperate,
it'll go a lot easier
on him.
Mickey, you tell this man
what he wants to know...
now.
This girl in my grade...
okay, the "pimps 'n ho's" thing
was her idea.
She planned everything,
scored the "x."
The only thing
Cassidy asked me to do
was put together a mix tape
and a couple mash-ups.
You've always been
the logical one,
see the whole picture.
With what you did to Lem
center foreground.
I always know
where you're coming from.
I'm appealing
to your good judgment,
even though I know
I will forever be
on the wrong end of it.
You got that right.
Vic is gonna land
you, me, and him in jail
for the rest of our lives
if he keeps going
in this direction.
He's doing what it takes
to protect his family.
That's one part
of the equation.
The other math
goes like this...
Vic takes down someone
who's done worse deeds than him,
it balances accounts
for Terry
in that big, old box of sins
God keeps on all of us.
I don't believe in God.
Oh, you will, because praying's
the only thing
that gets you out of a jail cell
twice a week.
Hey, look.
Vic still thinks the world's
worth fixing,
and he's the only one
that can do it.
You and me...
we're not like that.
This joint is broke for good,
and we both know it.
And taking down Pezuela
will not make
one goddamn bit of difference
on the streets.
Now, he'll listen to you.
Get him to settle this beef,
hand over the box,
give everybody a moment's peace.
You may hate me,
but you know what I'm saying...
you know it's right.
Short of a confession,
I'm not gonna make this case.
And I can't sweat one
out of him
without alerting the mother
he's a suspect,
in which case,
she circles the wagons around her
sweet teen killing machine.
It sounds like you've done
everything you can.
What if everything I've learned
in my career,
everything
I've been through,
is meant to bring me
to this exact place in time,
this kid, this case?
What happened to the higher
power who put you here?
Why wasn't he there to stop
Lloyd from pulling the trigger?
Who's the better
detective...
someone who arrests the bad guy
after he's killed 30 people,
or the one who prevents
30 murders
from happening
in the future?
None of us
can see the future.
I can give it a shove
in the right direction.
Hey, um, sorry your deposition
went sideways.
In retrospect, burying those
subpoenas was, uh, prudent.
Kleavon would have tracked you
down sooner or later.
What's the final word?
Insardi cut the deal.
She gave me
the only deposition tape.
She protected me.
D.A.'s locking in
the best win they can.
It's not just
about protecting you.
Yeah, well, this is the shape
of things to come for me...
more a liability
every passing day.
What were you just saying
about seeing the future?
All I have to do
is look at the present.
If Kleavon
can suss this out,
what happens when a real lawyer
decides to tear me apart
in some other case?
You're not a lead
detective anymore.
All you have to do
is manage people here.
Is that what I do now?
Dodged a few bullets
today.
Literally.
Just don't know which side
Olivia's on.
Which makes sleeping tonight
as rough as it was last night.
I'm not putting my head
on the pillow
until I know for sure.
Shane wants me to have
a "come to Jesus" conversation
with you about...
about ending the war,
turning over the box.
I figured he'd piss
in your ear.
It makes sense.
He's got a point.
We could stop this all
now.
I can't give back
something I don't have.
Aceveda's in possession
of the box,
and he ain't giving it back
to you and me
so we can get cuddly
with the armenians.
Besides, if Olivia's been
ratting us out to Pezuela,
we've got
even bigger problems.
This stays between us.
It was stand-up of Dutch
to take responsibility
for the subpoena-gate,
- but I want...
- old business.
I'm...
I'm not well.
But I'm not done here yet,
either.
I, uh, I need someone
I can count on,
backstop me full-time,
catch my mistakes.
Anything you need...
just say the word.
How would you like to be
reassigned to me on a permanent basis?
From tuna boat
to goddess duty?
That would work for me.
How much do you know
about lupus?
And we believe this boy?
He was telling the truth.
What are we supposed
to do...
handcuff Cassidy to the bedpost
till she's 21?
If we have to.
Of course, she can start learning
about consequences the hard way,
- like these people.
- Don't say that.
That's not the future I want
for our daughter, either.
She's a good kid.
She just took a wrong turn.
She's got to start acting
like a good kid.
I got to go.
Hey, hey.
I know how to deal
with this, okay?
My lawyer wants to know where
we are with that quit claim.
Tell him
I'm not signing it.
Wait a minute.
We agreed.
Maybe in your head.
You have no idea what it takes
to raise a child.
I knew what I was doing
when I decided to keep Lee.
You were never a part
of that plan.
I might not have been a part
of the plan,
but I was 50%
of the execution.
You want to see Lee
have a good upbringing?
Stay out of his life
and sign the damn document.
Hey, just because you've decided
that me being the father
is a shitty idea
does not mean that I'm gonna get
behind the even shittier idea
of abandoning my son.
My mom's in the shower.
Good, 'cause you and I
need to talk.
We both know it was your plan
all along to kill luis alvarez.
You convinced him to break
into your house.
You shot him, made sure
you had an airtight story,
so you could go out
and kill again,
because that's
what gets you off.
You might even think you're
gonna get away with it again,
but I'm not gonna
let that happen.
Dutch?
Why do you keep
calling him that?
Because he's been so helpful
to us.
Am interrupting
something?
No.
Actually,
Dutch just came by
to let us know
that the investigation
is officially closed.
It's all behind us.
What a relief!
Hands where I can see them.
Drop that.
You wanted some late-night
alone time,
you could have invited me
for a cocktail.
A fed with benefits
isn't on my get list.
How about that drink?
I already checked
your well.
You don't stock my pour.
- Which is...
- surprising...
you already know
everything else about me.
I found that
by your bedside.
Well, girls need nighttime
reading, too.
How long has Pezuela
had his hooks in you?
You know all the twists
and turns.
Do I?
I got a federal warrant on a racketeering
investigation two years ago,
seized documents in a...
in a bookmaking takedown.
And you made
those documents disappear,
because they showed
your brother was in hock
to a cartel-financed casino.
Without motive,
the grand jury dropped the
embezzlement charge against him.
I kept my brother
out of jail.
Pezuela followed
the treasure trail to you,
and now you're the one
serving time.
And his doberman, rios,
is your warden.
I thought it was a trade-off
that I could live with.
My brother's been putting
his life back together.
Any errands they had me running,
they were minimal...
record searches, financials.
They want you to get your fingers really
dirty to set the hook.
Rios told me that I had
to arrange safe passage
across the border
for some people.
So I put in for special assignment
traing down in San ysidro,
picked up four illegals,
played it off like I was taking
them to secondary search...
dropped them
at a safe house instead.
He had you dance with coyotes
for a night. So what?
The next day,
rios had me shadowing the Salvadoran
body draggings on kearney.
You think it was done
by the guys you brought over.
The timing's hard
to overlook.
And then you gave me
that intel
on the Robert Martin
shooting.
You couldn't have known.
They weren't coming here
to pick lettuce.
I knew enough.
How much of this
have you fed to rios?
I've kept you
out of the mix.
Because...
because...
because I didn't want
to hurt you.
And at some point, you're gonna
squeeze me for a favor?
I'm in this so deep...
...and I don't know how
to get myself out.
You're talking
to the right guy.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com