Do you ever think that
maybe they put you down here
to push your button every 108
minutes just to see if you would?
That all of this, the computer,
the button, is just a mind game.
Every single day.
What do you find it
so hard to believe?
- What do you find it so easy?
- It's never been easy.
Your tour of duty in the
Pearl will last 3 weeks.
You and your partner
will observe a
psychological experiment
in progress.
These team members are not aware
that they're under surveillance
or that they are the
subjects of an experiment.
Every single second
of my pathetic little life is
as useless as that button!
If you will not continue
to push the button, John,
I will.
One of our people was
captured by yours.
So? Go get him back.
We can't do that but you can.
And if you do,
we'll let you and Walt go free.
Walt?
Dad, don't leave me.
Don't leave me!
I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
I promise you,
I will get you out of here!
- Dad! Dad! I love you!
- I love you, too, Walt!
I'm writing four names down.
Four of your friends.
But if you don't bring all
the people on the list,
you'll never see Walt again.
Michael?
- Did you see Walt?
- No.
I have to get my son back.
We're gonna help you
do that, Michael.
But it's gotta be
the way I said, man.
You, me, Kate, Sawyer, Hurley--
that's it.
Then that's the way it'll be.
- I think Michael has been compromised.
- Why would he lie to us?
Because I believe he's
leading you into a trap.
All right,
let's go talk to him.
No, he must continue to
believe he's in control.
Boat.
Are we rescue? Are we saved?
You see anything?
No.
- Maybe it's a trap.
- What do you mean, a trap?
You hear that?
Oh, damn it!
You.
Okay, okay, just wait one second, okay?
I'll be right back.
Everybody needs to know what's going on,
Jack. There's a boat--
Just tell 'em Desmond's back
until I find out the rest, okay?
So, before you ran off,
I guess you just
forgot to mention that
you still have a sailboat.
Why'd you come back?
Do you think I
did it on purpose?
I was sailing for two and a half weeks,
bearing due west
and making 9 knots. I should have
been in Fiji in less than a week.
But the first piece of land I
saw wasn't fiji, was it? No.
No, it was here, this...
this island.
And you know why?
Because this is it.
This is all there is left--
this ocean and this place here.
We are stuck in a
bloody snow globe!
There's no outside world.
There's no escape!
So just... just go, yeah?
Let me drink.
Are you still pushing it?
Yeah, we're still pushing it.
Set of keys.
One pocket watch, gold-plated.
One photograph.
One book-- "our mutual friend."
Why didn't you
bring that inside?
To avoid temptation, brother.
I've read everything mr.
Charles dickens has ever written--
every wonderful word,
every book.
Except this one.
I'm saving it.
So it'll be the last thing
I ever read before I die.
Nice idea,
long as you know when you're gonna die.
Lance corporal
Desmond David Hume,
your sentence is
hereby complete,
and you are now and forever
dishonorably discharged
from the royal scots regiment
of her Majesty's armed forces.
Long live the queen.
Enjoy your sodding book.
You want a ride?
Not with you.
Get in the car.
- Did you bring me a present?
- Actually, two presents.
One of these boxescontains
your past, Hume--
the other, your future.
Go ahead. Open it.
You're a bastard,
you know that?
The fact that she
never received your...
sentiments is good for her--
good because as far as she's concerned,
you've  forsaken her,
and that's the way it's going to stay.
Is it now?
Penelope has moved on, Hume.
She's getting married.
This is for your new life...
away from my daughter.
The conditions are simple.
No contact. No calls, no posts.
You just... run away, Desmond.
And what makes you think
I would just run away?
Because you're a coward.
On the way to the funeral,
I told you that Michael had
been compromised by the others,
and then you asked me how we
might take advantage of that.
I believe fate has given us our answer--
the boat.
The boat?
This camp Michael is leading you to,
across the island--
That is where they
will set their trap.
While Michael
leads you by land,
I can approach far
more quickly by sea,
and I can go ashore undetected.
Go ashore and do what?
Scout them-- their numbers
and positions, their weapons.
Then I'll go to the nearest beach
and start a signal fire with these.
They  burn with a dark,
black smoke.
You and your team will come
to meet me at the signal...
and we will go in together.
We're not even sure if
Michael's been turned by them.
He  has been turned.
I'll have to tell Kate and Hurley
and Sawyer what we're doing--
No. Michael cannot sense
we know he is lying.
All we have is the
element of surprise, Jack.
Right now it's only your
responsibility to keep it secret.
Black smoke, huh?
This time...
they will know that we are coming.
Hello, John.
Where have you been?
I've been thinking.
About what?
That in a minute,
that computer's gonna start beeping,
and when it does,
you're gonna let it go.
You're gonna let it run down to zero--
past zero--
and you're not gonna
push the button.
But I am going to push the button.
Why wouldn't I?
Because you don't
wanna be a slave.
I am a slave to nothing.
You're a slave to that,
just like I was.
So I'm going to tell you again.
Don't push it.
Do not tell me what I can't do.
You cannot push that button.
No, it's not real!
We're only puppets--
puppets on strings!
Aah! As long as we push it,
we'll never be free.
Well, you're free now, John.
Do not come back.
No.
No way.
If I take that, I'm gonna kill someone.
Ain't that the point?
I thought the point
was to get Walt back.
What's the matter?
All that stuff we found
in the medical station--
costumes, makeup, fake beards?
What if these people just want
us to think they're hillbillies?
Listen, listen, I was there.
I saw them.
They are hillbillies.
They live in huts.
They eat fish.
They're probably more
scared than we are,
and they have no idea
we're on our way.
All right.
Enough jibber-jabber.
Let's roll.
I need your boat.
I wouldn't waste your time.
There's nothing out there, pal.
I'm not going out there.
I need to get to the north shore
of the island, and quickly.
Off to see the hostiles,
are you?
The what?
You know what?
Ignorance is bliss.
The boat's all yours, brother.
For all the good it'll do ya.
I don't know how to sail.
Then I suggest you
find someone who does.
Just give me whichever one has
the most caffeine in it, brother.
Oh, damn. Um...
I'm sorry.
I've just arrived, and, uh,
I spent all my american
money on a taxi.
I've got it.
- Uh, that's not necessary.
- It's just 4 bucks.
I n't suppose you have
42,000 more of those, do ya?
Depends on what it's for.
- I was joking.
- No, you weren't.
A solo sailing race
around the world?
I have eight months to get into
the best shape of my life.
But I'll tell you what, miss.
I'm going to win.
And what do you get if you do?
What really matters...
is who I win it from.
"Charles Widmore."
He tried to buy me off,
and when I didn't
take his money,
he took away the only
thing in the world that...
I ever truly cared about.
Who is she?
His daughter.
I was unsuitable
on several levels.
- And what's the 42 grand for?
- It's a wee bit complicated.
As of yet,
I don't actually have a boat.
Sorry, did I say
something wrong?
I have a boat.
It was my husband's, but...
he got sick and...
he wanted to sail to the Mediterranean,
but he never...
he passed away...
about a month ago.
I'm sorry.
I want you to have it.
I... I can't take
your boat, miss.
But you have to.
He'd want you to.
What was your husband's name?
David.
And what did he name his boat?
"Elizabeth."
He named it after me.
Then...
I thank you, Elizabeth.
And I shall win this race...
for love.
Would you excuse us, please?
I'll be at the shore.
Don't  even think about it.
It's a trap.
A net.
Rousseau's got 'em all over the island.
How the hell would
you know that?
Kind of tripped one with Jack.
We ended up...
never mind.
What?
When the doc told me y'all got caught in
a net, I thought he meant that, uh...
somethin' else.
And since when did you and
Jack start talking about me?
Did that bird just say my name?
Yeah, it did...
right before it crapped gold.
Sorry, man.
Guess I forgot to load that one.
Wanna hand me the mag?
John?
What happened to your face?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Hey, uh...
if you're feeling a little
sorry for yourself, you...
you may wanna have a drink
with your mate from the hatch.
I hear he's a little
despondent as well.
What?
Oh, that's right.
You weren't there for the
dramatic arrival
at the funeral.
I think he's pushed your button
too many times, if you ask me.
- Desmond?
- Yeah. Desmond.
I'm sure you two have
a lot to talk about.
I'm sorry if what I said
was confusing, but...
I asked Jin to come.
You need someone to translate,
and you need at least two
people who know how to sail.
Desmond managed by himself.
And look where he ended up.
You're wasting
your time, sister.
I shot myself with that stuff
every 9 days for 3 years.
He's lovely.
Is the...
is the father here on the island?
No. Nope,
he's been gone a long time.
Just sort of walked off the moment he
got a bit scared by the situation.
Well, maybe he knew
he'd be a lousy dad.
Thought he was doing
what was best for you.
He was doing what
was best for him.
How did you find me?
Landlord at your flat told
me you ran here every day--
How did you find me?
I have a lot of money, Desmond.
With enough money and determination,
you can find anyone.
Did  you read your beloved book--
the one you were saving?
Not yet.
I thought you might have
read it while you were away.
I was in prison.
Not away.
Why didn't you write to me?
When are you getting
married, Pen?
- We haven't set a date yet.
- I'll be back in a year.
What if you were
back right now?
I'm gonna win this race, Pen...
his race.
And in a year,
I'll be back.
Desmond, what are
you running from?
I have to get my honor back.
And that is what
I'm running to.
So what did one snowman
say to the other snowman?
"Smells like carrots."
Hello, Desmond.
Hello yourself, box man.
- Do you mind?
- Oh, I insist.
So you managed to fix the computer then,
did you?
The world's still here,
ain't it?
I'm not so sure
about that, brother.
Refresh my memory, Desmond.
How long did you say
that you were down
there in the hatch?
Three years.
Desmond, what if
I told you that...
for all that,
all those years that you and
all the men before you were down there,
pushing that button...
What if I told you it
was all for nothing?
I'd ask you how the hell did
you know something like that?
I found another hatch.
Another station on the island.
They called it the Pearl.
And I saw a film there--
an orientation film--
and it said that everything that
was happening in our hatch...
wasn't real.
That it was a test.
A psychological experiment.
You're lying.
You wanna take a walk?
I'll make the popcorn.
If you're so sure
it's not real,
then just stop
pushing the button!
Well, I have,
except, unfortunately,
someone else decided to start.
So you're gonna sober up.
And we're gonna get a good
night's sleep, and tomorrow
we're gonna find out what happens
if that button doesn't get pushed.
Dharma nutrabar?
No, thanks. Not hungry.
Are you serious?
Hey.
You all right?
Yeah, just, uh,
getting some more firewood.
Not feeling too hot.
You shouldn'tbe out here alone, huh?
I'll give you a hand.
Hey.
Thanks for coming out here,
risking your neck for my boy.
Live together, die alone, man.
Yeah.
I don't know what is
more disquieting--
the fact the rest of
the statue is missing...
or that it has four toes.
Eight... seven...
six... five... four...
...one.
John!
Neat trick.
Can you hear me?! Open up!
I hope you're sure
about this, brother.
I'm more sure about this than
anything in my entire life.
Don't do this! John!
All right, then, box man.
We wait.
Are you him?
What?
What did one snowman
say to the other?
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
I'm Inman.
Kelvin Inman.
W hat...
what happened to my boat?
I found you washed
upon the beach.
There was no boat.
What was all that about, then?
Just saving the world.
How many times you
gonna watch that thing?
Why are there missing parts?
Radzinsky made some edits.
- Who's Radzinsky?
- He was my partner.
And what happened to him?
Just make sure you put that back behind
"Turn of the screw" when you're done
with it.
Why do you wear that suit?
So I don't get
infected out there.
Give yourself a shot of
this every nine days.
You were out there a
while before I found you.
Hope it's not too late.
John!
Who is he, box man--
the man out there pounding on the door?
His name is Mr. Eko.
And why does Mr. Eko carry around
a stick covered in scripture?
Because he's a priest.
Open the door, please!
Don't do this.
John! Can you hear me? Open up!
We locked out a priest?
John!
Charlie, do you know how they
got the hatch door open?
No, but if you hum it,
I can probably play it.
How did they open it--
the door that says "quarantine"?
They blew it up. Why?
Charlie, I need your help.
Oh, now I'm back in your
good graces, father?
Charlie, John has locked
me out of the hatch,
and I believe he is doing this because
he's going to stop pushing that button,
and, Charlie, I am absolutely
certain that if he is successful,
in 90 minutes,
everyone on this island will die.
- All right, I'm in. I'm in.
- Thank you. Come on, quick.
So these others-- think they're
leftover from the Dharma folks?
I don't know, man.
My theory? They're aliens.
That's why they use the fake beards--
Their heads are made of plastetic.
Prosthetic, dude.
You can't even spell,
and now you're correcting me?
What do you think, freckles?
Just keep moving.
We're being followed.
- What?
- Just keep smiling.
There's a least two of
them across the river.
In about five seconds,
I'm gonna turn the tables on 'em.
Whoa, wait a second.
Are you in?
Kate!
He's getting away!
He's dead.
We have to find the other one.
No!
- I'm going. Sawyer--
- I said no!
You crazy?! We let him go, they'll
know we're coming! He'll warn them--
It doesn't matter if
we catch him now.
They've already been warned.
What do you mean, "warned"?
- Why don't you tell them, Michael?
- Jack...
- I don't know what you're talking--
- Stop lying!
Tell them.
Tell them what?
I know what you're doing, Michael!
Now tell them the truth.
Tell them!
It was the only way.
They gave me a list.
What list?
It had your names on it.
I had to bring all four of you back,
or they said I'd never see my son again!
Who are they?
It's like I said.
They live in a camp with huts, and...
I swear that's it!
You let Henry go?
Did you kill them?
Ana Lucia...
and Libby?
Did you?
I had to.
I... uh... I couldn't find any
other way, and Libby was a mistake.
I didn't have time to think.
But if you did have time...
you still would've
killed her, right?
I'm sorry.
Do you understand?
I am sorry. I'm sorry.
I... This is my son!
I'm going back.
No, Hurley.
Hurley, you can't.
We're all gonna get killed, and you
knew it, and you let us come anyway.
It's too late to go
back now, Hurley.
We already caught 'em
following us once.
If they don't believe that we
trust Michael, they'll kill us all!
I'm sorry that I
didn't say anything.
But you have to know that I would never
bring you out here if I didn't have
a plan.
What plan?
Sayid!
There.
That's the rock
Michael described.
We're here.
Quick, please.
Wait, Hurley showed me. It's around here
somewhere. It's definitely around...
- It's, uh...
- Quick, Charlie.
We're running out
of time, Charlie.
Yeah, yeah!
Here it is!
Told you.
Careful. Careful.
Dynamite is very unstable.
Don't end up like Dr. Arzt.
Careful.
Eko...
Hey! Eko.
Listen...
What if we hurt them?
Or-- or blow up the computer?
You can leave now, Charlie.
John, it's Charlie!
Let's work this
thing out, John.
John!
Eko is very upset, John.
Let's just open this door,
and we can talk about it.
John, you should know Eko is
gonna blow open the blast door.
Blow it open with what?
With dynamite from the
old ship in the jungle.
It would take an
atom bomb, brother.
Tell them not to bother.
You're sure it'll hold?
Aye.
I'm sure.
You ready?
Maybe you should do it.
Come on, Des,
you've seen me do it a hundred times.
Six... five... four...
three... two... one.
How do you even remember
where you left off from?
Slowly, Des.
Very, very slowly.
Man, you should've seen
Radzinksy do this.
He had photographic memory.
I mean, this whole baby was his idea.
Yeah, right, Radzinsky.
Radzinsky figured out
how to fake a lockdown.
Radzinsky created this
great invisible map.
More and more tales about your
former partner, yet for some reason,
you never wanna tell me what
bloody well happened to him.
See that brown stain there?
That's Radzinsky.
He put a shotgun in his
mouth when I was asleep.
The bitch of it was I only had 108
minutes to bury the poor bastard.
Well, if you don't
want me to go crazy...
next time let me go out.
Oh, you wanna go out there with
the quarantine and the hostiles?
I haven't been outside
for two bloody years.
Yes, I wanna go.
I was in the army, for god's sake!
Oh, right,
her Majesty's army, correct?
Tell me, Desmond, why'd you
leave that nice old lady's army?
Oh, I remember now.
You got kicked out because
you couldn't follow orders.
And why did you leave your army,
Kelvin, huh?
Because men followed my orders.
But then, thank God,
I joined the Dharma initiative.
"Namaste, thank you,
and good luck."
Please, Kelvin.
Let me go out.
Huh?
Just once.
Sorry, Des. You stay here.
You push the button.
That's an order.
John!
Look, seriously,
you're about to be detonated.
Hey.
What if John's right?
Maybe it's just
some colossal joke.
You know, it's just some old
computer connected to nothing.
Maybe it's just a
bunch of wires that...
Is that a joke?
I'll see myself out.
John, this is your last
chance to end this.
Open the door,
and I will forgive you.
Forgive me for what?!
Hey.
Hey. Eko?
Wait.
Just wait a second.
I don't think it's
a good idea, Eko.
We're in a very confined area.
Oh, bollocks!
Kelvin!
Hey, Kelvin!
I couldn't do it.
What is this?
This is the only other
way out, partner.
- What are you talking about?
- Fail-safe.
Just turn the key,
and this all goes away.
What's behind that
wall, Kelvin?
Huh?
What was the "incident"?
Electromagnetism.
Geologically unique.
The incident--
there was a leak.
So now the charge builds up,
and every time we push the button,
it discharges it...
before it gets too big.
Why make us do it--
push the button?
If we-- if we can just...
Now here's the real
question, Desmond--
do you have the courage to take
your finger out of the dam
and blow the whole
thing up instead?
I think your friends just
blew themselves up, brother.
They're not my friends.
I can't hear anything.
- Maybe we should open it.
- No, no!
It's a trick.
A trick? They could be hurt.
Is your doctor around?
Our doctor is...
God knows where. I...
And he sure as hell doesn't care
about anything happening down here.
Can I ask you a
question, brother?
Absolutely.
Is the reason you're
letting that clock there
run all the way down to
the very last tick...
Is it because you need to
look down the barrel of a gun
and find out what you
really believe, John?
I looked downthe barrel of the gun,
and I believed.
I thought...
it was my destiny to
get into this... place.
And-- and somebody died,
you know, a kid--
because he was stupid enough to believe
that I knew what I was talking about.
And on the night that
he died for nothing,
I was sitting right
up there all alone,
beating my hand bloody against that...
stupid door,
screaming to the heavens,
asking what I should do.
And then a light went on.
I thought it was a sign.
But it wasn't a sign.
Probably just you
going to the bathroom.
Jack?
What are they?
It's handwritten.
And it's all filled--
the whole book.
They're journal entries.
"0400-- S.R.
Moves ping-pong table again.
0415-- takes a shower."
What is this?
Hey, doc. What'd you say
Sayid's signal was gonna be
when the coast was clear
to hit that beach party?
That means he
found them, right?
That's miles from here.
Where were you taking us?
What?
Sayid said he'd light the signal so
that we could meet him at the shore.
Why aren't we
going to the beach?
- We are headed to the--
- We're nowhere near the beach!
- Listen, I had to--
- What?!
Sawyer!
Run! Go! Go!
Tell me about this other hatch
you found-- this... Pearl.
What do you wanna know?
Details.
The earl is a psychological
station full of TV monitors,
and, uh, two men sat in viewing
chairs and filled notebooks
with observations on
what happens in here,
and then they put the
notebooks in pneumatic tubes
that sent them backto
their headquarters
so they could evaluate
us as an experiment.
What?
What if you've
got it backwards?
Backwards?
What if the experiment wasn't on the two
men in here but on the two men
in there?
Look, I wanna see
that tape, John.
No, you can't.
There's no way to see it down here.
Well, was there anything
elsein that station?
- Was there a computer?
- Yeah.
- So what did it do?
- Nothin'. It didn't do anything.
It printed out numbers--
lots and lots of numbers.
What printout? Where is it?
Here. Reading material for the next
19 minutes. Knock yourself out.
You've been shaving every
day for the last three years.
You need to live a little.
Let go.
I'm never gonna
let go, brother.
Oh, that's the spirit.
Good-bye, Des.
Good-bye?
Yeah. Good-bye.
See you in a couple hours.
Well, gosh, I didn't think you
had the stones to come after me.
I was a spook for ten years, Des.
I know when I'm being followed.
What are you doin'
with my boat?
I'm fixing it.
You were leaving?
Well, I mean, not yet.
She's still about a week away.
You wrecked her
pretty good, Des.
So what do you think?
You wanna come with me?
Come where?!
What about the button?
Screw the button, man.
Who knows if it's even real?
That's not what you said when
you were going on and on
about dams and electromagnetics
and fail-safes!
Well, I was drunk.
Why did you lie to me?!
I lied to you because I needed a
sucker to save the world after I left.
You're crazy. You bastard!
- Oh, come on.
- You stole my life!
What else did you lie to me about?!
What else?! Tell me!
How could you do this to me?!
Get up.
Oh, my god.
System failure. System failure.
Come on!
What are you doing?
When did you come here?
What?
The island.
When did you come here?
- How long ago?
- 60, 65 days.
What was the date?
September 22nd.
It was september 22nd.
I think I crashed your plane.
Son of a bitch,
I'll kick your...
Hey!
Everybody just calm down.
It's fake.
We know that your
beard is fake.
Sorry, missy. I didn't get ya.
She said she knows your
beard's fake, Tom.
Well, thanks for
pointing that out, Kate.
I can't tell you how
much this thing itches.
And thanks for telling
'em my name, Bea.
Hello again.
Where's your beard?
I think they... know.
All right,
let's take care of business, shall we?
Eko! Eko!
Hey.
It's Charlie! Wake up!
- We need to push the button.
- No, we don't!
Did you not hear me, brother?
I crashed your bloody plane.
How did you manage to do that?
On that day,
those numbers turned to hieroglyphics,
and when the last one came down,
this whole place started to shake,
and that screen-- that screen
filled up with "system failure."
"System failure"!
And that number there-- 92204--
September the 22nd, 2004--
the day your plane crashed.
It's real! It's all bloody real! Now
push the damn button! I know what I saw!
It's a lie! It's not real!
None of it is real!
You don't wanna push the button?
Then I will.
No.
You've killed us.
You've killed us all.
No.
I've just saved us all.
Hey! Eko! Wake up!
Hey!
Hey! Can I get some help?!
- Can you help me?!
- I'm trying, brother.
Dearest des,
I am writing this letter to
you as you leave for prison,
and I've hidden it
in the one place
you would turn to in a
moment of great desperation.
I know you go away with the weight
of what happened on your shoulders,
and I know the only person who
can ever take it off is you.
Please don't give up, Des,
because all we really need to survive
is one person who truly loves us.
And you have her.
I will wait for you. Always.
I love you.
Pen.
It's all gone!
It's all...
it's all gone! All gone!
I've done everything
you wanted me to do!
So why did you do this?! Why?!
Three days before you came down here,
before we met,
I heard a banging on the
hatch door, shouting.
But it was you,
John, wasn't it?
You say there isn't any purpose,
there's no such thing as fate?
But you saved my life, brother,
so that I could save yours.
No, no! No!
None of this is real!
Nothing is gonna happen.
We're gonna be okay.
I've got to go, and you've got to get
as far away from here as possible.
Go where?! Stop!
I'm gonna blow the dam, John.
I'm sorry for whatever happened
that made you stop believing,
but it's all real.
And now I've got to go
and make it all go away.
Wait! Desmond!
I'll see you in
another life, brother.
System failure.
Eko! Wake up!
Are you all right?
Oh, look out!
All right,
come with me! Charlie...
No! I don't...
Get out of here, Charlie!
I was wrong.
All we really need to survive is
one person who truly loves us.
And you have her.
I will wait for you.
Always.
I love you.
I love you, Penny.
Charlie?
You okay?
Uh, it's... it's hard to tell,
exactly, but my ears, you know?
Where's Locke? Eko?
They're not back yet?
No.
I'm not happy about the arrangement
that was made with you, Michael, but
we got more thanwe bargained
for when Walt joined us, so
I suppose this is what's best.
And you let me go, set me free.
You lived up to your word.
We live up to our word, too.
Do you know how
to drive a boat?
Yeah, I can drive a boat.
Good. Then you're
gonna take this boat
and follow a compass
bearing of 325,
and if you do that exactly,
ou and your son will find rescue.
What, that's it?
I follow the bearing,
and me and my son get rescued.
Yes.
How do you know I won't tell
people about where I was?
Maybe you will,
maybe you won't.
But it won't matter.
Once you leave,
you'll never be able to get back here.
And my hunch is you won't
say a word to anybody.
Because if you do,
people will find out what
you did  get your son back.
My friends.
I was promised you
wouldn't hurt them.
Deal's a deal.
Who are you people?
We're the good guys, Michael.
All right. She's all yours.
What? What am I, stupid?
Where is my son?!
Walt's inside.
Walt?
Bon voyage, Michael.
Walt!
Dad! Dad!
Come here, come here.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
You're sure? Okay.
I got you now.
It's gonna be okay now. We're going
home, Walt. We are going home.
Hugo, you can go
back to your camp.
What?
Go back.
Your job is to tell
the rest of your people
they can never come here.
But... what about my friends?
Your friends are
coming home with us.
Go.
What happened out
there, Charlie?
You wanna hear
the part about me
nearly being killed by the flaming
fireball or the flying fork?
I want you to be serious.
Nothing happened.
Well, something happened.
I mean, that noise and the sky
turned that weird violet color.
Did it?
- Hello?
- Miss Widmore?
- Yes?
- It's us.
I think we found it.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com