Previously on "Lost"...
Michael.
I found them-- the others.
I saw one.
I followed him back to their camp.
They live in tents--
canvas tents and teepees.
They eat dried fish.
They're worse off than we are.
They have a hatch.
They keep it guarded 24/7--
two guards, two guns,
and two guns is all I saw.
Michael?
So I came back to tell you.
- Did you see Walt?
- No.
But I know he's there.
As soon as I get my
strength back...
I will take us back there,
and we are gonna
get my boy back.
Hey, John. John. I was hoping I
could borrow one of these guns.
Is this supposed
to be a secret?
- Jack's asleep.
- Oh.
More target practice?
Yeah, well, you know...
just wanna stay sharp.
- You got a date?
- Nah.
Old habits, you know?
- Yes, I do.
- Thanks, man.
Hey, can I just get a
couple of these bullets?
I promise I won't--
Ah, damn! I'm sorry.
No, that's all right. I got it.
Come on. Where are you?
You okay?
Ok, no time. Come soon?
I'm ready. Coming now.
You said north. North where?
When they take me out, there's huge
rocks with a big hole in the middle
by the beach you'll
know when you see.
It's gonna be okay. I'm coming.
I'm coming, Walt.
Locke?
John.
Stay in there.
- Stay. Michael, what are you--
- Stay in there, jack!
- Hey, whatever's going on--
- I'm going after my son.
I'm going after my son,
and nobody is going to stop me, okay?
Okay, that is my right.
That is a father's right.
Hey.
- What are you doing out here?
- Nothing. Just getting some air.
Well, come on. We should talk.
- How many?
- Rifles and pistols? 11 total.
That's it?
That's it. In case you forgot,
they took five of 'em right off us.
How long would it take
us to get to their camp?
We leave now and move fast--
middle of the night tomorrow.
Look, they have no idea
I know where they are.
They won't be expecting us.
So we get the guns and we go,
right now, just the five of us.
No, no, five's not enough.
You said there's at least 20 of them.
They've got our guns, and we're
not even sure if what you saw was--
Hey, I know what I saw!
We take too many people,
they'll hear us coming.
I'm not taking a damn army
across the island, Jack.
You sure you're in the best place to be
making decisions for all of us
right now?
You got a son, Jack?
They're dead!
Ana Lucia and Libby are dead.
I mean,
we haven't even buried 'em yet.
Me and you will
take Libby, okay?
- Can you...
- Yeah, of course.
- Sawyer, would you...
- Yeah.
You should stay here.
We bury them tonight, and...
then we'll figure
out what's next.
Hey!
Put your hands up.
Put 'em up! Don't move.
Relax, buddy. I ain't movin'.
- Why don't you just put that--
- Shut up!
You're Walt's old man,
aren't ya?
What?
What are you doing?!
We need him!
Bag him, quick!
His friends are
right behind us.
Hello.
I didn't hear you come in, man.
I left my shoes outside.
They were muddy.
Did you find him? Henry?
No.
I hear you're a priest.
Yes.
Guess you believe
in hell, then.
For a brief time I served in
a small parish in England.
Every  sunday after mass,
I would see a young boy waiting at
the back of the church, and then
one day the boy confessed to me that he
had beaten his dog to death with
a shovel.
He said the dog had bitten
his baby sister on the cheek,
and he needed to protect her.
And he wanted to know whether
he would go to hell for this.
I told him that god would understand,
that he would be forgiven...
as long as he was sorry.
But the boy did not
care about forgiveness.
He was only afraid that
if he did go to hell...
that dog would be
there waiting for him.
Hey.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I was coming back
to check on you.
Yeah, man.
I had to get out of there.
Just...
I have to get my son back.
We're gonna help you
do that, Michael.
It's gotta be the way I said, man.
Just the five of us.
Otherwise, it won't work.
It won't work.
I promise,
we're gonna figure that out.
But I have already
figured it out.
It's gotta be just the
people who already know--
You, me, Kate, Sawyer, Hurley.
That's it. Anybody else, and...
Look, it puts him in more danger.
You don't get to decide this.
It's my son! It's my call.
And that's the
way it has to be.
Then that's the way it'll be.
Hey.
Hey, Aaron. Hey, big guy.
Hi!
- Have you seen Eko?
- No.
You  know,
we're building a church.
Is there something
you want, Charlie?
Yeah.
I found something in the pallet
I thought you might need.
Vaccine?
I don't know what we'd need vaccine for,
but I figured
if anyone should have it,
you and the baby should.
It's all right. It's a...
it's a pneumatic injector.
You just, uh...
you put it into your leg, and...
it goes right in.
Quite painless, really.
You seem to knowa lot about it.
I tried it.
I wanted to make sure it was safe
before giving it to you and the baby.
Well, how do you feel?
I mean, did it do anything?
- Did it-- what did it do?
- I don't know. I feel fine.
Anyway, it says you're supposed to
give yourself a shot every nine days.
All right? So there's enough here
for you and the babyfor a while.
That's it.
All right. I'll put it...
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I should really feed him, so...
Yeah. Hey, Claire? Do you think
maybe you and I could, um...
Oh, my god. Michael's back.
Michael?
Okay?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
It's good to see you, too.
Are you all right?
Yeah. I'm...
it's just... I'm fine.
Who?
Ana Lucia and Libby.
What happened to them?
They were murdered.
Hey there, Michael.
Not gonna hold
that against you.
Fair's fair. I took your boy.
But don't do that again, okay?
Where is he,
you son of a bitch?
Hey, lookie what I found.
She was following her friends.
About half a klick behind us.
You make one sound...
you'll never see
your boy again.
Gag him.
Get ready with the torches.
I'm gonna go talk to her people.
I think we better head back.
What?
- Just to find the trail, John.
- I've lost the trail.
You don't just lose a trail.
You just don't wanna find him.
Yeah, that's right, Jack.
I've been running through the jungle
toward the sun of gunfire because
I don't care about Michael.
You know what happens if we
just turn around and go back?
We're never gonna see him again,
and that's gonna be on us,
on you and on me.
You're exactly right, Jack.
Who are you?
He's the son of a bitch
that shot me on the raft.
Why  don't you
point the gun down?
It's okay.
He's just delivering a message.
He has to scare your
friends to do it.
- I don't believe you.
- You don't believe what?
I think there's more of
us than there are of you.
That's an interesting theory.
Light 'em up!
Give me your weapon.
Turn around. Go home.
No.
I hoped it wouldn't
come to this.
Bring her out, Alex!
Go on.
- You...
- Come on, Alex.
Please?
Let's go. Up. Up.
Is Claire okay?
Did she have the baby?
Is it okay?
Is it a boy or a girl?
Like I said, curiosity...
You and me ain't done, Zeke.
His friends are going home.
Divvy 'em up.
Sorry.
What do you say, doc?
Here I was thinking the irish
drink when somebody dies.
I'm not irish.
Neither am I.
So what happened out
there in the jungle?
Exactly what he said happened.
He found the camp--
I ain't talking about Mike.
You and freckles...
Before you found him.
Y'all were gone all night.
We were caught in a net.
What the hell's that
supposed to mean?
It means we got
caught in a net.
That what they're
calling it these days?
Is  it true? Henry is gone?
Yeah.
Who's going after him?
Locke and Eko went out in
the middle of the night.
But we ain't seen
either of 'em since.
Those are the guns,
aren't they?
What are you doing with them?
What do you think we're doing?
It's time to finish this.
- When do we leave?
- In the mornin'.
You're not coming, Sayid.
Excuse me?
Michael wants to keep it small--
me, Kate, Hurley and-- and him.
Well, "him" says even though Pippi
Longstocking and the damn grape ape
are ideal candidates
for the dirty dozen,
I'm  just gonna say we might
wanna bring the red beret.
It's Michael's call.
He knows where we're going.
It is not his call, Jack.
It's ours.
Welcome aboard.
So... you wake up in
the middle of the night,
you grab your Jesus stick
and race off into the jungle.
You don't call.
You don't write.
I'm sorry.
I had work to do.
Right. Yeah.
Charlie, would
you do me a favor?
I was hoping you could bring
my things from the beach here.
What for?
You moving in here?
Fancy yourself a
little bachelor pad?
Yes. I am moving in here.
Well, what about the church?
You said we were supposed to
be building it together, man.
I am supposed to do
something different now.
What am I supposed to do?
Bring me my things.
Bring your own things.
Charlie, please.
You'd better leg it, mate.
Clock's tickin'.
Got some good news for ya.
Captain A-rab's in, too.
Cavalry ride's at sunrise.
- You told Sayid?
- Yeah, I told Sayid.
You shouldn'thave done that!
Oh, well, I'm sorry.
I just figured if we're going to war,
we'd want the one guy who's
actually been in a war.
That a problem?
Well, no.
It's not a problem.
All right, then.
Get off of me!
You got a problem, Michael?
You march me a day and a
night without any rest, yeah.
My problem is I'm tired.
Well, I'd offer to knock you out
and carry you, but we're here.
Put him right over here.
Tell her we're here.
I can't promise
this won't hurt.
What the... Ow! Damn it!
Relax. Just taking some blood.
Taking some blood for what?
Who are you people? Where's my son?
That's it. All done.
See ya in the funny pages.
- Hello, Michael.
- Where's my son?
My name is Ms. Klugh.
I was hoping you might help
me answer some questions...
about Walt.
- Where is he?
- Is he your biological son?
- What?
- Are you his father?
Yes, I'm his--
How old was he when
he started speaking?
I... she...
Did he have any illnesses growing up?
Headaches? Fainting spells?
What? No!
I don't-- I wasn't there!
He was halfway
around the world.
Why are you asking me
all these questions?
Did Walt ever appear in a
place he wasn't supposed to be?
You say he was halfway
around the world, but...
- did you see--
- I want my son!
You bring him to me right now!
I wanna see my boy!
For someone who wants
his son back so badly...
you don't seem to know
much about him, Michael.
Hey. You're not coming.
Welcome back, Michael.
Look, I know Sawyer told you,
all right, but, uh,
it's not gonna work.
You're not coming.
And why is it that
I'm not coming?
Because you're going
after the guy who escaped,
and I'm going after my son.
Are you implying I'd let a desire
for revenge compromise Walt's safety?
I'm implying that I decide who
stays and who goes, and you stay.
I know you wanna help, right?
But I've gotta do this my way.
Of course.
- Good luck, Michael.
- Yeah. Thanks.
Bloody hell.
Are you kidding me?
Did someone put you up to this?
Vincent?
You were supposed
to come right back.
You were out in the jungle all night.
What happened?
We were unable to
find Henry's trail.
Yeah, I got that.
Where's Locke?
I do not know.
We're burying Ana Lucia
and Libby at sunset.
Thank you.
I will mourn them
in my own way.
Who's gonna talk?
What?
At the funeral.
Who's gonna talk?
Well, I'm sure Hurley will
wanna say something about Libby.
I never even knew
her last name.
Ana Lucia.
It's Cortez.
Cortez.
Well, there you go.
I screwed her.
What?
That's how she got my gun.
Ana-- she jumped me.
We got caught in a net.
Why are you telling
me this, Sawyer?
'Cause you're about the closest
thing I got to a friend, doc.
'Cause she's gone.
Well, at least now we
get to kill somebody.
Jack fill you in on the plan?
What plan?
We're leaving first
thing tomorrow
back across the
island to their camp.
Okay.
What about you, man?
You coming with us?
Why would I want to go?
Because they killed her.
Michael, come on.
What do you say, Hugo?
Sorry about Walt, dude,
but I'm not coming.
- You're sorry about--
- Michael.
Dinner time.
When you gonna do it?
When I am going to do what?
Kill me.
I've seen where you live.
I know how to get here.
You have been
asking me questions
I don't know the
answer to for a week.
I don't even think my
son is alive, and--
He is alive, Michael.
He's standing outside right now.
What do you think, I'm stupid?
There's been a development
since you came here, Michael.
One of our people was
captured by yours.
- So go get him back.
- We can't do that.
But you can.
And if you do...
we'll let you and Walt go free.
I wanna see my son.
- Michael--
- I wanna see him!
If he is out there,
you bring him in!
You bring him in
here right now!
Pickett?
You have three minutes.
Walt?
Dad.
Let him go.
Let him go!
Get your hands off him right now!
Dad, don't!
Are you okay, huh?
Yeah.
Are you-- did they hurt you?
- They make me take tests.
- They make you what?!
We're not gonna
talk about that.
How's Vincent?
Vincent's... he's great.
He's great. He misses you.
Hey, don't be scared, man.
Don't be scared.
It's gonna be over
real soon, okay?
I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
They're not who they
say they are...
- Walt!
- They're pretending!
Do you want me to put
you in the room again?
- Pretending? Pretending what?!
- Okay, that's it. We're done.
No,  no, no, no, wait.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Come here, walt!
Wait, come here, wait. Come here!
Dad. Don't leave me.
Help me, please. Don't leave me.
I won't, man.
I'm gonna get you outta here, okay?
I promise you,
I will get you out of here!
- Dad, dad!
- Let him go! Let go of him!
I love you!
Walt, I'm gonna get
you out of here!
- I love you!
- I love you, too, Walt!
Put me down! Let me go! !Dad!
After you release our man,
I'm gonna need you to do something else.
I'll do it.
Whatever you want.
I'm writing four names down--
four of your friends.
We need you to bring them here.
You have to bring only these
four people, Michael, just them.
If you don't bring all
the people on the list...
you'll never see Walt again.
Yeah. Okay.
Do you understand, Michael?
- What do I tell them?
- It doesn't matter.
Make up a story.
They'll be angry enough to
believe whatever you say.
Who's James Ford?
You know him as "Sawyer."
You know the rest of them?
Yeah.
I know them.
If I do all this...
if I do what you say...
You'll get your son back.
You'll both go free.
And I want the boat.
When the plane crashed, I was on my
way to Los Angeles to bury my dad.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It seems like such
a long time ago now.
I was gonna go right from the
airport to the cemetery, but...
I had no idea what
I was gonna say.
Here we are again.
I think Michael has
been compromised.
Let's keep walking, Jack.
What do you mean, compromised--
His actions are not those of a
man who is telling the truth.
Why would he lie to us?
Because I believe a father
would do anything for his son,
because I believe that
Michael may have freed Henry,
and because I believe he's
leading you into a trap.
You believe a lot, Sayid.
And I also believed that
Henry was one of them.
All right.
Let's go talk to him.
No, he must continue to
believe he's in control.
Why the hell would
we want to do that?
So we can create an advantage.
- How?
-
I don't know yet.
But we have one more
night to figure that out.
Ana Lucia Cortez was...
before we crashed,
she was a police officer.
I don't think it was
easy for her being here,
but I think she did
the best she could.
She was a woman of few words,
and I'm gonna follow her example.
Rest in peace, Ana.
Libby was...
she was...
she...
Libby was a psychologist.
Or... psychiatrist.
One of those.
By the way,
she probably helped a lot of people.
She helped me.
She was my friend.
It's not fair that this happened to her.
It's not.
I'm going with you.
Good-bye, Libby.
Boat.
Boat!