Previously on "Lost"...
Boone, what do you see?
All right, all of you, get up.
We're moving out.
Moving out where?
Back to where you came from.
Your buddy ran off
into the jungle.
Michael-- he just left.
Walt!
What are we supposed to do,
wait for him?
What are you doing?
I'm going to help
him find his friend.
You thirsty, dog?
Yeah, you're always thirsty,
aren't you?
So drink.
Come on.
Gather your things.
Where are we going?
Sayid?
Come on. Right over here.
Where are we going?
What do you think?
Does it have an inside?
When did you do this?
It's all yours.
Thank you.
You're quite welcome.
I'm sorry.
You need to carry
that all the time?
I only carry it because I
have someone to protect.
Ana, it's got to
be over an hour.
Shouldn't we start
moving again?
Let 'em rest a
little while longer.
Yeah, but what if they come?
She's lost.
I am not lost.
Then tell me, Ponce de León,
which way are we supposed to go?
All right, then, genius.
Which way would you go?
Hey, I'm with you--
Sit tight and wait for Mr.
Eko to show up and guide us.
If your friend didn't run off,
Eko would still be here,
now wouldn't he?
You sure didn't have any problem
leaving him behind, though, huh?
Mike only cares about
himself and his kid.
Neither's got squat
to do with me.
Glad you feel that way.
Didn't expect to see you again.
Yeah, yeah, Chewie, I know.
My arm's about to fall off.
You okay?
Yes, but we have to go.
I saw them.
- What? How many were there?
- What do you mean, you saw them?
- Did you see the kids?
- Libby.
We need to go. Now.
All right.
We're moving out.
Now!
So does all this...
the tent, the flowers...
mean that we're serious now?
Quite definitely not.
I do this for all the girls
I meet on deserted islands.
Don't go anywhere.
- Where are you going?
- To get some water.
Let me.
I'll be right back.
That was quick.
There's nothing!
There's no one there.
I am telling you I saw Walt.
- It was a dream, Shannon.
- He was here.
I saw him.
He went into the tent.
I was only gone for a few moments.
You must have fallen asleep.
This was not a dream!
- I saw Walt!
- Then where is he?
Hey.
What's going on?
Nothing. It's just a dream.
Everything's fine.
Shannon.
What's wrong?
Shannon had a nightmare.
Why is he up?
- I woke him.
- You woke him?
I heard screams. I got worried.
Why, would you rather I had
left him over there alone?
You heard screams, so you woke up
the baby and ran towards them?
It sounded like
she needed help.
Well, he's gonna
need feeding now.
He's gonna be up all
night and fussy all day.
Sorry.
All right, well, no harm done.
Give him here, then. I got him.
It's okay.
Wait.
Wait!
Come back with me,
and let's talk about this.
Do you believe me?
I know what I saw.
Beautiful, Sophie.
Okay, can you bring your
shoulders down for me a little?
And stand up. Good. And finish.
Very nice, ladies.
Did  my papa see me?
I think so.
Wonderful.  All right. Thank you
for a great class today, ladies.
Very nice work, Gina.
He wants me to be his au pair.
Can you believe that?
Au pair, my ass.
"Live in my big 'ouse,
take care of my kids."
Next thing you know, it's...
"Oh, I'm so sorry.
I did not know you were in ze shower."
Oh, please! What a perv.
Hello?
Shannon, your father's
been in an accident.
I'm on my way to St. Sebastian's.
I'll meet you there.
- Mrs. Rutherford?
- Yes?
Why don't we talk down here?
Doctor, my husband Adam--
how is he?
Your husband was in a head-on
collision with an S.U.V.
He suffered massive
internal injuries.
He stopped breathing at
the site of the accident.
I'm afraid we were unable
to resuscitate him.
I'm so sorry.
- May I see him?
- Of course.
Would your daughter
like to come?
Stepdaughter.
Come on, Shannon.
How much further to their camp?
A day, maybe more.
Maybe less.
Thanks for being so specific.
Damn it!
I'm okay. I'm fine.
You want to let me just take
a look at your shoulder?
- What, are you a doctor?
- Clinical psychologist.
You're a shrink.
Maybe you ought to
talk to my shoulder.
How did you get shot anyway?
With a gun.
He got shot when
they took my kid.
It's bad, right?
Yeah, it's bad.
But it's not real bad.
Come on. You're gonna be okay.
Let's go.
All right. I'm fine.
Let me give you a hand, okay?
Tell me again why we're doing this here
when there's a dryer in the hatch?
I don't like the hatch.
Oh. It's 'cause of the doomsday button,
isn't it?
Well, who needs a dryer when
we've got sun and fresh air?
Wouldn't want to spoil ourselves,
now would we?
Yeah, "spoil."
Hey.
Do you guys know
where Michael and Walt
left the stuff they didn't
take with them on the raft?
- What kind of stuff?
- Their clothes.
Uh, I think their stuff's
still on the beach,
back where their tent is.
Thanks.
Poor thing.
It can't be easy losing the one
person you love on the island.
Here. Smell this.
That's his, right?
Come on, get a good whiff.
You're always trying to
run off and find him?
Then find him. Find Walt!
Good dog! Find Walt!
I know I woke you,
and I'm so very, very sorry.
But I mean,
staying awake for eight hours straight?
Isn't that just cruel
and unusual punishment?
How's that cradle treating you?
The cradle is great.
It's the baby that's the problem.
- What's wrong?
- He just won't sleep.
May I?
Sure.
Babies like the feeling
of being constricted.
It's not until we're older that
we develop a desire to be free.
There.
You know, I think everybody
knows more about my baby than me.
Everybody?
Charlie read me the Riot Act
last night for waking him.
And as mad as it made me,
turns out he was right.
You know, it's like we're
playing mom and dad to this baby,
yet I don't remember
marrying him.
No, seriously. I mean,
we're practically strangers, him and me.
For all I know,
Charlie could be some religious freak.
I seriously doubt that.
Then why is he carrying
around a Virgin Mary statue?
A what?
You know,
one of the little statues.
He says he found
it in the jungle.
Hmm.
How about that?
- Death sucks, doesn't it?
- Boone!
- Hey.
I'm so sorry, Shan.
You came back.
Where did the poster
of Marky Mark go?
I'm 18, Boone.
Your mom's gonna freak.
It's a wake.
I mean, seriously,
who doesn't serve booze at a wake?
Scotch?
To  your dad.
Maybe after all this you'll
come visit me in New York?
I won't have to visit
if I get that job at the
Martha Graham dance company.
I'll be living there.
Right. The internship.
I know it's like a 1
in 3,000 chance, but
I might get it.
Absolutely.
Have you spoken to my mother?
She's going through her thing,
and I'm going through mine.
Have you two been
getting along?
She hates me.
Just try to talk to her.
From day one,
she resented my relationship with him...
with dad.
We need a break.
Five minutes!
Here.
What are you looking at?
We have to cut inland.
What? Into the jungle?
They said their people were on
the beach. If we keep walking--
The beach curves into
a peninsula ahead.
It may not be passable.
"May not"?
May not.
You're doing this to get the
cowboy back faster, aren't you?
You would risk our
lives to help him?
It's the only way I know.
I liked you better when
you weren't talking.
I can't believe
he's still asleep.
Swaddling works every time.
Hey, do you want to hold him?
That's okay.
Put your arms out.
It's okay.
Here.
- He smells good.
- He does, doesn't he?
Oh!
- Hello, Charlie.
- Hello.
Hey, John just taught me
a new trick-- swaddling.
That's excellent.
I just came to take him so
you could have your walk.
Well, great timing. Yeah.
I've got to get going.
I got him.
Well, thanks for
your help, John.
You're welcome.
What?
Shh!
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Shh! Shut up.
What? They can't talk at all?
If he talks,
he's gonna get us all killed.
By what? Them?
I thought they lived
a day back that way.
How about you shut your mouth and
get your buddy over here moving?
What happened to you people?
You want us to take
you back with us? Fine.
But you want me to keep quiet?
Then you need to tell
me why I have to.
They came the first
night that we got here.
And they took three of us.
Nothing happened for two weeks.
Then they came back
and took nine more.
They're smart,
and they're animals.
And they could be
anywhere at any time.
Now we're moving
through the jungle--
their jungle--
just so that you can save your
little hick friend over here.
And if you think that one gun and
one bullet is gonna stop them,
think again.
So shut your mouth
and keep moving.
They took my son.
They took a lot of things.
I know what it is to lose
someone you care deeply about.
You really think that
this is all about Boone?
I saw Walt, Sayid.
Then why are we sitting
at Boone's grave?
- Just go back, Sayid.
- Where are you going?
To find him.
It came.
Really?
- Oh, my god.
- Open it.
- I can't open it.
- You what?
You open it.
You have been waiting six months for
this letter. No way I'm opening it.
I got it.
- You got it?
- I got it!
Oh, my god!
You're going to New York!
Hello?
Yeah,  this is her.
Um, that's impossible.
Okay. Are you sure?
Of course.
I will certainly do that.
Sorry.
What?
My rent check bounced.
But you're, like, rich.
I'm sorry. I would have
offered you something to drink,
but I have to be at a
meeting in ten minutes.
Yeah. Um...
my checks are bouncing.
Well, that's what happens
when you make withdrawals
and you don't make
deposits, Shannon.
When do I get the
money dad left me?
The money from the will?
There was no will.
What?
Shannon, your father and
I had a living trust.
Everything passed to me.
I'm afraid there was nothing
specifically designated for you.
Why would he do that?
Well, maybe he just wanted
you to find your own way.
We all have to work, Shannon.
Most of us are
the better for it.
I can work. I just got this
really prestigious internship,
and I'm not gonna make
any money for awhile,
but I'm gonna be working,
like, 16 hours a day.
The only thing I've ever seen you do
16 hours a day straight is sleep.
I just need to get to New York.
I need just something--
something to get started.
I'll pay you back.
This week it's an internship.
Last year it was what,
interior design?
You'll never pay me back.
And you'll only hate
yourself even more.
I really want this, Sabrina.
I can do this.
I'm sorry, Shannon.
You're on your own.
Oh. Double sixes.
How nice for you.
Lucky.
I hope you didn't
get the wrong idea,
seeing me with the baby.
What wrong idea would that be?
You and Claire are close, and
you spend a lot of
time with Aaron.
I just wouldn't want
to overstep my bounds.
Did she tell you
we had a fight?
She didn't say it was a fight.
She was gonna give it up,
you know.
For adoption.
She tell you that?
Yeah, when I built the cradle.
Oh, of course.
When you built the cradle.
- Why do you ask?
- She's...
She's got a bit to learn
about being a mum--
responsibility and all.
Hmm. Now that's an
interesting thingto say
for a heroin addict.
Recovering addict.
Recovering.
It's your turn.
Here, let me help you.
I got him.
I said I got him, man.
Take a break.
Look--
What, you suddenly
give a damn about me?
Just leave me alone,
both of you.
I got it.
Hey!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Hey.
Come here.
Hey. Sawyer? Hey, you okay?
I would've left you behind.
Shut up, man. Don't try that.
I did leave you behind.
Yeah, well,
good thing I ain't you.
Hey! Uh, hey, hey!
No, no, no, no. Sawyer! Sawyer!
Sawyer! Hey!
Water! Water!
- Sawyer!
- Here you go.
Sawyer. Come on, man.
Here. Here.
Come on.
Sawyer.
What's the matter with him?
Well, the fever--
he's got an infection. He's dehydrated.
We gotta keep moving.
- What?
- We gotta keep going.
You want to stay, that's fine.
But we're rolling out.
We can't just leave him, Ana.
Maybe if we just rest a little while,
he'll regain consciousness.
Rest? Here?
Do you remember what happened to us,
what they did to us?
You remember Goodwin?
Ana's right.
Maybe we should just push on.
Hey,  you know what?
I don't remember Goodwin.
And I'm really sorry about whatever
happened to him, but I don't care.
Mr. Eko?
Can you help me
make a stretcher?
Hey, Bernard, I need four sticks.
Sturdy ones about 5 feet long.
Yeah. You got it.
You're gonna carry your friend?
Yeah. We're gonna carry him.
Why are you doing
this, Shannon?
I didn't ask you to follow me.
No, you'd rather be out here
alone and get lost or hurt.
I don't need your help, Sayid.
Walt is not out here!
You're following a labrador,
not a bloodhound,
in an effort to find a boy who is on
a raft in the middle of the ocean!
- He's not on the raft.
- What are you talking about?
We found the bottle
on the beach.
The bottle with the messages
that they brought with them?
I know he's out here somewhere.
I saw Walt.
And the raft is gone,
and he is all alone.
Shannon.
Come on.
Cindy?
Okay.
Here.
Cindy!
Where's Cindy?
She was just here.
Cindy. Cindy!
I don't know. She was--
- Did they take her?
How could she just be gone?
Cindy! Cindy!
I'm going after her.
No. We stay together.
We split up,
we give them what they want.
This is all your fault.
We never should have
gone through the jungle.
You risked our lives to save him.
He's already dead!
This one's on you.
What the hell is that?
Oh, god!
Run!
- Hey.
She said no.
I guess she knew why
I asked for the money.
Can I crash at your
place in New York for...
just a little while,
until I get on my feet?
I'm leaving New York.
She offered me a job.
You're going to work
for your mother?
It's a really good
job, Shannon.
Look, this is all
I have right now,
but my trust fund's gonna kick
in at the end of the month.
And after that I could
absolutely keep you afloat.
Thank you, but, um...
I'm gonna figure out a
way to make my own money.
But who knows when that's gonna be?
Just take it.
What, you don't
think I can do it?
I didn't say that.
You believe I can,
or don't you, Boone?
Okay, you know what?
I really want you to just take your
money, go work for your mother.
I don't want it.
Just take it, all right?
- I'm trying to help you, Shannon!
- I don't want your money!
Okay.
Shannon!
Are you okay?
Do not help me up!
Let's go back.
Why don't you believe me?
I need you to believe in me!
- I do believe in you.
- You don't!
No one does.
They think that I am
some kind of joke.
They think I'm worthless.
Shannon, you are not worthless.
You say that now,
but you don't...
you're just gonna leave me.
I know as soon as we get out of here,
I will never leave you.
I love you.
And I believe you.
You do?
I do.
Shh.
Do you see him?
Walt!
- Walt!
- Shannon!
Walt! Wait!
Shannon!
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com