Previously on "Lost"...
- Good luck.
- Same to you.
- We have to fire the flare.
- It doesn't make--
Look, are you gonna give me the damn gun,
or am I gonna have to take it?
Please, god.
It's coming back!
We're gonna have
to take the boy.
What? What'd you say?
The boy--
we're gonna have to take him.
- Hey!
- Dad!
- No!
Dad! Help me!
- Walt!
- Help me, dad!
No, no, no.
Stop it!
Stop it! We can't!
Locke found a...
a hatch in the ground.
Sun comes up in three hours,
and we're all gonna be
here to see that happen.
We're gonna stay here tonight, okay?
Together.
- John, what are you doing?
- I'm going in.
Locke's going into that thing
whether you like it or not.
I'm going in the hatch.
Live together,
die alone, right?
Right.
John!
I think there's something down here!
Dad, please! Dad!
Walt! Walt!
Mike?!
Sawyer!
Hang on, Mike!
Hang on!
Mike!
Aah!
Mike.
Mike?
Mike!
Kate!
- Where's Walt?
- I don't know.
- Where is he?
Where the hell is my son?!
Walt!
How'd you hurt your leg?
Got hit by a car.
Ow.
Yeah.
So this is the paperwork
your ex-wife sent over.
She's not my ex-wife,
man, she's--
she's just Walt's mother.
She, uh-- Susan-- she just got a
job in Rome with her boyfriend.
They wanna take Walt with 'em.
Oh, don't worry. I'm gonna take
real good care of you, Mr. Dylan.
Dawson.
Right. Sorry. Dawson.
So this boyfriend--
this is this guy Brian Porter?
Yeah. Why? What's it say?
It seems that
Susan wants you to
relinquish your rights
as Walt's father so that Mr.
Porter can adopt him.
She wants me to
sign my son away?
It's the only way they can
proceed with the adoption, yeah.
Listen, if you sign this document,
legally,
he'll be no different than any
other kid you pass on the street.
You'd be giving up your
paternal rights-- all of them.
Yeah,
so then can I stop her from going?
Ooh,
I guess we could file an injunction
so she couldn't leave the city,
but--
Yeah, that. I wanna do that.
Right.
Um, Mr. Dawson.
The fact that you came
in through these doors--
that tells me something.
It tells me that I'm the
best that you can afford.
If we go forward with this,
it's gonna take money--
a lot of it,
even at my rates.
This is David and Goliath,
so I gotta ask you,
are you sure you
wanna do this?
They're not taking
my son away.
Walt!
Mike!
You should save your energy.
They took my son.
Yeah, I saw that-- onto a boat, which
means he's not in shoutin' distance.
You don't know that.
Well,
I got a pretty good sense.
And even if he was,
there's nothing you can do.
Look, if he can hear me,
he knows that I'm alive,
that I'm coming for him,
that I'm going to get him back!
Right now all I've got is that
maybe my son can hear me.
Does that make
any sense to you?
Yeah.
W alt!
Walt!
Kate?
Kate!
- John.
- Easy. Easy. Easy.
Behind you.
Are you him?
Jin!
J in!
Thought we had to
save our energy.
Yeah, well...
Jin's still out
there in the water,
so if it's okay by you,
I'm gonna keep shoutin' awhile.
Jin!
Feeling guilty?
What?
You made me fire that flare.
I made you fire...
What, this is my fault?!
They took my son.
They found us, took Walt,
because you made me fire the flare.
Well,
at least Walt is on a boat,
probably wrapped in a
blanket with a cup of cocoa,
- While we're on this piece--
- Get off my raft.
What?
Get--
What the hell is that?
I see you managed to hold
onto your best friend there.
Thing ain't gonna work anyway.
- It'll work.
- You were underwater.
What do you know about guns anyway,
hoss?
It'll work.
If the bullets are dry,
the powder's dry. If the powder's dry...
Oh, my--
what the hell is that?
It's a shark.
It's only a shark.
"It's only a shark"?
That's supposed to
make me feel better?
Well, I guess I know why the
shark is hanging around--
your shoulder.
Oh, well,
I'll just stop bleedin', then.
You suddenly forget
what happened,
why I got shot?
What?
I mean,
how abouta little gratitude here?
I mean, how about a thank you?
A thank you? For what?
For you trying to
save your own ass?
You want me off this raft?
You got it.
I was trying to
save your damn kid.
Let's talk about Walt, shall we, Mr.
Dawson?
Uh, sure. Okay.
When was the last time
you actually saw your son?
Um, about a year ago.
It was 14 months, actually.
Is that a question, Lizzy?
Why is that, Mr. Dawson?
Why so long?
Susan took him to Amsterdam,
for work.
And you didn't have
a problem with that?
Excuse me?
Well, since she's now going to Rome,
and you're filing an injunction.
Just seems a little
inconsistent to me.
Incon-- no.
- No, don't. Don't do--
- No, no, no.
She's baiting you.
Don't answer.
She took him, though.
- I didn't want her to go.
- Michael, please don't talk.
You said there was
nothing I could do.
And you didn't do anything,
did you?
He's not gonna answer
that question.
That's because
there is no answer.
You were in an accident recently,
hmm?
Yeah.
You had several surgeries,
spent weeks in a private hospital room,
extensive rehabilitation.
Who paid for all of that, Mr.
Dawson?
I didn't ask you for anything.
Could the record reflect that Mr.
Dawson acknowledged
that Miss Lloyd
paid his bills?
Susan, tell them that I
didn't ask you for anything.
Please don't address
my client directly.
Do you know what Walt's
first words were, Mr. Dawson?
- I'm sorry. What?
- His first words.
Do you know what they were?
I... no.
I wasn't there.
Do you know what his
favorite food is?
- Do you--
- No.
Okay, this is unnecessary.
No.
Well, for someone who wants to
retain his paternal rights so badly,
you don't seem to know much
about your son, Mr. Dawson.
I'm his father.
I'm sorry. Could you say that louder,
please, just for the record?
I'm his father.
Hey, are you crazy?
You  gonna take a bullet
out with your bare hands?
You got a better idea?
Then go to hell.
You're never gonna be able
to do it by yourself.
I thought we parted ways,
Mike.
We're caught in
the same current.
You still talking?
Come on.
You got a band-aid?
Are you?
Are you him?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
I can't believe it.
You're finally here.
Well...
here I am.
Who's she?
She's with me.
What did one snowman say
to the other snowman?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Get rid of the knife.
You're not him!
We didn't come
here to hurt you.
Yeah?
Then why did you come?
We were in a plane crash.
Were you now?
And when was that?
44 days ago.
44 days?
Move.
- How long have you been down here?
- Shut it.
Tie him up.
Do it!
Wait, wait, wait.
You're tying up the wrong person.
How's that, brother?
It's pointless to tie me up.
I'm not dangerous.
But her, she's a fugitive.
So what does that make you then,
brother?
I'm a regional collections manager
for a cardboard manufacturer.
Boxes, primarily.
All right, then,
box man, tie her up.
- Don't you think about touch--
- Hey!
You be a good girl, right?
What do you think
you're doing?
Doing what's best
for all of us.
Right, bring her here.
John. Hey. Wait! Hey!
Shut it.
Wait!
You're kidding, right?
You're going back?
Yeah.
What about all that
stuff you said about
waiting till morning and
watching the sunrise?
I changed my mind.
What do you suppose
all that's about?
I reckon Jack's gonna
do something heroic.
What?
You always try to be funny when you
don't want to answer a question.
- "Try to be funny"?
- Hmm.
What's this?
Oh. Found it in the jungle.
- You found it?
- Yeah.
Be careful.
Be careful with it.
Here. Here. Take Aaron.
Come here. There you go.
You gotta be careful there.
You know, it's the Virgin Mary.
She's holy.
Didn't realize you
were so religious.
I'm not. It's just, you know,
it might come in handy.
Be a nice thing
to have around.
Yeah.
It wasn't the flare.
I said, it wasn't the flare.
Those people that did this--
at first, I thought they were
fishermen or pirates or something.
Then I got a good
look at their boat.
You know anything about boats,
Mike?
Boat like that wasn't
built for the open ocean.
Water's comin' over the side,
first little squall.
Maybe got a range
of a hundred miles.
A boat like that had to have
left port from somewhere close,
like the island.
French chick said the others
were coming for the kid.
I think they came, Mike.
What?
He's the one they wanted,
why I got a bullet
in my shoulder.
Hell, Bluebeard blew us up
because they wanted your kid.
- You saying this is my fault?
- Yeah. That's what I'm sayin'.
They took my son
because of you.
- Me?
- They were sailing away!
They found us because they
were looking for us, for Walt!
Don't you ever say his name again,
ever!
What you gonna do, splash me?
- Look, I know how--
- Shut up.
Don't even.
You have no idea what it's like
to care for somebody else.
Hi.
Where  are your lawyers?
I told them I wanted to talk,
just you and me.
But if you want yours,
I understand.
No. That's okay.
I think you're gonna win.
Excuse me?
In court. I think you're gonna keep me
from leaving the country with Walt.
But I just...
have to ask you why.
Why what?
Why are you doing this?
He's my son.
Since when, Michael?
Look, I know you don't care
about what's best for me, but
in Rome,
I'll be a senior partner at the firm.
I'll be able to give
Walt anything he needs.
You're still on disability, Michael.
You can't work.
You're about to be evicted
from your apartment.
You got your lawyers
checking up on me now?
Well, of course I did,
just like you had your
lawyers checking up on me.
- Nobody's winning here.
- Then stop.
Michael, the first thing you need
to do is take care of yourself.
You need to get healthy.
You need to get back on
your feet financially
so that you can get back
to pursuing your art.
You have rare talent as an artist,
Michael.
But how are you gonna do that,
any of that,
and still be a part
of Walt's life?
I'll do it by doing it.
Walt is my responsibility,
too.
Then let him go.
Because it's not
about you or me.
It's about him.
I don't wanna go to court,
Michael.
So please just...
let him go.
The pilot said we had lost
radio contact, but by then,
we were already a thousand
miles off course.
Any search teams would
have given up weeks ago.
So you were traveling from
Sydney to Los Angeles?
Yes.
So they're all
still out there?
Yeah, as far as I know.
Could you tell me your name?
My name?
My name is Desmond.
Desmond, I'm John.
You should know,
the gun is really unnecessary.
Oh, yeah?
So I should just hand it
over to you then, should I?
How many of you are there?
Uh, 43,
but 4 sailed out this morning on a raft.
A raft?
That simulated sunlight--
is that because you never leave?
Is there another way out?
How many of your group
have gotten sick?
Sick?
Sick-- as in ill, as in dead.
Is that why it says "quarantine"
on the inside of the hatch?
Answer the question.
No one has. No one.
No one's sick.
Get up.
Move.
Stand right there.
Do you know how to use this,
box man?
I haven't seen one of
those in 20 years.
- Do you know how to use it?!
- Yes. Sit.
Right, now listen carefully.
Type in exactly what I tell you,
understand? Exactly. Nothing else.
4. 8. 15.
Did you hear that?
What?
What did you just put in?
What number did
you just put in?!
- 15.
- Right. 16.
23. 42. Now press "execute."
Uh... what's gonna happen?
Just push it!
Kate!
Locke!
Who the hell is that?
That would be Jack.
Who is he?
His name is Jack.
He's our doctor.
What's he doing here?
Well, to be honest with you,
I'm a little surprised to see him.
Your doctor has a gun,
brother.
Move.
Make one sound and I'll shoot.
Jack!
I wouldn't do that, Jack.
Where's Kate?
What the hell did you--
Move...
and I kill him.
- Put the gun down.
- Where's Kate?
- Jack, it's okay.
- I said drop it!
- Where's Kate?!
- She's fine.Just put down--
I'm not putting down anything.
Do you want him to die?
Put it down.
Is this what you were talking about,
Locke?
Is this your destiny?
"All roads lead here."
Calm down.
Lower your gun,
or I'll blow his darned head off,
brother!
You.
What the hell is that?
Part of the raft--
one of the pontoons.
Stop paddling.
Hey, stop it!
You're putting a strain on the vines.
It's going to break us up.
Damn it, you're gonna--
Sawyer!
Climb up.
I do, and we both sink.
I'm going for the pontoon.
Don't be an idiot.
You see that toothy
son of a bitch,
you aim and squeeze. Got it?
Got it.
Come on, come on, come on.
Sawyer?
Sawyer!
Give me your hand.
There he is. Do you see him?
- Hi.
- Oh!
Hey.
Hey, I'm sorry I'm late.
Packing's been a disaster,
and the plane leaves first
thing in the morning.
Sure.
No problem.
Uh, hey,
do you want to say hi, Walt?
Hi, Walt. I'm...
I'm...
Hey, uh, this is for you, man.
He like bears?
Yes. Uh, sure.
He's just really shy.
Hey, little man.
Oh, I guess I can't call you that.
I mean, 'cause look how big you are.
So...
you and I, we're not gonna see
each other for awhile, Walt.
Uh,
but you are gonna have a great life.
I know your mommy--
she's gonna take real good care of you,
and Brian is...
gonna take good care of you,
too.
But you know what?
I just want you to know that
no matter where you go, I...
that your daddy...
yeah, your daddy--
he loves you very, very much.
And I always will.
Always.
Okay?
I'm sorry. He's...
No.
It's okay.
Uh...
Hey, here. Uh...
Just, you know...
You know, let him know it's
from me sometime, okay?
Okay.
Good-bye, Michael.
Yeah. Bye.
It's... uh...
You all right, Mike?
It was my fault.
What?
I never should have
brought him on the raft.
I'm gonna get him back.
I'm gonna get back my son.
Well, how about that?
Current brought us back.
We're home.
Jin?
- Michael! Sawyer!
- Jin!
Oh, oh, oh!
Jin, what's wrong?
Others. Others. Others.
What?
Others! Others!
Others.
Transcript: RaceMan
Synchro: Travis