Previously on "Lost"...
We were together
for only one week.
They came.
They came and took her.
Alex...
They took my baby.
Somebody, please help me!
He had this-- this thing, like--
like a needle,
and he stabbed me with it.
He was trying to hurt my baby.
We got a problem.
The manifest--
the names of everyone
who survived--
I interviewed everyone.
One of them isn't in the manifest...
Hello there.
Ethan.
I think they've been taken.
Claire!
I don't remember Ethan.
I don't remember
what he did to me.
Help me!
Don't believe a word he says!
He's one of them.
I have no idea what
she's talking about.
For a long time, he will lie.
I don't know why you're asking
me all these questions.
This is all a mistake.
Tell me the truth!
Tell me who you are!
What if he's telling
the truth, John?
What if he's not?
Hey.
Hey, it's okay, sweetie.
Shh.
Hey, sweetie, it's all right.
- John? John? Wake up.
- What, Claire? What?
He's burning up,
and he's got a rash.
And I need to find Jack.
He's, uh,
he's on shift at the hatch.
- Okay.
- Uh, uh, no, Claire, wait.
- Claire, wait.
- No, I can't, John, okay?
No, no, no. You're not walking through
the jungle in the middle of the night.
I'll go get Jack.
I'll send him right back here.
- Okay.
- Don't worry.
Jack.
What's going on?
The baby's got a fever.
- A fever?
- Claire was coming here.
- He asleep?
- Not a sound all night.
I'll get back here
as soon as I can.
Shh.
Hey, hey, sweetie, it's okay.
It's okay.
Mommy's just gonna cool you down, okay?
Okay? Shh. It's okay.
Jack?
What are you doing here?
You stay away from us!
He's infected, isn't he?
What?
Your child-- he's sick.
Just get away.
You get away from us!
You don't remember, do you?
It's a vaccine.
We don't want him to get sick.
Hey, get back!
Get away from her!
What do you think
you're doing here?
What are you doing here?
Just get out of our camp.
What happened?
What did she say?
She said there's
something wrong with him.
It's just not like him.
He always sleeps through the night.
And this rash--
I mean, there's something wrong.
Babies get sick, Claire.
Okay, what about
the fever and cough?
Perfectly normal.
And he hasn't been
eating at all, and--
Claire, he's okay.
It's probably roseola.
It's a typical virus that's
common in children his age,
and the rash is a sign of it.
Okay. What if it's not?
What if he caught
something really bad?
Like some kind of infection?
Infection? Where did
you get that idea?
Rousseau was here.
What did she say to you?
She said she knew he was sick, okay?
That he's infected.
Claire, there is no infection.
We've been on this island for two
months, and no one's gotten sick.
Rousseau's crazy.
We're gonna let the fever
just run its course.
It's gonna be fine, okay?
Trust me.
I've gotta get
back to the hatch.
And I'll come back in a couple
hours and check on him again, okay?
-  Okay?
- Yeah.
Hey, I'm sure that if there was
something wrong, Jack would know.
Are you sure about this?
We don't really know her.
I think she can help me.
Hey.
Hey, guys.
So you're a shrink, right?
I'm a clinical psychologist,
but "shrink" works, too.
Can you help people
remember things?
I guess it depends on what
you need to remember.
So it was our second
week on the island.
I was out in the jungle,
and I--
I thought I was having the baby.
Charlie was with me.
And there was this man-- Ethan.
We thought he was one of us
from the plane, but he wasn't.
So he took me--
he took both of us. And...
I don't remember.
I don't remember anything.
When Jack and I found Charlie,
he was hanging from a tree by his neck.
I have no idea what happened,
and now I'm seeing
these flashes of things.
And, you know, I have amnesia.
There's two weeks
missing from my life.
Claire, I don't think
you have amnesia.
You know, sometimes when
something terrible happens to us,
there's a little switch in
your head that flicks on to
protect us from having
to deal with it.
Maybe your memories
aren't gone.
Maybe you're just
blocking them.
Then I need you
to unblock them.
'Cause my baby's sick,
and they did something to him.
Do you have to go
to the bathroom?
No.
Well,  just let us
know when you do.
Yeah, I'll look
forward to that.
Thought you might like
something to read.
Dostoevsky. You don't
have any Stephen King?
The library's a
little outdated.
Right. Well, thanks.
What's with the book?
Just something to
pass the time.
Did you know that Hemingway
was jealous of Dostoevsky?
No, John, I didn't know that.
He wanted to be the
world's greatest writer but
convinced himself that he could never
get out from under Dostoevsky's shadow.
Kind of sad, really.
What are we doing, Jack?
What are we doing?
We can't hide him
down here forever.
Changing shifts around is gonna
get people asking questions.
I just want to know what
the long-term plan is.
Well, John,
let me ask you this--
we don't have a long-term
plan for the button,
but we keep pushing it,
don't we?
Look, until we know who he is,
whether or not he's telling the truth,
we have to keep doing
what we're doing.
If you've got a better idea,
let's hear it.
How about you let me go?
Now we're away from all
the noises of the camp.
Just breathe.
Let your whole body relax.
Good.
Listen to the waves.
Good, in...
and out slowly. Good.
Keep your eyes closed.
Very relaxed, Claire.
Just keep breathing.
Now I want you to visualize
yourself when you were pregnant.
Keep listening to my voice.
Think about what you see.
It's a vaccine.
We don't want him to get sick.
When was your last
checkup, Claire?
Oh, I haven't been in a while.
I've been busy, and...
I'm going to Los Angeles.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Traveling in your third trimester,
that's not usually recommended.
Uh, there's a family there. I'm,
uh, giving the baby up for adoption.
Oh, of course. I understand.
The sedative I gave
you is very mild.
I know these exams
can be very stressful.
I'm going to give you
a shot now, Claire.
A little medicine
for your baby.
Don't worry.
You're just gonna feel a little pinch.
Aah!
It's okay. You're all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
It was Ethan! I saw Ethan!
I  saw him. It was Ethan!
- Claire, Claire, it's okay.
- No, it's not!
- You're all right.
- No, I'm not all right!
It was Ethan!
- What happened?
- I don't know. She just--
- What did you do?
- Nothing, she just--
Do it again!
No, Claire, you were screaming.
But I remembered, okay?
- I saw Ethan.
- Claire...
He was there,
and he was giving me an exam.
What you saw could be
combining experiences of what
happened before the crash to the things
that happened here on the island.
No, okay, no! This was real!
I was drugged.
He did something to me.
Claire, you need to calm down,
all right? It's not good for you.
You know what?
Aaron is sick, okay?
I need to find that place!
That room--
it's real. It's real.
Okay, and there's medicine there.
For the baby.
I need to find it.
Kate, Kate, please,
help me find it.
Hello?
- What's the--
- Shh.
- Hello?
- Howdy.
Hello, John. You are alone?
Not anymore.
- How many of you--
- Shut up.
I was hoping to borrow a saw.
Absolutely. Right this way.
I need a gun,
and you don't get to ask why.
Well,  Thelma, seeing as I got all
the guns, I do get to ask why.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, I do.
Watch.
Why?
Just give me a gun, Sawyer.
Check it out.
I found a new pair of glasses damn
near my prescription. You like 'em?
All right, I'm going into the
jungle to track down Rousseau.
The french chick? What for?
Claire thinks she knows where
there might be some medicine.
The baby's sick.
- Well, hell, I got medicine.
- She thinks he's really sick--
as in "quarantine" sick.
What do you think?
I  think she's a
little too worried.
But she's going after
Rousseau with or without me.
No boys allowed, huh?
All right, what do you want?
9 millimeter or rifle?
I don't think this
is a good idea.
Maybe you should
listen to Jack.
But what if jack's wrong, okay?
Jack said the fever would break,
and it hasn't. He's getting worse.
Just because it hasn't broken yet,
it doesn't--
Well, how long am I
supposed to wait, Sun?
A mother should not
leave her child.
I'm sorry. Are you a mother?
No...
I'm not.
Claire, are you sure
you want to do this?
What did you say?
Are you sure you
want to do this?
You need to be sure.
You have to get out of here--
Do you have to put
that in my tummy?
'Cause it really, really hurts.
I know.
I wish there was another way.
But the baby needs it, Claire.
Okay?
Okay.
There, all done.
That wasn't so bad, was it?
No.
And now because you've
been such a good girl,
I think it's time
for a surprise.
Claire, this way. Here we go.
Over here.
What is this place?
- It's for your baby, Claire.
- Oh, it's amazing.
Wow. Hey...
What-- what happened
to Charlie?
Charlie? Oh, he's fine.
When we got far enough from camp,
I let him go back.
Oh.
So where did it all come from?
Well, I'd love to explain
everything to you, Claire,
but I'm afraid it would be a
little overwhelming right now.
What...
Go ahead, turn it on.
Ethan?
Wait here. I'll be right back.
Okay.
What the hell happened?
You were supposed to make the list
and then bring her in. Was I unclear?
It's not my fault.
They knew I wasn't on the plane.
They had a manifest.
Well, what am I
supposed to tell him?
You know what he's gonna do when
he finds out? Damn it, Ethan.
Get out.
Get out of here.
Claire?
Claire, are you all right?
I, um...
Ready to go?
Hey, sweetheart, shh,
mommy's gotta go now, sweetheart, okay?
Shh, don't cry.
Don't cry. It's okay.
I'll be back really soon.
And I'll make you feel all better, okay?
I promise.
Thanks.
Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Are you sure this is her trail?
We started at the exact spot
where we chased her off the beach.
So what do you know
about Rousseau?
Not much.
You spent all that time with her when
you went out to "the Black Rock."
You must have talked
about something.
Just about her ship
crashing here--
her and her research
team getting stranded.
What happened to them?
They died.
How?
Tracks are gone.
Trail ends here.
Kate, how did they die?
She killed them.
What?
- Why-- why would she--
- Because they were infected.
You believe me now, don't you?
I want you to take
me back there.
Back?
- To where I scratched you.
- Claire--
No, okay, she knows I remember.
I remember a lot of it now.
I remember the room,
the medicine, a teenage girl.
Okay, so don't lie to me
and make out you don't know
what I'm talking about.
My baby is sick, and you're gonna take
me back there to get what he needs
right now.
It's not far from here.
Jack...
may I have a word with you?
Sure.
Who is he?
What?
The man that you are
keeping in the hatch.
Did Locke tell you--
Locke did not tell me anything.
Who is he?
We don't know.
I wish to speak to him.
Speak to him about what?
I wish to speak to him alone.
Can you arrange this?
Why should I do that?
Because you wish to
keep this a secret.
Why are we stopping here?
This is where you scratched me.
But there's nothing here.
Where do we go next?
Why are you asking me that?
You need to tell
me where to go!
Where is this room?!
Look, how can you
be saying that?
Okay, you grabbed me.
That's why I scratched you--
because you were taking
me back to them!
Is that what you think?
You said you remembered.
That's why I brought you here.
- You lied!
- Hey!
Get your hands off of her.
Go ahead.
Please.
Do it.
Claire!
Wake up.
How's it coming?
One down. One to go.
Now all's we need is a little
foot to put it on, huh?
Tell you what--
what do you say we sneak
out of here and take a walk?
Okay.
Whoa.
I'm sorry this is the first time
I've managed to get you out.
My friends are afraid
you'll run away.
Whoa-ho! Whoa!
- Don't tell on me, okay?
- Oh, okay.
Whoa. Easy now.
Easy. Easy! Whoa.
Okay.
Okay, here. This'll help.
Thanks.
- Mmm.
- What?
- That is really sour.
- Is it?
- Mmm.
- I hadn't noticed.
Blah.
Oh!
Hey--he's kicking.
- May I?
- Yeah...
Claire, can I tell
you a secret?
Yes.
I'm gonna miss you. I wi...
I wish you didn't have to go.
Maybe I don't have to go.
We've been through
this, Claire.
There's not enough vaccine
for you and the baby.
But I'm not-- I'm not sick.
Thank god.
And once you've delivered,
you can go back to your friends,
and hopefully you'll
stay that way.
What... what if I
want to see the baby?
Hey, nobody's going to take him from
you unless that's what you want.
You have a choice.
We're  good people, Claire.
We're a good family.
But if you're gonna
trust us with your child,
I want you to be sure.
Okay?
Sure.
There you are.
Where are you going?
I know this is it. It's here.
Claire!
Leave her alone.
- Excuse me?
- Let her look.
Look for what?
Claire!
Flashlights.
There are lights. I'm gonna
see if I can turn the power on.
Are you okay?
This way.
What is this place?
It's where they were
gonna keep him.
Wake up.
- Who are you?
- Shh! They'll hear you.
Look, you have to
get out of here.
What?
You have to get
out of here-- now!
- Wha-- no, no, no. I can't leave.
- Yes, you can. Come on.
I can't leave. No! Stop.
What are you doing?
Don't scream.
They're gonna do it tonight.
What? Do what?
What are you talking about? Ow!
You're going to die.
They're gonna cut him out of you.
I can get you back to your camp,
but we have to leave now.
No, no, no! Hey, you're lying.
You're lying, okay? I'm sure about this.
Where's Ethan? I want to talk to Ethan.
Ethan wouldn't hurt me.
You'll thank me
for this one day.
It's a vaccine.
We don't want him to get sick.
It's here.
The medicine's here.
Help me.
Help!
Kate! Come here!
I need some help!
Help me up with this.
What is it?
It's in here.
The vaccine's in here.
- Okay. Come on.
- Okay.
One, two, three!
Okay.
It was in here.
The vaccine was in here!
It was in--
where is it, where is it, where is it?
The vaccine was in here!
Where is it?!
You were bringing me back here.
You know where it is,
don't you?
Tell me! Tell me where it is!
Tell me!
Ethan?
Ethan!
Ethan, I'm sure.
Hey! Hey, Ethan!
Ethan!
I'm-- I'm sure I want--
I want you to take the baby.
Ethan!
Who are-- who are you?
- Claire!
- Yeah! I'm here!
I can hear you! Where are you?
Be quiet.
I'm here, Ethan! Be quiet.
No, no. It's okay.
I have to give him to them.
I have to give him to them
so he'll be safe, okay?
Help! I'm here! Ethan!
- Stop!
- No!
You weren't...
trying to take me back, were you?
You were trying to save me.
I carried you on my
back to your camp.
I left youwhere they
would find you.
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
You're not the only one who didn't
find what they were looking for.
This is as far as I go.
Your baby...
was it a girl?
Yes.
What was her name?
Alex...
Alexandra.
I remember a girl--
a girl with blue eyes?
She, uh, she helped me.
She saved me... just like you did.
She wasn't like the others.
She was good.
I'm sorry
that you didn't find what
you were looking for.
And I hope your
baby's not infected.
But if it is...
I hope you know
what must be done.
Back for more tools?
He knows, John.
Well, there you go.
Be careful what you say to him.
He's smart and curious.
Just give us a shout
when you're done.
And if the alarm goes off,
don't tell him what it's for.
What is it for?
Hello.
I am Mr. Eko.
Henry Gale.
Do you mind if I sit, Henry?
Okay.
How long have you been in here?
Two days.
Are they treating you well?
Treating me well?
I'm a... a prisoner.
And I don't know
why or for what--
You are a prisoner because
they are being careful.
They are being careful because
they believe you are lying.
Why would I lie?
They think I'm one of these...
"others"? Other what?
Please stop talking, Henry.
The first night I
spent on this island,
I was dragged into
the jungle by two men.
They never spoke a word to me,
nor I to them.
I killed these men--
smashed in their
head with a stone,
felt their blood on my arms.
I need you to know
how sorry I am for this.
I need you to know that I am
back on a righteous path now
and that I regret my actions.
I ask you for your forgiveness.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I needed
to tell someone.
He looks good. Fever's broken.
The rash has even
started to fade.
Thank you so much.
I didn't do anything.
I'll, uh,
check back in a couple of hours, okay?
Okay.
Hey.
Hi!
Look.
Mommy made this for you when you
were still inside her tummy. Yeah.
You know what?
I wanted them to take you.
But now I know--
now I know that we're
supposed to be together,
you and me.
We're supposed to take
care of each other, okay?
You're mine, and I love you.
I love you so much.
Yeah.
- No cheeseburgers, huh?
- No cheeseburgers.
Bon appétit.
Is that true what you
said about Hemingway?
- You have good ears.
- You have thin doors.
- You read Hemingway?
- Sure.
Guy ran with the bulls,
fought in the spanish civil war--
stuff I can wrap my brain around.
This I can't get through five pages of.
Hmm. Dostoevsky had
his virtues, too.
He was a genius, for one.
Bullfighting isn't everything.
So which one are you?
I'm sorry?
Are you the genius?
Or are you the guy who always feels like
he's living in the shadow of
the genius?
I was...
I was never very muchinto
literary analysis.
I just don't understand why you
let the doctor call the shots.
No one calls the shots.
Jack and imake
decisions together.
Right. Okay.
My mistake.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com