How little?
Providence,Rhode Island
Like when you put on "a little" eye shadow.
And,you know,all this stuff,
it's just very unprofessional.
Don't touch the troll!
Is that what your mom used to say to your dates?
Put the trolls down,or I'll put a
staple right between your eyes.
Now,I know it's hard.
It's hard to look up when you're down.
It's hard to look up and see the light.
But I'm here to tell you folks...
the lord is with you.
You don't have to suffer.
You don't have to be lost.
The lord is talking to you right now.
He's saying,"you are my child,and you have a purpose.¡±
You think god forgot about you?
I tell you,no!
All you got to do is listen.
Can't you just hear those angels singing?
Isn't it beautiful?
It's time.
It's time to receive the message he's sending.
It's time to listen to the word of god!
Can you hear the glory?
I said,can't you just hear it?
I say,can't you just hear the lord?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-gagegao
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Supernatural
Season 02 Episode 13
Good morning.
You're not the usual guy.
No,uh...
just filling in.
So,how you feeling today,gloria?
I've never felt better.
So,no disturbances lately?
You mean,am I stark-raving cuckoo for cocoa puffs?
I didn't say that.
It's all right.
I know what people must think.
What do you think?
I think what I saw was real.
"Houses Of The Holy"
I'd like to know what you saw.
It was all over the news.
I stabbed a man in the heart.
Why would you do that?
Because it was god's will.
Did god talk to you?
I get the sense god's a little busy for house calls.
No,he --
he sent someone.
Someone?
An angel.
It came to me in this beautiful white light.
And it filled me with this...
feeling.
It's --
it's hard to describe.
And this angel...
spoke god's word.
And the word was to kill someone?
I know it sounds strange.
But what I did was very important.
I helped him smite an evil man.
I was chosen...for redemption.
This man you stabbed --
did the angel give you his name?
No.
He just told me to wait for the sign,
and the very next day,
I saw it right beside the man's doorway,and I knew.
Why him?
I just know what the angel told me --
that this man was guilty to his deepest foundations.
And that was good enough for me.
Hey!
Hey,man,you got to try this.
I mean,there really is magic in the magic fingers.
Dean,you're enjoying that way too much.
It's kind of making me uncomfortable.
XXXXXXXXX You got me on lockdown here.
I'm bored out of my skull.
Hey,you were the bank robber on the 11:00 news,not me.
We can't risk you just walking into
a government facility.
Aw,damn it.
That was my last quarter.
Hey!
You got any quarters?
No.
- So,did you get in to see that crazy hooker?
- Yeah.
Gloria sitnik.
And I'm not so sure she's crazy.
But she seriously believes that she was...
touched by an angel?
Yeah.
Blinding light,feelingsof spiritual ecstasy,the works.
I mean,she's living in a locked ward,
and she's totallyat peace.
Oh,yeah,you're right --
sounds completely sane.
What about the dudeshe stabbed?
Uh,carl gulley.
Said she killed him'cause he was evil.
- Was he?
- I don't know.
I couldn't findany dirt on him.
He didn't havea criminal record,
he worked at the campus library,
had lots of friends,was a churchgoer.
So gloria's just your standard-issue wacko?
I mean,she wouldn't bethe first nut job in history
to kill in the name of religion,know what I mean?
No,but she'sthe second in town to
murderbecause an angel told them to.
Little bit odd,don't you think?
Odd -- yeah.
Supernatural -- maybe.
But angels -- I don't think so.
Why not?
'Cause there'sno such thing,sam.
Dean,there's 10 timesas much lore about angels as
there is about anything elsewe've ever hunted.
There's a ton of loreon unicorns,too.
I hear that they rideon silver moonbeams
and they shoot rainbowsout of their ass.
Wait,there's no such thingas unicorns?
That's cute.
I'm just saying,man,there's some legends
that you just fileunder "bull crap.¡±
And you got angelson the "bull crap" list?
- Yep.
- Why?
- Because I've neverseen one.
- So what?
So I believe inwhat I can see.
Dean,you and ihave seen things
most peoplecouldn't even dream about.
Exactly.
With our own eyes --
that's hard proof,okay?
But in all this time,I have never seen
anythingthat looks like an angel.
Don't you think we would have crossed paths with them
or at least know someone that crossed paths with them?
No.
This is a demon or a spirit.
They find people a few friesshort of a happy meal,
and they trick theminto killing these randoMs.
Maybe.
Can we just -- I'm going stir-crazy,man.
Let's go by gloria'sapartment,huh?
I was just there.
Nothing.
No sulfur,no E.M.F.
You didn't see any fluffy,white wing feathers?
But gloria did saythe angel gave her
a sign right besidecarl gulley's doorway.
Could be something at his house.
It's worth checking out.
Hey,sam.
Think I found it.
It's a sign from up above.
I think I learneda valuable lesson.
Always take downyour christmas decorations after new year's,
or you might get filletedby a hooker from god.
I'm laughingon the inside.
You know,gloria said the guy was guiltyto
his deepest foundations.
You think she literallymeant the foundation?
You got something?
What is it?
It's a fingernail.
So much for the innocent church going librarian.
Whatever spoke to gloria about
this knew what it was talkingabout --
I'll give you that.
Yes?
Hi.
My name is zach.
Can I help you?
Did you bring quarters?
Dude,
I'm not enabling your sick habit.
You're likeone of those lab rats that pushes
the pleasure buttoninstead of the food button until it dies.
What are you talking about?
I eat.And I got news.
- Me too.
- All right,you go first.
Three students have disappearedoff the campus this year.
All of them were last seenat the library.
- Where carl gulley worked.
- yep.
- Sick bastard.
- So gloria's angel --
- angel?
- Okay,whatever this thing is.
- Whatever it is,it struck again.
- What?
I was listeningto the police radio before you got here.
There was this guy,zach smith,some local drunk.
He went up to a stranger'sfront door last night,
stabbed him in the heart.
I'm guessing he wentto the police and confessed?
Yep.
Roma downey made him do it.
Now,I,uh...
got the victim's address.
Find anything?
Frank likedhis catalog shopping.
That's about all I got. You?
Not much here.
Except he's got this one lockedfile on his computer that...
hold on.
Not anymore.
God.
What?
He's gotall these e-mails,dozens,
to this ladynamed jennifer.
This ladywho's 13 years old.
Oh,I don't wantto hear this.
Looks like they metin a chat room.
These e-mailsare pretty personal,dean.
Look at that.
- Setting up a time and place to meet.
- Great.
They were supposed to meettoday.
Well,I guess if you'regonna stab someone,good timing.
I don't know,man.
This is weird.
I mean,sure,some spiritsare out for vengeance,
but this one's almostlike a do-gooder,like a --
avenging angel?
Well,how elsedo you explain it,dean?
Three guys not connectedto each other
all stabbedthrough the heart?
At least twowere world-class pervs,
and I bet if you dug deep enoughon the other guy --
- hey.
- What?
You said carl gulleywas a churchgoer,right?
- Yeah.
- What was the nameof his church?
our lady of the angels?
Of course that would bethe name.
Looks like frank wentto the same church.
So,you're interestedin joining the parish?
We just don't feel right unlesswe hit church every sunday.
Where'd you sayyou lived before?
- Premont,texas.
- Really? That's a nice town.
St.Teresa's parish.
You must knowthe priest there.
Sure,yeah.
No,it's fr.O'malley.
I knowa fr.Shaughnessy.
Shaughnessy,exactly.
What did I say?
You know,we're just happyto be here now,father.
And we're happyto have you.
We could usesome young blood around here.
I got to ask --
no offense,but the neighborhood...
it's gone to seed a little.
There's no denying that.
But that's why what the churchdoes here is so important.
Like I always say,you can expect a miracle,
but in the meantime,you work your butt off.
- Yeah,we heardabout the murders.
- yes.
The victims were parishionersof mine.
I've known them for years.
And the killers said thatan angel made them do that?
Yes.
Misguided souls.
To thinkthat god's messenger would appear
and incite peopleto murder --
it's tragic.
So,you don't believein those angel yarns,huh?
Oh,no,I absolutely believe.
It kind of goeswith the job description.
Father,that's michael,right?
That's right.
The archangel michael,with the flaming sword --
the fighter of demons,holy force against evil.
So,they're not reallythe hallmark-card
version that everybody thinks?
They're fierce,right?
Vigilant.
I like to think of themas more loving than wrathful,but,
yes,a lot of scripture paints angelsas god's warriors.
"An angel of the lord appeared to them,
"the glory of the lordshone down upon them,
and they were terrified.¡±
Luke 2:9.
- Well,thank youfor speaking with us,father.
- It's my pleasure.
- Hope to see you again.
- Father,what's all that for?
Oh,that's for fr.Gregory.
He was a priest here.
Was?
Passed awayright on these steps.
He's interredin the church crypt.
- When did this happen?
- Two months ago.
He was shot for his car keys.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah,me too.
He was a good friend.
I didn't even have time to administer his last rites.
But like I said,it's a tough neighborhood.
And ever since he died,I've been praying my heart out.
For what?
For deliverance...
from the violenceand the bloodshed around here.
We could use a little divine intervention,I suppose.
Well,padre,thanks.
We'll see you again.
Well,it's all startingto make sense.
Devoted priestdies a violent death --
that's vengeful-spirit material right there.
He knew all the stiffs'cause they went to church here.
I'm willing to bet,because he was their priest,
he knew things about them that nobody else knew.
Then again,fr.Reynoldsstarted praying for
god's help about two months ago,right?
Right about the timeall this started?
Oh,come on,man.
What's your deal?
What do you mean?
Look,I'll admit,I'm a bit of a skeptic,
but since when are youall Mr. "700 club?¡±
Seriously,from the get-go,
you've been willing to buythis angel crap,man.
What's next?
Are you gonnastart praying every day?
I do.
What?
I do pray every day.
I have for a long time.
The things you learn about a guy.
Come on.
Let's go check out fr. Gregory's grave.
Sam,come on,get the lead out.
Sammy?
Sammy!
Hey.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Come on.
You saw it,didn't you?
- Didn't you?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Dean,I saw an angel.
You --
all right,come on.
I don't want a drink.
So,what makes you thinkyou saw a,uh,angel?
Just...
it appeared before me,and I just --
this feeling washed over me,you know?
Like --
like peace,like grace.
Okay,ecstasy boy,maybe we'll get you some
glow sticksand a nice Dr. Seuss hat,huh?
Dean,I'm serious.
It spoke to me.
It knew who I was.
It's just a spirit,sam.
And it's not the first one to
be able to readpeople's minds.
Okay,let me guess --
you were personally chosento smite some sinner?
You just got to waitfor some divine bat signal.
Is that it?
Yeah,actually.
Great.
I don't suppose you askedwhat this alleged bad guy did.
Actually,I did,dean,and the angel told me.
He hasn't done anything...
yet.
But he will.
Oh,this is --
I don't believe this.
Dean,the angelhasn't been wrong yet.
Someone's gonna do somethingawful,and I can stop it.
You're supposed tobe bad,too,sam.
Maybe I shouldstop you right now.
You know what,dean?
I don't understand.
Why can't you even considerthe possibility?
- What,that this is an angel?
- Yes.
Maybe we're hunting an angelhere,and we should stop.
Maybe this is god's will.
Okay.
All right.
You know what? I get it.
You've got faith.
That's -- hey,good for you.
I'm sureit makes things easier.
I'll tell you who elsehad faith like that --
mom.
She used to tell mewhen she tucked me in
that angelswere watching over us.
In fact,that was the last thingshe ever said to me.
You never told me that.
What's to tell?
She was wrong.
There was nothingprotecting her.
There's no higher power.
There's no god.
There's just chaosand violence and random,
unpredictable evilthat comes out of nowhere
and rips you to shreds.
You want me to believein this stuff?
I'm gonna need to seesome hard proof.
You got any?
Well,I do.
Proof that we're dealingwith a spirit.
- That looks like --
- it's wormwood...
a plant associatedwith the dead,
specifically the onesthat are not at rest.
I don't see it growinganywhere else,
except overthe murdered priest's marker.
It's him,sam.
Maybe.
Maybe?
Dean,I don't knowwhat to think.
Okay.
Want some more proof?
I'll give you more proof.
How?
We'll summon gregory's spirit.
What?
Here?
In the church?
Yeah.
Yeah,we just needa few odds and ends and
that séance ritualin dad's journal.
A séance,great.
I hope whoopi's available.
That's funny,actually.
Seriously.
If fr.Gregory's spiritis around,
the séance will bring himright to us.
If it's him,then we'll put him to rest.
But if it's an angel,it won't show.
- Nothing will happen.
- Exactly.
It's one of the perksof the job,sam.
We don't have to operateon faith.
We can know for sure.
Don't you want to knowfor sure?
Dude...
all right,I'll admit,we've gone pretty ghettowith
the spell work before, ut this takes the cake.
I mean,a spongebob place matinstead of an altar cloth?
We'll just put itspongebob-side-down.
Dean,that's it.
What?
That's the sign.
Where?
Right behind that guy.
That's him,dean.
And we have to stop him.
- wait a minute.
- What are you doing? Let me go.
You're not gonna kill somebodybecause
a ghost told you to.
XXXXXX I'm not gonna kill him.
I'm gonna stop him.
Define "stop," huh?
I mean,what are you gonna do?
Dean,please.
He's gonna hurt someone. You know it.
All right,come on.
Dean.
Unlock my door.
You're not killing anyone,sam.
I got this guy.
You go do the séance.
Dean.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Father,please.
I can explain.
actually,maybe I can'T.
Um...
this is A...
- a séance.
- A séance?
Young man,you are in a house of god.
It's based on early christianrites,if that helps.
Enough.
You're coming with me.
Father,please,just wait a second.
Oh,my god.
Is that...
is that an angel?
No,it's not.
It's just fr.Gregory.
Thomas!
I've come in answerto your prayers.
Sam....
I thought I sent youon your path.
You should hurry.
Father,I'm sorry.
But you're not an angel.
Of course I am.
No.
You're a man.
You're a spirit.
And you need to rest.
I was a man...
but now I'm an angel.
I was on the stepsat the church.
I felt that bulletpierce right through me.
But there was no pain.
And,suddenly,I could see...
everything.
Fr.Reynolds,I saw you...
praying and crying here.
I came to help you.
Help me how?
Damn it!
Those murders --
that was becauseof you?
I receivedthe word of god.
He spoke to me,told me to smite the wicked.
I'm carrying outhis will.
You're driving innocent peopleto kill.
Those innocent people are being offered redemption.
Some peopleneed redemption.
Don't they,sam?
How can you call thisredemption?
You can'tunderstand it now.
But the rules of manand the rules of
god are twovery different things.
Those people --
they're locked up.
No,they're happy.
They've found peace,beaten their demons.
And I've given themthe keys to heaven.
No,no.
This is vengeance.It's wrong.
Thomas,this goes againsteverything you believed.
You're lost,misguided.
Father...
no,I'm not misguided.
You are not an angel,thomas.
Men cannot be angels.
But...
but I-I don't understand.
You prayed for meto come.
I prayed for god's help,not this.
What you're doingis not god's will.
"Thou shalt not kill.¡± That's the word of god.
How come we stopped?
Um,weren't we gonna goto the movies?
We should go,or we're gonna be late.
I'm sorry.
It's just,I've never done this before.
Look,I said I was sorry.
Please...
stop it!
Are you okay?
Thank god!
Damn it.
Are you sureyou're okay?
You have a cellphone?
Call 911.
Let us help you.
No.
It's time to rest,thomas,to be at peace.
Please.
Let me give you last rites.
O holy hosts above,
I call upon theeas a servant of christ
to sanctifyour actions this day in
fulfillmentof the will of god.
Fr.Reynolds?
Rest.
I call uponthe archangel raphael,
master of the air,to make open the way.
Let the fire of the holy spiritnow descend,
that this being might beawakened to the world beyond.
Holy...
How was your day?
You were right.
It wasn't an angel.
It was gregory.
I don't know,dean,I just...
I wanted to believe...
so badly.
It's so damn hardto do this --
what we do --
all alone,you know?
There's so much evilout in the world,dean,
I feel like I could drownin it.
And when I thinkabout my destiny,
when I think abouthow I could end up...
yeah,well,don't worryabout that,all right?
I'm watching out for you.
Yeah,I know you are.
But you're just one person,dean.
And I needed to think that there was
something elsewatching,too,you know?
Some...
higher power,some greater good.
And that maybe...
maybe what?
Maybe I could be saved.
but,
you know,that just clouded my judgment.
And you're right.
I mean,we got to gowith what we know,
with what's right therein front of our own two eyes.
Well,it's funny you say that.
why?
Gregory's spirit gave yousome pretty good information.
That guy in the carwas bad news.
I barely got therein time.
What happened?
He's dead.
Did you...
no.
But I'll tell youone thing.
The way he died,if I hadn't have seen it
with my own two eyes,I neverwould have believed it.
I mean...
I don't knowwhat to call it.
what?
dean,what did you see?
Maybe...
...god's will.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-gagegao
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Supernatural
Season 02 Episode 13