My name is melinda gordon.
I'm married,I live
in a small town,
and I own an antique shop.
I might be just like you,
except that from the
time I was a little girl,
I knew that I could
talk to the dead.
It's all right,honey.
Earthbound spirits,my
grandmother called them.
They're stuck here because they have
unfinished business with the living
and they come to me for help.
In order to tell you my story,
I have to tell you theirs.
thank godness Unbelievable.
Isn't that what
he's supposed to do?
In one game?
It's very good.
All right. What do I know?
I played field hockey.
You know,maybe it's not
too late for me to go pro.
I was a great third baseman.
Hey,I didn't know that you
played baseball in high school.
I didn'T. Little league.
I played a lot of years,though,huh?
You know,I was 12 when I
hit my first home run.
I can still remember the
pitch. It was a low fastball.
It was right over the middle
of the plate,and I golfed it,
you know,right over
the center field fence.
Nice.
I can still hear my
parents screaming.
You know what? I would've
loved to have seen that.
You can,actually.
My dad took a video.
Oh,I so want to see that.
No. No.
Let's do that again.
That was incredible.
Wait. We have to find out if
your mom still has the videotape
of you getting your
first home run.
Oh,she's got it.
I swear,sometimes
when I call her,
I can hear it playing
in the background.
What I want to know is,does
she still have my baseball cards?
wait here
Hey,sorry. I'm an emt.
Are you all right?
Yes. I think so.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-小野人王 cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Ghost Whisperer
Season 2 Episode 10
collapse on the field exactly caused problems
he didn't lose consciousness
he's awake, responsive
- How is he?
- Well,he's a little woozy.
There's no sign of trauma,
and his nose stopped bleeding.
We should go to the hospital.
Why? He's up. He's talking.
I did everything I could.
Yeah,but I haven'T.
So,the stadium lights,was
that some kind of warning?
Felt like it.
if you see a ghost
in here,tell me.
How? There's gonna be people around.
Just give me a signal.
Like what? You want me to whistle?
No,like a baseball signal.
See,the first two mean nothing.
This,hit and run.
Oh,don't tempt me.
I really,all I want to know is how the
ghosts are affecting people,you know?
So,just do something simple.
Ok.
what's that a sign for?
All right.
Hi,coach.
Don't mean to bother you.
We just thought we'd stop
by and see if justin is ok.
We're still waiting.
Sorry we didn't get a chance
to meet back at the school.
It was a little crazy.I'm john heath.
Jim clancy.It's my wife melinda.
I'm justin's mom tracy.
Thank you so much for your help.
It was really scary.
I think I'm still shaking.
I'm sure he'll be ok.
I hope so. He worked
so hard for this.
Excuse me. I think I'm
gonna go check again.
I hate this waiting.
Hey,how was he when
they brought him in?
Much better.He was telling
everybody he wanted to go home.
I had to tell him to shut up and
get his butt back in the room.
Is his dad in there with him?
No.His dad passed away.
That's too bad.
It's too bad he can't
see what his son is doing.
He's doing very well.
Hey,is this the first year
you're coaching at grandview?
Second.I was in chicago before.
When I got a chance to come
back home,I jumped at it.
I was born and raised
right here in grandview.
There they are.
there's nothing wrong with me.
They didn't find anything,ok?
The tests are negative.
Probably was a sudden
drop of blood pressure,
maybe brought on by the
exertion of the game.
Just take it easy for a day.
Thank you,doctor.
- You sure you're all right?
- He'll be good.
Thanks a lot.
So,what,no ghost?
Just give me a signal.
I signaled you 5 times,
this whole thing.
- What's that?
- This is the signal.
What is it that you wanted me to do,
give you a sign before the sign?
How about I sing "some enchanted evening"
or do a cartwheel down the hall
because you wouldn't have missed that.
Ok.I'm sorry.
Well,was he with anybody?
I don't know. He was
all over the place,
but when he saw the
coach,he was mad.
So,you think the ghost is
attached to the coach.
Well,maybe,but I don't think
justin collapsed from exhaustion.
That's why they couldn't
find anything wrong.
No medical report is
gonna pick out a ghost.
you all right?
How do I explain 3 broken
windows to our insurance agent?
It's vandalism.
Let's just hope they don't ask
whether the vandal is dead or alive.
You know,it's times like
this I wish I could see them.
Why?
"Why?" So I could
say,"look,pal.
What the hell do you
think you were doing?
Confrontation,not the best
way to deal with the dead.
Well,he's got no trouble
confronting you or us.
He just feels threatened.
What,he breaks our windows,
and he feels threatened?
You know,look.
This is what I'm
talking about.
It's frustrating when the
dead can do more than I can.
This ghost wants to hurt justin
or the coach,I don't know.
But what I do know is that he's mad as hell
and he doesn't want me messing with him.
And he wants to raise our deductible.
Ok.Now I know two things.
I just wish I could do more.
You do a lot,and
this ghost...well,
he can't do what you're
thinking about right now.
Works for me.
it was made about 1940.
You turn the switch once,
and the lamp comes on,
and then you turn it again,
and the skirt moves
and makes it look like
she's hula dancing.
Thanks.
I guess everyone in town
is cleaning out their closets.
Well,it's for a good cause.
I actually found stuff I thought
I gave away a long time ago.
Hey,you going to the game tonight?
Are you kidding me?
Jim would rather miss his own
funeral than the big playoff game.
Well,you better get there early
because everybody I know is going.
I'll see you at the game.
All right,but whoever gets
there first has to save seats.
PLAYERS & COACHES  ONLY
You ok,lady?
Wait,wait.You think grandview
high school is haunted?
It is a high school,and I know a few unresolved
issues that would keep me from crossing over,jim.
But you didn't actually
see a ghost there,did you?
No,not yet,but I think there was a ghost
there that definitely wanted me to stay away.
Sorry about that.
There's got to be a rational
explanation,you know--
sewage gas,mutant cockroaches.
If I ever see a mutant cockroach,
you have to deal with it.
Yeah. I'm your man.
You don't think
we're all like that?
Yeah,but I'm only 60 feet away.
At least you're in left field.
How you doing?
What did you want with him?
"Him"?
Justin...
stay away from him.
I know who you are-- matt vonner.
No !
justin,don't do this.
Matt...
no.
Who are you?
Justin,what the
hell are you doing?
Stay out of this.
I want to know
what was going on.
She broke it,ok?
Get off me.
Don't you walk away.
You know,just keep her away from me.
You stop right now,or you're gonna
be on the bench for saturday's game.
You know,I'm the only
reason we're in the playoffs,
and you know that.
If I don't play,you'll lose.
Watch your mouth,kid.
You know,I made it,jackie boy,
and you didn't,
but you never were good enough,
and you know that.
- Are you ok?
- Yeah.I'm fine.
I saw what happened.I understand
if you want to press charges.
I don'T. He wasn't himself.
Look.I'm gonna have to report this.
I don't know what's going
on with him lately,
but he's out of control.
I need to know what happened.
I don't know. It all
happened so fast.
It was probably
something I said to him.
Look.I don't care what kind
of pressure a kid is under.
There is no excuse for this.
You know,I really
have to think about this.
I'm sorry.I have to go.
Got a buyer for
the fishing lures.
That's the crazy crawler,
made by heddon in 1944.
The other one is the wotta
frog,made by paw paw in 1942.
Who's it for?
My husband.
He's a collector.
Oh,well,if you really
want to be a hero,
the vampire.
It's extremely rare,made in 1924.
No. I'm sorry--1923.
Oh,my goodness,I am never
bringing my husband in here.
You are the wife
he always dreamed of,
and I kept telling
him you don't exist.
Mel,look. I just
heard what happened.
I'm trying to stay calm.
- Ok,jim.
- No
but I'm gonna
tear his head off.
Jim!
Back room,please.
Thanks.
It wasn't justin.
It was matt vonner.
Well,who the hell is matt vonner?
All right.So,it's matt vonner.
I'll tear his head off.
Too late.He's already
dead.He's the ghost.
Matt vonner the baseball player?
Yeah.He was the one that I
saw at the game the other night.
He was also there today.
He's haunting justin,
not the coach,
and justin has no idea
what happened to him.
All right.Then the question is,
if I punch justin hard enough,
will matt vonner
the ghost feel it?
You're not helping.
Honey,just tell me first,ok,
so I don't hear it
from bob at the station,
who heard it from his brother harry,who
heard it from his kid who plays catcher.
What?
Ok.My bad,but when I
realized who the ghost was.
Matt vonner.
Graduated from grandview in '90.
And signed with the
chicago cubs the same year.
He spent a year in the minor leagues,
then got traded to the white sox.
He won rookie of the year and came in
second for the sid young award 3 times.
- "Sid"?
- Yeah.
That's an award they
give out for pitching,
and you thought i didn't know
anything about baseball.
Cy.
Cy young.He was an old
pitcher a long time ago.
Oh,sid,cy,whatever.
You know,I remember
reading about this guy.
Now,he was amazing,and
then he just went downhill.
I don't know what happened.
It was drugs or
gambling or something.
Wow,I remember how surprised
people were.He just fell apart,
but why would he
want to haunt justin?
I don't know.
You know,justin has
been recruited by,like,
5 major league teams,I mean,the a's,
the yankees,the red sox,the braves.
Maybe he wants to hurt justin
so justin can't make the bigs.
- "Bigs"?
- Majors.
Makes sense.
That is a possibility,
but either way,
I have to let justin know
what's happening to him.
All right,but with
me this time,ok?
Oh,I'm so sorry.
Do we have any noguchi lamps?
Duty calls.
We will talk some more about
the mutant cockroaches later.
Yeah,and I'll get you
that chemical bug spray.
Great.
You guys have your own code.
That's so cute.
My mom saved the video...
All 14 hours.
Ready for a jim marathon?
Is that really you?
Come on.Can't you tell?
Look at the pecs.
That kid is cut.
What is all this?
My mother is the greatest
living human being on earth.
She saved all my baseball stuff,
everything,and
look at this.
These are the cards..
my dad collected
when he was a kid.
I mean,look at these names--
mantle,mays,koufax,clemente.
That's reggie jackson.
I saw him play once.
My dad took me.
We had seats right
behind home plate.
That day,reggie hit 4
home runs.It's the truth.
That was the last game my dad
and I ever went to together.
It's weird.
Here it is.
I think I hit a double
here in this one.
Maybe it's the next pitch.
Now I know why they
call it a double.
Came here-- came here
to say I'm sorry.
I don't know why
I did what I did.
Come in.
You got to be kidding me.
You come into our house?
Jim...
I said I was sorry.
I feel really bad about it.
I just need to talk to you.
I need to talk to you,too.
Can you get us some drinks?
Yeah.
Hey,I'll be in the kitchen,
you know,the next room.
Did your coach ask
you to come here?
No,my mom.
Coach suspended me.
I need you to talk to him for me.
I can't be suspended,
and none of this is
what you think it is.
I don't take anything--
no drugs,nothing.
I know I get nosebleeds,
which is,like,a sign of it,
I know,but I'm not on anything.
I work my ass off every day.
I've been doing this since I was 5,
and everybody thinks
that I'm on something,
but I'm not. I
mean,we get tested.
Look. I'm not the
steroid police.
Well,isn't that why you've
been following me around?
You've got a different problem.
Ok.You don't understand.
This is all I've
ever wanted to do.
It's the one thing I've
always been good at.
It's the only thing that's
made my dad proud of me.
What happens when you go
out to play on the field,
when you start to pitch?
Do you feel anything different?
Um, I don't know.
I just--
I feel like I can't lose.
I feel stronger.
It's kind of hard to describe.
Do you know who matt vonner is?
Of course, yeah.Everybody does.
When you're out on
that field, it's him.
What?I don't know what you
mean. Matt vonner is dead.
Justin, it's his spirit.
A ghost?You're telling me that there's
a ghost out on the field  with me?
No,not with you. In you.
That's why you've been having
the nosebleeds.He's using you.
When I'm pitching.
That's what you think.
It doesn't mean that you're not good, but
he is controlling you when you're out there.
- You're lying.
- No,I'm not,and you know it.
Deep inside,you know it.
We have to get d of him.
No.It is me out there.
It's not him.It's not
anything else. It's me.
He's gonna hurt you.
Even if what you say is
true, he's making me great.
Do you think I want to give that
up? Do you think I can give that up?
I am better than I've ever been,
and even if I knew  how to
change that, I wouldn't want to.
Justin... justin!
Leave him alone.
Mel?
I'm gonna win again.
I'm gonna be great again.
Justin is  the best player
to come through here since me.
I'm taking him  all the way.
Justin isn't playing.
Is that what you want?
The coach? That's the son
of a bitch who killed me.
He killed me!
Melinda.
- You ok?
- Yeah. You?
They reversed your decision?
How can they do that?
They're  the school
board. It's what they do.
They do what they want,
and they didn't reverse it.
They just won't approve my decision
until they review the charges next week,
which really just means they're gonna make sure
justin pitches in saturday's championship game.
Does justin know that?
Eh, beats me.
I'm not the coach anymore.
What?
I told them if justin played,
I wouldn't coach.They agreed.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
That's ok.
Not as much fun  as
it used to be, anyway.
Used to be about playing.
Now it's about winning.
I don't know what's
happened to justin.
I mean, he was
like my own kid.
Every day, I
would work with him,
and now,the last 4 months, it's like
I don't even know who he is anymore.
Hey, I wonder what
happened to coach.
I hear he got fired.
Anybody know why?
Maybe he made
a bad decision.
You're the one that
shouldn't be out there.
Then why don't you
do something about it?
Hey! Watch out.
Why?
None of us want to go
out there if he pitches.
Why don't you tell us how
the coach got fired,justin?
Hey,hey,hey,
cut it out.
Back it up. Break itP.
Move back.
Justin, take a walk.
What the hell
happened to you, man?
I need to talk to
you about something,
someone.
Someone I know?
Matt vonner.
Well,we grew up together,
played on the same teams,
but matt was always the big deal,
a lot like justin is now.
Were you with him when he died?
Yeah. Why?
He blames you.
What do you mean?
He says  you killed him.
He says I killed him?
Look.It was matt that
grabbed me that day at school,
not justin.
Ok.You're gonna have to
catch me up a little here.
You saw matt vonner?
Yes.
You know he's dead.
I know  how it sounds,
but matt's spirit is still here,
and that's why justin is pitching so well,
and he knows it.
You know what's weird?
What?
He's been in my
dreams lately, matt,
and the accident.
Tell me what  happened that night.
We both got drafted the same
year right out of high school.
Matt went straight to the bigs,
and I spent 8 years in the minors.
Then one day,
I got called up.
I was beyond excited,
playing in the bigs
alongside my best friend.
Flew into chicago.
Took a cab ride over to his place.
I mean,he wanted to be the one
to bring me to my first game,
and he had a lot
of problems by then,
but he was ready
for his comeback.
Then on the ride
over to the stadium...
- I'm going to the bigs.
- You're going to the show,baby.
You're  going to the show.
Look out!
Matt was killed,
and that was the end
of it for me, too.
If this is real,
why would he  be doing this?
I think that he's trying to give
himself another chance by using justin.
It's like you said.
Everything is about winning,
even in death.
I don't really believe
in anything too much.
I pray when I get  on the
plane-- that's about it--
but if matt really is still here
and he's doing this to justin,
he's messing up a good kid.
Tell me  what I need to do.
Can you  talk to justin? He's
afraid that he'll fail without matt.
This is the biggest
game of his entire life.
He's got scouts from 6 different
major league teams looking at him.
I mean, what am I gonna
tell him, "don't pitch"?
Well, then maybe you
should talk to matt.
Justin.
What are you  doing here?
I want you to tell me what
happens when  you come out here.
We're trying to figure
out what's happening.
You believe her?
Justin, you
can stop this.
You know, I'm sorry
about what happened to you,
but that's your fault,not mine.
She shouldn't have come near me.
I have nothing to do with her.
He's behind you.
Justin, don't let him--
Matt, don't do this.
my god.
Jackie boy.
You know,I really wish you
were catching for me tonight.
Be like old times.
You're too old now,man.
You're not gonna  pitch tonight.
I'm not gonna
let it happen.
just get away
from him. Go.
You're gonna ruin him just
like you ruined yourself.
run Justin Run
Where the hell is he?
To your right.
I'm gonna tell you something
I should've told you 10 years ago.
You were a damn good  pitcher, matt,
but you weren't th much
better than anyone else.
You just thought you were because
of what you did to yourself.
I remember that one
game when you shot up.
We were right here in grandview.
Said it was just once,just to see
if it would  help give you an edge,
get us  into the playoffs,
and you got us in,I guess,
but I never really
felt right about it.
I never felt like we
really won that game.
Everybody else  always remembers
what a great game it was.
Not me.
Then you'd jack yourself up
another time and another time,
and somewhere in there, you just--
you forgot how to play
the game without it.
You didn't just
kill yourself, matt.
You killed the game.
You can't talk
to me like this.
He's the reason  I'm dead.
He thinks that you're
responsiblemfor his death.
You're wrong,matt.
You were driving,not me.
You were so jacked up that night,
you didn't know  what was going on.
I don't know what to say. It was
my first game, my big chance.
You don't know what it takes to
survive  up here.You don't know.
Ok. Fine. I don't know.
Thought I'd do you a favor by
giving you a ride to the game.
Matt, just drop it.
You want  to know something?
If it wasn't for me  asking for you,
they never would've  called you up.
What?
Yeah. I thought you'd be my good-luck
charm, you know, like the way it used to be,
but if you think you  can compete
in the bigs  without doing what I do,
you're gonna be catching washouts
in little rock by next weekend.
The last thing you said to me was,
"get with the
program, jackie boy,
or be happy riding pine.
No!
don't leave me here.
Don't leave me here.
He saved himself and left me to
die. Tell him I know what he did.
I'm not gonna
tell him that.
I tried to save
that son of a bitch.
It costs me my career.
Coach said he
tried to save you.
He's a liar.
Said it cost him  his career.
I saw something.
I remember something.
Because of what you were
on, you weren't clear.
You have to see what
really happened now, matt,
and you can do that now.
You can see what you did.
Don't leave me here.
Come on. Come on.
Matt! Matt...
matt! Come on.
Ok.stday with me  no no No!
How could I not
have remembered that?
You were thinking only
of what happened to you.
You were so focused
on your own pain
that you couldn't even see your
friend was trying to save you.
- I was dying.
- You were dead,matt.
You denied everything
you did wrong.
He lost it all
because of me.
How do I change it?
The only thing you can
do now is make it right.
Coach doesn't want
anything from you,
and justin,the way you make it
right with him is by letting him go.
I hit him.
I hit coach.
No, you didn'T.
Yeah. I did. I felt it.
It was my hand.
I mean, he was
always there for me.
How could i
do that to him?
He knows that
it wasn't you,
that it was matt,
and matt is here
right now.
It's ok. He just
wants to talk.
Tell him  I was afraid, afraid
of not being  anyone anymore.
He wants you to know
that he was afraid.
I just wanted to play
the game again, to pitch again.
That's when I felt
the most alive.
That's why I used you.
You're even better than I was.
I wanted to be on top again.
He thinks you're better than he
was. That's why he used you.
But I've hurt enough
people, so I'm out of here.
You're on your own.
He's gonna
cross over.
He wants you to know
that you're on your own.
What if I can't do
this without him?
Tell him he
never needed me.
I needed you.
He says that you
never needed him.
He needed you.
He wants you to
trust what you know.
I'm not sure what
I know anymore.
Justin...
Trust him,
like I should have.
Let him guide you.
There's nobody better than him.
Trust him.
Need you to warm up.
I don't know if
I can play, coach.
I don't care if you walk
the first 10 batters.
I want you out
there. Come on.
Batting eighth
and doing the catching
number 12,
and batting ninth,
doing the pitching--
number 21,
justin cotter.
where's matt?
I don't know. I don't
think he crossed over.
Having him pitch tonight might
not have been such a good idea.
I knew this would happen.
He thinks I'm out there.
He's mixed up.
He doesn't know the difference between
what I did to him and just being scared.
He's forgotten
how to be afraid.
Justin,
he's not out there.
He's right here.
I can't do this.
Stop thinking with your
head. Think with your arm.
He wants you to stop thinking with
your head. Think with your arm.
- Justin...
- what,man?
I'm on your team.
We all are.
Yeah. Yeah.I'm sorry.
I'm ok.
Coach tells us you're
the reason he's back.
Osis  let's win this.
You know,
tell matt...
I'll do that.
again
Yeah. I see it.
Is that the light?
I can't see it. It's for you.
Do I just  walk into it?
Yeah.
Hey,do you think
the babe is in there
or mantle or cy young?
Sorry. I don't
have a program.
You know what?
I bet they are.
Hey, one more thing.
Tell jackie boy
I'm sorry
and tell justin,
"throw for the corners.
"  Is he here?
No. He crossed over,
but he wanted me to tell you
that he's sorry,
and tell justin to
throw for the corners.
That's what I always
used to tell him to do.
Play ball!
Hey, good luck.
So... justin pitching.
- Yeah.
- Got any help?
8 other players.
Come on,justin!
All right,kid.
All right,justin!
Throw for the corners.
Go, justin!
Oh, and  it's going,
going... gone.
Home run.
There he goes,
the proud champion.
My first and only home run.
Well, the inning isn't over yet.
Wait. There's a ghost in the house?
Never mind. No.
Do not follow me.
- Do not follow me.
- I'm following you.
ghost whisperer
Season 02 Episode 01
sync:YTET-小野人王 cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
www.tvsubtitles.net