previously
on ghost whisperer.
how come you
can see me and they can't?
that's a long story.
there's
a better place for you.
well, that means
there's someone else
out there...
like me?
i know!
it's the 5 signs.
the dead dove
on the doorstep.
the bee.
the writing
on jim's back.
the dead will walk.
and now, the forgotten
have returned.
wait, so, all 5 of
those things have happened.
not the writing
on your back.
it was latin.
it translates to,
"death of a loved one."
what is this?
what are you doing
with all these spirits?
we're getting ready.
for what?
for what's coming.
he's been planning this
for quite some time.
no, this is
bigger than just him.
hey!
you shouldn't be here.
why not?
this is your fault.
no.
yeah?
hey, sorry,
i got lonely.
everybody's healthy
in grandview tonight.
i got no work.
i can't believe
i have a week of this.
what time is it?
4:10.
delia!
what?
i have to call you back.
hello?
it's melinda,
i'm so sorry.
what time is it?
10 after 4:00.
i'm so sorry,
i just--
i need to know
that you're ok.
well, i'm not.
you're not?
no, i'm awake
at 10 after 4:00.
why are you
doing this to me?
ok, i'm--i'm sorry.
go back to sleep.
ok, wait,
are you ok?
i'm fine.
forget i called.
all right,
good night,
good morning,
good bye.
www.1000fr.com present
capture:frm@
sync:frm@illuminatorl
once again
you have proven to be
my best customer.
this is a birthday gift
that ned will never expect.
you know, do you think
he's going to get it?
i mean,
will he know what it is?
oh, yeah, this is
all making a comeback.
because they discovered
vinyl produces
a better sound than digital.
can you believe that?
do they still make vinyl?
well, you know,
it's hard to find,
but it's out there.
besides, i still have
my whole collection
in a box somewhere.
right, i bet ned
can't wait to listen
to tom jones and neil young.
ok, so, we'll skip
my collection,
but a lot of bands
are releasing on vinyl
these days.
you know what?
i think it's great,
totally original.
hey....
did i dream
that phone call last night?
yes, you did.
oh, you are such a liar.
what was that?
were you sleep-dialing?
nothing, i just--
i just had
a weird dream.
about me?
i don't remember
what it was about.
but don't worry, ok?
now, when are you going
to give this to ned?
oh, well, tim is
trying to find
some really cool records.
before his birthday,
i hope.
so, that's going well?
yeah, i mean,
i don't know,
it just kinda
feels comfortable.
you know?
even if we're
just sitting there,
not even talking,
it just feels right.
that's great.
yeah, well, baby steps.
hey, do you mind
if i hide this in the back?
uh, if you can find
a place for it
in the black hole
back there,
be my guest.
hey! you know what?
i'm going to go
get some coffee,
do you want something?
yeah, that'd be great.
surprise me.
ok.
who are you?
they told me
you would know.
who told you?
they said you would help.
i don't understand.
mary o'connell.
mary o'connell?
that was the beginning.
the beginning of what?
you remember what happened,
don't you, lynn?
don't you remember?
that day, the accident?
your dad
tells me you've been
making these drawings
ever since.
well, tell me, please,
why have you been
making these drawings?
'cause i have to.
but why do you have to?
it's in my head,
isn't it?
every day, i have to.
same as it never was.
hey, it's me,
i'm looking right at you.
i forgot to ask
if you wanted anything
from java?
uh, no, i'm good.
you go ahead.
you know,
i think i'll wait.
i want to try
and get a head start--
whoa!
i am so sorry.
are you ok?
i didn't even see you.
no, it really was my fault,
i wasn't even
paying attention.
stay off cell phones.
delia, are you all right?
do you want to just
go sit for a minute?
no, i'm ok, really,
please, i'm fine.
it was a close call,
but that's it.
hey, everything's fine.
next show is 2 p.m.
i'm going
to be here all week.
it's fine, please,
i'm gonna just, um...
i'm going to go
sit down in the shop.
ok, i get it.
it's about water.
all right, so this woman
died on a ferry 2 years ago,
or maybe she didn't,
maybe she doesn't
know how she died,
and you have to tell her,
i don't know.
it sounds
simple to me, whatever.
yeah, but what about
the visions
of impending death?
you think they all
refer to delia?
look, there were
5 signs this past year.
the dead dove, the bee,
the dead will walk,
the return
of the forgotten.
the only thing
that hasn't happened
is death of a loved one.
don't you think that
it--it could be related?
how do i know? you're
the one that gets
all the neat visions.
you drink the champagne,
i only get the hangover.
sorry,
guess i caught you
at a bad time.
oh, no, no, you caught me
at a great time.
you seem to be packing.
yes, i'm packing.
i am going
on a sabbatical.
i have
a fantastic opportunity
to do research
in a peruvian jungle.
just like that,
up and gone?
just like that.
nothing supernatural,
either.
although, i should check
and see if jungle insects
have souls,
i'd hate to be haunted
by an earth-bound cicada.
you know we never really...
we never got to talk about
everything that happened.
talking's not always
the best thing.
i'm in that odd place
where i may speak
the unadulterated truth
about everything
i think and feel.
can't have that.
no, we can't have that.
anyway, nope,
this is going to be great.
really a--just a great time
for me to take a break.
i mean you do this
10 times a week.
you know,
you talk to ghosts,
argue with ghosts,
you get your heart
broken by a ghost,
but for us mere mortals,
come on.
hey, hey, hey, come on.
this is a good thing,
be happy for me.
i'm going to be doing
what i do and loving it.
i hope you'll
keep in touch.
maybe, maybe not.
maybe we'll just
be 2 ships passing
in the night.
don't say ships.
hey, good morning.
oh, thank you!
boy, do i need this.
yeah, you don't look like
you got enough sleep.
you look great, too.
as do you, tired or not.
nice backpedal.
listen, i really have
to talk to you.
ok.
hey,
look what i found.
pink floyd
wish you were here,
led zep 4.
mint condition,
still shrink-wrapped.
those are great.
where did you find these?
i'd rather not say.
in case i outlive
my usefulness, someday.
that way you'll
always come back to me
for the vinyl.
this is fantastic.
now all we need
is some today vinyl.
you know, bands ned
has actually heard of.
i'm all over it.
hey, you said
you needed to talk
to me about something?
oh, no, no,
never mind.
come for lunch?
i've got invoices
to do, but hey,
bring me back
something gooey.
all right.
bye.
buh-bye.
look, no offence,
but we're going
to have to wrap this up,
i don't have
flood insurance.
i know that you
died in a ferry accident
in england.
do you remember
anything about it?
the water
took my breath away.
i was so scared.
i'm alone now.
is there
something you need?
someone i can contact?
you can't help me.
why not?
i have to help you.
how can you help me?
is this a warning?
are you trying to tell me
something about my friend?
all eyes will be on you.
what do you mean?
i have to go
to the other place.
ok...
next time, bring a mop.
you say she's been
doing this for how long?
since the accident.
every day,
every single day.
can you ask her
why she keeps making these?
she says she has to.
it is in her head,
and she has to get it out.
it's too girly.
shush.
what do you want,
football helmets
on the curtains?
i don't want
curtains at all.
why do you want
to cover the windows?
i don't want to cover them,
i want to enhance them.
this house has had
enough enhancement.
when do we say,
"finished"?
ah, never.
why do i have the feeling
that the words "never"
and "home improvement"
go hand-in-hand
together, forever?
you know what?
you are very impatient.
ok, it takes a while
to make a house a home.
it took a while to make
this house a house.
aren't you late for work?
fine.
you know
what my theory is?
that window treatments
destroy marriages?
well, yeah, that's
one of my theories.
but...
you're nervous,
and you're
distracted by something,
and that's why
the house is getting
another makeover.
hmm, i was hoping
to appear industrious.
well, you hoped wrong.
i just keep getting
these weird visions,
and there's
this strange ghost.
strange ghost, huh?
she keeps
showing me things,
and i don't know why.
it's like she's sad
and in mourning.
well, you think she's
trying to warn you
about something?
i don't usually get
stuff about the future.
you did last year.
that turned out
to be right.
i just know that i'm
not going to rest easy
until
i can figure this out.
and i will.
and until then,
we get curtains?
exactly!
what is this place?
part of it.
of what?
of what you have to know.
what i have to show you.
who sent you to me?
they won't let me
see my husband.
not until
i show you everything.
so what do you think?
how many times
do i have to explain
the meaning of the word
"sabbatical" to you?
definition--
leave with pay
for teacher or professor
for extended period
of study or rest.
alternate definition--
an excuse for a confused
and troubled man
who wants to forget
about his real life
and go and study
cicadas instead.
don't forget
the "with pay" part.
you know,
have you ever thought about
new curtains
for this room?
i don't think i've thought
about curtains, period.
there might be more
to these visions
than just
a ferry accident.
well, you know what?
these visions might not
be about just some ghost.
you might have
a prophet ghost.
ooh, that's a new one.
prophet ghosts
are very common
in all mythologies.
i mean, ulysses
consulted a prophet ghost
for homer's odyssey.
native american traditions
are rich
with prophet ghosts.
let's not forget about
that rockin' trio--
the ghosts of christmas
past, present, and future.
so dickens knew about
the prophet ghosts
and i don't?
well, he didn't know
much about curtains,
so i guess
it all evens out.
can i just say
that this sabbatical
has not improved
your mood?
here's another theory.
how about this?
how about your dreams aren't
really about the accidents.
they're about the symbolism
behind the accidents.
such as?
well, you have a ferry
and a water motif,
which makes me think
of the river styx.
in greek mythology,
it's the river that separates
the living from the dead.
souls are ferried
across the river
into the underworld.
what about last night?
it was like there was
some kind of
mining accident.
yeah, but you said
they were all wearing
suits and ties.
i would think that
suits and ties in a mine
would be sort of
a fashion don't.
a tunnel collapse then?
a tunnel.
now you're talking.
that's the classic symbol
for crossing over.
there were souls
following the light.
it seems like someone's
trying to get you
to intercede in something.
what?
whatever's...coming.
he died, my boy, for three minutes.
then he came back.
is this why you came to see him?
you said he's been drawing something?
everyday
since the accident .
everywhere.
school, the walls,
even on pillowcases.
nice work stefano.
tell me why  you do this
i do it for her
who?
for her
it really does
sound better.
how come?
'cause
it's analog.
means it records
continuously.
digital
is cleaner,
but that's
because it has
to break it up
and reassemble it.
wow! i'm going out
with an audiophile.
who knew?
you're going out with a guy
who knows how to look up
stuff fast on the internet.
so this is
how you guys
listened to music
back in
the old days?
yeah. mm-hmm.
when dinosaurs
roamed the earth.
what are all those
crackles and pops?
it's just somehow
part of the whole
experience, you know?
when i hear it,
i am instantly
a teenager again,
lying on my bed,
dreaming about
the future.
hearing it makes me
feel like i have
a lot of pimples.
ooh! spoken like
a true poet.
oh, hey. party is over.
the boss is here.
hey! the party
is just getting
started.
ta-da!
damn! i forgot
the matches.
oh, and the candles.
and the song that
i was gonna sing to you.
i'm not very good
at birthdays.
hey, i still know
my part of the song.
i could sing it.
whoa! ha ha. that's ok.
we have a bunch of stuff
in the back.
here you go, bud.
hey. is that dope 6?
yeah!
tight.
nice.
yeah.
how did you know that?
i like music.
so do i.
yeah,
but i like music
even after 1990.
that hurt.
hmm.
hey, do you mind
if i skip out early
this afternoon?
sure. what's up?
i think i found a tenant
at long last
for the house
on colonial road.
ha ha. you mean
the mansion
on colonial road.
it's big, it's furnished,
and it's a rental.
it sounds like
what they need,
so i'm just going
to go take some pictures
and email them.
sure you don't mind?
are you kidding?
how many times
have you covered for me?
don't worry about it.
are you ok?
me? sure.
the last couple of days
you seemed
really distracted,
like something was wrong.
it's just stress.
the kind that you would
rather not know about.
hey, look, i don't--
you know how i feel
about all of this
supernatural stuff,
but i don't...
want it to put a wedge
between us.
i don't want to be
on the outside of
the rest of your life.
delia, this is my life.
ok? it's--
it's who i am.
there's no part of me
that's not
affected by it.
it's kind of like...
love me, love my ghosts.
ned! please don't
turn me into a clich?
just turn it down,
or i'm going
to take it away.
thank you.
you're gonna lose her.
you're gonna--
aah! aah! ahh!
???
ned...
i am so sorry.
what happened?
it was that turntable.
it started saying
weird things.
she tried
to turn it off, and...
she just froze.
i didn't even know
what was happening.
it's all right.
is she dead?
shh.
no, we don't talk
like that, all right?
ok.
she's gonna be
all right.
she's got a burn
on her hand,
she took a pretty
good jolt from
that turntable.
it was a freak short
or something.
yeah, maybe not so freaky.
tell me
all this later.
i've got to get back
out there.
flaherty's gonna
come stay with ned
as soon as he can.
ok.
all right.
bye.
???
melinda,
you're looking well.
what the hell
are you doing here?
good question.
it seems i'm a little early.
early for what?
call me sentimental.
i just can't seem
to get over grandview.
???
the guy's a freak.
he plastered a whole room
with your photograph.
he's stalking you.
yeah, i know.
i was there.
what was he doin'
at the hospital?
i don't know
exactly,
but he said he was
a little early.
little early, for what?
wait, you don't think
he was going to try
to grab delia's soul--
don't even say it.
you gotta think
gabriel had something
to do with this.
i mean, is this about
death of a loved one?
i don't know.
but i'm...scared.
i feel like
there's this game
being played,
and i'm the only one
who doesn't know
what it is.
you're not the only one.
and you will never be
the only one.
you're not alone.
aah!
aahh!
why are you showing me
all of this?
what does it mean?
so you can know
who to save.
why can't you tell me?
it's not for me
to know.
it was raining cars
and you didn't call me?
i did call you.
yeah, after the fun,
as usual.
all right, this is
what we have so far.
we have a prophet ghost
who's showing you
visions of
big disasters,
and these disasters
are metaphorical
for death itself.
you have a ferry,
you have a bridge
and a tunnel.
these are all
mythological journeys
of the soul.
and weird visions
of someone's death,
i think, delia's.
well, that could
bring to mind
the death of a loved one
warning that we had,
and last night
she almost
got fried, right?
uh, i would put it
a ???
but, yes.
and gabriel was there,
just hanging out
at the hospital
like a vulture.
yeah, the self-proclaimed
collector of souls
awaiting his spoils.
you gotta admit,
i turn a good phrase
now and then.
focus.
please stay focused.
all right, all right,
look, this is what's happening.
it's so secret
that in the past year,
the way things
have been going,
ghosts being able
to do things they never
could before,
it doesn't take
a genius to see
that the whole order
of things is being
shaken up,
that the veil between
the living and the dead
is very weak.
yeah, and all eyes
are on me, so what
do we do?
we?
oh, come on!
you can't tell me that
you're gonna leave now.
i mean,
with the thin veil
and everything?
oh, no, i should stay here
where cars fall from the sky
and wives betray me
from beyond the grave.
quitter.
look, melinda...
i'm gonna help you
do this.
you're the bravest person
i've ever met in my life,
and i won't quit on you.
and?
i'm waiting
for the joke.
yeah, i can't think of one.
the peruvian job
is gonna have to wait.
heh heh, all right, hey,
let's go tell delia
to watch her back.
so what am i
supposed to do,
just run away?
andrea was killed
last year, you know that.
yeah, because
of a plane crash.
because she knew what i knew,
and she acted on it.
look, if i had
never told her
what i could do,
then i wouldn't have had
to tell her about the signs
that i was getting,
and she never would have
gotten in her car.
so what are you saying?
that there's gonna be
another plane crash?
i don't know
what there's gonna be, ok?
but i keep getting signs
and having dreams,
and i think that they
involve you.
i think that they're trying
to hurt me by hurting
the people that i love.
you could be in danger.
jim could be in danger,
and i think that's
what happened last night.
last night was
an electrical problem
with an old turntable.
yes, it scared
the hell out of me,
but there was no--
ned told me about the voices
on the turntable.
the record
was skipping, melinda.
please.
ahem. if i could
barge into
this conversation.
um, i teach this type
of thing at the university,
i made a lifetime
studying it,
and i'm the world's
biggest skeptic.
until i met melinda,
i never believed in anything
i couldn't touch or see.
see, i'm a man of science,
miss banks.
although i've also
been taken for a man
of mystery,
man of intrigue--
is there a caboose
to this train
of thought, professor?
yes, there is.
you can fight it,
you can deny it,
you can turn
a blind eye to it,
but to quote
william shakespeare,
"there is more in heaven
in earth, horatio,"
or in this case, delia,
"that can be dreamt of
in your philosophy."
point, please.
the point...
the point is
what do you lose
by believing?
i think there is
something
very special
about you,
melinda, i do.
i believe
you feel things,
maybe even see things
that we can't.
are they ghosts,
can they hurt us,
can they actually change
the course of our lives
from beyond the grave?
i'm asking you
to believe that they are,
and that they do.
and i need you
to believe it,
because i need you
to be safe.
ok.
i believe you.
this is one of those
female bonding moments,
isn't it?
you've got to see this.
hey, uh, come on in.
don't be shy or anything.
it's not like it's 12:30
in the morning.
ok, this is about
the past and the future.
that's a pretty
sweeping statement.
you could be talking
about my credit
rating, or--
ok, just listen.
we have been assuming
that these visions
have been some sort
of sign or warning
that something's to come.
how's your italian?
bene.
well?
no, that's it. bene.
that's the italian i know.
i'm gonna kill him.
all right,
look at the date.
uh...
may 11, 2003.
ok, this bridge
collapsed 4 years ago,
killing more than
111 people.
then, a ferry
sinks off the coast
of england
may 11, 2005.
the tunnel vision?
a subway collapse
in moscow
on may 11, 2004.
flash forward.
plane crash
outside of grandview
may 11, 2006.
a terrible tragedy,
hundreds dead,
same date, same time,
all within the last
4 years.
this has been about stuff
that already happened.
what are you doing?
well, this might still
all be about the future.
how? all the visions
are accounted for.
yes, but there were
5 signs, melinda.
the, uh, the tunnel.
how many killed?
32, right?
3 plus 2 equals 5. next?
the ferry sinking,
311 dead.
3 plus one plus one, 5.
and how about
the bridge?
111 people,
2 on the ground.
one plus one plus one
plus two, 5.
ok, but wait.
the plane trash killed 238.
no, it didn't,
'cause the initial
reports were wrong.
family members
reporting the missing
were so frantic,
they reported them
missing 2, 3 times over.
and some of the people
that were pronounced dead
weren't even on the flight.
the official number's now
228 passengers,
and there were 2 victims
on the ground, that's 230.
look at this.
that's 230,
2 plus 3 equals 5.
this is all about fives.
5 signs, 4 accidents.
now we've come
full circle,
which means
something else
is going to happen
at the same time,
same date.
may 11, 2007.
one week from tonight.
hi, this is jim clancy.
leave me a message.
jim, i have to talk
to you right now.
i'm on my way
to the firehouse,
but call me
if you get this first.
jim! i was just
with payne, and--
mrs. gordon?
oh, um, i'm sorry,
who is this?
are you interested
in may the 11th?
who is this?
6700 colonial road,
right now.
no, wait a minute,
who is this?
hello?
you have something i want.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net