You remember
the Donnellys, right?
Sean, Kevin, Jimmy,
and Tommy?
Well, they got
into some trouble
a couple of days ago.
'Cause after Jimmy
kidnapped Louie,
the Italians put Sean
in the hospital.
So, Jimmy killed Louie.
To protect Jimmy,
Tommy and Kevin killed Sal,
the head of the Italian mob,
and Huey,
the head of the Irish mob.
Oh, yeah. Then they had
to get rid of Louie.
Now, Nicky's charging Tommy
a penalty for every day
Louie doesn't come home.
(CASH REGISTER DINGS)
Gonna get expensive!
Since then,
the Irish mob boss'
brother, Dokey,
was asking people
what happened.
And he didn't use that ax
for chopping wood.
Now, through all of this,
Tommy still thought he could
put everything behind him
and maybe get
Jenny Reilly back.
He should've known better.
I don't know
what's harder to take,
being out there
with a contract out
on me or this.
This. Trust me.
It's not as bad
as you think.
I mean, having people
come after you.
Where I come from,
it's normal.
I mean, guys'll kill you
for looking at them wrong.
'Course when this happens,
there's usually a fair amount
of alcohol involved.
Do you have brothers?
Nope.
I have three.
Best damn brothers
you could ask for.
Kind of brothers
that are always
looking out for you.
Even when you don't
know they're looking.
Really.
They killed for me.
I'd kill for a better
conversation.
JOEY. There are a lot of guys
in my neighborhood who
would still be alive today
if they'd just shut up
and gone to bed
the night before.
(VOMITING)
Then again, mornings
can be pretty crazy, too.
DOKEY: Jimmy Donnelly.
I should've known
I'd find you puking
in an alleyway.
Hey, Doke.
My guys were in
the bar last night
when you told that story
about how your brothers
killed for you.
They enjoyed it.
What?
Yeah.
My brother got killed.
You know anything about that?
God, no, Doke.
If I did,
I'd come to you.
I really liked Huey.
Well, your brothers
killed somebody.
Come on, who'd they kill?
I don't remember
what I said last night.
I talk lots of crap
when I'm drunk.
My brother wouldn't
even bail me out of jail,
let alone kill for me.
Shut up.
I'm trying to read.
Besides, you said
Jimmy Donnelly was in jail
for armed robbery.
Yeah, right.
But see,
Kevin had gone to visit him.
That's when Jimmy
persuaded Kevin to persuade
the witness not to testify.
Damn.
Which worked out.
'Cause Jimmy got out of jail.
Well, you better get
yourself cleaned up.
You can't pay your respects
like this, right?
You coming
to the wake, right?
Yeah. Sure.
I want you to call our guys
in the correctional union,
all right?
The night Huey got killed,
I want you to find out
what time he was
booked into The Tombs.
'Cause if that little punk
is lying to me,
I'm gonna find out.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
TOMMY: Kate.
JOEY. Kate Farrell.
Huey's widow.
There wasn't one guy
who hadn't fantasized
about her growing up,
including Tommy Donnelly.
That isn't her!
Yeah, it is!
How'd you get
naked photos of her?
Well, we have a thing going.
We were in bed together.
You know what?
I think it is her.
Yeah, those are
definitely her boobs.
I wouldn't have come by
like this so early.
(SNIFFLES) Unannounced.
But what I have to ask
should be in person.
I want you to hold
Huey's wake in your bar.
Dokey wants to have it
in his place, and I know
he won't do it right, so...
Well, if Dokey wants
to have it, maybe that'd
be better for everyone.
We'll throw it
at The Firecracker,
it's no problem.
We'll do it right.
I'll make you out
a check. Is that okay?
No, don't worry about it.
We'll take care of it.
We'll take care
of everything.
Thanks.
(GUNSHO TS)
JOEY. Jenny Reilly was
determined to move on
without Tommy Donnelly.
In fact, she'd sworn off
guys altogether.
But Samson Dawlish wasn't
just any neighborhood guy.
He was different from Tommy
in every way.
Except that he'd always
had a thing for Jenny.
I threw in an extra
dozen muffins.
You don't have
to keep doing that.
Don't make
a big deal out of it.
You'll get me in trouble.
That's $34.50.
You see the picture
of Huey?
Yeah, I saw it.
You know,
he was my hook.
Huey, he got me this job.
Yeah.
He was a good guy.
Black, no sugar. Right?
Thanks.
Hey, not for nothing,
but with Huey gone,
I don't know how much longer
I'm gonna have this gig,
so let's keep the muffins
between us.
Yeah, you got it.
Hey.
Are you going
to Huey's funeral?
Yeah.
Do you have a date?
I didn't mean "date."
That sounds terrible.
I mean...
You know,
maybe we could
go together
and get some coffee
or something
afterwards, the...
Yeah, you know what?
Forget it.
No.
You're really sweet.
Oh, boy,
that doesn't sound good,
does it? That's...
Oh, Samson, I can't.
Don't worry about it,
I understand.
I'll be seeing you.
Yeah.
Damn it!
These are all empty.
Yeah.
Jimmy's really
let the bar slide.
It would help if we didn't
sit around all day
drinking the stock.
This is a bar.
Aren't we supposed to have
more than two beers?
Why are you so
worried about it?
We're hosting
Huey's wake tonight.
What?
Kate Farrell came by
this morning.
She wants the wake
to be here.
Can I remind you that
we killed her husband?
Shut up, Kevin.
And you said yes to this?
Yeah, she didn't
really give me much
of a choice, okay?
What happened to the food
we had left over from
the party last week?
Tommy, when am I gonna get
a say in things?
There was a ham, meatballs,
and half a turkey.
(EXCLAIMS)
(GASPS)
What the hell is this?
Huh?
It's unplugged.
I think Jimmy's using
that outlet for his drill.
He's building a birdhouse.
A birdhouse? Beautiful.
Where are all
my damn guns?
Why do you need a gun, Jimmy?
Did you catch a bird
in your birdhouse?
At least I can
build something.
All you can do is
screw everything up!
Did you see what you did
to the food, Jimmy?
Why do you need
a gun, Jimmy?
'Cause I gotta kill Dokey.
Thanks to my idiot brother,
he thinks I killed Huey.
There's a shotgun
here somewhere.
You talked to Dokey?
What'd he say?
I had four guns in here!
Yeah, I got rid of them.
You what?
I got rid of them.
No guns?
Big shot wants
to take over the family,
he just got us all killed!
If Dokey really thought
you killed his brother,
you'd be dead.
He's asking everybody.
He's fishing, Jimmy.
Yeah, with us
he catches something.
You were in jail.
You got an alibi.
What do you gotta
worry about?
You just gotta get suited up,
go to the funeral,
put a rose
on Huey's casket,
and we're gonna get through
this day together, all right?
Nobody's gonna be suspicious
unless we act suspicious.
Did you go to school
to get that stupid?
You know,
you're right, Jimmy.
Get him a gun.
Why don't you wave it around
at Huey's funeral?
Wave it around at his wake.
That's gonna make us all
look really innocent.
I'm beginning to think
the wake's a really
bad idea, Tommy.
Well, you two idiots aren't
actually thinking about going
to Huey's wake, are you?
It's here.
You're lying.
Kate asked
to throw it here.
I said yes.
You gave away my bar
for Huey's wake?
We don't got a choice.
This is done.
You wanna play big man,
Tommy? You go ahead.
Now you're gonna
get out of my way.
You're leaving, too?
No, I'll help.
Really?
We have no money, no food,
and no booze.
What are you
gonna do, Kevin?
I'll get the booze.
How?
Will you give me
a little credit?
You're not the only one
who can handle things, Tommy.
Okay.
Get the booze, Kevin.
Being in charge of stocking
the bar is no small thing.
Which is why Kevin
came to me for help.
This is crazy.
Do we have credit?
Do we have money?
Do we even have a way
to transport the alcohol if
it were to fall from the sky?
You remember
when we were kids
and had a contest
to see who could
shut up the longest?
No. Who won?
Get the hell out.
Why?
Why don't I shoot you
and then explain it?
Who shoots somebody
with a gun in their pocket?
You're stealing my cab?
I know who you are,
you're a Donnelly!
Yeah?
Then you know that me
and my brothers will beat you
to a pulp if you report this.
6:00, cab will be
on this corner.
Get the hell
out of here, Jimmy!
Listen, I'm here...
(GRUNTS)
I'm here
'cause I'm crazy
about you, baby.
Yeah.
Don't tell me that, Jimmy!
If I was such a bad guy,
would I bring you this?
(LAUGHING) Yeah!
Give it.
You are such a jerk.
Jenny.
Hey, Tommy,
what can I get for you?
I gotta ask you a favor.
I wouldn't be asking
if it wasn't some kind
of an emergency.
What is it?
It's about Huey's wake.
It's gonna be
at The Firecracker.
But I only found out about it
this morning and we're
completely out of food.
(STAMMERING)
Wait a minute, you're
throwing Huey's wake?
Yeah.
Please tell me you know
how wrong that is.
(WHISPERING)
Could we not talk about
this right here?
What... Don't you
feel anything?
Do me a favor, okay?
Don't tell me
what I'm feeling.
I promised to throw the wake,
I can't change that.
So you gonna help me or not?
It's for Huey's family,
how can I say no?
Thanks, Jenny.
Yeah.
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Hey, Ma.
Have you seen Jimmy yet?
Not yet.
Half of me hopes
he won't show up.
I love your brother,
but we don't need
his kind of trouble.
Not today.
God, I hope it isn't
the long mass.
I have to get back
to Sean in the hospital.
WOMAN: Helen!
You go ahead.
I'll see you inside.
Hi, how are you?
I'm okay.
Hey.
Kate.
Tommy.
You gonna say hi,
Matty?
Hey, Matthew.
You taking care
of your mother? Yeah?
Tommy lost his dad, too,
when he was around your age.
He knows what it's like.
I understand it was
my sister-in-law who asked
you to hold the wake.
Yeah.
Personally, I wouldn't
have had it in such a dump.
You know?
That's just me.
I don't wanna cause
any friction in the family.
There's no friction.
Like you said,
he was my husband.
Yeah.
Hey, Matt.
You wanna go meet
some of your daddy's friends?
Real quick?
Come on, I'll take you.
They came a long way
to pay their respects.
Would you mind?
Thanks, Tommy.
Yeah.
Okay.
Go in and follow
your mother.
How you doing, kid?
Did somebody tell you
you were welcome here?
You're working on
this Friday's payment,
I hope.
Yeah, I would be
if I owed you any money.
How you doing, Nicky?
I didn't know
you knew Tommy.
Yeah, we're old friends.
Really?
You'll have to tell me
about that someday.
Don't you need to go
find your brothers?
Yeah.
Nice suit.
I'm on my way
to Sal's funeral.
I'm sure you're real broken up
over that turn of events, huh?
I came to pay my respects
to your brother.
Yeah.
My boss is under
the impression that
we have a deal.
Now he's wondering
why you're not living up
to your end.
What happened to
the paying your respects
part of this?
I just said
a silent prayer.
Now about the deal...
Let me stop you
right there, okay?
This is my brother in here.
I always told him the biggest
mistake he ever made was
working with you Italians.
But he didn't
listen to me.
And that's why
he's in here.
May I show you out?
(ORGAN PLAYING)
Can I have a few words
with my nephew before
we get started?
Okay, Matthew?
Why wouldn't it be okay?
Come on.
Are you okay?
No.
Is there anything I can do?
Yeah, maybe you
could sit with us.
With me and Matthew.
I'd be honored.
I know you're young, buddy.
But you're still a man.
So I don't wanna see you
crying in there, okay?
I don't have a son
of my own, Matt,
so I'm looking to you
to make me proud.
I want you
to walk in there,
standing tall with
your head held high.
That's the way your daddy
would've wanted it.
And you're a Farrell.
And Farrells don't
wear their hearts
on their sleeve.
All right?
Do you know
what that means?
It means you don't go
showing the world
how you feel.
You keep it locked up
real tight.
Right in here.
Okay?
That way people can't
take the good pieces
away from you.
Hey. I didn't
see you there.
Hi.
Hey, I just wanted to say...
About asking you out,
I didn't mean any disrespect.
Oh, no, no. Um...
It was just...
You know,
with all this Huey stuff...
I just need to get clear
on some things,
and it just wasn't
the right time.
Does that mean
there might be
a right time?
I'm gonna turn around now.
(WHISPERING)
Hey, handsome.
I want a word
with you.
Over here.
While the Father's up there,
here's what I want you
to think about.
I know that my brother
came to talk to you
in the hospital.
I know that he sent
his driver home,
that he called a cab,
and then he went
straight to Sal's.
Alone.
And he wouldn't do that,
Tommy.
So that tells me
you know why.
I wish I did.
I wish I could help you.
I don't believe you.
(ORGAN PLAYING)
FATHER DUFELT: Let us stand
and share Christ's welcome
with one another.
You get my money
from the mick?
JOEY. Alo was Nicky's boss.
He was upset
about losing Sal.
But losing the deal
Sal had with Huey,
that upset him
a whole lot more.
I gave him
a little more time.
Considering his brother's
funeral and all.
So you figure all business
stops because of a funeral?
What's this,
a birthday party?
I'll have it tomorrow.
Go talk to them.
Hey! Be a little
careful there,
jerk-off!
All of a sudden
he's cozy
with the Irish?
You're not gonna let up,
are you?
He's a first-class scumbag.
He put Sal in that box.
I don't know how he did it,
but he did it.
Maybe. For now, let's see
what kind of earner he is.
(CHUCKLING)
You know, this never
would've happened
if Tommy didn't
get me thrown in jail.
You come here without my money
and this is all you bring me?
What did he have
to go and kill Huey for?
Tommy killed Huey?
Huey Farrell?
I never would've done
anything that stupid!
It was the Italians
that beat up Sean.
that were coming after me,
not the Irish!
Then we got Dokey
gunning for our ass!
Would you calm down?
You know, if Tommy
would just listen to me
and stop trying
to run things...
This was between me
and the Italians.
Tommy wants me
to go to a funeral.
You got a nice dress?
(GRUNTS)
I always thought
I'd like to drive a cab.
Are you nuts?
Twenty hours
in a confined space,
being told what to do
by the kind of people
who can't even afford a car?
Here we go.
Where do they
keep the liquor?
I don't know.
I thought you said
you'd waitered here.
No, I applied.
Bastards wouldn't hire me
on account of my sketchy
employment record.
KEVIN: Crap!
All we got here
is Jew wine.
Are we allowed
to drink this stuff?
Who wouldn't allow you,
Kevin?
I don't know!
It's unholy or something.
It's fine!
And it's alcohol too, right?
Yeah, only it's
rabbi-approved alcohol.
What are you guys doing?
(GRUNTS)
I was gonna jump in,
but I saw that you had him.
Let us pray for the peaceful
repose of the soul
of Hugh William Farrell.
For his beloved wife,
Katherine Regina Farrell,
his son Matthew William
Hugh Farrell,
and his brother
Derek Timothy Farrell.
We pray to the Lord.
Lord, hear our prayer.
ALL: Lord hear our prayer.
Put it on!
I'm not wearing a tie!
You need to wear
a tie, Dad's dead!
What's the problem?
Uncle Huey, Jimmy's
not gonna wear a tie.
My dad never wore a tie.
Your dad wore a tie
on days like today.
Put it on.
Your mother's waiting.
Let me see this.
There you go.
Nice suit.
Thanks, Uncle Huey.
You know what?
Maybe it's time
you stopped calling me uncle.
You're a man now,
men call each other
by their first names.
Try it.
What's my name?
Huey.
There you go.
Okay?
You know what else
men do?
They take care of their mom
and their brothers,
no matter what.
JOEY. How was Huey to know
that one day that little
bit of advice
would be that thing
that got him killed?
FATHER DUFELT: And now
a member of Hugh's family
would like to say a few words.
I'll do it, sweetheart.
What?
Just let me do it.
Stay here.
(STAMMERING)
Huey and I,
we didn't spend...
We didn't spend as much time
in church as we should have.
But Huey was
a God-fearing man.
He was a good father,
he was a good husband,
he was a damn good boss.
And what happened to him
is a sin.
I'm not gonna forget,
for me or for my brother,
that I have
to make this right.
As God is my witness,
I will make this right.
PRIEST: In the name
of the Father, the Son,
and the Holy Spirit.
The Lord is my salvation
and my light.
Of whom shall I be afraid?
The Lord is the stronghold
of my life. Whom shall I fear?
(BOTH GIGGLING)
One thing have I asked
of the Lord,
that will I seek after,
We know him?
That I may dwell
in the house of the Lord
all the days of my life.
I think it's Jimmy Donnelly.
That's good
what you're doing
with the Irish.
Just looking for a bathroom!
I'm gonna cut it off.
Yeah, real smart,
Nicky.
Make sure the Feds
get a nice shot of you
doing it, too.
Come on!
Clean it up, let's go!
Thanks for doing
this, Jenny.
This is...
This is quite a spread.
(SCOFFS)
Oh, hey, Tommy,
how you doing?
Good, Samson.
Thanks for helping us out.
Oh, no, it's my pleasure.
Samson, can you bring me
the mustard and the potato
salad, please?
(TIRES SCREECH)
God.
Oh! You got a fare.
22 East 24th.
Get those inside.
Yeah, all right.
I'm not taking
any more fares.
22 East 24th!
What's the matter with you,
you didn't hear me?
Yeah, I heard you.
What kind of retarded cabbie
doesn't wanna take
somebody across town?
I'll show you what kind.
You should treat cab drivers
with more respect.
"Kosher."
Thanks, I'm glad
I trusted you.
It's alcohol and it's free,
what more do you want?
We're gonna need some
scotch. And a lot of it.
But we're not going to be
able to pay for it just yet.
Get out of here.
I think you're gonna
wanna give it to us.
Oh, yeah?
And why is that?
Because your daughter
has a crush on Kevin.
He's gonna date her
if you don't.
Hey, everybody,
we got scotch!
(ALL CHEERING)
If Dokey asks you anything,
we stick with what we agreed.
We were in the hospital
all night.
What's going on?
Dokey's trying to put
some things together.
Jimmy shooting his mouth off
is not helping us.
Where the hell are
the guns, Tommy?
Relax. I'm only telling you
this so we can keep
our stories straight.
You know I have
trouble talking
when I get nervous.
I always think so hard
about what I should say...
Kevin!
And I say the wrong thing.
Stop thinking.
Get a drink, okay?
We're gonna
take care of this.
Huey would have
been happy with this.
Yeah?
Turned out okay, huh?
I can't believe
I'm gonna ask you
for one more thing,
but would you mind saying
a few words later?
About Huey?
I know Dokey spoke in church,
but between you and me...
Yeah. That was
pretty interesting.
I know if you say something,
it'll come from the heart.
Sure. Yeah, sure,
I'll say something
if you want me to.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for Sean
to wake up.
Well, thanks for
staying with him,
but he shouldn't have more
than one visitor at a time
and I'm here now, so...
Okay, sure.
You'll tell him
I was here?
Of course.
(GROANS)
How you doing?
I'm not gonna cry.
You can cry.
Uncle Dokey said I shouldn't.
Oh.
He scared you, huh?
Mmm.
You know how Dokey
got his name, right?
No.
You ever heard of the song,
The Hokey Pokey?
Yeah.
Well, your Uncle Derek was
the king of The Hokey Pokey.
So everybody called him
Hokey Pokey Dokey.
(CHUCKLES)
Why don't you think of that
the next time you see him?
You won't be so scared, huh?
All right.
Jenny.
Yeah?
You got a minute?
Can I talk to you
for one second?
Yeah, sure.
The service
was beautiful.
Thank you.
I wanna ask you
about the night
that Huey died.
You were at the hospital
with the Donnellys, right?
Yeah.
Were you there
when Huey got there?
Yeah, yeah, I was.
He brought a pie
and took it into
the waiting room.
Always bringing
the pies, right?
(CHUCKLES)
Did you hear anything
that Tommy and Huey were
talking about? Anything?
No, no.
How long did you stay
at the hospital?
All night.
You know,
Tommy, the family...
Waiting to hear about Sean.
Tommy was there
the whole night?
Mmm-hmm.
What about Kevin?
Kevin? Yeah.
Don't look, but Jenny's
talking to Dokey.
What do you think
she's saying?
Don't look.
You know,
she's probably offering
her condolences, Kevin.
They looked at me.
So? Take it easy, Kevin.
You're gonna give yourself
a heart attack.
I'm just trying to piece
together the last moments,
you know? That's all.
'Cause none of this
seems right. None of it.
Would you excuse me
for a minute?
Sure.
Thanks.
(DOOR OPENS)
Are you okay?
You need something
to eat.
Why? You saying
I'm drunk?
No.
You know,
you're the one person,
the only person I thought
would never make me
feel this bad.
Maybe I can understand
what happened that night
because of Sean,
because you felt
you had no other choice.
But Huey?
Why did you have
to kill Huey?
If you really believe
what you said
about loving me,
you gotta stop asking.
You just trust me.
That night is done.
You said everything
was gonna be okay,
and I wanted to believe it.
But it's not.
So I have to try
wanting something else.
Hey, everybody!
You enjoying my bar?
Welcome!
Hey, Dokey!
Your brother, man...
Bummer.
Came to pay our respects.
Condolences.
This isn't gonna
be good.
Three shots!
Right over here.
There are a couple of things
you need to know
about the Irish.
I forget the first.
But the second thing is this.
They don't believe
that death is the end.
They think it's about
resurrection.
And what is more
life-affirming than sex?
Hey, I've been watching
you all night.
I'm not that drunk.
Okay, you're in mourning,
I get that.
Hey, I have been
watching you all night.
How's it going?
(PHONE RINGING)
Firecracker.
Uh...
I don't...
I...
I mean...
Hold on.
Who is it?
Where you going?
Who the hell is this?
TOMMY: Who was that?
It's Dokey.
It's Dokey calling?
He was just here.
He's still here.
He's in the basement.
He's calling us from
our own basement?
He wants us to join him.
Is he out of his mind?
Jenny's down there with him.
JOEY. The only thing worse
than having someone
threaten you
is having them threaten
the person you love most.
How Dokey knew that Jenny
was the one for Tommy,
I don't know.
But he knew.
I don't think I've ever
seen Tommy Donnelly
look that scared.
What's going on, Dokey?
Thanks, Earl.
Where's your other brother?
He had to run off.
That doesn't look good,
does it?
He's scared.
I guess I can understand
that, you know?
You should go.
Jimmy, take her upstairs.
No, you take her upstairs.
No, no, no one's taking
anybody upstairs.
You wanna tell us
what we're doing down here?
Shut up, Jimmy, okay?
You know what's funny?
There's all these people
right up there.
And we're down in here,
just a few feet away,
something totally different
going on, you know?
And they're none the wiser.
It's funny how that works.
You know, you guys
could wind up dead tonight.
I just say that
I was at a wake.
I mean, it's the truth,
I got witnesses.
You know?
Hey.
You ever find yourself
in a situation, Tommy,
with your brothers,
that people could've swore
you were there,
you know?
And yet you were
doing something else?
I need her to leave, Dokey.
I'm fine right here.
DOKEY: She's good.
I know you killed Huey.
I don't know how you did it,
but I know you killed him.
You were the last one
with him, Tommy.
And you, bigmouth,
shooting your mouth off
in the bar
that your brothers
killed for you.
You got a big mouth,
Jimmy.
You know, I'm not
the smartest guy
in the world.
But I do know
one way to get
to the truth.
Jimmy, would you
do me a favor?
Put your leg up there.
Stop this!
He was in The Tombs
when your brother
was killed, Dokey.
Yeah, I know, that's
really good. I would've
thought of that, too.
Now, would you put
your leg up there, please?
That's your bum leg,
isn't it?
(CHUCKLES)
You better
leave me dead, Doke,
'cause I'm gonna
stick this stump
straight down your throat.
You got it.
It's a promise.
You wanna know
what happened?
Do you?
I want her out of here.
Sure.
Take her upstairs.
I leave here,
I call the police.
She's not gonna call
the police with us down here.
Get your hands off me!
Please.
It's okay.
Is someone gonna do something?
'Cause my leg's getting tired.
Shut your mouth, okay?
And you got one chance
to tell me the truth.
We called Huey
'cause we screwed up.
And the Italians were
coming after us.
You screwed up how?
You know,
I'm getting a cramp.
Stay down!
You pull guns on me?
You are dead!
And you were acting
so friendly.
You want a gun?
Take it.
Oh, that's real smart,
Tommy.
I'm cool with my ax, Tommy.
We needed your brother's help
because we killed somebody.
Okay?
You needed
my brother's help.
Who did you kill?
An Italian,
you don't need to know who.
Tommy, don't tell me
what I need and don't
need to know, okay?
It was someone
who wanted Kevin dead.
He owed this guy money
and he couldn't pay.
It was an accident,
but it doesn't make
him any less dead.
Huey came to the hospital,
he said he had
a connection with Sal
and he'd try and help.
That's the last time
we saw him.
So all right,
you killed somebody,
it just wasn't Huey,
is that what you're saying?
He was standing
right where you are.
What'd you do?
You shoot him?
Yeah.
Well, shooting makes a mess.
Earl, roll over there
and put your fingers
in that drain, please.
Put them into the drain?
Earl, the drain.
JOEY. And this is the way
life works sometimes.
If they hadn't killed
Louie Downtown,
they would've been dead
right then and there.
Put the gun down, Jimmy.
Put it down.
Are we good here, Dokey?
You ever point
a gun at me again,
and I will hack you in half
while you're screaming.
You got it?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
I'm sorry.
Hey, Kate.
Hey.
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
Are you still okay
with saying something?
Yeah.
If I could
get your attention?
I wanted to say a few words
about Huey.
I...
I think if you can
remember what a person
meant to you,
and hold onto that feeling,
I think you can survive
a time like this.