Okay, here's what
you might have missed.
There were four
Donnelly brothers,
Sean, Kevin, Jimmy,
and Tommy.
They had this thing
for always getting
into trouble,
usually 'cause Jimmy
did something stupid
like stealing a truckload
of Hawaiian shirts,
leaving Tommy
to clean up the mess.
Did I mention that Tommy had
this thing for Jenny Reilly?
Okay. Skip to a couple
of days ago.
Kevin had a huge
gambling debt.
Damn.
So Jimmy got the idea
to kidnap an Italian.
To get back at the Donnellys,
the Italians beat up Sean.
To get back at the Italians,
Jimmy killed Louie.
At this point,
Tommy went to see Huey,
the head of the Irish mob,
to try and fix things,
but that didn't work.
So to protect his brother,
Tommy got Jimmy arrested
for the shirt thing,
then Tommy and Kevin
killed Sal, the head
of the Italian mob,
and Huey, the aforementioned
head of the Irish mob,
and hoped that, somehow,
no one would notice.
Me? I always wanted
brothers like that.
Joey, I am
your lawyer, okay?
You don't need
to lie to me.
What? Who's lying?
I'm an open book.
What do you wanna know?
Why I'm representing you.
'Cause I'm an innocent man.
I just... I hear things,
I pick up things.
Oh, God in heaven.
Like that night for example.
I wasn't there.
So there's no way
I could actually know
what happened.
And that was
Tommy's plan, see?
To keep his brothers safe
by keeping that night
a secret.
KEVIN:
Tommy, Tommy, wait.
We should go back.
I think somebody saw me.
Who?
I don't know.
It's just a feeling.
So we should go back
and be seen in order to
make sure that nobody saw us?
You don't have to use
sarcasm on me.
Kevin, nobody saw us.
What about the
parking lot guy?
We're five blocks away.
Yeah, but he nodded at me.
So we should kill him?
No! No, of course not.
I mean, unless
you think we...
Kevin, stop. Breathe.
Tommy, all the breathing
in the world is not gonna
change what we did.
Guns are loud.
People heard us.
And what if Sal and Huey
told someone that Jimmy
was coming?
They were planning
on killing Jimmy.
That's not something
you tell somebody.
Yeah, but these guys...
Shh. Kevin, no one saw us.
No one knows.
And as long as we keep
what happened between
the two of us, no one's gonna.
Okay?
Okay.
JOEY. But it's like
the old saying goes,
"The only way two people
can keep a secret
is if both of them are dead. "
You mean if one
of them is dead.
That's the saying.
Obviously we come
from different neighborhoods.
Which is why Kevin might
have been nervous when
Tommy asked for his gun.
What if there are guys
waiting for us back
at the hospital?
Just give me the damn gun.
Okay.
(GUNSHO TS)
JENNY: Hey, Henry.
We went for coffee.
Hey, Sean.
(E.K.G. BEEPING)
For such a pretty boy,
you sure are one
tough son of a bitch.
TOMMY:
Sean, this is important.
If anybody asks you
what happened,
you say you were mugged.
And you didn't
see who did it.
Can you hear me?
You understand?
Okay.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just ran down
for coffee.
Coffee.
For two hours?
With your brother
just out of surgery?
Yeah.
Your coat's wet.
Tommy...
Tommy, wait.
Tell me
what happened.
You can tell me,
it's okay.
What happened?
(SNIFFLES)
Tell me.
It's okay.
JOEY. However, not all
the Donnelly brothers
were enjoying the evening
quite as much.
Hey! Hey!
Answer the phone,
answer the phone.
Pick up the phone!
(RINGING)
Bro, you gonna
be all day?
Am I gonna be all day?
(GRUNTS)
HELEN: Tommy?
Tommy?
The doctor wants to see us.
DOCTOR 1:
We'll repeat the CAT scan
to see if the edema,
the swelling, has decreased.
Remember,
he is young and healthy
and he should respond
favorably to treatment.
We'll monitor him
for the next 24 hours.
And we'll need to do
additional tests
to determine what
the long-term effects
of his injuries will be.
But I feel confident...
DOCTOR 2:
His injuries are severe.
We won't know for a while
if there's nerve damage,
and the majority
of the breaks have fused.
What are you saying? Huh?
My Jimmy's a cripple?
Helen, let the doctor talk.
Mrs. Donnelly, we're hopeful
that your Jimmy will make
a full recovery,
but you have to be
prepared for the fact
that he may not walk again.
JOEY. That day,
Tommy made a deal.
He would pay whatever price
God demanded
...on earth as it is
in heaven, give us this day
our daily bread...
if he just let Jimmy
walk again.
...forgive those who
trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil,
for thine is the kingdom...
But for now,
Sean is stable.
Hopefully we'll know
more soon.
Thank you.
We gotta slip out.
Go ahead.
Where are we going?
Shopping.
Man!
Kim? You're still here?
Did we hear anything
from the doctor yet?
She says Sean's stable.
Good.
Hey, listen, Kim,
the guys who attacked Sean,
did you get a good
look at them?
I can definitely
describe one of them.
You know what would be good?
What?
What would be
the best thing for Sean?
For you to not remember
what those guys look like.
How would that be better?
You think I love my brother?
Yeah, of course you do.
It would really
be better for him,
okay?
Okay.
Thanks.
And don't let
my mother scare you.
I'll be all right.
Tommy, I hate shopping.
How close were you
to those two guys
when you shot them?
A few feet.
Which means you got blood
on your clothes whether
you can see it or not.
So I'll change
and burn them.
And when someone remembers
what you were wearing?
And they ask you
where those clothes are?
I thought you said
no one was gonna ask.
How much money you got?
A couple bucks.
(SIGHS)
How's he doing?
How do you think
he's doing?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Make sure the sensors
are at the bottom.
Where the hell
do you come up
with this?
Science class.
You see why you
should pay attention?
MAN 1: All set?
MAN 2: Yeah.
All right.
Excuse us.
(CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
Sal Minnetta
and Huey Farrell.
Gee, think there's
gonna be any
fallout from this?
I got a couple guys
say they work here.
No kidding?
You ask me, this isn't
the brightest idea
you've come up with.
Really?
What do you think
was my best idea?
The very best?
Best you can think of.
Squeezing Jimmy Donnelly
till he whacked Sal.
That worked out
pretty well, didn't it?
Why don't you
have a little faith?
Morning, Detective.
Nicky Cottero, right?
That's right,
Detective.
So I was, you know,
wondering if you had
any news.
You're a reporter now,
Nicky?
Well, Sal, you know,
he was a beloved employer.
It's understandable the staff
is gonna be upset.
I was just wondering
if you had something
I could pass on to them.
No. Right now
I just have questions.
Like what was the head
of the Irish mob
doing down here
with all these Italians?
Drinking,
watching porn,
I couldn't tell you.
So what brings you down here
this early in the morning?
Is it a responsibility
to brief the staff?
Well, I'm
the beverage manager.
People are gonna naturally
look to me for answers.
Well, why don't you go
upstairs and think of some,
and then when
I'm finished down here,
you can fill me in, too.
I'm glad to help.
This is
a terrible crime.
Thanks. You guys
are doing a great job.
Cocky son of a bitch
came down here
to plant a flag.
Meanwhile, Huey's brother,
Dokey,
was also curious about
who killed his brother,
and was asking some
questions of his own.
So you don't know
anything, huh?
(GROANING)
You know anything now?
TOMMY: Make sure
the ink part's face down.
KEVIN: Got it.
And you got enough
tin foil around it.
I got it, I got it.
Damn.
I'm telling you, Tommy...
Kevin, will you
stop worrying?
It's gonna be okay.
I can see the ink.
Are you wearing
two jackets?
How do you mean?
You are!
I told you we had to get rid
of what we were wearing.
Yeah, but it's
my favorite one.
Throw it out right now!
Oh, man.
I'm going to class.
You do what you normally do.
We gotta act like
it's a regular day
and nothing happened.
What are you staring at,
Kevin?
Kev!
Damn it, Jimmy.
Here you go, fellas.
Thanks a lot.
Okay.
It's coming right up,
May, okay?
Hey, no problem.
Here you go.
Hey!
Hey, Pop,
who hasn't ordered?
Everybody's good,
I got you covered.
You just coming
from the hospital now?
Yeah.
They kept that boy
in overnight?
Yeah. He's still in ICU.
It's terrible.
Yeah.
"Yeah"?
I hate to see
anyone get hurt.
Pop, just leave it for once.
There's just two sides
to every story.
There's two sides to Sean
being beaten so hard he might
have brain damage?
What's the second side
to that, Dad?
Well, you don't give somebody
a beating like that unless
you got a reason.
Are you good here?
'Cause I'm gonna
take a walk.
Jenny, listen to me, please.
I know you like Tommy.
And I don't think
he's a bad kid.
It's just that...
It's like something
is in their blood.
No matter how hard
they try to do good,
that blood is always
gonna seep through.
And it poisons
whatever it touches.
Gosh, Dad, why didn't
you ever tell me
you felt this way?
Jenny.
Come on, Jenny!
You wonder why
we have to keep
buying new stools.
I should've known Jimmy
was too messed up
to take care of anything.
Now we gotta get rid of a body
in broad daylight?
Okay, so we'll
wait till tonight.
Yeah, you're right, Kevin.
'Cause the smell of a rotting
body is not gonna attract
any attention.
Let's wait.
Again with the sarcasm.
I'm getting sick of it,
Tommy.
I mean, how could
he just dump it there?
What the hell is he thinking?
Come on,
where would you put it?
Not in the dumpster
behind the bar, Kevin!
Okay, so where?
I don't know.
How many bodies
you get rid of before?
Hey, what about
the landfill?
I mean, we could sneak in,
put him under some garbage,
they'd bury him for us.
The landfill on
Staten Island?
Yeah.
So what,
we just take a ferry,
just the three of us?
Okay. We stuff him
in a furnace.
Our furnace?
No, of course not,
somebody else's.
Oh, you know someone
with a furnace large
enough for a body?
Well, I'd have
to think about it.
How about a tub
full of acid?
Kevin,
stop making suggestions.
You're really freaking me out.
Okay, we can bury him.
Oh, you know a place
in the city where
we can bury a body?
Jersey.
(PHONE RINGING)
I know a place.
Hello?
JIMMY. Where the hell
have you been?
Jimmy!
I been calling
since 7.00!
You should be down here
to bail me out!
I don't know,
I guess we're
a little preoccupied,
what with Louie's body
out back in the trash!
What, now it's my fault
that I got arrested?
You told me you
took care of it.
I was going to...
You know, it's real smart,
Tommy, talking about this
on the phone.
Just get down here
and bail me.
Not gonna do it.
What do you mean?
I'm not gonna argue about it.
You wanna talk to somebody,
you can talk to Kevin.
Why me?
Hey, Jimmy.
We're not gonna do it!
JIMMY. Kevin, listen to me.
There's a bag under the bar.
From Sal.
You know what bag
I'm talking about.
Hold on.
Where under the bar?
It's under the taps,
I think.
This place is disgusting.
Sorry.
You know what? Stop looking,
I don't want you to get dirty.
Why is everyone using
sarcasm on me today?
Okay, I got it.
Just get down here
and get me out.
Wait, Jimmy, wait, wait.
What?
If I took this
to the track first,
I could double it.
You gamble a penny of that,
I'm gonna bite
your thumbs off!
You coming?
Where you going?
Nowhere.
What's in that bag?
Nothing.
Hmm?
Hey! Hey.
This is the ransom money!
You think?
Give it back, Tommy.
Hey!
Give it back!
What the hell's
wrong with you?
You think you can just
bail Jimmy out and suddenly
he's not gonna be the guy
who got us into
all this crap?
You wanna forget
the fact he shot Louie?
Yeah?
How many people
did we shoot last night?
Because of Jimmy!
I'm not gonna argue
with you, either.
We don't have enough time,
because we gotta go
clean up another one
of Jimmy's messes.
Look, there's 30 grand
in there. We could bail
Jimmy out with five.
You don't get it,
do you?
We're screwed here.
Let's go.
Wait. How do you
know any of this?
Oh.
Well, maybe
that particular time
I was there.
Hey, you guys take off,
I'll watch everything.
Where the hell
did you come from?
What? I been here
the whole time.
Don't worry,
mum's the word,
lips are sealed.
You pay for that beer?
Yeah, probably.
Psst. Tommy.
Pony car?
We're not going
for a joyride, Kevin.
Get in, I'll grab him
on this end.
You get in.
I'm driving.
Yeah, what's that got
to do with anything?
You don't get in,
I don't drive.
Let's go!
Damn, the stench of him.
I feel like it's in my skin.
Drive faster.
And get stopped
for a ticket? Smart.
Did you lock the door
at the back of the bar?
While you were berating me
or while I was digging
a corpse out of the dumpster?
Oh, that's sarcasm,
isn't it?
Don't make me laugh,
I'm pissed at you.
You're pissed at me?
Damn straight.
Are you sure we're going
in the right direction?
I'm sure.
How you know
about this place?
Jake Macey.
Used to steal cars
and drag race out here.
It's right by a swamp,
no one around for miles.
It's perfect.
This is it?
Yeah.
This is the abandoned swamp
with no one around
for miles and miles?
Last time I was here,
yeah.
It's not like you had
a better plan.
Yeah. Now who's stupid, huh?
You couldn't get
a bigger barrel?
They don't make
bigger barrels.
Come on.
(RUMBLING)
What are you doing?
He's alive!
Where did you get that?
How many guns did Jimmy
have at the bar, huh?
Come on.
Grab his legs again.
No, no! Not until
I know he's dead.
He's dead!
That was just gas
escaping from his body.
Then why did you jump?
Because you did!
Yeah.
We need holes
in the barrel, anyway.
Come on.
It's not gonna work.
Stay out of sight.
I'll be right back.
Hey!
Wait. Hey!
Whoa, whoa.
What's that for?
Strip down.
What?
Take off your clothes, Kevin.
Hold his ankles.
Tommy.
Do it, Kevin.
(VOMITING)
Come on, Kevin.
I can't.
Hello?
Tommy?
Tommy!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't
help over there.
I don't know
what happened to me.
It's just like...
I started shaking
and everything went dark.
Not now, Kevin.
What I'm trying to tell you
is it was just like...
Like I didn't
have any control.
And my hands and my legs...
Kevin,
I'm not really interested
in how you feel about
what happened here.
Please just
shut the hell up.
Did you take anything
out of that bag?
No.
What are you doing?
Counting the money.
We gotta get out of here.
You don't believe me,
why'd you even ask, huh?
I wanna see
if you were lying to me.
All right, fine!
I took some money, okay?
But only enough
to bail Jimmy out.
What a great idea.
I turn myself inside out
to get him into jail,
to rehab,
so that he won't be killed
or kill himself, and you're
gonna bail him out?
We're his brothers.
He's sick, he needs us.
I'm helping him.
No one gets help in there.
If you'd ever been in there
you'd know that.
Give me the money, Kevin.
No, it's not your money,
all right?
It was Jimmy's idea,
you didn't want
any part of it.
Give me the money.
I'm keeping it, all right?
It's my cut, I can do
with it what I want.
There is no cut,
don't you understand that?
This is ransom money,
and the Italians know
who they paid it to.
You want a chance of living,
we gotta give it back.
Give it back, Tommy?
This is part of your big plan
to make everything right?
Tommy, Louie is dead!
If they wanna
kill us for that,
giving back the money is
not gonna change anything.
Nobody knows Louie's dead.
The only people who knew
were Huey and Sal.
So what, they're gonna think
he went on vacation?
He's a low-level bookie.
Nobody cared
about him but Sal,
because he was his nephew.
Nobody's gonna care.
What they're gonna care about
is that money.
And we're giving it back.
You give the money back,
they're gonna blow
your brains out.
Then they're gonna come
looking for the rest of us.
Where is it?
Keep your hands off of me.
Do it again, Tommy,
I swear to God...
Yeah? What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do? Hmm?
(GROANS)
(SHOUTS)
Go ahead, Kevin.
You're right.
I'm the one trying
to hurt Jimmy.
Shoot me.
Pull the trigger.
Come on, Kevin,
pull the trigger.
Get up.
Get out of here, Kevin.
Here?
Yeah. Go home.
You been up for two days.
Get some sleep.
You coming?
Get out, Kevin.
Tommy.
Not gonna need it.
Go home.
I'll be there
in a couple hours.
No, you won't.
Thanks, honey.
Sure.
Whenever I watch
my boys sleeping,
I still see them
as five years old
in my head.
Does that sound crazy?
Always five.
And they're not
babies anymore.
But they're not
little men, either.
I'm so sorry
this happened.
Thanks for hanging in
with me.
I know it's not easy
watching people suffer.
No, it's not.
Do you know
what happened last night?
How do you mean?
You know what I mean.
I think
that if you know
someone's good,
you know it in your belly,
then you trust that if
they had to do something,
they had no other choice.
We're closed.
Yeah, I'm here
to see Nicky Cottero.
Someone's here for Nicky.
It's Tommy Donnelly.
Tommy Donnelly.
Okay.
The stairs are
in the back.
This way?
Yeah.
Thanks.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm too tired to sleep.
Stay put.
Whatever you say.
I mean it.
I'll be back in a minute.
I'll be here.
Anything happens,
(KNOCKING)
NICKY: Come in.
Take a seat.
You want a drink?
No.
No, thanks.
I heard about Sal.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, it's a real loss.
You here to pay
your respects?
I'm here with some
unfinished business.
My brother Jimmy kidnapped
Louie Downtown.
My brother's a junkie.
Never thinks things through.
So I took him to rehab,
and I let Louie go.
In the hopes
that it would end things.
I don't want
any bad blood.
There's 30,000 in there.
With Sal gone,
I assume it belongs to you.
Where's Louie?
Don't know.
Like I said,
I let him go.
Every day Louie's missing,
I lose money.
Tell you what
I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna accept
this money in good faith.
I appreciate it.
But I need you to pay me
$1,000 a week until
Louie gets back.
For disruption of business.
You understand?
That money makes us even.
You got a lost bookie,
that's your problem.
See you around.
Hey, kid!
Tell your brother Jimmy
I'm gonna be seeing him
real soon.
That'd be great.
He'd enjoy the visitor.
Didn't you hear?
Jimmy was arrested yesterday.
He's been in jail.
And one more time,
you know this because...
Oh, yeah.
I was there, too.
How'd it go?
Like it went.
What the hell's
Joey Ice Cream doing here?
I have no idea.
JOEY. We were that tight.
They never took
a step without me.
JOEY. Remember when I said
how as a kid Tommy Donnelly
tried to make that deal?
Well, God didn't hear him
right away.
So Tommy kept going back.
Kept trying
to get God's attention.
Until He finally listened.
Your mom's looking for you.
The doctor said
Jimmy's gonna walk.
Only thing is, Tommy never
negotiated the price.
I should have
told you last night.
I love you.
You got customers waiting?
Glad you came by.
Yeah. Me, too.
Because I wanted
to tell you that I can't...
Can't what?
Do this.
Be with you.
I really am sorry.
Wait.
Jenny...
If you want breakfast,
come on down.
JOEY. There was no way for him
to know way back then
that God was gonna
take away the one thing
Tommy wanted most.
But that's what life is like,
am I right?
When one door closes,
another window opens.
Tommy. Get in.
If you don't mind,
I'd just like to walk.
Hey, put him in the trunk.
I'm getting in.
I guess you heard,
somebody
shot my brother to death?
Yeah, I heard.
I'm really sorry.
You know, I can understand
somebody wanting to kill Huey.
He had enemies.
Who doesn't, right?
I just can't figure out
what he was doing
in Sal Minnetta's basement.
He didn't tell anyone?
I mean, the last thing
anybody knows,
he went to visit you
and your brother
at the hospital.
Brought you the pie
his wife made.
Yeah, he came by.
He was checking on Sean.
I heard that Sean took
quite a beating.
Is he okay?
He's gonna be okay.
That's good.
That's good you still
got your brother.
Did Huey say anything to you
before he left the hospital?
Where he was going?
Anything?
I wish I could tell you more.
Me, too.
All right,
get out of here.
Hey.
You hear anything,
all right?
I'll let you know.
Good.