You're still not
caught up yet?
This is ridiculous.
Remember that
delivery guy, Samson?
He won't take a hint.
But you've gotta leave,
right now.
Crybaby.
Little Jimmy had
something to cry about.
He never found out
which Italians
killed his dad.
But the Donnellys had
other worries, like Dokey,
who wanted them dead.
Until they made him a deal.
Now Dokey's asking favors,
like helping his friend get
rid of some squatters.
He said he was trying
to fix the building up.
You know, we're trying
But the squatters
had other ideas.
It's piss!
JOEY. Of course,
they had to go.
Whitey wanted
to leave town, too.
They got drugs
in Des Moines.
We could have
a future together.
He didn't get
as far as he hoped.
Too bad.
I kind of liked him.
I tell you to do
a simple job.
This is how you
deal with it?
You son of a bitch.
You used us.
I used you?
Here's your money.
If it's okay with you,
I never wanna see you again.
JOEY. Tommy knew
right then and there
he had a lot to learn
if he was ever gonna
run the four blocks
he got from Dokey.
THOMAS. Okay. Joey,
stop right there.
The thing you
have to remember
is that this is a grand jury
you're going in front of.
If you lie,
you perjure yourself.
Oh, well, gee, that could
get me in all kinds
of trouble, couldn't it?
If you think I'm gonna
let you take an oath
and then testify
that the Donnelly brothers'
entire enterprise consisted
of a four-block radius,
then it's time
for you to get...
What number lawyer am I?
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry, Joey,
I missed the funny part.
Enterprise.
Oh, you guys talk
like it was some kind
of big corporation.
It wasn't like that at all.
We were just a bunch of kids
hanging out in a bar.
At least,
that's how it started.
You got a visitor.
TOMMY: What the hell's
he doing here?
Wish I knew.
He won't talk to me.
He wouldn't talk
to me, either.
Tommy liked to pretend
he didn't know why people were
always coming to him for help.
Of course he knew.
He was Bobby Donnelly's son.
Here.
JOEY. There was
no escaping it.
You're a saint, Bobby.
I don't know what to say.
I'm embarrassed.
Hey, forget it.
Look, I'll get you
an extra day or two a week.
You pay me back, all right?
Okay, come on.
Kevin said you were
looking for me?
I never liked you.
I never liked
your whole family.
Great.
And the longer I sit here
waiting to ask you what
I came to ask you,
the more I hate you.
You know what, Mr. Reilly,
all I've done is
bend over backwards,
kissing your ass,
trying to make you happy.
You don't like me.
I don't like you.
Good.
Sit down.
I want to make you
a partner with me
in my diner.
Excuse me?
Here. Read that.
"This building has been deemed
structurally unsound.
"Prepare to vacate
the premise subject..."
This is for the diner?
That's why I need your help.
I called everybody.
Mortgage company says
call the Buildings
Department.
They say call
the mortgage company.
Now, I think what
you need to do now
is call a lawyer.
What good is a lawyer
gonna be against Dokey?
Dokey?
That son of a bitch
is behind this.
Tried to buy me out.
I wouldn't sell.
Now he's gonna
take it this way.
Hey, you!
You wanna listen,
come sit down.
Otherwise,
get the hell
away from here.
I wasn't listening.
Stop lying.
I've known you
your whole life.
Fix this for me.
Don't let them
take my diner.
Fix it and I'll
give you half.
Okay.
Give me this notice and
the name and the address
of your mortgage company.
But you're not giving me
half your diner.
The hell I'm not.
The last thing I want
is charity from
the likes of you.
And my Jenny doesn't
know anything about this.
And I wanna
keep it that way.
You're welcome,
Mr. Reilly.
Happy to help.
(GUNSHO TS)
KEVIN: Reilly says
Dokey's behind this?
Why don't we go
straight to Dokey?
TOMMY: Sure. Let's go
to Dokey, Kevin.
And he'll say,
"Are you guys with me
or aren't you?"
We'll say,
"No, we're with Reilly."
Is that the conversation
you wanna have?
Besides, think about it.
Dokey has us clean out
a building for Lambert,
Lambert burns
down the building,
now Reilly's building
gets condemned.
Gee, let me think,
is there a connection here?
So we're gonna threaten
Lambert, make him
tell us everything?
No. We're gonna
ask him first.
(GROANS)
JO ANIE. Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Jimmy!
I'm at Whitey's.
What?
You mind popping
over here?
I need you, babe.
Yeah, sure, Jimmy,
I'll just pop over,
with the cops all
over this place...
Don't argue with
me right now.
And bring something
with you.
What? This ain't
straight thinking, Jimmy.
(CLOSES PHONE)
Hey, Whitey!
You okay?
Lambert's office was
here yesterday, right?
We'll go to this Full City
Mortgage Company,
and find out
who's behind this.
Then what?
Then we're gonna
put a stop to it.
Their office is on
40 Worth Street.
Where's Worth Street?
Worth.
That way.
Yeah, one block away.
Come on.
KEVIN:
It's the same building.
Yep.
It's on the first floor.
Come on.
Excuse me.
I think maybe we're
in the wrong place.
Is this Full
City Mortgage?
This is our
message service.
So there's no one
here in person that
we can talk to?
So let me guess,
he's the smart one.
Just tell us where
the main office is.
To what?
Full City Mortgage.
I have no idea.
Hey, what are you being
so bitchy about?
We're just asking
you questions.
Listen, dunce...
What'd you call me?
You heard me.
We handle 75
different companies,
Full City is just
one of them.
Here. Leave your name
and number and I'll give
them the message.
Which is my job,
to take a message.
Okay, thanks.
Here is my cell
phone number.
If you need that, too.
Why would you do that?
Why would you give
that human hate machine
your phone number?
I really liked her.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(DOOR OPENING)
JOANIE: (SCREAMING)
Jimmy!
What?
What the hell?
Damn it!
Is he dead?
(SHUSHING)
Keep your voice down.
Is he dead?
What's wrong with you?
Keep your voice down,
I got a headache.
Jimmy, did
you kill him?
Hey, did you
bring the stuff?
Oh, my God.
My God...
Joanie, would you shut up?
He pulled a knife on me!
Oh, my God!
Joanie,
get yourself together,
I swear to God!
Okay, okay, I'm together!
Wait a minute.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
You called me!
Yeah, I did,
but the door was locked.
How'd you get in here?
Whitey gave me
a set of keys.
He gave you a set of keys.
Why would he do that?
In case I ever
needed something.
That's real
generous of him.
How many times
you need something?
(KICKS BODY)
Go to hell, Jimmy.
You're my girl.
Nobody else's.
Yeah?
Well, you don't act like it.
What do you want me to do?
Huh?
You want me to
buy you flowers?
(SCOFFS)
(GROANS)
I can't, Jimmy,
not with him
looking at me.
He's not looking at you.
Plus he's dead.
He can't see anything.
Forget it,
I'm not doing it!
Wait right there.
Okay?
Okay.
We gotta find
this guy, Lino.
The engineer who
signed off on this.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yeah?
Joey for you.
What?
You got a visitor. Dokey.
The good news is
he doesn't have
an axe with him.
30% of 10 grand.
There it is.
I want you to know
I got an extra 10
from Lambert.
But you don't get
a piece of that because
you weren't square with us.
When wasn't I
square with you?
You gave us a piece
of work to clear
out a building,
but you never
told us you were
gonna burn it down.
I say that's not square.
I say it's none
of your business.
I say that makes for
a tough partnership.
Oh, so now
we're partners? I see.
Let's you and I
go downstairs and talk
for a minute, all right?
Sure.
Who the hell are you
to accuse me of
setting fires?
You go down to those offices,
you're talking to people.
You're trying to help
Reilly out, aren't you?
See, you think I wouldn't
know about that, did you?
Reilly's a friend.
He's gonna lose the diner.
I'm trying to help him.
What's that to you, Dokey?
You know, you are
just like your father.
Excuse me?
You ask too many questions.
You wanna die like him?
Huh?
On the ground,
being beat to a pulp
until your heart stops?
If the answer is no, Tommy,
then stop going down
and talking to people about
anything, about real estate...
Stop.
Dokey?
What?
What's my father got
to do with any of this?
Nothing. I'm just
trying to make a point.
And I hope I made it.
He doesn't want us
helping Reilly.
Good.
Because I'm thinking
helping Reilly's a bad idea.
I'm thinking we need
to talk to somebody
who works for the city.
What happened to
the part about not
helping Reilly?
We're helping him.
Well, we could
always go to Jonesy.
I mean, he used
to work for the
Buildings Department
before he got caught
glomming stucco
for his new house.
And you're telling
me this now?
I still kind of
owe him some money.
How much?
Two grand.
I mean, you wouldn't believe
how uptight he is about it.
You know, if you had
just talked to me,
it wouldn't have
to be like this.
Samson...
You came into my home,
you kissed me.
You know,
when I kiss somebody,
that means something.
My Dad's inside.
Good!
Let's tell him
what a slut you are, huh?
Tell him what you did
to me that night.
Samson,
I'm gonna go in now.
I trusted you.
And you lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
I told you
it was a mistake.
Mistake?
I'm gonna give you
one more chance.
But you better
learn the lesson.
I'll call you later?
And now you're counting it?
You know what?
Give it back to me.
I can't...
I can't wait until
you owe me money
for 11 months
and see how you like it.
Kevin!
So what do you wanna know?
The number on here
for the Buildings
Department?
It says call for inquiries.
We called, got a recording.
It's the city,
what do you expect?
So how do we get in to talk
to somebody about this?
JONESY:
Oh, that's a good one.
What? Is it a fake?
Yeah, the notice is real.
The engineer is a fake.
This guy, Anthony Lino,
Chief Engineer?
Got his degree
from Wiseguy U.
He wouldn't know
a blueprint from
a ham sandwich.
It's a good bet
that this notice was
bought and paid for.
I'd go see Franny Kenny
down at the Buildings
Department.
He might be able to
tell you what's going on.
Franny Kenny?
He was friends
with your old man.
They told me you were
in the back. I hope
I'm not interrupting.
I don't want to get
you in any trouble.
No, no, no, it's okay.
It's pretty slow
in here today
and even if it wasn't...
And I wanted
to give you this.
It's a mix
of my favorite songs.
MAN: Pretty lame, dude.
Giving a homemade mix
to a girl that works
in a jukebox store?
You got no game at all.
You've got
great game.
Thank you.
Well, listen, I'll let you
get back to work.
Oh, okay.
Well, thanks.
Hey, would you wanna
hang out sometime?
I'd love that.
I get off early.
Okay.
All right, great.
Oh, I have to work.
But you know what?
Do you wanna just
stop by the Firecracker?
I'll be there.
(R AND B MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO)
Your boss just bought
up these two properties.
In Irish territory?
Trevor's about to fix
the zoning laws
so that the walk-ups
there now can be turned
into high-rises.
That could be
worth millions.
So you're telling me
that this is the business
that Trevor's got going on
with Alo and Dokey?
Isn't that what
you asked for?
You're a doll.
Hey, baby.
Meet Trish.
Trish, this is Corey.
Okay.
So we're finished?
Yeah.
Great, now we know
it's about real estate.
Big deal.
Vinnie, if I had to depend
on your nose for the truth,
me and you would be
in a lot of trouble.
Okay, what did I miss?
Whatever Dokey and Alo
got going on together,
it's about more than this.
You understand?
So then she lied to us.
No, no, no, she gave us
everything we needed.
She just doesn't know it.
Bobby Donnelly's boys.
I haven't seen you since
you were still dropping
a load in your diapers.
(CHUCKLES)
Which one are you, Jimmy?
No, Tommy.
How about you?
Sean, right?
0-for-2. Kevin.
You're little Kevin.
I bought you
a fire truck when...
No, no, that was you.
You, I bought a little horse
because your father
said you were lucky.
Yeah, I think I still
have that somewhere.
How's your mother?
Good.
Good. That's good.
She had a hard go
there for a while.
What can I do
for you boys?
Anthony Lino was
the engineer.
Let me guess,
somebody's getting screwed.
The past 12 years,
the city's put everything
on computers.
But there's always
a hard copy filed away.
You can't trace a search
on a hard copy.
You never know
who's checking it,
right, boys?
(CHUCKLING)
(KEVIN CHUCKLES)
What are you laughing at?
I don't know.
He's laughing,
I'm laughing.
Looks like Lino's condemned
nine other buildings
in the neighborhood
in the past six months.
Nine?
That's what I said.
So how do we find Lino?
Lino can't help you.
He'll just call his buddies
and you'll be into
a whole world of hurt.
No. We gotta go
after the legit guys,
the ones who
have paid Lino off.
Now, we have to find
out who really owns
these buildings.
Reilly owns his building.
Whoever holds the mortgage
owns the buildings.
Now, we find out
who they are,
you tell them
you're gonna publicize
the fact
that nine other buildings
in the neighborhood
have received phony
condemnation notices.
You say "newspapers,"
they'll give you
anything you want.
See, okay, Grand Limited.
Now they've been sold to...
Safety Net Limited.
All right.
FRANNY: K Boyle Limited now
owned by Tomorrow Ventures.
Tall Pines now owned by
Green and Green Incorporated,
now owned by
Miller Road Development.
Okay. Let's see
what this gives us.
Sorry, boys.
It's the end of the line.
What about this
Longdale Properties?
Where does that lead?
You'd spend months
tracking those guys down.
But I can't help you.
No, we're done here, boys.
C'est la vie.
What the hell's
that mean?
It's French for
"We're screwed."
That's what you're
telling us, right?
Was he better
looking than me?
Only in some places.
Which places?
Not that, you jerk.
He had nicer teeth than you.
Oh, my God,
that's it!
What?
His teeth.
That's how we'll
get rid of him.
You hammer out his teeth,
you cut off his hands,
we could dump him anywhere.
They can't identify him.
"Hammer out his teeth"?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
I can't believe you
just said that.
So who you been dealing with
at Full City Mortgage?
Nobody.
I got the loan from
my bank 30 years ago.
(PHONE RINGING)
Reilly's Diner.
Hello?
Anyway, about six months ago
I got a letter
telling me to pay
that company, Full City.
But I never talked
to anybody, not like
a real person.
You never talked to
anybody at the company?
Didn't I just say that?
I sent them checks,
that's all I know!
Why are you yelling at us?
We're helping you.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
What?
Ma, slow down.
Ma...
I'm gonna keep digging.
Tommy,
Ma wants us home.
She sounds really upset.
Was that Tommy?
Yeah.
What did he want?
Nothing.
(PHONE RINGING)
Reilly's Diner.
Hello?
Who is this?
Damn!
It's been happening all day.
NICKY:
You remember this place?
This is where you let
Ray hit me in the
head with a shovel.
Don't even think
about it, Vinnie!
Yeah.
But they had a gun
to my head.
Yeah, yeah.
But I'm telling you,
a 10-year peace
between Alo and Huey
couldn't hold for
something this small.
Considering Alo hates
the Irish as much as
we do, I agree.
I'm telling you,
it's gotta be
something bigger.
Okay.
What?
Look at this.
That's those two
buildings right there.
VINNIE: Yeah, those are
the two buildings that
are going high-rise.
Yeah, I know,
except you remember
what Alo said?
Where are you?
(GRUNTS)
Tell me what this place is.
He's making a point.
Not only is he buying
those two walk-ups,
he's buying the ground
we're standing on.
And how much you wanna bet
he's buying a whole bunch
of lots from here to there?
Son of a bitch!
What the hell for?
This neighborhood's been dead
like 100 years.
It'll never happen.
A whole lot
is happening.
And you know what?
He's getting a piece of it.
And whatever it is,
Trevor and Dokey are
getting a cut, too.
The only reason why
we don't know about it
is because we're out.
If we're out,
we're dead, right?
Vinnie, we were dead
10 minutes ago.
Now Alo's dead.
Jimmy, Ma's been calling you,
I've been calling you,
where are you?
It's important.
Okay.
I wanted to do this with
the three of you, but...
Ma!
What is it?
What are you trying
to do for Jenny's father?
I know you like the girl,
but what kind of trouble are
you getting yourselves into?
They condemned
the man's building
for no good reason.
We're trying to help.
What's the problem?
The problem
is it's none
of your business.
What are you talking
to Franny Kenny about?
Did he call you?
What's wrong
with Franny Kenny?
I thought he was
a friend of Dad's.
Just answer my question.
About what?
Reilly's building?
Can someone tell me
what's going on?
Okay.
You go to your room.
Ma, you can't tell me
to go to my room.
Now.
God help you
if Sean's been pulled
into any of this.
Ma, what is it you're
so worried about?
And who is
Franny Kenny anyway?
Franny Kenny is nobody,
he's a hanger-on.
Kissed Huey Farrell's
ass his entire life
till Huey kicked him
out the day after
your father died.
This isn't about him.
It's about you and
your brothers stopping
whatever it is you're doing.
We're helping Jenny
and her father.
We're not stopping.
Open it.
There's more.
Look at them all.
I went and got these
so I'd never forget what
they did to your father.
Why'd you show me these?
Because I'm so afraid that
the same thing is gonna happen
to you and your brothers
if you don't leave
this thing alone.
Tommy,
do not ask another
question about any of this.
I'm asking you to do that.
I expect it to happen.
What happened?
Where you going?
I'm going to Reilly's.
Dropping this thing.
Franny Kenny?
God, it's been years
since I've heard that name.
TOMMY:
Is he a good guy?
He worked for Huey
at the union.
We'd have dinner
once in a while.
But I never
really knew him.
TOMMY:
What'd he do for Huey?
I don't know what
his official title was.
But whenever
it came to money
or handling money,
he was the go-to guy,
or at least that's
what Huey called him.
So they had a falling out?
Huey had a falling out
with everybody at
one point or another.
This is after
my dad died,
right?
Yeah, I guess it was
around there.
Why you asking
all these questions?
Kevin and I are
trying to find out
who owns this building
that's being condemned.
Franny said he could help,
but then he said he couldn't.
You're talking
about a building
in the neighborhood.
Yeah.
Well, that's crap.
Pick a building, Franny
could tell you who owns it,
when they bought it,
who they bought it from,
and how much they cheated
the previous owner out of.
At least he could
when I knew him.
What if we made it
look like a suicide?
How we gonna do that?
We slice up his wrists
and when that didn't work,
he started stabbing himself.
I would believe that.
Yeah, but nobody
else would.
Well, we're gonna have
to deal with this.
I am dealing with it.
This is how I do
my best thinking.
Hold on!
You know what
we should do?
We should put him
on the subway. Let him
ride around and...
Take them weeks
before they figure
out who he was.
How we gonna get
him to the subway?
I don't know.
Put a sheet over him
and carry him downstairs.
What if we meet
somebody on the stairs?
Or in the 10 blocks
to get to the subway?
Maybe we could fit him
in the garbage chute.
It's a three-story building.
There's no garbage chute.
Use your head.
Well, I don't see you
coming up with
any suggestions.
Maybe we could use your
old standby and throw
him out the window.
That's not a bad idea.
You might notice
I've never been
arrested for that.
WOMAN ON TV. No!
Leave me alone!
SEAN: So you like working
there? At the store?
I get to listen to
my favorite bands all day.
And it's making me the money
I need to go to music school.
I hate school,
but music school?
That sounds fun,
not like a real school.
Twentieth Century Techniques,
History of Opera,
Equal Interval Orchestration
and Advanced Instrumental
Reading Lab,
and that's just
my first quarter.
That's brutal.
I'd rather go to real school.
My dad taught me
to play guitar
when I was little.
I've been hooked
ever since.
He died about
a year ago.
Heart attack.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's a lot harder on
my mom than it is on me.
I loved my dad
more than anything,
but I hate
to see her alone.
I want her
to find someone.
I know, I lost my dad
a long time ago.
It gets easier.
Really?
So your mom's okay now?
Oh, yeah.
She married again?
No.
But she found someone.
What happened to your dad?
My mom told me
he choked on a peanut
butter sandwich.
I wanted to believe her
for a really long time.
I mean, he went
to lunch one day
and never came back.
But I knew it wasn't true.
Come on, what kind of
restaurant sells
peanut butter sandwiches?
He was murdered.
Now, people don't
wanna say what really
happened,
but I believe
my brother Jimmy.
He says that
my dad died because
he wouldn't back down
to a bunch of
greaseball Italians,
so they beat him to death.
I'm Greek.
Oh. Good.
Hey.
Can we talk for a second?
I call you, you hang up on me.
I call back, you don't even
have the courtesy to pick
up the phone,
but now you wanna talk?
Samson, I know
I hurt you, okay?
I accept
responsibility for that.
Love is not a one-way street.
Love, Samson?
We had sex.
Once. Okay?
I was drunk.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
I'm sorry I took
advantage of you.
It was wrong,
it was selfish,
and I know that.
(INAUDIBLE)
Oh, you know what?
To hell with that.
You wanna hurt me?
Try it.
But whatever I need
to do to protect myself,
I'll do it.
I promise you that.
I will hurt you right back.
I never knew
you were so tough.
I guess one of us
will have to be looking
over their shoulder, huh?
Yeah, you.
KEVIN: Why you making
me do this, huh?
Why don't you
just talk to me?
(FRANNY GROANING)
Kevin, what are
you doing?
Hey, Tommy.
Huh? What are you doing?
You okay?
Nice way to treat somebody
who tried to help you.
(GRUNTS)
Don't lie to us, all right?
You never tried to
help anybody!
Stop with the smacking!
Look, Ma's been
hiding something
from us, all right?
And it has something
to do with this guy.
How do you know that?
Because I'm a gambler.
I may not be lucky,
but I'm good, all right?
I know people's tells.
I saw Mom's when
we asked her about him.
She ran her hand
through her hair twice.
Since we were kids
she's been doing that.
She doesn't do it
when it's a lie.
She does it more
when she's avoiding a lie.
And it has something
to do with this guy.
That's why I'm beating
the crap out of him.
I know he lied to us earlier.
I just don't know
what he lied about.
Okay.
Just follow my lead.
All right?
No more lies.
Or he's really
gonna hurt you.
You can hurt me
all you want.
But what you boys
don't understand is
I'm trying to help you.
Hit him.
(GASPS)
Who owns
Reilly's building?
I know you know.
I don't.
Kevin.
(GRUNTS)
(MOANS)
Corporations, like I said!
You said it went on and on.
In a circle.
That it doesn't stop.
But it does, doesn't it?
I wanna know where.
It doesn't go on and on.
It stops with
Longdale Properties.
Who's behind Longdale?
I want names!
The people that we're
gonna threaten with
going to the papers,
that's what you
said, right? Huh?
Wait! Wait.
Wait.
Huey Farrell.
Probably Dokey now,
and Al. Al Onotaro.
And me, once upon a time.
That's Longdale Properties.
The Italians
and the Irish together?
Yeah.
Why?
The land,
real estate money...
Everybody forgives
for money.
My father,
was he a part of it?
Was he a part
of this land deal?
Of course he was.
Huey and he were
partners with everything.
But your father was
against this deal.
He hated the fact that
the Italians were buying up
land in the neighborhood.
He told Huey he wouldn't
have any part of this.
Is that why my father
was killed?
Yes.
Who did it?
I don't know.
You're a liar!
Who did it?
I wanna know
who punched him.
who kicked him.
I want names!
I didn't know.
The only thing I know is
your father asked me to meet
him at the diner that day.
I was late, he was dead
when I got there.
JOEY. Tommy wanted to stop.
He knew whatever
he was gonna find out
was gonna be something
that he couldn't bear.
An unimaginable hurt.
And yet, he didn't stop.
(SHOUTS)
You let him go down there
alone 'cause you knew
they were gonna kill him!
I didn't know,
I swear to God
I didn't know!
Who did it?
I don't know!
You do know!
Who? Come on!
Who did it?
Tommy Donnelly.
Always getting me
out in the night.
This gonna be good?
What's up?
Man-to-man, I wanna know.
Did Huey set up my dad?
Are you hallucinating?
Is Huey the reason
my father's dead?
Tommy, one time,
it's hilarious.
Don't forget I got
an axe in the car, okay?
I know everything.
What do you know?
I know that my dad
and Huey were partners.
And I know Huey was in bed
with the Italians.
I know it was
all about land.
And my father was against it.
And that's why your
son of a bitch brother
let him get killed.
My brother cried
when your father died.
We all did.
We all loved him.
Everyone thought
they knew what happened
to Bobby Donnelly that day.
It had kind of become
neighborhood legend.
Sal?
Thanks for meeting us, Bobby.
We appreciate it. Sit.
I don't need to sit, Sal.
Huey can do
whatever he wants.
This is our neighborhood
and it's our union.
As far as I'm concerned,
you're staying out.
(MEN GRUNTING)
But nobody really
knew what happened.
Thanks for taking the meet,
Bobby, we appreciate it.
You know what, guys?
This is wrong.
You do what you want,
but I'm done here.
Unfortunately for Bobby,
Huey saw it coming.
He knew that no amount
of money could make Bobby
betray the neighborhood.
(BOBBY GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
JOEY. The Irish were renowned
for taking care of their own.
So to prove his loyalty
to the Italians,
Huey had to show them
that he could kill his own.
Huey was there
that morning, okay?
So he told me
what happened.
Could he have
helped your father?
Absolutely not.
You know, I really don't
hate you enough
to tell you what
happened, okay?
But I will tell you this.
You need to think
about who gained
by sending
your father
down there.
Who sent your father
down there, Tommy?
How come you
don't ask that
question? Huh?
You wanna know?
Go ask your mother.
What?
Go home and ask your mother.
This is really
becoming a hassle.
MAN ON TV.
A guy comes home, okay?
His best friend's
in bed with his wife.
He looks, he says,
"Max, I have to.
"But you?"
I got a cousin
in med school.
Maybe he wants him.
My head hurts.
I need a breather.
Give me that.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Who's this?
Oh, hi, Frankie.
Yeah.
Uh, no.
Yeah, Dad's already upstairs.
No, everything's fine.
All right, okay,
thanks for calling.
Bye.
JOEY. Remember that
unimaginable hurt
I told you about?
The thing that Tommy
was gonna figure out
he couldn't bear?
HELEN: You've got
a wife and four kids.
You can't lose
your job at the union.
BOBBY: There are people
in this neighborhood who
depend on me, Helen.
They've gotta
feed their kids, too.
Let the neighborhood
take care of itself.
You and Huey have come
all this way together,
you've worked too hard.
Just worry about your own.
Don't do this, Bobby.
JOEY. If Tommy let himself
remember what his mother said,
he'd have to admit
to himself that it
was his mother
who sent his father
to the diner that day.
It was his mother who
forced Bobby Donnelly
to take that meeting.
How'd you do?
No more Christmas
presents from Franny.
JIMMY:
What's all this hullabaloo?
Where the hell
have you been?
With his new squeeze.
You wanna know
where I've been, Ma?
Only having probably
the best day of my life.
Really?
Things are going so well
with me and Joanie,
it's fantastic.
I think I'm in love.
Oh, God.
Hey, I got some news.
I'm thinking about going
back to school.
If you thought there
was a chance I was gonna
let you do anything else,
I don't know what world
you're living in.
I think we're saying
the same thing.
What the hell are you
so quiet about?
Nothing.
Let's eat.