Thank you.
Good afternoon.
You know, I've got some important news for you.
No one is born rich.
No one.
Everyone is born naked and penniless.
So how do you get rich?
How do you stay rich?
How do you get even richer?
That's why we're here.
That's what we want to know, right?
Me? My theory?
It all boils down to six words:
What are you willing to do?
Can you stand up for me, please?
How much do you make a year, ma'am?
I'd rather not say.
I'll give you $100 to say.
Two hundred.
Uh, I make about $37,500 a year.
$37,700 now.
Liking this, right?
Money's good.
Money is good.
Are you wearing clean underwear?
Pardon me?
It's just a question.
And I will give you $100 to tell me.
Sure.
I'm wearing clean underwear.
Take off all of your clothes,
right here, right now,
in front of everybody,
and I will double your annual income.
Bring you up to a cool $75,000.
What do you say?
No, no,
I can't do that.
No, no, no, no.
Is that your husband?
Yes.
Couldn't he use the money, too?
It doesn't matter, I...
I'm not gonna do it.
Besides, he doesn't want me to do it, either.
Me! I'll do it!
Pick me!
I didn't ask you!
It's easy for you.
I'm asking her.
You know, it's 3:15 in the afternoon.
By 3:16, you could have doubled your annual income.
You could have twice as much money as you have right now.
You could pay off your bills.
You could buy yourself something nice.
All you have to do is...
But I can't. Um...
Thank you, anyway.
Okay, I will triple your annual salary.
Bring you up to $112,500.
That's six figures.
That's really nice.
Just take off your clothes.
But I can't.
Why don't you ask one of them?
'Cause I'm asking you.
Okay, I'll triple your annual salary,
not just this year,
but for the rest of your life.
Let's say you live over 30 years.
That's over two million dollars.
You'd be rich.
You'd be a millionaire.
What do you say?
I can't.
You can't or you won't?
I won't do it.
Is that your final answer?
Yes, yes,
that's my final answer.
Remember these six words, folks:
What are you willing to do?
What about you, sir?
Excuse me?
Well, sure, I'd take off my clothes for a couple million.
No, the question is:
Will you take hers off?
If she lives 30 years,
that's over $2,250,000.
You'd be a millionaire.
You'd be rich.
What are you willing to do?
I want to go.
I want to leave!
Shut up!
What are you willing to do?
Get off of me!
A hundred dollars for anybody to help me!
What do you think about this?
Nice.
I don't want nice.
It's jury duty.
I want something that says "You can't trust this man."
What do you think?
Bowling or pineapples?
I have no idea.
Come on!
This is your area.
Help me out here,
give me a little guidance-- pick one.
I'll give you a hundred bucks.
Go naked.
The kids are up.
I heard noises.
Decided to go with clothes after all, huh?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Help me!
What is going on?
She's gonna murder me!
There you are!
No screaming.
It's 6:30 in the morning.
You're gonna wake the baby.
That's my shirt,
that's my sweater,
that's my hair band.
I put them out last night and she woke up first and she took them.
Tell her she has to take them off!
Bridgette...
Take... them... off!
But she took out 15 different things!
Three. I was choosing.
And I choose that!
Okay, no snatching.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hold on a second.
Everybody back up.
Bridgette, you're wearing your sister's clothes.
Did you ask before you put them on?
Huh?
No, she didn't.
Why are you smiling?
Did you ask?
Okay, Ariel-- do you think,
if she asks nicely,
could you possibly wear one of the other two outfits
that were contenders for today?
I don't know.
Why should I?
Please?
I guess.
Okay.
Thank you, Ariel.
Whatever.
It doesn't look good on you, anyway.
See?
Another crisis averted.
Joe Dubois--
our juries need citizens like you.
Don't even say that.
Someone might hear.
Take that back.
I will not.
I am proud that you're summoned for jury duty.
What's jury duty?
It's a gigantic waste of Daddy's time, that's what it is.
It's one of the things that makes our justice system great.
When people get in trouble,
they get to be judged by people just like them.
It's called a jury.
And it's every citizen's obligation to be on one.
And it's an honor to be asked.
Mommy's right.
It is an honor.
It's just a really inconvenient honor because Daddy has, like,
three million things that he has to do at work,
and I really can't afford the day.
You'll be lucky if it's a day.
It'll be a lot longer,
if you get picked.
Don't worry, I'm not going to get picked.
You got a lot of faith in that shirt.
It's not the shirt I'm counting on, darling; it's you.
Me? What about me?
You. You work for the DA.
Think about it.
What defense attorney is going to want the spouse of somebody who works for
the DA sitting up there judging his or her client?
You, darling,
are my "Get Out of Jail Free" card.
Mr. District Attorney...
do you have a moment?
Take your time,
counselor.
We're both going to the same place.
They can't start without us.
Well, how about we don't start at all.
I've made six plea offers.
You haven't even responded.
Make me a serious proposal,
I'll be happy to respond.
Okay. Class-B Criminal Negligence with a fine and community service.
A fine and community service?
Your client killed his wife.
No, he did not.
Come on, the facts are not in dispute here.
They were on the boat,
they were both drinking,
he went to sleep and she fell overboard in the middle of the night.
It's a horrible,
terrible accident but it is not a violation of the law.
Well actually, counselor,
the facts are in dispute here.
I'm not sure I believe your client's story.
Excuse me?!
But let's put that aside for the time being.
Let's say we accept his version of things.
He still committed a crime.
It's called criminally negligent homicide.
He left his severely intoxicated wife on the deck of a boat at sea.
There was substantial and reasonable risk she would die.
Yeah, I know the statute.
Oh, I'm sure you do.
And I know that you know that any kind of homicide requires proof that the
victim be actually dead.
Like a body.
Which you do not have.
You've had divers at the bottom of that lake for nine weeks.
You have come up with nothing.
So let's talk plea.
Let's not.
Moving along to number 19,
Mr. Joseph Dubois.
Joseph Dubois?
Yes... Sorry.
Yes. Present.
Now, before the attorneys begin,
I'd like to ask you about one thing.
I noticed on your jury questionnaire,
you noted that your wife works for the district attorney.
Is that correct?
Yes, that is correct.
Mr. Dubois, as a juror,
you have an obligation not to discuss this case or your opinions with anyone,
including your wife.
Will that be a problem?
I don't think so, no.
All right.
Mr. Devalos?
Has Mrs. Dubois done any work on this case at all?
Has she met with Stephen Garner or any of the other witnesses?
No, Your Honor, she has not.
All right.
Mr. Devalos,
you may begin.
We have no questions for Mr. Dubois.
Thank you.
Ms. Romney,
I'm certain you do have some questions for Mr. Dubois.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Just a few.
Mr. Dubois...
you say in your questionnaire that you work in the aerospace industry.
What do you do exactly?
I'm a systems design mathematician.
And do you make a good living doing that?
I do all right.
Do you work with people who do much better than you do?
Sure.
A lot of our suppliers are start-ups, so...
if you patent the right concept,
you can start your own company.
There's a lot of money in aerospace.
Interesting.
And how do you feel about those people,
the ones who managed to strike it rich in your field?
I guess I hope to be one... someday.
Here's hoping.
Do you drink, Mr. Dubois?
Mm, sometimes.
In moderation.
Did you ever drink a little too much?
Sure...
well, not for awhile.
When I was younger.
In college.
And, during one of those times,
when you were under the influence of alcohol,
did you ever make a decision you regretted?
Or do something or say something that was...
I don't know... ill-advised?
Sure. Absolutely.
I mean,
isn't that what college is for?
Thank you, Mr. Dubois.
- Okay. You're welcome.
- No more questions.
All right, approach.
Mr. Dubois is certainly an acceptable juror to the prosecution.
What a surprise.
Ms. Romney?
Mr. Dubois is equally acceptable to the defense.
Terrific.
Your Honor,
I'm concerned that either defense is setting up grounds for an appeal based
on incompetent counsel or she needs another cup of espresso.
No, Your Honor.
Actually, Mr. Dubois is just what I'm looking for.
He seems like an intelligent man, a logical man,
with no apparent prejudices or predispositions against people who have more
money than he does.
He claims to have and understanding of how alcohol can impair your judgment,
and, most of all,
he seems like a fair man.
And at the end of the day,
what more can I ask for?
Thank you.
Mr. Dubois...
Yes.
Uh, sorry, your Honor,
I was just hoping that I could get my, um,
my slip from the clerk.
Well, no, Mr. Dubois,
you're not dismissed.
You're serving on this jury.
Congratulations.
They finally asleep?
That took awhile.
I'm going to do lunches in the morning.
I'm too tired.
Okay.
You almost ready for bed?
Yeah.
I just got to finish this.
Until this trial's over,
it's like I got two jobs.
Hey, who's that?
...in the death of his wife,
Jessica Garner.
Hey, that's the guy who was in my dream last night.
...of criminally negligenthomicide in a trial that begins today...
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Where are you going?
I can't watch that news report.
That's my case.
I can't watch that.
That's the case I was picked to be a juror on.
Turning to weather....
The forecast,
mostly sunny skies today,
with brisky, chilly winds...
Is it over?
The scary part's over.
So that's your case, huh?
I don't even think I'm allowed to answer that.
Oh, come on. I don't know anything about it, honest.
Ally, you just told me you had a dream about the guy.
Yeah, it wasn't that kind of dream.
It was a crazy dream.
A nonsense dream.
Al, I don't want to talk about it, okay?
Wow. Look who got religion.
This morning you would have done anything to get out of jury duty.
Now suddenly, you're the jury duty poster boy.
Cute.
You're not too bad yourself.
Okay, guys,
jackets and backpacks.
Have a great day, guys.
Bye, Mom.
Bye, Dad.
Bye, baby.
Can we drive all together everyday?
If gas doesn't get any cheaper, we might have to.
It's kind of special today,
sweetie.
Mommy and Daddy are working at the same place.
Bridgette, come on.
Bye, pumpkin.
Bye, darlin'.
Bye.
I'm coming.
Allison...
What are you doing?
Oh, just catching up on the Stephen Garner case.
Okay... I just need you to stop reading what you're reading,
get up and walk out of this room.
Excuse me?
Your husband is on the jury,
Allison.
No, I know, I wasn't going to discuss any of this.
It's just...
I've been having dreams.
You've had dreams about this case?
Anything definite?
Anything that we should be investigating?
Well, maybe.
I don't...
I don't know how the pieces fit together.
Okay, forget it.
Allison, I just need you to please get up and walk out of this room.
But why?
Why?
Because if a judge finds out that you are working on this case in any capacity--
if he walked in right now and saw you with these files,
we'd be looking at a mistrial.
And Stephen Garner would walk.
He would have murdered his wife and walked away.
I don't understand.
He's not on trial for murder.
It was an accident,
it was negligence, wasn't it?
You know,
it's funny, most of the time I'm staring at a crime and I'm looking for motive,
means and opportunity.
Here, I've got all three and yet I'm forced to behave as if there's no crime.
I'm sorry,
I'm not following you.
In my opinion,
Stephen Garner took his rich wife out on that boat and killed her.
Maybe he got her drunk and pushed her.
Maybe he just smashed in her skull and threw her overboard.
I don't have a body so I don't know.
But whatever happened, the final result is she's dead and he did it on purpose.
- But why?
- Money.
Hers...
a $40 million trust fund.
But I can't prove that.
So I'm hoping to get a conviction on criminally negligent homicide,
and then, maybe, I can put him away for four years.
Four years on a garbage charge.
And that's all the justice I can offer this poor woman.
So, please, don't make an impossible task harder.
Just get up, walk out, and I'll give the files back to Sondra.
We didn't even get on the water till after 10:00.
Dropped anchor in Jefferson Cove.
I started to cook dinner while she got out the wine.
How much wine did your wife drink?
I'm not sure.
We finished, maybe,
three bottles.
Three bottles of wine for two people.
Would you say she was intoxicated?
Yes. Uh, we both were.
But, uh...
it's not like we had to drive anywhere.
I mean, we were in the middle of a lake on a boat.
I really didn't think anything could happen.
Mr. Garner,
you testified that at midnight you went below and left your wife alone on deck.
Yes, sir, that's correct.
That... I was tired.
Tired...
from all the alcohol you consumed?
Well, certainly that was part of it.
And what was the rest of it?
I'm sorry, you said that was part of it.
We had an argument.
I'm sorry, could you speak a little louder?
Did you say,
you and your wife had a fight?
No. It was an argument.
It was like a disagreement.
An argument.
You never mentioned an argument in your pre-trial deposition.
Your Honor, I need a moment to confer with my client.
Well, your client chose to testify in his own defense, Miss Romney.
He can confer after court.
So, you had an argument.
Was it heated?
Was it violent?
No, of course not.
It was just... it was an argument.
Jess was very insecure about the way she looked.
And sometimes when she drank she'd accuse me of marrying her for her money.
Really?
Any truth to that, Mr. Garner?
Did you marry her for money?
Objection. Irrelevant.
I married her because I had no choice.
I married her because the moment I met her I could think of nothing else.
I married her because the thought of spending a single day without her by my side...
And I'll bet the money didn't hurt.
Objection, Your Honor.
Sustained.
Yeah, "but I bet the money didn't hurt." I don't like that guy.
Who, the D.A.?
- Yeah.
- Well, he's got to try and make a case.
What are you talking about?
There is no case.
A guy goes to sleep, wakes up and his wife's gone.
That's a crime?
Hell, half the world is guilty,
then, including my ex.
This is a tragedy,
maybe a mystery,
but it isn't any crime.
Daddy!
Hi.
Hi. Whoa.
Daddy!
I'll see you tomorrow, Joe.
I got to go buy a seat cushion.
Okay.
Mommy said that if we all came,
then we could all go out to dinner and I could choose where.
Yeah? Well, if that's what Mommy said, that's what Mommy said.
Really?
Oh, God I love this.
We drive in together,
I'm done by 5:00, we eat together.
Forget everything I said this morning.
I may apply to become a career juror.
Well, don't fill out that application just yet.
You might want to give it a week or two.
I don't know.
If today's any indication,
I don't know if this thing's going to go a week or two.
Frankly, I don't think your boss has very much to work with.
Okay, what's it going to be,
sweetie?
I want chicken fingers.
Pick a chicken place!
My turn to choose and I choose Italian.
Italian? Okay. Where's Mom?
Where's Mommy going?
Hi.
They hate your boss.
They think he has no case.
Who, the jury?
I thought we weren't supposed to discuss...
No, I'm not talking about the facts of the case.
I'm just talking about your boss.
Tell him to lighten up.
Or don't. I...
It's just so weird not being able to talk to you about something that
consumes so much of my day.
Well, yeah, likewise.
Remember, if we see her,
you're on your own--
I can't be a part of this.
Understood.
Tell me again,
what'd you see exactly?
They were in bed,
they were making love.
What do you want, details?
Sure, if you're offering.
His wife's been gone seven months.
I wouldn't be crazy to think he's got a girlfriend.
Well,
that's true,
but yesterday they went out of their way to act like they didn't know each other.
I'll meet you here ten minutes before the, uh, lunch recess.
Thank you.
Sure.
Mr. Hammond, when...
your daughter Jessica was born,
you arranged for a trust fund to protect her inheritance.
Can you tell me how much that fund is worth today?
I would say approximately $42 million.
$42 million.
And upon her death,
who would inherit that money?
Her husband.
With all due respect,
Mr. Hammond, doesn't that...
give you pause?
Objection, Your Honor.
The district attorney is asking for an opinion
that has no relevance to the case before this court.
Overruled.
I'll allow it.
H-Have you ever met my son-in-law, sir?
He came into my office 12 years ago.
He had on a sport coat that looked like it probably cost.
.. $60 and a tie that cost about ten,
and he said, "I'd like to work for you, sir.
"I'd like to learn from you, sir,
I'd like to learn how to make money." And, uh,
I asked him the question I ask everyone who says they want to work for me.
I asked,
"What are you willing to do?
" And he said, "I'm willing to do anything, sir." And he was telling the truth.
For the next year and a half,
he unstopped toilets,
he delivered mail,
he ran errands,
he brought everyone lunch.
He was the first one there in the morning and the last one to leave at night.
He knew nothing about finance.
But after 18 months,
he was teaching me things.
That's who my son-in-law is.
And...
how did he come to meet your daughter?
Well, I introduced them.
Uh...
put them together anyway.
And how did that come about?
From time to time in my business,
there are work-related functions.
Uh, charity events,
award dinners.
I was always encouraging Stephen to go,
but he would always decline.
Finally, he confessed to me that he was intimidated,
afraid of making a fool of himself.
Picking up the wrong fork,
drinking from the wrong glass,
that sort of thing.
While a man who looks like him certainly had no shortage of women in his life,
he did let me know that none of them
were of a caliber he felt comfortable
bringing to a work-related function.
So I suggested that perhaps he should ask Jessica to accompany him.
And...
obviously, that worked out.
My Jessica...
...was asleep for the first 24 years of her life,
and then she met... this man,
and... and she...
I was...
I was hoping that she would...
have children.
I know they both want...
desperately wanted children.
I'm sorry.
I've completely forgotten the question.
The $42 million.
Doesn't it make you wonder?
About what?
That's her.
You better go now.
I knew him in college;
I haven't talked to him since then.
You went to school with him?
No. He lived in town.
He worked at his stepfather's bar.
Anyway, he was great looking back then, too,
and I knew my parents wouldn't approve, so...
I had to have him.
You dated him?
You could call it dating.
It was more like sex and fighting.
So wait, I'm confused.
If you haven't talked to him in years,
why are you coming to court every day?
Saw it in the papers.
See something like that,
and you know the people it happened to,
it freaks you out a little.
And I guess I felt...
a little responsible.
What do you mean?
I sort of introduced them.
Wait a second, I thought I read in the paper,
uh, that the dad introduced them,
that they met through work or something.
I read that, too.
The truth is,
we were all at the country club one night, and...
This was, like, 13 years ago,
way before he ever started working for her father.
Oh, God, Jess didn't even notice Stephen.
I mean, why would she?
He was the bartender.
But she definitely made an impression on him.
What do you mean?
Well, he heard she had serious money.
So after the party, he wanted to know everything about her.
What did she like to do,
what kind of guys did she like.
I mean, he wanted to know everything there was to know about Jessie Hammond.
And this was 13 years ago.
Mm-hmm. I told him he didn't have a chance  with her--
she was a real daddy's girl.
You know, only child,
no mom, shy.
I guess he figured the key to Jess was her dad,
'cause the next thing I knew...
he was working for him.
Well, I still don't get it-- you knew the guy,
you had a thing with the guy,
but that was some time ago,
and yet here you are coming to court every day.
I told you, I guess I feel a little responsible.
Why?
I don't know, um,
Stephen was asking me about Jessica for,
like, the hundredth time.
You know, like, did I think she really had that much money,
that sort of thing,
like he's on a mission.
And I told him to forget about it,
that it was never gonna happen--
I mean...
that boy likes the bedroom.
I knew he was nailing me and, like, six other girls.
The thought of him getting married,
the thought of him being exclusive,
I just... I didn't think he had it in him.
And I told him so.
And I told him that if he married Jess...
she'd care.
And her dad would care more.
Anyway, I remember Stephen looked at me,
and he said...
hey, a person would just have to marry her,
he wouldn't necessarily have to stay married to her.
Ask me what I know.
Doesn't matter.
You're right,
it was a plan.
He's been working it since the early '90s.
The guy is a classic sociopath.
Allison, it doesn't matter.
Court the father, then court her.
Marry her,
then kill her and take her money.
A girl he once knew,
an old lover,
she saw the whole thing happen.
I believe you, Allison, but,
honestly, it does not matter.
It does!
The jury is with him.
They're not with you.
This is what he's great at--
winning people over.
You have to give them some evidence.
This woman, I know,
Scanlon seems to think most of what she has to offer is hearsay,
but I think you take it to the judge, you tell him what this woman...
Allison.
We finished our closing arguments over an hour ago.
The case is with the jury; it's over.
Go home.
And let's both try to get a good night's sleep.
Absolutely, there's not a doubt in my mind.
Even if I'm off by an hour,
I will definitely be in the office by 3:00.
No, tomorrow, I'll be done.
Okay, tomorrow.
They can't exist without me for three days.
I guess that's the good news.
How can you be so sure he'll be back at the office by 3:00?
Aren't deliberations starting tomorrow?
Darling, there's nothing to deliberate.
The only suspense is how long it's gonna take to count the hands.
Is that what you've been upset about since you got home?
Al, talk to me.
I can't.
No! Please, God!
No! I love you!
No! Please, don't!
Please! Oh, my God!
I love you! Please!
Hey... you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, I'm okay,
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
Oh, I don't know,
I don't know.
Don't ask me;
I can't tell you.
I can't talk about it.
What do you mean?
What is there not to talk about?
Oh.
It's okay.
Really, I'm okay.
Just go back to sleep.
Hey, whatcha doing?
Waiting for you to wake up.
Come on, go back to sleep.
I need you to tell me.
Tell you what?
You're dreaming.
Every night.
If this case were as simple as the one that's being presented in that courtroom,
there'd be nothing for you to dream about.
So?
So I want to know what you're seeing.
I want to know what you know.
I can't tell you what I know.
I wish I could.
I wish it would make a difference, but...
it just doesn't.
I know you all have lives and other things to do,
so as your newly elected foreman,
I'd like to get the ball rolling.
I'd also like to, uh,
take a test vote just to see where we stand.
Remember, there's only one charge here:
guilty or not guilty due to criminally negligent homicide.
So can I see some hands?
Not guilty.
Uh, Mr. Dubois,
I said "not guilty."
That means, you know,
he didn't do it.
Yes, I understood the question.
Easy, everyone.
The man is entitled to his opinion.
Yeah, well, I think the man wasn't in the same courtroom as everyone else.
Are you telling me that you really think that this guy did something wrong?
No, I just... I...
I think we have a job to do,
and we have to do it carefully,
that's all.
Then I'd like to see your hand.
We're here to vote.
That is your job.
No, it isn't, Mack.
I'm here to examine the evidence,
deliberate, make a decision.
My job's to do all those things.
Examine the evidence?
What evidence?
Can you show me a scrap of evidence that tells me that this guy did anything--
anything--
to hurt his wife?
No, I can't. Not now.
Maybe never.
But his wife is dead, and he is staring at a potful of money.
And I just know that I'd feel a lot more comfortable telling this guy he's
free to walk if I knew that I'd spent a little bit of time just going over
everything that I'd heard just in case there's something,
something that we might've missed.
You know, I wouldn't mind a quick review of everything just to be sure.
A quick review of everything, huh?
Okay, so, Stephen Garner said that he and his wife Jessica left their home...
9:00 p.m. to drive up to Lake Prescott.
No word yet.
Excuse me?
The jury-- they're still deliberating.
Who knows?
Maybe we do have a chance.
I'm sorry.
Was there something else?
This box.
Yeah, it's the case file:
Phoenix, Arizona vs. Stephen Garner.
Care to take a look?
Can't do any harm now.
Yeah, I-I wouldn't mind.
Go ahead.
Have a party.
I need to speak with you.
Speak.
I think I know where she is--
her body, I mean.
He killed her in the woods--
a place called the Mazatzal Mountains.
The reason you couldn't find her in the lake is she never got on that boat.
Say something.
The jury's back.
In the matter of the State vs.
Stephen Garneron the charge of criminally negligent homicide, how do you find?
We find the defendant...
not guilty.
So say you all, Mr. Foreman?
So say we all.
And if you do this a hundred times every night,
your hair will never tangle and it will always shine.
A whole hundred?
A whole hundred.
Will it shine like yours?
Uh-huh.
Cool...
Come on, girls.
It's already ten minutes past your bedtime.
Hello?
Want to hear something funny?
I've been doing some checking.
The Hammond family has a hunting lodge in the mountains.
It's been in the family for 50 years.
Guess what town it's in?
Mazatzal.
I'm going to take a drive out there tomorrow,
take a look around.
Don't know what I'll do if I find anything.
It's never easy to charge a man a second time around for something he's
already been acquitted of,
but I guess I'll cross that bridge when I come to it...
if I come to it.
What do you think he's thinking right now?
He's gloating.
He's thinking about everything he did,
everything he was willing to do.
He's thinking about...
how smart he is...
how dumb we are.
And he's hoping with all his might...
that there really is no hell.
No! No! God, no!
Please, don't! No!
God, please, no!
No! Don't!
No!
Did you get your warrant?
It's all public conservation land.
The Hammonds donated it.
What's that?
Deer carcasses.
They're buried all up and down these woods.
Makes it hard going.
The dogs are getting confused.
You think he wants his land back?
What in the hell is going on here?
Mr. Hammond...
What are you doing?
My son-in-law was acquitted yesterday.
Sir, we're only attempting to follow up on every lead...
Why do you feel the need to continue this obsession,
this harassment?
My daughter fell out of a boat, not...
- Please, Mr. Hammond...
- Detective!
Excuse me.
We got something.
What is it?
Oh, crap.
That's Jessie's ring.
Mr. Hammond, we should go inside and let the officers work...
Oh, this bag's full of body parts.
Mr. Hammond...
One, two, three, four,
I declare a thumb war.
I win! I'm the champion of the world!
Ha, ha, you lose.
I'm the co-champion of the world!
All right,
world champions!
Daddy, are we all driving all together tomorrow?
No, not tomorrow, sweetie.
Jury duty's over.
So did you send somebody to jail,
or did they not do it?
I'll get that.
Uh, well, he did do it...
but no, he's not going to jail.
Not yet.
But that doesn't make sense.
It's complicated, sweetie.
It's too complicated for 9:00.
Now, everybody sleep.
Night, Daddy.
What? What's going on?
I guess a couple hours ago,
the father, Mr. Hammond,
went into Devalos' office and... turned himself in.
What? What are you talking about?
Turned himself in for what?
Apparently, he drove his son-in-law Stephen up to the woods.
He gave him a three-minute head start,
then hunted him down...
and shot him.
He shot him 23 times.
But I'm the champion!
I beat Daddy!
We're co-champions,
stupid.
That means we're both champions.
I'll get it.
No, no...
Nuh-uh.
Hey, girls!
Come on, it's time for bed.
I beat Daddy...
Transcript : Raceman - Synchro : Alucardo
www.forom.com