Richard Cypher,
you are the true seeker.
Legend of the Seeker 2x04
Torched
Original Air Date on November 28, 2009
Sync, corrections
elderman
People have tried for years
to find the Forest of the Night Wisp's.
Had you come here on your own,
they'd have never shown themselves.
They only come out
for those they trust.
I come to ask you for your help.
A dreamcaster sent me a message
that said I'd be the last Confessor.
I need to know
if there are any Confessors still alive.
Will you help me find them?
May the spirits protect you.
You're beautiful.
Are you trying to tell me something?
Who were you talking to?
Myself.
Who else do I have to talk to?
It is late, get some sleep.
Father, I'm almost a grown woman.
I can't stay here forever.
I want to travel to distant lands,
and fall in love, and get married.
That will never happen, Annabelle.
You're safe here.
That is all that matters.
What is it?
The Night Wisp searched everywhere
in the Midlands and beyond
looking for another Confessor.
But they only found one.
Only one.
Then who is this other Confessor.
It's strange.
The Night Wisp
didn't know who she was.
At least she's still alive.
But for how long?
She's in a tower.
in Lonville Castle, in Ausridge.
Sounds like she's a prisoner.
We can be there and back
in three days.
Ausridge?
I've traveled across the Midlands
with you people for weeks now
because you said you had to get me
and this thing on my hand
to Bemoord to find your
precious Stone of Tears.
But instead, we're going to Ausridge?
Perhaps before we see
about this Confessor
we should get the Stone and
rid ourselves of extraneous cargo.
I'll go and meet with you in Pamorah.
You're not going alone.
Zedd
You and Cara can go to Pamorah
Owen, you can come with us.
What!
Why?
I've been thinking...
we know this Roan has a key
but we don't know what it opens
or who or what might try to stop
us from getting it.
You and Cara should find out
before we put the rune or Flynn
in harm's way.
We'll meet back here in three days.
Thank you, Tharla.
Father.
- Help him.
- It's just a sleeping potion.
I had to set you free,
Annabelle.
But...
He'll keep you locked
up forever.
We must hurry.
Before his men catch us.
You're too late.
The servant Tharla
poisoned his Lordship.
He's dead. She took Annabelle.
Took her where?
I don't know.
They rode away,
taking the fastest horses.
Annabelle?
She's a Confessor?
How did you know?
Was she a prisoner here?
She was Lord Callum's daughter.
Years ago, Lord Callum
was a powerful
D'Haran commander.
He attacked
a neighboring village.
But the villagers
had the Confessor Josephine
on their side.
She confessed
Lord Callum in battle.
He was betrothed
to a beautiful duchess,
a woman he'd loved
since childhood.
But once Callum was confessed,
he thought of no one
but Josephine.
She took him as her mate.
Soon she was with child.
But the birth was not an easy one.
And when she died,
he was released.
He suddenly realized
everything he had lost
when he became confessed.
Feed her to the crows.
I feared he might
kill the child too,
he was in such rage.
But Lord Callum could not
bring himself to slay
his own flesh and blood.
He swore that no one would ever
suffer at his daughter's hands
as he did at her mother's.
He hid her away
for her whole life
in the tallest tower
of the castle.
He never told her
of her powers.
Her curse, as he called it.
We have to find her.
They can't have gotten far.
Where are we going?
Someplace safe.
Why are we here?
I see you've brought the girl.
A hundred gold pieces
was our agreement.
What agreement?
What are you doing?
I need proof that she is
what you say she is.
She doesn't know what she is.
She's never used her powers.
What powers?
A demonstration
won't be necessary.
I don't have any powers.
What are you doing to me?
All right, that's enough.
No more until you pay.
Or he kills the girl.
No, no.
I have enough
to see if it's genuine.
Master, how can I serve you?
Kill...her.
No.
You're going
to be very useful to me.
Let her go!
The Seeker.
And the Mother Confessor.
Kill him and take her.
Hide her.
Run!
- Run, Annabelle!
- Get her!
Are you all right?
Where did you come from?
Oh, I just wait around in trees
hoping to rescue pretty girls.
Think you can stand?
Richard!
Are you a prince?
Is it that obvious?
Are you all right?
Let them go.
We have to get Annabelle.
Annabelle, no!
Flynn.
Command me, Confessor.
- What's wrong with him?
- He's been confessed.
Not your fault. You don't have
control over your powers yet.
What powers?
You're a Confessor.
Just like I am.
Confessor?
When you touch someone
with your powers,
they become enslaved to you.
They lose their free will.
I did that?
I enslaved him?
I'm glad you did.
I want to serve you.
How do I take it away?
You can't.
He'll be confessed to you
for the rest of your life.
I didn't know.
Your father didn't tell you
because he was afraid
of your powers.
That's why he kept you
locked in a tower.
You talked to my father?
I'm so sorry, Annabelle.
Your father is dead.
Dead?
He was poisoned.
Tharla killed him.
So she could sell me
to that sorcerer.
He wanted to take your magic.
But don't worry.
He won't come near you again.
We're gonna take you to a place
where you can be trained.
- Trained?
- So they can teach you
how to control your magic,
so nothing like this
will ever happen again.
Stop. You're scaring her.
She just found
out her father died.
She needs to know
everything's all right.
I won't let anything
bad happen to you. Ever.
Annabelle, you have a
very rare and special gift.
If I can teach you about it,
if you'll come with us...
It's all right.
They're good people.
I'll go wherever he goes.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Pardon me, madam.
You and your Agiels
don't exactly inspire
a warm welcome.
I've learned it's more useful
to be feared than liked.
Excuse me, sir.
- What do you want?
- Could you tell us
where we could find
the Cloister of Pamorah?
In the Sentinel Hills,
east of the city.
But I wouldn't go now.
You don't wanna be
on the road after nightfall.
W-Wait, sir, w-why?
Thank you for seeing me,
Miss Prioress.
Have you seen
this symbol before?
The parchment will
do you no good.
The tomb must
be opened by the one
who bears the rune
on his hand.
What tomb?
In times past,
the tomb was the site
of many a pilgrimage.
Legend has it the Stone of Tears
was buried there.
Darken Rahl sent his men
to Pamorah to open the tomb.
They tried everything,
but no one
could get inside it.
Without the rune.
Rahl believed
the bearer of the rune
would arrive one day,
so he stationed an elite guard
around the tomb.
After Rahl fell, the villagers
rose up, and killed them.
Every last D'Haran.
But they came back
from the dead.
Banelings.
That's what everyone around
here is so afraid of.
They accepted the Keeper's
twisted bargain.
Killing to stay alive.
They're still waiting
for the bearer
of the rune to arrive.
To make sure no one
gets the stone.
Where is this tomb?
In a cemetery, to the south.
But going anywhere
near it means certain death.
I wonder where
Flynn's family is?
I never asked him.
It's not your fault
this happened.
We took him with us
because we needed him.
Now he'll spend the rest
of his life desperately longing
for someone he'll
never see again.
Well, maybe after Pamorah...
No.
Flynn will be a distraction.
My whole life
I wanted to see the world.
And now that I'm out here,
I don't understand any of it.
I'll teach you.
Kahlan says I have
to go to a place
called Aydindril to be trained.
- I'll come with you.
- She says you can't.
That you have something
more important to do
in Pamorah with Richard.
I don't want to go
anywhere without you.
Then you'll get your wish.
How?
It's late.
We all need some sleep.
My mistress is cold.
I'm gonna get some more wood
for the fire.
Maybe Flynn and I can get married.
I'm sorry, Annabelle.
That isn't going to happen.
But he loves me.
And I love him.
And in the books I've read...
It isn't the same with Confessors.
We serve a higher purpose.
But our gift makes the kind
of romance you've read about...
...impossible.
So you can't get married?
A Confessor takes a mate,
but not for love.
To continue our line.
And there aren't
very many of us left.
I think you and I may be
the only ones.
So one day, when you're ready,
you'll take a suitable mate.
What makes a mate suitable?
Well, uh, he should be
strong, noble and brave.
A leader.
So Richard's your mate, then?
No.
I love Richard,
but if he and I
were to be together
in that way,
he would become confessed.
But he already loves you.
Richard has an important mission
only he can carry out.
If he were confessed,
his love for me would be
all-consuming.
It would distract him so much
he would go mad.
And he couldn't
complete his quest.
So you can never
be with someone you love?
Once you start your training
and see how
important our work is,
you'll understand
that it makes up
for the things we can't have.
The sorcerer's men!
They're coming!
Keep her safe!
Come on.
What are you doing?
Granting your wish.
There's no one here.
Flynn.
They're gone.
And so are the horses.
You're bleeding.
I had to make it look real.
I fooled them
so that we could get away.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Does it hurt?
For you, nothing hurts.
When I was in the tower,
the servants used to secretly
bring me books to read.
Have you ever heard the story
of Rosalind and Palomar?
Yeah, everybody knows that story.
She saved him from the dragon.
And then they sail away
on the ocean together.
You remind me of Palomar.
At least the way I imagined him.
I'd save you from a dragon.
Would you take me
to see the ocean?
I'd take you anywhere.
What?
This rune is the key
to finding the Stone of Tears.
Unless Richard has it,
the Keeper will destroy all life.
Including yours.
Maybe we should go back.
How do you know
what they told you is true?
My father told me there
was nothing but war
and wickedness in this world.
That was a lie.
You're proof of that.
And even if what
they're saying is true,
I'd rather die with you
than be locked
in another tower without you.
I should've separated
them right away.
He was comforting a scared girl.
It would have been cruel.
She would have been safe.
We'll find them.
Look.
The tracks split.
One horse went north.
The other east.
He was trying to make it harder
for us to follow him.
- Clever.
- Not clever enough.
These tracks are deeper.
The horse that went that way
wasn't carrying any weight.
Hungry?
Wait here.
You know what we do
with thieves around here?
Show them mercy?
Flynn!
Well. Two thieves.
Maybe you've got something
to bargain with.
Stay away from her.
Command me, Confessor.
Hey!
Stop them.
The only way to kill banelings
is to burn them.
We'll need oil and torches.
Why not just use Wizard's Fire?
I don't think
that would be wise.
It's because I'm a Mord-Sith,
isn't it?
You think if you
use your magic,
I'll turn it against you.
I've had chances before.
With the Seeker
and Confessor nearby.
And now you know
where the tomb is.
Do you honestly think that's why
I've followed Richard
all this way?
In the hopes
that he'd send me here
with you alone
so that I could find a way
to steal the stone for myself?
Probably not.
But what's at stake
is far too important
to rely on probability.
I don't believe you have
the luxury of caution.
Get them!
I think that's all of them.
For now.
But this is a place of death.
Others may crawl out
of the earth to replace them.
We should get
Flynn back here
with the rune
as quickly as we can.
We?
Are you sure
you can trust me?
No. But I don't have
the luxury of caution.
Flynn. Annabelle.
I know this is hard for you,
but we have to get moving.
We've lost enough time as it is.
If you don't leave,
my friends
will make you leave.
Richard, they're all confessed.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I know Richard and Kahlan.
Sooner or later, they'll catch us.
Kahlan!
No!
Richard!
Richard?
Richard.
Mistress...
...how can I serve you?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. Let's go.
I'll come with you, Mistress.
Everything he does
is to save lives.
He saved yours.
And you've destroyed him.
I'm sorry, Kahlan.
But you didn't leave me a choice.
And you leave me no choice.
- I won't let you kill her.
- Kill me?
It's the only way to release me
from Confession.
But don't worry Mistress.
I'll protect you.
Richard, I don't want
to fight you.
Then put down your weapon.
I'll get the horse.
What are you doing?
Don't hurt him.
Let him go.
You will order
both of these men
to come with me
to Pamorah right now,
or I will kill him.
You wouldn't hurt him. You need
the rune on his hand.
I need him in Pamorah.
If he doesn't go,
he's of no use to me.
If we go with you
and Flynn gets you your stone,
will you let us be together?
You have my word.
It's a trap.
She'll try to kill you
the first chance she gets.
Richard, I know you're confessed
to her, but you know me.
I'm not a liar.
No, she isn't.
Put your sword down.
We're going with her.
She said she'd order Flynn
to go to Pamorah with us
if I let them live.
And you agreed to that?
I had to.
Either Richard
was going to kill me,
or I was gonna kill him.
I needed Zedd.
No!
Flynn!
You promised!
You lied to me!
I had to!
If the Keeper wins,
everyone will die!
I need the Seeker to fight him
and seal the rift
in the Underworld.
I need you to be you, Richard!
- Annabelle!
- No! Don't kill her. I love her!
I love her as much
as I ever loved you.
I know you, Kahlan.
You don't want to murder
the last Confessor.
I never asked to be a Confessor.
I never asked
to be locked in a tower.
I just want to be
like everyone else.
If there was any other way...
Maybe there is.
The sorcerer's quillion.
If we can get it we can use it
to drain Annabelle's powers.
Would Richard and Flynn
be released?
I doubt it's ever been tried.
But in theory,
they shouldn't be bound by magic
she herself no longer possesses.
Kahlan, if you love me you'll
give it a try.
He's only saying that
because he's been confessed.
Confessed or not,
Richard would do anything
to save a life.
We have to get the stone first.
And then we'll go
to the sorcerer's cave
and get his quillion.
I don't believe what I'm hearing.
You want us to risk everything...
Our lives, Richard's life.
...to save her?
If you don't have the stomach
to kill her, I will.
I seem to remember Richard
going to great lengths
to save your life.
And if it doesn't release him?
Then I'll do what needs
to be done.
It's another locket.
Maybe there'
another rune inside it.
Or maybe it holds
the Stone of Tears.
The Seeker should be
the one to open it.
When he's released
from confession.
Not when he's
this unpredictable.
You got what you came for.
We need to go after
the quillion.
He can still fight.
He'd do anything
to save her life.
We both know Richard
can't be relied upon right now.
Then Cara and I will
just have to take care
of the sorcerer ourselves.
Are you sure?
Any sorcerer as powerful as Lorcus
is going to be able
to see right through us
if we aren't convincing.
If you insist.
This will hurt.
Just do it.
I have something the sorcerer
would be very interested in.
Surrender your weapon.
Go ahead. Take it.
I know the power of the Agiel.
Lay it down yourself.
And the other one.
Now summon your sorcerer,
or I take
my merchandise elsewhere.
And what would
a Mord-Sith expect in return
for her "merchandise?"
A thousand gold pieces.
Why would I pay such a price?
Rumor has it you're in
the market for Confessor power.
This is the Mother Confessor.
I sincerely doubt you'd
be made a better offer.
She's no use to me dead.
She's not dead.
Just compliant.
How do I know that?
Examine her yourself.
Command me, Confessor.
Call off your guards.
Stop!
Don't harm them.
Give me the quillion.
You spared my life
even when your friends
told you not to.
You can thank me if this works.
If it does,
you'll be the last Confessor.
You'll have to take a mate.
Yes.
Someday I will.
Richard would make a good father
for a Confessor, wouldn't he?
Annabelle...
If he's confessed to me,
you can't hurt him.
And he could give you a child.
And then when you take my magic
he'll be released, won't he?
Yes, but,
that isn't the way that...
Kahlan.
Maybe you should consider
what she is suggesting.
If something were
to happen to you,
then the race of Confessors
would be no longer.
I want to do something for you
while I'm still a Confessor.
Please.
But I don't love her.
I love you.
This will make me very happy.
Go to her.
And love her
as you would love me.
Kahlan.
It's all right.
Richard. Richard.
What are you thinking about?
Pleasing you.
Because your mistress
ordered you to?
Yes.
You really love her, don't you?
With all my heart.
Did I do something wrong?
No.
You didn't do anything wrong.
But my mistress
commanded me to...
I know.
I guess I wouldn't want to give
myself to Flynn like that
if he was thinking
about somebody else.
It isn't just that.
Richard would never use magic
to force someone
to act against their will.
But it's not really
against his will.
If he wasn't confessed,
he would want to.
But he is confessed.
And I'm not prepared
to make that decision for him.
Or to make him a father
without his blessing.
But for Confessors...
Isn't it always like that?
That's why we don't take men
we love as mates.
It's kind of like being locked
in a tower, isn't it?
We should get started.
If this works,
I can get married one day.
I hope you will.
But Flynn won't love me anymore.
He's just the first one you met.
There will be other men.
But what if he's the only one
that I'll ever love?
Annabelle, are you all right?
It didn't work.
I'm not confessed anymore.
I was just making sure
she was all right.
Richard?
We'll see you safely hom
Your father's castle
is rightfully yours now.
Thank you, but, uh,
I think I've spent enough
of my life there.
I want to see the world.
Where we're going won't be safe.
I'll go myself.
I've always wanted
to see the ocean.
I don't think it's safe for you
to travel alone.
I'll take her.
I mean, um, I'm headed
toward Wynnmore anyway.
I... I have
a cousin there.
It's near the ocean.
What?
You don't need me anymore.
So you can come along,
if you want to.
Well, I can't say
it's been fun,
but it's been interesting.
It's only me now.
No.
You got us.
Kahlan,
I can understand why you
couldn't go through with it.
But part of me wishes you had.
Me too.
And now that
we have our Seeker back...
It's time to open this.
Is it the Stone of Tears?
No. I think it's a compass.
"This orb will guide
the Seeker's way."
To what?
Hopefully the Stone of Tears.
Let's not waste time, then.
We head north.
Sync, corrections
elderman