The prophecy says
that the seeker
Will defeat darken rahl.
Thanks to the seeker,
that monster is dead
And rotting for all eternity
in the underworld.
Kneel before the keeper.
Forgive me, master.
I have failed you.
No, you have succeeded
Exactly as I intended.
It's a tear in the veil
That separates the underworld
from the living.
This happened
when I killed rahl.
As long as it's open
there's no way
To prevent the keeper
of the underworld
From sending his minions
to bring death
To every living thing.
The only way to close the rift
Is the way the creator
sealed the underworld.
The stone of tears.
We'll find it.
Seek out the abbot of ulrich,
For he keeps the secret of
the stone close to his heart.
She's the one who helped me
kill darken rahl.
She did it to save
her own skin.
If you're foolish enough
to turn down
The throne of d'hara,
then you need me all the more.
If this is some sort of trick,
I will kill you.
Mark of the keeper.
The one who would
destroy all life.
Richard cypher,
you are the true seeker.
- Watch subtitled tv shows online
for free @ www.onlinesubtitles.org -
Season 02 Episode 2
"Baneling"
Thanks for letting me
borrow this.
Although I can't say it helped
me sleep more soundly.
It's gonna take a while
to get used
To having
a mord-sith in camp.
Well, if richard trusts cara,
I suppose we'll have
to learn to as well.
Does it hurt?
It's nothing.
The spirit of the tyrant
you killed
Comes back from the grave
And burns the mark of the keeper
in your chest?
It's not nothing, richard.
I wish I knew
what it meant.
What we do know is that we need
to seal the rift
Between this world
and the underworld.
And to do that, we need to find
the stone of tears,
And to find the stone, we need
to get to the abbot of ulrich.
It must have burned at least
three months ago.
These weeds
are at least that old.
D'harans did this.
Then where are the corpses?
If the abbot isn't here,
Then we've come a long way
for nothing.
If d'harans did this,
And they didn't
kill the monks,
Where would they
have taken them?
From here, they would have been
taken to tothrayne.
What's tothrayne?
A death camp.
No, please, no!
I have a son!
The war is over!
I don't want to die!
Move! The faster
you get this loaded,
The faster
you'll get your reward.
General, why are we still
Executing prisoners?
The war is over.
We should be getting
far away from this place.
You've heard the reports
of reprisals against d'harans.
The best way to ensure
there are no reprisals
For what's been done here
Is to make certain that no one
lives to tell the tale.
Don't worry, commander.
We'll take this treasure
and we'll be faaway from here
By the time anyone comes
looking for retribution.
Just as soon as we've finished
the task at hand.
Stay there!
And now
here's your reward.
All right,
I'll do you a favor.
I'll leave it loose.
You'll take longer to die.
The seeker. Kill him!
Thanks for the favor.
Bless you, seeker.
We're looking
for the abbot of ulrich.
We believe
he was brought here.
I'm sorry, I don't know
anything about the abbot.
There are children here
we have to free.
The d'harans didn't just come
for resistance fighters.
They took our families too.
Where are they?
Come. I'll show you.
it's all right.
You're safe.
I need to find my son.
What's his name?
William. I'm eleanor.
Don't worry.
I'll help you find him.
Mother!
William! William!
Oh!
I thought I'd lost you.
Oh, thank the spirits
you're safe!
The abbot of ulrich.
He was brought here.
Where is he?
The general had him
executed yesterday.
I tried to stop
the executions.
You didn't try hard enough.
We all lived in fear
of the general.
There's a reason
that we called him the butcher.
If we hadn't
followed his orders
It would've been our necks
in nooses.
It may still be.
But that's for
the mother confessor to decide.
Lock them in the cells.
We came here
for the abbot.
He's dead.
There's no reason
for us to stay.
Look at these people.
They're sick, they're scared.
They have no place to go.
We can't just
leave them here.
There's already enough sickness
in this place.
Let's bury these bodies
before it gets any worse.
Lord rahl?
You served me well in life,
general.
It is my hope that you will
do the same for the keeper,
Now that you are dead.
I don't understand.
It's quite simple.
The keeper of the underworld
Wants to make you an offer.
Those of you
that are well enough
To travel are free to leave,
but those of you that aren't,
We'll be making a camp
just outside the prison.
If these prisoners are going
to gain their strength back,
We're gonna have to feed them
something more substantial
Than d'haran gruel.
Should we draw them warm baths?
Do you know of anyone heading
in the direction of deerfork?
The dragon corps wiped out
deerfork months ago.
But that's
my father's village.
We'll try to find out where
the survivors have relocated.
Deerfork was a resistance
stronghold.
No one would've been
left alive.
My father wasn't
a resistance fighter.
He was just a locksmith.
That would've made no difference
to the dragon corps.
Where will we go?
The rest of my family
died here.
I am so sorry
for your loss.
But you need to be strong
for your son.
We'll see what we can find out
about your father.
You shouldn't give her
false hope.
It wasn't so long ago
That you served the one
who caused all this misery.
At least try to show
some compassion.
Come with me.
I checked the store rooms.
There's barely enough
to feed the rats.
How can there be this many
people with no food?
When the war ended,
supply shipments stopped.
What food there was
went to the guards.
The d'harans would sooner
put a knife in our bellies
Than a hot meal.
I'm sending cara out
To get provisions.
Hopefully there'll be enough
for everyone.
Move.
Everyone?
We'd have more if we didn't have
so many mouths to feed.
The d'harans will be brought
to justice,
But we're not gonna
starve them to get it.
Yes, mother confessor.
I need a horse.
We need the horses
to get provisions.
You can bury him outside
with the others.
I'm not burying my brother
Alongside the d'harans
who killed him.
He should be laid to rest
beside our mother and father.
We're going to need fresh water.
My village is half a day's ride.
I'll have the horse back
to you by morning.
Check on the sister.
Do it quickly.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Seeker?
I heard you were looking
for abbot henry.
I was a member of his order.
We need to confide in you
a great secret.
There's been a tear
in the veil
Between this world
and the underworld.
The keeper is waging war
on the land of the living.
He's using the rift to send
horrible creatures
Into our world.
And the only way
to close this rift
Is for us to find
the stone of tears.
We were told that abbot henry
had knowledge
Of the secret location
of the stone.
The abbots of our order
always wore a locket.
It has a rose inscribed
on its face
And it was passed down
from abbot to abbot.
Shota said the abbot would keep
the secret close to his heart.
The d'harans took the locket
When they brought us
to this awful place.
We lived in peace until
the d'harans came.
Seize the abbot.
What is this?
What is the meaning of this?
You have no authority here.
There's no need for this.
We're men of peace.
No! No! Please!
Please! That's sacred!
Anything taken from the abbot
Would've been kept
with the valuables
We took from the other
prisoners.
It was the butcher's plan
to escape with the treasure.
To disappear,
And use it to make new lives
for himself and his men.
Now the treasure can help us
give the prisoners
Their lives back. Open it.
I've seen him before.
A man came to the stables
Asking for a horse so he could
take his brother to be buried.
Apparently he took
the treasure instead.
And you believed
his story?
The confessor told me
I had to show more compassion.
Are you saying
this is my fault?
Yes.
It doesn't matter
whose fault it is.
We need to find him.
I came to give them some food.
Did you see who did this?
It was the butcher.
He's come back
from the grave.
Quickly, everyone get inside.
This way.
Is it true
what they're saying?
That the butcher
killed those people?
I don't know.
But you'll be safe
inside the prison.
We need to set up a guard
through the night,
Make sure no one
gets in or out.
I can take first watch.
Keep the doors locked.
Keep everyone inside.
That won't stop him.
I got to see what
the butcher was capable of
When he killed my friends.
If he has come back
to take his revenge,
He won't stop
until he's killed us all.
Whoever it is,
we'll keep them out.
But just in case.
I've looked everywhere.
There's no sign of whoever
murdered these men.
Is it possible
the rumors are true?
The butcher's come back
from the grave?
Like darken rahl did.
Darken rahl was just a spirit.
Spirits don't have bodies.
They can't pick up knives
and slaughter people.
Well, we're going to find
who did.
In the meantime,
I need you to find the man
who stole the abbot's locket.
He can't
have gotten far.
I don't want him tortured
or killed.
Bring him back alive.
I'll do my best.
If this butcher's escaped
from the grave,
I'd like to see it
for myself.
Someone dug him up.
No.
He clawed his way out.
So did the rest
of the d'harans we buried.
Could this be the work
of the keeper?
Darken rahl?
It's possible.
Who else could bring
the dead back to life?
The mord-sith.
Cara's with us now.
Why would she come all this way
to resurrect some d'harans
With the breath of life?
She served rahl
and fought side-by-side
With the d'harans for years.
Cara helped me defeat rahl.
That should earn her
some trust.
Whoever did this,
however it happened,
We have a big problem.
How do you kill something
that's already dead?
We have to find them first.
I'm not here to harm you.
Who are you?
I am abbot henry.
The d'harans told us
that you had been hung.
After the d'harans
executed me,
I awoke in the underworld.
In a pit of unimaginable
suffering,
I was greeted
by darken rahl himself.
Rahl?
He told me that the keeper
wished to make me an offer.
He would allow me to return
to the land of the living,
But he demanded
an awful price.
In exchange
for letting me live again,
I had to agree
to kill for the keeper.
He made you a baneling.
Banelings are dead souls
Who selfishly bargain
for a second life
In exchange for killing others.
I thought they were
just a legend.
So did I,
But it seems the keeper
is using the tear in the veil
To give the dead a chance
To return to the world
of the living.
I guess the butcher and his men
accepted his offer.
So can anyone who die
become a baneling?
Maybe not.
Maybe only
in places like tothrayne.
The veil between our world
and the underworld
Is weakest in places
of great death.
The rift is growing.
If we don't close it soon,
The keeper could send banelings
back anywhere.
We need to find
the stone of tears
To close the rift in the veil.
Brother bertrand told us
that the secret of the stone
Was inside your locket.
Yes.
That's why I had to take
the keeper's offer.
To reclaim the locket and ensure
the stone's location
Wasn't lost forever.
Well, we're trying to find
the locket right now.
what's wrong?
I haven't fulfilled my end
of the keeper's bargain.
I haven't killed anyone yet.
I'm being called back
to the underworld.
Tell us what we need to do
with the locket.
I spent years learning
the rituals I would need
To pass on to you.
There's simply not enough time.
Well, we have to buy you time.
How?
You have to kill someone.
I'm not sure I can do this.
You'll be killing a d'haran
Guilty of horrible crimes.
It may be the only way
to defeat the keeper.
They're already dead.
We have to find someone else
for him to kill.
There's no time.
You must listen to me.
The locket contains
a runescriber.
The magic imprints a rune
Onto the palm
of the one who opens it.
You must take the rune
to the province of pamorah.
The rune is the key
That will open the--
What about me?
Don't I get any?
Oh, there's plenty
to go around.
Sorry to interrupt.
I know you're mourning
the loss of your brother.
We all grieve
in our own way.
Where's the treasure?
I'm not afraid of you.
Do you know what horrible things
they did to me at tothrayne?
Intimately.
I didn't break when
they put me on the rack
Or when they threw me
in the drowning pool,
Or when they spun me
on the wheel of pain.
Torture me all you want.
You'll be wasting
your time.
Oh, I don't want
to torture you.
I have other ways
of loosening your tongue.
After the awful way
they treated you in that place,
I can see why you would hire
those women
To bring you some comfort.
But I'll do things to you
those women can't even imagine.
Many know of a mord-sith's
ability to bring pain,
But few know we are equally
skilled at bringing pleasure.
First, I'm going to...
And then I'll...
But first
you need to tell me where--
In a cave
three leagues outside town.
At the fork in the river.
Get dressed.
But I told you
where the treasure was.
Take me to it.
Now.
What about that thing
you were going to do?
And that other thing
sounded good too.
All right, all right.
Just the first thing, then.
The rune is the key,
but a key to what?
We have no idea what to do
with it once we get there.
We have a bigger problem:
The butcher and his men are
out somewhere
And they need to kill.
But who killed these men?
The butcher wouldn't bother
with a locked cell
When there's much easier prey
within these walls.
Who else would
want them dead?
I'm sure any prisoner would want
revenge against the d'harans.
But only one of them
had keys to the cells.
Who?
A prisoner.
A resistance fighter.
Find him.
What's stopping
these dead d'harans
From taking the keeper's deal
And becoming banelings
themselves?
You said banelings are creatures
of the flesh.
When their souls return to this
world, they need a body.
What are you thinking?
We burn them, zedd.
Richard.
This is what
you're looking for.
Did you open this?
Answer me.
Yes.
Some strange ink came out
and did this.
What?
You've been marked
by powerful magic, boy.
We have to take him
with us to pamorah.
I'm not going anywhere
with you.
Take him to kahlan.
Have her confess him.
No. We don't know how
the confessor's touch
Will affect the rune's magic.
Seems this is worth
quite a bit to you.
At least as much
as the treasure.
You want me to go with you
to this pamorah?
It'll cost you.
You're not getting
the treasure.
Well, then, I guess I'm not
going anywhere.
And this hand goes
where I go.
Not if I cut it off.
When do we leave?
Lock him
in the warden's office
Until we deal
with the banelings.
You know,
this would be a good place
For you to keep up
your end of our bargain.
Hey. Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Our thief won't be going
anywhere without us.
You brought him back
without a scratch.
How'd you manage that?
I have other methods.
What kind of methods?
Well, however you did it,
It's good work.
Did you expect anything less?
I'm just glad to have you
on our side.
Maybe you can tell
zedd and kahlan
That they can stop sleeping with
weapons under their pillows.
The d'haran guards
were killed on your watch.
I gave you keys
to the cells and a weapon.
You wanted revenge
for the death of your friends?
I won't lie to you,
mother confessor.
After what they did
to my friends,
I'm not sorry
they're dead.
I'm just sorry I wasn't
the one who did it.
I believe you.
Which means there's still
a killer out there.
Look, you can let me out.
I'm not going to try
to escape.
I'll go with you
to this pamorah.
He's dead.
He was the key
to the stone of tears.
Please, don't hurt me.
There's nothing to fear here.
Where am I?
In the underworld.
I-- I'm dead?
Yes.
But you don't have
to remain that way.
All the keeper asks is that
in exchange for life,
You kill for him.
No, please!
You bear the rune.
No!
Are you all right?
Can you talk?
I-- I thought I was dead.
I brought you back.
You're welcome.
I saw darken rahl.
Darken rahl?
Who stabbed you?
At first I couldn't figure out
How you got into a locked cell
to kill the d'harans.
But then I remembered.
You're the daughter
of a locksmith.
You must have died
before we arrived.
I only accepted
the keeper's offer
So that I could
watch over william.
This war has already made
so many orphans.
I couldn't bear the thought
of my son
Being so alone
and helpless.
I had to keep killing
to satisfy the keeper.
But after what
the d'harans did to us,
They deserved it.
And when you ran out
of d'harans?
Wouldn't you kill to protect
the ones you love?
You know we can't let you
kill any more people.
Promise me
That you'll make sure
my william is safe.
We need to get to the armory and
grab every weapon we can find.
And how will we find
the butcher and his men?
Well, they need to kill.
They'll go where they can find
the easiest prey.
That's the last of them.
We'll need more.
Then we'll head north.
I have a more important task
for you, general.
My lord.
You must capture the one who
bears the rune of pamorah.
Tell me where
I can find him.
He's in tothrayne.
But my lord,
the seeker is there.
Then you don't have much time.
The runebearer is the key
to finding the stone of tears.
If the seeker
should acquire the stone,
Then the rift between
the two worlds will be closed,
And all of you returned
to the underworld.
I will not fail you.
Kahlan is keeping
everyone safe.
You, cara and I are going
to track the banelings.
And when we find them?
We trap them and burn them.
We're not gonna
need the horses.
Give us the one
who bears the rune.
Again!
Put your backs into it, men!
When flynn was in
the underworld,
Rahl must've seen the rune.
He must know it's the key
to the stone of tears.
These walls are strong.
If the banelings can't
get to us, they can't kill
And they'll die again.
He'll just send his men
to find more victims.
They'll grown stronger out there
while we grow weaker in here.
They're not gonna stop
until they get in.
Well, if they want in,
we'll let them come.
And what about kahlan
and all the others?
We'll get them out the back way.
This is a prison.
There is no back way.
We can make one.
Quickly!
Let's go, come on.
Hang on.
Hurry.
Come on.
They've all gone.
Not all of us.
Welcome back to tothrayne.
After all the suffering
These people have been through,
Now they'll have a chance
to rebuild their lives.
Zedd's already helping them
with that.
That's for you.
Thank you.
For your family.
You know,
It's a long road to pamorah.
It could get
a little lonely.
You're right.
It is a long road
to pamorah.
aah!
And if you want to make
it there in one piece,
You won't try my patience.
The seeker said
you needed me alive.
Yes.
But he didn't say
you had to be comfortable.
William, this is bertrand.
He's gonna take you
to a place called timberfalls.
There's a family there
that can't wait to meet you.
I think
you'll like it there.
Lots of children
to play with.
Does that sound all right?
Thank you. Goodbye.
Now I know what rahl meant
When he said I was marked
for the keeper.
With every person I kill,
I'm giving the keeper another
soldier to add to his army.
Killing my enemies
only makes him stronger.
It's not just your enemies.
It's people like eleanor.
Good people desperate enough
to accept the keeper's offer.
He's using their desire for life
to create more death.
Then can we risk
killing our enemies?
We don't have a choice.
If we have to kill to save
an innocent life, we'll do it.
No matter how many souls
the keeper claims,
As long as there are even a few
people left to create life,
And as long as people are
willing to protect that life,
The keeper can't win.
It's just over
this next hill.
You know, the other children
will be so excited to see you.
Hey, uh...
You all right, william?
Are you hurt?
You're a baneling.
- Watch more episodes online @ www.onlinesubtitles.org -