Previously on Legend of the Seeker
He is the first true Seeker
in the last thousand years.
- He has a destiny.
- Who are you to decide a man's destiny?
- It's not me. It's the Prophecy.
- Prophecy be damned.
So, it doesn't matter Darken Rahl
is growing more powerful everyday?
That people in the Midlands are losing
their freedom, dying by the thousands?
Stop. What are you talking about?
- And what's a Seeker?
- A Seeker is a hero who arises
in a time of trouble and suffering.
This is the Sword of Truth.
In anyone else's hands,
this is just a piece of steel.
But in a Seeker's hands,
bestows the power to fight evil.
And with it,
you will kill Darken Rahl.
Let it be known
throughout the three territories,
that whoever brings me the Seeker
will be rewarded beyond imagining.
Any sign of him?
Only a burned-out campfire.
Did you follow the tracks
leading away from it?
- No, they were too well-covered.
- So you found nothing, then?
Just this worthless trinket,
caught in some underbrush.
So much for the bounty.
It's his.
Sync: Kasius
There he is!
Grab him!
You think you can steal food
from Lord Rahl's army?
- I didn't steal anything.
- Liar.
My men found the food in your barn.
We were starving.
Then where's the rest
of your band of thieves?
I'm the only one.
There's no one else.
How can I help you today, sir?
I need a map.
A map?
I've got many maps.
How about a map
to the Ruins of Kelabra?
How about the Twin Barrier Peaks?
Falls of the White Plume?
It's very popular.
I need a map to track someone.
A map to track someone?
I'm not sure a map like that
actually exists.
Course if it did,
it'd be very costly.
I'd need something that belonged
to the person you wanted to track.
Who'd you say
that pendant belonged to again?
- He's getting away.
- Whose fault is that?
- "Wait for my signal. Flush him out."
- I waited. He didn't.
Did I get it?
So much for dinner.
Wizard of the First Order.
Really?
I was hungry.
It was getting away.
You torched the only game
we've seen in two days.
Food used to be plentiful around here.
But the D'Harans have been over-hunting.
Too bad that elk
got away from us yesterday.
Don't remind me, Zedd. I lost
my father's pendant chasing after it.
I'm sorry.
I know it meant a lot to you.
Wait. Kahlan, no!
- Hold still. I'll burn the ropes.
- And end up like that rabbit?
Hurry, Zedd.
- Do it now.
- Don't move.
The Sword.
I didn't agree to fight a Wizard.
Cowards!
I almost had him.
Well, at least you got his money.
He'll be paying for dinner.
What's that?
It's a map.
It's moving.
It appears to have stopped.
What's that light?
I think it's you.
A map that knows where I am?
Cartogromancy is
a rare and powerful magic.
Few know of its existence,
much less its practice.
- Could Darken Rahl have made it?
- If Rahl had a way of tracking you,
he would have sent the entire
D'Haran army. You'd be dead already.
- That's comforting.
- Luckily, the map is in our hands now.
Well, it could be useful.
If we got split up,
you'd know where to find me.
Like those highwaymen did.
Why would they have such a thing?
Where would they get it?
They weren't highwaymen.
They were bounty hunters.
"A thousand gold pieces for the Seeker."
If Rahl's offering that kind of money,
bounty hunters won't be
the only ones looking for you.
I'm telling you, it's him.
You're right.
Let's go.
It's him. The Seeker. He's mine.
We don't want any trouble.
Trouble it is.
Run! Now!
Thank you for your help.
Good to know not everyone
in this town is against us.
Are you really the Seeker?
Then I need your help.
My little brother Liam and I
were attacked by a Shadrin.
- It took him.
- A Shadrin?
One of the most feared creatures
in the Midlands.
Few who have seen it
have lived to describe it.
It happened so fast.
All I saw were claws and teeth.
I thought the Shadrin was a myth.
Did a myth do this to me?
I couldn't fight it off.
I wasn't strong enough.
And none of those cowards in the tavern
would help me.
The Shadrin hunt during the day.
They keep their prey alive
until nightfall,
then they feed.
Then there's still time.
Please, you have to help him.
He's just a boy.
- Where did this thing attack you?
- I can take you there.
What about the people trying
to collect the bounty on your head?
You mean the ones trying to capture me
when she stepped in?
We can take care of ourselves.
Lilly's brother can't.
You got my message.
What makes you think I'd be
so interested in one of your maps?
Because this one
will lead you to the Seeker.
You can be the one to claim the bounty.
It'll cost you.
Great, I can buy a new quill.
There you go. Careful.
That's one of a kind.
This is where it attacked us.
Liam had skinned his knee.
He was crying
- when it just came and took him.
- The Shadrin are nearly blind.
They hunt by sound.
It must have been drawn by the cries.
Let's see if we can pick up its trail
and follow it back to the nest.
In the stories I've heard,
the Shadrin build their nests in caves.
There are some caves up ahead.
- Don't have much time before sundown.
- You're right. We better hurry.
My cart threw a wheel. I could use
some help getting it back on.
Sorry. But we have to help a boy who's
in danger. We'll come back if we can.
- Zedd, get her out of here!
- Richard!
Another one.
Where did you get this?
You'd better answer the Confessor.
Sebastian,
- the mapmaker in South Caston.
- If he's selling these maps,
it's only a matter of time
before we're ambushed by his customers.
You can't risk helping me.
You need to keep moving.
- The Seeker is too important.
- We're going to find your brother.
You go after Lilly's brother.
And I'll find this mapmaker.
This will take me to the Seeker?
It's a one-of-a-kind item.
As my best customer,
I wanted to give you first chance at it.
Happy hunting.
Back so soon?
I need another map.
- I can't.
- Why not?
I'm out of ink.
But if you have something else
that belonged to the Seeker,
we can make it work.
You had plenty of ink when I left here.
You made more maps,
didn't you, you weasel?
Who'd you sell them to?
I just sold the last one.
To the man who just left.
He has markings on his face.
If you leave now, you can catch him.
Richard, look at this.
We're not far from the map's border.
If we move beyond it, anyone who has
one of these won't be able to track you.
We could double back to the north
and cross the river.
What about Lilly?
The Shadrin's in the other direction.
You have a bigger destiny
than helping one boy.
Especially one
that might already be dead.
It's only a matter of time
before someone finds you
and turns you in for the bounty.
How are we to hunt Darken
if we're being hunted ourselves?
And running away is going to help?
- You'll be alive.
- By sacrificing Lilly's brother.
We've all made sacrifices.
I lost my sister trying to find you.
I don't regret that decision.
I've sworn to protect you with my life.
Even from yourself.
The caves are just up ahead.
Is something wrong?
No, we're coming.
It hunts by sound.
Lilly.
Liam!
We're closed.
Not yet you're not.
I've hear you're selling maps
to track the Seeker.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But...
maybe I can interest you
in a map of the Ruins of Kelabra?
I don't really know
where you got that,
old man.
You're going to tell me
how you made this,
how many you made,
and who you sold them to.
A bounty hunter. He had a pendant.
He said it belonged to the Seeker.
- I used it to make the map.
- How many did you make?
One.
Three. I just sold the last one.
And did you sell any to the D'Harans?
Course not.
They don't buy maps.
They take 'em.
I loathe the D'Harans.
And yet you would help them
by aiding those
who would capture the Seeker
for Darken Rahl?
Where was the Seeker
when we were suffering under Lord Rahl?
You know,
I used to be in the service of kings?
Then the D'Harans moved in.
I gotta provide for my family.
To do that, I make maps.
Well, now you're gonna make one for me.
I need to find the bounty hunter
who bought the last map.
I can't do it.
Gotta have something
that belonged to him.
- Something he valued greatly.
- He paid you, didn't he?
What could be more valuable
to a bounty hunter than his money?
- I left her back in the cave.
- You trapped her with that beast?
Please.
Everyone knows the Shadrin's a myth.
This ought to lead you
to the bounty hunter.
If you leave now, you can catch him.
I'll be leaving.
But if you make any more maps
that track the Seeker,
I'll be back.
Why are you doing this?
I was trying to help you.
That's right,
because you're the Seeker?
I don't believe that fairy tale.
But if the D'Harans do,
and they're willing to pay,
all the better for me.
I don't see what they're so afraid of.
- They're afraid of the Prophecy.
- Right.
You're gonna defeat Darken Rahl
and save everyone in the Midlands.
- You're the only thing stopping me.
- And look how hard that was.
The D'Harans don't need to send an army.
All it takes is a few tears
and an ample bosom.
Hand over the map
and I'll let you live.
How about this? You walk away
and I won't kill you.
You can keep your half.
Damn.
You didn't think the Seeker
was gonna stay in one place, did you?
This is your lucky day.
You see him?
That's the Seeker.
And you get to be the hero
who goes back to your captain
and tells him that I've got him.
If he wants the Seeker,
he can meet me at Demon Rock.
But tell him I don't want the bounty.
I want something else.
So tell me, what's worth more to you
than the bounty on the Seeker?
My brother.
So I guess the Shadrin didn't take him.
No, worse.
He was arrested by the D'Harans.
They were gonna execute him
for stealing.
- Did he do it?
- No. I did.
He just confessed to protect me.
- So you're a thief.
- What choice do I have?
The only food around here is
what you can poach from the D'Harans.
It's either steal or starve,
and I am not gonna starve.
My brother is all I have left.
I will not let the D'Harans kill him.
Don't you see?
I'm on your side.
If you had told me the truth,
I would have helped your brother.
Maybe when you thought
he was an innocent boy.
With everyone trying to collect
a bounty on you, if I had asked you
to ride into a D'Haran garrison
to help a thief,
would you have said yes?
I thought you might want some food.
I know you're hungry.
I'm sorry I hit you before.
I just had to put on a good show
in front of my men.
It's okay. Take it.
No one will know.
Thank you.
Fool.
We hang thieves.
We don't fatten them up.
Unshackle me.
We can go back for Kahlan,
and then we can all rescue your brother.
What guarantee do I have you won't
take off the second I unshackle you?
I give you my word as the Seeker.
That would mean something
if I believed in the Seeker.
- The Seeker is mine.
- Don't be a fool.
There's no guarantee he's gonna stay
on one half of the map.
- What are you suggesting?
- We work together.
We've already split the map.
Let's split the bounty.
Two against one
is better odds.
You agreed to that a little too quickly.
How do I know
- you're not trying to trick me?
- You suggested it a little too quickly.
How do I know
you're not trying to trick me?
All right.
The longer we argue,
the more time the Seeker has to escape.
We're just gonna have
to trust each other.
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine. How about you?
Next time,
when I tell you we can't help someone,
don't trust them. Trust me.
- She was very convincing.
- Yes, she was.
I'm so sorry I got you into all this.
Apology accepted.
Move.
On the ground, Confessor.
We could get something for her too?
Once we collect on the Seeker,
there'll be plenty for both of us.
Until he double-crosses you.
Who are you?
Someone who knows this man
a lot better than you do.
- I've never seen this woman before.
- We can share the bounty.
And whatever else
you might be interested in.
Don't listen to her.
What kind of deal are we talking about?
I knew you'd stab me in the back.
I won't be so gentle.
Where do you think you're going?
That takes care of all three maps.
Even so,
there's still a bounty on your head.
- We should get going.
- What are we gonna do about her?
You may as well kill me.
If I don't deliver the Seeker
to the D'Harans,
my brother's as good as dead.
What are you doing?
Keeping my promise.
I'm going to save her brother.
Have you learned nothing?
She tried to feed me to a Shadrin.
- She thought it was a myth.
- She tried to sell you to the D'Harans.
- She was trying to save her brother.
- And you believe her?
Everything out of her mouth
has been a lie.
- Tell me you don't trust this woman.
- No.
But I do trust Richard.
And the people must know that the Seeker
will stand and fight for them.
- What has she done to deserve our help?
- How do we decide who deserves it?
It should be enough that she needs it.
Don't be naive.
- This isn't Westland.
- Exactly.
Darken Rahl has forced
people of the Midlands
to do anything to just survive.
Including serving you
up to the D'Harans.
People like her
- are only looking out for themselves.
- If the Seeker's just out for himself,
what chance do they have?
I know where the Seeker is.
- Why haven't you brought him to me?
- He's been captured.
- By whom?
- A woman has him.
- A woman?
- Yes. But she doesn't want the bounty.
What does she want?
Two patrols along the perimeter.
Four sentries at the main gate.
- A few dozen D'Harans inside.
- I think this can work.
It's a smart plan, Richard.
But it all depends on trusting Lilly.
If she's lying to us,
you'll be captured and killed,
and Darken Rahl will win.
- What is it you want?
- You're holding a prisoner named Liam.
You release him,
you can have the Seeker.
- Where is the Seeker?
- This map will take you there.
If you hurry, you can get the Confessor
and the Wizard as well.
But if you want it,
I want to see my brother.
Very well.
Take her to her brother.
We had an agreement!
You bastards!
- What have they done to you?
- I'm all right.
- What are you doing here?
- Trying to get you out.
All I wanted was you to be safe.
I couldn't just stand by
and let them execute you.
So now what?
We both die.
Not today.
I want every available man ready.
- We're going after the Seeker.
- Yes, sir.
The Seeker's up ahead.
It's this way.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on, men.
The Seeker's in here.
It's not the Seeker.
We've been tricked.
Guess the D'Harans believed
you gave them the right map.
It wasn't that hard convincing them.
I'm a devious, conniving woman.
I want to thank you
for saving my brother.
- Despite the fact that I lied to you.
- And tried to sell me to the D'Harans
- and kill my friends.
- Those are just what you know.
You did all this just to help us.
He's the Seeker.
Richard, we should get moving.
Well, if you ever come back this way,
maybe we'll see each other again.
You'd better hope not.
The D'Harans have no intention
of paying the bounty on the Seeker.
Anyone who tries to collect will find
themselves inside a D'Haran prison cell.
Besides, the Seeker's on our side.
He's fighting for us.
The least we can do is help him out.
- How did you do that?
- It's called additive magic.
Try to hold on to it this time.
It's the only thing
I have of my father's.
I'm not letting it
out of my sight again.
I just want you to know that I really
appreciate you looking out for me.
Well, if you'd listened to me,
that boy would have been executed.
You saved him.
After living under Rahl for so long,
people have forgotten what a hero is.
But you stood up and fought for them.
Word will spread.
The people will know
that the Seeker has returned.
We should get going soon.
Come on. What's the hurry?
If you're gonna rescue every damsel
in distress, there's no time to waste.