Richard Cypher,
you are the true seeker.
( heroic theme playing )
Legend of the Seeker 2x05
Wizard
Original Air Date on December 5, 2009
-- Sync, HI corrections by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --
It's holding steady
at north-northeast.
Which should bring us within
a league of Winterhaven by noon.
We could stop there
for a hot meal.
I thought the compass
was supposed to point the way
to the Stone of Tears,
not the nearest tavern.
To reach the Stone of Tears,
we need all the sustenance
we can get.
Zedd.
Look.
Somebody's favorite fruit.
The persimmon is far more
than my favorite fruit.
It's the pinnacle
of creation.
One doesn't often see
such a perfect specimen
this late in the season.
I hope none of you
are expecting a slice
of the last persimmon
of the year.
Wouldn't think of it.
That's very generous of you.
Mm. Mm. Mm.
Any persimmon you can eat
without getting juice
on your chin...
Mm. --isn't worth eating
in the first place.
Can I have a, um...?
A drink of, uh...?
Argh.
(Cara)- Water?
(Zedd)- Yes. Water.
Thank you, Kahlan.
My name is Cara.
I know that.
You called me Kahlan.
I absolutely did not.
Zedd, you did.
I did?
Are you all right?
No, I'm not all right.
It's not indignity enough that
I have more aches in my joints
than joints in my body,
that I stumble to the privy
six times a night.
Now I'm forgetting
the word for water,
and calling people
by the wrong name.
I must be older
than I thought.
You? Old?
Zedd, I'd be lucky
to be half as sharp as you are
when I'm your age.
( sighs )
Where's Tarralyn?
Tarralyn?
Yes, Tarralyn, my daughter.
Where is she?
Zedd, Tarralyn
isn't with us anymore.
She died last summer.
My daughter's dead?
How can that be?
You've known about Tarralyn
for a long time.
This is not like you.
You have the best memory
of anybody I've ever met.
Zedd, something
is happening to you.
Happening. Yes.
Something's happening.
The persimmon.
Zedd's the only one who ate it.
Maybe it was poisoned.
Not poisoned. Spelled.
A spell of f-f-forgetting.
Is there a way to undo it?
Yes.
- A potion.
- A potion of what?
Elderberry blossoms, mandragora,
and the dust
of a Shadrin's horn.
We'll find them.
Zedd, who would have
done this to you?
There's only one person
powerful enough
to spell a Wizard
of the First Order.
Who knows exactly what fruit
I wouldn't be able to resist.
Who?
Zedd, who?
Shota.
Why would Shota
want to do this to you?
Why would who want to do what?
Take away your memory.
- Let go of me.
- Zedd.
Why are you all looking at me
like that? Who are you people?
Find elderberry blossoms.
I'll get the mandragora.
For the Shadrin, we'll have to
go into the caves we passed.
Keep Zedd calm.
Zedd. Zedd, it's all right.
Get away from me!
Don't let him get away.
No!
( Richard grunts )
Richard.
( panting )
(Kahlan)
Richard, are you all right?
Unh. Where's Zedd?
He ran off.
You and I will go up to the
caves and try to find a Shadrin.
You follow Zedd.
He can't use his magic
against you.
When you find him,
bring him back here.
He's a very big Wizard.
I may have to do it my way.
Just don't kill him. Go. Unh.
( chickens clucking )
(Man)
Do you think I like having to
come down here personally?
Third week running
we've only gotten
four gold pieces
from you.
Didn't we agree
your fair share
of maintaining the beauty
of our great city was eight?
( man grunting )
Stop that.
You're hurting him.
What are you gonna do
about it, old man?
( chuckles )
( men laughing )
( man grunts )
Excuse me.
Yes?
You're very beautiful.
So I've heard.
( crowd laughing )
Payment upfront.
Payment?
You didn't think you could
partake of my wares for free,
did you?
( giggles )
Coins, old man. Those little
round, shiny things
you keep in that purse
on your belt.
Purse.
Oh, yes.
Coins.
I'm afraid
you'll need ten of those.
The price has gone up.
Now that half of every farthing
I earn goes to Drago.
I wish I had ten.
( magic chimes )
Do that again.
I'll try.
( magic chimes )
( crowd gasps )
Girls, uh, take this
gentleman upstairs
and see that he has
the best night of his life.
( women giggling )
What about her?
(Inkeeper)
Well, that would be
up to Salindra,
and Salindra's very choosy.
But if you ask her nicely,
she might go upstairs with you.
Salindra.
Will you come upstairs with me?
Sorry.
You remind me too much
of my grandfather.
( both laugh )
Come along, handsome.
Who needs her
when you've got us?
( giggling )
( loud bang )
( crowd gasps )
Why is it that when
I'm hunting down a man,
I never have to look further
than the first brothel
past the city gates?
- Keep away from me.
(Cara)- Sorry.
Your little adventure is over.
I'm taking you back
to Richard and Kahlan.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
I think you'll reconsider.
( bird calling )
(Shota)
Thank the Spirits you're safe.
Who are you?
How did I get here?
I'm Shota.
I brought you here.
I'm your friend.
If you're my friend, then
send me back to where I was.
Oh, I can't.
That woman in red
would have killed you.
I saved your life.
( chuckles )
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I love you.
I don't even know you.
Have the years taken that much
from you, Zeddicus?
Have you forgotten even me?
Zeddicus?
Oh, my love.
You don't know that you are
Zeddicus Zu'l Zorander,
the greatest and most powerful
Wizard the world has known
in 3,000 years.
- I am?
- Yes.
There is so much to say, but we
don't have very much time.
The world is in terrible
trouble, and only we can help.
A rift has been torn
in the veil
between the Underworld
and the Land of the Living.
If the Seeker of Truth does not
find the Stone of Tears,
the Keeper will put an end
to all life.
The Seeker of Truth?
Who's that?
A great hero,
one that can only be named
by a Wizard of the First Order,
and you, you are the only
Wizard of the First Order alive.
- The only one?
- Yes.
But as you got older
and began to lose your memories,
you made a mistake.
You named the wrong Seeker.
A Seeker prophesied to fail.
That's terrible.
Yes, but fortunately,
I've found a new one,
a young man of great courage.
And once you name him,
and he is able
to fulfill his quest,
then not only
will the world be saved,
but then you and I will be free
to live together,
as we did long ago, in bliss.
And with our combined powers,
Zeddicus,
we will master the world
and protect it from evil.
But how can I help?
An old man, who doesn't remember
his own name?
Oh...
I can restore
what you have lost.
Your youth and the mastery
of all the spells and magic
that were yours
in that golden time long ago,
back when you were at the height
of your powers.
( inhales )
( suspenseful theme playing )
( exhales )
Come.
You are the great love
of my life, Zeddicus.
I'm not surprised.
The Keeper isn't resting,
and neither can we.
In order to name a new Seeker
and send him off on his quest,
we need two things.
First,
the Sword of Truth.
(Zedd)- I know them.
(Shota)- Yes.
The man you wrongly named
the Seeker,
and the misguided Confessor
who protects him.
They tried to attack me.
Of course they did.
To prevent you from naming
the new Seeker.
Shadrin.
( growling )
( roars )
(Man)
Halt and drop your weapons.
Poaching on the personal reserve
of Drago,
High Lord and Master
of Winterhaven,
is a crime
punishable by death.
We didn't know we were on
anyone's personal reserve.
Lord Drago was a great friend
of Lord Rahl's.
He'll be more than happy to see
the Seeker and the Confessor
hanging from his gallows.
Take them.
But don't let her touch you.
She's deadlier
than a poison dart.
( Richard yells )
( all grunting )
For what I am going to do,
I need to join my magic
with yours.
Give me your hand.
Think, Zeddicus.
You know the words
to the Spell of Taking.
I've restored them to you.
Yes.
Yes, I remember them.
Say them with me.
( grunting )
( chanting in ancient tongue )
( panting )
Astounding.
Not for us, Zeddicus.
For us, it's barely more
than a parlor trick.
( all grunting )
Richard!
The new Seeker needs one more
thing to complete his quest.
Stop! Unh!
( Richard grunting )
What's this?
Witchcraft.
( all grunting )
( grunts )
( panting )
- What is it?
- A compass.
In the hands of the Seeker named
by a Wizard of the First Order,
it will illuminate and light
the way to the Stone of Tears
and the salvation of the world.
But the province where we will
find the new Seeker
is many leagues from here.
We must leave immediately.
- Leave?
- Yes.
- Right now.
- I don't want to leave.
I like it here.
Is it Winterhaven that you like,
or one of the harlots?
I should have known that by
giving you a beautiful face
it wouldn't make you
any less of an old fool.
Fool, am I?
Many thanks for the beautiful
young face.
And the wonderful spells.
But I'm not going anywhere
with you.
( chants in ancient tongue )
( sighs )
( crowd chattering )
(Zedd)
Hello, Salindra.
Do I know you?
Well, I guess I don't look like
your grandfather anymore.
Oh. It's you.
Well, you certainly have a lot
of tricks up your sleeve. Heh.
What are you wasting your time
on a mouse like this for?
Oh, he is hardly a mouse.
Are you trying to impress me?
What is it?
Why are you looking at me
that way?
When I first saw you,
I thought you might be
the princess
I was looking for.
But I don't know,
dressed like that.
( crowd gasps )
(Zedd)
And what
self-respecting princess
goes around without a footman...
( crowd gasps )
(Zedd)
...and ladies in waiting?
( crowd gasps )
Well, the real question is,
what kind of princess
goes around without a prince?
( majestic theme playing )
Do you like the view?
(Salindra)
Very much.
Then allow me to welcome you
to your new palace.
I don't see a palace.
Not yet.
Girls?
Mm. Half a dozen of them.
Hanging all over him.
And then he disappeared.
I've been searching for him
all night.
Look.
I guess we know
where Zedd is.
Let's go.
Does this meet
with Your Majesty's approval?
I think it will do.
Once we get there, how do we get
Zedd to drink the potion?
(Shota)
You won't be able
to get near him.
Shota.
He thinks you're his enemies.
He'll obliterate you.
I don't know
what you did to him, or why,
but I'm gonna stop him before
he hurts somebody or himself.
Oh, just because you have
flowers and roots
and a Shadrin's horn,
that doesn't mean
you can reverse my spell.
No, what I have done,
only I can undo.
Then do it.
Oh, heh, I will.
After he has named a new Seeker.
What?
( laughs ):
Oh.
He hasn't told you about
the Prophecy.
What Prophecy?
A month ago I told him
that it was written
in the Halls of Prophecy
that Richard Cypher will fail
in his quest to defeat
the Keeper.
Fail how? What do you mean?
I don't care about Prophecy,
and I don't have time
for your riddles and tricks.
None of my prophecies
have ever proved false.
I begged Zedd
to name a new Seeker,
but he was too blinded
by his sentimental attachment
to his grandson.
I hoped that if I stripped him
of his memories,
I might convince him to do
what had to be done.
Richard is the Seeker.
Of course you'd say that
about the man who you love.
But I didn't come here
expecting your help.
I came hoping for yours.
Why would I help you?
Because you don't care
who bears the name of Seeker,
you only care about
protecting Richard Rahl.
But if he continues
on this doomed quest,
the Keeper will win,
and he will die
along with everyone else
in the world.
Now, Zedd can't use his magic
against you.
If you subdue him,
then I can force him to do
what must be done.
Funny, how people always curse
the Mord-Sith,
until they need one.
Do you want Richard to live
or don't you?
You're right.
Wizards can't use their magic
against a Mord-Sith.
And neither can witches.
( screaming )
( Agiel whining )
There's only one way to
stop that from happening again:
Undo the spell you put on Zedd.
(Man)
No matter how much we give them,
Great Wizard,
Drago always wants more.
(Zedd)
I swear to you, sir,
and to all citizens
of Winterhaven,
such cruelty will never again
be tolerated in this city.
They've destroyed all my wares,
my children will go hungry.
If there's something
you can do to help...
( laughing )
Ha-ha! Thank you, thank you,
Great Wizard.
(Zedd)
Monica.
Will you accept this trifle,
in thanks for befriending me
when I was a ragged old man
with no castle to my name?
(Monica)
It's very beautiful,
Great Wizard.
But there's trouble
in Winterhaven
that all the jewels
of Athanasia can't fix.
The dead coming back to life,
murdering people in their homes.
The Keeper's work,
people say.
Same for the cracks in the
ground, opening up all over.
A tear in the veil
between the Underworld
and the Land of the Living.
There's a rift just outside
the walls of the city.
A monster crawled
out of it last week,
slaughtered two
of my best customers,
on their way back
to their village.
You have to help us.
To help you seal the rift,
and defeat the Keeper,
we need to find
the Stone of Tears.
And to find the Stone of Tears,
we need a Seeker.
Yes. Richard Cypher.
Hm, I'm afraid we can't rely
on Richard Cypher.
There's a Prophecy that says
he's destined to fail.
Don't worry,
we'll have a new Seeker.
Only a Wizard of the First Order
can name one,
and fortunately,
I am such a Wizard.
Who will you name?
As Wizard of the First Order,
I hereby name as Seeker of Truth
and Bearer of the Sword...
Zeddicus Zu'l Zorander!
( all cheer )
( dramatic theme playing )
Yes.
The compass points
the Seeker's way.
My princess and I
will depart at once
on the quest
for the Stone of Tears.
( all cheer )
Secure horses
and provisions
for all those who wish
to accompany us.
Yes, My Lord.
What sorcerer dares to raise
a castle in my city?
I'm no sorcerer.
I am Zeddicus,
greatest of all Wizards,
Seeker of Truth,
and high lord
and master of Winterhaven.
This man will die.
And let it be known
that any friend of his
is an enemy of mine.
( giggles )
Oh, Drago,
you always were
a man who overestimated
what he had in his quiver.
I'm afraid this time you've
met more than your match.
Kill her first.
( screams )
The choice is yours.
You can join me on my quest,
or you can suffer the same fate.
Which is it going to be?
A wise choice.
( all cheering )
( chuckles )
( men screaming )
Drago.
My Lord.
You're alive?
No.
And neither are you.
Then this place--
(Rahl)
The Underworld.
You served me well
in life, Drago.
I did my best, Lord Rahl.
And I will reward you with
an offer from the Keeper:
Kill and live.
My Lord?
One more day of life
for every soul
you deliver to the Keeper.
I gratefully accept,
Lord Rahl.
And I will begin
by ripping out the heart
of Zeddicus Zu'l Zorander
and feeding it to my dogs.
Zorander the Wizard?
Yes, Wizard,
and now Seeker of Truth.
Seeker of Truth?
Yes, My Lord.
He named himself.
The former Seeker,
and the Mother Confessor,
are they with him?
Not that I saw.
But when I send
the Wizard to the Keeper,
you can ask him yourself.
Unfortunately,
a Wizard of the First Order
is not so easy to kill,
as you yourself discovered.
But don't worry,
your death will be avenged.
( dramatic theme playing )
( trumpet plays fanfare )
( rift rumbling )
Halt!
( rumbling continues )
So this is a rift
between the Underworld
and the land of the living?
Yes, Wizard.
One of many,
all over the countryside.
(Zedd)
Do you hear me, Keeper?
Your plans will come to nothing,
for I, Zeddicus,
greatest of all Wizards,
high lord and master
of Winterhaven,
Seeker of the Truth,
and Sealer of the Rift,
will lock you in your
prison for all eternity.
( gasps )
( suspenseful theme playing )
( crowd gasps )
( chatter )
( grunts )
She's dead.
My love,
I will bring you back.
( chants in ancient tongue )
( gasps )
(Rahl)
Salindra.
(Salindra)
Lord Rahl.
( gasps )
(Rahl)
Don't be frightened.
It's much too late for fear
to do you any good.
What are you
going to do to me?
That would be up to you.
If you like,
I could give you a second life.
At what price?
Only small one.
Simply deliver the Wizard
to the Underworld,
along with the Sword of Truth
and the compass.
What do you need them for?
Haven't you heard?
The Keeper is fighting a war
to conquer
the World of the Living
and he needs your help.
Can he count on you?
Isn't there some
other price I could pay?
Don't tell me you've
fallen in love with him.
He's a nice fellow.
He's been kind to me.
They're all nice fellows to you,
as long as they have
a little gold in their pocket.
On the other hand,
you're welcome to stay here
with us in the Underworld.
The Keeper maintains a very
special chamber of torments
for those
who traffic in love.
Ask yourself,
what is the life of one Wizard?
Come, Salindra.
You're a practical girl.
( dramatic theme playing )
( chants in ancient tongue )
She's getting cold.
She's not coming back.
(Man)
There are some things
nobody can do.
- Not even you, Great Wizard.
- No.
There's nothing I can't do.
( chanting in ancient tongue )
( screams )
( gasps )
My beauty.
I've brought you back.
Zeddicus.
What am I doing here?
I said no.
What do you mean?
Oh, Darken Rahl told me
I could come back to life
if I turned against you,
but I refused.
( panting )
He was about to throw me
in the pit.
You can't imagine
how horrible it was...
And then suddenly
I was looking up at you.
You brought me back.
Yes.
And I'll never
let you go again.
Behold, I am Zeddicus,
greatest of all Wizards,
high lord and master
of Winterhaven,
Sealer of the Rift,
Seeker of Truth,
Defeater of Death
and Restorer of Life!
( all cheering )
That's Zedd?
Yes, that's Zedd.
He's named himself the Seeker?
This is a catastrophe.
When I have found
the Stone of Tears,
I will banish death
from this world.
Undo the spell.
No. It's too dangerous.
His magic's too powerful.
I'm not going out there
until you subdue him.
And leave you here?
To do whatever it is
you please
with Richard and Kahlan
the second
my back is turned?
( chuckles )
I don't think so.
Then we have a problem.
If you don't start moving,
you're going to have
a bigger problem.
No. We need to do this without
putting anybody in danger.
How?
When Shota took
away his memories,
he lost everything
he's learned in life:
wisdom, judgment,
knowing about consequences.
Don't forget about humility.
Of which he had precious
little to start with.
He thinks he's more powerful
than the Keeper.
He's turned himself
into a king.
He's even
found himself a queen.
If he sees us all coming,
he'll think we're trying to take
everything away from him.
Shota's right,
he could obliterate us.
So, what do we do?
With his powers,
he could actually succeed
in finding the Stone.
But he's not the true Seeker.
You are.
I doesn't matter
who has the title,
or who gets the glory,
as long as the Stone is found
and the rift is sealed.
(Kahlan)
He's lost his mind.
There's no way
we can count on him.
You're right.
( sighs )
But we don't want to make
him feel threatened.
Not now.
Whatever he's forgotten,
he's still Zedd.
If I can
get close to him,
talk to him,
gain his confidence,
maybe I could make him
see what he's doing,
and what the cost could be.
I'm so frightened for you.
About what?
Do you promise you won't
do anything crazy and reckless?
Salindra, tell me.
When I was in the Underworld,
in that awful,
terrible place,
I heard Darken Rahl
talking to the Keeper.
They're happy you've
taken up the Seeker's quest.
They think that while you're
chasing after
the Stone of Tears,
they will have time
to destroy us all.
But there's one thing
they're terrified of.
What?
They're terrified that you
are going to march into the rift
and battle the Keeper
with the Sword of Truth,
because they know
you would win.
Oh, Zeddicus, I'm so afraid you
will try something like that.
(Man)
Sir, this man wanted to see you.
He said it was
extremely important.
We've searched him head to foot,
he isn't armed.
I know him.
You remember me?
Yes,
you're the false Seeker.
You and your friends
tried to attack me
when I was still
an old man.
We weren't trying to attack you,
we were worried about you.
Do you remember anything
before yesterday?
No. Heh.
But why would I need to?
Nothing of any importance
happened to me before yesterday.
Something terrible did happen.
While you and I were walking
through the forest,
you ate a persimmon
that was spelled by a witch,
and you suddenly
lost your memory.
You were scared and confused.
We tried to calm you down,
but you ran away.
Who are you exactly?
I'm your grandson.
- Grandson?
- Yes.
And a man never
had a better grandfather.
You risked your life
for me hundreds of times.
Without you, the most evil
despot who ever lived
would still be on his throne.
- Would he?
- Yes.
You saved the world.
Many times.
Mm. Well, grandson,
I look forward
to knowing you better,
but right now,
I have a pressing engagement
with the Keeper.
Zeddicus. No.
Yes, Salindra.
I'm marching into the rift alone
to do battle with the Keeper.
You can't go into the rift.
Ah, but I can.
Zedd, no--
Don't worry, you won't
lose your grandfather.
I'll come back, with the blood
of Death himself on my sword.
No one goes into the Underworld
and comes out alive.
Nobody except me.
You'll be killed!
And the Keeper will have
the Sword of Truth,
and the compass.
The Keeper fears me.
What makes you think that?
I was told by somebody
who heard it with her own ears.
She's lying to you.
She's trying to lead you
into some kind of trap.
She wouldn't trick me.
She wouldn't lie to me.
She loves me. Stay back.
Zedd, no!
( grunts )
( suspenseful theme playing )
(woman)
Look out!
The Confessor is coming.
(Man)
Get her!
( grunting )
This isn't farewell.
Just a brief parting.
May the Spirits be with you,
Zeddicus.
They always are.
( grunting )
Get him out.
( chants in ancient tongue )
( grunts )
He went into the rift!
(Kahlan) No.
( gas hissing )
I'm going after him.
Richard, no!
I can't abandon Zedd.
Then I'm coming with you.
If Zedd and I don't come back,
someone needs to stay alive
to find the Stone.
Kahlan, the quest is bigger
than any of us.
Don't follow me.
( dramatic theme playing )
( suspenseful theme playing )
Zedd!
Don't go any farther!
( groans )
(Richard)- No, Zedd!
(Rahl)
Youth is fleeting,
isn't it, Zeddicus?
(Richard)
Zedd, get away from him.
Zedd!
For all of us, it would seem.
Including the Seeker.
Zedd, we have to go.
A valiant effort,
dear brother,
but the Keeper
has granted me
power over the gates
of his dominion.
( rumbling )
Richard!
( heroic theme playing )
Richard.
Zedd.
(Zedd)
I failed.
( Salindra grunts )
( gasping )
Don't worry, my beauty.
Whatever's wrong,
I'll heal you.
You can't.
I didn't deliver my side
of the bargain.
The Keeper's calling
in the debt.
Debt?
I tricked you.
Why?
I-- I--
I'm a practical girl.
( gasps )
( whimpers )
( sobbing )
( melancholic theme playing )
Break the spell.
Now.
( chanting in ancient tongue )
( dramatic theme playing )
(Zedd)
Richard. Kahlan.
What in the name of creation
have I done?
Whatever you did,
it's not your fault,
it's Shota's.
(Shota) No.
I was trying to save everyone.
And I might have succeeded,
if I hadn't underestimated
your pride and arrogance.
Which are exceeded
only by your own.
(Cara)
She's of no use to us now.
Should I kill her?
(Richard)
No.
We may need her someday.
Apparently, you've gainedwisdom.
When you're ready to name
a new Seeker, call on me.
Meanwhile,
enjoy the one you've got.
(Kahlan)
Zedd...
...can you do anything?
( chants in ancient tongue )
( sighs )
Something on your mind?
There's plenty on my mind.
Starting with
"I wonder if Zedd
"didn't tell me
about the Prophecy
because he believes
it to be true."
Is that a new power
of yours?
Being able to read
people's thoughts?
I didn't tell you not because
I had doubts about
your ability to succeed,
but because I didn't want you
to start having doubts
of your own.
What if Shota's right?
About some young swain of hers
she wants me to anoint
so she can wield
the Sword of the Truth
herself by proxy?
Shota thinks only of Shota.
If any proof were ever needed
that not just anybody
can be the Seeker,
my own behavior today
provided it.
Will you have
to name me again?
No.
You were always the Seeker,
long before you first
held the Sword of Truth.
You faced death for me.
Literally.
What was it like,
being young again?
Oh, Richard,
it's years beyond count
since I felt that way.
That there was no mountain
I couldn't climb,
no woman I couldn't win.
( chuckles )
You made me young again.
Could you do that
to yourself?
Yes.
Then why don't you?
Because one journey down
the agonizing gauntlet
of youth
is enough for any man.
She was very beautiful.
Yes, she was, wasn't she?
( soft theme playing )
-- Sync, HI corrections by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --