Hi. It's me, Don Konkey. I'm a
photographer for Dirt Now magazine.
I'm also a highly functional
schizophrenic, blah, blah, blah.
Dad, I think it's time.
No offense, but if you
don't know that by now,
then you have worse
attention skills than me.
That's Lucy Spiller.
Again, no offense, but you should
be up on this shit by now.
Lucy has sort of
a problem with men.
You're not gonna use a stun--
Good night, Holt.
But that's not the case
with Holt McLaren.
Lucy got what she wanted.
Holt got worms.
Remember those pictures I took
of happily married action hero
and international superstar
Jack Dawson and Lucy's brother Leo
a while back?
They're starting to cause
a lot of trouble.
Holt didn't see the worms
when he threw up,
but he did see the track marks
on the arms of his girlfriend
- Julia Mallory.
- What the hell is that?
Jesus Christ, Julia!
What are you doing?
- It's not a big deal.
- The magazine is doing this big story
about this cheerleader murder.
Turns out the murdered girl
was involved with the town preacher.
I've I. D.'d the father of
the victim's unborn baby.
- Oh. And she was pregnant.
- My God.
He was also sleeping
with his daughter.
I don't think there'll be
any World's Greatest Dad mugs
coming his way soon.
Lucy ran that on the cover.
God bless Don Konkey.
He had the right shots all along.
Not everyone was happy.
Who told you my father killed
Amber? Who said that?
I did it! Not Daddy!
On the bright side,
I'm dating again,
and I'm 99% sure
this one is real.
Wait. Don't move.
Don't move. Don't move.
Don't move.
Okay.
Oh, God!
You want to go again?
Don't you want to save
one for the home team?
I heard she moved from
prescription drugs
to self-medication.
What is she on?
I'm asking as a friend.
You want a beer?
Yeah. You?
This is wrong.
Don't take me
on your guilt trip.
No. You're poison, Lucy.
Excuse me?
We have to stop.
Then what are you doing
standing here?
Synchro:
Metalmarco, Pasbel, Yellow Sub
Transcript: Swsub.com
SynchFix: Metalmarco
::ITA-SA:: & _/Yellow Sub\_
Proudly Present:
Dirt - Season 01 Episode 07 -
"Come Together"
Herring worm's rare.
Human cases like yours are more
common in Japan, Netherlands.
Bet you like sushi.
I used to.
Okay.
Thiabendazole.
You're gonna be fine.
Joanna,
can you schedule another
ultrasound for next week
so we can get a head count?
And, uh, would you mind?
What happened to the one
we already took?
My glasses
reflected the flash.
All right.
1, 2-- Oh, wait.
There we go.
And 3.
Willa, right?
- I'm Brent Barrow.
- Oh. Of course you are.
Oh, I'm sorry. I mean of course
I know who you are.
That's all right.
That story-- the reverend who
molested his kid and
knocked up her
cheerleader friend was...
juicy.
You're a very talented
young woman.
- Uh, Thank you, Mr. Barrow.
- What are you working on now?
Uh, it's the same story.
The reverend's daughter
told me that she's the one who
killed her best friend.
She confessed that to you?
Yeah. The cops
don't even know yet.
Lucy thinks the confession cover
might hit the stands
before she's even arrested.
Chuck and I are going back today
to get her full interview.
No. No. Come on.
You don't need to share your byline
with that old boozer.
Tell Lucy to show you more respect.
You're editorial material, Willa.
- Thank you.
- Listen, please.
Reporters like you make my job
an honor and a pleasure.
Uh, Chuck?
Time to go?
Uh, I'm worried
about this interview.
Nothing to worry about.
Well, Maddy called me specifically.
It's because she trusts me.
You want to go eat on the way?
I vote for Quiznos.
Look, Chuck, she's
a sexual abuse victim.
I don't want her to clam up
because there's a man in the room.
Little Willa wants to fly solo
and not share a byline.
It's nothing personal.
It's just...
Lucy's wrong. I don't
need help with this.
I agree.
Really?
You got my blessing.
Will you clear it
with Lucy?
We'll tell her after.
Thank you.
Isn't it great?
I discovered
the artist myself.
Do you get it?
Average person spends
two weeks of their life on hold.
How sick is that?
I like hold.
It's free time.
My God, you're right.
I never thought of it like that.
What's your IQ?
I don't know.
You should get tested.
You're probably over 140.
My best friend in New York--
he's a published poet-- he's 140.
What's your process?
When you write on your photographs,
how long does it take?
I wake up...
it's there.
Oh. You black out.
What are you, epileptic?
Narcoleptic?
Schizophrenic.
Genius does not go unpunished.
Meet the bulimic.
Relax.
I use the other hand.
Have you and your father
always been close?
Madonna's mom died, too.
So did Rosie O'Donnell's.
Is that when it started?
When it was just
the two of you?
Have you ever interviewed
Nicole or Lindsay?
Um...
No, I haven't.
Maddy, come here.
Come here.
This is hard.
I love my dad.
I'm just here to write
what you tell me.
It's up to you,
okay? This is your story.
She's just here
to take some photos.
Of me?
Is that okay?
Maddy, when did you find out
that Amber was pregnant?
She told me
after the pep rally.
We both painted the tips
of my batons cherry red,
like snow cones.
What did she say?
They loved each other.
Amber and your father.
And that God had blessed their love
by giving them a child.
She said she was Sarah,
Abraham's wife,
and now she would
be my mother.
I told her no way she was Sarah.
She was Hagar,
Sarah's servant.
Hagar's baby
is not blessed.
It says in the Bible--
God says,
"Hagar's son will live in hostility
toward all of his brothers."
I told her, "Read your Scripture".
"You can't have this baby".
"I'm Sarah".
"Daddy calls me Sarah
when he puts his love in me."
I hit her
with my baton.
Shouldn't I
have make-up?
No, honey.
Your skin is beautiful.
Are you sure?
Well, maybe
just a little lip gloss.
- Here.
- Kiehl's.
It's yours.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hey.
The car's here.
I'm gonna go to work.
I'll see you in a little bit, all right?
- No. No.
- Hey. The car's here.
I want to go with you.
No. Go back to sleep.
I'll see you in a little while.
Please, I want to come
to the set.
They're kind of freaky
about guests.
You know, today's
a little tricky, so--
I won't talk to anyone. I'll-I'll just--
I'll stay in your trailer.
I'm ready.
Come on, you haven't
even taken a shower yet.
Come on, Holt. I can't
stay here by myself.
All right?
You don't know. You don't.
I feel like I'm gonna die.
Yeah,
it's the damn Vicodan.
Why don't you stop
taking so many of 'em?
- All right?
- Okay. I-- I won't take any.
I won't take any
if I can come with you.
I'm gonna be fine if I'm--
if I just am on set.
I just need to be
around people, that's all.
Please, Holt.
Then why don't you go hang out
with Hannah and Peter today?
I can't. They're working.
Everybody's working.
Nobody's got time.
Damn it, I miss Kira.
Oh, I'll go shower, and I'll--
I'll get dressed in 10 minutes, okay?
Jack Dawson
says he's not gay.
He's got The Bulldog
on speed dial.
I got the peter-eater
Really?
Prepared to testify?
That's not the way it works.
You want a dogfight?
'Cause I really don't.
Oh, don't clench, Brett.
You'll get hemorrhoids.
Hi.
Hi, Lucy.
We talked
this morning, right?
- I told you to stay on Julia Mallory.
- Yeah.
Oh, you have something
already?
I need you.
What?
I'm here. What's wrong?
I need to make sure
she's real.
Okay.
Okay, very quiet,
people, please. We're rolling.
We've got a chair for you
right over here.
And slate.
Crane.
Action.
This is all I have
for you.
Too bad.
That's enough.
And cut.
How was that for you?
Pretty tight.
Remember, I told you about paragliding
off the Dolomites of Italy.
This...
is so much better.
I need to change my panties.
Yeah.
That's what my girl likes, hmm?
You're a pig.
No, he's sweet.
He let me
crash your party.
Come on. Let 'em
kick him to the curb.
You'd do that to me, Garbo?
For her?
What do you think?
She is Julia Mallory,
and my love for her
cannot be quantified.
Subliminal Velocity,
Hell House--
Camp Crusades: brilliant.
But you-- you changed
my life with:
* All for one, and God
will have some fun *
* Come on, boys,
come on, girls *
* Come on,
let's put our mark *
* On this wild,
wild world *
* This wild, wild world *
What?
I want to play, too.
- Keep your dick out of my face.
- No problem.
No problem.
So you girls
can screw me, suck me,
spank me raw for all I care.
Whatever you want.
Julia?
Okay.
She comes with me.
* This wild, wild world *
Here you go.
Thank you.
Be right back.
Very real.
I can still smell
the patchouli.
I like
the way she smells.
Well, if you like it,
then I like it.
- How long do we have to sit here?
- Just a few minutes.
She thinks I'm a genius.
Don't I always
tell you that?
- So you're Don's boss.
- Friend.
You went to college together.
He told me.
I'm sorry. I don't
read your magazine.
Oh, it's not a judgment thing.
I just don't have the time.
Uh, speaking of time...
Julia?
I have to go to work.
Wait. To the magazine?
I thought we agreed.
Agreed?
That Don shouldn't
waste his energy on star stuff.
Have you seen his artwork,
his picture poems?
Yes, I have.
Oh, so then you know.
Well, maybe just this once.
To pay the bills.
Okay.
- We'll talk more tonight?
- Bye.
Thanks, Lucy.
He sent me here
to see if you were real.
He's schizophrenic.
He told me.
Did he tell you he writes those picture
poems when he forgets to take his meds?
Uh, I know you mean well,
but you're not really helping him.
You're using him.
I'm gonna chalk that up
to young and dumb.
Look, play patron of the arts
if that's what gets you off.
But don't play
with people's lives.
That's what you do
for a living.
Thought you didn't
read the magazine.
Only in the toilet.
Okay. Let's not
personalize this.
I'm glad that Don has a friend
who appreciates him.
And you're right.
He's very talented.
He's also
caring and loyal,
and he has
a very real disease.
He has a label
given to him by a society
that won't tolerate anything
but the status quo.
Don's an artist.
Art is born of pain.
He's entitled to feel
what he feels.
Get someone else
to cut an ear off for you.
Like you got him
to cut off his finger?
Leo.
Don't recognize me
in the burkha?
Justine Dawson.
I have to dress like my maid
to avoid the paparazzi.
Aren't you gonna say hello?
- Look, I'm sorry--
- I liked your color sense.
I'm just sorry you couldn't
keep your hands off my husband.
- Jack came on to me.
- I don't give a shit.
- I'm not the first.
- Just the first to sell him out--
and not even for the money,
just revenge.
What a big baby you are.
Here, I want you
to have these.
This is a letter from my 11-year-old
asking her father to come home.
Oh, didn't you know?
Jack moved out of the house.
And here!
Ben found this in his desk.
"Your dad
is a pipe smoker."
It's a clever drawing.
He's lighting his own penis.
- This wasn't--
- Emma's 11,
and Ben's only 8.
So maybe that isn't
much of a score.
But they will carry this with them
for the rest of their lives.
So congratulations.
Revenge is sweet.
- Watch--
- Go!
Get off me!
I see you took my advice.
Well, it was really good advice.
What are you gonna do to celebrate?
Some of the gang told me
they'd take me out for a drink.
And what about after?
Excuse me, Miss.
I was just looking for the toilet.
Hello, Bulldog.
I'd get up, but that might be
mistaken for a sign of respect.
I got a call from Jack Dawson.
Don't take the case.
I know how you hate to lose.
I will be subpoenaing your brother.
I know he's the source.
Every story in this magazine
is verified by more than one source.
Fag makes grab at movie star's pistol
and gets fired on the spot.
Big sister cooks up a story to save
his pride and up her sales.
I don't need to cook it up in this town.
I step in it the minutes
I walk out the door.
And you sure stepped
in it this time, sugar.
I'd think about printing a retraction,
and an apology.
And I'd think about that hat.
Um, you guys go ahead,
and I'll meet up with you later.
Maddy? Hello?
You have to help me.
Grandma says I'm going to jail.
I can't go! I won't!
You said it would be all right.
What-- Hey--
Just slow down. I--
I lied to you, Willa!
I'm sorry.
It wasn't me.
I didn't-- I didn't kill Amber. He did.
My daddy.
What? Maddy--
He-- He made me lie.
He told me to lie. He made me.
All right, look, I'm coming
to see you. Just stay there.
Don't talk to anybody.
Okay.
Hey. Chefs don't clean up.
- Leo, let it go.
- Can't.
- You can.
- You didn't see her.
She married his box office.
Her whole life is a lie.
Those kids are going through hell.
No worse than we did.
Yeah. Look at us.
You have to stop worrying about her
and start thinking about yourself.
Jack Dawson's lawyer is threatening
to put you on the stand
if you don't make a retraction.
Okay? You know I can't do that.
You'd rather drag everyone
through a public hearing?
Okay, I asked you more than once,
"Are you sure you want to do this, Leo?"
You said to me "You bet your ass."
That is a direct quote. Yes, it is.
- I warned you.
- You warned me.
Warning me was bullshit.
You should have said
"He has a family and two kids."
Oh, like you didn't know that?
God.
Are people even real to you?
Yes. You're real.
This is so unfair, Leo!
You have to tell me the truth.
Look, I can't help you
unless I know what happened.
Maddy.
Amber told Daddy he had to marry her,
and if he didn't, she'd tell the police
he raped her.
You were there?
What happened?
They argued.
He hit her with my baton,
then he stabbed her.
That's the truth.
You have to fix it.
You said nothing bad would happen.
You promised. You promised me!
Okay.
- What do you want for these?
- They're yours.
The negatives in the vault?
Why waste the space?
I can get more anytime.
So can anyone else
Here.
Conquistador House.
It's east of Santa Barbara.
I made a call. They'll have a bed
ready for her tomorrow.
I never even heard of it.
Total privacy, and total
commitment to recovery.
Why are you doing all this?
Two more badges, and I make Eagle Scout.
Do you even know why you stick around?
Is it love, or is it guilt?
Are you afraid to find out?
I'm not.
You didn't know her before everything.
She was always happy.
She was just--
She was full of light.
Laughed all the time.
Jesus, Holt, she's not dead.
Yet.
Lucy.
Maddy didn't kill Amber.
Reverend Sweet did it.
He forced her to confess, but
the story's already been shipped.
What are we gonna do?
Relax. We have the transcripts.
The story is solid.
But Maddy could go to jail
for a murder she didn't commit.
Okay. Get a follow-up
statement from Sweet
Is he still in prison?
Her father manipulated her
into taking the blame.
We have to do something:
insert a denial or something.
How about a press release
saying "Don't buy Dirt Now"?
How's that?
She's just a little girl. I promised her
that I would protect her.
She is a story. She's not your friend.
You protect your source.
You protect the truth.
You don't protect the little girl.
She's a liar, Willa. You know that.
She told you herself.
You both got what you wanted.
You got your cover story.
Leo. Hi, it's me.
Would you please pick up?
I want to talk to you.
Come on. I know you're there.
You know, you really
are a dick sometimes.
She's not really your friend, Don.
I hope you don't mind me saying this.
Who?
Lucy.
Lucy's my friend.
If she were, she wouldn't
ask you to sell your soul.
Is that her?
No.
Your salacious lies have put
Jack Dawson's career
as a leading man in the crapper.
Good news, though.
He's always wanted to be
a media tycoon, so we'll settle
for everything
in Gibson Horne's portfolio.
Oh, my--
Two scenarios:
lawsuit.
Process of discovery.
Our lawyers call every gigolo,
masseuse, trainer, pool boy,
and ass toy
Jack's ever employed.
All rumors, innuendoes, and impressions
become facts of the case,
and that means
we can publish them.
I mean, that should be worth--
what do you think, five covers at least?
Jack Dawson will be
America's proud gay icon.
Scenario 2:
drop the lawsuit.
Look, the damage has been done, people.
There's not enough money
to indemnify you against
the lawsuit we will bring.
One year from today...
you will all be
working for Jack Dawson.
Well,
until he fires you. Good day.
Mom? Dad?
Seen this?
She didn't do it, Chuck.
She was covering for her father.
Cops found the baton.
Plenty of prints:
Maddy, not Daddy.
That's because it was her baton.
The medical examiner
matched the angle and depth
of Amber's stab wounds
to Maddy's height and weight.
Innocent until proven guilty, of course.
Arise, my little "protege'",
and join the ranks.
I shouldn't have cut you out.
I wasn't ready.
You did great.
No, I didn't handle it right.
I let her get to me.
When it stops getting to you,
that's when you're in trouble.
You missed a spot.
You'll get it.
I don't need this.
You can help me.
I don't need to be here.
Sweetie, listen to me.
There's something I've never told you.
Please, babe, can we just go home?
You remember that day that we met?
Well, I wasn't really there to audition.
I followed you from the coffee shop.
And you got your drink, and the guy made
a mistake with your change, and...
he gave you a 20 instead of a 1.
And you gave it back.
Then I couldn't think of anyone
that wouldn't have kept the 20.
And you were so beautiful.
You were the most beautiful
thing I'd ever seen.
I want that girl back.
No, it's okay. I got this.
I got it.
No. No!
Julia, come here.
Please, Holt, please!
No, please.
Sorry, come on.
No! No! No!
- Please stop.
- No!
Calm down. Come on.
Come on.
Julia, stop.
Julia. Julia, stop
No!
Come on. Listen.
Listen.
Everything's gonna be all right.
You can trust me.
Come here.
Everything's gonna be all right.
You're not the first.
Stop beating yourself up.
Thank you.
Lucy thinks I'm an amateur.
I'm so pissed to myself.
Close your eyes...
and tell me what color you see.
It's an old trick I learned from
a-a bushman in Zimbabwe.
What do you got to lose?
Okay.
Red.
All right.
Put that red...
right there.
Now...
see it move down.
Down your shoulder,
down your arm...
into your wrist...
your hand...
fingers--
- What are you doing?
Don't talk. Don't-- ...look.
Just...
No feeling is bad if
you know what to do with it.
What are you feeling right now?
Well, thank you,
and I want to get right to
the photos that appeared
in the magazine.
How did that happen?
Tabloids will print anything
to sell paper, Tony, even
if they have to make it up.
We just don't pay attention.
My lawyers told me that I should sue,
but I will not dignify these lies
with a legal response.
Justine and I, we know who we are.
We don't have to spend time or
money proving anything
to anyone.
- Good God.
I want you to know, Tony,
this is the last time I'm gonna give
an interview on the topic.
- Never again?
- Never again.
No, no. Justine and I--
Hey, turn on the TV. Channel 4.
God's in His heaven, and
all is right with the world.
- You're pregnant?
- Absolutely.
Come on. I know you're there.
I miss you.
Show him the ring.
Jack Dawson's backing off.
He's not gonna sue.
That is a stun--
I was gonna call you to say good-bye.
You going somewhere?
Oh, my God, of course you are.
One of your little walkabouts.
You always run away.
Nothing keeping me here.
You can hide, Leo, but the old shit's
gonna be here when you come back
Look, I don't want to fight.
Where are you going?
How can I reach you?
I don't know, but if I did,
I wouldn't tell you.
Is that a joke?
Look, hon, you can't leave me.
I need to get away from you for a while.
I think it's catching. The last couple
of days, I've felt, uh...
numb.
Is that how it starts?
You can't be mad at me forever.
I know.
Justine, thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Jack, always good to see you.
They are back in the news
and yes, at it again.
But this time, Lindsay
and Paris are fighting--
no, not over a boy toy, Shaun-- no,
over an actual movie role.
Yeah, that's right, Tony.
The two scrappy vixens are battling
over which one will play the role
of Maddy Sweet in the hottest
new film property in town.
Now, Sweetis based on
the infamous cheerleader murder
in Walnut Valley, California.
You know, maybe Lindsay
and Paris could make up
and do the film together.
One could play Maddy, and
the other could play
Amber Carmichael.
You know, Amber's the victim,
and everybody says
the bad girl role
is always the better role.
- You're probably right about that.
- Maybe.
Either way, Adaptation
helmer Spike Jones
is rumored to be looking
to direct, and production
on Sweet is slated to start
as early as this summer
for a holiday release. What, a
better family film I cannot find.
Yeah. Sounds like someone
might be looking for a nomination.