Hi. I'm Don Konkey.
I'm a photographer.
Technically, I'm a freelancer,
but outside of the occasional
Cat Fancier magazine photo,
I'm exclusive to Dirt Now.
Last week, I was covering
a story for Lucy Spiller,
my best friend and boss.
- And things didn't go so well.
- Get him!
I ended up in jail.
- Don, are you okay?
- Yeah.
Not the best place for a schizophrenic.
That's Holt McLaren. He gets Lucy dirt.
With her help, he's gonna be the
next big thing in action movies.
You're gonna have to bulk up.
That's Holt's girlfriend, Julia Mallory.
With the help of her dealer, Garbo,
she's gonna be
the next big thing in rehab.
Holt's relationship with Lucy and Julia
is starting to take
a toll on his stomach.
We all have something.
Papa! No!
Lucy's dad committed suicide
when she was 15.
Now, her relationships
with men aren't so good.
Did you come the last time?
Maybe you could give me
some direction.
I could draw you a map.
It's not gonna happen.
I have better luck alone.
Good thing she's got me.
- So, we were thinking--
- If it works for you--
And this'll be exclusive.
If it works for you,
I get caught in
a lesbian affair with Chyna.
And we've already talked to her,
and she's totally in.
And once it hits, Chris will accept it.
Yeah. I accept it,
and then we move in together
as a "thrupple."
But when that dies down,
I get jealous of him and Chyna.
So Chyna and
I have Adrianne move out.
And I have to win him back.
Thank you.
That is good stuff. It really is.
You've obviously put
a lot of thought into it.
I have to deal with an editorial issue,
but you can come back, right?
Oh, sure. And just so you know,
we're completely flexible on the story.
These are just a few ideas.
Okay, great. I'll have
Kenny show you out.
- Be in touch.
- Okay.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Dude, we are totally getting a cover.
400,000 for an exclusive on the wedding,
and some waiter with a
cell phone cam scoops us?
They're crap images.
People want to see the glam.
"People want to see the glam"?
What is that, a Shakira lyric?
I want to see an exclusive!
What do we know
about this dead cheerleader?
Amber Carmichael,
disappeared at a pep rally,
found the next day in the woods
behind her high school.
Not a lot on the wires.
No arrest yet. Small town story.
How small a town?
Walnut Valley, about an hour
and a half out of L. A.
Population, 11,000.
Now that's a solid cover.
It's a great cover, but I mean,
we have about two days to close,
and we don't even have a reason
to think she had a secret life.
Everyone has a secret life.
She was murdered!
Her secret life is our next cover.
You better all get to work.
Synchro:
Metalmarco, Pasbel, Yellow Sub
Transcript :
Swsub.com
Dirt - Season 01 Episode 06 -
"The Secret Lives of Altar Girls"
Hello.
Your office just seems
to get bigger and bigger.
Same office, Chuck.
And yet, bigger.
Maybe I should do a story.
"Mysterious Expanding
Office Takes on All in its Path."
I need you on something.
You already have me up
to my ears in nuts and sluts.
I got, "Family Keeps
Pet Hippo in Living Room,"
"Idaho Potato Looks Like Virgin Mary."
- My plate's kinda full.
- I need you on a cover.
It's a crime story.
I'm sending a small army
to Walnut Valley
to get into
this cheerleader murder.
These knuckleheads will treat it like
some premiere after-party.
I need hard journalism.
M. E. reports, D. A.'s office--
I have two Polk Awards and a Peabody.
I know how to cover
a damn crime story, Lucy.
That's why I called you.
You sending me for a cover, or a story?
Meaning?
Well, you've already picked out
your headline: "Her Secret Life."
If this girl had
no secrets, fine, come home.
I'll run something else.
Girl's dead. Maybe some things
should just stay secret?
Do you want the story or not?
- Yeah, I'll take the story.
- Okay.
I want Willa McPherson to go with you.
You think a chaperone
can keep me on the wagon?
One can only hope.
She seems hungry.
Maybe she'll learn
something from you.
Like you did?
If she's lucky.
Hey.
$400,000 for exclusives on
Cheryl Lane's wedding,
and you're bumpin' the cover?
"Exclusive" being the operative word.
Pictures all over
the Internet. The deal's off.
So what's the cover?
Or do you plan on surprising me again,
'cause, as I recall,
that didn't go so well last time.
Meet Amber Carmichael.
Never heard of her.
White, attractive, murdered
in her cheerleading uniform.
- America's gonna love her.
- More than Cheryl Lane
and her fairy tale wedding?
Celebrity murder always trumps
celebrity wedding. You know that.
She's not a celebrity.
Yes, well, she will be.
Okay, guys, check with me
before you head out,
even if you have your assignments.
There you are.
Hi.
We're doing a story
for Dirt Now Magazine.
Did any of you know Amber Carmichael?
Poor bastards'll
never know what hit 'em.
Um, we're uh--
Lucy's told us to wait--
You don't have to tell me
what Lucy said.
Everything she knows about reporting,
she learned from me.
Lucy learned from you?
I was her mentor at The Trib.
Back when I was a respected journalist?
Hard to believe, I know.
Wow, you worked with Lucy at
The Trib? I thought you were like,
the Dirt spooks-and-kooks
guy since forever.
Hmm. Nice interview technique, subtle.
All right. Let's regroup.
What have we got so far?
Well, I called the D. A.'s office but
they don't have a press liaison, so--
Hmm, interesting.
Look, there's a memorial for this girl
at the local church in two hours.
Why don't we go there,
check it out, see what we see?
How did you know about it?
Big, complicated story like this?
Intricate local politics?
You really gotta know how to dig.
It's nice out. Let's walk.
Maybe we'll, uh, find another
scoop on the way.
So, what was Lucy like
when she was starting out?
I mean, what was her first big story?
How did she rise so far and so fast?
You're a one-man press conference.
Look, you want to be a reporter?
Remember this.
Everyone wants to tell their story.
You gotta cultivate your source.
One question at a time.
Sometimes no questions.
Sorry.
So, what was Lucy like
when she started out?
Kind of a little bit like you.
Not necessarily a compliment.
So we'll do the flowers ourselves.
Fine, I'll call, then.
I will. I--I gotta go.
Sorry. People hear it's a wedding
- and the prices triple.
- Not interested.
Has Don called?
- No. You want me to try him again?
- Yes.
And can you just use our florist?
We spend a fortune there every month;
it should count for something.
- Thank you.
- Are you dialing Don?
Yes.
Don?
Hey.
I love you, Don.
Local cops. They got nothin'.
How can you tell?
No one's talking to them,
they're talking to no one.
Well, maybe they're just
being respectful.
Mm, their mistake.
Killer isn't ID'd in the first 24 hours,
probably won't be.
No one in this crowd's gonna give
up any dirt on the girl.
No dirt, no suspect.
Well,
if they're not gonna give it up
for their own cops,
what makes you think
that they're gonna talk to us?
We're in a church.
Maybe we can get
a blessing from the reverend.
Come on.
Reverend,
I'm Chuck Lafoon.
This is Willa McPherson.
We're from Dirt Now Magazine.
- I'm sorry for the intrusion--
- Please,
this is a house of mourning.
Impressive.
Excuse me,
did you say you're from Dirt Now?
Yes.
A- Amber and I were best friends.
We're both totally into Dirt Now.
I mean, we were.
She was.
I still can't believe she's gone.
I'm so sorry.
Anyway, I saw you
talking to my dad, so--
Your father's the minister.
Uh, Willa has family in the clergy.
Constant chore, right?
Yeah. Totally.
Well, uh,
you probably
want to focus on the service.
Maybe you guys could
get together afterwards,
and talk a little bit. Get some
- background for the magazine.
- Sure. Yeah! Okay.
- Should I--
- We'll find you after.
Cool.
Well, you got your first
crime story interview.
God help us.
Okay, Quinn. No, that's great.
Okay, listen. I just got home,
so I gotta go.
All right. I will.
Hey.
Quinn says "hi."
If he wants to talk to me,
he could answer one of
my goddamn phone calls.
He said he called.
He wants to have lunch with you.
When's the last time
you checked your voice-mail?
Hard Charger deal just closed.
Name above the title.
Sheet!
That's--
- That's--
- Huge!
Oh, yeah, after Dawson fell out,
Johnny Gage's people were all over him,
but they only wanted me.
Three movies in a row.
All summer tent-poles.
- Babe, that's awesome.
- Yeah.
Come here.
Just lay back.
What the hell is that?
I scratched myself in the taxi.
You scratched yourself?
Let me see.
- Let me see!
- Jeez. What?
Jesus Christ, Julia.
What the hell are you doin'?
It's not a big deal. God.
I knew you were
gonna be a bummer today.
Don?
Don!
Hey.
Don?
You haven't been returning my calls.
I'm working.
You're writing on your photos.
I have to get it out.
Now, I worry about you
when you don't call me back.
Sorry, Lucy.
How's your finger?
It throbs a lot,
but the doctor said that's good.
Good.
I brought you some food.
It's your favorite soup
from Nate 'n Al's.
Okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Hey...what happened?
You seemed to be doing
so much better.
Do you want to go to the hospital?
No!
It's just police, you know.
I didn't like their bathrooms.
You're still upset about the arrest.
Well, they still might come back for me.
No. I took care of it.
The police will not come back.
Okay.
I'm fine.
It's just, you know,
it's up and down like always.
I just need to work,
you know, for focus.
- It'll help.
- Okay.
Why don't you come in on Wednesday,
and I'll have something for you?
It's okay.
You actually know Britney?
Well, it was just a little interview.
But we did have a burping contest.
Bet she won.
Oh, hands down.
This is all Britney.
Amber and I made it together.
Did K-Fed really sleep in the basement?
That one she wouldn't answer.
So who else was Amber into?
She was a Lindsay girl
all the way.
I'm all about Paris. You?
Uh, Paris.
I know, right?
We always have this debate.
Well, had.
We had it.
How long were you friends?
Forever.
We shared everything.
Did she have a boyfriend?
We're not supposed to date.
We both took
the church chastity vows.
We're supposed to wait to be married.
But now, she'll never have that chance.
Um, Maddy?
Would you mind if I borrowed this?
I'd give it back.
For the magazine?
Yeah. Do you want to see my others?
Holt! Holt.
No sorbet, extra peach and bee pollen.
Thanks, man.
Bee pollen's good for stress.
When, uh--
when things get tough at home,
I always double up on the bee pollen.
If you want I could grab a bottle
so you could bring i home for Julia.
I, uh--
I heard she's been
having a rough time, so--
Oh, you heard, huh?
Well, I mean,
the magazines and stuff, but I'm
I'm sure it's all
bullshit anyway, right?
Yeah, it is. Believe me.
- She's fine.
- Good. Good.
Um, all right. They'll be ready
for you in five, so--
Press one to leave a message.
Hey, it's me.
I'm just checkin' in.
Hey, I really hope
you're checkin' your voice-mail.
All right, I'm workin' late,
so call my cell.
Jesus, man!
- Sorry. Sorry
- Was I not loud enough for you?
- What?
- Did you just miss something?
- No. I just--
- You fishin' for a story, Junior?
- No, I--
- Are you sellin' to the tabs?
What are they payin' you?
How much?
- What are you talking about?
- How much?
- Holt, I swear to God.
It's just they're ready
for you on set, man.
They're ready for you on set.
That's it.
No, no. Now listen, the chief and I
agreed, we are not talking to the press.
On the record. It is a matter in
our local justice system.
We are gonna let
the system do the work.
Thanks. That's great.
Seriously. No. I get it.
"Let the system do the work."
It's a strong quote.
Aloof, in charge, gives the sense
you're closing in.
Have you worked a lot of big,
high-profile murder cases?
High prof--
This is Walnut Valley.
When I covered
the Blue River Killer murders--
Of course, that was 14 years ago--
It was that D. A.'s
first big murder case.
Blue R--
You're Chuck Lafoon.
I knew I knew you.
I read your book.
Did you read his book?
Uh, yeah.
The prosecutor
you wrote about, Engler, he is like
one of the reasons I became a D. A.
Engler's great. He made that case.
Th-- the fingerprint on the light bulb
in the hallway? That was genius!
He's an amazing guy.
The book-worthy cases always have great
characters like that.
A leading man making the case...
and a twist.
- You gotta have a twist.
- Oh, this story has a major twist--
No worries. We're off the record.
Come here.
Anything you give me
on deep background,
not for attribution, whatever--
It won't get back to you.
No one knew I was talking to Engler
till the verdict was in.
All right,
the M. E.'s report won't be out
for a couple of days, but the, uh,
the victim, the girl?
She was pregnant.
- Holy shit.
- What?
Lucy was right. Girl did have
a goddamn secret life.
Residents of Walnut Valley
have been shocked and outraged
to find out the truth about their
favourite cheerleader.
Tell me the networks are using our name.
We got them all different exclusives,
in exchange for crediting us
for breaking the story in the new issue.
The numbers should be great.
I'm glad we upped the West Coast draw.
Oh, and somebody please
get this guy a stylist!
Or at least some powder.
He's gonna drown in his own flop-sweat.
We're not gonna have it
all to ourselves next week.
Does anyone have a jump
on the next cover?
We're thinkin' emotional.
Victim's parents, something like this.
That's filler.
The girl was pregnant.
Who is the baby's father?
I haven't found a boyfriend yet.
Willa, stop telling me
what you don't have.
You've got an in with the best friend.
Get the story.
I'm working on it.
Just want to come by
and congratulate everybody.
Good job this week.
Thanks, Brent.
Is that next week's cover?
That's something
we're playing around with.
I'll let you know when it's locked.
We have the parents' cooperation?
We'll see.
Talk to Legal.
They're not public figures.
If they won't cooperate--
Last week, they weren't public figures.
- Today, the whole world knows them.
- Because of us.
You only worry about your image.
I'm worried about the magazine's image.
What we publish has consequences.
This case was going nowhere
until we stepped in.
If we keep at it,
we may just raise enough hell
to bring this girl's killer to justice.
How's that for consequences?
Wow. Seems like I hit a nerve.
What are the odds of that,
like one in a billion?
Oh, God.
The competition on this case
is about to get intense.
We need to continue breaking this story.
If we do, we won't get
just one more cover, we'll get five.
"Explosive Reveal
of Unborn Baby's Father."
The arrest,
perp walk,
trial, justice--
This girl is dead.
I wanna know who. I wanna know what.
I wanna know why.
Fun story, huh?
Yeah, everyone loves a murder.
Fifteen and bam!
It's over just like that.
Yeah.
You're not objective.
Excuse me?
This story.
I know why you're so obsessed by it.
Why? I'm a mad genius?
Or is it just my God-given
gift to find editorial gold?
It's the girl.
I remember way back
one night you got drunk at McClootey's.
Told me the whole story
of your father's suicide.
How you found his body when you were 15.
How you never understood why he did it.
You were 15,
just like this girl.
You said you died that day.
Your words: "I died that day."
You said that's why
you wanted to be a reporter.
So you could know the why of things.
I said that?
- You were drunk.
- Yeah.
Must have been.
You said your father's suicide
was the one mystery
you most wanted to solve.
You said it like
everything would just fall into place
if you knew the answer
to that one question, why?
Why'd he do it?
Aren't you curious?
About her life, her death?
Don't you want to know what happened?
Or have your reporting instincts gone
the way of your liver?
You can stop negating my concern
by focusing on my alcoholism.
I concede. I'm a drunk.
But you are emotionally
involved in this story and--
I'm finding answers.
Not everything has an answer.
Cheerleader muder
Her Secret life
Don't tell me you can't
do an interview.
You're sitting here getting
a makeover for Larry King.
Everything has to go throh my publicist.
How'd you get a publicist, Andy?
Anything to do with all
the coverage I gave you?
I'm not saying no, Chuck. Okay?
It's just the deal
with CNN is exclusive.
I think it's just TV, but I don't know.
We may be talking about print.
I can get a different leading man.
It's still my story.
Larry's ready when you are.
Just look right into the camera.
Wait, wait.
I'm not saying no, okay?
It's just that they're talkin'
about a book deal.
Call my publicist.
I may need a ghost writer.
And four, three, two, one--
Well?
And you want to release this?
Oh, no. Not release.
It'll be "stolen" from
her bedroom by a worker.
But not a Mexican,
'cause we don't want to be racist.
I have to be honest with you.
I don't think anybody really
cares to see this sex tape.
These are the numbers
from our VH1 wedding special.
Check out the 18-34 demo.
Boys love her.
And every girl wants a little Brady.
Plus, this video totally takes the image
thing and just smashes it on this head.
Yeah
You know what? Fast-forward
to the part where you choke me.
I pass out for at least ten seconds.
It's way edgy.
I want to see the part where you drip
the hot candle wax on my balls.
There it is.
Okay, let me think about this.
All right? And kick it around
with my staff.
- Okay. - Okay.
I'll be in touch with Rema.
- Great.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry, Lucy.
No. I'm glad you're here.
We just finished.
- Who are they?
- A favor to a publicist.
You look good.
- You have work?
- I do.
We're doing a crime story
in Walnut Valley.
I need candids of the victim's
friends and family,
school, whatever you can get.
You want me to do civilian candids.
- That's what we're doing this week.
- Okay.
What?
Not really... challenging.
Well, I think staying on your meds
and off the streets
is challenge enough for this week.
Cheerleader muder
Her Secret life
She looks sweet. Sad.
- Why? She's smiling.
- Sad smile.
She reminds me of you
when you were younger.
Wildcats, Wildcats
Fight, fight, win
And then we'd do this,
like, flip-switch thing.
It was cool.
So, what did you think of the story?
I don't know.
What? You can tell me.
It was all about the crime
and her being pregnant.
I mean, that's not her whole life,
who she was.
It didn't mention anything
about her friends, or--
I know. I'm trying to get them
to let me do a piece on that.
You know, who she was,
and her social life--
baton-twirling partner, boys.
She wasn't about boys.
She was about cheerleading,
and her friends, and church.
Maddy, the police want to question
whoever got her pregnant.
It's not their business.
Well, it is.
It's too bad, but it is.
- He didn't kill her.
- Who?
I just wish people could
remember the good things.
Us-- us smiling, like this.
You know, I think
that this would be
a great cover story.
That'd be--
And the more I talk to you, the more
I think that this was who she was
with you.
But my editor is insane
about cover stories.
There needs to be
some more information.
It just can't be background.
I don't agree with it,
but that's her deal.
So, if you know who
Amber was sleeping with--
Look, Maddy, the police
are going to find out anyway.
So if you tell me, at least I can paint
the right picture for people.
Amber did sort of have a boyfriend.
Tyler Kurta.
She wasn't allowed to date,
so no one really knew.
Hello?
Is anyone out there?
Are you lost?
I-- I think so.
Come with me.
- It's quiet.
- Yes.
Can I take your picture?
Of course.
But first...
let's pray.
You know, the book's jammed for
the next few issues, but call me;
we'll see what we can do.
Thank you.
There you are.
Char, I'd like you to meet
our editor-in-chief, Lucy Spiller.
Lucy, this is Char. She's a, uh,
a very talented singer.
Oh, I'm sure she is.
So the new issue is killing.
Just got the newsstand
numbers, 1.34.
Oh, I hate to say "I told you so."
Yeah. That's her favorite expression.
So, still exploiting
the dead girl next week?
I don't know, Brent. Still exploiting
the live girl this week?
Looks, brains, and venom.
How do you stay single?
- Oh, you know. It's a battle.
- Yeah.
Clearly.
- Shall we?
- Nice to meet you.
but, you know,
her sister's in town, so--
Yeah.
Holt McLaren.
Hi. I heard you closed the deal
to star in Teddy Jick's new
Hard Charger movies.
I did.
Great. You got a few exclusive
comments for the magazine?
Of course. Yeah.
Excuse me, fellas.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I don't know how many times
I can tell the same stories
to a bunch of strangers
that think they know me.
You know?
Party vampires. Get used to it.
Can I get another one, please?
I hate these damn things.
You got to find a way
to make it amusing.
I like to look and see if
I can find the people
who donated 500 bucks to get in,
but spent 10 grand on a dress.
Yeah, that one does sort of scream,
"Screw the homeless," right?
I'm done here.
I got a car out back.
You want a ride home?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
So, star of you own
big action franchise.
How does it feel?
The first one's not even made.
Who knows if it's gonna hit?
It'll hit.
Look at you.
That's what gonna make you huge,
you know that?
You're a really good actor,
but the thing that'll
make you pop is that
you have the look,
and you don't even know it.
If I pop, it's just
because of your magazine.
That too.
So, I guess I owe you.
Yeah, you do.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Home, sweet home.
Yeah, I can't come in.
- Julia's expecting me.
- Did I invite you in?
I'm-- I'm sorry.
- No, listen. I'm so sorry.
- No, don't apologize.
I'm glad we left at the same time.
The car'll take you home.
Thank you.
Any time.
Yo, I need you to pull over.
Yo, pull over, please!
No, no, no. Don't mind me.
I'm just gonna grab some shit
and see myself out.
Jesus, I didn't even
hear you come in.
Yeah, obviously.
Please, babe. Come on.
- Come on! We were just--
- Just let him go. Who cares?
Shut up. Holt.
Don't come near me!
Don't come near me.
Baby, please, come on.
- Listen to yourself begging.
- Get out!
Now! Out!
Honey, what are you doing?
You really have her
on a leash, don't you?
- Please, baby. Nothing happened.
- I don't want to hear it.
I'm done with your shit.
I am. I'm done.
No! No!
Nothing really happened.
All right? And it didn't mean
anything, I mean...
these pills, and
and the accident.
You did Johnny Gage on your movie
long before the accident.
No, I didn't.
I saw the tape!
- I saw it.
- What?
Well, yeah, Johnny givin' it to you from
behind in some hotel or some shit?
Yeah.
I saw the tape months ago.
Jesus!
You knew someone had a sex tape
on me, and you didn't tell me.
What kind of a person are you?
Been askin' the same thing
about you for a long time.
Look, I loved Amber.
And I'd never do anything to hurt her.
You think the police are
really gonna believe that?
Look, this is your chance to get out
your side of the story.
We never did anything wrong.
And we're good Christians, both of us.
She was pregnant, Tyler.
That's not possible.
We took the "True Love Waits"
chastity pledge.
- Everyone at church does.
- Tyler--
Look, we never had sex.
Okay, not "sex" sex.
We just--
Look, there's no way
I got Amber pregnant. Okay?
Her virginity was sacred to both of us.
That's why we agreed
I'd only put it in her butt.
There are no shots of the boyfriend.
He's her minister.
Okay, but Don, I need
shots of the boyfriend.
I can do that.
You look different.
I do?
Your hands are relaxed
and your eyes are soft.
These shots are useless.
I need you to go back
and get more.
Less pious minister,
more ass-banging boyfriend.
Okay.
Grab something to eat.
Peanut butter and bana on the croissant.
I've seen your stuff
in a gallery somewhere, right?
No. No.
Nah, this is--
This is just for me.
It's too bad. They're beautiful.
Where'd you go?
Just out drivin'.
Did you expect everything to be
different when you got back here?
What happened to us?
I don't know.
Other things just took over.
How do we go back?
I wish we could just
get out of here, you know?
Go someplace nobody knows us.
Where?
These stories always
need great characters.
A hero making the case.
Could be the medical examiner.
You can drop the sales pitch.
NationalEnquirer's already offered me
10 grand for a first look at my report.
So... what's it really worth?
This small town's just not as quaint
as it used to be, is it?
Twenty grand, cash.
And that's exclusive.
No one else sees it.
Okay.
Better be worth it.
Oh, it is.
We've I. D.'d the father
of the victim's unborn baby.
My God.
Cheerleader murder, he did it.
Rev's shocking admission
God bless Don Konkey.
He had the right shots all along.
What do you think?
I think it's not accurate.
Excuse me?
It implies he killed the girl.
He's her minister, he got her pregnant,
she's murdered--
readers will draw their own conclusions.
Off a headline that reads,
"He did it"?
It refers to getting her pregnant.
Oh, please.
The cover's a lie, and you know it.
The cover is a sales tool,
the story is inside, and it's accurate.
This is why I don't do this anymore.
I get sent in to get facts,
and they get twisted around
to make the cover work.
The guy is a child-violating asshole.
That is fact.
You can keep goin' after
everyone in the world,
expose everyone else's secrets, but
it's not gonna get you what you want.
It's not gonna tell you
why your father killed himself.
Get out! Drunk.
The wall is locked. Get it to press.
Reverend Thomas Sweet was
arrested today
for the murder of
15-year-old Amber Carmichael
in Walnut Valley, California.
Dirt Now's new issue says that
according to the coroner's report,
Reverend Sweet was the father
of the victim's unborn child.
Oh, my God, Willa.
Oh, my God.
I got here as fast as I could.
Are you okay?
Who told you my father killed Amber?
Who said that?
Look, Maddy, I know that
you must be really freaked out,
seeing your father get arrested--
It's in your magazine.
The cover. "He did it."
He didn't do it.
Maddy, your father got Amber pregnant.
I know, but he didn't kill her!
It's all wrong!
I loved him.
She seduced him.
She preyed on him.
It was her.
What?
Look, it's okay. You can--
It's not okay.
He's my father.
He loved me, not her.
What we had was ours. Sacred!
Ours, and God's,
and no one else's. That's what he said!
When she told me she was going
to have his baby, I just--
I had to kill her.
I did!
He wasn't supposed to be
with anyone but me!
That was our promise!
So I killed her!
I did it...
not Daddy.
This should be me on the cover.
Me.
Synchro:
Metalmarco, Pasbel, Yellow Sub
Transcript :
Swsub.com
::Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]
_/Yellow Sub\_
contact@yellowsubteam.com