It's fine...
Everything's fine.
Nothing's wrong. All fine!
'Scuse me! What day is it?
- Saturday.
Good.
- Good, I like Saturdays.
- So, I just met Rose Tyler?
Yeah.
But she's locked away
in a parallel world.
Exactly.
If she can cross from her world,
to your parallel world,
the walls of the universe
are breaking down.
Which puts everything in danger,
everything!
But how?!
Thing is, Doctor.
No matter what's happening,
and I'm sure it's bad, I get that,
but...
Rose is coming back.
Isn't that good?
Yeah.
- What the hell was that?!
- It came from outside.
But... we're in space.
How did that happen?
What did you do?
We haven't moved, we're fixed...
It can't have! No!
The TARDIS is still in the same place.
But the Earth has gone.
The entire planet.
It's gone.
FAR ACCROSS THE UNIVERSE...
Right now!
Confirm all stations on line,
can anyone hear me?
Have you got contact...
What was that?
Some sort of earthquake, or...
Jalandra, you all right?
Is anyone hurt? We've lost power,
will someone get the lights back on.
DaCosta, see to it right now!
- Suzanne, are you OK?
- Martha.
- Look at the sky.
- Why, what is it?
Just look at the sky!
Whoa! What happened?
Was it the Rift?
Gwen, Ianto, you OK?
No broken bones.
Slight loss of dignity.
- No change there then.
- The whole city must've felt that...
- the whole of South Wales!
- I'll look outside.
Little bit bigger than South Wales.
Luke, are you all right?
Felt like some sort of
cross-dimensional spatial transference.
But it's night! It wasn't night,
it was eight o'clock in the morning...
Mr Smith! I need you!
I wish you'd stop giving that fanfare,
you just tell me what happened?
Sarah Jane,
I think you should look outside.
I think you'll find the visual
evidence most conclusive.
It's gone dark!
It's them aliens, I'll bet my pension!
What d'you want this time,
you green swine!
Dad...
Look, you get back inside, Sylvia.
They always want the women!
No, Dad, just look. Oh, my God.
Look at the sky!
That's impossible...
That's just impossible...
It can't be...
Right, now we're in trouble...
And it's only just beginning.
Doctor Who - 4x12
"The Stolen Earth"
Transcript by evarin
www.transcripts.subtitle.me.uk
Subtitles by LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
But if the Earth's been moved,
they've lost the sun!
What about my Mum?
And Grandad? They're dead,
aren't they? Are they dead?
I don't know, Donna, I'm sorry,
I don't know...
That's my family.
- My whole world.
- There's no readings. Nothing.
Not a trace.
Not even a whisper.
Oh, that is fearsome technology.
- So what do we do?
- We've got to get help.
From where?
Donna...
I'm taking you to the
Shadow Proclamation.
Hold tight!
The United Nations has issued an edict,
asking the citizens of the world
not to panic.
So far,
there has been no explanation of the 26
planets which have appeared in the sky.
But it's an empirical fact!
The planets didn't come to us,
we came to them!
Just look at the stars.
We're in a completely different region
of space, we've travelled.
D'you know what, I look up,
and there's all these moons and things!
Have you seen them?
I thought, what was I drinking
last night? Furniture polish?
Ianto. Time and a place.
- He is funny, though.
- Gwen, come and see!
Rhys, I've got no idea,
just stay indoors.
Can you phone my mother,
tell her, erm,
oh, I dunno, just tell her to
take her pills and go to sleep.
I'll come home as soon as I can,
I promise.
I love you, you big idiot.
Someone's established an artificial
atmospheric shell.
Keeping the air and holding the heat.
Whoever's done this wants
the Human Race alive. That's a plus.
27 planets, including the Earth.
No, but what's that?
That's not a planet...
The reading seems to be
artificial in construction.
Some sort of space station.
Sitting at the heart of the web.
They're fine... Maria and her dad,
they're in Cornwall.
I told them to stay indoors.
Clyde's OK, he's with his mum.
Sarah Jane,
I have detected movement.
Observe.
Spaceships!
Tracking 200 objects.
Earthbound trajectory!
Geneva is calling a Code Red.
Everyone to battle positions!
Dr Jones, if you're not too busy.
I'm trying to phone the Doctor, sir.
And?
There's no signal!
This number calls anywhere
in the universe, it never breaks down.
They must be blocking it.
Whoever 'they' are.
We're about to find out.
They're coming into orbit.
The end of the world, darlin'!
End of the stinkin' world!
Have one on me, mate.
Right, you two.
You can put that stuff down,
or run for your lives.
D'you like my gun?
We're now getting confirmed
reports of spaceships.
The Pentagon has issued
an emergency report.
Dad, come and see!
They're saying spaceships!
- Did you find her?
- No, no, there's no reply.
Where are you, Donna?
Where are you, sweetheart?
3,000 miles and closing...
But who are they?!
Martha Jones! Voice of a nightingale!
Tell me you put something in my drink.
No such luck,
have you heard from the Doctor?
Not a word.
- Where are you?
- New York.
- Nice for some.
- I've been promoted.
- Medical Director on Project Indigo.
- D'you get that thing working?
Indigo's top secret,
no-one's supposed to know about it.
- I met a soldier in a bar, long story.
- When was that?
- Strictly professional!
- 1,500 miles, boys,
and accelerating.
They're almost here.
I'm receiving a communication
from the Earthbound ships.
They have a message for the human race.
Put it through, let's hear it.
Exterminate! Exterminate!
Exterminate! EXTERMINATE!
Exterminate! Exterminate...
No...
EXTERMINATE!
Exterminate!
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
Who are they?
D'you know them? Jack?
Exterminate, exterminate,
exterminate, exterminate...
No.
There's nothing I can do.
I'm sorry. We're dead.
Exterminate, exterminate...
Not Luke. You're so young.
Dalek fleet in battle formation!
- All systems locked and primed!
- Crucible at 90% efficiency!
The Human Harvest will commence!
Battle stations!
Geneva declaring Ultimate Code Red!
Ladies and gentlemen, we are at war!
Supreme Dalek on the Bridge!
Soon, the Crucible will be complete!
We have waited long for this
ultimate destiny.
Now the Daleks are
the masters of Earth!
Daleks are the masters of Earth!
So go on then, what is
the Shadow Proclamation anyway?
Posh name for police.
Outer space police. Here we go!
Sco bo tro no flo jo ko fo. To to!
No bo ho sho ko ro to so.
Bo-ko-do-zo-go-bo-fo-po-jo!
Mo ho.
Time Lords are the stuff of legend.
They belong in the myths and
whispers of the Higher Species. You,
cannot possibly exist.
Yeah, more to the point,
I've got a missing planet!
Then you're not as wise
as the stories would say.
The picture is far bigger
than you imagine.
The whole universe
is in outrage, Doctor.
24 worlds have been
taken from the sky.
How many?!
Which ones?! Show me!
Locations range far and wide.
But all disappeared at the exact
same moment. Leaving no trace.
Callufrax Minor. Jahoo.
Shallacatop. Woman Wept...
Clom! Clom's gone!
Who'd want Clom?!
All different sizes,
some populated, some not.
But all unconnected.
What about Pyrovillia?
Who is the female?
Donna! I'm a Human Being,
maybe not the stuff of legend
but every bit as important
as Time Lords, thank you.
Way back when we were in Pompeii,
Lucius said Pyrovillia had gone missing.
Pyrovillia is cold case.
Not relevant!
How d'you mean, cold case?
The planet Pyrovillia
can't be part of this,
it disappeared over 2,000 years ago.
Yes, yes, hang on.
But there's the Adipose
Breeding Planet too,
Miss Foster said that was lost,
but that must've been a long time ago.
That's it! Donna! Brilliant!
Planets are being taken
out of time as well as space...
Let's put this into 3-D...
Now, if we add Pyrovillia...
And Adipose 3.
Something missing. Where else,
where else? Lost, lost, lost... Oh!
The Lost Moon of Poosh!
- What did you do?
- Nothing.
The planets rearranged themselves
into the optimum pattern.
Oh, look at that!
27 planets in perfect balance.
Come on, that is gorgeous!
Oi, don't get all spaceman,
what does it mean?
All those worlds fit together
like pieces of an engine.
It's like a powerhouse!
- What for?
- Who could design such a thing?
Someone tried to move
the Earth once before.
Long time ago...
can't be...
Maximum extermination!
The shields are down!
There's so many, abandon ship.
The Valiant's down.
Airforce retreating over North Africa!
Daleks landing in Japan.
We've lost contact with the Prime
Minister's plane... Jack! Manhattan!
- Martha, get out of there !
- I can't Jack, I've got a job to do.
They're targeting military bases,
you're next on the list!
Dr Jones, you will come with me.
Project Indigo is being activated.
Quick march!
But we can't use Project Indigo,
it hasn't been tested,
sir, we don't even know if it works.
Unit forces will be exterminated.
Annihilate Unit.
Exterminate!
Put it on, fast as you can.
Martha, I'm telling you,
don't use Project Indigo, it's not safe.
You take your orders from UNIT,
Dr Jones, not from Torchwood.
But why me?
You're our only hope
of finding the Doctor.
But failing that,
if no help is coming,
then with the power invested in me
by the Unified Intelligence Taskforce,
I authorise you, to take this:
The Osterhagen Key.
I can't take that, sir.
You know what to do.
For the sake of the Human Race.
Daleks one five
reaching north corridor.
- Dr Jones... good luck.
- Exterminate, exterminate...
Exterminate...
Bye, Jack.
Martha, don't do it!
DON'T!!!!
What's Project Indigo?
Experimental teleport.
Salvaged from the Sontarans.
But they haven't got coordinates,
or stabilisation.
So where is she?
Scattered into atoms.
Martha's down.
Commence the landings.
Bring the Humans here!
- Prepare the Crucible!
- Supreme Dalek,
is there news?
Earth has been subjugated!
I mean, is there news of him?
Negative! No reports of Time Lord.
We are beyond the Doctor's reach!
Fascinating. If I had not elevated
you beyond crude emotions,
I could almost mistake
that tone for one of victory.
Beware your pride.
The Doctor cannot stop us!
And yet, Dalek Caan is uneasy.
The Abomination is insane.
Show respect.
Without Dalek Caan,
none of this would be possible.
And he speaks only the truth.
He is coming.
The threefold man, he dances
in the lonely places.
Oh, creator of us all.
The Doctor is coming...
You need sustenance.
Take the water. It purifies.
Thanks.
There was something on your back.
How d'you know that?
You are something new.
Not me.
I'm just a temp.
Shorthand, filing,
100 words per minute,
fat lot of good that is now.
I'm no use to anyone.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Yeah.
My whole planet's gone.
I mean the loss that is yet to come.
God save you.
Come on, think, Earth!
Must've been some sort of warning.
Was there anything happening, like,
electrical storms, freak weather,
patterns in the sky?
Well, how should I know?
Um... no,
I don't think so, no.
- OK, never mind.
- Although...
there were the bees disappearing.
The bees disappearing...
The bees disappearing.
How is that significant?
On Earth we have these insects.
Some people said it was pollution,
or mobile phone...
Or, they were going home!
- Back home where?
- The planet Melissa Majoria!
- Are you saying bees are aliens?!
- Don't be so daft. Not all of them.
But if the migrant bees felt something
coming, and escaped...
Tandocca!
The Tandocca Scale!
It's wavelengths used as
a carrier signal. Infinitely small!
It's like looking for a speck
of cinnamon in the Sahara, but look,
There it is. The Tandocca trail.
The transmat that moved the planets used
the same wavelength, we can follow it!
Find the Earth?!
Stop talking and do it!
I am!
We're a bit late.
The signal's scattered.
But it's a start!
I've got a blip! Just a blip!
But definitely a blip!
According to the Strictures
of the Shadow Proclamation,
I will have to seize your
transport and your technology.
Oh, really, what for?
The planets were stolen
with hostile intent.
We are declaring war, Doctor.
Right across the universe.
And you will lead us into battle!
Right, yes,
course I will.
I'll just go and...
get you the key.
Doctor! Come back!
By the Holy Writ
of the Shadow Proclamation,
I order you to stop!
All Humans will leave their homes!
The males, the females,
the descendants, you will come with us!
Resistance is useless!
- Where are you taking us?
- Daleks do not answer Human questions!
- Stand in line!
- Dad, please come home.
- They're leaving our street alone.
- Yeah, I've got a weapon!
- It's a paint gun!
- Exactly!
Them Dalek things,
they've only got one eye...
Good splodge of paint,
they'd be blinded!
We're not going! D'you hear me?
Laura, get back inside the house!
Simon! Get inside! Go!
Get back in the sky,
get back where you came from,
and leave us alone!
Dalek attack formation seven.
Maximum extermination!
- They're monsters.
- Please, Dad.
Come home.
- Halt! You will come with me!
- Will I heck!
My vision is NOT impaired!
- I warned you, Dad!
- Hostility will not be tolerated!
Exterminate! Exterminate! Exter...
- Do you want to swap?
- You're Donna Noble's family, right?
I'm Rose Tyler. And I need you.
I've tried calling her,
but I can't get through!
But she's still with the Doctor,
I know that much...
and the last time she phoned,
it was from a planet called Midnight,
made of diamonds!
What the hell are you two on about?
Look, she's out there, sweetheart.
Your daughter.
She's travelling the stars,
with that Doctor, she always has been!
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Oh, come on open your eyes!
Look at the sky! Look at the Daleks!
You can't start denying things now!
You were my last hope.
If we can't find Donna,
then we can't find the Doctor...
Where is he?!
It's stopped.
What d'you mean?
Is that good or bad?
Where are we?
The Medusa Cascade.
I came here when I was just a kid.
90 years old.
It was the centre of
a rift in time and space...
So...
where are the 27 planets?
Nowhere.
The Tandocca Trail stops dead.
End of the line.
So what do we do?
Doctor? What do we do?
Now don't do this to me.
No, don't,
don't do this to me.
Not now.
Tell me, what are we going do?
You never give up.
Please.
This is the Commander General
of the United Nations
calling the Dalek Fleet.
We surrender, repeat, we surrender.
Planet Earth surrenders.
Humans selected for testing
will follow Dalek instruction...
The Daleks reign supreme.
All hail the Daleks.
You will obey Dalek
instructions without question.
You will obey your Dalek Ma...
Can anyone hear me?
The Subwave Network is open.
You should be able to hear my voice.
Is there anyone there?
I know that voice.
- Who's that?
- Some poor soul calling for help.
- Can anyone...
- There's nothing we can do.
But look at Mr Smith.
Processing incoming soundwave.
This message is of
the utmost importance.
We haven't much time...
Can anyone hear me?
Someone's trying to get in touch.
The whole world's crying out.
Just leave it.
Captain Jack Harkness,
shame on you!
Now stand to attention, sir!
What?!
Who is that?
Harriet Jones,
former Prime Minister.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Harriet! It's me, it's me.
Oh, she can't hear me...
Have you got a webcam?
She wouldn't let me,
said they're naughty.
- I can't speak to her then, can I?
- Sarah Jane Smith,
- 13 Bannerman Road... are you there?
- Yeah. I'm here! That's me!
Good... Now, let's see
if we can talk to each other.
The fourth contact is having
some trouble getting through.
That's me! Harriet! That's me!
I'll just boost the signal...
Hello?
Martha Jones!
Who's she? I want to get through!
Martha, where are you?!
I guess Project Indigo
was more clever than we thought.
One second I was in Manhattan...
Next second...
Maybe Indigo tapped into my mind.
Cos I ended up in the
one place that I wanted to be.
Mum!
You came home..
At the end of the world,
you came back to me.
But then all of a sudden,
it's like the laptop turned itself on.
It did. That was me.
Harriet Jones,
former Prime Minister.
Yes, I know who you are.
I thought it was about time we all met.
Given the current crisis.
Torchwood, this is Sarah Jane Smith.
I've been following your work.
Nice job with the Slitheen.
Yeah, well I've been
staying away from you lot.
Too many guns!
All the same,
might I say, looking good, ma'am.
Really? Oh.
Not now, Captain.
And Martha Jones,
former companion to the Doctor.
Oi! So was I!!
But how did you find me?
This, ladies and gentlemen,
this is the Subwave Network.
A sentient piece of software, programmed
to seek out anyone at everyone
who can help to contact the Doctor.
What if the Daleks can hear us?
No, that's the beauty of the Subwave,
it's undetectable.
And you invented it?
I developed it. It was created
by the Mr Copper Foundation.
Yeah, but what we need, is a weapon!
Martha, back there at UNIT,
what did they give you,
what was that key thing?
The Osterhagen Key.
That key is not to be used, Dr Jones.
Not under any circumstances.
But what is an Osterhagen Key?
Forget about the key
and that's an order.
All we need is the Doctor.
Excuse me, Harriet, but,
if you're looking for the Doctor...
- didn't he depose you?
- He did.
And I've wondering about that for
a long time. Whether I was wrong,
but I stand by my actions, to this day.
Because I knew, I knew that one day,
the Earth would be in danger,
and the Doctor would fail to appear.
I told him so myself.
And he didn't listen.
But I've been trying to find him,
he got my phone, on the TARDIS,
but I can't get through.
Nor me, and I was here first!
That's why we need the Subwave.
To bring us all together,
combine forces.
The Doctor's secret army.
Wait a minute...
we boost the signal! That's it!
We transmit that telephone number
through Torchwood,
using all the power of the Rift...
And we've got Mr Smith!
He can link up with every
telephone exchange on the Earth!
Can get the whole world to
call same number, at the same time!
Billions of phones,
calling out, all at once!
Brilliant! Who's the kid?
That's my son!
But, excuse me, sorry,
sorry, hello, Ianto Jones.
If we start transmitting,
then this Subwave Network
is going to become visible.
I mean, to the Daleks.
Yes, and they'll trace it back to me.
But my life doesn't matter.
Not if it saves the Earth.
- Ma'am.
- Thank you, Captain.
But there are people out there dying,
on the streets.
Marvellous woman. I voted for her.
You did not.
Now enough of words. Let's begin!
Rift Power activated!
All terminals coordinated!
National grid online...
giving you everything we've got!
Connecting you to Mr Smith!
All telephone networks combined!
Sending you the number... now!
Opening Subwave Network to maximum.
Mr Smith...
- make that call!
- Calling the Doctor!
So am I!
A-a-a-and sending!
- Phone!
Martha, is that you?!
It's the signal!
- Can we follow it?
- Just watch me!
Emergency! Unknown network detected!
Subwave frequency!
Find the point of origin.
Find and exterminate!
I warned you, Supreme One...
Just as Dalek Caan foretold.
The Children of Time
are moving against us.
But everything is falling into place.
I think we've got a fix!
Mr Smith, now at 200%.
Oh, come on, Doctor!
Find me, Doctor.
Find me.
Got it! Locking on!
Harriet! A saucer's locked on
to your location,
they've found you...
I know. I'm using the Network
to mask your transmission. Keep going!
Exterminate!
We're travelling through time.
One second in the future!
The phone call's pulling us through!
Captain,
I'm transferring the Subwave Network
to Torchwood, you're in charge now.
And tell the Doctor from me...
he chose his companions well.
It's been an honour.
Harriet Jones.
Former Prime Minister.
Yes, we know who you are.
Oh, you know nothing of any Human.
And that will be your downfall.
Exterminate!
Three! Two! One!
27 planets.
And there's the Earth!
Why couldn't we see them?!
The entire Medusa Cascade
has been put a second out of sync
with the rest of the universe.
Perfect hiding place, tiny little pocket
of time. But we found them!
Ooh, ooh, what's that?
Hold on, hold on,
some sort of Subwave Network...
Where the hell have you been?!
Doctor, it's the Daleks!
- He's nice I thought he'd be older.
- He's not that young.
The Daleks are taking people
to their spaceship...
Look, Doctor, I've got a son!
It's not just Dalek Caan!
- That's Donna!
- That's my girl!
Sarah Jane! Who's that boy?
That must be Torchwood.
Aren't they brilliant?
Look at you all, you clever people.
That's Martha. And who's... he?
Captain Jack. Don't. Just... don't.
Doctor, it's me,
I came back.
It's like an outer space Facebook.
Everyone except Rose.
He is here.
The Dark Lord is come.
Supreme One, this Subwave Network,
I would address it, give me access.
We've lost them!
No, no, no, there's another signal.
There's someone else out there.
Hello? Can you hear me?
Rose?
Your voice is different. And yet,
its arrogance is unchanged.
No.
But he's dead...
Welcome to my new Empire, Doctor.
It is only fitting that you should bear
witness to the resurrection,
and the triumph, of Davros.
Lord and Creator of the Dalek Race!
- Doctor?
- Have you nothing to say?
Doctor, it's all right.
We're in the TARDIS. We're safe.
But you were destroyed.
In the very first year of the Time War.
At the Gates of Elysium.
I saw your command ship fly into
the jaws of the Nightmare Child.
I tried to save you.
But it took one stronger than you.
Dalek Caan himself.
I flew into the wild and fire,
I danced and died a thousand times.
Emergency Temporal Shift took
him back into the Time War itself.
That's impossible!
The entire war is timelocked!
And yet he succeeded.
Oh, it cost him his mind.
But imagine,
a single, simple Dalek succeeded where
Emperors and Time Lords have failed.
A testament, don't you think,
to my remarkable creations?
And you made a new race of Daleks?
I gave myself to them.
Quite literally.
Each one grown from a cell
of my own body.
New Daleks.
True Daleks.
I have my children, Doctor.
What do you have, now?
After all this time.
Everything we saw.
Everything we lost.
I have only one thing to say to you...
Bye!
Emergency!
Locate the TARDIS! Find the Doctor!
He will go to the Earth,
to find his precious Human allies!
And death is coming.
Oh, I can see it.
Everlasting death for
the most faithful companion...
Subwave Network rerouted.
New location : Torchwood!
Then exterminate them, at once!
Exterminate Torchwood!
Gwen,
Dalek saucer heading for the Bay.
They've found us.
Martha, open that Indigo device...
Lift the central panel, there's
a string of numbers that change...
The fourth number oscillates between
two digits, tell me what they are.
It's a four, and a nine,
we could never work out what that was.
That's the teleport base code.
And that's all I need,
to get this thing working again!
Oscillating four and nine...
Thank you, Martha Jones!
I've gotta go,
I've gotta find the Doctor,
I'll come back,
I'm coming back.
Don't worry about us! Just go!
- We'll be fine!
- You'd better be.
Exterminate! Exterminate!
They're here...
TARDIS heading for Vector 7,
- grid reference 665.
- But there are Daleks out there!
I know, I'm sorry,
but I have got to find the Doctor...
Don't move, don't leave the house,
don't do anything.
I will protect the boy,
Sarah Jane.
I love you.
Remember that.
Control? I need another shift.
Lock me on to the TARDIS... now!
Right, I'm gonna find them.
Wish me luck!
- Oh, good luck.
- Yeah, good luck, sweetheart!
It's like a ghost town.
Sarah Jane said they were
taking the people. What for?
Think, Donna, when you met Rose in
that parallel world, what did she say?
Just... the darkness is coming.
Anything else?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
Exterminate!
I've got you, it missed you.
Look, it's me.
- Rose...
- Hi.
- Long time no see...
- Yeah,
been busy, y'know.
Don't die, oh, my God, don't die.
My god, don't die.
Get him into the TARDIS,
quick. Move!
- But they don't work against Daleks!
- Well, I'm going out fighting.
Like Owen... Like Tosh.
How about you?
Yes, ma'am!
What. What do we do?!
There must be some medicine,
or something.
Just step back. Rose!
Do as I say, and get back!
He's dying and you know
what happens next.
What d'you mean?
Oh, no, I came all this way.
What d'you mean? What happens next?
It's starting...
All Human transport is forbidden!
- I surrender! I'm sorry!
- Daleks do not accept apologies!
You will be exterminated!
Exterminate! Exterminate!
Exterminate. Exterminate.
Here we go.
Good luck, Doctor!
- Will someone tell me what is going on!
- When he's dying, his body...
it repairs itself. It changes.
- But you can't!
- I'm sorry, it's too late.
I'm regenerating.
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~