The Tardis is in the same place
but the Earth has gone.
Exterminate!
Welcome to my new empire.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are at war.
Exterminate Torchwood!
I surrender! I'm sorry!
The Doctor is coming.
He's dying, and you know
what happens next.
He can't.
- What do you mean, what happens next?
- I'm regenerating.
Doctor Who - 4x13
"Journey's End"
Transcript by evarin
www.transcripts.subtitle.me.uk
Subtitles by LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
Now then. Where were we?
Exterminate. Exterminate.
Mickey?
Us Smiths gotta stick together!
Jackie Tyler. Rose's mum.
Now where the hell is my daughter?!
What the hell?
There now...
You see?
Used the regeneration energy
to heal myself,
but as soon as that was done,
I didn't need to change, why would I?
Look at me!
To stop the energy going all the way,
I siphoned off the rest
into a bio-matching receptacle,
namely, my hand,
my hand there, my handy spare hand!
Remember, Christmas Day,
Sycorax, lost my hand in a swordfight?
That's my hand.
What d'you think?
You...
You're still you?
I'm still me.
You can hug me, if you want.
No, really, you can hug me.
It's a Time Lock!
The ultimate defence programme.
Tosh was working on it, I never
thought she finished it, but she did!
The Hub's sealed in a time bubble,
nothing can get in!
But that means we can't get out.
Nope.
Not without unlocking that Dalek.
We're trapped inside.
It's all up to Jack now.
Report! Tardis has been located!
Bring it here!
Bring the Doctor to me!
Initiate temporal prison!
Temporal prison initiated!
They've got us! Power's gone!
Some kind of chronon loop.
Transferring Tardis to the Crucible.
Those teleport things,
can we use them?
If they've taken the Doctor to the Dalek
spaceship, that's where we need to be.
It's not just a teleport,
it's a Dimension Jump.
It rips a hole in the fabric of space.
But can we use it?
Not yet, it burns up energy,
needs half an hour between jumps.
- Then put down your guns.
- Do what?
If you're carrying a gun,
they'll shoot you dead.
Daleks!
I surrender!
All humans in this Sector
will be taken to the Crucible!
- She's bloody mad!
- Yeah, but Mickey,
if they've got the Doctor,
then they've got Rose.
And us! We surrender!
Jack's explained the base code,
I know how the teleport works. I think.
But you stay indoors,
there's no Daleks on this street,
you should be OK, just keep quiet.
But where are you going?
I'm a member of UNIT.
They gave me the Osterhagen Key.
I've got to do my job.
I'm sorry.
Martha.
What's an Osterhagen Key?
Tell me.
What does it do?
Love you.
GERMANY
60 miles outside Nuremberg.
Exterminieren! Exterminieren!
Halt!
Sonst werden wir Sie exterminieren!
Sie sind jetzt
ein Gefangener der Daleks!
Exterminieren! Exterminieren!
There's a massive Dalek ship
at the centre of the planets.
They're calling it the Crucible.
Guess that's our destination.
You said these planets were like
an engine. But what for?
Rose, you've been in a parallel world,
that worl's running ahead of universe.
You've seen the future. What was it?
It's the darkness.
The stars were going out.
One by one. We looked up
at the sky and they were just dying.
Basically, we've been
building this, um...
this, travel machine, this,
er, Dimension Cannon, so I could...
- Well, so I could...
- What?
So I could come back.
Shut up.
Anyway, suddenly,
it started to work
and the dimensions started to collapse.
Not just in our world
not just in yours, but the whole
of reality. Even the Void was dead.
Something is destroying everything.
In that parallel world...
You said something about me.
The Dimension Cannon
could measure Time Lines.
It's weird, Donna,
but they all seemed to converge on you.
But why me?
I mean, what have I ever done?
I'm a temp. From Chiswick!
The Dalek Crucible. All aboard!
The Tardis is secured.
Doctor, you will step forth or die.
We'll have to go out.
Cos if we don't, they'll get in.
You told me nothing could
get through those doors.
You've got Extrapolator shielding!
Last time we fought the Daleks,
they were scavengers
and hybrids... and mad,
but this is a fully-fledged
Dalek Empire,
at the height of its power,
experts at fighting Tardises,
they can do anything.
Right now, that wooden door...
is just wood.
What about your Dimension Jump?
It needs another 20 minutes,
and anyway, I'm not leaving.
- What about your Teleport?
- Went down with the power loss.
Right, then, all of us together. Yeah.
Donna?
- Donna?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing else we can do.
Look, I know.
Surrender, Doctor,
and face your Dalek masters.
Crucible on maximum alert.
Daleks.
Oh, God!
It's been good, though, hasn't it?
All of us, all of it.
Everything we did.
You were brilliant.
And you were brilliant.
Blimey!
Daleks reign supreme.
All hail the Daleks!
- All hail the Daleks!
- Behold, Doctor!
Behold the might
of the true Dalek race!
Donna,
you're no safer in there.
Donna?
Doctor? What have you done?
- It wasn't me, I didn't do anything!
- Oi, oi, I'm not staying behind!
- What did you do?!
- This is not of Dalek origin.
Doctor!
Stop it, she's my friend,
now open the door and let her out.
This is Time Lord treachery.
Please, the door just closed on its own!
Nevertheless, the Tardis is a weapon.
And it will be destroyed.
What are you doing? Bring it back!
Doctor!
What've you done, where's it going?!
The Crucible has a heart
of Z-Neutrino Energy.
The Tardis will be deposited
into the core.
You can't,
you've taken the defences down,
it'll be torn apart!
- But Donna's still in there!
- Let her go!
The female and the Tardis
will perish together.
Observe!
The last child of Gallifrey
is powerless.
Please, I'm begging you,
I'll do anything!
Put me in her place,
you can do anything to me,
I don't care, just get her out of there!
You are connected to the Tardis.
Now feel it die!
- It's you.
- Oh, yes!
- You're naked.
Total Tardis destruction in ten rels,
nine, eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three,
two, one...
The Tardis has been destroyed.
Now tell me, Doctor.
What do you feel?
Anger?
Sorrow?
Despair?
Yeah.
Then if emotions are so important,
surely we have enhanced you?
Yeah? Feel this!
Exterminate!
Jack!
Oh, my God! Oh, no!
Rose,
come here, leave him.
- They killed him.
- I know. I'm sorry.
Escort them to the Vault.
There's nothing we can do.
They are the playthings of Davros now.
All repaired. Lovely.
Ssh! No-one knows we're here.
Gotta keep quiet.
Silent running, like on submarines!
Don't drop a spanner.
- I like blue. What d'you think?
- You are bonkers!
- What's wrong with blue?
- Is that what Time Lords do?
Lop a bit off, grow another?
You're like worms!
No, no, no. I'm unique.
Never been another like me.
Cos all regeneration
energy went into the hand.
Look at my hand! I love that hand!
But then you touched it, wham!
Instantaneous biological metacrisis.
I grew... out of you.
- Still, could be worse.
- Oi! Watch it, space man!
Oi! Watch it, Earth girl!
Oh... I sound like you.
I sound all sort of... rough.
- Oi!
- Spanners! Ssh!
I must've picked up a bit of your voice,
that's all. Is it? Did I? No! Oh!
You are kidding me, no way.
One heart. I've got one heart!
This body has got only one heart!
What?
- What, like you're human?
- Oh, that's disgusting.
- Oi!
- Stop it!
- No, wait, I'm...
part Time Lord, part human.
Well, isn't that wizard?
I kept hearing that noise,
that heartbeat...
That was me, my single heart.
Cos I'm a complicated event in time
and space, must have rippled back.
- Converging on you.
- But why me?
- Cos you're special.
- I keep telling you, I'm not!
No, but you are.
Oh.
You really don't believe that,
do you?
I can see, Donna.
What you're thinking.
All that attitude. All that lip.
Cos all this time...
you think you're not worth it.
Stop it.
Shouting at the world.
Cos no-one's listening.
- Well, why should they?
- Doctor.
- Stop it.
- But look at what you did.
No,
No, it's more than that, it's like...
..we were always heading for this.
You came to the Tardis.
Then you found me again.
Your granddad! Your car.
Donna, your car, you parked your car
right where the Tardis was going
to land, that's not coincidence!
We've been blind.
Something's been drawing us
together for a long time.
But you're talking like... destiny.
- There's no such thing, is there?
- It's still not finished.
It's like,
the pattern's not complete,
the strands are still
drawing together.
But heading for what?
Hier ist niemand.
Was immer Sie wollen,
gehen Sie fort.
Lassen Sie mich in Ruhe.
Ich heisse Martha Jones.
Ich komme von UNIT.
Agentin funf sechs sechs sieben eins,
- von der medizinicshen Abteilung.
- Es hiess Sie kamen vorbei.
That accent, that is London, ja?
I went to London.
Long time ago.
Thought this place
was supposed to be guarded.
They were soldiers. Boys.
I brought them food, every day.
But when der Albtraum came
from the sky... they went home,
for die.
- But not you?
- I've got a job to do.
London, in those days. To see it!
So much glamour. I was so young.
I heard the soldiers talking.
Many times.
They would speak of the Osterhagen Key.
I think London must be
changed now, yes?
But still... the glamour.
You will not go.
I've got no choice.
I know the Key.
What it does.
Sie sind der Albtraum.
Nicht die anderen, Sie!
Ich sollte Sie umbringen,
am besten gleich jetzt!
Then do it.
Martha...
Zur Hoelle mit Dir!
I know.
Commence disposal. Incinerate!
Disposal completed.
This is Osterhagen Station One.
My name is Martha Jones.
Is there anyone there? Over.
Prisoners now on board the Crucible!
They will be taken for testing!
One step closer to the Doctor.
Activate the Holding Cells.
Excellent.
Even when powerless,
a Time Lord is best contained.
Still scared of me, then?
It is time we talked, Doctor.
After so very long.
No, we're not doing the nostalgia tour,
I want to know what's happening,
right here, right now,
cos the Supreme Dalek said Vault,
yeah?
As in dungeon, cellar?
Prison?
You're not in charge
of the Daleks, are you?
They've got you locked away
down here in the basement like, what,
a servant? A slave?
- Court jester?
- We have...
- an arrangement.
- No, no, no, no... no.
I've got the word.
You're the Dalek's pet!
So very full of fire, is he not?
And to think you crossed
entire universes,
striding parallel to parallel,
to find him again.
- Leave her alone.
- She is mine, to do as I please.
Then why am I still alive?
You must be here. It was foretold.
Even the Supreme Dalek would not
dare to contradict
the prophecies of Dalek Caan.
So cold and dark,
fire is coming,
the endless flames.
What is that thing?
You've met before.
The last of the Cult of Skaro.
But it flew into the Time War,
unprotected.
Caan did more than that,
he saw Time.
Its infinite complexity and majesty,
raging through his mind.
And he saw you.
Both of you.
This I have foreseen,
in the wild, and the wind,
the Doctor will be here, as witness.
At the end of everything.
The Doctor and his
precious Children of Time.
And one of them will die.
Was it you, Caan? Did you kill Donna?
Why did the Tardis door close, tell me!
Oh, that's it! The anger!
The fire! The rage of a Time Lord
who butchered millions!
There he is!
Why so shy?
Show your companion.
Show her your true self.
Dalek Caan has promised me that, too.
I have seen. At the time of ending.
The Doctor's soul will be revealed.
- What does that mean?
- We will discover it together.
Our final journey.
Because the ending approaches,
the testing begins!
Testing of what?
The Reality Bomb.
Prisoners will stand
in the designated area!
Move! Move!
You will stand!
- I can't...
- You will stand!
I can't. Please!
On your feet. On your feet!
Mickey.
Jackie!
Prisoners will stand
in the designated area!
- We can't just leave her!
- No, Mickey, wait!
What does it mean?
What are they testing,
what are they gonna do?
I reckon it's that thing there.
Testing calibration of Reality Bomb!
Firing in ten rels, nine,
eight, seven...
Behold the apotheosis of my genius!
two, one, zero...
Activate planetary alignment field!
It's the planets. The 27 planets!
But that's Z-Neutrino Energy...
Flattened by the alignment of
the planets into a single string. No!
Davros!
Davros, you can't!
YOU CAN'T! No!
Single-string Z-Neutrinos
compressed into...
No.
No way!
30 minutes... it's recharged!
I'm so sorry.
Test completed.
What was it?
Doctor?
What did it do?
- Doctor? What happened?
- Electrical energy, Miss Tyler.
Every atom in existence
is bound by an electrical field.
The Reality Bomb cancels it out.
Structure falls apart.
That test was focused on
the prisoners alone.
Full transmission will
dissolve every form of matter.
Stars are going out.
The 27 planets.
They become one vast transmitter.
Blasting that wavelength...
Across the entire universe.
Never stopping, never faltering,
never fading.
People and planets and stars
will become dust,
and the dust will become atoms,
and the atoms will become... nothing.
And the wavelength will continue,
breaking through the Rift
at the heart of the Medusa Cascade
into every dimension,
every parallel,
every single corner of creation!
This is my ultimate victory, Doctor!
The destruction...
of reality itself!
Prepare for universal detonation!
The fleet will gather at the Crucible!
All Daleks will return
to shelter from the cataclysm!
We will become the only
life forms in existence!
They're leaving!
Dad, the Daleks are going!
Going where, though?
And Donna's still out there.
It's not over yet, sweetheart.
Just my luck.
I climb through two miles
of ventilation shafts,
chasing life signs on this thing...
And who do I find? Mickey Mouse.
You can talk, Captain Cheesecake!
Good to see you...
and that's beefcake.
And that's enough hugging.
We meet at last, Miss Smith.
There is something we can do.
You've got to understand.
I have a son down there on Earth.
He's only 14 years old.
I've brought this.
It was given to me
by a Verron Soothsayer. He said...
"This is for the End of Days."
Is that a Warp Star?
Gonna tell me what a Warp Star is?
A warpfold conjugation
trapped in a carbonised shell.
It's an explosion, Mickey.
An explosion waiting to happen.
This is Osterhagen Station Five.
Are you receiving, Station One?
I've got you. That makes three of us.
Three is all we need.
My name is Anna Zhou, what's yours?
Martha Jones. What about you,
Station Four? You never said.
I don't want my name on this.
Given what we're about to do.
So what happens now? Do we do it?
No. Not yet.
UNIT instructions say, once
three Osterhagen Stations are online...
I've got a higher authority,
way above UNIT.
And there's one more
thing the Doctor would do.
-What's this thing?
- It's our only hope,
a Z-Neutrino biological
inversion catalyser.
Earth girl, remember?
Davros built those Daleks from himself.
His genetic code runs through the race.
If I can use it to lock the Crucible's
transmission onto Davros...
It destroys the Daleks!
Biggest backfire in history!
Incoming transmission!
Origin Planet Earth.
Display!
This is Martha Jones, representing
the UNIT, on behalf of the Human Race.
Send transmission to the Vault.
Continue to monitor.
This message is for the Dalek Crucible,
repeat, can you hear me?
- Put me through.
- It begins. As Dalek Caan foretold.
The Children of Time will gather.
And one of them will die.
Stop saying that! Put me through!
Doctor.
I'm sorry. I had to...
Oh, but the Doctor is powerless.
My prisoner! State your intent.
I've got the Osterhagen Key.
Leave this planet and its people
alone. Or I'll use it.
Osterhagen what?
What's an Osterhagen Key?!
There's a chain of 25 nuclear warheads,
placed in strategic points
beneath the Earth's crust.
If I use the key... they detonate.
And the Earth gets ripped apart.
What?! Who invented that?!
Well, someone called Osterhagen,
I suppose. Martha, are you insane?
The Osterhagen Key is to be used...
if the suffering
of the Human Race is so great,
so without hope,
that this becomes the final option.
That's never an option!
Don't argue with me, Doctor!
Cos it's more than that.
Now, I reckon the Daleks
need these 27 planets
for something,
but what if it becomes 26?
What happens then? Daleks?
Would you risk it?
She's good.
- Who's that?
- My name's Rose. Rose Tyler.
Oh, my God!
He found you.
Second transmission, internal!
Display!
Captain Jack Harkness,
calling all Dalek boys and girls,
are you receiving me?
Don't send in your goons,
or I'll set this thing off!
He's still alive!
Oh, my God, that's my mum!
And Mickey!
Captain, what are you doing?
I've got a Warp Star wired into
the mainframe. I break this shell,
the entire Crucible goes up.
You can't! Where did you
get a Warp Star?!
From me.
We had no choice.
We saw what happened to the prisoners.
Impossible. That face.
After all these years.
Davros?
It's been quite a while.
Sarah Jane Smith, remember?
Oh, this is meant to be!
The Circle of Time is closing.
You were there, on Skaro,
at the very beginning of my creation.
And I've learnt how to fight since then.
Let the Doctor go,
or this Warp Star gets opened.
I'll do it!
Don't imagine I wouldn't.
Now that's what I call a ransom!
Doctor?
And the prophecy unfolds.
The Doctor's soul is revealed.
See him! See the heart of him!
The man who abhors violence.
Never carrying a gun.
But this is the truth, Doctor!
You take ordinary people
and you fashion THEM into weapons.
Behold your Children of Time,
transformed into murderers.
I made the Daleks, Doctor.
- You made this.
- They're trying to help.
Already, I have seen them sacrificed
today, for their beloved Doctor.
The Earth woman, who fell,
opening the Subwave Network.
- Who was that?
- Harriet Jones.
She gave her life to get you here.
How many more? Just think!
How many have died? In your name?
The Doctor.
The man who keeps running,
never looking back.
Because he dare not, out of shame.
This is my final victory, Doctor.
I have shown you...
yourself.
Enough.
Engage defence zero-five.
It's the Crucible or the Earth.
Transmat engaged!
- I've got you.
-Don't move, all of you, stay still!
Guard them!
On your knees, all of you!
- Surrender!
- Do as he says.
Mum. I told you not to.
I couldn't leave you.
The final prophecy is in place.
The Doctor and his children,
all gathered as witnesses!
Supreme Dalek, the time has come.
Now...
Detonate the Reality Bomb!
Activate planetary alignment field!
Universal Reality
detonation in 200 rels.
You can't, Davros,
just listen to me!
Just stop!
Nothing can stop the detonation.
Nothing and no-one!
Ready? Maximum power!
But that's...
Impossible!
Brilliant!
Don't!
Activate Holding Cell.
Doctor...
I've got it.
But I don't know what to do!
Donna!
Donna! Are you all right, Donna?
Destroy the weapon.
I was wrong about your warriors, Doctor.
They are pathetic!
How come there's two of you?
Human biological metacrisis.
Never mind. Now we've got no way
to stop the Reality Bomb!
Detonation in 20 rels...
Nineteen...
Stand witness, Time Lord!
Stand witness, humans!
Your strategies have failed!
Your weapons are useless!
And, oh, the end
of the universe is come.
Nine... eight... seven...
six... five...
four... three...
two... one...
Closing all Z-Neutrino relay loops
using an internalised synchronous
back-feed reversal loop.
That button there!
- System in shutdown!
- Detonation negative!
Explain! Explain!
EXPLAIN!!
- Donna, you can't even change a plug!
- D'you wanna bet, Time Boy?
You'll suffer for this!
Oh, bio-electric dampening field
with a retrogressive arc inversion?
Exterminate her!
Exterminate!
Weapons non-functional.
Macrotransmission
of a K-filter wavelength
blocking Dalek weaponry in self
replicating energy blindfold matrix?
How d'you work that out?
You... Time Lord!
Part Time Lord!
Part human! Oh, yes!
That was a two-way
biological metacrisis.
- Half Doctor, half Donna.
- The DoctorDonna!
Just like the Ood said, remember?
They saw it coming!
The DoctorDonna!
Holding Cells deactivated!
Unseal the Vault.
Well, don't just stand there,
you skinny boys in suits! Get to work!
Stop them!
Get them away from the controls.
A-A-And spin.
Help me, help me!
A-A-And the other way.
- What did you do?!
- Trip-stitch circuit-breaker
in psycho-kinetic
threshold manipulator!
That's brilliant!
- Why did we never think of that?
- Because you two were just Time Lords,
you dumbos,
lacking that little bit of human,
that gut instinct
that comes with Planet Earth.
Can think of ideas you wouldn't
dream of in a million years!
The universe has been waiting for me!
Now, let's send that
trip-stitch all over the ship!
Did I ever tell you?
Best temp in Chiswick,
100 words per minute!
Ha!
- System... malfunction!
- Motor casing interference!
What is happening?
Explain!
Come on then, boys,
we've got 27 planets to send home!
Activate Magnetron!
Stop this at once!
Mickey!
You will desist.
Just stay where you are, mister.
Out of the way!
- Good to see you again!
- Oh, you too!
Ready?
And reverse!
Off you go, Clom!
Back home, Adipose 3!
Shallacatop, Pyrovillia
and the Lost Moon of Poosh, sorted!
Ha!
We need more power.
Is anyone gonna tell us what's going on?
He poured his regeneration energy
into his spare hand,
I touched the hand, he grew out of that.
That fed back into me.
But it just stayed dormant in my head
till the synapses got that extra spark,
kicking them into life.
Thank you, Davros!
Part human, part Time Lord.
And I got the best bit
of the Doctor.
I got his mind!
So there's three of you?
Three Doctors?
I can't tell you
what I'm thinking right now.
You're so unique the Time Lines
were converging on you.
A human with a Time Lord brain!
But you promised me, Dalek Caan!
Why did you not foresee this?
Oh, I think he did.
Something's been manipulating
the Time Lines for ages.
Getting Donna Noble to the
right place at the right time.
This would always have happened.
I only helped, Doctor.
You betrayed the Daleks!
I saw the Daleks.
What we have done,
throughout time and space,
I saw the truth of us,
Creator, and I decreed, "No more!"
I will descend... to the Vault!
Heads up!
Davros! You have betrayed us!
- It was Dalek Caan.
- The Vault will be purged!
You will all be exterminated!
Like I was saying. Feel this!
We've lost the Magnetron!
And there's only one planet left!
Guess which one?
But we can use the Tardis.
Holding Earth stability.
Maintaining atmospheric shell.
The prophecy must complete.
Don't listen to him!
I have seen the end
of everything, Dalek,
and you must make it happen, Doctor.
He's right. Cos with or without
a Reality Bomb,
this Dalek Empire's
big enough to slaughter the cosmos.
- They've got to be stopped.
- Just wait for the Doctor.
I am the Doctor!
Maximising Dalekenium power feeds!
Blasting them back!
What have you done?
Fulfilling the prophecy.
There goes the Time Lock!
D'you know what you've done?
Now get in the Tardis!
Everyone! All of you, inside!
- Run! In! In! In! In!
- Sarah Jane! Rose!
Jackie! Jack! Mickey!
Davros! Come with me!
I promise I can save you.
Never forget, Doctor. You did this!
I name you, forever...
you are the Destroyer of the Worlds!
One will still die.
And... off we go.
What about the Earth?
It's stuck in the wrong part of space!
I'm on it! Torchwood, this is
the Doctor! Are you receiving me?
Loud and clear! Is Jack there?
Can't get rid of him!
Jack, what's her name?
Gwen Cooper.
Tell me, Gwen Cooper,
are you from an old Cardiff family?
Yes, all the way back to the 1800s!
Thought so, spatial genetic
multiplicity, funny old world.
Torchwood, open that Rift Manipulator.
Send all the power to me.
Doing it now, sir!
What's that for?
It's a tow-rope. Sarah,
what was your son's name?
Luke, he's called Luke.
The computer's called Mr Smith.
Calling Luke and Mr Smith.
This is the Doctor.
Come on Luke, shake your leg.
- Is Mum there?
- Oh, she's fine and dandy.
Mr Smith, harness the Rift Power
and loop it around the Tardis,
you got that?
I regret, I will need remote access
to Tardis basecode numerals.
- Oh, blimey, that's gonna take a while.
- No, no, no, let me!
- K9! Out you come!
- Affirmative, Mistress!
Oh, good dog!
- K9, give Mr Smith the basecode!
- Master!
Tardis basecode now
being transferred.
The process is simple!
Now then, you lot...
Sarah, hold that down.
Mickey, you hold that.
D'you know why this Tardis
always rattles about?
Rose, that, there.
It's designed to have six pilots.
I do it single handed! Martha,
keep that level.
But not any more!
Jack, there you go, steady that...
Now we can fly this thing...
No, Jackie, no, no, not you,
don't touch anything, just...
stand back.
Like it's meant to be flown!
We've got the Torchwood Rift
looped around the Tardis by Mr Smith,
and we're gonna fly
Planet Earth back home!
Right then! Off we go!
That's really good, Jack.
I think you're the best.
You know, you act
like such a lonely man.
But look at you.
You've got the biggest
family on Earth!
Gotta go. He's only 14.
It's a long story. And thank you!
Yeah, I'm fine, are you all right?
Yeah, I know.
I'm gonna miss you.
- More than anyone.
- What d'you mean?
The Doctor's going
to take us home, isn't he?
Well, that's the point.
I told you.
No teleport!
And Martha,
get rid of that Osterhagen thing, eh?
Save the world one more time.
Consider it done.
You know, I'm not sure
about UNIT these days.
Maybe there's something else
you could be doing.
Oi, where are you going?
I'm not stupid.
I can work out what happens next.
And hey, I had a good time in that
parallel world, but my gran passed away.
Nice and peaceful. She spent
her last years living in a mansion!
There's nothing there for me now,
certainly not Rose.
What will you do?
Anything! Brand new life!
Just you watch.
See you, boss.
Hey, you two!
I thought I'd got rid of you.
Just time for one last trip.
Darlig Ulv Stranden.
Better known as...
Bad Wolf Bay
Fat lot of good this is!
Back of beyond. Bloody Norway!
I'm going to have to phone your father,
he's on the nursery run.
I was pregnant, do you remember?
Had a baby boy.
Ah, brilliant.
- What did you call him?
- Doctor.
- Really?
- No, you plum!
He's called Tony.
Hold on. This is
the parallel universe, right?
You're back home.
The walls of the world
are closing again,
now the Reality Bomb never
happened. Dimensional retroclosure.
See, I really get that stuff now.
No but...
I spent all that time trying to find
you. I'm not going back now.
But you've got to.
Cos we saved the universe,
but at a cost,
and the cost is him.
He destroyed the Daleks.
He committed genocide.
He's too dangerous
to be left on his own.
You made me.
Exactly. You were born in battle.
Full of blood and anger and revenge.
Remind you of someone?
That's me, when we first met.
And you made me better.
- Now you can do the same for him.
- But he's not you.
He needs you.
That's very me.
But it's better than that, though.
Don't you see
what he's trying to give you?
Tell her, go on.
I look like him. I think like him.
Same memories, same thoughts,
same everything,
- except I've only got one heart.
- Which means?
I'm part human.
Specifically, the ageing part.
I'll grow old and never regenerate.
I've only got one life, Rose Tyler.
I could spend it with you...
if you want.
You'll grow old...
at the same time as me?
Together.
We've got to go,
this reality is sealing itself off...
for ever.
But... it's still not right.
Cos the Doctor's... still you.
- And I'm him!
- All right.
Both of you. Answer me this.
When I last stood on this beach,
on the worst day of my life,
what was the last thing you said to me?
Go on, say it.
I said, "Rose Tyler."
Yeah, and how was
that sentence gonna end?
Does it need saying?
And you, Doctor?
What was the end of that sentence?
I thought we could try the planet
Felspoon! Just cos...
What a good name! Felspoon!
Apparently, it's got mountains
that sway in the breeze
mountains that move, can you imagine?
And how d'you know that?
Because it's in your head.
And if it's in your head, it's in mine!
- And how does that feel?
- Brilliant!
Fantastic! Molto bene!
Great big universe,
packed into my brain!
You could fix that chameleon circuit
if you hotbind the fragment-links
and supersede the binary, binary,
binary, binary, binary, binary, ...
binary, binary... I'm fine!
Never mind Felspoon.
Know who I'd like to meet?
Charlie Chaplin! shall we do that?
Shall we go see Charlie Chaplin?
Charlie Chaplin?
Charlie Chester?
Charlie Brown, no, he's fiction,
friction, fixing, mixing,
Rickston, Brixton...
Oh, my God!
D'you know what's happening?
Yeah.
There's never been a Human/Time Lord
metacrisis before now.
And you know why.
Because there can't be.
I want to stay.
Look at me.
Donna. Look at me.
I was gonna be with you.
Forever.
I know.
Rest of my life.
Travelling.
In the Tardis.
The DoctorDonna.
Oh!
Oh, but I... I can't go back.
Don't make me go back.
Doctor, please,
please don't make me go back.
Donna.
Oh, Donna Noble. I am so sorry.
But we had the best of times.
The best.
- Goodbye.
- No, no, no, please!
Please, no, no!
No!
That must be her! Donna?
- Help me.
- Donna?
Donna?
She took my mind into her own head.
But that's a Time Lord consciousness.
All that knowledge,
it was killing her.
But she'll get better now?
I had to wipe her mind completely.
Every trace of me, or the Tardis,
anything we did together,
anywhere we went... had to go.
All those wonderful things she did.
I know.
But that version of Donna is dead.
Cos if she remembers,
just for a second, she'll burn up.
You can never tell her.
You can't mention me or any of it...
for the rest of her life.
The whole world's talking about it,
we travelled across space.
It'll just be a story.
One of those Donna Noble stories
where she missed it all again.
But she was better with you.
- Don't say that.
- No, she was.
I just want you to know
there are worlds out there,
safe in the sky, because of her.
That there are people
living in the light,
and singing songs of Donna Noble,
a thousand million light years away.
They will never forget her...
while she can never remember.
And for one moment...
one shining moment...
she was the most important
woman in the whole wide universe.
She still is. She's my daughter.
Then maybe you should
tell her that once in a while.
I was asleep! On my bed!
In my clothes! Like a flippin' kid!
What d'you let me do that for?
Don't mind me. Donna.
John Smith.
Mr Smith was just leaving.
My phone's gone mad, 32 texts!
Veena's gone barmy,
she's saying planets in the sky!
What have I missed now?
Nice to meet you.
As I said... I think you should go.
How thick d'you think I am? Planets!
Tell you what that was, dumbo?
That was those two lagers
you get down the offy
cos you fancy
that little man with the goatee!
Yes, you do. I've seen you!
Donna. I was just going.
Yeah, see you.
You're wasting your time with that one,
because Susie Mair, she went on
that dating site, and she saw him...
No, listen, this is important!
Susie Mair wouldn't lie!
Not unless it was about calories!
Ah.
You'll have quite a bit of this.
Atmospheric disturbance.
Still, it'll pass.
Everything does.
Bye then, Wilfred.
Oh, Doctor.
What about you now?
Who have you got?
I mean, all those friends of yours...
They've all got someone else.
Still, that's fine.
- I'm fine.
- I'll watch out for you, sir.
You can't ever tell her.
No, no, no.
But every night, Doctor,
when it gets dark,
and the stars come out,
I'll look up...
on her behalf.
I'll look up at the sky...
and think of you.
Thank you.
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~