Doctor Who - Special Christmas 2008
Preview
Subtitles by Ash & LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
Mistletoe! Mistletoe!
Morning.
Go on, then!
Chesnuts! Chesnuts!
You there, boy,
what day is this?
- Christmas Eve, sir.
- What year?
- You thick or something?
- Oi! Just answer the question.
Year of our Lord 1851, sir.
Right! Nice year.
A bit dull.
Doctor!
Who, me?
Don't worry, don't worry.
Stand back. Come over here.
Woo!
I got it. Whatever's behind that door
I think you should get out of here.
Doctor!
No, it's alright I'm here, hello!
Don't be stupid!
Who are you?
- I'm the Doctor.
- Doctor who?
- Just the Doctor.
- Well, there can't be two of ya !
Where the hell have you been?
Right there, don't worry! Stand back.
What we've got here, then?
- Hold on, who are you?
- I'm the Doctor.
Simply the Doctor.
The one, the only, and the best.
- Rosita, give me the sonic screwdriver.
- The what?
Quickly, get back to the Tardis.
- Back to the what?
- If you could stand back, sir, this...
is a job for a Time Lord.
A job for what lord?
Oh, that's new!
Allons-y!