Previously on Jericho
Hello, Jonah.
Guy did four years at Lansing
for extortion and assault.
Why are you talking to him?
It's okay, all right?
It didn't have anything to do with you.
He's my father...
it has everything to do with me.
Jonah agrees to leave town
and not come back.
Exile.
Johnston, you SOB.
How the hell did you lose an election?
No, the question is how did you get
to be in charge of New Bern?
They get tired of you
being the sheriff?
No, I m still sheriff.
Just got a little more authority.
Does this thing work?
Can we get power from it?
Probably sometime tomorrow.
All right, let's get it up
as fast as we can.
Can we bust some more
of these things?
You got one of the only salt mines
around for 400 miles.
We're going to need food.
Ten wind turbines for, let's say...
ten percent of your spring crop.
Okay, look, we'll give you the food.
We're going to need ten Jericho men
to help us build them.
I didn't know you guys
were coming back today.
It wasn't safe for us there anymore.
- Where's my brother?
- He hasn't been seen for a few days.
You can't just ride into New Bern
and start breaking china.
It's a full inventory of Jericho.
They sliced it up like they own it.
They're making mortar rounds.
They're getting ready for war.
Hold it!
There was going to be
an explosion in town.
Hopefully, we can somehow
get Jake and Eric out of there.
Everybody, go!
All right, keep alert.
Jake said the New Bern guys
might be coming right behind them.
Maybe they're already here.
What is that?
What happened?
We got a major problem, Gray.
Where's Eric?
He's fine.
He's at the med center.
Well, is it about the mine?
It's a lot worse than that.
Who are you?
Stop moving.
You hear me?
I'm talking to you.
Freeze!
Who are you?
I think we killed...
six in New Bern.
I counted eight.
Who's this?
Says he's from New Bern.
Wanted to talk to you.
What is this about?
Am I speaking to Gray Anderson?
This is Phil Constantino.
Henry, you can
come home now, son.
We're still cleaning the blood
of eight deputies
off the sidewalks of New Bern,
so you need to understand
our position.
We need seven farms,
including the Jackson farm,
the Herbert farm,
and the Richmond farm.
And we need half the salt mine.
You have four hours to respond.
I don't understand.
What are you asking us to do?
Jericho is about to be invaded.
For the sake of your people,
I'm asking you...
to surrender.
Season 1 - Episode 21
" Coalition Of The Willing "
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Synchro ]
Hutch / aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
We have border patrol on duty
at all the checkpoints
and all the new roadblocks,
but we're scrambling
to cover everywhere else.
- Did you see anything out there?
- No, nothing.
What is he actually going to do?
Just march in here and
start shooting us?
We were high school football rivals
five months ago.
They tortured my brother to find out
how many troops we have, what weapons.
They have made hundreds of mortars.
My guess says they can hit
from as far as...
two miles out.
Having them and using them on people
are two different things.
That's what they said
about nuclear bombs.
How much time left?
50 minutes.
Haven't been able to get a pulse
from this baby for an hour.
Respiration is 16, pulse is 84.
Fetal heart rate is less than
five beats per minute.
Just hold the pressure.
Put pressure right there,
right there.
Press.
Harder. Damn it!
- I can't hear anything.
- What is going on?
- I am trying to save April.
- The baby's heart has stopped.
- What do you mean it's stopped?
- Do something.
Oh, Mom.
Oh, God.
Come on.
Let's get you fixed up, okay?
Come on, sweetheart.
We're not going to give anything
to these people.
Mrs. Herbert?
I just wanted to offer the town
a solution.
You cannot give away that farm.
Gray said it's too far out of town
for the rangers to help.
I can't stand out there with a rifle.
- Then I'll defend it.
- Really?
Are you abandoning it?
The bank owns half of that farm anyway.
You just...
do whatever you want, Dale.
Wait, let's be clear.
If I defend it, then it's all mine.
If you can defend it.
Dale, how are we going
to defend that farm?
Get me every refugee you can find.
All right.
Careful.
I was so scared.
When you didn't come back, I thought...
I'm back.
Oh, God!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to hurt you.
I'm okay.
Listen up! Guys!
They said you had some food here.
Yeah... I do have food.
As of this morning, I own
the second biggest farm in Jericho.
Now...
I'm going to need men to defend it
if we're invaded.
What do we get?
The promise of three meals a day.
You want us to risk our lives
for a promise?
No way.
Guys, listen, listen!
Since you've been here, you've been
asking for a place to live, food.
You came here as refugees,
and you're still being treated
like second-class citizens.
That's no way to live.
If you fight for my farm and we win,
then everybody gets an equal split
It'll be your farm.
You'll have a stake in this town
that nobody can take away from you.
You'll never have to ask anyone
for anything ever again.
So...
who wants a future?
Constantin said four hours.
It's already been four hours.
You okay?
Come here.
What do we hear from the rangers?
Runners came in.
They haven't seen anything.
Should we call Constantino?
I don't have anything to tell him.
And I'm not just going
to give the town away.
There's something I need to tell you.
It's crazy. Everybody's saying
that New Bern's going to attack us.
We don't know. Look...
Something happened to Heather.
She found out New Bern
was building mortars.
She tried to stop them and they...
they caught her.
Nobody's seen her since.
- What did they do to her?
- I don't know.
Is she dead?
Jake, is she dead?
Get away from the windows!
Are you hurt?
- Are you hurt?
- I'm good. I'm good.
Wait here.
Are you okay?
Somebody help!
Mom.
Mom!
Cover your eyes!
Jake, you okay?
Honey?
- Mom.
- Sweetheart, look at me.
- Look at me.
- I can't hear.
I know, sweetie.
That'll come back.
- We're right here, Mom.
- What's happening?
It's all right, sweetie.
Everything's going to be fine.
Let's get you to the med center,
honey.
Come on.
Get everybody off the street.
There might be more coming.
We got to open the shelters
and the town hall
and the medical center...
Move!
Constantino.
He's on the radio.
Constantino, you son of a bitch,
what the hell are you doing?
I'm sorry for your troubles.
We got a dozen injured people
on the street here.
I warned you what would happen
if you didn't meet our demands.
Demands?
I will make it my,
my purpose in life
to see that you are held accountable
for what you've just done.
Take another hour...
Do not fire any more
of those things in here!
One hour, Gray.
We need seven farms.
It was just two mortars this time.
Next time there'll be three.
Try to retaliate,
or refuse our demands,
we'll send more.
We'll do this day and night
for as long as it takes.
The patrols said that it looked like
they were fired from the west.
Get as many rangers as you can,
all right, go out there,
find those mortars.
And we are gonna take them out!
Move!
Come on.
- Darcy, are you okay ?
- Yeah, but what happened ?
It's New Bern.
They're firing mortars at us.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah!
Look, we've got to get the kids
and you got to get out of here.
Where are we going to go?
There's a safe house I know of.
If we could just get there.
It's in Montana.
Go to Montana on these roads?
What are our chances
of getting there?
I don't know.
- You heard from Constantino?
- No, no, but I...
sent out a squad of rangers
to try to take out the mortars.
I should have been with them.
You weren't here,
and I couldn't wait.
What should we do?
I don't know.
We've got to get underground, now.
Everybody!
You have got to get underground.
You, get everybody underground.
Let's go home.
Okay.
I have to get back to town.
Sam, get away fromhere.
Dad, there's more water in the garage.
You want me to get it?
That is the safest room
in the house.
It's concrete, rebar, reinforced.
That's where we should be, D.
Come on.
Come on in.
This is cool!
Sam, Allison, go in the other room.
- Why can't...
- Come on, Sam. Let's go.
But this room's boring.
No more secrets.
Those mortars didn't come
from very far off.
- How much time do we have?
- About four minutes left.
This is Stanley Richmond.
Mayor Anderson, can you hear me?
- We hear you.
- Okay,
we're about 100 yards away
from the mortar cannons.
There's two of them,
sitting on the back of a flatbed truck.
Where are you, Stanley?
We're in the woods
by the old Shaw Creek Bridge,
about two miles west of town.
There's out ten men
guarding the truck.
- They're arked in a clearing.
- Can you get to them?
Yeah, I think so. There's a path
leading into the clearing.
Tell him he's got to send scouts out
on both flanks.
There's no time to reposition.
They have to know
what they're going into.
I'm not gonna give them
another chance to drop bombs on us.
Gray, these men are not soldiers...
Johnston, you can stay or you can go,
but how this happens is my call.
- Stanley, get out of there. Don't do!
- Let go!
What should we do?
Take 'em out.
Got it.
So why now?
You know I always thought
that I could keep you safe.
But now, uh, today...
I'm just not so sure.
Nothing is safe.
Not anymore.
But, you know, in...
in the middle of all of this...
in this madness...
the only thing that make sense to me,
I mean really, the...
only thing...
is you and the kids.
It took me a while to realize
that and I'm...
sorry.
I am...
so sorry.
I missed you.
How do we know if it worked?
Come on.
Is he shot?
Sit down. Sit down.
Get him to the med center.
Is he all right?
Are you shot?
Where's everybody else?
Stanley, what happened out there?
I don't know.
We were moving
towards the mortar truck
and they were waiting,
they were waiting
on both sides of it for us.
They wouldn't...
they wouldn't stop firing.
Stanley, where's everybody else?
Where are they, son?
They're...
they're all dead.
They're all dead.
This is insane.
This is insane!
You son of a bitch!
Back off. Hold on.
Hold on.
Bailey's... now.
Stanley said the mortars were
on trucks here,
right here, just east
of Shaw Creek Bridge.
They're going to fire and move.
Check the tracks, see which
direction they were headed.
And Jake, just scout them.
We're not not going to do
anything else half-cocked.
First, we find 'em, then
we'll formulate a plan of attack.
Got it.
Just scout 'em.
I'm coming with you.
It was not a request.
All right.
From the tracks, I'd say three,
maybe four trucks
headed down that fire road.
They could hit the town from anywhere
once they get to Route 6.
Hawkins spotted a five-ton truck
coming this way from New Bern
about three miles back
Could be a supply truck
heading to the next mortar site.
We can get it.
All right. Let's go.
Stop the truck now!
Stop it!
They're all right.
Let 'em go.
You two finally turned to
a life of crime.
We're going to need
your men, Dale.
My men don't fight for
Gray Anderson.
We're asking you
to help defend the town.
We lose, you don't have anything.
If we fight with you,
we keep Mrs. Herbert's farm.
And we get the abandoned
Surrey farm also.
You already own half a salt mine,
and a percentage of every farm
in the county. Now you want more?
- It's just business.
- This isn't about business.
I'm asking you to do this for me.
We need your help.
Let's get ready to move.
They'll be looking for this truck.
Last time I was in town,
those people were trying to lynch me.
They can all go to hell.
Just listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
I've been watching New Bern
moving weapons
and supplies around here
for the last three days.
This is going to be a bloodbath.
The best thing you can do
is come with me.
Jericho's my home.
And I'm your father.
It's survival of the fastest
and strongest out here.
You think I'm safer with you,
robbing trucks?
I haven't lost a man yet.
And if New Bern doesn't get Jericho,
somebody else will.
Come with me.
Give us the maps,
help us take out the mortars,
help us fight.
We'll give you half.
Half of all weapons,
food and fuel that we take.
And if New Bern's army's as
big as you say it is,
you'll do whole lot better than
hitting one truck at a time out here.
You got more of me in you
than you're ever going to admit.
Change of plans!
When the federal government
comes back, we have our deeds.
We get our farms back then.
What if the government
doesn't come back?
What if this is the way it stays?
But they are coming here
intent on killing us.
Gray says we're only
three farms away from a deal.
And besides,
we're not prepared to fight.
I will get us prepared.
You talk to those farmers,
you don't let them give in.
Who else you got willing
to fight, Johnston?
The cops?
The rangers?
Dad?
There are 11 potential mortar sites.
Question is, which one is next?
Driver said... this one.
If we can trust him.
How were the trucks guarded?
- They have men hidden in the brush.
- I'm not sure I'm taking your deal.
They have nearly 30 guys guarding
that mortar truck.
I see nine here.
Gray's got the seven farmers he needs.
He's going to call New Bern
and give them up.
Surrenders those farms,
New Bern will occupy them in 30 minutes.
We'll never get rid of them.
So, what do we do?
I guess I'm about to make
a deal with the devil.
You flatter me.
get back over to town hall,
do whatever it takes,
but don't let Gray make that call.
What do you mean, do whatever
it takes? What are you saying?
I'm saying it's time to pick a side.
Why'd you bring Grey in here?
They just want to talk
to you for a second.
Don't make that deal
with Constantino.
It's not a debate.
If you make this deal, they're not
going to stop with seven farms.
People are going to starve
to death, Gray.
And that's if they don't kill us
outright when the food gets scarce.
I need you to leave.
- Now!
- Come on, Gray.
Why are you so ready to give up?
I almost gave my life
for this town, Gray.
You better listen to me,
you understand?
- It wasn't your fault those men died.
- Get 'em out of here!
Get them out of here!
You're going to listen
to what I have to say.
It's not your fault.
Calm down!
Put 'em down!
We have men out there, Gray.
What?
We have men out there.
Put 'em down!
- Brooks, put 'em down!
- You, too. Put 'em down..
Who is out there ?
Who is out there and
what are they doing?
Jake, Hawkins, my dad.
And they're going to try
and take out the mortars.
The three of them?
What do they think they're going to do?
You cannot give up those farms.
- Do you understand?
- We can't fight!
We can't fight.
You saw what happened this morning.
We're not ready for this.
I have been talking to Constantino,
and I promised him that
we will not retaliate
if he just gives us time
to put this deal together.
We've got maps of all
of New Bern's positions.
- Supply line, everything.
- Where did you get this stuff?
We've got trucks. We've got fuel.
We've got guns.
What are you talking about?
Where did you get all this?
Jonah Prowse is fighting with us.
He's got about 30 men
fighting with him. 30 men!
Well, they can get us all killed.
This is New Bern. Over.
Don't go near that radio, Gray.
Mayor Anderson, are you there?
Johnston Green, right?
Two years ago,  you came over
to New Bern and finished fourth
in a bass fishing contest
up at Big Hill Lake.
I finished second.
Let's go.
Mayor Anderson,
your time is running out.
She tried to tell Constantino
that I did not send them out there.
Gray, don't make that deal.
Buy some time to take out those mortars.
Negotiate with Constantino.
So, we pop out of here,
it gets bad, Jonah going
will have our backs, right?
You are filling me
with confidence, Jake.
Emily's with him.
He'll be there.
Mayor Anderson, are you there?
Yeah, I'm here, Phil.
What's your decision?
You're a good businessman, Gray.
You know how to do it.
Well, we don't want to fight.
So,
what about the... Levine
and Hides Dairy farms,
in-instead of the Richmond farm?
That's less acreage.
Yeah, I know, but...
then you would have a dairy
and a soybean farm,
and also Hides has 50 acres of corn,
and I got to tell you, that deal would
be a lot easier to sell to my people.
Where you been?
Supposed to be here three hours ago.
I got sniped at by
a gang over near Calvert.
Had to come all the way back around
through... back through Van Ness.
Got a half a barbecued venison in back.
You're kidding?
God, we need it.
We got chow!
We'll eat in shifts.
Don't pull everybody off
the perimeter at the same time.
Don't move.
And drop your weapons.
Get in the truck.
Move!
My people are telling me
that all the cattle out
at Hides farm have been
slaughtered for food.
Really?
I don't think so, but
I can find out for you.
Let's talk about the salt mine now.
You've already got 25% of the mine.
Can't we just leave it at that?
What are you doing, Gray?
What are you talking about?
This negotiation is over.
No, Phil, come on.
30 seconds, Gray,
or I send more mortars.
We almost have a deal here, Phil.
Come on!
They're here!
They're in the camp!
I'm closing the camp!
Come on. Get up there!
Where the hell is Jonah?
He doesn't want to get hit
in our crossfire.
Cease fire!
Stop!
This one's yours.
Meet you back at the camp.
Wait.
What are you talking about?
Deal's changed.
The hell it has.
It's a new split:
I get all the weapons, the food,
the fuel, the guns, everything.
- Deal's 50-50.
- And what do we get?
You get to have bombs
not falling on your head.
Listen here, Jonah...
This is about to get a lot worse.
We need those guns!
Why are you doing this?
You owe me a lot more than that!
I am a thief, not a soldier.
You promised you'd help us.
Look, you shouldn't be near me.
You're a schoolteacher, kid.
A schoolteacher.
Go on.
We're just gonna let him go?
We need those guns.
Guns.
Guns are easy.
You had this the whole time
and you didn't say anything?
I never thought I was gonna call
this town my home.
Let's get them loaded up.
What's he doing?
Why hasn't he fired the mortars?
Did we take them out?
He would have come back
on the radio.
We took out the mortars.
Hell, yeah.
Are you there?
Now, you've brought this on yourself.
There's no deals, no mercy.
We're coming.
This means war.
Do you hear me, Gray?
I need your help.
Stanley, get me every
runner you can find.
I want to get orders out
to all the patrols.
Most of you have no idea what to do
or what's coming.
Some of you do.
This isn't a fight about land
or about this town.
This is a fight for our very existence.
Pray for each other.
While you're at it, pray for the men
and women of New Bern.
Pray that God forgives us.
Every able-bodied person...
who needs a gun...
16 years of age or older...
line up.
[ www.seriessub.com ]