Transcript: Raceman Synchro: ikpko
www.forom.com
(When there's nowhere else to run)
(Is there room for one more son?)
(One more son)
(If you can hold on)
(If you can hold on...)
(hold on)
(I wanna stand up,)
(I wanna let go)
(You know, you know,)
(no, you don't, you don't)
(I wanna shine on in the hearts of men)
(I want a meaning from the back of my broken hand )
(Another head aches, another heart breaks)
(I'm so much older than I can take... )
...is high on Capital Hill
as an emergency session of Congress
prepares to hear the President address the issue
of global violence.
Recent attacks have pushed this administration
to take extreme action
raising more fears than it's alleviated.
With global tension rising,
the President is taking a risky step
by confronting what some political observers...
Oh, I can't believe it.
Jake Green.
How you doing, man?
--When did you get back to town?
--Just now.
Is that Bonnie?
You grew up.
Wait a minute, where the hell you been?
You know, around.
--Jake, no one's been around for five years.
--The Army.
--I've been in the Army.
--Good for you.
--Who's that?
--She's from the IRS.
--IRS? Audit IRS?
--Yeah.
--Not going well?
--No. Forget it.
How about you and I, we go out
tonight and we catch up?
I'd love to, but I just came in
to see my grandfather, and
--I've got to get back, so...
--Okay.
Bonnie.
Bonnie, we need a pie.
One strawberry rhubarb.
Welcome back to Jericho, Jake.
His wife is lovely,
but I don't know about him.
Mrs. Olsen made me promise not to tell,
but she heard that he bought the old Thompson
place in cash.
Cash.
--That color looks really good on you.
--I know.
--Why didn't your mom take you to New York?
--'Cause she hates me.
What are you looking at, loser?
I could be shopping in SoHo right now
instead of Gracie's Market.
--I know. Look at this thing--
--so ugly.
--Promise not to tell?
--Promise, Mrs. Leigh.
What about you, Jake?
Where have you been keeping yourself?
I've been playing minor league baseball.
Oh, is that a fact?
Well...
when do you get in from Chicago?
All right.
Good. I'll pick you up.
I love you, too.
--Hey.
--Sorry, hi. Um...
What are you doing here?
I just came in for the day to visit my grandfather,
--see the family.
--Yeah, of course, sure.
--I just didn't hear.
--Anyway, how you been?
Mom tells me you're teaching at the high school now.
--Yeah, it's weird, huh?
--Yeah.
I love it.
I just bought a house in the Pines.
The East Side on a teacher's salary?
Uh, my-my fianc?
he's in banking, so...
--Oh, that helps.
--Yeah, Roger really loves it here.
Well, I'm happy for you, Emily.
--How about you, you got somebody?
--No.
--I'm sorry, I shouldn't...
--No, you're not, you love it.
--Where have you been?
--The Navy.
Oh, why do I even bother?
Seriously...
where have you been?
(And you ask me what I want this year)
(And I try to make this kind and clear)
(Just a chance that maybe we'll find better days )
('Cause I don't need boxes wrapped in strings)
(And desire and love and empty things)
(Just a chance that maybe we'll find better days)
(So take these words..)
Oh, Jake!
Oh, honey!
--Oh, you're home!
--You're choking me, Mom.
I thought I heard an annoying voice.
--Hey, brother.
--Good to see you.
('Cause tonight's the night the world begins again.)
I'm not here to interfere with your campaign, Dad.
All  I want is your signature,
then I'll visit Grandpa...
After five years, Jake,
that's all you have to say to Dad?
--It's none of your business, Eric.
--It is his business, it is all our business.
--What you put this family through...
--Johnston. For god's sake.
--Now, he could've been...
--We could spend a week talking about what
I could've been, all right?
I've  apologized.
I've made amends.
This is me now.
--I have a plan, but I need my money to make a clean start.
--It's not your money,
--it's your grandfather's money.
--I know, but he gave it to me for a reason.
And he gave me authority over it for a reason.
--You convince me you're leading a more
productive life and then...
--That's right, Jake.
We  were both born on third base.
Quit pretending you hit a triple.
--Now, when are you going to realize
I'm 32-years-old.
--When you do.
Can I talk to my mayor then, huh?
Let's go see your grandfather.
--I just...
--Stop it, Jake.
--The one thing I can't...
--You would have been here if you could.
I brought money.
--Here.
--I can't, Mom.
--I'll talk to your father.
--He doesn't get it.
--Because you won't tell him
why you really need the money.
--Mom.
You don't give him enough credit.
--Your dad's had a few trials of his own, you know?
--He can never know.
Just...
--Stay one more day.
--I got to get back to San Diego by tomorrow.
--Mom, one more thing.
--Hmm?
You have clumsy hands.
I love you.
Be careful now, okay?
Mr. Speaker, the President of the United States.
Do I have to watch this?
(Old McDonald had a farm E-I-E-I-O)
Yeah, well, we finally found
a garage where we can fix it.
We had to take a detour.
...ocean of hatred...
Feel like I'm back in D.C.
...in our great nation, and yet,
we all know that these divisions
pale in comparison
to the fundamental dangers
posed by the threat of terror.
We have an eternal commitment
to leave the world
a better place for our children and grandchildren.
This has always been our promise and this
will always...
Five, four, three, two, one.
We'll be back in an hour, Mr. McVey.
Mr. McVey? Hello?
...carried on...
We have...
No fun, Woody.
You have to hide better!
Woody?
What are you looking at?
Look! Look it!
Hurry on there right now.
Yeah, you better hurry up and get on home then.
Where's Cody?!
Has anyone seen Cody?
We haven't got time.
Shh.
Gail, what's going on?
Oh, Johnston.
Nothing.
All right, it looks like the explosion
came from the west,
maybe Denver.
Jimmy, get on the radio.
I want everybody at the sheriff's station.
--I'll pick up Eric. Let's move.
--All right.
Dad, don't leave.
Come here.
I'll be back real soon, all right?
Johnston.
Jake.
We'll find him.
We're bringing them out of the mine,
five at a time like always.
No need to start a panic.
--You're just trying to get another
hour's work out of my men!
--Stop it, the both of you.
Norman, get everybody out of the mine immediately.
And Shep, help him for a change.
--Sheriff? Chief?
--Yeah?
--Damage, fires, buildings?
--Nothing, Mr. Mayor.
--The town's fine.
--Well, let's hope you're right.
What does that mean?
Do we have any Geiger counters?
Excuse me?
Uh, excuse me.
Did something happen?
So, what does the emergency plan say?
Contact the governor, National Guard
and state troopers.
--Are we under attack?
--Son, I don't want to hear that word again.
Now look, this could have been a test.
It could have been an accident.
There's, uh, military bases near Denver.
One explosion does not make an attack.
If we stay calm,
the town stays calm, okay?
Oh.
--I found the Geiger counters.
--Thanks.
Oh, Grey, good to see you.
--We can use the extra help.
--Well, thank you, Johnston, Eric.
--Well, what can I do to help?
--We'll let you know.
Does it work, Dad?
Looks okay.
Mr. Mayor.
--Sheriff-- the bomb?
--Yes, ma'am, so far there's no sign
of any radiation.
--We'll keep checking around town.
--No. No, sir.
The school bus isn't back from
the field trip with my daughter.
--Well, do something!
--I got it.
--You-You should be out there looking for Stacy.
--Yes, ma'am. Ma'am, Teresa,
this is the first we've heard of it,
but we will deal with it, all right?
--Just please don't worry.
--That's easy for you to say.
You don't have a child out there.
So the school bus was here at the caves.
Now, who can tell me where they might have
gone for repairs?
--Well, there's Wilson's garage off 160.
--Or Cedar Run Road.
Principal Movey said they took a detour
before the phone cut out.
Well, I figure two teams.
There's only so many places they could be.
--Now, what about the parents?
--Right, right.
Folks. Folks! Folks.
Now,  look, I know that every part of you
wantsto just rush out there.
I don't blame you.
But as your friend, I'm asking you to
think about that.
You're safe here.
Now, what if, God forbid,
you go out there, and you get stranded,
and your child comes back an orphan?
You know the sheriff and his men.
You know they'll find your kids, so please.
Help!
Mister!
Mister, please!
What? What is it?
Mister, help!
--Mister, please!
--I think they're...
I think they're dying!
That's fine.
Let's go find out.
Jimmy, get over there and calm those folks down.
Hey, Pete, come on!
We have our frequencies, sir,
but outside, it's like there's no one there.
All right, um...
what about analog?
We could contact the governor
with a Ham radio, couldn't we?
That could work, but there's only one in town
that I know of.
I was afraid you were going to say that.
Excuse me, Sheriff?
Robert Hawkins.
Well, it's good to meet you, Mr. Hawkins,
but as you can see, we've got our hands full.
Could you use an extra man?
No civilians, mayor's orders.
But I used to be a cop-- St. Louis.
--Do you know the roads around here?
--No, just moved to town.
Then I'm afraid you'd just slow us down,
I'm sorry.
You might want to get some black spray paint.
You know, cover that?
Look, I know you're telling people
it was an accident,
and I hope it was,
but if it was an attack, Sheriff,
and there's chaos out there,
you might not want the wrong people knowing
that Jericho is still here.
With all due respect, Mr. Hawkins,
this is not St. Louis.
--Dad, are you okay?
--Yeah, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Oh, Oliver, would you stop that?
Sorry, Johnston.
Thought you were aliens.
Well, we're under attack by aliens, don't you know?
Yes, we do. That's why we're here.
--Do you have your Ham radio?
--Yeah.
--For you, 50 cents.
--Oliver.
--Well, I need my 50 cents.
--Okay.
Let me get you change.
Hi, Dale. Sorry I didn't call sooner, Angel
but we decided to stay in the city
an extra couple of days.
--Put down the phone and come to bed.
--Honey, stop that. It's my kid.
--Baby, what are you staring at out the window?
--Get over here and look at this!
What-What is that?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Hi, Dale. Sorry I didn't call sooner, Angel,
but we decided to stay in the city
an extra couple of days.
--Put down the phone and come to bed.
--Honey...
...but we decided to stay in
the city an extra couple days.
Put down the phone and come to bed.
Hon... Hi, Dale. Sorry I didn't call sooner, Angel
but we decided...
Hi, Dale. Sorry I didn't call sooner, Angel
but  we decided to stay in
the city an extra couple days.
--Put down the phone and come to bed.
--Honey, stop that. It's my kid. Baby...
--How could we lose power?
--I don't know.
Bomb could have fried the relays.
--That's possible.
--Maybe.
They could've blown up the power station for all we know.
Guys, it was probably just a drain on
the system from Denver.
You a science teacher?
--Robert Hawkins.
--Chief Carroll.
--Hey.
Jimmy, what's your 20?
Willow Creek, Sheriff.
There is nothing in sight.
The deer went crazy and started running
all over the road.
All right, just don't look at it.
Is he alive?
Yeah.
--Are you okay?
--Yeah.
I think my leg is broken.
--Can you feel your toes?
--Yeah.
Don't worry about me.
Worry about them.
Is anybody hurt?
Huh? Anybody?
Stacy's sick.
She can't breathe.
What's wrong?
What happened?
When the bus stopped,
she was like this.
It's okay, Stacy, let me see.
Let me see it?
Can I see?
Let me just see, Stacy.
It's okay. It's okay.
Do you have an ice pack?
We've got to stop the swelling now.
Lucas, the first aid kit is under the seat.
You're okay.
Come on, it's all right.
Just keep breathing.
Breathe normally, all right?
It's okay. It's okay, you're fine.
Just keep breathing normally.
Okay, you're okay.
You're okay.
Please.
Calm down, calm down.
Hey? Hey, Stacy?
No, no, no. No.
Think. Think.
Think.
All right.
Look, I need everyone's help right now.
Who has a pen?
Does anyone?
Does anybody have a pen?
All right, I need a pen.
--We have pencils.
--No, I need a tube.
Something hollow, um...
A straw.
--I have a straw.
--Here, let me see it.
Let me see it, come on.
That's too thin.
Does anyone else have a juice box?
--I do!
--All right, get them out, get them out.
Get some Band-Aids out.
--What's your name?
--Julie.
All right, everybody give your straws to Julie.
Okay? Hurry, quick.
Make them into a circle.
All right, you got that?
There you go, now tape them
together with those Band-Aids.
Come on, Stacy.
All right, who's the strongest kid?
You. I need you to hold her shoulders down,
in case she wakes up. All right?
Don't look.
Where's my straws?
Come on, come on.
Breathe for me, okay? Please?
Come on. Come on.
Wait,  I see something.
--Okay, okay, we see the bus.
--Uh, good.
--You want us?
--No, no, you keep looking for Jake.
Let's get down there, boys.
How'd you learn how to do that?
Uh, military school.
Were you a soldier?
No, a screw up.
Sheriff.
Sheriff, look at this.
It's the wrong bus!
Riley, Riley get over here!
Riley!
Oh, great.
Where's the damn rescue party?
Oh, hi, Dale.
Come on in, honey.
Come on, we're all trying
to get through this together.
Hi, Dale.
You okay, honey?
What you got there?
It's my mom.
Hi, Dale, sorry I didn't call sooner, Angel
but we decided to stay in the
city an extra couple days.
--Put down the phone and come to bed.
--Honey, stop that, it's my kid.
Baby, what are you staring at out the window?
Get over here and look at this!
What, what is that?
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Oh, Dale, I am so sorry.
I didn't know your mother was in Denver.
She wasn't in Denver.
She was in Atlanta.
Oh, my God.
I'm sure that they'll have some answers.
How is she?
We have to get her back.
Right here. Right here.
Miss Lisinski, are we going to
have school tomorrow?
We'll figure it out, honey.
I vote no.
Dale, Dale, what are you doing, honey?
Please, please don't steal from me.
Dale!
--Ready?
--Yeah, yeah.
Hey, you got extra there?
First come, first serve.
You filled up your truck, you
going to mow your lawn, too?
--I've got a family, you know?
--We've all got families.
Come on.
Get your hand off the can.
What do you think you're doing, hmm?
--What are you doing?
--What's your problem?
All right, everybody sit down.
Hurry.
Food won't go rotten as long
as the weather stays cool.
Hopefully the power will be fixed by then.
Thank you for this, Dale.
Anything for you, ma'am.
--Step away from the car.
--Get out of the car.
--Hey, hey, hey, hey, come on,
--break it up.
Get off.
You need to get some lights on
before people start losing it.
All we have is lanterns and flashlights.
That's not enough to light up
the street though.
But your town does roadwork at night, right?
Excuse me.
--The machine doesn't work.
--Well, you guys have to pay cash or something!
You sure you're not the science teacher?
Chief, we got a little problem
down here at the gas station.
We need your help right away.
--I'm on my way.
--I got this.
--I'll come with you.
--All right, thanks.
Sir.
Something's going on at the gas station.
Big crowd.
Looks like trouble.
Gonna need help down here.
--Dad.
--I heard.
Go, go.
--Sara?
--It's okay.
Honey?
I don't have time right now.
--Some damn fool...
--Johnston.
--What?
--Listen to me.
Dale Turner's mother died
tonight in another explosion.
Atlanta.
Oh, my God.
Sheriff?
Yeah, there's no sign of Jake out here
in fact, there's, uh, no sign of anybody.
We're going to,
we're going to head back.
Let me know if the kids need anything
Sheriff, you there?
Stay awake.
Stay awake, don't--
Does this bus have a gas can?
If the bus...
If it stops...
Okay.
Kids, listen to me.
If the bus stops again,
we're going to need you to walk back to town
and get help, okay?
I don't know where we are.
When we get to the stop sign,
turn left, all right?
Take a left.
Which way is left?
Hold up your hands...
stick out your thumbs.
The one that makes the L,
that's your left.
Get your hands off me!
Do something, will you?
County Edwards! Carl! Carl!
Stop it right now!
Yeah, Morty, I'm talking to you!
Michael Stevenson.
Carl Meeks... Carl!
Why are you turning on each other?
Stealing from your neighbors?
You are fighting the wrong people!
We are literally in the dark.
All I'm saying is that I-I think
we need to get organized.
I...
I don't know where the mayor is,
but maybe it's time we came up
with a plan ourselves.
What's going on, Gray?
We making speeches?
With all due respect, Mr. Mayor
we have a missing bus,
no police,
firemen doing policemen's job.
--How dare you politicize it!
--Eric. Eric.
I'm not talking to my opponent
I'm talking to my mayor.
Now, I don't care about the election
I care about survival.
We just might be on our own here,
and I need to know what my mayor intends to do!
Folks, I know we've been through a lot tonight.
I want to tell you something.
I've been to big cities and
I've been to foreign countries,
--but I will take the good people of--
--The good people of Jericho
over any other city
we know, Mr. Mayor, we've heard the speech.
Well, Shep, I hope you don't think
I've been asleep at the switch.
We had all hoped this was an accident
but the unfortunate truth is
there was another explosion in Atlanta.
--What?
--Oh, my God.
--I been busy trying to contact the governor.
--Yeah? Well, what if the governor's dead?
There is no report of anything happening in Topeka.
--How are we going to get reports
without television?
--Or no phones?
What about New York?
--We don't know anything about New York.
--When are we going to get the power back on?
--Is the drinking water okay?
--One at a time, please.
--Calm down.
--Calm down? My boy is still out there.
The sheriff is out there right now
looking for your boy and my boy.
What if we had more police officers out there?
--We need to know what you're going to do now.
--No one can answer that.
Help them! Help them!
It's Stacy.
Hey, there, little one.
--You're okay.
--I got you.
What's your name?
--Heather.
--Jake.
--Nice to meet you, Jake.
--You, too.
Mommy!
--I missed you so much.
--I love you.
Hey, Buddy.
Dad, there was this deer...
Mommy's right here.
I'm right here, honey.
Everything's going to be okay.
--Jake.
--Mom.
--Oh, your face.
--I'll be all right.
--Oh, honey.
--You okay?
Of course.
Eric, help your brother.
--Put your arm around me.
--Careful. Careful.
Easy. Easy.
Okay.
--Eric, get April.
We'll meet you the medical center.
--Okay.
Hey, hey, there's an empty
prison bus out there.
--Whereabouts?
--Cedar Run.
All right, just relax.
I'll take care of it.
--God! Look at you. You're a mess.
--It's fine.
--Stop worrying about me.
--Well, good luck with that.
Hey, Shep?
You said earlier that you had
heard that speech before.
Ever ask yourself why I say it?
'Cause I happen to trust you people.
'Cause I love my town.
Now, something happened in Denver, in Atlanta,
and it could be that we wake up
and we find out that's where it stopped.
But, until we know,
are we going to use our imaginations
to solve problems
or to cause them?
We can find out how big this thing is.
If we have to, we can fight.
We can fight anybody.
We can fight all enemies.
The only way that's going to happen
is if we work together.
Now, go on home.
We'll meet tomorrow at the town hall.
And, folks,
don't you break my heart again.
Chief, keep all the men at their posts
until the sheriff gets back.
Hey, Shep.
I was afraid I was never going
to see you again.
Come on. You think I'd
let Dad have the last word?
Hey.
Quit talking about me.
You did a great thing out there tonight.
Thanks.
Your grandfather would have been proud.
I'm going to go see what's
taking these guys so long.
You know, I go away for a few years
and the town goes to hell.
I'm glad you're home.
Yeah, we'll see.
What are you thinking?
I was just wondering what it was all going
to look like in the morning.
(I'll sing it one last time for you)
(Then we really have to go)
(You've been the only thing that's right)
(In all I've done...)
What's happening?
(Light up, light up)
(As if you have a choice)
(even if you cannot hear... )
Transcript: Raceman Synchro: ikpko
www.forom.com