previously on jericho
O: All right,it looks like the explosion came from the west,maybe denver.
If it was an attack and there's chaos out there
you might not want the wrong people knowing that jericho is still here.
Johnston: The unfortunate truth is,there was another explosion in atlanta.
So,do we have a plan?
I will talk to april.
Tonight.
Secrets of a small town.
Divorce papers.
I had them drawn up before the bombs went off.
I don't want it.
The train that never showed up-- smashed into a car.
There's a ton of food just sitting on it.
If I knew anything I would tell your mayor.
hello.
This assistant secretary walsh from the department of homeland security.
Stay where you are.
Do not attempt to leave.
what's going on?
All right,everybody calm down,all right?
We'll have it back in a second.
are those ours or theirs?
They're headed up.
They must be ours.
Nearest missile silo's in wyoming,100 miles away.
So this is it?
We're at war?
enter psw
what's the target?
ours ot theirs
i'm compromised
Dad?
Hey,I want you to get your mom and samuel down here,and you wait for me until I come out.
What are you...
no,now,baby,now.
Well,if we're sending missiles,they must have figured out who attacked us.
God bless america.
Could have just decided to take out one of the usual suspects.
Which means there could be more missiles headed in our direction.
Well,is this the federal response we've all been waiting for?
end transmission
robert,the circuit breaker wasn't the breaker.
It was an emp.
It's an electromagnetic pulse.
Fries anything with a circuit board.
That means all electronics,appliances,anything with wires.
Does that mean another bomb has gone off somewhere?
What the hell was that?
Jake: It was an emp.
Everything's dead.
Well,is help on its way or not?
I don't think so.
sync:fisherchen
www.ydy.com
proudly presents
2 weeks later
oh,dude!
Slow down.
What's the matter with you,huh?
Dale,hey,whoa,whoa,whoa.
What are you doing?
He broke our window,you saw him.
Dale.
Thanks a lot.
Dale,hold up.
What?
You all right?
They tried to break into the store twice this week.
Oh,that's terrible.
You got a problem?
Not me.
Dale's my buddy.
Right,dale?
You can't go around shoving people in the street,all right?
If you got a problem,you take it up with jimmy or bill.
All they'll do is write a report.
All right,well,then,come to me.
I can take care of myself.
There's got to be an easier way.
Maybe we can rig up the washing machine to work with the hand crank or something?
I'll be back tonight.
Where are you going,dad?
To the station.
So why you heading off to play cop?
Because people are starting to react to the fact that no one is coming to save them.
Okay?No one.
Because the world we knew does not exist anymore.
So if we can't keep order,we will not survivE.
Alison,give me a minute with your father.
Mom,I just...
now.
What the hell are you doing scaring our kids about the end of the world,robert?
Well,they have to understand what's going on.
You haven't been around for four years.
I'm the parent here,okay?
I'll decide what they need.
We cannot have photos up.
They might raise questions about us as a family.
I'm not in this.
Get rid of them,darcy.
People are trespassing on my land.
Well,we don't have the resources to control the whole town,carla.
You have to keep an eye on your own properties.
Our street's got a busted water main.My whole front lawn is flooded.
I'm trying to get some men on that right now.
Where's mayor green?
He is home recuperating from the flu.
Then who's running this town?
The mayor is still in charge,and,you know,these guys are doing the best job they can with a short staff.
Who the hell are you?
He is a volunteer and a deputy.
Now settle down and we'll get to you.
But you have to be patient.
Please.
Mary: How's your brother?
Eric pretty much keeps to himself.
Spends a lot of time at work making sure the town stays on its feet.
Really?
That's odd.
I just figured he'd be spending a little more time with his wife.
You know,now that they've lost the house and all.
They seem pretty happy together.
Man: Mitchell,wait up.
Looking good,mary.
We are not doing this again,mitch.
You're not welcome here.
Oh,come on,with everything that's happened,I'm just looking for a cold beer.
Well,we haven't served cold anything in a long time.
All right,just give me whatever you got.
Or I'll get it myself.
You might want to rethink that.
Everyone thought you went up in the blast.
But I knew you'd find a way to survive.
Oh,come on,let's not do it like this.
Besides,anyone should have a grudge,it's me,right?
I mean,you left me holding the bad when you blew town.
You know what,you're right.
Don't make me kick your ass again.
Robert: HeY.
Is everything all right?
You travel with your own personal bodyguard now?
That's probably not a bad idea.
Robert: What's the trouble here?
Oh,no trouble.
We're just two old friends catching up.
Well,maybe you should do that some other place.
And some other time.
See you soon.
Hey,mom.
Hi.
What are you doing home?
I'm just snagging another citation ledger.
Taken more complaints these last few days than we normally do in a month.
Well,jake and I are going out to the ranch to feed the horses in a little bit.
If you'd like to join us,maybe we could talk.
I'm sorry,I can'T.
With dad down,I'm struggling just to make sure things don't fall apart out there.
How 'bout things closer to home?
What's that supposed to mean?
How are you and april doing?
Why,did she say something?
Eric...
how's johnston?
I wish I had better news.
His fever's getting worse.
I'll try to dig up a stronger course of antibiotics at the med center,but we're running low on supplies.
God,if I could just get him to ear something.
Can you stay?
Don't worry about me,mom.
There's a box protein bars at the station.I'll just grab one of those.
Okay.
If you wait ten minutes,maybe we could walk together?
I got to go.
There's an important meeting.
Then that's where you should be.
We'll talk tonight.
Maybe we can put in a new starter.
No one can find a starter that works.
uncle sam!
To what do we owe the pleasure?
Can you please not call me that?
what did she say?
Oh,she says she likes your shoes.
Thank you.
I have a proposition.
The hotel I was staying in closed,and since you owe the government more than...$180,000...
no one's heard from the government in weeks.
Consider me the government.
Fine,then I still get to call you uncle sam.
Nice watch.
It's a rolex.
You got the time?
It's,um...
it just stopped working after the pulse,just like everyone else'S.
Well,I how about I pay you when it starts up again?
You're being an idiot.
I am trying to give you a chance to protect your interests.
You're too kind.
Hey,here's the deal.
You let me stay here,and I will deduct my room and board from what you owe the irs.
Fine,fine,why not?
I can use an extra field hand,and you can help bonnie with the cooking and the washing.
Okay,maybe you don't understand the nature of a deal.
I don't do housework.
Is that a cockroach?
We don't have cockroaches here.
Well,it landed right on me!
It's probably attracted to all that chicken crap in the yard.
Stanley,what's wrong?
What do you got there?
Rap sheet on mitchell cafferty.
Armed robbery,assault,gun-trafficking.
Yeah.
Mitch isn't one of jericho's finest.
What do you know about him?
Well,he hasn't given us trouble in a while.
He stays on the edge of town in a sort of compound with a bunch of guys.
Like survivalists?
I guess.
Why are you so interested?
Well,he was in bailey's this morning.
Had some words with your brother.
Looked like there was a bit of history there.
What did jake do about it?
Kept his cool,didn't engage.
Well,it's best we leave it alone,then.
Like you said,it's history.
Well,one thing that hasn't changed...
all this.
You remember when you first started riding?
Took to it like a fish to water.
You know,if you'd favored your father a little less and your dinky uncle dennis a little more,you would've been a hell of a jockey.
Talk to me.
I'm tired of hearing my own voice.
You okay?
Yeah,just tired.
I'm gonna get the water.
mom!Stay down!
Who are those guys?
xxxxxxxxx
I'll get you some aspirin for the pain and swelling.
I'm sorry I can't offer anything stronger.
I-it's okay,honey.
I don't need anything else.
Don't argue with her,gail-- doctor's orders.
Damn bastards.
Jake?
Where are you going?
To find mitch.
And then what?
I don't know yet.
Well,hold on,jake,you don't know for sure if he's behind this.
It was him.
You said yourself you didn't get a good look.
Now,look...
you know,I would like nothing better than to string up the guys who did this,but that's not the way we do things.
Last time you got mixed up with mitch cafferty,you left town and a boy was dead.
I'm not that guy anymore.Yeah?
Let's just make sure that it stays that way.
Look,if I don't care of him,he'll come back.
We've got to do this right.
You know that...
if this family starts breaking the law,how are we supposed to enforce it?
Gracie,you still have those crop pesticides?
Everything I got left is right there on that shelf.
Thank god.I'm gonna need everything you got to protect my corn.
Can anyone even eat that corn?
What about that rain we had?
No,it's okay.
The husks kept it safe from the fallout.
It was already mature,so the ears didn't take up any of that moisture.
You sure about that?
Gracie,you think I'd let my sister eat it if I didn't ink it was safe?
You think i would?
After what I've been exposed to?
I'll give you 20 bushels for those pesticides.
Well,I was thinking we'd split the harvest,half and half.
Half?
What are you,crazy?
Well,how you gonna sell your corn?
Give it to me,I'll sell it here,and we'll share the profit.
Mimi: Richmond farm belongs to the U.S.Treasury.
You're lucky we just don't commandeer what we need.
I'd like to see you try.
All right,let's go.
Hey,jimmy.
Eric,what's up?
Hey,mary.
Where the hell have you been?
We think mitch cafferty and his cohorts stole some horses.
I know they were here earlier; I thought maybe you might have heard something.
Anything you might know,mary,would really help.
There was a man here this afternoon.
I heard him say that he bought a horse from some guys out at the airfield.
The airfield.
All right.
Thanks.
Eric.
The last time I saw you,you were gonna tell your wife about us and we were gonna start our life together.
That thought has kept me going.
That was nearly two weeks ago.
I don't know...
what you're thinking,I don't know if you're okay.
I don't know if I'm okay,mary.
I know this is not what I wanted.
Mary,I think about you every minute of every day.
Man,I wake up in the morning,and I want it to be you there so badly.
I know I...
I'm still married,and I have a wife,and I owe her...
something.
I don't know what to say,mary.
I wish I did,but I don'T.
It's like a damn infirmary in here.
Thought it'd be at least 20 years before it came to this.
I'm hot!
I'll bet you didn't expect a house full of kids,either.
I'm worried about jake.
So am I.
I don't think I'll ever forget the night I got that call.
Went out there and saw that mitch cafferty in handcuffs,that other kid all covered in blood,and all I could think is...
one of those boys could've been jake.
oh,hi,stanley.
Hi.
Sorry to bother you,mrs.Green,mayor,but I,uh...
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I found corn worms in my crop...
and I know this is a long shot,but I was hoping maybe you'd have some pesticides out at your ranch.
None of the other farms can spare 'em.
Sorry,stanley.Have you tried gracie's?
Yeah.She-she won't give 'em up.
You see,I need to kill these bugs,or I'd have to harvest what's good today,or it's-it's all gone.
Does she realize you have the biggest farm in jericho?
I mean,if we lose his crops,we all starve.
We're just gonna have to put together a crew as quick as we can,and we'll have to figure out how to ration it.
Stanley: Hang on a minute.
This is my corn.
Well,of course it is,stanley-- it's just right now we need you to share.
I mean,we're on our own here,and the town's nearly out of food.
Well,now,I'm willing to do my part,mayor,but I'm not giving up my crop.
Stanley,there'll be plenty enough for you and bonnie.
Plenty enough for everyone.
For 5,000 people plus livestock for god knows how many months?
I am not the only farm in this town.Why am I being targeted?
Stanley,nobody's being targeted.
It sure doesn't seem that way,sir-- all of a sudden everybody's laying claim to my crop-- the irs,gracie,and now you.
Stanley,we're just...
all due respect,I'll take care of it myself.
Oh,stanley,come and sit down,honey.
Stanley,come on back here,now.
hey,girl.
Jake.
Dale,what are you doing here?
I'm so sorry.I didn't know.
Didn't know what?
Jake!
jake?
You back away.
Get the hell out of here,dale.
No.
Stick around-- think of this as initiation.
You've crossed the line.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
Coming to our family's ranch.
I crossed the line?
I went to jail...
that night that you bailed on us.
My best friend...
had half of his head blown off.
I told you I wasn't gonna rob anybody.
Oh,come on,stop acting like an angel.
You come back to...settle down?
Raise a family,maybe do a little farming?
I never planned on staying.
Of course not.
But where you gonna go?
Cars don't work.
We're fresh out of horses.
Jake: If you...
or anybody ever come near my family again,I will kill you.
Now,that's the jake I know.
All right,now get uP.
I'm taking you to go see john.
stop!Sheriff!
Don't even move.
Where's mitchell?
Don't know.
I know you,sean.You're lying.
Dale?
You're next.
What am I gonna do about this?
Can't charge them with anything and the nearest judge is in the county seat and we don't even know if that exists anymore.
Is this about these kids?
Or mitchell cafferty?
He stole my mother's horses and he could have gotten her killed.
Oh,you had run-ins with this guy long before that,jake.
I've read his file.
He's gonna be a problem,right?
And now with the sheriff and half our deputies dead,mitchell and his kind are gonna prey on this town like locusts.
We need to stop them now.
Well,if it's information you want,first thing we do is separate them.
All right,I'll take sean into the hallway.
No.
I'll do it.
Get up.We're going for a walk.
Screw that,I don't have to...
Walk.
Some pesticides got stolen over at gracie'S.
Do you know anything about it?
No.I mean,I was there earlier trying to buy some,but...
but what?
All right.What's going on?Why are you acting like this?
Gracie came down to the station.
Started raising all kinds of hell.
She says you stole 'em.
She told you I stole them?
You mind if I take a look around?
Yeah,I do,bill.This is nuts!
What's going on?
I don't know.
One of my best friends is accusing me of stealing pesticides.
I'm gonna check the barn.
I didn't say you could go in there.
Watch it.
It's okay.Just let him do what he wants to do.
Fine,check the barn.
Check the whole damn house!
How you got mixed up with mitchell but you need to stay away from him.
I'm serious.You can wind up in jail or a lot worse.
How did you get mixed up with him?
I was stupid.
And bored and looking for trouble.
Are you looking for trouble?
Dale.
Why are they keeping you here?What'd you do?
I'm just talking to him.
You can't without an attorney.
I'm not a cop.
I'm bailing him out anyway.
I know the machines are down,but you have to take it.
Get out of here.
You're letting me go?
Jake: Yeah.
Just trying to talk some sense into you.
Believe me,you don't want to go down this road.
I think I know where mitchell is.
I'll show you.
dad?
Dad?
Come on,out of here.
Are all those cities gone?
What do you think?
How do you know?
I don't for sure.
Okay.
Those are the cities I heard about through the ham radio,and the satellite feed before the emp.
Home come your laptop wasn't fried like everything else?
It's ruggedized.
It is built to withstand an emp.
The,um...
the government issues them,baby.
So you're some kind of spy?
That's why you moved us here.
You knew this was gonna happen.
Why do you have that gun?What's it for?
Shooting.
And I think it's probably time you learned how.
You see,the way things are going...
you may have to defend yourself one day.
Do you understand?
Hey,what's going on?
We were just catching up.
Right?
You're clear.
Are you sure?
Because we can check the fields.We can go through them row by row.
We got a complaint.
So all you gotta do now is accuse someone?
Stanley.
No.
What about my word,bill?
I'm just doing my job,man.
Mimi: What are you doing?
I'm gonna burn the field.
You've completely lost your mind.What happened to you?
I'm not gonna burn the whole field,just the infested partS.
Oh,my god,stanley.
You don't need to do this.
Look,it's the only thing I can think of.
I got the pesticides.
What are you talking about?
I paid some kids to steal them from gracie's store.
We just have to get into town and pick them up.
You stole the pesticides?
What,am I talking to myself?
I paid someone to steal them.
I gave them my diamond watch.
I can't believe this is what we've come to.
We don't really have a choice,stanley.
It's every man for himself now.
He's finally asleep.
Great.
How are you feeling?
I'm hanging in there.
I'm sorry there isn't more I can do for him.
That's one obstinate guy in there.
I guess the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Certainly not as far as jake's concerned.
I don't know as I've ever really thought of eric as being stubborn.
Hard to reach,then?
Well,he's had a lot on his plate.
Since the missiles...
not to mention your new living arrangement.
Yeah.
It started long before all of this.
I've been where you are.
Putting something back together...
isn't ever easy.
But somebody's got to take the first step.
Now,if you want to fight for this thing,start fighting.
You need to be smarter about who you hang out with.
I don't hang out with those guys.
I needed sean and mitch to help me move some stuff,that's all.
I didn't know about the horses.
Well,what did you think,dale?
Hey,you never should have tried to protect them.
I wasn'T.I was trying to protect gracie.
What do you mean?
A train crashed full of food supplies.
It's how I've been keeping gracie stocked.
I didn't want anyone to know about it.
It's all in there.
What?
This place was full.It was stacked to the rafters.
I guess we know who took it.
Gracie.
You get the hell out of my store.I know you stole from me.
No,I didn't,gracie.I swear I didn'T.
Gracie,how long have you known me?
My whole life,right?
We have to trust each other.
Just,just,let me show you.
Follow me.
You see,gracie?It's all here.
Nobody stole anything from anyone,okay?
It was a misunderstanding.
Eric: Do you have any idea where he would have moved it to?
Dale: No,no,I don'T.
You stay here.
Stop right there,mitchell!
Put your gun down.
Put your gun down!
Now put your hands up.
where's the food?
Eric: Jake...
stop.
What are you doing?I said,"stop.
" Where's the food?
Stop!
So what are we doing to do about him?
Eric: We lock him up for now.
Maybe we can send someone to fielding,see if the courthouse is still running.
His friends aren't going to let this go.
I can handle it.
Yeah,you handled it real good back at the barn.
I should have killed him.
Stop it,jake!
You're not that guy anymore.
What about these two?
Eric: Now I can see letting dale go,but sean helped steal the horses.
He's still a boy.
A boy who could have gotten you killed,mom.
Well,it doesn't matter,eric,because I'm not pressing charges.
This cell is too small to hold everybody who ever made a mistake.
What do you suggest?
Rehabilitation.
Okay.
Okay,hold it.
All fingers wrapped.
Okay,relax.
Right.
It's okay.
Breathe.
Nice.Stand with your legs like so.
A little further apart.
Right.
Now bend your knees,take your sight.
Try to keep your eyes open.
Squeeze.
Right.Good job,good job.
All right.
That's a very good job.
You like that?
are you sure this is going to work?
In theorY.
You've never done this before?
Nope.
Well,don't get it on your shoes.
Seriously,get away from me.
Oh,my god,I wish I prayed.
Gail: Stanley.
you said you needed to harvest today.
We're here to help,no strings attached.
thanks.
mom.
Well,hello.
I'm really sorry,mrs.Green.
I'm sorry for everything.
All right,well,go make yourselves useful.
forget it.
Man: Uncle sam.
You ever slept in a barn before?
You know,it's not like it is in the movies.
It can get pretty fragrant in there with all the pigs and goats brushing up against you.
You're bluffing.
Try me,please.
these are for you.
I lost my head,stanley.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
you have any idea what you're doing?
not a clue.
thanks for your help.
this is our home,too.
Right.
is he a good man or a bad man?
baby,there's no such thing.
kind of cool,huh?
Yeah.
Especially if you like corn.
Tough work,huh?
Yeah.
I was thinking maybe when we leave here,we could,uh,I was going to say go for a walk,but we'll be too tired...
april,stop,please.Okay?
What?
This.
What you're doing.
It's making things worse.
I'm just trying to talk to you,get you to look at me,something.
Well,three weeks ago,you were asking about a divorce.
Three weeks ago,we lived on a different planet.
Things have changed.
Never mind.
april,wait.
There's always the walk home.
Why don't we start there,see how we feel.
this town...
jake.
You ready for this?
You know he's going to come for me.
And then,he's going to come looking for you.
There's no running away this time,jake.
sync:fisherchen
www.ydy.com
proudly presents