Previously on Jericho
We're the United States Marines
and we're here to help.
- Lance Corporal Mullen.
- Jake.
- Maggie.
They've got somebody on the edge of town
pretending to be their headquarters.
- Is any of this real?
- The gun's real.
Hands up!
Get 'em up!
You're a smart girl.
You need to get out before
these guys get you killed.
And go where?
Justin, you SOB.
How the hell did you lose an election?
The question is how did you get
to be in charge of New Bern?
They get tired of you being sheriff?
No, I'm still sheriff.
Just got a little more authority.
This thing work?
We get power from it?
Probably sometime tomorrow.
Let's get it up as fast as we can.
Can we buy some more
of these things?
You got one of the only salt
mines around for 400 miles.
We're gonna need food.
Ten wind turbines
for let's say...
ten percent of your spring crop.
Okay, we'll give you the food.
We're gonna need ten Jericho men
to help us build it.
What you are about to do
means this town's survival.
All right, let's move out.
Anything happens to any of them...
you're the first one I come for.
I didn't know you guys
were coming back today.
It wasn't safe for us there anymore.
- Where's my brother?
- He hasn't been seen for a few days.
You can't just ride into New Bern
and start breaking china.
It's a full inventory of Jericho.
They sliceit up like they own it.
They're making mortar rounds.
They're getting ready for war.
Hold it!
Come on.
This doesn't look good.
It could turn into a
full-blown riot.
As our guys show up,
you keep them back out of sight.
I don't want those New Bern
guys getting trigger-happy.
This salt mine is
private property!
You have 30 seconds to
get the hell out of here!
What did I tell you, Ted?
Sorry.
I knew it was you.
Yeah, but if it wasn't me...
you just gave up my name.
I want you to tell me
who your friend is
and where I can find him.
Things are gonna get
very bad for you
and your brother,
vxyou don't help us, Jake.
Why would I want to help you?
This is what I know...
is that you, your friend
and your brother
were caught attempting to sabotage
this town's sole means of manufacture.
Manufacturing weapons. You were man...
So I'm gonna
repeat the question:
Where is your friend?
Why don't you tell me what
vvhappened to Heather Lisinski?
Take him back.
Let's go, boy.
Word's gonna get back.
It's gonna get back to Jericho
about what you're doing,
and there's nothing you
can do to stop it!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Looks like they went easy on you.
- Yeah, for now.
They haven't found Hawkins yet.
We're gonna get out of here.
How many people have to die
before you don't care anymore?
April's death was not your fault.
I can't even be sure Heather's dead
with the lies they're spreading.
I've seen, Jake.
I don't think I can go back.
Staying here and getting
yourself killed
isn't going to make you
feel any better, trust me.
Remember the time
I was supposed to...
wake you up for that meteor shower?
Yeah, it was supposed
to be this...
once-in-a-lifetime thing.
Anyway...
you were so pissed at me,
so I finally gave up
and let you sleep.
I'm not giving up this time.
I should arrest you right here!
It's not his fault. We had to deal
with him in New Bern.
Gray, what the hell is this?
There's no deal!
I'm not giving away anything!
Listen, we'll think of something.
Right now we need to stand down.
No, we're not leaving
without our salt.
- It's not worth people getting hurt.
- She's right.
- All right, everybody...
- What are you doing?
Dale, I'm not going to
let people get killed.
- This was your idea.
- This is over!
Get your guys out of here!
Hey! Gray, come on!
Season 1 - Epsiode 20
" One If By Land "
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Synchro ]
Hutch / Loky / aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
How many more are there?
I'm not sure.
Six, maybe seven.
We need gurneys.
What happened?
Some guys from New Bern showed up
trying to steal our salt.
There was a shootout.
Oh, my God!
Okay, Harry...
Harry, we're gonna get you
cleaned up, buddy, okay?
All right, you need me
to look at your arm?
No, it's okay. I can wait.
We shouldn't be patching
those guys up.
We should be arresting them.
They opened fire on us!
We don't know who shot first, all right?
I'll get to an investigation.
Right now we need to make
sure people don't die.
Oh, my God.
Get him to Kenchy... now.
Could we get some ice, please?
She twisted her ankle.
I'm fine.
Hang on.
Hold on, Harry.
Hey, Mrs. Carmichael.
Is he gonna be all right?
No, he's not gonna be all right!
I didn't want this to happen.
Why should we expect
anything different?
As long as you and your boyfriend are
all set, the rest of us can go to hell!
Wouldn't your father be proud?
What is that supposed to mean?
Okay, come on.
She's just nervous.
Caroline, take a look at
her ankle, will ya?
Don't worry about it.
Gail, we heard about the shooting.
I brought the antiseptic
I've been working on.
What can we do to help?
Look, I need charts on
everybody who's checked in.
Annie, show her how to
fill one out, will ya?
- What's all this gonna mean for Eric?
- I don't know.
But haven't we heard anything?
I told you I don't know.
Johnston's working on it.
Now what I could use is a roll
of gauze and some bandages.
They're on the cart
next to the ultrasound.
I just don't know
what that looks like.
Never mind. I'll do it myself.
What the hell did you think
was gonna happen?!
You didn't have to bring
rangers in there.
I was protec...
What?!
I'm afraid we've had
our first fatality.
One of your guys
from New Bern...
Dawson.
I didn't get the first name.
Jim Dawson.
You have got to let me
go back to New Bern
and tell them that you support
this salt mine deal.
No, that's not happening.
If they so much as think that
you fired the first shot...
- The who fi... What?
- Come on, Gray.
We need to work together
while we still can.
Things are bad in New Bern.
And when they find out
that six of us came here
and only five are coming back...
What are you saying, Russell?
You got people there.
You should bring 'em home.
Eric's still there.
Johnston, you need
to know something.
vEric hasn't been seen
for a few days.
And yesterday, Jake went
back there to try and find him.
You're telling me this now?
All right, come on. We leave now,
we can get there before dawn.
- No, no, no. I'm not authori...
- Did you hear him?
Constantino wants a bigger fight.
He's not gonna have
my sons as human shields.
Let's go!
Maggie?
Of all the jail cells, right?
Hardly recognize you
without your wardrobe.
What happened?
You guys get caught?
Kind of hard to pull that
voff without the tank.
We...
pretty much split up after Jericho.
I came to New Bern with
a couple of the guys,
but we got turned away at the border
a few weeks ago.
I was dumb enough to try
and sneak back in.
Why? This place is hell.
- It's worse out there.
- Really? That's hard to imagine.
I heard you two got dragged
in front of the Town Hall.
I don't want to scare you, Jake,
but you gotta get out of here.
It isn't exactly easy.
You could do it if you
got someone outside.
Why?
Do you?
Know someone outside?
No.
I'm just trying to help.
Last time you tried to help,
you nearly wiped out
my town's supplies.
- I was trying to survive.
- Yeah, so were we.
Look, I'm not saying it was right.
We had something people
wanted and we used it.
That's how it works.
You think you're helpless in here?
You're not.
Not if you have something they want.
What makes you think
I have something they want?
I don't think they're beating
the two of you up for fun.
Even if I did have something,
I wouldn't give it to them.
You're right. You shouldn't.
But I could.
Yeah, right.
No, thanks.
Listen, if you talk... they're going
to throw you back in your cell.
There's no way they're letting
either of you out of here.
But if I had the information,
I could trade it for my freedom.
And I can go get help.
What... give myself up
to get you out?
So I can get all three of us out.
And you can take me
back to Jericho.
I can't go anywhere without you.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Get up!
Hey, where are you taking him?
He's already told you
everything he knows!
How are things here?
Harry's going to be okay, but...
I'm worried about the staff.
Everybody's exhausted.
You sure you're okay to drive?
Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Better hit the road.
Be careful.
If I lose all three of you...
I swear to God...
I'm going to bring them home.
You get some sleep.
Got to go.
What's going on?
What are you doing to him?
Jake, just give me a chance, please.
We can end this.
His name is Robert Hawkins.
He said he's probably in a hunting cabin
owned by a guy named Ted Lewis.
He works at the factory.
Find out where it is.
Get over there.
You're supposed to
take me with you.
What?
That's... the deal I made
with Constantino.
I go with you, and as soon as
you see the guy's there,
you drop me off at the checkpoint.
Just talk to Constantino.
This is... he was supposed
to be here!
Take her with you.
If he's not there, kill her.
This is Johnston Green
from Jericho.
- We need talk to the sheriff.
- He's up at the cabin.
We have orders
he's not to be interrupted.
He'll want to be
interrupted for this.
It's not exactly Mayberry, is it?
Not since Ravenwood.
How are you with a rifle?
I hunted jackrabbits before.
Well, I've never shot a person,
if that's what you're asking.
We need to go back to the factory.
We need mortars.
Well, for what?
We can't launch them
over that fence.
We're not going
to launch them from here.
Phil.
Nice spread you got here.
I always wanted you
to see this place.
Well, I just...
wish it were under
better circumstances.
I just found out Eric's been
missing a couple of days.
I'd like a little update on that.
And there was an incident
at the salt mine.
Some of our people got hurt.
Let's take a walk.
I'll go around back.
I got the front.
You watch her.
Let's go.
You better hope he's home.
This mine deal,
this is your idea?
I thought it could help the town,
create a partnership.
- That didn't quite work out, did it?
- It was...
mishandled all the way around.
We were hoping we could
reach some agreement.
It's a little late for that.
You opened fire on our citizens.
- We don't know who shot first.
- Come on, Phil.
A bunch of guys shows up with guns
in the middle of the night
trying to take our salt.
What would you have done?
Jericho's continuous acts of
aggression against this town
are unjustifiable.
- What "continuous acts"?
We're neighbors, for God's sake.
I didn't hear much talk of neighbors
when you sent Ravenwood
straight to our door.
We almost blew everything
to hell and gone
trying to defend ourselves
against those mercenaries.
We had no idea where
they were headed next.
You couldn't try and warn us?
You couldn't help us when they were
raiding what little we had left,
shooting whoever got in their way?
My deputies, my friends?
Then I find both of your sons.
Both of them in my factory
trying to destroy the last form
of capital this town's got.
Slow down.
Jake was apprehended yesterday,
attempting to sabotage my factory.
That makes no sense.
The factory's producing wind turbines.
Your sons are pretty
bent on the idea.
I caught Eric the day before
trying to do the same thing.
We're holding both of them.
Now, you listen to me.
I don't care what you think
we've done to you,
but if any harm comes
to either of those boys,
this is not going to end well.
There's been little chance
of this ending well for some time.
I want to see my boys. Now.
What the hell's
taking them so long?
Who are you?
- Don't shoot!
- Who are you?
I'm with Jake.
- Columbus! Columbus!
- What you say?
Jake said if I said Columbus
you'd know he sent me. I was...
I was with him in prison.
He sent me to help you.
He sent me to help you!
Columbus, Columbus.
I got it.
How is Jake doing?
He's okay.
Yeah?
That's Ted.
He's with me.
I'm Maggie.
Jake sent me.
Where are the cops?
They've been dealt with.
You don't want to go in there.
Here, this is everything.
So, what's the plan?
Plan?
There's going to be
an explosion in town.
Hopefully, it'll cause enough chaos
that we can somehow
get Jake and Eric out of there.
I think I can help you do that.
I have an in with Constantino.
Come on. Get up.
What the hell happened?
I didn't tell them anything.
But I already gave them Hawkins.
It's not about Hawkins.
They want to know about Jericho.
What our defenses are like.
Do we have any troops?
Where are they posted?
Do we have a stockpile of weapons?
We have to get back.
We have to warn them.
We will.
We're not going to die in here.
Hey. I'm taking off.
Thanks for all your help.
Yeah. No problem.
You need to get some rest.
I will.
Listen.
I am sorry if I was abrupt earlier.
We're all under a lot of pressure.
Mary's really trying.
Maybe... maybe
you could give her a chance.
Yeah, I know.
It's... it's just being here.
This was April's whole world.
I miss her so much.
I know. It's not fair.
For what it's worth,
you and Mary have a lot in common.
What? We both love Eric?
No. I was actually going to say
you're both pretty tough broads.
You're both... a little hardheaded.
In a bar fight...
even money.
- Everything okay back here?
- Fine.
Thought you were supposed
to stay off your ankle.
Whatever. It's not like I got shot.
I told you, Skylar. It wasn't our fault.
I know. I just
don't understand why now it's okay
for all this random criticism about
my dad to come flying out at me.
What is that?
Especially coming from people
who were supposedly his friends.
I guess they're not his friends.
The Carmichaels used
to come over, like,
every other week for dinner.
We used to go on vacations together.
Why would they do
that if they hated him?
They don't hate him.
They're just scared of him.
My dad was a good person.
He gave them the money
for the clock on Main Street.
He... he did lots of good things.
Maybe he did,
but that's not why
they were nice to him.
They were nice to him because
he had a lot of power.
That's how it works.
We made it to the factory.
You both ready?
We're going to need someone to cover
those guards over there.
Ted, be ready to take them out.
I thought I was driving.
Someone's got to be on those guards
while I get Jake and Eric out.
Cover them until I get back,
and if need be,
take out the sniper first.
5 months ago,
you know what I was doing?
Customizing my truck.
I was getting ready to defend
my dissertation.
Russian lit.
How about you? What were you doing
last time things were normal?
I can't remember back that far.
Is everybody ready?
How will we know when
you're finished over there?
You'll know.
I'll wait here.
Russell, these are not your sons.
You can go on home.
We can fix this.
It doesn't have to end this way.
I get the feeling
it's just getting started.
You can come to Jericho if
you want to. You know that.
I've got family here,
a little girl.
This is our home.
And I keep thinking if I stay here,
maybe we can stop this.
You get in a bad situation, go to
the railroad tracks and go east.
It'll take you to Route 70 and
you can skip the checkpoint.
Thank you, Russell.
Good luck.
We're going to have
to do this another time.
- What?
- My deputy says it isn't a good day.
You can come back tomorrow.
I'm not leaving until
I see my sons, Phil.
I'll tell you what.
You bring back all of my citizens
who were shot in Jericho last night
and I'll give you 15 minutes
with your sons.
You don't want to do this.
Let's go, Mr. Green.
What's this?
We're going to escort you
back to the checkpoint.
Get in the car, please, Mr. Green.
Mortars are good to go.
Get up.
Don't shoot me!
Don't shoot!
I'm the one they sent to get
the guy from Jericho!
He tried to kill me.
Please, I need to talk to Constantino
right away, please.
Constantino, I'm just telling you
what he told me.
He's going right now to the factory
to blow it up, and
then he's gonna... he's gonna
blow up the town hall
so that he can get Jake and Eric out.
- You expect me to believe
he wired a government building
under 24-hour armed surveillance?
I'm just telling you what he told me.
I'm trying to help you,
so you'll let me stay as a citizen.
- Please don't lock me in here!
- Do you think I've forgotten
how quickly you turned
on your own friends
when we first brought you in here?
I don't believe a word
that comes out of your mouth.
Get him out of here.
What is this?
Come on.
You already know everything.
What do you want from us?
- I already told you everything I know.
- Maybe so,
but maybe your brother'll
be a little more...
more forthcoming
if he thinks it'll save your life.
Let him go!
Move that barricade
and let him through.
- Let him go.
- Tell me.
Let him go!
How many of the roads
out of Jericho are wired?!
- I don't know!
- What you know!
How do you defeat Ravenwood?!
Tell me!
- Tell me right now!
- Eric, look at me!
- Don't tell him anything!
- How many spies have you sent here?!
Tell us what you know
or we slice his throat.
Leave him alone, Perkins!
What was that?
Come on!
There was an explosion at the factory.
- Move them to the warehouse.
- What about the other prisoners?
Just them, now!
Uncuff them.
Come on. Let's go.
Un-handcuff them!
Let's go!
Come on. Move!
Jeez.
Where you going?
To get the... to get the truck.
You were told to wait here
till I got back.
I know.
Breathe.
Just breathe.
Everything's going fine.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry, no.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Get up!
- You okay?
- I'm good.
Jake, look out!
Over here!
Everybody go!
Go! Get up!
Come on!
New Arrivals. Potatoes meat
inquire inside for trade.
Thanks, Wayne.
Uh, with the rest in aisle 4.
Can I help you, Mrs. Carmichael?
I heard you've got some meat.
One of Mr. Henderson's
mares broke her leg,
but she was healthy.
I'll take a quarter pound.
This is a pound of grain.
That's not gonna be enough.
But that's what it says.
It says 4 pounds of grain
for a pound of meat.
The price went up.
Sorry.
Please.
It's for Harry.
The doctor said he needs protein.
It's up to you.
My father was a good man,
Mrs. Carmichael.
Yes, he was.
There's a quarter pound.
Thank you.
We're closed!
I just wanted to return this.
- The antiseptic really helped.
- Thank you.
I have a fresh batch.
We'll take it.
So there's no one in town who
wants to have a drink tonight?
You'd think the big draw
would be the atmosphere
and the gracious hospitality,
but turns out,
it's the booze.
They'll be back when
I make more vodka.
Thank you.
How's everything going
down at the center?
Well...
it's calmed down.
We had to break up a lot of fights.
This whole New Bern thing
is making everybody really jumpy.
Talked to Gray.
Said if they're not back by dawn,
then he'd go up there himself.
Then it's gonna be a long night.
You're welcome to stay,
listen to music or...
I think I'll go home and wait there.
If I hear anything...
I'll let you know.
Same here.
Night, Mary.
I didn't think we'd make it this far
with the gas in that tank.
We, uh, we got about 12 miles
to cover, and,
I don't think she's gonna make it.
We have to try.
She didn't leave us.
We're not leaving her.
Here's your knife.
- How's your shoulder?
- Yeah.
Hurts like hell.
It's good.
How you holding up?
I'm still walking.
Yes, you are.
This is real whiskey.
This is actual whiskey.
- I kept a stash just for emergencies.
- I bet you did.
What do you think?
It's no meteor shower, but...
Thanks for coming to get me.
Smell that?
First wheat's going in.
Used to be my favorite time of year.
Listen to that wind.
Still moving, even
after everything we did.
With everything that's coming.
We should go.
[ www.seriessub.com ]