Today started out like any other day....
Ohhh. Dolphins won again.
Mmm.
Here you go.
I'm gonna be hearing about this all day.
Dr Cox and Jordan were still
looking for a pedetrician.
This time, try not to
scare off the doctor.
I did not scare off the last guy!
You bit him.
I _tripped_ and my
teeth hit his shoulder.
Uh-huh. And once that happened,
did you clamp down a little bit?
Jordan!
Oh, you come on!
Well, he had a bad attitude!
Zachary, remember what Mr. Cookiepants
always says about blowing your nose:
"If it's clear, have no fear; if
it's bloody, come see your buddy!"
What do you want?
Well, we're looking for a new
pediatrician for our son....
And you figured that, even
though my patient load is full,
since you're on the board
of directors and Dr. Cox here
is not only an attending
at the hospital but
also an internationally
renowned pain-in-the-ass,
you both could show complete
disregard for my schedule
and make me want to cause
you grievous bodily harm
even before we were
properly introduced...?
Helloooo. I'm Dr. Norris.
Charmed.
Like I said: Same ol', same ol'.
Heh-hah-hah. You
drew on the wall.
You drew on the wall!
You pulled the paper away!
Stop lyin'. It's gonna come off, right?
Dan, don't! That's dad's indelible
space pen! And prom is in like two weeks!
Good evening Mr. and Mrs. Shefford.
I'm...here to pick up Amy for...prom.
Yeah, that, that'll come
off, you won't have to
get laser surgery or skin
from your ass or anything.
Hmm?
Transcripts : Michelle V.L. M.
Resynchro par foromuser10 pour www.forom.com
Scrubs 3x04
Come on!
In a hospital, lots of things last
longer than you wish they would....
Especially certain stupid relationships
with stupid Sea World trainers
who stole my stupid girl!
Well, I've, uh, I've
got whales to train.
Stupid whales.
Hey, Sean! Right on, brother!
Bye.
Bye!
Where the hell are my interns!?
As third-year residents, you really
have to stay on top of your interns.
These! Right here! You see these names!?
They are called patients!
This one needs brain work!
This one needs a heart!
This guy needs courage.
Helping or hurting,
J.D.? Helping or hurting?
The point is, they
will live or die based
on your lame-assed post-ops; so,
please, people, shape the hell up!
Yes, Dr. Turk.
Dr. Jerk!
The girl one just called you "Dr. Jerk"!
No sweat. You should hear
what they call Dr. Michead.
I decided to take a different
tack with my interns.
Look, guys, I'm not here
to overwork ya, okay?
I'm not--I'm not just your
resident -- I'm your buddy,
I'm your go-to guy....
I'm J.D.
Of course, my tack
had its own drawbacks.
But it is crucial I have everyone
here at 9 a.m. sharp tomorrow, okay?
Oh, uh...is it cool if I come at 9:30?
Absolutely. Anyone else need to be late?
I can't.
Bad for me.
Okay, well, why don't we--why don't
we just make it 10, then? Okay?
Break!
I can be here at 9.
But I said 10!
I guess everyone has their own style.
Today for lunch, the cafeteria has...
Bruce, name a manifestation of
normal pressure hydrocephalus!
Urinary incontinence!
He-hell yes, Bruce!
Go place a Foley cath.
On Bed 4! As for the
rest of Team E, I'm--
Well, if it isn't Dr. Haircut and
her not-ready-for-primetime players!
Actually, sir, we rock, so feel
free to sit back and enjoy the show!
Well, don't worry about it, son,
those things are a dime a dozen.
Really?
In fact, if you get bored,
why don't you just hijack
an ice cream truck and drive it
through our brand new pathology lab?
But do me a favor and
spare the paper shredder,
because I'll need that to
turn your next twelve paychecks
into a clown wig you can wear
for the rest of your internship!
Dr. Reid, you may have an
exciting new look and a boyfriend
who smells vaguely like my
tackle-box, but I remain,
as always, underwhelmed.
I think, Dr. Norris,
what we're looking for
is someone who's not too alarmist
but also not too lax, either.
Oh, God, please let that someone be me!
Look, you're obviously a
little busy with your doll....
My doll? It's a collectible.
Someone's gonna get his ass bit!
Right.... I think we
should probably take off.
We're gonna be back to
you with our decision.
Super. I'll be by my
giant pretend phone,
pretending to give a crap.
- Oh, uh, by the way...
-Brrring! Helloo? Gotta take it.
Uh-huh....
I love him!
Of course you
do -- he's you!
And nobody loves you more
than you! You know that.
Yeah, but, still.... He
_is_ the best pediatrician
on staff, and since we
both work here we're gonna
have a lot of pull over
him. I mean, come on, Jordan,
you haven't let me make
one decision about our son.
Which is why, by the way,
you'll be doing the answering
when he asks why daddy's wee-wee
doesn't have a turtleneck on it like his.
Yeah, fine. Whatever you said.
Hey, Carla? Hey.... I
had to redo the NG tube
one of your nurses put on Mrs.
Hemmel, so if you could spread the word
to leave that to me and
my guys, it would be great.
Oh, no problem, Bambi.
Oh! But the reason
my nurses had to do that is because
none of your interns know how.
So if you keep flapping your mouth
without knowing all the facts, I'm
gonna see if I can fit my foot in it!
Okay. Good talk!
Brian? You know how to
place an NG tube, don't you?
You did it for me both times.
Jimmy, didn't you do one yesterday?
No, you let me go home 'cause I forgot
to set my TiVo for the
Styx 'Behind the Music'?
Do not miss that! It's awesome! Seth?
That was when I realized what
I'd turned my interns into.
Bruce! This is gonna be your
third Foley cath. in a row!
You can do this. You didn't need
to page me seventeen
times between the time
I bought the rum-raisin
muffin and then...
threw it away because
alcoholism runs in my family.
After this morning, I just wanted to
make sure that I _really_ have this down.
What are you doing?
It's just a nervous habit.
It helps me concentrate.
Yeah, well, you know
what helps me concentrate?
Me not doing that?
No, bunnies.
Say, I don't want to
embarrass you, there,
Big Jack, but, uh...you've got
a little something on your face.
Hardly notice it.
What was that?
Come on, Jordan. Don't
tell me you're gonna be one
of those parents who makes a big
deal out of every single cough.
Look out, Michead!
Okay, tough guy. Good night!
What the!? Maybe I
diluted this too much.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaagggggggggggggggggghhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Eh, can't blame the cleanser.
Even though my interns sucked, I
decided to turn it into a positive.
Elliot, uh, I need some pointers
on how to deal with my interns.
aaagghhh-hagh-haaaaggghhhh!!!!..
Hey, Doug.
Anyway, do you think we could, like,
meet up after work or something?
Sure. What'd you have in mind?
No! Don't do it!
Nothin' major.
You know, Benjamin, it's not a bad thing
that you play with it,
it's just that your mom
wants you to take breaks for meals!
Excuse me, Jack here, uh,
Jack here's got a cough.
And on account of the meconium
problem he had at birth,
I'm thinking it just might be pneumonia.
Take this cup, fill 'er up, right?
What in the hell do
you think you are doing?
You arrogant son of a
bitch, if you ever interrupt
an exam of mine again, I will personally
take my stethoscope
and shove it up your---
Benjamin! What happened?
I don't have to go.
Oh, well it happens
to the big boys, too.
Try again. Go on!
Is his temperature under
a hundred-point-five?
Barely.
Eating, peeing, pooing?
Sometimes all at the same time. Come on,
it's a really persistent
cough. What do you say?
Office hours, tomorrow,
5 o'clock. Bye-bye.
I'm gonna go ahead and
put this in a language
that you can understand:
You had better see my son now,
or I'm gonna kick your ass.
Okay, here she comes.
Don't be over-eager!
Elliot!!! Over here!!!
Hey!
Wow...you look great.
Thanks.
Oh, hey, J.D.
Hey, Sean's here, everybody...
Hey, Sean! Heeeyyy!
You know, since he's a
trainer, Sean is really good
with behavior and communication.
I mean, he helped me
so much with my interns
that I thought maybe
he could help you with yours.
Okay, stay calm -- at
least she's here, too.
Oh, Bruce again
-- gotta go.
Bye.
This'll be fun!
And just like that, I had
another rough night ahead of me.
At least I wasn't the only one.
You paged me for another Foley catheter?
I'm great at these now!
Just watch this one.
Don't mind if I do!
Yep, it's gonna be a long, long night.
I'm, heh, right here, Bruce.
Hello, David. I've been expecting you.
Agh!
Yeah, I just thought I'd come by and
play with some of your stuffed animals
-
- and, I know, I know, they're "for the kids", heh.
Also, wanted to let you know
that I _will_ be bringing
my son by this _morning_.
Yeah, I don't think so, there, chief.
Where's Mr. Cookiepants?
Oh, que pasa?
I said, Where's Mr. Cookiepants!?
He's in a safe place, Dave.
If you touch one hair on
his head, I swear to God
I'll inject your kid with chickenpox!
No, you won't.
I know.
For God's sakes, it's
an innocent doll!!!
No, David. It's a collectible.
Whatever.
The kid's a good doctor, he just...
falls apart every time Kelso
looks over his shoulder.
Well, why don't you just
tell Kelso to back off?
I-I've taken a lot of
positive steps this year
but when it comes to standing
up to Kelso, I just...
I can't get over that hump
yet. He's like my white whale.
Yeah.... Mine's Frank.
Oh, no, I meant like
in 'Moby Dick' --
Kelso is a giant pain in my ass.
Oh. Well, thing is,
I love Frank. Just...
he can drive me crazy
every now and then.
Every day! Every day! Every day!
Hey, J.D.? I was thinking
we'd start out by me,
you know, watching how you
interact with your interns.
Uh, and then, your
brain's gonna tell you
to be a little self-conscious,
but you just need
to ignore the voice in your head.
Kick him in the crotch and run.
I'll try, Sean!
You be nice to the teacher,
okay? I'm sleeping with him.
Oh, my God! I haven't
said that since college!
Mmmmgh! Norris hasn't
budged, and he just moved
the appointment back
to six, the rat-bastard!
Watch your language in front of the kid,
you stupid bicky-bicky!
You see, _I_ am adapting.
You, on the other hand,
are behaving like a complete lunatic.
No, I'm not!
Carla?
You're one of them bossy-pants types
who always tells people their problems
whether they ask for it or not, right?
I like to think I've
learned when to hold back.
You're in.
You've totally lost sight
of what's important, here.
You are a parent now, okay?
You don't come first anymore--
No.
-
-you've got to do what's best for your son,
even if it means sucking up
to the one doctor on earth
who's more obnoxious than you are.
Oh, my God. I loved doing that so much,
it makes my hand shake a little!
So, how are your interns doing?
Hey, yeah, it still burns a little,
but at least I can hear okay.
Fantastic, sport. But
that's the brachial artery
and it's not how we draw
blood. Now, if we need
to inject him with heroin,
you'll be the first one I call.
Dr. Kelso...
What is it, Dr. Reid? Do
you have something to say?
...No.
You know, son, you
remind me of her so much,
you're just a break-down in the supply
closet away from being the same person!
Look, Brian, if you're
having that much trouble
with your case report, I'd be glad
to take a look at it for you, pal.
Cool. Try to have it back by 5.
O...kay. I have a lot
of things to do...but....
Hey, J.D.? Can I offer a
little constructive criticism?
Kick him in the crotch,
dammit! The crotch!
You know, you're worried
so much about whether
your interns like you
or not that I don't think
they respect you very much.
I had one of mine run out this
morning and get me some dome wax.
Check it
-- zing!
That's really shiny.
Yeah!
You know, I had the same problem when
I started working with the dolphins---
Okay, that's it. I-I-I'm
sorry, Sean, I'm a doctor, okay?
I-I'm teaching humans,
not dolphins, okay?
So it isn't really helpful for
me to know what works on fish.
They're mammals, actually.
Oh, well, Sean! Unfortunately
for me, my interns aren't mammals!
J.D., they are.
S-sh--I don't
care, Sean!
Come on, Turk!
Hey. I just wanted you to know
I don't have a problem with you,
I just can't resist a good storm-off.
Oh, who can?
Stain, I won't lie to ya --
this is gonna hurt a little bit.
Why don't you just paint over it?
Can you believe that
crap Sean was saying?
He was right. Even in college, you cared
way too much about everybody liking you.
Hey, who wants to help me move?
Me!
J.D., could you walk my dog tonight
while I have casual sex
with your friend, Miguel?
Love to!
Hey. Who wants to help me move back?
I know where it all goes...!
Think about it, man. Cox
has taught you the most
since you've been here,
right? Do you really think
he gives a damn whether
you like him or not?
I'd like to think so.
Out of my way, space-waster!
I felt the love.
Catch him and kick him in his junk!
Enjoy. I didn't cut the hand off --
I used a different puppet for that.
Well, if you want, you could give
that one to me and I could fix it.
And have it...for the kids.
Disturbing fetishes aside, I--I
feel like I owe you an apology
on account of acting like
a jackass. But I don't think
that my son should be the
one who has to pay for it.
You actually think that I
would endanger the health
of a child because you're a jackass?
Look, buddy, most of the parents
I deal with are jackasses; now, don't
get me wrong, you're in the top five.
Thank you!
You're welcome. So, the reason
why I have yet to see your child
is because he has the sniffles.
The sniffles?
The sniffles! Look,
you're a doctor, you have
what I like to call The
Burden of Knowledge --
you're gonna be worse than every parent
who freaks out because
their kid eats Play-Doh.
Why? Because you've seen too much;
you've seen what can really go wrong.
If you can get a handle on
that, it's gonna gross you.
You have kids?
One. She hates dolls.
Boy, that's a bummer.
Tell me about it.
That's horrible work. Horrible!
Dr. Kelso, I do have something to say.
Remember earlier, you asked
me if I had something to say?
No!
Well, you did. And...the
reason that I came back here
is because you said that Bruce
and I are alike. And you know what?
You're right. Because you're
treating him the exact same way
you treated me when I first got here!
Dr. Kelso, you only judge us
by these, like, twenty-minute,
pressure-filled windows that you see
us through twice a week, and you--
you never get to know us or how hard
we really work. Because, if you did,
you'd realize that a lot of the times we
fail, it's not our fault -- it's yours.
Is that how you feel, future dentist?
W-well...sometimes you make me feel
like...I can't do anything well,
and I can do lots of things well!
Like what?
I'm a pretty solid human beat-box.
Bru-Bruce, I think he was
talking about medical...things.
No, no-no, I-I'd like to hear him
demonstrate this "beef-box" thing.
Well--well, o-okay. Uh, I g--I guess this
one goes out to my boy, Wayne, in room 302.
He has fluid in his lungs.
Young man! Enjoy your moment.
Oh, my God, Bruce! That was amazing!
Where did you learn how to do that?
In temple.
You're right -- I can
totally see my reflection!
Tell your friends, baby!
Hey, Sean, you were right
about me and my interns.
I guess I owe you an apology.
Damn straight, you do! You know
what your problem is, Bambi? You're--
Oh! Turk! Please? Just one more
second? I need the rush! Please?
I'm coming back for you!
J.D., it's no big deal. We both
know that it wasn't about that.
Well, you...you like Elliot.
Sorry.
Don't sweat it.
You're not pissed off? I'd be pissed
off. Why aren't you pissed off?
I dunno. I guess I just...I don't
see you as that much of a threat.
Ohh.... Cool.
I don't care. All that matters is
finding a way to sleep at night.
Whether it's finally standing
up to your white whale...
...painting over your black spot...
...or imagining Shamu
taking Sean's arm off.
You don't need a doctor to tell you that a
good night's sleep can fix almost anything.
He's got fluid.
www.tvsubtitles.net