Previously on Angel:
None of us are ready just yet.
I don't want you to work for me.
I'll work for you.
Careful with that hand.
You might lose it.
- Isn't that right?
- There's worse things to lose.
They want Angel alive,
Boo-hoo! Let me wipe my tears
with my plastic hand.
If he won't play by the rules,
why should we?
SIG alerts on the 405, 101 and 60,
Better take a helicopter to work,
Your L.A. weather today is sunny,
bright and beautiful,
Am I a lucky guy or what?
I get to meet with the board
and get the quarterlies out.
- Morning, sweetie. Hungry?
- No time.
Oh, have a muffin.
Where's my sugar?
- A manly handshake, huh? Come here.
- Dad.
- We're late.
- I'll start the van.
Jesse, take your vitamins in the car.
Hayley, homework.
Come on, let's go.
Jesse, where are your books?
- I got them.
- And the vitamins.
I got them too. Just keep going.
Come on, Dad. We're gonna be late!
Cordelia. Cordelia! Cordy!
Get her some water.
What is it?
What'd you see?
- How about Western Pacific Power?
- There's threat of investigation.
That's why I was asking.
Where are we with them?
We can tie it up.
They won't miss a dividend.
They've already looted
3.5 billion since deregulation.
Are you suggesting
our clients admit that?
Great idea. They can go to jail
and pay us how?
Litigation is bad PR.
If they refund half a billion...
...we take 20 percent off the top.
Everybody wins.
I'll consider both options.
And the current status of Angel?
He's up, he's down.
He's a barrel of dead monkeys.
He's back with his group.
Sources say he's doing better.
He's not spending all of his time
on the warpath...
...trying to kill...
...well, us.
When do you and Lindsey
meet with Lycor's CFO?
- Oh, I think it's--
- Thursday at 11.
Good. Friday, we'll be
re-evaluating your division.
You can catch me up then.
Let's get to work.
Could you stab me in my back
a little deeper?
You know what re-evaluation means.
One of us gets cut.
- Here, that's a literal cutting.
- Nothing lasts forever.
- That's deep. Why don't you go f--?
- Lindsey, join me?
Some advice about your
attitude towards Angel.
Now, I realize what he did
to you was heartless.
Naturally, your attitude
towards him would be complex.
But it's not professional to air
feelings around colleagues.
People look up to you.
Which reminds me,
I made an appointment for you today.
It'll take a while,
so I cleared your calendar.
Yes. Well, just a....
Well, you'll see.
He had to be crazy.
But he didn't feel crazy.
He felt normal, you know?
- Until he stabbed himself.
- Where did this occur?
I told you, it was in a house.
It could've been...
...an apartment, in a kitchen.
- Narrow it down.
- A nice kitchen? I don't--
- We'll figure it out.
- Start by calling the hospitals.
What? "Did my uncle stab
a knife in his eye?"
They only give information
to relatives.
- I got the hospitals job.
- I'll go to the morgues.
- I'll see if there's a new terror.
- Good idea.
- Keep an eye on her.
- Sure.
We'll be back.
Can I get you anything? Cup of tea?
You let me know.
Lindsey. I'm Dr. Melman.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hi.
Your vitals are good. You've had
all the childhood diseases...
...and you're not allergic.
Let's start with
two milligrams of Versed.
A little something to relax you
before we begin.
- Have any questions?
- What the hell's going on?
- Your boss didn't say?
- No.
- They have a funny sense of humor.
- They keep us hopping.
Your firm is a major source
of our funding.
We see most of you
for your primary care...
...but there are some
less publicized aspects.
- What the hell are you gonna do?
- Please, don't be alarmed.
They moved you to the top
of the transplant list.
- Transplant?
- Yes, your hand.
We're gonna give you a new one.
Don't be so nervous.
This is cause for applause.
In just a few hours' time,
you'll be doing the applauding.
- Let's go.
- Get the soft tissue ready.
- Here you go. 4.0 silk.
- Connecting the extensors.
You're doing great, Lindsey.
Where's the Pockla?
Release the tourniquet.
I'm waiting on the Pockla.
Here it comes.
Okay, let's get him to post-op.
My father's name is Henry Addison.
Yeah, I'm his son, Gunn. Ter.
Gunter Addison.
But if he's had a manic episode,
he might not know his name.
It'd be a serious knife
wound in his eye.
- You sure? All right, thanks.
- How's she doing?
She grunted once around noon, then
got on with the maniacal cleaning.
Guess what I found? More nothing
than usual. How about you?
- Nothing.
- We need more to go on.
We'll just have to talk
to Cordelia, get her to--
Dig a little deeper?
Go ahead. Best not to crowd her.
You're the one in charge now.
You're right. That's why
I'm assigning this one to you.
Hey.
Boy, you could see your reflection
in that glass.
I couldn't because of
the vampire situation.
- But a normal person....
- What do you want?
We need help.
We're not getting anywhere.
I'm sorry. He's probably dead by now.
We don't know that for sure.
There could be others.
I wish it would stop hurting.
What do you want me to do?
Not exactly sure.
Maybe you can look again.
You know, inside.
That's all I've been doing, all day.
That guy in the kitchen.
A normal guy...
...and he picks up a knife.
And--
Oh, God! I think he had kids.
- How do you know that?
- Cereal bowls on the table.
And there was a book bag.
It has a name of a school on it.
D-something. Delaney or....
Delancey School.
That's good, that's great.
Anything else?
I just keep seeing it.
Get some rest.
Wesley and Gunn will look into it.
- Can I get you anything?
- Why does everyone ask me that?
No reason.
She's still rocking,
We've got weather and traffic coming,
so keep it right here,
- Good to see you. Pleasure.
- One of our finest.
- Here's Lilah Morgan. Mr. Kraigle.
- Nice to see you.
Use my office.
Irv, call me if you need anything.
You're in good hands.
- Thanks.
- Mr. Kraigle.
- Please, call me Irv.
- Thank you.
That's an expensive operation,
quarter mil.
I guess they like you.
They really like you.
- He's waiting.
- You think you have it in the bag.
I don't think anything, Lilah.
You're the one in pain here?
I can't believe they chose you.
- We didn't do anything wrong,
- It's not about that.
It's about what a jury may award.
Cancer from chocolate? How?
Sell it in a tin
that leaches cytoclistomene.
But how could we know that?
The Chinese sold us the tin.
Don't worry. If a jury ever
hears this, and that's a big "if"...
...they'll be handpicked
or enchanted by us.
Why can't people take responsibility?
The Chinese gave them cancer.
- Actually, it was the Drizon Company.
- Who?
It's a corporation that split
from your company six years ago.
They're responsible
for the tin containers...
...your company fills with chocolate.
- Really?
- The plaintiffs want to sue Drizon.
But they're going bankrupt
this summer.
Are you getting this?
- He's good, isn't he?
- Yeah, he's great.
Well, this is very helpful.
Very comforting.
We're not doing anything unlawful?
No. More importantly,
we're preserving your company.
I have to go.
- Something wrong?
- No. No, nothing is wrong.
Who are you?
Thanks, keep the change.
A whole dollar just for me.
I'm the luckiest delivery man....
- What's all this?
- Lunch. I was hungry.
You don't eat food.
It doesn't keep me alive,
but I get a hankering.
For turkey, ham
and roast beef sandwiches?
You missed the vegetarian.
Soup and salad too?
What is going on here?
- I forgot what you liked.
- Why didn't you ask me?
You said, why does everyone...
...ask if they can get you anything?
So you did this instead?
Yeah.
I love you.
You ought to do that more.
- Buy you food?
- Smile.
What?
Okay, this is weird.
Before he put the knife in his eye...
...he was happy about his eye.
- Like it was new or something.
- New.
We found him. Joseph Kramer.
Has two kids.
They go to the Delancey School.
Kids didn't show up.
Mom called.
Said she's taking them away.
Their father supposedly
got a promotion.
- Get a home address?
- We've been there.
- And?
- No trace of belongings.
The place had been cleaned.
The carpet was still wet.
To get rid of the blood.
Little piece of molding they missed.
- Wanna sniff?
- How about I just believe you?
- What do we know?
- Nothing.
Guy's gone, family's gone.
Someone has the power to make
them all disappear in a day.
- We're at a dead end.
- I thought we had more.
There's only one thing we can do.
Oh, God. Oh, no.
- The karaoke bar.
- Angel's gonna sing?
- Isn't there another way?
- There has to be.
Hey, what?
Pretty girl on every corner
Sunshine turns the sky to gold
Warm, warm, it's always warm here
And I can't take the cold
You should pick something short.
- "Stairway to Heaven"?
- Don't even joke about that.
- Oh, my God, look who's--
- Lindsey?
Isn't he fabulous?
He comes here?
He came a lot, before someone
chopped off his strumming hand.
Looks like he's got a new one.
She's pretty as a picture
Wow! He's good.
Lawyer's got some pipes.
Fills me with love and laughter
- You think he's good?
- Shh.
I can't feel a thing
The sky's gonna open
People gonna pray and crawl
What is that? Rock? Country? Ballad?
Pick a style.
- Shh.
- Don't make me ask you to leave.
The sky's gonna open
People gonna pray and sing
I can't feel
- I can't sing now.
- You won't have to.
Sure is good to have you back
in the saddle.
Your favorite, TNT.
I got a crazy man's hand
who wants to kill someone...
...maybe me.
What do you see?
Well, the hand is quicker
than the eye.
- You'll get that later.
- I need help.
I'll say. You might want
to start with the singing.
Hi. You probably don't remember me.
Cordelia.
I know you're evil and everything
but that was just so amazing.
- That was tight.
- Terrific.
Is everyone drunk?
What's he doing here?
What are you looking at?
I don't allow violence in here.
Angel's here for the reason you are.
- How's that?
- Two enemies, one case.
Coming together in a beautiful way.
- They're working together on this?
- Work with him? With him?
- Did anyone see 48 Hours?
- I got a murderous hand...
...and you're teaming me up with
the guy who cut mine off?
I'm telling you what's what, sugar.
What you do with it is up to you.
If I ever see you outside the club,
I'm gonna kill you.
Resentment's an ugly emotion.
I hope you've overcome yours.
Right now, he has your case in the...
...forgive me, palm of his hand. Toodles.
If he's the lead,
shouldn't we follow him?
The guy in your vision got an eye,
and Lindsey got a hand.
We should find where
the transplants were done.
- So we're following him, right?
- We need to follow his new hand.
I wonder who it belonged to.
Hand belongs to a white male,
Bradley Scott.
Served two years for embezzlement.
Paroled last month.
- How'd you find out?
- I'm a detective.
- Did he have a life?
- Why don't you look--?
I am.
Impressive, Angel.
Well, sometimes you gotta
follow your--
So how did your--?
Get you into the NCIC?
- The what?
- National Crime and Information Center.
Long story.
How's it coming over there?
We got time.
Nobody used to question
my methods or my singing.
You're half right.
I hired a private detective.
He's got a friend.
- We're private detectives.
- We have friends.
We did. She got fired.
Get over it.
Bradley Scott.
While dumping bearer bonds
on the black market, he worked...
- ...at Wolfram & Hart.
- Is he still alive?
His records say he reported to his
parole officer, then disappeared.
He gets out of jail, then-- Whack!
They give his hand to Lindsey.
They really wanna give him everything.
- Who is it?
- You don't know me.
My name's Lindsey McDonald.
I work for Wolfram & Hart.
- What do you want?
- To talk to you.
Can I come in?
Oh, it's okay. I'm alone.
Professional habit.
I see a lot of lowlifes.
I guess so, being a parole officer.
This is off the record.
I had a procedure done
at Fairfield Clinic.
They've paid you to do things
for them in the past.
I need to find out
where they get their body parts.
- What's the code?
- Code?
If you're with Wolfram & Hart,
you know it.
I'm a lawyer there
but this isn't my case.
I don't know the code.
I can pay you--
Tell me what the game is.
It's no game, all right?
This is about me.
Goodbye.
- Friend of yours?
- No, he's not.
I'm about to put a bullet
in your buddy's brain here!
I got him. I know I got him.
- What are you doing?
- Saving your life?
- I don't need you!
- Watch that!
- A little gratitude.
- You got no business--
- Why aren't you trying to kill me?
- I'm on a case.
Why is it always about killing you?
You guys got issues, so I'll just--
You're choking my lead!
"My lead!"
Are we on a schoolyard?
You gotta learn how
to play with others.
I'm gonna loosen the rope.
Tell me all about Bradley Scott.
- Who?
- Guy whose hand you got. Listen up.
- Don't tell me what to do.
- So immature.
Shut up!
- We're waiting.
- I'm not telling you zip.
You can kill me.
Wolfram & Hart will do worse.
Kill you?
Why would I kill you
when I could live off you for a month?
- Can't you taste the butterfat?
- You're gross.
I'll tell you!
Scott stole some bearer bonds.
When he got paroled,
Wolfram & Hart assigned him to me.
Your file says he was a no-show.
But you saw him.
- Once.
- You took him to Fairfield Clinic?
No, not there.
- Where?
- Just some address.
I don't know what they do there
and I don't wanna know.
Her vision hangovers
are getting longer and longer.
She can't rest until it's done.
I know. She inherited them from Doyle.
He was half-demon.
I' m not sure the human body
can carry....
Last year, a demon unleashed a slew
of visions on her.
She wound up in hospital,
out of her mind.
She's been a little cranky lately,
but she's not...
Angel, where are you?
I can't hear you.
- ...crazy.
- Are you there?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Gunn and Wesley are playing with
the doors. I'm trying to work here.
Okay, we'll wait here.
I'm fine. Just get it done.
Funny thing happened the other day.
A guy sticks a butcher knife
in his own eye.
Guess he went to the same clinic.
Your hand hasn't been doing
anything funny lately, has it?
It's none of my business,
but you don't seem happy.
I know you're Mr. Save-a-Soul.
You used to fight with your enemies.
I guess it's a lot to carry.
I mean, losing Darla.
I mean, even me, in a way,
as a place to focus your rage.
It's ironic. I mean, here you are,
young and healthy...
...good job, new hand.
The more you get, the less you have.
Am I getting through here?
You just keep on moping.
You're good at that.
Okay. That where you took him?
- Know this place?
- No.
I'm thinking security
will be top drawer.
Window sensors,
motion detectors, guards.
- I don't have my laptop.
- Huh?
To hack into the system
and break the codes--
Wait a minute. That's a bother.
Why don't we just fight?
You might want to step aside.
Come on, work off some
of that aggression.
The floor is hollow.
What is this?
You know what this is.
Spare parts for guys like you.
You got your "before"...
...and your "after."
More like "during," I guess.
Your firm in action, Lindsey.
Lot to be proud of, huh?
Pockla blessed this place.
- Who are they?
- Demon healers.
They know how to regenerate flesh.
That's why the transplants
aren't taking well.
One was there
when they gave me my hand.
Your hand? I think it belonged
to that guy over there.
Or what's left of him, anyway.
Oh, God. I know him.
I didn't get the name before.
We worked in the mailroom together.
Brad.
Kill.
Kill who? Huh?
Who do you want to kill?
Kill me.
Please.
What am I supposed to do?
I know what I'd do,
but this is your deal.
Whatever it is, do it quick.
They're gonna come in force.
We gotta help them.
I'm sorry.
Help these people upstairs.
Get them to the car.
How's everything in your head?
What?
Any vision aftermaths?
It's better.
What?
It's just-- They're starting
to take a toll.
It's part of the job, right?
These re-evaluations
are a mixed blessing.
Sad, as we lose one of our own.
But also hopeful,
as we promote one of our own.
Lilah, you have made a lot
of great contributions...
...and you've tried your best--
No!
Lilah, please.
They chose me.
I'm clearly the guy.
Yes, you are.
You could have had it.
You didn't have what it takes.
An evil hand. I mean, come on.
Who here does, huh? Leon doesn't.
Charlie doesn't.
You know you gave me
an evil hand?
I've been writing "kill"
on everything.
It's crazy.
Anything could happen.
- Allan.
- Allan, how are you?
It's gonna hurt in the morning!
Come here.
Stop it, evil hand. Stop it!
I just can't control my evil hand.
Nathan, I'm so proud
that you chose me. Charlie!
But if I was in your shoes...
...I would've chosen Lilah.
You know why?
Do you have any idea
the hours she's logged in?
The files she has on you guys?
Deep stuff.
Ronnie, your stock manipulations.
Nathan's offshore accounts.
Can you imagine if those files
got back to the senior partners?
They'd eat you alive!
She's been working overtime.
She's all you ever dreamed of.
Lilah is your guy.
Me?
I'm unreliable.
I got these evil-hand issues...
...and I'm bored with this crap.
Besides, I'm leaving,
so if you wanna chase me...
...be my guest.
But remember. Evil.
Charlie.
Good luck.
Evil.
Well, let's amend the minutes.
Lilah Morgan was promoted.
And someone call an ambulance.
If you're here to kill me, get in line.
I really like this truck.
'56, right?
First year they had
wraparound windshields.
Back in the '50s, we all thought life
would be like The Jetsons now.
Air cars, robots. I'd love to have
an air car. Wouldn't that be cool?
You're gonna talk me to death?
Things don't always
work out like you think.
I bet Wolfram & Hart aren't happy
losing one of their best.
Let them try to stop me.
It'll be fun.
Is that a healthy attitude?
Where are you going, Lindsey?
Back to your roots?
Something like that.
Hope you're not waiting for me
to say I learned a lesson.
That now I see the light--
If you say that, I'd have to kill you.
No. I'm just here to say bon voyage.
Don't come back.
To L.A.? No.
You can have this place.
Good. Glad I didn't have
to do something immature.
The key to Wolfram & Hart...
...don't let them make you play
their game.
Make them play yours.
Thanks. I'll keep that in mind.
Don't drive too fast, now.
Lot of cops out there.