Previously on Angel:
There are forces
you know nothing about.
You think I'll stand by
while you finish the game?
Police. Nobody move!
Stay down or they'll kill you.
- Darla, how are you?
- I'm fine, Holland.
They brought her back.
I need to know why. Why human?
You were given a second chance.
Don't throw it away--
- I'm dying.
- Syphilitic heart condition. Terminal.
I won't leave you.
Every moment you have...
...I'll be by your side.
You'll never be alone.
How did you think this would end?
We're almost there.
Anybody home?
- Oh, my God.
- What happened?
He's been in and out.
Only got half the story.
- It didn't make sense.
- Angel?
- There's no time, no time.
- Let's sit him down here.
- Where was he?
- The motel.
- Darla's?
- Should've heard them.
I got him to the truck
before he burst into flames.
He's hurt.
Something not good went down.
- Angel?
- I was just so tired.
- Where is Darla?
- I don't know.
I knew it. She did this to him.
- I knew she couldn't be trusted.
- She's dead.
- What?
- I should've stopped them.
- They made her drink.
- Angel?
She didn't want to.
You think that you can resist...
...but then it's too late.
- Someone made Darla drink?
- It was her.
Way too many pronouns here.
Who's "her"?
Drusilla.
- Drusilla's here?
- Good lord.
Who's Drusilla?
Angel?
I'm guessing she's got a set of teeth?
- Yes, she's a vampire.
- I'm getting the picture.
- You should sit.
- I must find her.
Drusilla?
She ain't in there.
- He's delirious.
- I can save her.
- Save whom?
- Darla.
If what you say is so, there's no
saving Darla. It's too late.
- It's not too late.
- It is.
She's dead already
and she will rise again.
She won't.
I can save her from that.
I'm still trying to get this
family tree straight.
- Darla sired Angel.
- Correct.
- Angel sired Drusilla.
- When he and Darla were together.
- But before Angel got his soul back?
- Certainly.
These lawyers brought
Darla back as human.
- Now this Drusilla bites Darla?
- So it would seem.
- Making her a vampire again.
- That's the cosmological upshot.
Darla's human self has died, and
before dawn, unless Angel stops it...
...she will rise again,
a soulless demon.
- That means--
- Clock is ticking.
What I'm saying is, the granddaughter
remade the grandmother.
Oh. Yes.
Man, that weirds me out
more than the blood-sucking thing.
How do you feel?
What do you got?
Sunset is at 5:47 pm,
which...
...was six minutes ago,
and sunrise is at 6:15 am.
It could happen anytime before then.
Anything?
Lindsey McDonald's assistant says
he's in the office, but in a meeting.
- Has been all day.
- Right.
You can't go into
those offices undetected.
I'm not going to.
That's what they want.
You don't believe he's there.
I was at the only meeting
Lindsey had today.
- So where are you going?
- To his home.
- I'll go with you.
- We all will.
No. You're all staying here.
You can't go in uninvited.
You need us.
Not this time.
What's the plan?
Stand outside and make remarks?
He invited me in once.
This time, when I kick that door down,
I go through it. Alone.
Excuse me.
The open house isn't until Saturday.
Where is the man who lived here?
Moved.
When?
- The truck was here yesterday.
- Did he leave a forwarding address?
I can't give out--
It's an emergency,
regarding a friend...
...who's in need of some
immediate medical attention.
Well, he's asked that I forward
everything to his place of employment.
- Do you know where that is?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
This is about the cousin, isn't it?
- Cousin?
- That sweet...
...but very odd English girl
who was visiting him?
Yeah. Yes, it is.
I knew that pregnancy was in trouble.
Thin as a rail.
Couldn't be healthy for the baby.
She's having a baby?
She was very excited about
getting the nursery ready.
Of course.
Dru would want the ritual.
She wasn't interested,
wanted something on the west side.
She insisted her daughter
be born near the stars.
- Stars?
- Well, she's foreign.
I told her you can live your whole
life in L.A. and never see a star.
I can hear them singing to me.
So this place works for you?
Oh, yeah.
Grandmother is very pleased with it.
I can tell.
Aren't you, Grandmother?
- My daughter.
- Can she hear you?
She's dead.
Oh. Of course.
Shh. Just for now.
Got a shot with her now?
- Lilah....
- Don't let me interrupt you.
Drusilla, you are positively glowing.
- I'm going to be a mummy.
- Yes. Yes, you are.
- Is there anything you need?
- No.
If you do,
you know how to contact us.
We would love to stay for the birth,
but we have a previous engagement.
- I have preparations to make myself.
- Of course you do.
And we'll leave you to it, then.
- Lindsey?
- Maybe I should stay.
This is a family matter, Lindsey.
We'd best leave it that way.
Run and catch
The lamb is caught...
...in the blackberry patch
Here's the list of local cemeteries,
funeral homes and mausoleums.
We have to go to each place
and dig up graves?
- She'll want the body in the ground.
- Are you certain?
Burial isn't necessary
for a new vampire.
- Will be for her. She's a classicist.
- She's a loony.
Stick with cemeteries
with a view of the night sky.
- So just outside cemeteries, then?
- Doesn't narrow it down much.
If it's just a burial she's after, one
doesn't need a cemetery. Just dirt.
Still not narrowing.
Whole planet, made up of dirt.
Maybe I'm looking at this wrong.
Dru doesn't see this thing
as a death, but as a birth.
She talked about the nursery.
I fear you may be looking
for a logical pattern...
...in the rantings of someone
who isn't logical.
Soil.
Soil near the stars.
She wanted to be near the stars.
She talked to them. She spent hours
in my garden communing with the sky.
Maybe she didn't mean baby nursery.
You said she liked the garden.
Plant nursery's got dirt, the view.
It's more a birth than a death place.
Maybe if we find one up high,
that'll be it.
Maybe one with a relationship
with Wolfram & Hart.
Large firm like that, they may do
business with a corporate supplier.
That's not a fitting gift at all
for our newborn grandmummy.
I saw you coming, my lovely.
The moon showed me.
It told me to come
into the 20th century.
It's the 21st century, Dru.
I'm still lagging.
Now everybody's home.
Baby's up from her little nap.
Grandmum!
Angel?
- How'd it go?
- Gear up. We need to move fast.
I guess not great?
- They're out there.
- So you did find them?
- Where are they?
- I don't know.
- You know where they'll be?
- Not exactly.
- Yet you have your suspicions?
- Actually, I don't.
- It's more like a hunch.
- Not a hunch.
Would you say inkling?
Please tell me you could say that.
If we find them before they join up...
...we can stop something ugly
before it starts.
I don't think the four of us
in one car is going to yield results.
Which is why we'll follow
the one solid lead we have.
- We'll go to Wolfram & Hart.
- Hit the pause button.
Wolfram & Hart? Vampire detectors,
security system and armed guards?
- Nice plan, General Custer.
- Drusilla's insane. Deadly.
Darla needs to feed.
Once she does, she'll be stronger.
Either we go back to the people
who brought them here...
...or we sit and wait
for the bodies to pile up.
I decided not to wait. If you want
to join me, my car's outside.
If not, that's fine too.
- You had me at "Everyone gear up."
- Let's go.
Lindsey, my wife wants to know if
you're bringing a date this evening.
Something about how many
crab cakes to order.
No, I don't have a date.
You've been doing stellar work. Don't
think the partners haven't noticed.
- I'm happy to hear that.
- Your work isn't all they notice.
It's also important to have healthy
attachments outside of the office.
I know our roles don't allow
much time to socialize.
- Find the time.
- Yes, sir.
Don't be late. I'm uncorking
a case of 1928 Chateau Latour.
- I wouldn't miss it.
- We've worked hard.
Let's enjoy our success.
I drank Chateau Latour once.
- It tasted like lion's blood.
- Drusilla. I apologize.
I didn't realize you were here.
I trust everything went as you hoped.
I'm very worried about Grandmum.
The building was quite tall, you know.
Darla's a survivor.
- Angelus wasn't happy in the least.
- Angel found you?
Well, not unexpected.
How did he fare?
Angelus is on his way here now.
He's very cross.
I wouldn't worry about that.
We've taken precautions.
The important thing is that
we reunite you with your baby.
Yes?
General alert. An untamed
vampire is in the building.
Perhaps we should take
our guest to security.
Darla.
Lindsey, no sudden movement.
Warm.
Let them leave the building
without incident.
Healthy attachments, Lindsey.
It's no good if we don't
get there in one piece.
We don't have much time.
- Angel, pull over.
- I'll slow down.
No, she's having a vision.
Tell me it ain't us she's seeing
wrapped around a lamppost.
It's the other way. Turn around!
- We're almost there.
- Angel.
- She should've done this before.
- Angel!
Maybe it's a false alarm.
Did I do something to displease you?
Grandmother, why?
Don't be angry.
Why?
For you.
All for you.
I thought it was what you wanted.
To be saved.
All alone.
All alone in the dirt.
We've lost our way, and the little
wormy won't dance if he's told to.
No. No.
You two want to move it
out of the street?
That's right, sweetheart.
Why don't you and your girlfriend
make out at home?
The rest of us have lives.
Not for long.
You're all new again.
Let's go shopping.
Morgog, I worship you.
Ruler of the universe, I will throw
out my worthless life to you.
Morgog.
- What do you want?
- We're here to help.
I have to do this. Morgog
commands me. His will be done.
- Don't! You stay back.
- Easy, boss.
He's ready to snap, crackle and pop.
I felt it in my vision.
We've got to handle him with care.
You know, delicate.
- Wait, jeez. Oh, jeez.
- Listen. I'm not here to hurt you.
Morgog's not the way. He couldn't
find his hump without a map.
So don't kill yourself.
He's not worth it.
And you've got, you know,
a million reasons to live. I bet.
Okay? Got it? Good.
- We're not done.
- I am.
There's a reason why we're here.
- I don't have time for this.
- Maybe that's the plan.
And that young man
still needs our help.
Go help him. I got
more important things to do.
Can I have it? Can I?
Of course. But a little color
would bring out your eyes more.
- Such pretty eyes.
- Men are drawn to them.
Aren't they, though?
- Here.
- Ooh.
Ooh. I'm ringing.
Do you hear it?
I'm ringing all over.
Oh, yeah. Forgot about that.
Hello, Holland.
Darla. Feeling better, I trust.
- Like my old self again,
- Splendid,
I understand you girls
have been on a little spree,
- Is that a problem?
- On the contrary,
As a matter of fact,
I was just thinking,
Why settle for a spree
when you could have, say...
...a massacre?
- A massacre?
- Ooh.
I like the sound of that.
Of course, you have the support
of Wolfram & Hart behind you.
I appreciate that.
Not at all, Darla.
That's what we're here for.
Do you like it?
- Am I pretty, then?
- As a picture.
Now if we can only get
some shoes to go with it.
Excuse me, miss.
Any shoe suggestions
for my friend's ensemble?
I said, excuse me.
Customer with a question here.
Service in this place
is really unacceptable.
They'll keep Angel busy.
- Until he kills them.
- He'll find that...
...more difficult than he realizes.
Lilah's correct.
We won't have to worry about Angel--
- Dru and Darla, where are they?
- Angel.
I don't believe
we've had the pleasure.
I'd be careful who
you offer that hand to.
You might just lose it.
Isn't that right, Lindsey?
There's worse things to lose,
aren't there?
- So you pull the strings here.
- A few of them.
- I am Head of Special Projects.
- Projects like Darla?
Darla's just a tool.
Means to an end.
You're the project.
I can take your life
before they lift a finger.
I'm sure you can.
As sure as I am you won't.
- Won't I?
- You don't kill humans.
You don't qualify.
You set things in motion.
Play your little games up here in your
glass tower and innocent people die.
And yet, I just can't seem to care.
But you do.
While you make threats and waste time,
crashing through windows...
...your girls are out
painting the town red, red, red.
- Where?
- That would be telling.
In any case, you should hurry.
Lives hang in the balance, waiting
for their champion to save them.
Mm-hm. You'll let me walk out of here?
As a matter of fact, I will.
You misunderstand us, Angel.
We don't want you dead. Yet.
If we did, you wouldn't
be standing here.
Please escort our guest
out of the building.
I'd walk you out myself,
but I'm late for a wine tasting.
And just so we're clear
on the matter...
...you're not invited.
I'll send a bill for the window.
After I stop Darla and Dru,
I'll pay you in person.
Yeah. Go do your champion thing.
Then come see me.
If you make bail. Give him a nice
holding cell, officers. With a window.
Southern exposure preferred.
The firm may not want you dead...
- ...but I'm cool with it.
- Watch your head.
Perfect.
Go.
How do you want to do this? Should I
escape now or wait? Because I'm not--
Two people were murdered
in a clothing store.
Reports say two women were spotted.
One matches the description
of your pal, Darla.
They're not done, are they?
No.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I don't think
I can stop them.
Maybe you can. Pull over.
- Lindsey, welcome.
- Good evening, Catherine.
Holland's downstairs
lording over his wine cellar.
These are lovely. Thank you.
The senior partners have informed me
they are very pleased...
...with the work
our division has done.
Things have been
progressing nicely...
...and ahead of schedule,
I might add.
I'd be remiss without
extending well-earned praise...
...to the two members of our team
who made it possible.
- Lilah Morgan and Lindsey McDonald.
- Thank you, Holland.
It's no secret our work is
one small element...
...in a much larger, greater plan.
One which the senior
partners hoped....
Ladies.
- How--?
- Your wife kindly invited us in.
- Ah.
- Very sweet, she was.
Like clover.
And honey.
Think of it as our way
of giving you what you want.
- What would I...?
- I believe you said something about...
...a massacre.
Just keep that area blocked off.
Pretty lawyers, all in a row.
Eenie-meenie....
I'm glad you're alive, Darla.
I'm glad we were able to save you.
Are you?
I guess you really care
about me as a person.
I guess I owe all of you.
The whole team.
You have beautiful skin.
I moisturize.
That was very thoughtful of you.
You brought me back as human.
A dying one, at that.
Let me wallow with a soul,
then sent me back to Angel...
...for him to restore me.
Which he should have done
right away. But I miscalculated.
I thought he cared more.
Like you do.
Grandmum won't eat the doublespeak.
No. No, she won't eat that.
It's okay. It's all over.
They're gone now.
- They killed those people.
- I know.
The police are here.
They'll take care of you.
You were in here the entire time?
I needed a new dress
for the office party.
This one was too expensive,
but I couldn't make up my mind.
I kept thinking they would
come in and kill me too.
Did you see or hear any of it?
I mostly heard.
I was lucky because of the party.
- It's okay. You'll make your party.
- No, their party.
- They were in a hurry to get to it.
- They said something about a party?
A tasting.
You just go on outside
and find an officer.
You'll be okay.
Thank you.
It was just too much.
I hear the sirens.
They don't know if the world
will be there in the morning.
Do you hear the sirens?
Are the police coming?
No.
She senses what this place
was built for.
Yes, you're right. This was originally
a bomb shelter in the '50s.
We had it converted.
Wine has always been my passion.
People...
...huddled together...
...crouching in fear.
I imagine that's what it
would have been like in a war.
No. Now.
She means now.
Ah-ha.
I guess I stepped into that one.
Listen, Darla, I am sorry
that you had to suffer...
...but look what's come out of it.
You've been restored.
You're a superior being.
You can have anything.
There's not a person who won't work
around the clock to see you get it.
Gung ho, are they?
Because all I'm sensing right now
is big, stinky fear.
But not from you.
You know what I'm getting
from you, Lindsey?
Nothing.
Why aren't you afraid?
I don't know.
You could die here.
Chances are, you will.
Yeah.
- And you don't care?
- I care.
I guess I just don't mind.
No one's dying. It's a friendly
get-together amongst colleagues.
We're all on the same side.
I love this room. Dru, honey.
In our new digs,
we have to put in a people cellar.
Help us.
Daddy's home.
Angelus.
- Here for the tasting?
- Look what we have for you.
It's not Daddy. It's never Daddy.
It's the Angel-beast.
- Come to punish us.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Spank us till Tuesday.
We promise to be bad if you do.
Angel....
- I'm sorry I didn't get there in time.
- I'm not.
He's soul-sick.
Not even thinking about
his own family.
Only thinking about them.
Come on, love. I never did
get that goodbye kiss.
You will.
But not tonight.
- For God's sake, help us.
- Angel, please.
People are going to die.
And yet, somehow,
I just can't seem to care.
Angel, please. We can negotiate.
Daddy.
No, no!
They're killing us! Killing us!
And you just walked away?
No, I walked to my car
and then I drove away.
You didn't do anything?
You gave Darla and Drusilla free rein?
I didn't bring either of them
into this. They did.
- You could've stopped them.
- I will.
When? After they've finished off
the people you don't like?
It's true these lawyers
brought this on themselves.
But what you did--
- Is wrong.
- You went too far.
We've all been worried about you.
I guess we share some of the blame.
- We should've spoken up sooner.
- And louder.
You have to change the way
you do things.
Don't you see
where this is taking you?
Right now the three of us are all
that stands between you and darkness.
Best believe that, man.
I do.
You're all fired.
Thank you, thank you very much,