The Hyperion Hotel.
- It seems to be abandoned.
- 68 rooms, 68 vacancies.
- I'd say, built in the late '20s.
- That's my guess.
It's in what used to be old Hollywood.
Probably empty for years.
From the look of it.
English Breakfast tea...
...coffee, O-pos.
Is its current condition due to more
than just the tourist trade drying up?
Yeah.
Something the matter?
I, uh....
I think it's gone bad.
It's starting to coagulate.
No, that's cinnamon.
I can't try something?
What do we do?
I need you two to find out
about this place.
- Who's the client?
- No client. I'll check back later.
- Cryptic much?
- This goes beyond real estate.
Look at cold police files.
Homicides, missing persons...
...everything from
the beginning to now.
You think whatever lived there
did so for some time.
Probably right up to the end.
Returned mail for 315.
Mr. Ferris should try using stamps.
Mrs. Miggins' breakfast from Val's
Liquors. They've cut off her credit.
And the weekly bill for 217.
Whoa, whoa, why me?
I did it last time.
Guy gives me the heebie-jeebies.
Say, how about instead
I deliver an eviction notice?
We cannot evict residents
because they're strange.
If we did, we'd close down.
Ever look into his eyes?
There's nothing there.
Hello? Bellman. Anybody home?
Okay. Well, I guess
you've gone out, so....
I'll just leave this here...
...and you can pick it up
when it's convenient.
Come on, come on.
Are you now or have you ever been a
member of the Communist Party?
I'm framing my answer in the
only way an American citizen--
Then you deny....
Come on, honey. This is how
Lana Turner got started.
No messages for 217.
Mr. Carter's bag to 515. Thanks.
I know what the sign says,
but we have no vacancies right now.
Sign's wrong. Sure it is. Come on.
Yes....
I understand.
Of course.
I am.
I'll be finished in two shakes, sir.
You're not the maid.
What do you mean?
You're no maid.
There's no trolley outside...
...those sheets are dirty...
...and you're the wrong color.
I'm sorry.
The door was open. I just--
There's nothing to steal.
No, I wasn't stealing.
I can explain--
Not interested. Just go.
- I can't.
- I'll help you.
My boyfriend,
he's the jealous type.
Then you shouldn't
wander into men's rooms.
He can't find me.
Where is she?
Look, pal,
this is none of your business.
That's why you're gonna go away.
I know you're hiding her in there.
- I'm not hiding anybody.
- No?
Then send her out here
so I don't have to get her.
You're not coming in here.
You won't mind if I come in
and look around, then?
Guess I do mind.
He's going down.
Gosh. That was.... Gosh!
Listen, I know we got off on
the wrong foot. My name is Judy.
The hotel closed its doors
on December 16, 1919,
That morning, the concierge made
his rounds with a 12-gauge shotgun...
...room to room.
It's been empty ever since.
According to city records,
it was declared a landmark.
The company that owns it has been
trying to sell for 10 years...
- ...no buyers.
- Well, no wonder.
These records indicate
a storied legacy...
...of murder and mayhem
dating back to '28...
...when a roofer killed himself
and two others.
Wow. That's really interesting.
What are we doing?
- Doing?
- Yes.
Angel never told us
the point of all this.
Ah, well. I mean, clearly...
...he has us organizing data,
compiling incidents so that....
Yes, I did notice that,
the "no point" thing.
Frankly, I haven't the slightest idea
what to do with all this.
Wesley.
Look who was staying here in '52.
Well, now we know
one thing for certain.
Yup, vampires do photograph,
they just don't do it well.
I mean, we know that Angel had
a connection to this place.
So why didn't he just tell us?
Perhaps he was ashamed to.
Yes.
Yes, I did.
Yes, I do.
She was cleaning
when she found him.
- She touch anything?
- Consuela? Does she ever?
Oh, my goodness.
This is the third one in three months.
Why does this happen here?
- The guy seemed depressed.
- How could you tell?
Kind of cheap, though. The
death-wishers usually tip better.
Take a look at the way his body
is laid down. You can tell....
Three in three months,
they'll shut you down,
Yes. They will.
Who do you want me to call first?
What?
- The carpet cleaners or the cops?
- Don't call anyone.
- They'll shut us down.
- What about him?
- We can't leave him.
Right. Store him in the meat locker.
Store him?
We're gonna store him?
The salesman in 215 shot himself.
- Really, suicide?
- In this hotel.
- They're not reporting it.
- Terrible!
Why? It was a suicide.
Why involve anyone else?
- Are all writers crass?
- Are all actors naive?
Do you want the press
to get involved?
- Nothing wrong with discretion.
- That's what I say.
Maybe this wasn't a suicide,
Are you sure you're safe here?
The world ends in 10 minutes.
I saw you over here.
I thought I'd say hello. Hello!
Have you seen the show?
You should.
It makes whatever problems
we have seem insignificant.
The entire universe explodes.
- Sounds exciting.
- Well, it's air-conditioned.
And it's cheaper than
going to the pictures.
I had to get out of the hotel.
Did he come back?
Come back?
Your boyfriend.
Oh. No.
I mean the guy in 215.
- He killed himself.
- Yeah. I guess so.
Imagine that wallpaper being
the last thing you ever see?
Maybe it was the wallpaper
that drove him to it.
I sort of hate it there.
I guess it's nicer than some places.
It's a place.
Listen, I know you didn't
want to help me before...
...but you did.
And I want to thank you.
You're gonna miss
the end of the world.
Right.
See you around.
Yeah.
Put Frank Gilnitz in '52.
But he wasn't executed until '54.
Shouldn't he go there?
He wasn't executed until '54,
but the crime...
...of murdering a salesman and
storing his body in the meat locker...
That occurred in '52.
It's like a puzzle.
The who-died-horribly-because
Angel-screwed up-50-years-ago game.
--so the guy asks me:
- "Do they serve peanuts here?"
- So?
- So he was thinking about peanuts?
- Maybe he was hungry.
- This wasn't suicide.
- I thought his door was locked.
- Exactly.
- It's too perfect.
Locked-door mystery.
I've written it a hundred times.
Hey!
Can you come in for a sec?
Did you hear?
Hear what?
The guy in 215.
It wasn't a suicide.
He was murdered.
- I don't think so.
- So it's true.
There's gonna be police
and questions...
...and I thought that you might
want to know, in case maybe--
- Not that you're hiding anything.
- Everyone here's hiding something.
Yeah....
I kind of owe you one, on account
of what you did for me before.
Thanks.
I guess if we left now,
it would look bad.
That all depends.
This have anything to do with
that P.I. I tossed out of here?
You knew he wasn't my boyfriend.
I had a hunch.
I think he works
for my former employers.
City Trust Bank of Salina, Kansas.
I was a teller there.
I think maybe they want this back.
I haven't spent any of it.
Not a dime. I won't touch it.
- Why take it?
- I don't know.
I was angry. I panicked.
Things were going so well.
I loved this job
and I loved this guy.
We were engaged and...
...they found out about me
and I got fired.
And then Peter dumped me
and I just couldn't go back there...
...so I took this and I just ran.
Aren't you gonna ask
why they fired me?
Why did they fire you?
Because I'm not what I say I am.
- I've been passing since I was 15.
- Passing?
For white.
My mom was colored. My father...
...I didn't know him.
My blood isn't pure. It's tainted.
It's just blood, Judy.
It's all just blood.
Nobody believes that.
Not even my mother's family.
I'm not one thing or the other.
I am nothing.
I know what that's like.
Yes. Yes, I am.
I am something.
I'm a thief.
I've never stolen anything before
in my life. I swear it.
- The things they called me.
- Fear makes people do stupid things.
It was stupid. And I'm sorry.
I didn't mean you.
I meant your employers.
They were afraid so they fired you.
What am I going to do?
I am trapped.
- You're not trapped.
- I am!
If I leave now, it'll look suspicious,
but if the cops find this--
They're not gonna find it.
Because I'm gonna help you.
So where do we put her?
When did she die?
Doesn't say. Just that she was
tracked by the FBI for robbery.
She checked into the Hyperion in '52
and was never heard from again.
- '52?
- '52.
It'll be okay down here.
For a few days,
until the cops are gone.
Judy, there are no cops.
Well, not yet.
God, I can't go to prison.
I just can't.
The thought of being confined,
trapped. It'd be like death.
No, it'd be something
worse than death.
It'd be like being buried alive.
Go back to your room. Stay there.
There's something in this hotel.
And it makes people crazy.
If somehow the money ended up
on the bank's doorstep...
If they saw that I didn't spend it...
...you think they'd call off that P.I.?
- Maybe I could go free.
- Maybe.
There is such a thing
as forgiveness, right?
I can sense it.
There's a pattern here.
A force lived at the hotel
in the last decades...
...affecting staff and residents.
- I just fear there's no way to--
- A Thesulac.
Paranoia demon.
Whispers to its victims,
feeds on their innate insecurities.
- Angel wants to talk to you.
- Hello?
Thesulac's been here
since the day it was built.
Thought maybe we could track it,
but it's still here.
I want you, Gunn and Cordy
here ASAP. We're gonna raise it.
- Raise it?
- We have to in order to kill it.
You want me to research
the raising ritual?
Already done it.
A zany redhead? Could be a brunette,
for all I can tell.
I'll have to take their word for it.
You Denver?
That's me. What can I do you for?
I need information on demons.
Do you now?
Possessing entities...
...demonic suggestions, exorcisms,
cleansing rituals....
Try this one.
That's right.
Run, coward of the night!
I'm seriously thinking of putting
my bed right in here.
So you can't come in here.
Do you know who I am?
You've got a reputation.
Now I will draw blood...
...if you pull any more crap.
Understand?
I want the books in the back.
- What took you so long?
- He wouldn't fit.
What?
- What'd you do with him?
- He's in there.
I had to make him fit.
- Any chance I'd get in trouble for that?
- Don't be paranoid.
- You had reasons to kill him!
- What?
I didn't know him.
But if he saw you
with one of your trysts...
...he could expose your little
peccadilloes to the press.
You hack! Just because the studio
won't take your calls, comrade!
- Pansy!
- Red!
- There's a murderer here.
- And we're gonna find him.
They know, they'll turn you in,
You'll go to prison,
How long do you think someone
like you will last in prison?
So you were my age
when you were made?
- I don't know. How old are you?
- Just north of 30.
No.
How do I kill Thesulac?
- You don't. You run away.
- There's got to be a way.
Well....
You gotta make it fat, corporeal.
But that only happens after it eats.
Or if you raise it. But that's tricky.
How?
The incantation's in the book,
but you need an Orb.
- I'll sell you one cheap--
- For free.
For free.
Now, you also need sacred herbs...
...divining powder,
and something to hit it with.
- That'll kill it?
- Maybe.
It wouldn't hurt
to have a lightning strike.
Short of that, I'd go with
something big and heavy.
Pack it up.
A vampire helping humans?
- I just don't get it.
- To be honest, I don't either.
Right! You once asked me
where you could get a gun.
- For protection.
- From a salesman about to bust you.
- He shot himself.
- Did he? Were you there?
Consuela found him!
She could have shot him.
Hey!
Name's C. Mulvihill, P.I.
He looks suspicious.
I'm looking for this woman.
Let's do this.
We call thee forth,
Thesulac of the netherworld...
...and command you to join us
on the physical plane.
- The Orb of Ramjarin.
- How about a "please"?
Please. And be careful.
Conjuring orbs are very fragile.
- Angel!
- Don't listen to it. Just ignore it.
- They were like this in the car.
- Oh.
We invoke thee by the power
of all the priests of Ramjarin.
What was once in our thoughts...
...be now in our midst.
Why are you hiding out up here?
- You're hurting me! Stop!
- Then start talking.
- You registered under a fake name.
- We have proof!
What else has the slut lied about?
I'm sorry. It wasn't me!
Sorry for what?
It wasn't me! It wasn't me!
It was him! Look in his room.
He's got blood! He's a monster!
What kind of maniac are you?
Grab him! Get him!
We got you now!
String him up!
Push him! Push him!
Come on, push him out!
Swing, you freak!
Yeah, you had that coming.
Lord, what did we do?
What?
What's wrong?
I don't get it.
Where's everybody going?
It's just a....
I don't know about you...
...but I'm stuffed!
God, I love people.
Don't you?
They feed me the worst.
And I serve it right back.
And the fear and prejudice
turns to certainty and hate...
...and I take another bite
and mmm, mmm, mmm!
What a beautiful, beautiful dance!
You got your feelings hurt,
didn't you?
Stick your neck out...
...and they throw a rope around it.
And you thought you made a friend.
News flash, you had!
That's what made her
the yummiest morsel of all.
You reached her.
Restored her faith in people.
Without you, she would've been
just another appetizer.
But you plumped her up good.
Now she's a meal
that's gonna last me a lifetime!
Hey, you know what?
There's a whole hotel here
full of tortured souls...
...who could really use your help.
What do you say?
Take them all.
- Watch his tentacles.
- Pardon?
Tentacles.
I didn't order takeout...
...but this looks good.
Not as good as the last one...
...but full of tasty paranoia
just the same.
Especially that one.
What did he mean by that?
You've had your last meal.
- You should've gotten out then.
- Gotten out?
Now why would I want to do that...
...when the room service is so good?
Has been for 50 years.
The paranoia here is like fine wine.
It gets better with age.
You're still feeding. Gunn!
Kitchen's closed.
What did it mean,
"especially that one"?
Judy?
I don't hear them anymore.
Are they gone?
Yeah.
- It's you.
- Yeah, Judy...
...it's me.
You look the same.
I'm not.
They killed you...
...because of me. I killed you.
No.
He kept them from the door.
He told me I'd be safe.
Am I safe?
You're safe.
- Can I go out now?
- Yeah. You can go out.
Let me help you.
I just....
I need to take a little rest first.
Just a little rest.
Easy.
I'm so sorry I killed you.
Can you forgive me?
Of course.
I'm just going to rest.
Just for a minute.
And then I'm going to go out.
I've been called many things before.
But paranoid has never
been one of them.
Unless people have said
it behind my back.
- You all right, man?
- Yeah.
We finished?
I think so.
Good. I will be glad
to see the last of this place.
It scares me.
No lie. And it stinks.
You notice that?
70 years of violence
and mayhem? Bad vibes.
- We're moving in.
- What's not to love?
Angel?
Surely you realize...
...that this place has housed
not only a demonic presence...
...but the worst faces of humanity.
This is a house of evil.
Not anymore.
Angel, you don't find me
especially paranoid, do you?
- Not especially.
- Oh, thank God.
I was worried.