Previously on Angel:
- I'm Lilah Morgan.
- Wolfram & Hart.
I'm an associate here.
We're all pleased you're here, Darla.
- I can't believe you're here.
- Let Darla take care of you.
All you have to do is let me.
Exciting, isn't it?
Darla.
I didn't see you.
Going through their things.
The hidden pieces of themselves...
...locked up, giving you
a thrill of control.
I keep up with his latest project.
He's probably in my office right now.
That's just how it works at our firm.
All you busy little worker bees,
plotting your little schemes.
Calynthia powder?
That's how you keep Angel sleeping
when he's with you?
There's nothing so lovely as dreams.
Everything's in them.
Everything hidden.
Open those chambers,
you'll truly understand someone...
...and control them.
And what's hidden
in Angel's secret chambers?
Horrors.
- That's typical of your type.
- At least I'm not a sheep.
- I'm not a sheep!
- You've never had a single opinion...
- ...You didn't read.
- At least I read.
Don't even try it.
I was top 10 percent of my class.
What class? "Advanced Bosoms"?
Hey! What the hell's going on here?
We were discussing whether or not
we should pay Gunn.
- No, you weren't.
- Our discussions last three minutes.
- Then it's strictly name-calling.
- Ebenezer doesn't want to share.
I merely said Gunn
might be insulted by the offer.
- He's a proud sort of fellow.
- He's been helping. He should be paid.
- I'll think about it.
- No think. Pay.
How about we pretend
that you work for me?
- You're so unpleasant when--
- Let's pretend that you don't.
You can't fire me. I'm Vision Girl.
Okay, I'll think about asking him.
Maybe on a case-by-case.
- My hero.
- I was gonna suggest that.
Mm-hm.
- Is there coffee?
- In the morning. It's 10:00 at night.
I was disoriented.
I've been sleeping weird.
Weird how?
I don't know.
It's been like this for a bit.
You sleep more, you're less rested.
Are you dreaming?
Boys, I think we have a customer.
Okay, a girl. She's in an alley.
Hollywood and Wilcox.
- Oh, she's so scared.
- Go.
God, he's gonna be too late.
Why are you making us run around?
Hey, I get it first.
Think I want your seconds? You pig.
The guy's a pig.
- So what do we got here?
- You're not--
Get behind the tape. You wanna gawk,
go watch a high-speed chase on Fox.
- Keep the tourists away.
- But--
I'm out of Vice three weeks,
I come back to all this amateur crap.
Pretend you're not a Cub Scout
and tell me about this.
Well, detective, we had
to scrape him off the wall.
Guys got pinned by a two-ton dumpster.
- It fell on them?
- No, they were pinned to the wall.
Looks like somebody
shoved it from the side.
Have to be pretty strong.
You're telling me.
Splashed them all the way up here.
That's not their blood.
Excuse me?
You seen a girl tonight?
Maybe a little scared and beat up?
Nobody but our Mr. Bills.
You know, "Oh, no, Mr. Bill!"
Right.
So, what do we got here?
Hey.
What do you want?
- You're bleeding.
- Stay away from me.
- I just wanna ask you a few questions.
- You don't understand.
I'm really upset right now,
and I think it's best if you just--
- You were in that alley, weren't you?
- No! I mean....
What alley?
- I'm going.
- Hold on a second.
Oh, God! I told you.
I tried to tell you.
Please wait.
What are you?
I've come to help you.
My name is Angel.
I stabbed an angel.
Now I'll never get into heaven.
I'm not an angel. It's just a name.
But how did you--?
Well, I'm different
from most people, like you are.
Those men in the alley,
they tried to hurt you, didn't they?
- But you stopped them.
- I didn't mean to. They followed me.
- It wasn't--
- It's okay.
- Yeah, it's just great.
- You're not from L.A., are you?
You got family in town?
Me neither.
Town kind of attracts loners,
don't you think?
You can't make me go
anywhere with you.
I think that message got through.
I would never try.
Wait.
Take this.
If you need anything,
a place to stay....
- I'm staying with a friend.
- Someone to talk to.
Think about it.
I won't hurt you...
...and you can't hurt me.
You may need that.
Okay, maybe she can hurt me a little.
- Bethany.
- Hi. Sorry I'm late.
I was starting to get worried.
So how was the club? You have any fun?
- It was okay.
- Any cute boys?
Sorry I didn't go. Work got insane.
Our new clients are monsters.
- Here, let me.
- Oh, I like folding.
It's like a Zen exercise.
It levels me out.
You've gotta let me help.
I've gotta at least--
It's enough, you letting me stay.
Didn't we vow you'd stop that?
Didn't we make a blood oath?
I love having you here.
You know, when you came
and spoke at our school, I was so:
"There was someone who got out,
made it by themselves."
- I'm saying it wrong. I--
- No, you're not.
I couldn't believe
you even talked to me.
See, you have no idea.
You're special, Bethany.
In the non-retarded sense of the word.
You think I tour high schools
saying "look me up" to everyone I meet?
You have a power about you.
Other people will start to know that.
- I guess I'm getting kind of sleepy.
- I bet you are.
I'm still kind of wired.
I might stare at the TV for a while.
Good night, Lilah.
Sweet dreams.
I can't get this bandage to....
Stop moving.
- I'm not.
- Then stop breathing.
I don't breathe.
Then stop flexing your manly
boob muscles, or whatever.
- That's an ugly wound.
- Doesn't feel pretty.
We should approach her with caution.
I guess you already figured that out.
She's very powerful.
We must find out all we can.
- Like oh, say, her name?
- I was impaled at the time.
Of course. Perfectly understandable.
You know how hard it is to think
straight with a rebar in your torso?
Actually, I do.
Benefits of a Sunnydale education.
- No address or anything?
- She's staying with a friend.
Where do we keep the list
of "people with friends"?
She's not local. Traces of an accent.
Northeast. Maybe Ohio.
Everything about her says
she's on the run.
- Look into northeastern runaways.
- Crossed with supernatural events.
The way she is, she's not low-profile.
Angel, you sure this isn't
a demon of some kind?
- She's just a girl.
- One that could kill you by blinking.
She needs help.
She's out of control.
She's just lost.
What do we know about telekinesis?
Ah, yes. The power of
moving things with one's mind.
That's pretty much it.
The power of moving....
I'm better with demons, really.
Time to broaden your horizons.
You call, I come.
Loaded for bear, ready for battle....
- Any other "B" thing.
- What's that?
Isn't this the thing?
My camp kids put it together.
- I wanted to use it tonight.
- Men are all alike.
- Fair one, you still saving my life?
- Every minute.
- How's it going?
- You're alive, right?
What kind of scaly pus-monster
will I slay this time?
We need you to do legwork.
Legwork? That means
I can't use my cool new ax.
I'm trying to find a girl.
She smashed two rapists
with a dumpster.
- She must be hefty.
- We think she's psychic.
- Telekinesis: the power of moving--
- I have heard the word.
What should I do?
- Find out about the guys who got--
- Smooshed?
--near your neighborhood.
You think you can find them?
Sure. But if I return on
the end of a spatula...
...I'm expecting some
serious workman's comp.
See? Workman's comp.
He wants to get paid.
Cordelia--
The poor man can't even
afford a real ax!
Okay, okay.
Look, I'll bring it up.
I'm going to bed.
It's been a long day.
You've been up for three hours.
Cordelia....
Find the girl.
Shh, Rabbit.
Let's go downstairs. Just you and me.
Don't make a fuss, Rabbit.
- Bethany....
- I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
Don't. Don't go!
Remember, don't you?
In front of the fire...
...with the gypsy girl,
all bound and gagged.
We took her right there.
We sucked her blood till she was dry.
Well?
Top of the middle of the day
to you too.
No leads worth mentioning.
Of course, we lost time
during my hour of sleep.
Good thing I left clothes here,
or you'd smell me even now.
Gunn check in?
How about you? How's it coming?
Most of my reading suggests that
telekinesis is a psychic phenomenon...
...that occurs during
extreme emotional distress.
That tracks. We gotta find her.
Well, I think I may have a lead.
How are you?
Bethany. Bethany Chaulk.
You said I couldn't hurt you.
- That if I needed anything....
- You're safe here.
We're all safe people.
This is Wesley and Cordelia.
So it's a family business, huh?
Friends. Come on in.
Sorry.
I'm just so tired.
- Would you like some tea?
- Yeah, please.
You shouldn't worry. Angel does
this kind of thing all the time.
Makes tea?
Helps people. You know,
he helps people with problems.
- So what's wrong with you?
- Where to begin?
Well, our little girl gave you
one heck of a shiner, didn't she?
Was the L.A. scenario too much?
I assure you, I have
the utmost confidence that--
Don't "utmost confidence" me.
Some might say you've lost
control of this girl.
If so, what happens when you
pull the trigger?
She has the profile. But an assassin's
no good if it can't be controlled.
But do you know what I say?
Nonsense.
I say Lilah Morgan found this girl...
...Lilah Morgan recruited
this girl for a reason...
...and Lilah Morgan's gonna
bring this girl...
...into the welcoming arms
of Wolfram & Hart.
I will find her.
Hello.
Bethany.
No, I am so glad you called.
I was worried.
No, I'm fine.
Where are you?
They're Cordy's. I feel kind of funny.
You look nice.
You get ahold of your friend?
Is she okay?
She says she's fine. Worried about me.
How do you explain...?
She'd just think I'm crazy.
- Are you?
- What?
Well, if you are, you know, crazy...
...I just think things will go
smoother if I know up front.
I probably am.
I don't wanna....
I don't wanna talk about me
and share, or whatever.
We can talk about stuff, but....
I don't know.
You're the expert, right?
I wouldn't say that.
I just have experience in dealing...
...with the kind of power
that needs control.
I don't want to control it.
I want it gone.
- What is she doing?
- They're talking, yes?
There's something. She's got a vibe.
I'm getting a vibe. She's vibe-y.
I didn't notice a vibe.
All evidence to the contrary,
you're not a woman.
Women and sex. It's not like you guys.
We see more levels.
Are you even listening?
It's like there's a flash.
Like something pops in my brain.
And then...
...it's like there's an undertow,
like there's no gravity.
My body's being pulled
in different directions...
...but inside, you know?
Does it hurt?
Yes. No. Just for a second,
then I'm back.
You only feel it
when you make things move?
I don't make them move. When I come to,
things aren't where I left them.
- You've never done it on purpose?
- Of course not.
You never thought, "That remote's far.
I'd have to get up--"
It's not a parlor trick!
It's-- It's a disease.
We don't know what it is yet.
I just want to know about you.
Don't ask stupid questions.
"When were you potty-trained?
Name all your pets.
Do you like hide-and-seek?"
- They weren't on my list.
- You know nothing! I shouldn't be here.
I agree. She doesn't want our help.
Let's not waste our time with her.
- Wesley--
- There are people who need us...
...with graver issues
than impulse control.
- That's enough.
- Send her to her friend's.
Toss the furniture. Maybe we
should send you to your father.
- You sure nothing's broken?
- I'm sure.
Nothing at all? Say, your brain?
What happened to
"approach with caution" ?
If she'd gotten her defenses up--
She wouldn't be crying,
and you and Angel wouldn't be hurt.
What did you say?
- I mentioned her father.
- Well, who's her father?
The trauma that can
produce psychic power...
...usually involves abuse
of some kind, early on.
You'd mentioned a sexual vibe.
She made that crack
about "family business."
Statistically speaking,
the father was the best guess.
There's not enough yuck in the world.
- How is she?
- Settling. You, go.
You can't fire him! I'll quit too!
Unless you're firm.
I'm not firing anyone.
My presence won't help her
trust issues. I'll be at my flat.
Call me if....
It helps that we know.
I hope so.
- Stay at your place, in case she--
- Be careful.
I doubt she'll go off again.
There you are.
I came up here.
I feel safe up here.
You did pick the one room
that may collapse to feel safe in.
I'm really embarrassed.
And that just makes me....
Horrible things have happened,
been done to me.
Guys have died...
...and I'm freaking
because I'm so embarrassed.
People are pathetic.
I don't know.
I like them.
The time I've lived, I've seen
some horrors, scary behavior...
...and a couple of fashion trends
I constantly pray to forget.
But I see people try.
- I've seen them try to be better.
- You sound like an old guy.
Oh, you know, I'm very well-preserved.
I'd like that.
To see people the way you do.
- Darla?
- It's just me.
What's up?
What's--? Is there trouble?
I just didn't want to sleep.
I heard a voice in here
and thought maybe you were awake.
I was having a nightmare.
It looked like a pretty happy dream.
Or maybe the covers were just rumpled.
I figured I'd come in.
It's nicer than my room.
Is there something
you wanted to talk about?
No.
I figured we'd have fun.
You can do stuff to me
and, you know...
- ...we'll have some fun.
- That's not gonna happen.
Like I'm some frightened little mouse?
I've done stuff.
I can make you happy.
You wouldn't like me when I'm happy.
- Come on.
- It won't mean anything.
- I said stop it.
- Get off me!
You wanna make love,
but not be touched?
"Make love"?
Are you from the 18th century?
- I was just.... I just wanted--
- What did you want?
- Are you shocked I'm a great big slut?
- You'll find I'm not easily shocked.
Everyone thinks I'm so fragile
and innocent. Men love it.
- Do you?
- Do I love it?
Who cares?
I'm like the chambermaid.
I just leave.
When a guy's on me, I....
I made up the room, I showed him in...
...and I leave till he's gone.
Come back and clean up the mess.
And the men?
You think they'd notice
or care I'm not there?
Would you?
- Everyone's not as bad as you think.
- Oh, right. You love the people.
You love them so much you've got
100 rooms to be alone in.
I'm thinking maybe you're not
exactly qualified to help me.
Maybe I'm the only one who is.
- Try to get some sleep.
- Who's Darla?
Good night, Bethany.
He's not sleeping,
- It puts a cramp in Lindsey's project.
- Yes, but--
Lindsey understands the big picture.
All his efforts
go towards that picture.
Your girl is messing up his efforts.
- I understand, sir.
- I know you do.
Get her out. Not just for the sake
of the big picture.
For yours.
I feel funny. Sweaty funny, I think.
Just try. You can always stop.
- What if it blows up?
- I'll buy Cordelia a new one.
Okay. Just drop it on the floor.
See?
You can control it.
Nice look.
Gunn wants you to meet him here.
- Brentwood?
- I'll watch Bethany. We can shop.
Sure. Sounds like fun.
I'll be back soon.
You're not gonna wear this?
Knock, knock! This works great.
You break, I enter.
- If he's still alive, I can't enter.
- Guy's on the critical list.
You see what I'm seeing?
- Doesn't fit the thug profile.
- No. I hear he was muscle for hire.
- So he was sent.
- Somebody wanted her hurt.
Or wanted to see what would happen.
Look for an address book.
Checks, statements.
I'm still dealing with this
ugly living room.
- Some people shouldn't have money.
- About money...
...how would you feel maybe...
...on a case-by-case basis...?
- Are you offering to pay me?
- Yeah.
Cool.
- You're a very graceful man.
- Someone's off the critical list.
Rapist for hire. You see me crying?
Wolfram & Hart,
How may I direct your call?
- You were right, this is great.
- The vanilla makes it less latte-y.
Yeah.
Where I'm from, they just have coffee.
Everything else is "L.A. stuff."
- Don't bone my boss.
- What?
Angel's strictly a no-bone.
I wasn't-- Cordelia, I don't
wanna sleep with Angel.
The thing about Angel,
he's old-fashioned. Old-fashioned.
Like, the age of chivalry.
He sees you as...
...the damsel in distress.
I think it's more
complicated than that.
- Why are you--?
- I think you're kind of dangerous.
I'm not being mean. I like you.
But you come on all helpless...
...and people who have thought
you were helpless have died.
Those men in the alley....
That was the only....
They were gonna hurt me.
You could have floated them away...
...or spun them until they puked.
You squashed them.
You don't know how scary it was.
Yes, I do.
I had a vision of you.
That's how Angel found you.
I felt everything.
And those guys are better off
squashed, I truly think.
But in that moment,
a decision got made.
I don't want that
to happen to my friends.
Or, and I can't
stress this enough, me.
No matter what,
sex complicates the equation...
...even more than you think.
I get it.
- You don't have to worry.
- Good.
- So are you and Angel--?
- Oh, no.
I like my men less broody
and more spendy.
He is kind of earnest.
He always seems--
What a jerk.
You're about to drop your--
Stop! Police!
Stay with me, stay with me.
Come on! No, Bethany, come on!
Come on! Come on, Bethany!
Bethany! You can squash those guys!
Cordelia!
Tan van! Fetch!
Take the wheel.
Closer!
Shut up! Just shut up!
One more excuse,
and I'll bury you alive...
...next to my house,
so I can hear you screaming.
He took her to the hotel? Great.
He wants to play with
little Miss Time Bomb, let him.
Pull the trigger.
- Bethany.
- No, it's someone else!
I know Lilah.
She's not what you think.
- She's my friend!
- Angel.
It's not her! You're making it up!
You're playing with me!
- I don't want to play!
- Control yourself.
Don't touch me!
Maybe she just needs a time-out.
- Bethany, stop.
- I won't listen.
- You can control this. Listen!
- No!
You have the power here.
You gonna kill us? You gonna die?
Then they win. Don't let them.
Don't let them touch you.
Hello, Rabbit.
- Daddy.
- God, Bethany, I've been so worried.
I couldn't have found you, except....
Your friend Lilah and I
only want to help you.
I know what you can do, Bethany.
I know you don't mean to hurt anyone.
You're a good girl. I know that.
No more worries, all right?
You're coming with me.
We'll be a family again.
Wouldn't you like to stop running?
To come back where
people know you, love you?
It'll be just like it was before.
I've missed you so much.
Shh, Rabbit.
Bethany--
There you go.
Why don't we go downstairs,
just you and me?
What are you doing?
Stop it! Put me down!
I can't breathe.
Help me, please! Stop her!
Bethany, you've got the power.
Use it.
- Finish it.
- It hurts.
Make it stop.
Goodbye.
You think that's it? Poof, you're
cured, the nightmares are gone?
- I'm not an idiot or a child.
- Yes, you are, and you need us.
Your powers will get out of control,
and you'll need a friend.
Friends don't hire men
to rape and kidnap me.
At least not my close ones.
I was trying to make you stronger.
Good job.
Bethany. Bethany, wait.
- You could've been important.
- You gotta learn to lose.
You're not invited in.
Don't try to find me. I mean it.
But our firm doesn't want
to lose-- You're not....
He is a vampire, you know.
Weird.
You'll have to find
someone else's brain to play with.
Yeah, we have someone in mind.
Good night, Lilah.
Sweet dreams.
Thank you, thank you very much,