[ Disco, Woman Vocalizing ]
[ Lorne ] Uh-huh.
Oh, I promise you. It'll be fabulous.
Believe me,Jerry. Yes.
It's Grapes of Wrath
in outer space. Uh-huh.
Oh, it's got heart.
Yes, it's got laser battles.
It's got a timely message
of interstellar poverty.
Uh-huh. Listen, have your assistant
call my assistant.
We'll set somethin' up.
Good enough.
J.C., listen,
just got off the Nextel with Big B.
Yeah, intrigued, but wants to know
who's playing Tom Joad. Uh-huh.
Well, I'm pretty sure that
Henry Fonda's dead, sweetie.
Yeah. ''Bring him back to life''?
Let me talk to my science people.
Okay, no promises.
- Directors. Harmonica!
- Lorney Tunes!
Oh, the eyes, the hair, the dress.
It's no wonder the fourth floor
has a crush on you.
Hey, tell me, priceless.
Where do I find Angel?
Just called. He's on his way back in
from a field mission.
Though I wouldn't, if I were you.
It sounds like he's in a mood.
Oh, don't worry, darlin'. I've pulled
the big boy out of many a broodfest.
- It shouldn't be that--
- [ Squishy Footsteps ]
Ew.
Angel, how did the new
neural-intercept grenade work?
It didn't.
Right. I'll take it down to Fred,
have her look at it.
Hey, Angelheart.
Wes, if you see Fred...
can you have her
pencil me in for later?
I've gotta talk to her about
Henry Fonda's big comeback.
- [ Wesley ] All right.
- Angel, we gotta have a confab.
- Es muy importante.
- Lorne--
It's about the party. I've done
all I can do for the big to-do...
but we've still got a few bugs
to comb out of the cootie garage.
A bridge too far?
Let me try it again.
Lorne, I've been out all night.
I'm beat up. I'm exhausted.
I'm covered head to toe in Thraxis blood,
which actually kind of burns...
so this is all gonna have to wait
until I take a shower.
- You killed a Thraxis? But--
- Shower.
Van, why don't we scratch the Thraxis
off of the invite list?
And you got a copy of that print ad
we're gonna run this week?
- Yeah. Right.
- What is this?
''Wolfram and Hart
wants to be up your alley''?
That's like a bus station
pickup line. Change it.
On second thought, burn it.
Grab yourself a bagel or somethin' too.
You look a little waxy.
[ Sighs ]
Ooh, ouch.
That's an adult-size bangaroo. Hello!
- [ Groaning ]
- Oh, Mr. Smiles?
Oh, come on.
You can't ignore me forever.
- [ Sighs ]
- Well, fine.
Looks like you're gonna have to
slap a Band Aid on that melon...
and draw a grin on that bewitching
green mug and go right back out there.
On the count of nine, sunshine.
One, two, three--
The show stops for no demon, Lorne.
Four, five--
They're all waiting for you.
Six, seven--
They're counting on you.
Eight-- Comin' up on nine.
They're gonna eat you up
with a spoon because you're so...
- scrumptious.!
- Shut up!
[ Sighs ]
[ Shower Running ]
[ Shower Stops ]
[ Eve ]
Hi.
The door was open.
Well, unlocked.
Well, I had a key.
- [ Key Clatters ]
- So, uh, wow.
You take a long shower for a guy.
Were we having some
gentleman's time?
- ''Gentleman's''?
- I mean, I understand.
You're running the whole circus now,
a lot of pressure.
Especially with your hands-on policy.
No pun intended.
I'm sure you could use a release.
No releasing,just bathing.
That's what one does...
after bashing open a demonic pinata
full of rancid Tabasco.
- What do you want, Eve?
- You stood me up.
We had a 7:30, Angel.
A meeting.
- Oh, right. Uh, I'll get my pants.
- [ Elevator Bell Dings ]
- So how's it going, Angel?
- [ Sighs ]
I don't know how
to answer that question.
I don't know. Good. Bad.
I spent years doing everything
I could to bring this company down.
Now I'm the C.E.O., and I have to
question every move I make...
because any one of them could be
exactly what the senior partners want.
So, no, I have no idea how it's goin'.
Hey, at least you can still get
your nocturnal jollies...
saving the downtrodden
from things that go bump in the night.
You said it yourself--
''Everyone needs a release.''
No, I said you need a release.
Not everyone bottles
all this stuff up like you.
- I don't bottle.
- You bottle.
- [ Bell Dings ]
[ Groaning ]
Why does it look like
we're havin' a party in here?
Maybe 'cause we're
havin' a party in here.
The Wolfram and Hart Halloween bash?
Ring a bell? Biggest event
on the company calendar?
I sent you a small
forest's worth of memos on it.
- We're havin' it here?
- You see what I'm up against?
That's what our 7:30 was about, Angel--
your party.
- My party?
- Yeah, listen, here's the snafu in a nutshell, top cat.
Uh, nobody's comin'.
Well, some people are comin',
but the right people--
the A-list people--
they seem to be giving it a miss.
- And if they don't show up,
this shindig is gonna be a bust.
- Good.
- Good?
- Yeah, I wasn't too crazy
about this thing to begin with.
I mean, we are talking about
our clients, right?
Our evil clients. Not the sort of folks
I'd really like to show a good time.
I'd be a lot happier if the whole thing
just kind of fell through.
- Then we can get back to--
- [ Laughs ] Okay! Okay, you're killin' me!
Can't you just feel up
the big picture, Mr. Magoo?
It's not about good and evil.
It's about party.
Party! Capital P,
rhymes with me.
I'm about to have a stroke here,
'cause you're killin' me!
Listen, I can see that
you're in a state...
a mood, a snit, even.
So what say we talk about this once
you've calmed down a bit?
Yeah, sure. That's fine with--
Great. Your office, 25 minutes.
- Was Angel mad?
- Shouldn't he be?
We sent him out there with
a defective piece of weaponry.
Which ''we'' are we talking about?
Fred, these techno-mystical hybrids
are a complicated affair.
I don't know.
They seem kind of simple to me.
It's just a little handheld,
spell-casting robot, right?
So it's either the robot or the spell
that we have a problem with.
Well, the grenade's core
enchantment looks operational...
so I think we're talking about
a faulty trigger mechanism.
No. Wait a minute.
I designed that mechanism myself.
Yeah, that's right, and I machined it.
It was beautiful work
on both counts, if I may say.
- You may.
- [ Chuckles ]
I agree, as a sculptural piece.
But the device's trigger
may not have been refined enough...
to actually trigger the effect.
Happy Halloween, kids.
How do you know your spell-casters
didn't screw up the payload?
Because I went over the work,
and I got that knowing feeling
you get when you know something.
- Trick or treat?
- Hi, Lorne.
- Hi.
What do you say we put away your
little sci-fi toys for a little bit, huh?
Maybe we could talk about
something a little more important...
like my monster mash.
Oh, yeah, your party.
Our party, Tweety Bird, which,
by the way, is dying on the vine.
I could really, really, really use
some help from you guys. Some backup.
I wasn't really planning on going.
Wes, do you hear this crazy talk?
Uh, well, I really hadn't given
much thought to going myself.
Et tu, Brutuses?
Why is it so hard to get anyone
to have any fun around here?
[ Knox ]
You should go.
It's the Halloween blowout
to end all blowouts.
Last year, uh,
[ Chuckling ]
they took a bunch of cows...
and put them in this
giant wicker effigy of Krishna...
doused it with Sambuca and--
Uh, well, anyway,
it's a hell of a good time.
I really wanna get this operational
before Angel goes out again.
- Yes, I'll stay too.
- Wha--
- I'm sure we can work it out together.
- No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no! Wes, Fred,
you're coming. Look at yourselves.
You're wound tighter
than Martha Stewart's watch.
Isn't there anyone else who could fix
the little boo-boos on this thing?
[ Knox ]
I can do that.
It's probably the trigger
mechanism anyway.
Great. Problem solved.
I'll see you two in Angel's office,
1 5 minutes.
[ Knocking On Door ]
- Hey, Lorne.
- Hey, hey.
Uh, sorry to interrupt.
Not to be a pest...
but I just wanted to go over
a little stratego, amigo.
- Sorry?
- Um, you're my big gun, Gunn.
Ace in hole.
Ball in pocket.
You're the key on my kite string.
Okay.
We gotta turn Angel around
on this whole party idea.
- We do?
- I know he's the boss and everything...
but you're up and coming here, and it's time
for you to spread your wings, legal eagle.
From now on, I want you
to stake out your territory...
and I want you to keep it staked.
Stake. Territory. Sure.
Lorne, I'm a little busy right now.
I have a deposition to get ready for.
- But I will definitely get to that.
- Great.
Just what I wanted to hear.
Angel's office, 1 0 minutes.
[ Door Closes ]
In my day, no self-respecting
creature of the night...
went out on All Hallow's Eve.
We left that to the poseurs-- the blighters
who had to dress up and try to be scary.
Magic windows.
Will the perks never end?
[ Italian ]
Ciao.
- What'd I miss?
- Us waiting.
Oh, right. Sorry.
So, uh, Angel, we just wanted
to take a moment...
and emphasize how important
this party really is to us.
I gotta say Lorne is right.
We gotta show all the big-bads
that the new regime is here to stay...
which, for the most part,
boils down to image.
And image-wise, if this party
doesn't kick ass, we lose face.
And believe me, Milk Dud,
speaking as the head...
of your P.R. department,
we need all the face we can get.
- ''Milk Dud''?
- Said with affection.
Okay, listen, I understand the whole
keeping-up-appearances concept...
but everyone comin' to this thing
is unrepentant, dyed-in-the-wool evil.
Angel, a good host just doesn't
make these sort of judgments.
We don't know how many of them are holdin'
grudges against us or against each other.
It's a perfect recipe for
an out-of-control bloodbath.
That's describing every good party
I've ever been to. [ Laughs ]
Listen, Angel, don't worry about a thing.
This is my forte.
I ran Caritas for years--
a nightclub with an open-door policy.
The good, the bad,
the hideously ugly--
They all bellied up to my demon bar...
but they all played nicely
together while they were there.
This is exactly the kind of ethical
tightrope you've got to walk now.
Which brings up another point--
your employees.
- Also evil.
- Here's your blood, bossy.
[ Clears Throat ]
Boss.
Some of them,yes. But all of them
work hard for this firm.
And Halloween--
Well, around here it's like Christmas.
Simply put, this is a morale thing.
[ Scoffs ] Good luck.
Morale around here stinks.
- What?
- Uh-huh. Everybody thinks you suck.
Well, come on, boss. They're all out there
sweating through their Matsudas...
worried if you're gonna ax them or,
you know, ax them.
Okay, look.
Hey, I haven't--
Okay, look, I may have killed
a couple of them--
And several clients.
And maybe some potential clients.
Why do you think my R.S.V.P. list is only
a fifth of the size of last year's?
- It's you, babe.
- What do they think--
I'm throwin' this thing
so I can slaughter them?
Fine. I surrender.
Go ahead, Lorne.
Put on your best dog and pony.
I won't get in the way.
I don't want you to sit back
and just let it happen, Angel.
- I need you to get out there and make it happen.
- What does that mean?
[ Lorne ]
Archduke Sebassis...
bona fide nobility
for the fiery down under...
commands over 40 legions.
He's the living end of a pure bloodline
of demonic royalty.
- Great.Just great.
- Yeah, well, also the very peak...
of the A-list mountain.
He's the crown jewel
of the underworld jet set.
If we convince him to come,
[ Chuckles ]
all the other glitterati
will just domino in right behind him...
and then--
then we'll be in business.
This really matters to you,
doesn't it?
Of course. The new Wolfram and Hart.
I mean, we have to--
No. I mean, this really matters
to you... personally.
Yeah. You know, Angel, I--
I don't have superhuman strength...
and I'm not a fighter...
and quantum physics
makes me nauseous.
I barely made a passing grade
in mystical studies.
But I'm on your team.
This is something I can do.
I believe it has a purpose that can
help you, even if you don't.
I'm here, aren't I?
I agreed to this.
No, you did. You did.
And I promise you won't regret it.
But, hey, let's say that you let me
do most of the talking, huh?
You just kind of smile and try not
to rip anybody apart, okay?
So, this is the mighty Angel.
I've been told
many things about you.
A bit of a restless frog, hmm?
Making lots of waves
in your little swamp.
Yeah. Well, I'm just trying
to keep the fly population down.
- [ Laughing ]
- Yes.
Though I do prefer the tales
of your counterpart, Angelus.
Ah,you had flair back then, child.
Well, I guess we all mellow
in our old age.
[ Chuckles ]
Your contempt is fragrant.
Uh, so, Your Lordship...
we were deeply grieved when
you declined our invitation.
I mean, we'd love
for you to reconsider.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I mean...
a party just isn't a party
without the archduke.
- You're sure you wouldn't like some?
- I'm fine.
- But thanks.
- Oh, come, come.
We're all blood drinkers here.
Ah, but that's right.
You choose to drink
the blood of swine.
- Filthy beasts.
- Actually, that's a misconception.
Filthy! Yes. Honestly,
I don't know how he does it.
[ Chuckles ]
Mmm.
Wow, this is--
You, uh-- You really-- You taste great.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, in light of
this amusing chat...
and of my long-standing
acquaintance with you, Lorne...
I will come to the gala.
[ Lorne ]
That's wonderful news, Your Lordship.
Well, we don't wanna waste
any more of your valuable time.
We'll-- We'll show ourselves out.
I still think it's a trap,
My Lordship.
Maybe, Artode.
But I am in the mood for intrigue.
So we'll go to their celebration.
We'll just make sure
we're properly dressed.
[ Woman Singing Disco ]
Man, this is lame.
I mean, where's the ritual sacrifiiice?
How do you get the ball rolling
without a ritual sacrifice?
Hey, guys, come on. You're representing
our glorious firm here.
Dude, it's our night off.
Dude, this is your night on!
Now, mingle. Mingle, mingle,
mingle, mingle, mingle!
- All right.
- Lorne.!
[ Laughing ]
Hey there, Devlin.
So, what are you supposed to be?
You no get? A human being.
[ Laughs ]
Look, I do human being.
[ Clears Throat ]
I proud my honor roll student.
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughing Continues ]
Look at Lorne. I mean, God,
he's just so good at this.
- He fits in with everybody.
- Right. That's, uh--
So tell me. That mask, uh,
it is rubber, right?
My other car a Lamborghini.
[ Both Laughing ]
Okay. So, uh, then, uh-- uh--
- You be good and everything. [ Chuckles ]
- [ Laughing ]
[ Fred ]
I guess I've always hated parties.
I never know
what to do with myself.
I just end up at the hors d'oeuvres table
trying to look occupied.
- Hey there, wallflowers.
- Wallflowers?
I need you to give me a hand and help
light the fuse on this powder keg.
Look at the dance floor.
The only thing on it is Harmony.
Hey, you keep pushin'
that envelope, baby!
I'm afraid this really
isn't our element, Lorne.
- Yeah. We're wallflowers.
- No, no, no, no, no, sweetie.
You're the young,
the beautiful, the ready to--
Well, here's one problem.
You're totally sober!
It's Halloween. You should be
three sheets to the wind already.
Try and get into
the spirit of things, okay?
[ Disco Continues ]
Angel, it is a graveyard out there.
And all the guests want to meet
the new guy in charge.
Look, Lorne, I-- I-- I have things.
I'm busy. I'm brooding.
- Oh,you're watching hockey.!
- Yeah, but my team is losing.
Get up off your keister
and get out there!
I can't steer this ship of fools
by my lonesome. I just can't do it!
[ Groaning ]
Lorne?
Let's boogie, Sweet Tart.
[ Claps ]
Well, so, uh, over there,
we have the Britzai representatives.
We can get to them later.
Oh, and there's the elder
of the Fell Brotherhood.
Come on. Let's go say hi.
- [ Dance ]
- [ Laughing ]
Yeah.!
[ Gasps ]
- Come on, Spikey. Come dance with me.
- You have got to be kidding.
Oh, come on.
Listen, chippie,
you can gyrate all you like.
I'll go to hell before these ghost shoes
touch that dance floor.
Oh, Blondie Bear,
where is your Halloween spirit?
Dearly departed.
All this claptrap over a bit
of dusty old Druid nonsense.
The whole silly lot of you
can get hung, if you ask me.
What are you even doing here then?
What am I doing here?
Yeah, Spike. I thought you hated
these kind of things.
- I would've thought the same of you.
- Oh, no, he's doin' great.
He's already not killed,
like, 1 00 guests.
He doesn't have to.
- The party's already dead.
- Oh, really, Spike.
Would it kill you to be
a little more positive, hmm?
The Archduke Sebassis.!
- Oh, great honor, Your Lordship!
- Okay, sport, you're on.
And please, for me,
can you try to be nice to him--
just this one time, huh?
Yes. Fine.
Sycophants, worms.
Don't writhe all at once.
It's sickening.
Archduke Sebassis.
- Thanks so much for coming.
- Yes, well--
Really, really thrilled
that you're here.
Artode, welcome, welcome.
Love thejacket, by the way.
- It's Pylean.
- Oh, made in Pylea, my home dimension.
Not made in, made from.
I skinned it myself.
Anybody you know?
[ Chuckles ]
Well, great. Thanks for dropping by.
[ Chuckling ]
And you look-- I don't have to tell you
how awesome you look.
You know how awesome you look.
He knows how awesome he looks, right?
Angel, we don't want to
be greedy with His Eminence.
Thank you, Your Lordship.
Thank you.
Absolutely really thrilled
to have you here.
Okeydokey. Okay, that'll do it.
Thank you. Come on.
[ Whispering, Indistinct ]
[ Slurring ] Yeah, for eight years straight,
I went out dressed as Raggedy Ann.
[ Laughs ]
[ Slurring ] Sorry.
Sounds like fun, I suppose.
We never really celebrated
Halloween in England.
Oh, that's so sad.
Look, pot stickers!
Watch your step, guys.
Somebody peed all over there.
Well, that's just--just wrong.
- Revolting.
- Castiglio! Hey, how's the family?
There you are, Umbrigon. How are you?
Nice to see you. Nice to see you.
- Shouldn't be a problem at all.
- Sea Breeze, Tony.
So, come in next week, 'cause I'm sure
we can untangle that for you.
- All right. Thanks.
- Lorne!
- Looks like this thing's gonna work out.
- Yeah. Fingers crossed.
Man, I wish I had a tenth of your energy.
How do you do it?
I'll let you in on a little secret.
I had my sleep removed.
A little procedure
they have here at the company.
Yeah, you know, I haven't
slept a wink in about a month.
You had Wolfram and Hart
remove your sleep?
Lorne, that's great!
In and out, 20 minutes, no scarring.
I'll tell you.
You oughta think about it.
It would go nicely with
that legal upgrade of yours.
- Yeah, I'll definitely look into that.
- All right. See you later.
The vampire is setting his trap.
Our antidetection spells
worked nicely, Artode.
They won't expect us to be armed.
And if he tries something?
Kill them all.
Will you excuse me, Lordship?
[ Sniffs ]
Pee-pee.
I have to say I'm impressed.
I saw you with Sebassis.
I honestly didn't know
you had it in you.
Yeah, well, it was an act.
I think.
I picked up on that
from 1 00 yards away.
Yep,you were bangin'it out
to the cheap seats.
Funny, I was gonna say
the same thing about that dress.
Oh, you two, really.
The sexual tension--
with a knife you could cut it, huh?
Get a room.
- This seems a little sudden.
- Uh-huh.
- Do you even have a last name?
- Do you?
[ Continues ]
[ Lock Rattling ]
Excuse me.
[ Rattling Intensifiies ]
Ocupado.
[ Banging ]
[ Screams ]
[ Continues ]
[ Whooping ]
- [ Laughing ] Oh!
- Whoo!
[ Whooping ]
Conga.!
[ Laughing ]
Whoo!
Find Artode.
Ooh!
[ Slurring ]
Hey, you want a piece of me, buddy?
That's right. Keep walkin'.
- You walk alone! You walk alone!
- [ Slurring ] Careful.
Oh!
- That thing's loaded.
- So am I.
I mean, wow, Wes.
Wesley, I am totally drunk-faced.
[ Laughs ]
Because you can't hold your--
- What are you drinking?
- Nothing.
You can't hold that.
Oh, yeah, lightweight?
How much have you had?
Including this, I've had...
- about a third of a half of this beer.
- [ Laughs ]
That's weird, right?
Yes, I think so.
I think that's weird.
There's Gunn.
Let's go ask him if that's weird.
Hey.
Hey, Gunn,
is something weird going on?
[ Urinating ]
Charles, you just peed on my shoes.
I'll be damned.
- [ Zipper Zips ]
- That's weird.
Hey, is this a great party or what?
Okay, something is definitely
wrong with this picture.
This might be
the greatest song ever written.
Yes, we appear to be under the effect
of something-- a spell.
Spike, how long have you been...
you know-- this?
It's great, isn't it?
I don't know.
It happened a bit after I
talked with Angel and Lorne.
Yeah, uh, Lorne told me
to think positively.
- Lorne!
- [ Snaps Fingers ]
Whoo.!
[ Whooping ]
Hey, kittens!
Oh, that dance floor is smokin'!
What?
Come on, guys. I'm tellin' you. I--
I did not do anything.
- Angel, you in here? Angel?
- [ Angel Grunts ]
- What?
- [ All Gasping ]
[ Spike ]
Hey, Angel's gettin'some.
- Good on you, mate.
- What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with--
What are you doin' with that--
- Hey, watch it, pal.
- He must be under the effect of Lorne--
And Eve, too, presum-- ''presumily.''
[ Snorting Laugh ]
''Presumily.''
- Lorne's doing it-- something to all of us.
- I am not.
Everything he's told us to do,
we're doing.
Spike's thinking positive.
Gunn is peeing all over the offiice.
- And we're a little bit drunk.
- Yes, but not because we drank.
Because Lorne told us to be drunk.
Lorne told you to pee
all over the office?
- Lord, I hope so.
- This is crazy.
I am not doing this.
I would know if I was doing this.
- I don't even know what this is.
- You know, I really love your desk.
Well, I don't get it. I thought Lorne
was just an empath demon.
Territory! Wait. This morning,
Lorne told me to stake out my territory.
Right. Territorial marking,
taken a little too literally.
- Hey, guys, keep it in your pants!
- Oh!
Hey, I did not tell Gunn
to go water the ferns.
- I did not do anything.
- You had your sleep removed.
- What?
- He hasn't slept in a month.
Oh, dear. An empath demon
deprived of sleep for that long?
- What does that have to do with it?
- Something, apparently.
- Lorne, why'd you let them do that to you?
- Well, I had to do something.
I mean, you don't know
what I've had to deal with.
I mean, I'm the center of gravity
in a town that's full of...
borderline-disorder celebrities
and power brokers.
I mean, all the hand-holding
and the ego stroking...
- and the 4:00 a.m.Jacuzzi strategy sessions?
- [ Urinating ]
I just couldn't keep up with it,
even without sleeping.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell us? And I would've--
- What, fired me?
- I would've helped you, which is
what I'm gonna do now.
- Well, I-- Well, I-- Okay.
- [ Gasps ]
- Wes, Fred, go find Lorne's sleep...
- [ Moaning ]
and figure out a way
to put it back in his head.
- Yes, sir.
- Done and doner.
Lorne, you just stay tight
and try not to, you know, talk.
We've still got a party goin' on. Someone
has to make sure there's ice in the drinks.
- Oh, right.
- Oh! Oh! Me! Me! I'm your people person.
Gunn, go on the floor, see if anyone else
is under the Lorne effect.
- Check.
- And stop with the--
-Do my best.
-And Eve, you stay here with me.
- We'll have more sex. Okay.
- I'm on it.
Brilliant plan. Excellent.
Icky.
[ Sighing ]
Lorne's sleep should
be in here... somewhere.
Lorne's sleep.
Looking for Lorne's sleep.
You know, I think we have
pretty interesting lives.
Oh, I'd say that's true,
given the average.
And I'm having such
a good time right now.
We should do stuff like this
more often, you know?
Just hang out like we used to.
- Friend stuff.
- Absolutely.
Frankly, I always--
Well, I always thought we'd
be better friends than we are.
Oh, we should be.
Let's be better friends
than we are... right now.
- Great.
- You know, share stuff...
talk to each other and tell each other
what we're thinking.
Yes, that would be-- I would--
It would be nice.
We could be confidantes...
confiding confidentially.
[ Whispers ] I've been wanting to do that
for some time now.
[ Both Laugh ]
What do you think of Knox?
What a fantastic entrance.
- Sebassis?
- The nerve.
The raw nerve to lay a hand
on one of mine.!
What is this?
Lower your weapons.
These darts are poisoned,
vampire.
Powerful enough to put you
in a coma for a week.
Enough to kill any one of them
before their next heartbeat.
You murdered Artode.
I imagine we were to be next.
- I didn't murder anyone.
- Dress yourself, Angel.
You have a public execution to attend.
- That's a big mistake.
- [ Woman Screams ]
Move!
- [ Nervous Chattering ]
- Hey!
Oh, boy.
Yeah. Somebody
really dipped his chip.
Okay, Sebassis.
I don't know what's goin' on here...
but we are not behind it.
- Enough lies, vampire.
- Okay, everybody, okay.
Yes, the party's taken
an unfortunate turn momentarily.
- So let's not... fight.
- [ Weapon Clicks ]
''Sleep disorders, Edelmyer complex...
Eldritch causes, empaths.''
Hey, they don't just do sleep here.
Madeline Chu in Accounting,
she had her ennui removed.
Here it is. Lorne's sleep.
Now we just have to find
the delivery device.
This isn't good.
''The effects of
long-term sleeplessness...
on the subconscious mind
of an empath...
can be catastrophic.''
''Catastrophic'' sounds not good.
Under normal conditions...
Lorne has the ability
to read people's destinies...
but now I think
he's writing them.
So what-- instead of receiving,
he's transmitting?
And that's just phase one.
''If you sever the empath
from his subconscious for too long...
that subconscious can--''
It can manifest.
What do you mean, ''manifest''?
Wait. Please wait.
I'm doing this. It's me.
I mean, it's not me.
But I haven't been myself lately.
Somehow, I'm making people do things,
and I'm controlling them.
- [ Chuckles ]
- Whoa!
Well, then, Pylean,
you're making me kill you.
Is that consistent with your theory?
[ Growling ]
- [ Growling Continues ]
- [ Nervous Chatter]
[ Yelling ]
- [ Roaring ]
- Oh, my God!
It's m-me.
That's one bitchin' big suit!
[ Groans ]
- Lorne, what the hell is this?
- Stop it! Stop killing!
Listen to me, me.!
Oh, wow, I must really hate myself.
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
Did-- Did you press--
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
Come on, come on, come on.
Sebassis, run.
- [ Groaning ]
- Oh, sorry about that.
- [ Blows Landing ]
- [ People Shouting ]
- It's here! It's manifested!
- Angel!
Shoot it, Fred.! Now.!
- Oh. Oh! Oh.
- [ Weapon Fires ]
Oh, my God!
They shot Lorney Tunes!
No, I'm-- I'm okay.
I'm just gonna rest my--
my eyes a little-- a little bit.
[ Growling ]
[ Lorne Snoring ]
[ Snoring Continues ]
- [ Elevator Bell Dings ]
- I gotta hand it to 'em.
- I think this is better than last year.
- [ Both Chuckle ]
Uh, we-- we have people who do that.
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
- I-- I fixed our baby.
- What?
The-- The stun grenade.
I, uh-- I figured it out.
Oh.
What I can't figure out
is why I said I'd do it tonight.
Yeah. A lot of us are having
that kind of problem.
I kind of wished you were here.
Well, the night is still young.
Well, I mean, no,
it's over, actually.
But, uh, did you-- do you
wanna get a cup of coffee?
Actually, I could use a drink.
That thing-- I think it was
a manifestation of Lorne's subconscious.
It peeled away from his mind,
using Lorne's supernatural powers...
to punch its way into our world.
''Punch'' is the right word.
Why was it trying to kill everyone?
I don't think it was.
It may have just been processing
the conflicts...
that Lorne normally
deals with in his sleep...
acting out on the emotional responses
he has to the people around him.
I guess Lorne makes
some judgments after all. Eve--
So, I guess we should--
I don't know-- talk?
About what?
About what happened,
you know, back there, with us.
Angel, it's not like this is
the first time I've had sex...
under a mystical influence.
I went to U.C. Santa Cruz.
[ Door Opens ]
How you doin'?
I don't know.
- [ Sniffs ]
- [ Laughs ]
I'm a slob.
[ Laughs ]
Hey, I spoke with Sebassis's people,
explained what I could.
Yeah, so what've we got?
Lawsuit? Demon war?
No. Seems like they enjoy a little
blood sport at their social functions.
- Looks like we're okay.
- We're not okay.
We've been so focused
on the dangers outside...
that we didn't see the ones within.
This place is tryin'
to change us, Gunn.
We can't ever forget that.
Pretty damn good party though.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Well, you know, today, but later.
- Oh, and your chair--
- What?
Don't sit in it.
I already called Janitorial.
Why can't I--
You pissed in the big man's chair?
That's fantastic.
Spike, can you please turn off
that warm fuzzy?
What, the Lorne thing? Wore off.
I just think that's bloody fabulous.
All right, guys. Good night.
Let Lorne get some sleep, all right?
Out.
All right.Just this once.
[ Lorne Moans, Mumbles ]
I'm sorry.
[ Mumbling Continues ]
Hey, it's okay, Lorne.
-Just try to get some rest. Get some sleep.
- Mmm.
Yeah. 'Cause it's-- it's hard to--
It's hard bein'--
bein' the host of the party.
Bein'--
Stop tryin' to be.
Grr! Arrgh!