[Lorne] Hey, uh, who wants some mu shu?
I got beaucoup mu shu here.
[Fred]
I'll take some. Thanks.
Angel, this little picnic
was such a good idea.
[Gunn] Yeah, man.
Why haven't we done this before?
[Angel] Oh, you know,
you've all been working so hard.
- [Wesley] Has anyone seen the plum sauce?
- [Device Whirring]
We're clean. Nobody's listening.
- You were late.
- I thought I was being followed.
[Gunn] I get that we have to be careful,
but it feels weird...
hiding from the company
we're supposed to be running.
We're not hiding.
We're being safe.
There are factions at Wolfram and Hart,
people who want to see us destroyed.
But still, it's not like everyone there is evil.
I mean, we work with these people.
Some of them I see more than
I see you guys, at least lately anyway.
And you think you can trust him?
- Them.
- What?
These people. The ones you're spending
so much time with lately.
Knox, for example.
Um, we're, you know...
[Nervous Laugh]
Friendly, but he's under me.
Or, I'm on top of him... professionally.
All I'm saying is he's not evil.
I think we're all agreed that
the senior partners are.
They put us in charge for a reason.
What we need to know is... Why?
Only been there a month.
Turns out running a company doesn't leave
a lot of time for, you know, covert ops.
Yeah, I'm up to my horns schmoozing starlets
and boozing hipsters, Angel.
What about Gunn?
- What about Gunn?
- It's, well...
what they put in your head and all that
law knowledge and whatever.
Maybe you know something
more than the rest of us.
- The alteration to your mental capacity...
- My capacity's the same.
The good doctor just revved up some idling
brain cells, set 'em in motion.
It's a legitimate concern.
You gave them access to...
I made a deal. We all did. Seems like I'm
the only one who's willing to accept that.
Everybody here got something
out of this.
Fear, mistrust, a great motor pool.
I got the Nancy Sinatra
collection. Original 45s.
I did get a rather nice pen.
Sterling. Has my name on it,
which is not the point at all.
No, the point is what?
That I'm some spy for the senior partners?
- Nobody's saying that.
- Just thinking it.
- No. Charles...
- The point is that the senior
partners have a plan for us.
- And if we're not prepared...
- Angel, it's not like we don't wanna be ready.
We just have, you know, plates.
Big, heaping full plates.
Between running our departments,
handling clients, dealing with Spike...
Spike is a distraction. As soon as he's released
from his ties from Wolfram and Hart...
- That could take years.
- Using the amulet to destroy the Hellmouth...
- it turned Spike into...
- A spook?
Well, he's more than a ghost.
He's something unique.
- [Wesley] Regardless, whatever binds him...
- Can I borrow your pen?
Sure.
- [Gasping]
- [Creature Roaring]
- [Whimpering]
- [Ferocious Growling]
[Screaming]
[Growling]
- [Vehicle Door Opens, Closes]
- [Engine Starts]
- [Tires Screech]
- Damn it.
She was bitten.
I smelled her blood on him.
Tonight's the second night of the full moon...
two more nights for her to go all dog-girl.
- Twelve hours till moonrise and then...
if she hurts anyone...
- She won't. We'll find her.
We better. She won't even know
what's happening to her.
She'll figure it out soon enough.
McManus did. The guy you...
Killed.
I pulled his credit card records,
cross-checked them with police reports.
He left his wife and kids
a couple years ago.
Kept moving, staying in the middle
of nowhere most of the time.
First year or so, a few mangled bodies
showed up here and there.
But the last six months,
guy was leaving corpses like bread crumbs.
Probably tried to control 'em
for a while, then just gave up.
Thought he had to fight it alone and ended up
with nothing worth fighting for.
But this girl, she's not alone.
She's got us.
- Well, aren't we the busy little beaver.
- Hi, Spike.
I, uh, don't suppose all this bugaboo's
about yours ghostly.
- What? No, not you. It's...
- Werewolf girl.
Right. Heard about that.
Bloody shame about
the poor little miss. But...
Spike, I'm sorry, but I'm kind of busy
right now with the situation.
Hey. I'm a situation, remember?
I'm a bloody phantom.
And you and your serious-girl spectacles were
gonna help me with my bloody little problem.
I know and I bloody will.
I had some ideas.
- Really? What? What ideas?
- They're gonna have to wait till...
Later? There may not be a later, love.
It's getting worse.
Worse? You mean, you're...
Am I winking out of existence? Yeah.
And I'm not talking about quick pops to
the netherworld. They're lasting longer now.
- How long?
- Feels like forever.
Look, something's trying to
hold on to me on the other side.
If you don't do something soon,
one of these times...
I may not come back.
- Wesley might be able to...
- No.
- He-He knows more about the mystical...
- I can't.
We got a history, him and me.
What?
It was a long time ago.
He was a young Watcher, fresh out of
the academy, when we crossed paths.
It was a, what you call, battle of wills.
Blood was spilled.
Vendettas were sworn. It was a whole...
My God.
- You're so full of crap.
- Yeah, okay.
Truth is, I just don't want anyone else
knowing about my condition, right?
- Last thing I need is this getting back to Angel.
- I appreciate your condition...
but right now we have a more pressing
priority, like finding and helping this girl.
And me, I'm just left
to fade into nothingness.
There's no need to be dramatic.
Look, just try not to disappear,
and we'll figure it out eventually.
This place,
we have access to everything.
We're useless. Is that what you're trying to
tell me? All these resources...
- We're doing everything we can.
- Two years of history on the dead guy...
and we can't get one lead
on a living, breathing girl.
Fingerprints. Have his, don't have hers.
There must be something
at the attack scene.
So far, not even an earring.
[Spike] Bloody shame,
letting the girl run offlike that.
Somebody's slipping.
I want people on the street
with this in 15 minutes.
You find anybody who's seen her,
you let me know.
- What about tire prints?
- I'm working on it. It takes time, Angel.
Psychics are working on
traces of the girl's blood.
They pick up images, imprints.
Must be her bedroom. Can they
make it clearer? Maybe they could...
- It's not like a photograph.
- [Camera Shutter Clicking]
Pretty rare breed you've got here.
[Wesley]
Dr. Royce is a cryptozoologist on my staff.
I brought him in to tell us what we'll be
dealing with when we find the girl.
Lycanthropus exterus. Undocumented
in North America... till now, obviously.
How is it different from
a standard werewolf?
Biped, for one thing. Walks upright.
Canines are a bit longer than normal.
- Arm span is...
- I don't care about that.
- All I care about is the girl.
- That's rough.
'Cause here on out,
she's in the kill or be killed club.
Here on out,
she's under my protection.
If you find her before she turns.
Catch her after she goes all growly,
won't be easy taking her out.
I had a wee spat with
a werewolf myself once.
Fought for over an hour.
Brutal. Vicious. Almost lost my...
Angel killed him with a pen.
[Grunting Softly]
Oh. Oh.
[Child Laughing]
[Erratic Breathing]
- Careful with the knife.
- It's not even sharp.
It's sharp enough.
Hey, look who's up.
- How long was I out for?
- All day.
I figured you must be sick.
Zack called. He said he missed you
in Life Drawing.
- That's nice.
- [Loud Buzzing]
- Why is your neck purple?
- I don't know.
Is there something
you wanna tell me?
No. L...
I must have tripped on my run.
- Don't overcook the meat.
- Ooh, can I flip?
Ask Auntie Nina to help.
Hey, are you sure you're up for
watching Amanda tonight?
I could try to change shifts.
No, l... I just needed to...
- Aunt Nina?
- [Gasps]
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Those fine lines?
Bad for the car, good for us.
Apparently, they mean
old tires, at least five years.
Thank you. Nice sketch. Somebody saw
your girl last night. East Hollywood.
All right, so we're looking for
a midsize sedan, at least five years old...
- somewhere in the Hollywood area.
- Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
And the moon's arisin',
ladies and gents.
I'm in the D.M. V. Database, but there are
thousands of possible matches.
Color me clever. Sister gets slammed around
by a werewolf, she's putting pedal to metal.
I mean, red light,
green light, same diff.
- Traffic cameras. We networked?
- Yep.
I'm looking at the cameras.
You get set to run with it if I find a match.
Course, I might leak the info to
the senior partners, 'cause we're tight.
- Just do it.
- Is the van ready?
- Yep, I triple-checked.
- Good. 'Cause we got less than an hour.
Lot of fuss over one girl. Other things to do
around here. Important things.
You know that "whoosh" thing that you do
when you're suddenly not there anymore?
- I love that.
- 10:19 last night.
1992 Honda Civic ran a red light
at Western and Franklin.
- Blonde woman.
- That's her.
License number 2ABM543.
Address: 2315 Harvard.
Name: Nina Ash.
How's that?
- Does this look better?
- [Laughs]
- Yeah. Do that.
- Nah, you want something nice.
[Humming]
- [Loud Scratching Sound]
- [Humming Continues]
- What's wrong?
- I'm gonna...
- lie down.
- Mm-hmm.
[Gasps]
Aunt Nina?
- Aunt Nina?
- [Loud Grunts]
[Erratic Breathing]
Aunt Nina?
- Can I come in?
- [Heavy Breathing]
- [Low Growling]
- Can I come in?
Aunt Nina?
- Are you okay?
- [Growling]
Hey, doggie. Come and get it.
Nice shot.
[Vehicle Driving Away]
Oh, God.
- Who are you?
- It's okay.
[Lock Clicks]
My name's Angel. You're safe now.
Safe?
Oh...
[Sniffles]
Well, great. That's...
Get off me! Let go of me!
- Help me, somebody!
- What I'm trying to do, Nina, is help you.
Said the psycho rapist.
How do you know my name?
- What do you want with me?
- Just want you to see something.
I don't... What am I
supposed to be looking...
- God, what is that?
- You don't remember?
- Remember?
- Two nights ago.
You were attacked in the woods.
You were jogging.
Jogging. Wait, yeah.
I remember that l...
That... thing attacked me.
Not exactly.
I was in the area. I heard screams, but
by the time I got there...
That was you. Yeah. I remember.
You-You saved me.
I was too late.
Oh, my God.
It was a werewolf, Nina...
and you were bitten.
No. This is insane.
The bite already started a process.
You may have already started to feel the effects.
Distorted vision. Heightened senses.
Blood. Jill, my sister,
she was cooking meat.
Oh, my God. L-I smelled
the blood. It was making me...
Oh, God. Amanda. My niece.
- She's okay and so is your sister.
- No, you don't get it.
- Nina, it's okay.
- No, it's not.
- You didn't...
- I wanted to rip her throat out.
It wasn't you.
It was that thing inside.
- Oh, like there's a difference?
- There is. A big one.
- I know this is a lot...
- Don't tell me what you know.
You didn't wake up
and find out you're a... monster.
You don't know anything.
L-I'm not a werewolf... like you.
But-But, I know what it's like.
I'm a monster too.
So, what, you're like a Frankenstein?
What? No.
Um, I'm-I'm a vampire.
- Vampire.
- But I have a soul.
I'm not evil, and neither are you.
- But vampires kill people and they...
- Can control themselves...
if they want to.
I do it every day and so can you.
I'll help.
Can you... cure me?
No. But I can keep you safe.
How is she doing?
Oh, agreed to stay in the holding cell tonight,
but she's pretty scared.
So, what do we do now?
[Spike] We wait for the show.
Should be a good one.
Everyone on pins and needles, dreading
the moonrise. Then pop goes the werewolf.
I can't stop what's gonna happen,
but I can keep her from getting hurt.
These first few transformations
are the worst.
The werewolf s strength combined with...
the disorientation and fear.
You mean she could hurt herself?
Oh, I've seen them bang their heads
against walls, claw at their own skin.
We'll just have to tranq her,
let her sleep through it.
Well, that could work for tonight,
but over the long haul, a bad idea.
Well, there has to be something.
They like familiar scents, images.
Maybe if you took her home let her get a
few things, uh, could have a calming effect.
Fetching a blankie's not going to
make a bloody bit of difference.
- Spike, really not helping.
- I'm just saying... the girl's a killer.
Maybe not tonight, or tomorrow,
but she will get out of that cage.
- Not if she doesn't want to.
- Oh, she'll want to.
- It's unfortunate, but...
- And when it's not that time of month?
She'll be wracked by the guilties.
What with a soul and all.
- Didn't seem to bother you.
- Oh, it's been nothing but a pain in my...
Finally. I'll take Nina by her house.
Angel, it's the middle of the day,
unless you plan on waiting in the car.
Take security, in case
she changes her mind.
So, the entourage. All this for me?
Um, no... Well, yeah, kind of.
I mean, it's just in case you, you know.
- Run away?
- It's-It's not like you're a prisoner.
You're totally not.
It's just... [Exhales]
Really important that
you stay with us tonight.
This is just so... [Scoffs]
I should be in ceramics class right now.
We're learning raku.
Seems like somebody else's life.
Nina, it's just three nights a month,
not even days.
Your life doesn't have to change... much.
How would you... You're not
a monster too, are you?
Nope. Standard issue science nerd.
I did spend five years in a
demon dimension... till Angel saved me.
I guess he saves a lot of girls, huh?
Girls, guys, puppies.
He's pretty much
an equal opportunity saver.
So you two are, like, a couple?
Me and Angel?
Oh, God, no. He...
He was seeing someone, sort of.
But, she... Angel doesn't date much...
at all... 'cause of his circumstances.
- 'Cause he's a vampire.
- Kind of.
That doesn't mean that...
His situation's just complicated.
Must be lonely.
Sometimes, maybe.
But, it's not like
he doesn't have anyone.
We all...
We try to be there for each other.
- Like a family.
- Yeah.
A demon-hunting, helpless-helping...
dysfunctional family.
You sign this, we're all set to turn
McManus's body over to his family.
They made arrangements to
transport his body back to...
- [Sighs]
- The North Pole.
Turns out he had a close,
personal relationship with Santa.
Angel?
What? Oh, I'm with you.
Turning over the... Santa?
Angel, you saved that girl's life.
- If you hadn't gotten there when you did...
- Werewolf would've killed her.
I know. Doesn't change what
she's gonna have to go through.
Well, that part sucks, no doubt,
but you did everything you could.
You know what, Gunn? Don't need
a pep talk right now. Just do your job.
Right. I'll just go do that
someplace else.
Whoa, watch it there. Just passin'by and got
splashed with a heap of grouchy.
Gotta tell ya, Angelkins, that extra weight
is not looking so good on you.
I'm talking about psychic pounds, pumpkin.
Why don't you consider me
theJenny Craig for the soul, huh?
- So let's hear it.
- I'm not gonna sing.
Couldn't bear it if you did. No, it's talking
you need. Or maybe a shoulder...
- I'm not gonna cry either.
- I was going to a leaning place.
Okay, Atlas, how about a shrug?
Look, so you've got
the weight of the world. [Chuckles]
A burden sure, but breaking news it ain't.
- Listen, Lorne, this isn't a good time.
- No. No, it never is.
Spike showing up your first day in
the Wolfram and Hart saddle?
Took the jolly
right out of the rancher.
We've been feeling it
ever since then, Angelcakes.
Okay, so it's no secret.
I don't like the guy.
Like him, don't like him.
That's up to you.
You're fighting so many enemies around you,
Angel, your punches are getting sloppy.
And we've got
the bruises to prove it.
We're operating in
unfriendly territory, champ.
I don't want you to forget about
the people covering your back.
I changed my mind.
I could go in first, explain...
- No, let's just...
- Hey. I know you're scared...
- but running away's not gonna help.
- [Sighs]
What about fleeing? Can I flee?
Maybe they're not even here.
What the hell happened to you?
I've been worried... Who are you?
- I'm Fred. It's nice...
- I come home, and you're just gone.
- Amanda was terrified.
- Jill, I'm sorry.
Who leaves the house without their purse or
keys? What'd you do, jump out the window?
- I thought Amanda heard me say I was leaving.
- Oh, that's great.
- Blame it on a nine-year-old.
- It's my fault.
I called Nina, like, totally suicidal 'cause
this guy in our ceramics class dumped me.
A-And then my car got towed and she wanted
to call, but my cell phone battery...
Do you mind, whoever you are?
This has nothing to do with you.
- Leave her alone.
- Oh, like you left Mandy alone?
In the house? At night? Do you know
she didn't want to go to school today?
- I had to lie. Tell her I'd heard from you.
- Shut up. Just shut up.
I called the police. I thought...
You sleep all day. You've got bruises
you don't remember getting.
Just tell me. What's going on?
I'm sorry about last night...
but you can't count on me
all the time.
Since when?
Just... find another babysitter.
I'll just... if that's okay.
And, maybe. She's, uh, she'll be okay.
So she was yelling
and furious, but that's good.
It means, you know, she cares.
- If something happened to Amanda...
- But it didn't...
- and it's not going to.
- You don't know that.
Angel... That's weird.
And really not good. Run!
[Nina Screaming]
- [Nina Groans]
- [Cell Phone Rings]
- We got the package.
- Bring it around back. I just had the floors done.
No! Let me go! No, don't.
What are you doing? Let me go!
You have to let me go.
Please.
[Crying]
[Gasping]
[Singing Pop]
- [Continues]
- [Wesley]
Lorne's read the entire security team already.
And the lab staff, as well as
half of my department.
If the kidnappers had someone inside
at Wolfram and Hart, Lorne'll know.
What if she was detected somehow,
before we found her?
- Yeah, but by who?
- The scariest thing was how organized they were.
Almost military.
An underground, monster-hunting
military organization.
- It's happened before.
- It's all my fault.
- I'm stupid.
- Anything happens to Nina, it's on me.
"Hmm, that's weird. Why don't I just
approach the mysteriously ajar door?"
Stop with the mocking.
Get enough of that from Blondie Bear.
- Spike. Has anyone seen him...
- Since he went poof? No.
But it's been hours. Angel...
- What do you got?
- Usual suspects.
There's the sacrificers. Wackos who wanna
rid the world of abominations.
And werewolf packs
looking for new recruits.
Then there's the paranormal
sporting groups.
- L... I'll be...
- Vampire hunting in Eastern Europe.
- That kind of thing.
- Spike.
Hey, Spike.
Spike. Stop.
Spike? Spike, wait.
Spike, wait!
[Groans]
Damn. Like he can't hear me.
Just whoot! Right through the...
- Were you looking for me?
- Oh, is this your office?
I'm so sorry. I was following Spike...
and l-I kind of made a mess.
He just went right through the wall.
It's so annoying when he does that...
'cause there's nothing
you can do to...
stop him.
You're right. It's calendula. He must've
known we'd have him sing for Lorne.
So he came prepared
to block the reading.
It's like taking a Valium
to pass a polygraph test.
I knew as soon as I saw
the vial in the trash can.
How'd you end up going through
Royce's trash anyway?
It was, well, Spike.
- He led me in here.
- Yo, here we go.
We got ourselves a secret panel.
- Where is she?
- I don't know what you're...
- Wrong answer.
- But it's a secret.
If I tell you, this man, he's not like you.
You're a good guy.
But he's a... Well, no offense,
but he's scarier than you.
Wanna bet?
Are they...
[Disgusted Sound]
We'll just, yeah, burning.
Burning would be good for these.
Not exactly an autopsy knife.
You're not gonna believe this.
Oh, God.
- I know where she is.
- Angel, we found...
- It's what they plan to do to her.
- It's a menu.
- [Creaking]
- [Murmuring]
[Scattered Applause]
[Whimpering]
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
for coming together on such short notice.
We have a very rare
and special treat for you tonight.
Moonrise is in 15 minutes.
Shortly thereafter...
dinner will be served.
When I dined on werewolf in Seville...
the cocinera used an understated mole
sauce to bring out the meat's tanginess.
I've never forgotten
that exquisite burst of taste.
But Chef Renault swears
serving it anaise...
with a light drizzle of white truffle oil
will be quietly surprising.
[Knocking]
I'm all up in the law now, but damn
it feels good to get my violence on.
- Crane's not gonna like this.
- If I were you, I'd just be hoping the girl's alive.
She has to be, at least through dinner. Once
a werewolf dies, it reverts to its human state.
You mean, to eat werewolf
they gotta eat her alive?
Evan. You've brought guests.
- We're just here to pick up a friend.
- [Cocks Gun]
- [Woman] Watch it.
- [Woman Screams]
- Geez, they garnished you?
- No, get away.
Just let them choke on me.
Listen to me.
Tomorrow you're gonna be home.
This is what I am.
I can't go back there, ever.
- This is better.
- Nothing better about ending up
in a doggie bag.
- [Clattering]
- What, no leprechaun soufflé?
There's no such thing as leprechauns.
- We've hit a snag.
- We're not leaving without the girl.
I'm willing to let my men die.
Can you say the same?
- I go, you're going with me.
- It's a risk. What can I say?
You probably should've
told me to drop this.
[Relieved Sigh]
- This is the part where we take our friend and go.
- I'm afraid not.
Tonight may not be salvageable...
but my guests have paid a high price,
some higher than others.
And I promised them a werewolf.
- [Growls]
- [Screams]
- [Royce Groaning]
- And a month from now you'll have one.
No. No.
Mr. Crane, please.
Oh, no. No, please.
Don't do this to me,
Mr. Crane. I'm sorry.
[Whimpering]
Mr. Crane, I'm sorry.
No. Oh.! Oh.!
Mr. Crane, I'm begging you. No.
[Gasps]
[Exhales]
Spike.
I've been looking for you.
You were there again.
Where you go when you're not...
here.
There.
Nowhere.
[Forced Chuckle]
I didn't think I was coming back.
But you did... mostly.
And you led me to
Dr. Royce's office, which was...
completely not on purpose, was it?
But, still, you're here.
Last gasp before eternal fire
and brimstone. Let's party.
We have to tell Angel.
- No.
- But he could do something.
- Talk to the senior partners.
- I said no.
Okay, then I'm going to help you.
Well, I don't know exactly...
but I am going to
find a way to bring you back.
Really bring you back. I promise.
Well, all right, then.
No need to get dramatic.
[Singing]
This is it.
She's a really good artist.
Oh, our refrigerator's always available
if she's looking to show.
How do you live with it?
Knowing that you've killed people?
Nina, they were going to
eat you for dinner.
I just wanna wake up, you know?
At some point, you'll be
at the grocery store or with Amanda...
and, the whole werewolf thing,
it'll just be a part of who you are.
Next you're gonna tell me
you actually like being a vampire.
Well, being nearly indestructible's cool.
I can't tell them.
Maybe, maybe not.
That part's not covered in the manual.
They're waiting for you.
You don't ever think about letting go?
Disappearing somewhere?
Look, if you separate yourself from the ones
you love, the monster wins.
- You make it sound simple.
- It's not.
See you next month.
[Car Door Closes]
[Pop]
[Engine Starts]
[Lorne]
Mmm. Talk about a room with a view.
- [Fred] Wow, is that the hotel?
- [Wesley] Where?
- No, I think that's the Center for Scientology.
- Oh. Right.
They look, um,
nothing alike at all.
I was starting to think we were never
gonna see the inside of this place.
I'm sorry. I probably should've
had you guys over sooner...
but I'm trying to get
used to the place myself.
Look at this.
I'm home.
Hey, Cosmos all around?
- [Fred] Sounds good.
- Quite luxurious.
It's not bad.
- Don't mean to talk shop,
but Crane's Bistro of the Bizarre?
- Out ofbusiness.
- Permanently.
- What if I have a craving for Sasquatch soup?
Is that something you English eat
with your beans on toast?
Mmm, you guys are making me hungry.
Who wants Chinese?
As long as nothing
comes tartare, I'm in.
- No, I'm too tired to make any decisions.
- Just order the usual, Fredikins.
- I'm buying.
- Ladies and gentlemen, hell just froze over.
So, werewolf girl.
Think you got a shot?
- She gave me a look.
- [Wesley] Really?
A look?
We moved, actually, to a law firm.
Uh-huh. Different. No. Nice.
Okay. Um, one mu shu chicken.
Two beef and broccolis.
One cashew shrimp.
Um, maybe some lettuce wraps.
Grr! Arrgh!