[ Crashing ]
He's been here.
Picking up loads
of trace signatures.
- Fred.
- Hair follicles, enzymes and something--
Blood. But it's not his.
It's--
- Oh, God.
- I think God is out at the moment.
Why would Greenway do this?
It was just a stupid racketeering charge.
I told him we'd get him off with probation
so long as he shut down operations.
He's a Wolfram and Hart client--
our client.
Oh, and he's evil.
What are the odds?
- What do we do now?
- Now I find Greenway, and I kill every inch of him.
You won't.
Five holy women.
This wasn't random. It's ritual.
He's jumped dimensions.
- What?
- Also, not shockingly,
our client practices black arts.
He's escaped through
a pan-dimensional doorway...
disappeared into any one
of infinite universes.
- Fred?
- My equipment's not calibrated...
to track anything
out of this dimension.
- Even if such a thing was possible,
it would take months or maybe years.
- That's it.
But probably months,
or maybe weeks, if I really pushed.
- I can't do this anymore.
- [ Gunn ] Do what?
Any of this. Living with it.
Running Wolfram and Hart.
I quit.
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Gasps ]
There's nothing more to discuss.
I'm resigning.
Gee, seems like a ripe topic
for discussion to me.
What happened last night was tragic.
- It's a terrible setback, but--
- Setback, Wes?
Status quo. Evil wins...
'cause instead of just wiping it out,
we negotiate with it--
or worse, for it.
Angel, we're doing the best we can.
It's not that you guys aren't doing your jobs.
It's that we shouldn't be doing these jobs
in the first place-- or I shouldn't.
Let's say we've all had a bellyful.
Any thought about what'd happen to us
if we tried to say bye-bye?
The ramifications, I mean.
Think the senior partners are gonna let us
breeze on out the front door?
- You're saying we're trapped?
- I'm saying we knew what we were gettin' into...
when we signed up for this gig.
Let's not start pretending that this
was some lease with an option to buy.
Gunn, do you really think they won't let us out?
Or is it that you just don't want to leave?
Okay. Maybe I don't.
It's 'cause I believe in what we're doin'.
We made the right call.
And I'm sure that legal-brain upgrade
they gave you has got nothin' to do with--
We all got somethin' out of this.
[ Phone Rings ]
Yeah. It's Angel.
What?
What is it?
It's Cordelia.
- Cordelia?
- [ Cordelia ] Yeah.
That chick's in rough shape.
You'd think they'd give
Miss One-foot-in-the-grave a private room.
Which brings me to-- Hey!
Couldn't you stick me someplace that smells
a little less like ammonia-soaked death?
Ahh!
- Cordy.
- Yeah. It's me.
- [ Laughing ]
- It's extraordinary.
You're-- You look--
- I don't want to say really hot, but--
- Oh, yes, you do.
I'm a vision of hotliness.
And how weird is that? Uh! Mystical comas.
You know, if you can stand the horror of
a higher power hijacking your mind and body...
so that it can give birth to itself?
- Really recommend 'em.
- You remember?
Last year?
Yeah. I remember everything,
pretty much...
at least until I slipped into slumberland.
Maternal instincts aside,
I hope you kicked its ass for me.
- Is everybody all right?
- Yeah.
- Uh, great. We're all--
- Yes, super.
Super, yes. Super.
- Hey, why don't we get you outta here?
- Ahh! I love that plan.
I hope you brought me some clothes, 'cause--
Damn.
- Oh. Well, we-- we weren't expecting--
- We could stop and buy some.
Ooh! Great! Shopping! Ha-ha!
I love that idea, 'cause, you know,
I'm not so ready to go back to the hotel yet.
- [ Laughs ]
- Not a problem.
[ Bell Dings ]
- I can't.
- It's okay.
[ Sighs ]
See? It's just an offiice...
going about its day.
Uh, nothing scary popping out at you.
-Just regular people going about--
- Aah!
[ Man ] Yeah. I found the scamp
hiding in one of the copiers, you know?
Livin'on nothin'but toner fluid.
Can you beat that?
The slave, I mean. I assume the archduke
is gonna beat him and all that?
That's-- Heh! Nothing.
- Hey, do you want to see my office?
- Yeah.
- Lorne!
- Are you huggable?
It is so good to see--
Oh, my God. Gunn?
You have hair.
Oh. Heh! Yeah.
What'd you think, I was prematurely bald?
- I wasn't.
- [ Cordelia Laughing ]
- Ohh. Hey, Fred.
- Hi, Cordy!
- Ohh. So where's Connor?
- [ Laughs ]
- [ Gunn ] Who?
- What do you mean, who? Connor. Isn't he--
- Angel, where's your--
- [ Squealing ] Oh, my God!
Aah!
I can't believe you're here!
Likewise, especially since the last time
I saw you, you tried to kill me.
Oh, Harmony, she's--
Actually, sh-- she's my secretary.
Oh. Well, things just keep
getting better and better.
I know!
You and me, together again.
So, how was the coma?
Uh, Harmony, I think Cordy's had
enough excitement for the day.
Why don't you--
Why doesn't everybody get back to work?
- Great to see you.
- Bye.
- [ Whispers ] We'll talk later.
- Hey, listen, crumb cake.
When you're ready to splash back into
that acting pool,just say the word.
- I'll have you lunching with Colin Farrell like that.
- [ Snaps Fingers ]
- Who's Colin Farrell?
- Cordy, I know there's a lot to take in,
a lot of changes.
But I promise you--
things here are workin' out.
- Really?
- Yeah!
With these resources...
there's nothin' we can't do,
no one we can't save.
Except maybe yourself.
What?
I had a vision...
from the you-know-what That Be.
That's what woke me up.
And you know something?
When higher powers send you coma visions,
you better pay attention.
What'd you see?
You, in trouble.
Also...
these weird symbols--
glyphs, I guess--
on a wall...
and on flesh.
A tattoo,
and there's a woman behind you.
- You saw a woman in your vision?
- No, lunkhead, right now. Behind you.
You weren't home upstairs. Didn't think
you'd mind me using your private elevator.
Eve, I mind you breathing.
Get out.
Yeah. Sure. Except I'm here
to convey the partners' concern.
Little issue of you letting a client
skip out of our dimension.
The dead nuns we can deal with...
but the firm's out
1 0 million in bail costs.
I ask you-- is that any way to run a business?
Who's your friend, Angel?
I'm Cordelia Chase.
- Oh. My name is--
- I didn't ask.
Right.
Cordelia Chase.
Oh, yeah. Angel talked a lot
about you... at first.
I thought I told Security
not to let you in this building.
Sweetie, I'm liaison
to the senior partners.
You honestly think you have any control
over my comings and goings?
Well, maybe not my goings, but you did have
a way with my comings at the Halloween party.
So you two are groin buddies?
- And I thought Darla was rock bottom.
- We're not--
[ Sighs ]
Just... once.
There were special circumstances.
Lorne told us to, but mystically.
We'll talk business later, big guy.
I'll let you two catch up.
And I'll let you walk out of here
with your head still attached to your body.
Harmony, I want Security keeping tabs
on Eve while she's in the building.
- Got it, bossy.
- That's the kind of person
you do business with now.
Angel, do you realize what's happening?
You've made a deal with the devil.
Oh, come on, Cordy.
You're being a little overdramatic. It's not that--
I gotta go. Everything's in place.
I'll draw up the paperwork.
- Good. Great.
- Uh, racquetball Thursday?
Okay, then.
- Uh!
- What did I do?
- [ Video Game Beeping ]
- Made the biggest mistake of your life...
and I'm gonna make you pay.
- Oh, yeah.
- [Joystick Clicking ]
Feel my wrath,
gorilla throwin' barrels.
Bloody hell.
Really should knock
on a bloke's door...
especially one that's got no qualms
about killin' trespassers.
Come on. Is that any way
to talk to your benefactor?
Just a little concerned about you.
You haven't been out in the field lately.
In case you haven't been keepin' up with the
sports pages, I got my bloody hands hacked off...
- by that deranged Slayer you sent me after.
- Yeah.
Sorry about that.
But, hey, good ol' buddies at Wolfram and Hart
managed to reattach 'em just fine, huh?
- You sit around here and play video games.
- Rehab, mate.
Workin' out the digits.
You got no idea
how rotten this feels.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, amazingly enough, I do.
Yeah. Got my hand cut off a few years back.
Line of duty.
So believe me when I tell you,
I can feel your pain.
Oh, half of it anyway.
Give you that.
- [ Opens Can ]
- Don't forget you've got a job to do.
The Powers That Be are countin' on their
champion. So are all the other helpless people--
Don't need a pep talk, Doyle.
I already plan on goin' out.
You just get one of your visions
and tell me when and where.
- That's what I-- That's what I like to hear.
- [ Phone Ringing ]
- [ Beeps ]
- Yeah?
- [ Eve ] We got a big problem.
- Can this wait?
Kinda not.
Cordelia Chase is awake.
- Really?
- She's talking about some vision she had...
steering Angel right toward you.
Come on. You stupid plumber!
Bloody pathetic.!
- Well, now. Guess this calls for a change of plans.
- [ Spike ] Hear me? You're dead!
[ Doyle's Voice ]
''If you need help, then look no further.
''Angel Investigations is the best.
- Our rats are low''--
- [ Cordelia's Voice ] ''Rates.''
It says rats.
''Our rates are low, but our standards are high.
''When the chips are down...
''and you're at the end of your rope...
''you need someone that you can count on.
''And that's what you'll find here--
''someone who'll go all the way...
''who'll protect you no matter what.
- So don't lose hope. ''
- [ TVBeeps Off]
Sorry. I was snooping.
- I found this.
- No, it's okay.
Just-- Uh, you couldn't sleep?
Oh, no sleep for me.
I've slept enough for one lifetime.
Been a long while since I've seen that.
[ Sighs ]
- First soldier down.
- Yeah.
Doyle pissed me off so righteously
going out like that.
But he knew.
He knew what he had to do.
Didn't compromise.
He used his last breath
to make sure you'd keep fighting.
I get that now.
Cordy...
there are reasons I agreed to take over
Wolfram and Hart, reasons you don't understand.
I understand just fine.
They seduced you
with all their fancy facilities...
manpower, threw a whole bunch
of money at you...
plied you with all these expensive toys
and penthouses with spectacular views, and--
Really spectacular.
What was I saying?
- I've been seduced.
- That's right, pal.
They dazzled you with shiny objects
and beautiful things.
- And there is no reason you could give me for--
- Connor.
- Where is Connor? Why did Gunn ask--
- They don't remember him.
It was part of my agreement to take this job.
The senior partners altered reality.
Gave... Connor a life,
a real family, a childhood--
somethin' I could never give him.
He's got no memories of us...
and no one remembers him...
except me and you...
and Eve, for some reason.
So, not only did you strike a deal with
your worst enemy to give up your son...
you let them rape the memories
of your friends who trust you.
He was about to kill you and himself.
He was so torn up.
I didn't have any other way to stop him...
any way to help him.
- Connor's happy now. And--
- [ Sighs ]
And we're doin' fine here. I mean, we've--
we've done some great work here.
Don't give me that ''everything's fine here''
company line.
I'm not buying it
and neither are you.
And neither are
the Powers That Be.
Why do you think they woke me up?
Gave me that vision?
They know you slipped the track,
and they want me to help put you back on it.
You're wrong about the Powers.
They're not in my corner anymore.
Looks like Spike
is their new champion.
Spike. Spike who?
Spike. He's got a soul now,
and he saved the world.
And he's out there on the streets--
you know, helpin' the-- the helpless.
Okay. Spike's a hero...
and you're C.E.O. of Hell, Incorporated.
What frickin' Bizarro World
did I wake up in?
- I'm sorry.
- I naturally assumed you'd be lost without me.
But this?
I am lost without you.
- You just forgot who you are.
- Remind me.
Oh, no.
That's for you to figure out, Bubba.
I can tell you who you were--
a guy who always fought his hardest for what
was right, even when he couldn't remember why...
even when he was miserable, which was--
let's face it-- a not-small portion of the time.
He did right,
and that gave him something--
a light, a glimmer.
And that's the guy I fell in--
the, um--
the guy I knew.
I see him around here,
and maybe I'll start believing.
Let me know if you do.
Do you ever wonder...
do you ever think about...
if we'd met up that night
and had a chance to--
All the time.
Guess we missed
our moment, huh?
Maybe we were meant to.
Or maybe people like us
just don't get to... have that.
Angel...
there are no people like us.
You're not worried at all?
She's awake.
That means the Powers That Be
are getting nervous, taking an interest.
Higher stakes.
That likes me fine.
We're not sittin' at
the five-dollar table anymore.
You know the house always wins.
So the question becomes:
Whose house are we in?
Senior partners gave that Eurotrash vampire
everything I'd worked for.
Couldn't let that slide.
They didn't see me comin'.
Maybe they're gettin' too old for this.
It all comes back to Angel, doesn't it?
He's still the center of your universe.
No, baby.
You are.
Remember how I said...
''Let's not have your department
looking for those symbols I saw in my vision.
Let's do this like we used to--
you and me, crackin' the books''?
- Yes.
- Well, that was dumb.
What'd you ever listen to me for?
I don't know.
I think I sort of missed this.
You and me and the books.
Kickin' it old school, as they say.
And I never will again.
[ Laughs ]
Wes...
last year when that,
um, higher, uh...
[ Scoffs ]
whatever...
took over my body...
did those things--
Nobody's talking about it.
What's to say?
We all understand it wasn't you.
Do you?
- You didn't kill Lilah.
- I know.
Still, um--
[ Whispers ]
I'm sorry.
Huh! I just wanted
to tell you that before--
Hey, that's them.
Those, the tats.
Look. Ah!
Oh. Protection runes, derived
from the Enochian alphabet.
The ones from your vision
are symbols...
some kind of concealment spell.
- ''Clouds before the all-seeing eyes''--
- Mm. Okay.
This part I didn't miss--
cryptic poetry.
They protect the bearer
from being viewed remotely...
from higher powers, seers, mystics.
Or, transposed to today,
any means of modern surveillance.
Somebody really
wants to stay hidden.
- [ Beeping ]
- [ Door Unlocking ]
[ Device Beeping ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gurgling ]
Place is like a rat maze...
complete with rats.
Spike. Well, well.
Heard you weren't evil anymore,
which kinda makes the hair silly.
- [ Growling ]
- Uh, or nice.
[ Screaming ]
- You took me on and lost, remember, old man?
- Yeah. Touch Cordelia again...
- get ready for our very last rematch.
- She's evil, you gormless tit!
- Excuse me! Who bit whom?
- Did you call me a tit?
- I thought he had a soul.
- I thought she didn't.
- I do!
- So do I.
- Well, clearly, mine's better.
- Look--
I see fangs,
I'm gonna play dentist.
- And you called this guy the big hero?
- You called me a hero?
- I didn't know you were eating people.
- [ Grunts ]
- Ow!
- God!
It was a taste test, you git.
Needed to know if what
my source said was true.
And actually, well,
you don't taste evil.
Demons are more astringent,
with a sort of oaky--
- What source?
- I got a guy.
Has an in with the Powers That Whatsit.
Gets his visions.
- Visions?
- Yeah. Said Cordelia was taken over
by some big bad.
- Came to destroy you all.
- His vision's a rerun.
The thing that possessed Cordy's
long dead, Spike.
Well, looks like tattoo boy
was wrong this time.
Wait. Tattoos?
What kind of tattoos?
I don't know--
symbols, tribal-like.
This guy with the visions,
do you have a name?
Called himself Doyle.
[ Indistinct Conversation ]
No, he didn't kill her.
She's still alive.
- Now they're talking... a lot.
- [ Lindsey ] Hey, it was a long shot.
Listen, babe, I'm almost there.
All right? So get out of the building...
right now.
Can we have a word with you, Eve?
- Now's really not a good time. Ow!
- Let's go, Lilah Jr.
- We've got a problem, Eve.
- Damn right you do.
When I tell the partners
you assaulted me--
Couple weeks ago,
a man approached Spike...
told him that the Powers That Be
have some missions for him.
- Spike, brain trust that he is, went along with it.
- Hey.
He's the one who told Spike
to save me from the parasite--
the parasite you put on me
in the first place.
- Oh, not this again.
- Get out of that chair...
and I will feed you
those Manolo Blahniks--
which are stunning, by the way.
Seems to me like you and this guy
are workin'together.
Look. I don't know what you're talking about.
But you--you can't keep me here.
- I have to leave.
- But the thing that really, really pisses me off...
is that this guy seems to be
going by the name of Doyle.
- Doesn't ring a bell.
- It does to me.
It rings a big frickin' gong,
and I want to know who has the nerve...
to be using that name.
I'm gonna give you one chance
to tell me where he is.
Look. I don't know what--
- Excuse me, boss?
- Not now, Harmony.
Okay. But do I get
the afternoon off too?
- What are you talking about?
- Everybody's gone.
The whole building cleared out
a few minutes ago.
What's goin' on, Eve?
[ Machine Powers Up ]
[ Switch Clicks ]
Wakey, wakey.
I checked the server. Message went out,
Code 7, right before the building emptied.
- What's a Code 7, Eve?
- I don't know.
Seriously.
- Okay, this is getting us nowhere.
Angel, torture her.
- What?
- You heard me.
Building's clearing out.
Means we don't have a lot of time. Have at it.
I can't just... torture her.
- Like, wha--
- He's right, Cordy.
- If we sink to their level, then--
- [ Harmony Grunts ]
- Harmony!
- Is this okay?
I mean, I am evil, technically.
I don't mind torturing her for the team.
Yeah. Okay.
Come on, you hussy!
Spill it!
Okay, okay! Stop.
It's a fail-safe.
They built a fail-safe.
[ Groans ]
- Harmony, she's talking.
- She is?
Already? Well, that sucks.
Look. The senior partners were never certain
they could keep you under their thumb...
so they created a fail-safe,
housed it in the sublevels of the building.
- What kind of fail-safe?
- I don't know what it is exactly, but it's huge...
and alive and specifically
designed to destroy you.
How can I stop it?
Only way to shut it down's
in the chamber itself.
Well, if that's true,
then who activated it in the first place?
- You were with us when the building cleared out.
- Had to be someone else--
someone with the ability to slip past
Wolfram and Hart's security systems.
Like our magically tattooed faux Doyle.
Spike, I don't want to go in blind.
Anything else you know about this guy?
Not much.
Uh, average size.
Dressed like an urban cowboy.
Got his hand chopped off once.
His hand?
He's back.
- Lindsey.
- Who?
Lock the building down. Make sure he can't
get out. Don't trust security systems.
He won't show up
because of those tattoos of his.
There could be a way to fix that.
I'll need some help.
- Oh, my dance card's free.
- Who is Lindsey?
A lawyer. Wolfram and Hart's former golden boy,
till he ran off to go find himself.
Yeah. Should've stayed lost.
Harmony, guard Eve.
- She moves, eat her.
- Really? Thanks. Hm!
- Angel, you're not going down there alone.
- Fail-safe's meant for me.
- I'm not gonna risk anybody I care about.
- I'll go.
Okay. Be ready to evacuate. This thing
gets past me, get the hell out of the building.
- Past us.
- No, no. Cordy--
Yeah. Save it, Angel.
You can order me around all you want.
But I know my rights,
and I want to see a lawyer.
- What the bloody hell is this?
- Let's find out.
[ Alarm Blaring ]
Zombies. Ohh, swell.
- We don't have time for this!
- Go on. I'll hold 'em back.
Come on, lads.
No need to be gentle.
We're all dead men here.
Bye-bye, Angel.
Hello, Lindsey.
And the hero arrives,
right on schedule.
And with a date.
Yeah. Dinner and a show,
and you're both.
Is this the part where I get all weak in the knees?
Promise I'll never do it again?
- Little late for that, ''Doyle.''
- There's always time for redemption.
- Isn't that your whole thing?
- You had your chance.
I guess some people,
they just never change.
[ Groaning ]
I did.
- You just gonna lay there and bleed?
- Cordy, get out of here.
No.
Hang out.
This won't take long.
Angel!
Oh. Well, it's not the size that matters,
big guy.
- It's how you use it.
- Shut it down.
- Say ''please.''
- I wasn't talkin' to you.
Oh, right! On it.
- [ Rapid Departing Footsteps ]
- So, go and get yourself a little mojo?
- Should never have come back, Lindsey.
- What can I say?
I missed you.
Uh, okay.
Let's try the blue one.
- [ Crackles ]
- Ow! Ah! Okay. Not the blue one.
A little something I picked up in Nepal.
You like it?
They sell that crap at the airport.
You know, all my carefully laid-out plans,
my designs--
When you get right down to it,
this is pretty sweet, too, huh?
Reason enough for me
to come back.
You, me...
fight to the death--yours.
Seen your tough act before,
you squirt.
First time we ever met,
you put on a show--
huffing and puffing, tellin' me I couldn't
lay a hand on your scumbag client.
- So you kicked him out a window.
- Good times.
- It was a defining moment.
- [ Rumbling ]
Kinda like this one.
Ohh, crap.
- ''Woodbury lichen.''
- Check.
- Where's our danbeetle skeleton?
- Already in the bowl.
Man, I should be down there. Got enough
Betty Crockers. I should be throwin' some hurt.
''Sprinkle ingredients with
the arterial blood of an unclean. ''
A demon.
[ Chuckles ]
We're unclean. Like you're so April fre--
You sure that thing said,
uh, ''arterial blood''?
- Sorry.
- Why don't they ever need
the urine of an unclean?
I've got plenty of unclean urine.
[ Chuckles Weakly ]
Look. Uh, think I'm making some right now.
That must've stung.
Worse than when you
cut off my hand.
Angel.!
Who is this?
- [ Coughs ]
- I came to fight the vampire with a soul.
Guess you shouldn't have sold it, huh?
Look at ya. From champion to pathetic
corporate puppet in just a few months.
Used to have fire in your heart.
Now all you got in there
is that big, honkin' sword.
- How's that feel, champ?
- Could be worse.
Aah! If it had been made out of wood,
you dumb-ass!
Now, you are gonna give it up.
[ Machine Powers Down ]
- Like that was so hard.
- No!
All those tattoos,
all those new tricks you've learned--
just don't matter.
Doesn't matter what you try.
Doesn't matter where I am
or how badass you think you've become.
'Cause you know what?
I'm Angel.
I beat the bad guys.
[ Chuckle ]
- You okay?
- I've been worse.
So what now, huh?
Think you got it in you to kill me?
Really don't think I have to.
Sweetie, your epidermis is showing.
[ Reciting Latin ]
I think I can feel it working.
- Oh, damn.
- I think the senior partners would like a word.
You don't think they're angry, do you?
[ Weak Chuckle ]
It's really been a pleasure.
Let's never keep in touch.
It's a new game, Eve.
If I were you, I'd start thinkin' strategy.
- And here I am thinking revenge.
- And what do you imagine
the senior partners are thinking?
Well, uh, I'm thinkin' Sea Breeze, compadres.
I gave up a lot of blood for this gig.
And I didn't get any.
I kept begging Eve to run, but--
Well, I've been prancin' around
thinkin' I had a destiny.
- I'd love to drown my embarrassment
in a few pints.
- We should all go get a drink.
We haven't done that in... ever.
- I'm in. Cat and Fiddle?
- Yeah. Unless, of course, you're busy packing.
Uh, a drink sounds good.
- I'll go get my coat.
- [ Bell Dings ]
Uh, you guys go ahead.
We'll catch up.
Oh, and, uh, Wesley?
You still work the best mojo in town.
I bleed from the neck, he gets the props.
[ Chuckles ]
- [ Sighs ]
- So...
you feel good?
Yeah. I do.
I just-- I kinda feel bad about it.
My God.
You are a piece of work.
[ Laughs ]
I just-- I just don't feel like I deserve--
I mean,
all I did was beat up a tiny Texan.
- It's not like I helped anyone.
- Sure you did.
- Who?
- Boy, I really do fall for dumb ones.
You know how you're always trying to save,
oh, every single person in the world?
Did it ever occur to you
you are one of them?
No, it-- it never did.
Well, you made the list, gorgeous,
and you needed some help.
And you were the one
that helped me.
I did my part.
[ Chuckles ]
You know, Lindsey wasted a lot of energy
trying to make me doubt myself.
I know it's not even close to over.
I do feel like I can do this.
Wolfram and Hart, whatever's coming,
I feel like we can beat it.
- I know.
- You do?
I always did.
I-- I just needed you
to know it too.
- So all that stuff about the deals with the devil--
- Is God's honest truth.
But you're bigger than that.
You'll win this in the end.
I, uh,just wish
I could be there to see it.
[ Laughs ]
- [ Sighs ]
- What do you mean? You're not--
I can't stay.
This isn't me anymore.
You can say good-bye
to the gang for me.
Explain everything...
once you understand.
That's gonna be never.
I-- I need you here.
Don't make this hard, Angel.
I'm just on a different road...
and this is my off-ramp.
The Powers That Be owed me one,
and I didn't waste it.
I got my guy back on track.
- Cordy, there's just, uh--
- We take what we can get, champ,
and we do our best with it.
[ Tearfully ]
I'll be seeing you.
Oh, what the hell.
One for the road?
- [ Sighs ]
- [ Phone Rings ]
- [ Ringing ]
- You know, um, I--
[ Whispers ]
I don't need to get that.
[ Sighs ]
That... you have to get.
- [ Ringing ]
- [ Sniffles ]
[ Exhales Deeply ]
Oh, and you're welcome.
Hello?
Yes, I know, she's--
But that's impossible.
She's standin' right--
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Uh, so when did she die?
Did she, uh--
She never did wake up.
I see.
Thank you.
Grr! Arrgh!