Previously on "dexter"...
two treasure hunters made
a ghastly discovery today
When they stumbled
on what appears to be
An underwater graveyard in a
crevice off the coast of miami.
do you know
what that means?
Means there might be
a new mass murderer out there,
Way worse than
the ice-Truck killer.
The "bay harbor butcher"?
That's what the press is calling
whoever dumped bodies offshore.
The last thing miami needs
is another serial killer.
13 and counting.
They're so swamped up there,
They had to bring in
outside talent.
frank lundy?
The green river killer,
the d. C. Sniper -
If the case was impossible,
he broke it.
so, this is the man who
stands between me and death row.
With your help, we'll find
whoever did this awful thing.
So, let's get a jump-Start
on the bay harbor butcher.
With doakes tailing me,
My life's been all jekyll
and no hyde.
Paul kept insisting to me
That you knocked him
over the head,
Dragged him to his motel,
and shot him up with drugs.
I hit paul to protect you
and the kids.
Look, if there is anything left
between us,
You will answer me
this one question
And you will tell me
the truth.
Are you an addict?
Yes, i have an addiction.
My name is caroline.
I'm an addict.
hi, caroline.
um, i started taking pain pills
After my back surgery.
I don't need them
for the pain anymore.
Now i...
now i just need them.
And i need duct tape -
Three or four rolls.
Running low
on heavy-Duty trash bags.
When's the last time
i sharpened my knives?
And i lost my license.
Tears now?
It's very hard
to concentrate in here.
How am i supposed
to get any work done?
My husband says he's gonna leave
me if i don't stay sober.
But i have to do this
for myself.
"No self-Control, lost
everything, trying to stop. "
Same whiny story
over and over for...
10 minutes -
Feels like 10 hours.
...taking lortabs
and darvocet and percocet
And anything
i could get my hands on.
And even now...
i'd kill for a vicodin.
Lightweight.
First i thought, "narcotics
anonymous," i don't belong here.
You guys are real addicts.
so, how was the meeting?
Tell me everything.
It was, uh, interesting,
Hearing the same story
over and over again.
Knowing you're not alone. Exactly.
Did you get fortune cookies?
Only the ones
with the good fortunes.
So, did you share
or just listen?
I just wanted to take it all in
my first time out.
Think they forgot...
ah, here they are.
Spring rolls.
And what about a sponsor?
Did you find one?
I didn't want to rush
into anything.
It's an important
relationship.
Absolutely.
Okay, so, let's see
your newcomer's chip.
Newcomer's chip.
Yeah...
you did stay until the end,
didn't you?
Of course i did.
Right to the end.
You're a terrible liar.
I know too much
about 12-Step programs
To be easily conned,
dexter.
I didn't stay till the end end,
if that's what you mean.
I had some important errands
to run.
Mmm.
Important?
What? Am i important?
Are the kids?
Yeah.
Yes, of course.
Well, you're just gonna have
to figure out how important,
Because if you don't work
the program -
And i mean really work it -
I just...
i can't go through this
again.
All right, kids.
Dinner.
How important are they?
I'm sure someone with a heart
could answer that question.
Tomorrow.
I'll go tomorrow.
I'll stay.
Okay.
Okay?
Hold the elevator!
Thanks.
Nice dodge last night, flooring
it through that yellow light.
Oh...
were you behind me?
See you tonight.
we will get to all of you.
Okay, take their names
And keep them out of the bullpen
till we figure this out.
sue macmillan.
She disappeared four years ago.
Who are they?
every family member
Of every missing person
for the last decade.
Including some sad, lonely,
and presumably single women,
Courtesy
of lieutenant pascal.
It's not her fault.
That reporter's an asshole.
Sergeant?
Yeah, hold the rest of them
downstairs.
We're out of room here.
You seen pascal?
You know, pascal is just caught
in a cycle of reaction.
She's not co-Creating
her own reality.
You know those words don't
actually mean anything, right?
Look around you, bro.
She's manifesting negativity.
it's on again.
Excuse me, lieutenant?
No comment.
We have reports there
were dozens of bodies found
In that
underwater grave site.
Not dozens.
The boss' sweater melons
look bigger on tv.
The operative word is "boss. "
Show some respect.
I thought i was.
One dozen? Two dozen? 18 or so.
Have the families
been notified?
We're still trying
to identify them.
If viewers have information,
they should contact you?
Yes. Fine.
So, there you have it.
Police are seeking any leads
that can help them identify
The 18 faceless victims
of the bay harbor butcher.
If you have any information,
please contact...
pascal
is definitely off her game.
Word is, her fianc?Is catching
some strange on the sly.
That'd do it.
The shit stops here.
Give it to me.
most of these people
won't find answers here.
Chances are good
Their loved ones
weren't among my chosen few.
may i have
your attention, please?
First of all,
i want to tell you
What a great job you've all been
doing on this horrific case.
And with the help of
the best man hunter in the fbi,
We should have answers soon.
In the meantime,
the daily work of this precinct
Must continue
to serve the public,
So we'll be dividing up
our resources.
Agent lundy has requested
the following officers
For his joint task force.
Officer cook...
lundy made me Lfi.
Lfi?
Lead forensics investigator.
Sorry you got boned,
but, hey, no blood spatter.
Sucks to be me.
Actually, it keeps me
off lundy's radar.
Sergeant lee.
Detective ramos...
...officer panko...
detective batista...
yes!
I saw this happening.
...and officer debra morgan.
Those called will report
directly to special agent lundy.
And let's not forget
this is on all of us, folks.
Let's keep our eyes
and our ears open.
The ice-Truck killer was
an amateur compared to this guy.
i'd also appreciate it
If your lieutenant
would consult with me
Before speaking
to the press.
I'll rip her a new one...
if i can find her.
Prints, fiber,
trace evidence -
No, they won't find anything.
I followed
all of harry's
Painstaking
preventative measures.
He knew that nothing
stays buried forever.
His code will protect me.
Still, i wish my own sister
weren't hunting me -
Makes for
an awkward family dynamic.
so, i'm a fed.
My suit proves it.
The other suits here are feds.
But suit or...
ugly hawaiian shirt -
No offense -
We're a team.
And our first play
is i. D.Ing those bodies.
Once we know who they are,
We'll fill in every detail
of their lives,
From their huevos ranchos
to their crèMe brûLéE.
And, uh,
get used to food references
'Cause, well, i like food.
Vince masuka and his team
Are gathering dna, prints,
and dental records.
The rest of us are going to cull through
cold cases and missing-Persons files.
Also, i want that crowd
out there interviewed -
Though most of them
will be a waste of time.
Negative thinking.
You four, move them out
as quickly as you can,
But be thorough.
If we get even one hit,
it'll be worth it.
Everyone else, work the files.
Remember,
i. D.S will lead to a pattern,
Which will lead to our man.
When the manhunt is on,
the hunted go shopping.
Not for a new car -
For my next project.
I won't act on it... yet.
I'm still laying low.
Harry would insist on that.
Just getting the research
out of the way.
Someone talked his way
into the homes of two women
And didn't leave
till they were dead.
Ann cohen and,
a month before her, lynn hall.
A certain car dealership ran
credit checks on both women.
Both bought cars elsewhere,
So nobody
thought about it twice.
But who requested
those credit checks?
Roger hicks.
All i need
is some dna proof -
Cup of coffee
should do the trick.
How many kids you got?
Enough.
I hear you.
When my two came along,
it was bye-Bye, convertible.
Of course...
they're worth it.
Must take after their mom.
That they do.
Thank god.
I tell you,
i miss my convertible,
But, uh, truth -
My minivan's
got a much nicer ride.
So you own one.
Oh, the same one
you're looking at.
I mean, i know -
Whipped, right?
But, uh, my kids
love the twin dvds.
They're just crazy about
spongebob, you know what i mean?
Actually, i do.
My wife loves the nav system
and all the safety features.
And when they're happy...
you're happy.
That's right.
Except the kids don't exist,
neither does the wife.
And he owns a beemer,
not a minivan.
Still, he's seamless.
Impressive.
It's not flashy, but...
what did flash ever get me?
It got me pulled over,
that's what.
I'm definitely
not into flash.
You got to sit
in the captain's chair, though.
It's like a 747, man.
Manuel, hold up.
Thank you, sir.
So, uh...
we should take it out.
Check out the ride.
I'm just doing research.
Okay, you don't want
a big sales pitch.
I get that.
Let me at least
pull the specs for you.
Because, truthfully,
We have a hard time
keeping these on the lot.
You might want to grab
the test-Drive
While it's still here.
I think i have
all the information i need
To make a decision.
Yeah?
Well, then,
you've seen the, uh,
The stow 'n go
seating system, right?
I have had
everything in here
From a soccer team
to a freakin' deer carcass.
It was an accident,
of course.
But, uh, i sure was glad
for the ample cargo space,
Not to mention
the tinted windows.
I can see
how that might come in handy.
I'll just grab the keys.
I go to stalk a killer
and i end up with a new car?
How'd that happen?
New car?
Yeah.
You get married?
Not that i know of.
Huh.
So what's with
the mommy mobile?
I'm, uh...
not sure.
Synthetic.
Even roger's hair is a lie.
I could learn a thing or two
from this guy.
Who's your daddy?
Uh... harry morgan.
Dude, the lead
forensics investigator
Of the joint task force -
That's who.
Oh, okay.
So, you want in
on this bitch or not?
What bitch?
The only bitch in town, baby.
The bay harbor butcher.
I got you
temporarily assigned.
Vince, you didn't
have to do that.
Nothing sexy, of course,
Just some bone-Marrow
collection for dna i. D.S.
But it'll get you
in the tent.
And you got to see
the tent.
Amazing.
Say it.
You're my daddy.
It sounds weird
when you say it.
I haven't been much use
since he disappeared.
I know i'm supposed to
move on,
But...
here's the picture of him.
He looks...
...nice.
Not according to my mother...
or the police.
He was in and out of jail,
But my heart raced
whenever i saw him.
I brought his toothbrush.
They say
you can get dna off it.
You can find him
with this, right?
Special agent lundy?
Look, thanks for choosing me
for the task force and all,
But i'd appreciate
you finding someone else.
You want off?
Just as soon as
you can replace me, sir.
This is a chance to solve
a pretty important case.
Most people get into this
line of work to do just that.
Well, i've got
cases of my own backing up,
And the precinct's shorthanded
with all this shit.
So, if you don't mind...
i'll see what i can do.
In the meantime, if you could
continue the interviews...
yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Thank you.
Most of 'em have
been underwater for years.
But some, it's awesome,
you can't even tell.
The temperature
on the ocean floor
And the airtight bags
kept them intact.
I mean, a little gelatinous
residue, sure. But...
i'd rather remember my
old playmates as they were -
Neat, clean little packages.
You know, vince, i appreciate
you doing me this favor but -
Actually, you're
doing me the favor.
I need your help, buddy.
The pressure's
fucking ridonkulous.
Glad to be of service.
Field morgue
for the overflow,
But it's
state-Of-The-Art.
Fucking fbi, eh?
A good percentage
are just bones.
Must have fed the fish
when the bags tore.
Humpty fucking dumpty,
right?
Exactly.
They weren't
meant to be put together again.
They were meant to remain
in the silent shadows,
Keeping their secrets.
Now they're
exposed to the glare,
Reflecting my darkness like
some grotesque carnival mirror.
Harry was right -
Nothing stays buried.
Perhaps not even me.
Looking for my taurus,
sergeant?
Keep looking.
You don't need to know
where i'm going tonight.
And genius me,
Not only do i leave
my works in my girlfriend's car,
But also all the dead fish
from the fishing trip, right?
Then i collapse
in her parents' house,
Scare her kids,
And get myself fired,
'cause guess what -
We work together.
aw.
Yeah.
So, now, well,
I'm 20-Days sober...
again...
hoping to make it to 21.
Thanks, gordon.
This meeting recognizes
lengths of sobriety with chips.
So, if there's anyone who
would like a newcomer's chip...
you've got three minutes
to share if you want it.
Oh, really?
Go ahead, man.
You among friends.
Well, i, uh...
what's your name?
Bob.
hi, bob.
Hi.
And i'm, um...
an addict.
I use... heroin -
Shoot it.
It's affecting my job.
My boss found my works.
He fired my ass.
But i showed him -
I spent every penny
of my final paycheck on junk.
Doctor said i...
...uh...
...i almost died.
Coffee sucks...
as bad
as the doughnuts.
It's better next door.
Come on.
Mmm.
It is good coffee.
Thank you.
So, tell me...
exactly how full of shit
are you?
I'm not full of anything.
It was a nice performance
in there.
Where did you download it from?
Addict. Com?
Look,
i have no reason to lie.
Sure you do.
We all do.
You thought i was lying?
I don't know...
bob.
Well, it is anonymous.
Everyone in that room
Has heard or lived far worse
than anything you've ever done.
I doubt it.
Oh, so you're
super-Junkie.
I don't mean to imply
That what you've been through
hasn't been difficult.
But there's no way
That i could know what
you've experienced, right?
I couldn't
possibly feel that need.
Like a thousand hiding voices
whispering,
"This is who you are. "
And you fight the pressure,
The growing need
rising like a wave,
Prickling and teasing
and prodding to be fed.
But the whispering
gets louder
Until it's screaming, "now!"
And it's the only voice
you hear...
the only voice
you want to hear.
And you belong to it,
To this...
shadow self.
dark passenger.
Yes.
The dark passenger.
No.
I'm sorry,
but i need to go.
Thanks for the coffee.
She knows.
She recognizes demons...
dark passengers.
Maybe the others can, too.
This program is too risky,
especially now.
Rita will have to understand.
Hey.
You just missed story time.
I was at a meeting.
Thank you.
It made me realize
something important.
Oh, really?
What's that?
Those meetings are
not a good place for me.
I know how this sounds,
but i can do this on my own.
Dexter, you need a program.
I've read studies -
People are 10 times as likely
To change on their own
As they are with the help
of doctors or programs.
So you're quoting studies?
Look, i lived this.
I watched paul try and fail
with white-Knuckle sobriety.
I'm not paul.
I'm not any of those people.
Going to those meetings
will do more harm than good,
I swear to you.
I'm better off alone.
I pray you change your mind.
What just happened?
Deb?
Thought you were staying
at rita's.
Uh...
taking the night off.
I thought you'd be
on the treadmill.
Taking the night off.
With no money down, guaranteed,
Or we'll make
your first two payments...
a night off is good
to remember what's important.
Two women are dead,
The killer is selling minivans,
And i have an opportunity
to prove it,
Even if i am laying low.
Having a victim
prepped and ready
Will take the edge
off the wait...
i hope.
Hey, hang on
just a second, okay?
What's going on, dex? Hey.
Any problems, the service center
can take care of you,
But they're
around the corner.
Actually,
the minivan's fine.
Well, of course it is.
I never sold a lemon in my life.
I'm just rethinking
the extended warranty.
Great, i'll set you up
with a warranty writer, then.
And i'm thinking roof rack
and premium sound system.
Going all out.
Yeah.
That's great,
but i'm with a customer.
And so
one of my associates -
I'd rather deal with you.
I'll just wait for you
in your office.
Outstanding.
Dna, dna, come out and play.
Uh-Oh, roger's got you
in the box.
Once you're in the box, you
don't leave without a deal.
Uh-Oh.
Don't worry.
You're safe with roger.
He's the best.
I'm just dropping off
this thank-You note.
Well, i was just leaving.
He sent you across the street,
didn't he?
Across the street?
It's okay, he told me
not to tell anyone either.
Yeah, i don't know
how he makes a living
Sending all of his commissions
to other dealers.
Maybe he has
ulterior motives.
Or maybe he knows
i can't afford his price.
After he ran a credit check?
Trw doesn't lie.
So, you're single?
Y- Yeah.
Makes it tougher to afford
Those big-Ticket items,
like cars and houses.
You rent an apartment?
A house. I hate sharing walls.
You can hear everything.
Tell me about it.
No pets, though, right?
Yeah.
Is this a come-On?
'Cause it's a little weird.
It must be
why i'm still single.
Another brunette.
Single, neighbors
at a distance, no guard dog.
The credit check gets roger
all the details he needs.
She's next, and i can't do
anything about it -
Not until this manhunt ends.
Harry would insist on it.
What?
No, i'll take care of it.
I know the card is in his name.
I just want to check
the charges.
Well, the supervisor i spoke
with this morning allowed it.
Yes - No, uh...
yeah, i'll hold.
Yes?
Just a reminder
That the biscayne drive-By
warrant needs your approval.
I'll look at it.
And the homicide
that came in last night
Still needs to be assigned.
Right, thanks.
Look, esmee,
i know that things are rough
With you and your fianc?Right
now, and i'm sorry, really,
But we need to keep clearing
that board out there.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry.
I seem to have had my head
up my ass lately.
It's called "being human. "
Okay, who's up?
Samuels and kent are up.
Put them
on the liquor-Store shooting.
And where
is the biscayne warrant?
Oh, right here.
Simms and hoagie
want s. W.A.T. For entry.
I think it's a good measure,
given the weapons charge.
Excuse me, i'm -
I'm gonna need a minute.
Just...
uh...
just gonna need a minute.
Esmee?
Oh.
Please, maria.
I'll handle it.
You're not taking my calls,
And now you're checking
my credit-Card charges, esmee?
Roger's dna matches the semen
found at both crime scenes.
Irrefutable.
If i do nothing,
another woman dies.
Is that my long-Dormant
conscience talking
Or the dark passenger
whispering?
Hi, it's me.
Hi, dexter.
Kids home from school yet?
Colleen's
bringing them home now.
I'm a... little confused.
I'm sorry you're confused.
I mean, it's pizza night.
Should i pick up the usual?
Did you go back?
To a meeting -
Thinking about it.
The kids and i
will order in, then.
Uh, okay.
So...
...is this it?
That's up to you, dexter.
I want to know,
Where is she,
mi teresita.
She's so young -
7 year old.
You help me.
I know you find her.
We'll do what we can.
Por favor!
Don't cry.
Pero yo rec?
Y dios me mand?A ti.
No spanish. No habla.
T?La encontraráS.
Only english.
Angel?
Just tell her
we'll call her.
Me encontrar?/I>
a mi teresita, ¿Verdad?
Necesito saber dóNde est?/I>
y lo que le ha pasado.
She thinks you can find
the daughter.
There are no kids
down there.
Tell her i can't help her.
She -
I- I can't help you.
Por favor!
Morgan?
Morgan!
It's been 24 hours
since i asked to be replaced.
Has it?
What's taking so long?
Every cop on the damn force
wants in on this case.
Just take your pick.
I've been wondering
about that, actually.
Everyone wants on,
but you want off.
I told you, i have cases.
I don't think so.
You don't think so.
Jesus, i just don't want to be
on your task force, all right?
Why?
Because i'm the last person in
the world that should be on it.
You want me
to find a serial killer?
I was engaged to one,
for christ's sake.
What kind of cop -
What kind of -
That's why i chose you,
you know -
Because of what
you went through.
You survived.
I don't know how.
I can't begin to imagine
the strength it took -
Continues to take.
More than that,
you got a firsthand look
Into the mind and heart
of a killer,
And you're still here.
If you can accept that -
Really accept it -
You could use it.
Mix that with some
of your strength, and...
you could catch someone
even worse
Than the ice-Truck killer.
But you have to stop running.
Finish today's interviews.
Then, if you still want out,
you got it.
Lead fucking investigator.
Translation -
Everyone's bitch.
I do have a life, you know.
You do?
Just give me
your bone-Marrow dna results.
No matches.
Big surprise.
Do me a favor on your way out,
will you?
Drop these dental x-Rays
at the field morgue for me?
Tech should still be there.
Fucking bay harbor butcher
Is butchering
my online social life.
Sorry.
Next.
i figured you'd still be here.
You were a pain in the ass
but always a damn hard worker.
And, of course, you knew
how to handle the press.
Come here a minute.
The public needs to believe
that we can protect them,
Or all hell breaks loose,
so i need all my people
Operating at their
very highest levels.
I agree.
Should i be worried
about pascal?
Pascal?
Why?
You can cut the crap, maria.
I know she's been awol
on personal matters.
The press fuckup is huge,
And now i'm beginning to hear
rumors about erratic behavior.
And you're asking me
because...
because you've done the job.
So if she's out,
that means you're back in.
That makes you her harshest
critic, and i want it straight.
So...
take your shot, maria.
Hmm.
You know what
"erratic" means?
It's code for "non-Male,"
And it's the same bullshit
sexism i put up with
When i was in charge.
I won't dignify rumors, captain.
Pascal's fine.
Minivan's that way.
Field morgue's this way.
I'll wait.
You should take the night off,
sergeant.
On pizza night?
No way.
What does that girlfriend
of yours see
In a freak show like you
anyway?
You have to ask her.
Maybe i will.
What exactly is it
you think i've done?
I know you're connected
to the ice-Truck killer.
Could you be more vague?
I know you're too careful.
You keep
your assets in cash.
You don't belong to any
organizations or alumni groups.
You were top of your class
in med school,
But you traded it
for fucking blood spatter.
I know you studied martial arts
in college,
But i don't know what a lab geek
needs with advanced jujitsu.
Do you know
what an easy credit is?
I know
you're a good liar, too.
Not good enough.
sergeant doakes
thinks he knows my secrets,
But he only needs to look
at this, my body of work,
To know the real me.
Suit up
if you're gonna touch them.
Oh.
No, i'm just, uh...
dropping off some x-Rays.
I'm dexter morgan.
I know who you are.
Right.
Looks like the lab tech's
gone home for the night,
So i'll just...
you hoping
they'll talk to you?
The ones with heads,
anyway.
They always speak...
eventually.
Just got to ask
the right question.
Which is?
"Why were they chosen?"
You looking for a pattern?
One doesn't kill
this many people
In this careful, methodical way
without a reason -
Some...
twisted set of principles.
Yeah, they would have to be
twisted, wouldn't they?
The worst killers in history
are usually the ones
Who think their murders
were somehow... just -
Even deserved.
Leaders have slaughtered
whole populations
For the same warped reason.
But there's never
any justification for killing.
No.
Well, one, of course.
To save an innocent life.
How many more bodies
would there be
Had i not stopped
those killers?
I didn't do it to save lives...
but save lives i did.
Motivation aside,
I think harry and lundy
would agree on this one.
roger the artful dodger.
Jesus!
You scared me, bro.
We have
some unfinished business.
Oh, yeah, right,
the warranty and stuff.
Listen, uh...
i can't write you up right now.
I got the wife
waiting for me.
You're not married.
Ex-Wife.
I got to take the kids.
You don't have kids.
Stepkids - They're hers.
Nope.
Okay, how about this one?
I don't give a shit.
Neither do i.
You were right
about the ample cargo space.
Where am i?
Looks different
under plastic,
But you spent
an evening here...
with ann cohen.
You took her last breath
from her right over there.
You remember?
No.
You're - You're wrong.
I wouldn't.
You would and you did and
you were about to do it again.
That's why we're here.
No, this is crazy.
You got the wrong guy.
I -
I sell cars, for god's sake.
I've never hurt anyone in my
life - Definitely not a woman.
Why can't i do that?
Do what?
Lie like that.
I mean, i thought i was good,
but you, it's... mwah.
I don't lie.
Okay, that one was weak.
Okay, look, any car on the lot,
it's yours.
T- Bird, town car, you name it -
Yours free.
I'll call it in right now.
Lot's closed.
I'll have them open it up.
I'm the manager.
The manager's name
is rick buxton.
Yeah, but i've been there
longer than he has.
You've been there three months. At the other lot.
It's like watching someone
ski moguls.
You just hop
from one lie to the next -
No shame, no embarrassment.
You just don't give a shit.
That's the key, right?
Not to care
about anyone or anything.
I care.
I care a lot.
No, it was a compliment.
I don't care, either.
Yes, you do.
Like about your wife.
Not married.
Girlfriend, then.
I saw it the minute
you walked on the lot.
What did you see?
Tell me.
Look, most guys your age,
they beeline...
right for the horsepower -
You know,
something flashy, sexy.
But you -
You're there all alone,
no one there to nag you,
And you don't even glance
at the coupes.
The only thing you look at
is the minivan,
Like you can see her
in the passenger's seat
And the kids in the back.
Leave the kids out.
See?
You're lying to yourself
if you think you don't care.
She's just a companion,
really.
Started that way,
anyway.
Someone who...
looked good, normal.
They worm their way in.
Yeah, they do.
Then they shut you out.
That's what this is about -
That she shut you out?
Oh.
Man, okay, i get it.
I- I - I've been there.
But you can't let her
get to you like this,
'Cause - 'Cause
they're all the same -
Fucking bitches.
You do everything for them,
and then they fuck you.
She's not worth it,
all right?
You're better off
without that cunt.
Don't...
...talk that way
about my girlfriend.
i'm dexter,
and i'm not sure what i am.
hi, dexter.
I just know
there's something dark in me...
and i hide it.
I certainly
don't talk about it...
but it's there...
always.
This dark passenger.
And when he's driving,
i feel...
alive...
half sick with the thrill
of complete wrongness.
I don't fight him.
I don't want to.
He's all i've got.
Nothing else could love me,
Not even...
...especially not me.
Or is that just a lie
the dark passenger tells me?
Because lately there are
these moments when i feel...
...connected
to something else - Someone.
It's like...
the mask is slipping...
...and things...
...people...
who never mattered before
are suddenly starting to matter.
It scares the hell out of me.
Hello...
dexter.
that's all the time
we have for sharing.
Would someone lead us
in the serenity prayer?
Lila.
I knew there
was something wrong with you.
The secrets,
the sneaking around -
Now it all makes sense.
god grant me
serenity to accept...
a lot of cops
have been where you are.
The booze, the drugs...
makes the job go down easier.
Stay clean and stay out of
my way, we won't have a problem.
Oh, and you owe me a new
michelin, you motherfucker.
I have all your forms,
So we'll do what we can
to bring your dad home.
I'm sorry.
You don't understand.
I don't want him home.
Just tell me he's dead.
We need to know he's gone.
Right, you want closure.
I want peace.
He made our lives
a living hell.
When he'd go to prison,
it was a blessing, but, uh...
you kept letting him out.
I need to tell
my mother, my sister
That they're safe
and that he's rotting in hell.
Call me
when you can tell me that.
Lundy, wait.
Uh...
i think - I mean,
it could be a coincidence -
But there are two of them.
Two...
missing people with records -
Prison records.
Interesting.
And who typically has
a prison record?
I don't know.
Bad guys?
Bad guys.
Do you think
it could be a -
A pattern?
Maybe.
We'll run all the victims' dna
against the criminal database.
D.C. Lab is still open.
Come on.
Let's get to work.
Dexter, what?
You were right.
I'm sorry to wake you up,
But i had to let you know
that you were right.
About what?
The program.
It's...
it's good.
It's really good.
I...
am always so in my head.
But this - It was...
good.
In fact,
it's already helped me a lot.
Thank you.
Oh.
Mmm.
Oh, i do love this car.
Yeah, i thought you might.
So, i will pick you up
in an hour.
We'll go someplace nice
for lunch.
Oh, there's my sponsor.
Really? Where?
The guy in the blue shirt?
No, next to him - Lila.
Huh.
Bye.
I'm back.