±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
êèñªåð¹ù µú¶þ¼¾µú7¼¯
-=ææàãðü×öä»×é=-
·­òë£º¸öèëid
ð£¶ô£º¸öèëid
ê±¼äöá£º¾æäò·¹´ü ²ý¸ùã»å®
â¼öæ£º¸öèëid
qianqing
you??
do u ???
???
maybe ???
you???
are you ???
???
dex??
dexter ???
those ??
???
it's
how much
you ???
i've been??
i know??
he could??
he broke??
he's probably gonna start
tailing me again.
sergeant doakes tailed you?
i followed him
to an n.a. meeting.
that asshole
lied about that, too.
you're obsessed.
i'm not.
and i need you to see it!
dinner was fantastic,
rita. wow.
i kind of like her.
lila: dex,
just calling to check in.
imagine rita's face
if i told her
that you and i had spent
the night together in a hotel.
it's over, dexter.
i guess i just hope with lundy
it will be different.
why?
i respect him.
you love him.
no. he's like my dad.
you want to tell me
what's going on?
you're the one who said i'm
supposed to feel my feelings!
well, now i'm telling you
to get them under control!
which step was that?
that night, forest grew
lila:
use the entire canvas.
start from the top.
work your way down.
light, feathery strokes.
perfect!
stunning.
try longer strokes now.
perfect.
you really know what you want,
don't you?
i hope you don't mind.
some men do.
no.
i've always found
instruction manuals...
quite useful.
okay, your turn.
what do you want?
i think that was it.
hmm, come on.
you must have
some dark fantasies...
...unfulfilled urges.
i'm pretty good
at acting on those.
really?
then fuck me like that.
your light's burned out.
it's the wiring.
i've been asking my landlord
to fix it for weeks.
well, now i can see better.
that's where
my landlord lives.
now he'll have to fix it.
see you later.
got to admire lila for taking
things into her own hands.
that includes me.
ohh. mom. [ sighs ]
come on, let's go!
no more moping.
i'm not moping.
i'm sleeping.
oversleeping --
third time this week.
the only way you're gonna
get over dexter
is if you take charge
of your day.
come on. you're not
in high school anymore.
go scrub your face,
and i'll heat up some oatmeal.
didn't hear you
come in last night.
well, it was late.
i was quiet.
yeah,
you're good at quiet.
guess you kind of have to be
with me crashing here
and rita's mom over there.
you and rita
fuck quiet, too?
and she's off,
right out of the gate.
because me --
i wake the goddamn dead.
it's a problem.
oh, i know,
only too well.
scary, right?
sometimes i disturb myself.
so [chuckles] what kind
of noises does rita make?
could we not talk
about sex...
or rita?
why?
'cause we broke up...
for real.
it's over.
you break up,
you get back together --
that's just what goes on.
i mean,
you and rita are forever.
just say you're sorry
and send some fucking flowers.
you're not hearing me.
look,
when all this blows over,
i'll spend a few days
at gabriel's, and...
you can screw rita
as loud as you want.
big news, dex.
whoa! feel like i got caught
in a wave.
the miami tribune received
a 32-page manifesto in the mail.
it's looking good
for the bay harbor butcher.
well, i've heard
that one before.
look, this may be legit.
the manifesto includes the names
of three victims
we never released
to the press.
oh, that is big news.
i'm heading over to the tribune
now for special agent lundy.
he put me in charge
of the team.
go, angel.
yeah, i'm psyched.
yeah, me too.
i'm about to be published.
i sent that manifesto
to the tribune.
guess i've been taking
some cues from lila lately,
and not just in bed.
i'm tired of reacting
to the moves of agent lundy
and his super posse.
time to control their actions
for a change.
betsy court, 16.
blunt-force beating.
it looks like
she was sunning herself
and never saw it coming.
who called in the body?
craig wilson, the stepfather.
he's right over there.
wilson told
the reporting officer
that he came home for lunch
and found her that way.
um, you and dexter
resolve your issues?
as far as i'm concerned.
why? the bitch come crying
to you again?
no.
there's blood work
to be done here,
and if you can't
control yourself,
i need to call in
another detective.
i won't say anything to hurt
the little girl's feelings.
god damn it, james,
i'm not joking.
do i look like
i'm laughing?
no. you don't. i wish you would.
you used to.
bullshit.
i never laughed.
[ scoffs ] yeah, you know what?
you're probably right.
now, look, i'm not gonna try
to scare you anymore.
the reality is,
you're out of free passes.
now, i already stopped dexter
from filing a complaint
against you once.
i never asked you to do that, maria.
well, i did it,
out of my own concern
over your obsessive behavior.
now i'm on the line,
so if you bully dexter
in any way --
if you even
look at him wrong,
i will not be responsible
for the fallout.
you got it?
i got it.
you're backing
the fucking freaktard.
james.
where you been, dexter?
you don't bring me
doughnuts.
you don't sing me love songs.
how are you, camilla?
i've been better.
well,
that doesn't sound good.
sergeant doakes dropped by
my file room yesterday.
he requested the case files
for the 1973
shipping-yard murders.
i gave him the same line
i gave you
when you came
sniffing around,
said all that old stuff
was boxed up
in the basement
of city hall.
that made him real angry.
he scared me, dexter.
that's not right.
he shouldn't do that.
look, dex, i always assumed
that your father asked me
to destroy those files
to protect you.
now i'm not sure
what's going on.
camilla...
now,
i don't want to know.
i just don't want
to get fired.
i'm retiring next year.
did i tell you?
i've been looking forward
to staying home with gene.
you won't lose your retirement.
i won't let that happen.
i can stall sergeant doakes
for a few days,
but eventually,
he'll figure out
that that case file's missing,
just like you did.
and he'll track it back to me,
you know, just like you did.
i'll take care of this.
you have my word.
so much for threatening doakes.
he won't back off till
he exposes the twisted branches
of my family tree,
from my father's indiscretions
to my murderous brother
to the root of all evil -- me.
hey.
why aren't you
at the tribune?
what for?
our guy's not gonna leave
dna evidence on a document.
oh, but the thrill
of the hunt.
i've had
that particular thrill.
i'll leave it
to younger men.
besides, it's easier for me
to do my part from here.
yeah?
what part is that?
operating on favors,
political leanings, posturing.
i've been trying to find
the right music.
right.
so, i'm off duty today,
but here are those
marina reports.
and after my workout,
i'll swing by and pick up a copy
of the manifesto.
look at that board.
these kills are precise,
but there's also a fluidity,
even some improvisation.
if i could just find
the music...
want to borrow my ipod?
got any chopin?
no.
fresh out of chopin.
shit.
chopin's perfect.
did you just swear?
[ chuckles ]
what can i say?
you're rubbing off
on me, morgan.
but chopin is perfect.
so this is how you do
what you do.
the truth speaks to me
from a peaceful place.
i got to set the stage
to hear it.
you know what i mean?
no.
i thrive on chaos.
but this is good, too.
i didn't kill her.
i was just trying
to stop the blood.
no forceful impact spatter --
he's telling the truth.
i can tell.
palms up, please.
when i found betsy,
she was still breathing.
i wanted to help her.
you believe me, right?
i'm just the lab guy,
mr. wilson. sorry.
arms down
at your sides, please.
blood misting. huh.
i need to collect his shirt
for evidence.
morgan!
the girl's mother
was at work,
but she isn't really defending
her husband.
wilson and his stepdaughter
fought all the time.
the neighbors heard him yelling
at her this morning.
then he comes home for lunch --
motive and opportunity.
what'd the blood say?
well, the blood on his hands
could have come
from trying to help her,
like he claims.
but i did detect, uh, blood mist
on his shirt.
a blood mist --
the kind that comes from beating
on a teenage girl?
no.
yes.
you're absolutely sure?
it's too fine
for a bludgeoning.
the mist is from
a bludgeoning.
medium-velocity impact
spatters -- no doubt about it.
okay, morgan.
just make sure you get me
your blood report
as soon as possible.
this is my chance
to make doakes go away
without spilling a single drop
of his blood.
of course, i have to sell
an innocent man down the river.
sorry, mr. wilson, but i won't
let you float too far.
i was just thinking
about you.
hmm.
i like the sound of that.
yeah, i had to do a little
creative problem-solving
at someone else's expense.
bravo.
yeah,
i figured you'd like that.
what's up?
well, you know
that art installation
that i've been working on?
the cannibals.
they're not cannibals.
how barbaric!
their eating is symbolic
of the way we consume others
to feed our needs.
that's what i meant.
well, it sold.
i-i didn't even create it
to sell, but one of my buyers
fell in love with it,
and i named an outrageous price,
and she paid me a deposit
on the spot.
so...
you in the mood
to celebrate?
definitely.
i'm afraid we just can't
seat you tonight
without a reservation.
as you can see, we are
completely at capacity.
oh, well --
no, i'm sorry.
you have to help us.
i made this reservation
two months ago.
this is our
10-year anniversary.
this is the place where dexter
proposed to me --
on the patio,
in front of the fountain.
he told me to make a wish,
and when i looked down,
there was my diamond ring,
sparkling under the water.
that is so romantic.
dexter:
in case you're wondering,
there's nothing sparkling
under that water tonight.
[ chuckles ] oh, i'm sure
you'll dazzle me somehow.
you're a creative problem-solver
now, right?
a changed man,
or at least "changing."
i suppose.
there's no supposing
about it, dexter.
you've taken control
of your addiction
in a way
that few people do.
it's been about a week
since we've even discussed
your recovery.
i think you're right.
and you haven't felt the need
to use?
incredibly, no.
i feel...
you know, like i'm finally
in control of things again.
we call that warm fuzzy feeling
the pink cloud.
it's when an addict experiences
acceptance for the first time.
you're saying
it won't last?
i'm saying that you have
to work it -- that's all.
but i know that you will,
because i believe that
we've found a true substitute
for your addiction.
what's that?
life.
you're making us all
look bad.
i'm the manager
of il bistro vino.
happy anniversary --
on the house.
thank you.
[ chuckles ]
oh, did you hear that,
darling?
oh, i heard it,
darling.
enjoy your evening.
thank you.
happy anniversary,
my love.
aren't we in recovery?
oh, this?
it's just bubbles.
we're not gonna shoot it up,
are we?
you really have a way.
you know that?
a way of what?
of whatever the hell
you want.
well, here's to 10 more
glorious years
of whatever the hell i want.
hi, i'm cody,
and i researched saudi arabia
for my cultural report.
gail:
that's good, sweetie.
now, look at me
when you talk, okay?
and try and stand up
straight.
my board is covered in sand
because saudi arabia
is one big desert.
one great big desert.
it only rains in a tiny corner
of the country,
so they save rainwater --
okay, now, try and keep
your fingers off your face.
you don't want people to think
you're picking your nose.
you mean like this?
cody, you need
to take this seriously.
dexter said it should be fun.
dexter does drugs.
he's wrong.
i finished my homework.
for the week?
hey, guys. i'm home.
mom!
sorry i'm so late.
i'm so happy to see you!
mom!
oh, wow!
what a greeting.
okay, why don't you guys
go get ready for bed?
really, mom?
i just got home.
they need their rest.
i will be in in just a minute
to check on you.
those two are making
great progress.
progress -- towards what?
their full potential!
mom, i know you're really good
at these things,
but now that you're here,
have you thought about applying
for a teaching job?
no, i'm through
with the schools.
well, i thought teaching
was your life.
and your children are going
to be the beneficiaries
of all that i have
to offer.
our injunction
stopped the tribune
from publishing
the manifesto -- for now.
at the very least,
we'll have time
to get a jump on things
before the news frenzy hits.
so, let's take advantage
of this window.
our goal for the next 48 hours
is to wade through
this shining piece
of social commentary.
i've never seen so many dense
and convoluted ideas in my life,
but we need to search them all
for clues to his identity.
so, first impressions?
i got something.
there are a lot of literary
references in this document.
how do you know?
i like to read books.
what kind of books?
all kinds. who cares?
anyway...i see lots of
references, like this one.
"you can't depend
on your eyes
when your imagination
is out of focus."
[ chuckles ]
he's a trekker!
that shit's straight
from "deep space nine."
what?
mark twain said that.
it's one of
his most famous quotes.
twain was never
on "deep space nine."
he was on "next generation."
he didn't say it
on "star trek."
okay, so what's it from?
"a connecticut yankee
in king arthur's court."
angel, what other literary
quotes are in that manifesto?
this guy -- he's the best boxing
student i have ever had.
after four weeks, he's getting
in shots to my head.
and finally he says,
"i think i'm ready."
i'm like,
"you're ready for what?"
and he says,
"to kick my mom's ass."
i'm like,
"you're learning how to box
because you want to beat up
your mom?"
what the fuck?!
did -- did you hear
what i said?
i was gonna hit the showers.
i'll meet you back here
in 10 minutes.
okay, yeah, 10 minutes.
who the fuck are you?
oh, hi! i'm lila.
oh, pardon my tits.
um, we thought you were crashing
at your boyfriend's tonight.
we -- we who?
dexter and i.
could you just...wait here
a minute?
who's the skank?
deb, did knocking occur
to you?
who is she?
and are you trying to fuck her
or set her on fire?
i didn't do this to you when you
were riding square-jaw guy
with the handcuffs.
that's different. i wasn't cheating on anyone
with gabriel.
how could you do this to rita,
not to mention her kids?
you're like their father.
hey, rita broke up
with me, okay?
you fucked up, dex...
...big-time.
ew. excuse me.
don't worry.
she just needs some time
to adjust -- that's all.
i had officers tear apart
the stepfather's house --
no murder weapon, but he had
to hide it somewhere.
where is wilson now?
interview room 2.
we still have him?
why didn't his lawyer post bond?
well, he tried, but i pulled in
a favor at the courthouse
and got a bail enhancement,
so they had to start
the paperwork all over again.
i'm gonna break
that cocksucker today.
what evidence you say
we got on this guy?
he was dripping
in the victim's blood.
he was home alone with her.
they fought the morning of the murder.
all circumstantial.
yeah, but the blood spatter
on his shirt was a direct result
of a blunt-force
beating, maria.
i'd like to see
the blood report.
you'll get it
as soon as i do.
if you're looking for me,
i'll be questioning the suspect.
they're still playing my tune.
it's like i'm conducting
a final symphony,
"requiem for demonic dexter."
and forming the entire
brass section,
sergeant james doakes.
when i reach the end,
maybe i can lay to rest
the monster
formerly known as dexter.
just hang in there, mr. wilson.
i've asked a psycholinguist
at m.i.t.
to analyze our manifesto.
his computer tabulates
punctuation, misspellings,
and sentence structure
to identify a set of key words,
which he'll use to create
a profile of our killer.
sounds...complicated.
stay on it.
okay, we've been at this
too long.
it's, uh, 1:00.
let's break for lunch.
are you all right?
huh? yeah, i'm fine.
anything you want
to talk about?
no, not really.
well,if you change your mind --
it's my brother.
he was dating this chick --
supersweet,
a little doe-eyed.
but, god, for him,
fucking perfect,
and he just threw her away.
i'm just pissed at dexter,
not to mention my boyfriend,
who did absolutely
nothing wrong.
but every time he opened
his mouth last night,
i wanted to fucking
slap him.
you've been listening
to chopin.
yeah,
i downloaded a chopin --
um, "nocturne number 2
in e flat major."
one of my favorites.
it, uh, can have this effect
on people.
it can stir up some dust.
no shit.
listen, you --
you can heal yourself, sir.
just -- you just need
to talk to me.
get it off you,
otherwise, it's gonna haunt you
for the rest of your life.
why don't you
just listen to me?
i didn't do this.
you -- you can't say it
and make it true.
you have a conscience,
and it's really fucking
with you right now.
i wish it were me.
i wish i were dead.
yeah.
why are we questioning
that guy?
he's a murder suspect.
no, he's not.
he's innocent.
what did you say?
my blood report
backed his story.
mr. wilson found
his stepdaughter dead,
just like i told sergeant doakes
at the crime scene.
you turned in the blood report?
when?
i don't know --
at some point
before i went home last night.
i put it right
on the sergeant's desk,
just like he asked.
the green folder.
yeah,
according to my findings,
the mist on the stepfather's
shirt was exhaled
from the victim when he tried
to revive her.
the autopsy confirmed she had
severe internal bleeding,
due to the bludgeoning.
yeah, but he could have
beaten her first.
that's impossible.
the crime-scene photos show
blood radiating outward
around the victim's body.
that kind of bludgeoning would
have covered the real killer
in blood from head to toe.
thanks.
mr. wilson,
you're free to go.
what the hell? lieutenant,
this man is a killer.
this man has been through enough
for one day.
there's an officer
in the hallway.
he'll see that you get
your personal belongings back
and take you home.
thank you, ma'am.
thank you so much.
what the hell
are you doing?
trying to save your career,
james, if it isn't too late.
did you even check
the blood report?
i didn't get
the blood report.
it's on your desk,
and it exonerates your suspect.
we should be out there
looking for the real killer.
maria, that is not
what he told me at --
that motherfucker.
he's good.
who?
morgan.
he planned this whole thing.
maria,
that psychopath set me up.
dexter again?
you're blaming dexter for this?
do you have any idea
how pathetic that sounds?
this is not about dexter!
this is about the poor judgment
you have been displaying
in this department
for months now!
you want to work out?
no.
i wasn't talking
about the gym.
you're sweet,
but i'm really not in the mood.
so, what do you want to do?
uh...
i think i want to break up.
for real?
yeah.
is that okay?
no.
no, it's not okay.
fuck, what did i do, deb?
nothing.
i swear to god.
you're...smoking hot
and...fun
and...soulful and...
age-appropriate.
and but what?
but...
sometimes the truth speaks
from a peaceful place.
it's taken me a long time
to find that place,
but i think i have,
and it's telling me you're not
the right one for me.
i'm so sorry.
you live in a nice
neighborhood.
yeah, i had no idea.
i'm usually passing by
at 35 miles per hour.
i'm not a real big walker.
everybody walks in london.
of course, they're usually
walking to the pub.
how far are we going?
oh, you're a bit grumpy
tonight.
what's wrong?
come on.
don't close up on me now.
no,
i honestly don't know.
i mean, thanks to you,
things are...
actually looking up.
some people at work
have been...after me.
i think i have 'em
under control.
so, why the grouchiness?
is it because your sister thinks
i'm a trollop?
it's not just...deb.
it's the suddenness
of all of this --
losing rita, the kids.
they've been the only thing
keeping me human
for a long time.
were they keeping you human,
though,
or were they the ones making
you feel like the monster
that you were talking about?
keep going.
your friends and family
have to accept you
for who you're evolving into
now that you're clean.
is that what i am --
clean?
'cause i don't feel that way
at all.
no, you certainly don't.
mmm, god.
i wish i could fuck you
right now.
whose house is this?
couldn't tell you.
god.
he's a man of many talents.
ah!
look.
i'm some old bitch.
better not press our luck.
we should go.
hello?
hi, dexter.
cody?
can you come
to my school tomorrow?
what's at your school,
buddy?
i'm doing
my cultural report.
saudi arabia.
can you watch me?
i'm kind of scared.
cody,
what are you doing?
who is this?
dexter.
hello?
who was that?
rita's son.
he wants me to come see him
at school tomorrow.
oh, poor kid.
he doesn't understand
that you've gone.
i think i'll go.
whatever you think's best.
hey, guys!
i'm home!
hello?
they're in bed.
why so early?
cody is being punished
for sneaking away
to make a phone call
without permission.
astor joined him in a misguided
show of support.
well, who was cody calling?
dexter.
the boy was trying
to invite him to his school.
can you imagine?
oh.
mom, we need to have a talk.
i made a phone call
of my own today.
i spoke with aunt cecilia.
she told me the school district
fired you almost a year ago.
we had philosophical
differences.
the educational system
is falling apart.
school should be life itself,
not a preparation for living.
do you know that they give
trophies to every child now
whether they win or lose?
yeah, i finally get it.
it took me a few decades,
but it's not just me --
nobody can deal with you.
you don't leave room
for anybody else to exist.
it's not my fault that
so many people are willing
to settle for mediocrity.
just look at you --
first paul, then dexter.
rita, you lack
even common sense,
and now you're passing
that torch of ordinary character
on to your children.
shut the fuck up.
nobody talks about my kids
that way.
thatagirl.
that's what i've been waiting
to see.
yeah!
i'm done with you.
no, you're not.
but you go --
you give me hell.
no.
no, i won't do that.
i won't let you turn me
into...you.
rita --
here's what's gonna happen --
first thing in the morning,
you're gonna pack up
and go home.
you'll come and visit us
for birthdays and holidays,
but you're not gonna live
with us anymore.
well...
...if that's what i have
to sacrifice
to get you on your feet...
"kill one man,
and you're a murderer.
"kill thousands,
a conqueror.
kill them all,
and you're a god."
does it sound to you
like our guy
has a narcissistic
personality disorder,
a classic god complex?
i think you're
onto something, angel.
to tell you the truth,
i don't know what
my alter ego had in mind
when he wrote that crap.
i just pulled from various
blogs on the internet,
mixed and matched --
presto manifesto.
you finally decided
to fight back.
i been waiting.
hope you don't expect me
to comment on that
so you can record it
on your hidden tape recorder.
i wasn't born yesterday.
you might have been,
for all i know.
your past is a bigger mystery
than fucking jimmy hoffa.
i tried every avenue,
legal and otherwise,
but there ain't no
paper trail
on the early years
of dexter morgan.
i guess there's no recorder
running, after all.
no, man.
unlike you, i do everything
out in the open.
well, in that case,
sergeant,
let me put this in the open
for you.
no matter what you try,
no matter when,
no matter how hard you work,
i'll always be a step ahead
of you for one simple reason.
and what's that?
i own you.
aah!
aah! fuck!
get him off of me!
get off me!
why are you doing this?!
stop!
i want your gun, your badge,
and your police i.d.
i want your
access card, too --
now!
type a statement
that sergeant doakes
is on administrative leave,
pending an internal affairs
investigation.
you two,
get him out of here.
thanks.
what the hell happened?
i don't know.
he just...jumped me.
that guy's always
had it out for me.
thanks for meeting
with me, don.
well, i don't know
what the point is.
the district court injunction
hearing starts in three hours.
which everyone here knows
we're going to lose.
don't look so shocked.
we always lose these things.
you bastards
and your free speech.
my boss never
lets me say anything.
i'll tell you what --
i will agree to dropping
the injunction,
which will save us days
of courtroom arguments
and a boatload
of legal fees,
if we can agree
on some simple ground rules
on how you publish
that document.
"ground rules."
we're not gonna have
any ground rules.
my only goal here is to avoid
compromising an investigation
of a mass murderer...
who could hurt
a lot more people.
give me just a second,
will you, frank?
i can't believe
you got those assholes
to publish the manifesto
without the victims' names
and as a page-3 story.
no sense hyping it.
it might just inspire the killer
to greater heights.
wait.
it's quiet here...
peaceful.
it's a good spot.
for what?
it's 1:00.
so it is.
i brought my own sandwich.
i thought you didn't like
the quiet, morgan.
i didn't.
i don't.
when i'm alone
and it's quiet, i get scared...
shitless,
like i start hearing
what's really going on inside.
i see.
so if it's all the same
to you,
maybe i can just practice
when you're around.
okay.
'cause when you're around,
i kind of feel like i can deal
with anything, you know?
like what happened to me --
i don't have to run from it.
i don't have to jump into bed
with some guy and hide there.
you give me strength.
i'm kind of
opening up here.
what do you want me to say?
i don't know.
you're the fucking zen master.
figure it out.
morgan...
i've got plaque
in my arteries.
i know the lyrics
to elevator music.
my hair isn't getting
any thicker.
you're gonna do great
up there.
you just have
to remember something --
they're more frightened
than you are.
no, they're not.
are so.
you're gonna be staring at them
the whole time.
if one of those unsuspecting
moms or dads
does something embarrassing
while you're up on stage...
like pick their nose?
...you're gonna be the one
who sees it.
yeah.
now that's power.
now go have fun.
dexter, over here.
we saved you a seat.
thanks, guys.
there you go -- $18,000.
i'll send a truck
for the piece tomorrow.
i am telling you, lila,
this is going to create
a critical mass for you.
according to the
psycholinguistic analysis
of the manifesto,
our killer is a white male
in his 50s.
what else?
uh, the killer
has no girlfriends
and considers himself
a good catholic.
hold on.
hold on. hold on.
how can you tell all that
by putting words in a computer?
i don't know, dude.
it's science.
how 'bout common sense?
i think the guy that
we're looking for is
pissed off at god,
and that's why
he kills people.
really? i actually found him
very politically motivated.
yeah, like a modern-day
revolutionary.
which would suggest that
he's killing for social change.
this is what he wants.
what's that?
confusion, chaos --
it's what the killer wants.
he's always been an intensely
private figure,
dispatching victims silently.
now he's suddenly a media whore?
it doesn't make sense.
he's creating
a clusterfuck.
very good, officer morgan.
the killer's making us
chase our tails.
you know what that means?
he knows how we work.
look how he hits
every major theme --
political,
environmental, religious.
in one section, he manages to
weave together julius caesar,
berlin, germany, the pittsburgh
steelers, and gandhi.
it's scattershot.
he knew that this would
send us scurrying
like squirrels for nuts.
yeah, but to suggest that
he might be one of us --
how can you be sure?
hi, i'm cody,
and i researched saudi arabia
for my cultural report.
my board is covered in sand
because saudi arabia
is one big desert.
as you can see, i used coffee
beans to write "saudi arabia."
arabic coffee is very famous.
i'm a little confused.
lila is the one showing me
how to take control,
stop killing,
get my life clean.
but this is the first time
since i went into recovery
that i actually feel clean.
the children in saudi arabia
are just like us,
because they...
this is the saudi arabian flag.
the arabic letters mean
"there is no god except allah."
do you know how tough it is
for a woman in saudi arabia?
they can't drive or have
powerful jobs.
or get this -- they can't even
go to the movies
without men's permission.
after they turn 12, they have
to wear long black sleeves,
and they can't hardly even talk
to men until they get married.
the new king, abdullah,
is trying to change
some old bad rules,
so women can do more things...
thank you very much
for listening.
or, as they say
in arabic, "shokran."
i can't believe how calm
you were up there.
yeah, you were like
a professional talker.
you were pretty good.
can dexter come
for ice cream with us?
can he, mom, please?
uh...sure,
dexter can join us.
i wouldn't miss it.
maybe they'll have some
delicious saudi flavors,
like sand or oil.
hang on a sec, guys.
hello.
are you hurt?
o-okay, okay.
i'm coming now.
i know. me too.
come on, kids.
dexter won't be joining us.
rita, it's an emergency.
look, i'm so sorry,
you guys.
i'm gonna make it up
to you,
but i got to help a friend
who's in trouble.
there was a fire
at her place.
i'm so sorry.
hey, let's go.
dexter.
what happened?
i was working on my piece
with the blowtorch,
and it just caught fire.
i was so scared.
oh, i guess so.
promise me that you won't
leave me,
that you won't go anywhere.
i'm not going anywhere.
hey, you got
your light fixed.
ææàãðü×öä»×é
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë