Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- previously on dexter...
- bathtub, jumper, bludgeon.
Lundy came to miami
to hunt this guy.
I think he got too close,
And i think it got him
killed and me shot.
- i can't even imagine
looking into the eyes
Of the person you love...
Watching as he takes
his last breath.
- how much did you
tell christine
About the lundy shooting?
- i learned my lesson.
I never even took the lundy
files out of the station.
There's no way she
could have seen it.
- how did she know that?
How tall was my shooter?
- my height.
- then it wasn't trinity.
Look, i know it's really tough
for reporters right now,
So maybe i can give you
That interview
you've been wanting from me.
- i'm married.
- we have this connection.
- i have dexter.
- that smudge you found
at the crime scene--
How do you think he got
the ashes to stick to the wall?
- we got
the killer's goddamn dna.
- going out of town?
- yeah.
a four walls build.
- an out-of-town build--
Is his cycle
starting over again?
- this is where
it all started.
Vera saw me.
I startled her,
and she slipped...
Shattered
the shower doors.
The glass
sliced her leg.
She was dead by the time
the ambulance came.
Don't touch my sister!
- fuck you and fuck vera.
- get the fuck off him!
I should have fucking killed you
when i had the chance.
- hi, dad.
- a hypodermic needle.
The perfect drug
delivery system.
Rapid. efficient.
Especially
in the right hands.
- so how's everyone doing
over there?
- honey, i know.
everything's gonna be okay.
- are you okay?
- well, i'm not the one
getting four booster shots.
I don't know how you're
not a complete wreck.
- serial killer. remember?
Well, a little pain now
means a lot less later on.
I should know.
I had my chance to eliminate
arthur early on.
I didn't and now--
- we ready?
- okay, buddy,
look at daddy.
- i know, i know,
i know.
- all right, that's one down.
three more to go.
- the good news is,
you won't remember any of this.
I didn't remember what happened
to me as a child...
Until i was forced to.
Keeping my tools
in a shipping container
Makes more sense
than a backyard shed.
After all, it's where
my dark passenger was born.
And, after tonight,
It's where arthur mitchell
will call home.
Arthur is a man of ritual,
like me.
Gas up the car,
a quick stop at starbucks,
Choir practice...
And that's where
i'm going to take him
When he's alone in
the parking lot of his church.
Wait.
why isn't he stopping?
- scott, hold your sister's hand
until we're inside.
- you're not my mother.
- if arthur thinks
he can lose me in a crowd,
He's dead wrong.
- "nick, barb, scott...
Abby."
? ?
- i know that look.
I'm not the only one
on a stalk.
But it's too soon.
Arthur just finished
his last kill cycle.
By saving his life, have i
set it all in motion again?
Where'd you go?
- scott,
i'm officer carney.
- am--am i in trouble?
- no, no.
Are your mom and dad
nick and barb?
- yes.
- i'm afraid they've been
in a car accident.
- are they okay?
- they're gonna be fine,
but they've asked me to take you
To go see them
in the hospital.
- we have to go get
my sister.
- no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
My partner's got abby
in our patrol car.
Come on.
I'm just glad
i found you.
- it wasn't the babysitter
he was after.
- this isn't a police car.
- i work undercover.
- wait, where's my sister?
- well, let me radio in
and see where my partner is.
- arthur!
- shit.
- kyle, i don't appreciate
being followed.
- arthur,
what are you doing?
- i don't know
what you think you saw,
But i promise i'll preserve
this boy's innocence.
- i'm calling the police.
- if i so much as see
a police car,
The boy pays the price.
You like protecting children,
don't you?
Like my son.
- arthur, just pull over.
tell me where you are.
- i have a process.
As long
as it's not interrupted,
I'll set the boy free.
- arthur, don't do this.
let the boy go.
- dexter, he's gonna
kill that child.
- he's never taken a child
before.
- that you know of.
If this is new,
this is on you.
- not if i find him first.
- mr. butler?
- where's your mother?
- she's picking up rebecca
from ballet,
But she'll be back
any minute.
I really don't think
that you--
- jonah, don't talk.
Just listen and answer.
Do you have any idea
where your father is?
- he's at some teaching thing
up in naples.
- how long?
- a couple days.
- a couple of days.
good.
If arthur's process
takes that long,
The boy still has time.
- you know, it's like
thanksgiving never happened.
- except for this.
Why are you still here?
- i can't leave my mom
and sister alone with him,
And my mom won't leave,
so i'm fucked.
- look, i need to find
your dad, and fast.
I need your help.
- don't you understand?
The longer he's gone,
the better, for all of us.
- jonah, we both know
what he's capable of.
- did--did he hurt
someone else?
- i hope not.
That's why i need
to find him
To keep him from doing
something really wrong.
You have the chance
to finally break the cycle.
- what do you want me to do?
- go through his desk,
journals, computer.
Anything, everything.
Find out
what he's been working on.
- he'd kill me.
- i'll make sure
he never finds out.
- you know, i...
I'm--i'm not--
i'm not sure if i can--
If i can do it.
That's my mom
and rebecca.
- there is a great big shit-ugly
world out there, jonah.
The bad stuff doesn't
just end at your doorstep.
You can help put an end
to all of it.
- to all of what?
- the sins of your father.
Help me, jonah.
- where am i?
What is this place?
- do you like trains,
arthur?
- my name isn't arthur.
it's scott.
- look at that.
It's a thing of beauty.
- i want my mom and dad.
whoo-whoo.
Choo-choo-choo-choo-choo
choo-choo-choo-choo
Choo-choo-choo-choo
choo-choo-choo.
Whoo-whoo.
- if arthur's ritual, like mine,
was born in the past,
The past
is where i'll find him.
His last cycle of kills
took place in new orleans.
Matthew hicks,
ten years old,
Went to the local pool,
never came home.
Five days before a woman was
found murdered in her bathtub.
Before?
- you always did have
a soft spot for kids.
They remind you
of what you lost that day
In the shipping container.
- innocence.
- arthur said that's
what he would preserve
In the boy he took.
If each of arthur's victims
Represents
members of his family,
Then the boy...
- must be arthur himself.
He was ten
when his sister died.
Omaha, another ten-year-old
goes missing.
Five days later,
another bathtub murder.
St. paul.
Denver.
- lundy misread the pattern.
- it's not three victims
he leaves behind; it's four.
Lundy didn't think to look
at missing children
Because they were never
recorded as homicides.
- which means five days
Before the lisa bell
bathtub murder here in miami...
- another ten-year-old
went missing.
My god.
the boys begin the cycle.
- hey.
- sorry. working late.
- like always.
- is everything okay?
- harrison isn't sleeping,
So i'm gonna keep him
in our bed tonight.
- i'll be there in a sec.
- okay.
- arthur could have that boy
anywhere,
And now there'll be
an army of police
And volunteers
surrounding his parents
To help find their son.
I need to be one of them.
If arthur picked this
particular boy for a reason,
I need to know.
Come in.
- hey, dex,
you wanted to see me?
- gordy,
thanks for coming.
- yeah, sure, no sweat.
what's up?
- i dinged a parked van
last night,
And i left a note,
But the driver
hasn't called me back.
And i'm thinking,
after i totaled my car,
I can't afford
To let the insurance companies
get involved.
You think you can do
a stake and notify
So i can find this guy,
pay him in cash?
- yeah, sure. just, uh,
give me the plate,
And if patrol
spots your van,
I'll give you a heads-up
on its location.
- perfect.
- hold on. as soon as he's done
with the uni, i'm next.
- next for what?
- i have to talk to him.
- he's right in there.
- i'm still figuring out
how to phrase it.
- how gay are you?
- look, i--
I saw something at thanksgiving
i wish i hadn't.
- morgan.
- gordon.
Jesus,
ever hear of a comb?
It looks like you have
a cat on your head.
- i'm kind of on a mission here.
what's up?
- i've got that interview
with quinn's squeeze today.
- christine?
Are you sure
it's a good idea
To dredge up
all that lundy stuff?
- actually, i've got
a few questions for her.
I think she might have
some ideas about who shot him.
The real question is,
do i give quinn a heads-up or--
- no, you don't.
I gotta go.
- just no?
he's my partner.
- yeah, he's also
her boyfriend.
You don't know where
his loyalties are.
Deb, i've got field work
i've got to do.
- yeah, and i've got
a briefing on trinity
In, like, two minutes.
My case.
I need your big brain, bro.
- there's no new blood.
there's no need.
- no way.
You do realize i will stand here
all fucking morning.
If trinity works
in the public school system
And we can't get the okay
to swab these guys,
We are beyond boned.
- if he's even in
the school system.
Sorry, deb, but the sooner
this is over,
The sooner i get to
that missing boy's parents.
- we've had better luck
with private schools,
And so far
we're looking at 240 males
Who fit our trinity profile.
- well, collect their samples
and get them to masuka.
- oh, wonderful.
more old man spit.
- dexter, i need the blood
evidence in that bar stabbing.
- proofing it.
- proof faster.
prelim's tomorrow.
Where are we
on the lundy shooting?
- i'm still on
the foreign nationals
That were staying
at the hotel.
So, no significant
developments.
- when you say it
like that, no.
- okay.
- hey, uh, dex,
you got a minute?
It's about thanksgiving.
- later, vince.
- uh...
Okay.
- uh, lieutenant, could you
authorize this requisition?
Could it be so wrong
if you and i
Hopped on the first plane
to an island somewhere?
- yes, and this isn't
a requisition.
It's a thai menu.
- mm-hmm.
- thank you for bringing that
to my attention, sergeant.
- start at community colleges,
work our way up?
- detectives.
- babe?
- keep it in your pants.
she's here to see me.
- oh, you're finally
doing the interview?
- she is persistent.
- tell me about it.
- and when i'm done,
Everyone in miami is gonna know
what a true hero is.
- don't forget your partner.
that's quinn with two ns.
- oh, shit, i forgot to
run something by batista.
Will you show her
to the box?
And i'll be there
in two seconds?
- yeah.
- i need you to watch
christine interview me.
- and i would do that why?
- this could have something
to do with the lundy shooting.
No significant developments,
remember?
- okay.
- i'm hungry.
- well, why don't you
put your pajamas on
And we'll have
something to eat.
- no, i won't do it.
I won't do anything
you tell me to.
- don't you understand?
Father drinks,
and mother pays the price.
I'm just trying
to protect you, arthur.
- my name is scott!
- very well.
- mr. smith.
- yes.
- i'm dexter morgan,
miami metro.
I'm not here
in any official capacity.
I just want to do
anything i can
To help find
your missing son.
- we haven't set up
phone banks yet,
But, uh, we have
some flyers.
- may i take some with me?
- great.
- i'm the only one here
who knows what happened.
I could point the police in
arthur mitchell's direction.
But the slightest misstep
on their part
Ensures this family
is never whole again.
- is there any information
at all on your son?
A tip, a lead,
a phone call?
Anything that could point me
in a direction?
- none.
I keep waiting
for a ransom note.
Something.
- i'd better go
post these.
I'm gonna do everything i can
to help you get your son back.
- thank you.
- can you imagine walking by
your kid's empty bedroom,
Not knowing where he is?
- no. i can't.
- how does a guy like this
make a dead body
Just disappear
into thin air?
- the gulf stream
does the trick for me.
- but there's no ocean
in omaha,
Des moines, st. paul,
or denver.
- the four walls houses.
He goes to each one
of those cities on a build
As a pretext
for his killing cycle.
- construction site
Would be a convenient place
to bury a body.
- or to hold a boy captive.
- three years on patrol,
Two years in vice.
Why homicide?
- my dad
was a detective here.
- hmm.
- but it was completely
different being a cop back then.
- yeah, i bet.
talk about your man's world.
- oh, no, no,
it wasn't just that.
I think you had to rely more
on your instincts back then.
There wasn't
all this forensics stuff
To lean on
to break a case.
Back then, you had to rely
on your gut.
- amen to that.
- have you seen these?
- forensically, we're at
a dead end with the lundy case,
So i just stare at these,
looking for answers.
- you know what?
I've got enough
background info.
How about i just write this up
and give you a call
If, uh, we didn't cover
everything?
- sure.
Can i ask you something?
You live over in the gables,
right?
- yeah.
- ah, that must be
really nice,
Being away from all that
touristy stuff.
- well, i got lucky.
found a great building.
- yeah, so the gables,
that's what, like, uh,
60 minutes from the hotel
where frank was staying?
- i guess.
- wow.
You sure got to
the crime scene fast.
There's no traffic
at 5:00 a.m.
- oh, i know that.
But dispatch didn't
put out the call till 5:05.
You were the first reporter
on scene at 5:20.
- i like to roll out of bed
and hit the gym early.
I was on my way there
when i heard the scanner.
- bullshit.
she's lying.
- um, how do i
get out of here?
- you just
follow the windows
Till you get
to the elevator.
- we've got to tread
very, very lightly with it.
If quinn--
- no shit.
That's why i'm asking you
to help me sort through this.
Tell me i'm not crazy.
- you're not crazy.
I spoke to christine
at your crime scene.
Hair made, full makeup.
No way she rolled out of bed
at 5:00 a.m. looking like that.
- i'm telling you she knows more
than she's letting on.
She's a hard-boiled
crime scene reporter,
And she couldn't even fucking
look at those photos of lundy.
- suspicious,
but it doesn't prove a thing.
- well,
there's something else.
I know it sounds weird,
but the other day,
She was talking to me
about how i was
Looking in lundy's eyes
when he died.
How the fuck does she know
he didn't die instantly?
- laguerta got broward
county school district
To let us collect samples.
Still working on dade.
- great.
- everything okay?
- yeah. great.
Be right there.
- great.
- we can't be doing this
with quinn around.
- thank you.
- build's nearly finished.
No one's here.
They're not here.
Fuck!
Hello?
- kyle, i went through
my dad's desk.
You know,
there's nothing here.
- what about his computer?
- i already looked.
There's--it's just
school stuff.
- look at the search history.
does anything stand out?
- okay, okay, okay.
one sec, one sec.
Nothing, really.
We got some bible stuff.
A hardware store.
a real estate agency.
The local paper.
- the real estate site.
What was he looking at?
- uh, let's see.
It's just a bunch of homes
for sale.
- an empty house.
Good place to ensure
his process isn't disturbed.
- i can email you the list
if you want.
I don't have email.
- who doesn't have email,
kyle?
- off the top of my head,
people who don't exist.
Fax them to the kinko's
near your house under my name.
I'll pick them up there.
- okay.
- jonah, you're doing
the right thing.
- you know, how--
How come
you're the only one
Who can see my dad
for what he is?
- we have a few things
in common.
- police are searching
for a north miami boy
Who went missing
last night.
Ten-year-old scott smith
was in an arcade with his sister
And their nanny
at around 7:45 p.m.
When the nanny,
susan peterson,
Realized that scott
was no longer at her side.
fight, fight, fight!
Fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight!
- cody?
- let go.
let go of him, cody.
- cody! cody, come here.
cody, what are you doing?
- he said he saw dexter leave
the young sailors camp-out
In the middle of the night
'cause he was scared,
So i hit him.
- i'm so sorry.
boys, huh?
- if my son said
that's what he saw,
I believe him.
Come on.
- why, hello.
I'm so glad
i finally got you.
- actually, i'm in the middle
of a project.
- dad, i really
need to see you.
- you just did.
thanksgiving night.
- i can't wait another
four months until my birthday.
Can we meet in between
our usual visits?
Just this once?
- there's a reason
why we only see each other
A couple of times a year,
christine.
I have a full life
and a family who needs me.
- i'm your family too.
I need you.
more than they do.
- sorry, sweetie,
it'll have to wait.
Love you.
- i think i'm in trouble.
Dad?
- so are you
gonna let me go?
- in due time, arthur.
- why do you keep
calling me that?
? ?
- is that food for me?
- you can have
something to eat
Once you put
your pajamas on, arthur.
Oh, this is delicious.
- so far i've looked at six
empty houses on jonah's list.
This one, not so empty.
- hey.
- dexter, are you
on your way home?
- just finishing up
a few things.
- oh. the baby
has a fever.
How long do you think
you're gonna be?
- not very.
There's still another house
i can check on the way home.
- scott?
Scott smith?
- me and my kids
got nowhere else to be.
My babies just need a place
to feel safe at night.
We don't make a mess
or nothin'.
You ain't gonna tell?
- no.
No, i won't.
- shh.
Thank god.
Hey, can you take him?
- yeah.
Oh, he's so warm.
- yeah. those shots really
did a number on him.
Look, can you take
his temperature again?
The thermometer's
on the counter.
You're late.
big day?
- yeah, i was helping out
with that missing boy.
- oh, that's so sweet.
those poor parents.
Speaking of which,
paul's folks called.
They want to take the kids
to disney world one weekend.
- you sure
that's a good idea?
I've never even met them.
- they're nothing like paul.
He was the abusive black sheep
of the family.
Plus, i think it would be good
for cody right now.
- what happened to his eye?
- one of the young sailors
said you disappeared
The night
of the camping trip.
Cody was defending
your honor.
- huh.
The only time i left
my tent that night
Was to find a tree.
- well, cody doesn't want to be
part of the group anymore.
He said he doesn't want to be
around somebody who tells lies.
- too late.
100.1.
- oy.
You mind giving him
a sponge bath, cool him off?
Food will be ready
when you're done.
- okay.
- this is so frustrating.
None of it makes
any fucking sense.
- what if christine
was covering for a source
That knew something
about this?
- possibly.
I couldn't even look quinn
in the eye.
- don't worry.
We're gonna
figure this out.
We just gotta think
outside the box.
- how's this
for outside the box?
Christine's the same height
as the shooter.
- christine shoots lundy.
why?
- beats the mother-fuck
out of me.
She doesn't have a record.
- you ran her prints?
- after the interview,
I lifted them off some pictures
i got her to pick up.
- maybe she has priors that
she hasn't been nailed on.
- we get her dna, we check it
against the database.
- you and i both know
We don't have enough
to get a warrant.
- think outside the box,
sergeant.
- nothing like clean,
cool water,
Huh, big guy?
You'll be as good as new
in no time.
But will i?
I killed an innocent man
When i left the campsite
that night.
Now rita and cody have been
drawn into defending a lie.
My lie.
Trinity's not the only one
Using his family
as human shields.
- are you out
of your fucking mind?
No way christine
had anything
To do with shooting you
or lundy!
- you've been dating her
for what, two months?
How well do you even
fucking know her?
- what is this, some morgan
vendetta against me?
Is your asshole brother
behind this?
- why the fuck would my brother
have anything to do with this?
- forget it. it--
Look, you're probably right
about christine,
And i am totally off-base,
But you're a cop,
and a good one,
And i know
you know what it's like
When you have a hunch.
- who else knows
about this?
- batista.
- great. you're making me
look like a fucking asshole.
- don't make this
about you.
Does she
keep a toothbrush here?
Christine will never know
about this.
And when the results
come back clean,
You can shove this up my ass
anytime you want.
I need you to get
a dna panel on this asap.
- that's your emergency?
project runway is on.
fuck you.
- i'll owe you one, all right?
- who's it belong to?
- we may have a big fucking
lead on the lundy case,
And...
just fucking run it.
- six houses down,
another eight to go,
And i'm running out of time.
Morgan.
- dexter,
where the hell are you?
- en route.
traffic.
- okay, well, the da's all
over me about that blood report.
- i'll have it on your desk
in half an hour.
- what?
- i was just thinking.
Christmas is coming up.
You got any plans?
- you and me.
- what about your family?
- hmm.
we're not that close.
- i guess that's why
you never talk about them.
- have you seen
my toothbrush?
- oh, the cleaning lady must
have thrown it out by mistake.
- she's jealous
of my perfect teeth.
- here. brand new.
- are you okay?
- yeah.
- yeah?
Are you sure?
- now's not a good time.
- well, maybe it is
a good time for me.
You ever consider that?
- wow. um...
- this is about your partner,
isn't it?
Did she say
something to you?
- about what?
- she gave
a shitty interview.
I'm ditching the article.
- so you think she's pissed
about that?
- i don't know.
it doesn't matter.
I'm gonna be late
for work.
Daddy, i can't wait.
i need to see you now.
We might be in trouble.
We have to talk about,
uh...
That woman in the bathtub
that night
When i was little.
Please call me back.
please.
- now what'll we call
this station?
- why can't i go home?
- northern springs?
rainbow valley?
How about, uh,
copper flats?
- this is stupid!
You should take me home.
I want to see
my mom and dad.
- ? hey, venus ?
? oh, venus ?
? venus, make her fair ?
? a lovely girl
with sunlight in her hair ?
? and take the brightest stars
up in the skies ?
? and place them
in her eyes for me ?
? ?
- ? venus, goddess of love
that you are ?
- ? surely the things
i ask ?
- why are you so sad?
- ? can't be too great
a task ?
- it was
vera's favorite song.
- ? venus, if you do ?
- she was my sister.
- ? i promise
that i always will be true ?
- what happened to her?
- ? i'll give her
all the love i have to give ?
? as long as we both
shall live ?
- she died.
It wasn't my fault.
- ? goddess of love
that you are ?
? surely the things
i ask ?
- listen.
Uh, i'm sorry
about your sister.
And if it'll make you feel
any better,
You can call me arthur.
- ? i'll give her
all the love i have to give ?
- you'd let me do that?
- sure.
Now how about we play trains
a little bit more
And then you can
take me home.
- ? venus ?
? make my wish come true ?
? ?
- you're a dear boy,
arthur.
So innocent.
Kind-hearted.
Promise me
you'll always stay that way.
- sure.
- hey, do you like
ice cream?
After you've, uh,
Finished your treat...
I think it's time
to let you go free.
- yeah, i'm calling about
the house on olive.
Yeah, i'm sure
the curbside appeal is great,
But i need to know,
is the house occupied?
Oh, the current owners
are still living there.
Great.
yes, okay.
No need for a drive-by.
You stay blessed too.
Lieutenant, blood report
on the bar stabbing.
- hey, dexter, just got word
on that stake and notify.
We found your van
about 20 minutes ago.
It was at a diner
on flagler and fourth.
Hope you find your guy.
- me too.
If arthur's van was spotted
close to where he has the boy,
That should narrow
my search down considerably.
Fourth and flagler.
Four listings
in the area.
Two within a mile.
- uh, hey, dex...
- where are you off to?
- kill the guy
you're looking for.
Save a kid. remember
to pick up diapers.
I have to be
two places at once.
Not a great day.
- i hear you.
I'm half out of my mind trying
to crack this lundy thing.
- debra morgan!
- fuck me twice on sunday.
that's all i need.
- who's that?
- one of dad's
old fuck buddies.
Emphasis on old.
- harry's past
is a minefield.
But i've got my own
ticking bomb to defuse.
Let me know what happens.
- what's up, valerie?
- i'm sorry i said those things
about your father.
He dumped me for another ci,
And all this time,
it still hurts.
- do you happen to remember
this other woman's name?
- no, but i bet
she'd remember me.
God, i was completely
out of my mind.
Went to her house,
confronted her.
- valerie, i have to go.
i will call you.
- so, um,
pick you up later?
Get a bottle of wine?
- you're...
- in love with
a beautiful woman.
So shoot me.
- lieutenant.
The dna results
on christine hill are back.
- she's fucking related
to trinity.
- bomb shelter.
- 1960s miami.
Cuban missile crisis.
Irony is,
places like this were built
To keep people safe.
- i hate irony.
They were here...
And i just missed them.
- i'm sorry, daddy.
Thanks for meeting me.
I never told you because
i thought it was a dream.
And i wanted it to be,
but it wasn't.
- now, now, now, now, now,
slow down.
What are you talking about?
- i saw you that night.
Back when i was five.
- you told me to stay
in the car, but i didn't.
So i got out and i went
into that woman's house.
And i saw you
in the bathtub with her.
The water was so red.
- it was a dream.
You were right
the first time.
- it wasn't.
I knew it wasn't
When it happened again
in the same house
30 years later.
- i couldn't
figure this out in time.
- you'll have another shot
at arthur.
Isn't that what you want?
- what if it was harrison
or cody?
- your priorities
have changed.
I'm a father now.
- i went back
and i looked through
All the postcards
you sent me over the years.
Every trip you took
in every city you went,
A woman died in a bathtub.
- you don't know what
you're talking about.
- it's all right.
i protected you.
That fbi agent? lundy.
He was starting to get close,
but i stopped him.
I got in with
the homicide department
So i'd know what they knew.
And i followed lundy
And i saw you
run into him.
And he started
putting things together,
And he was never gonna stop,
so i shot him.
- you what?
- it's okay.
I made it look like
another crime spree.
The vacation murders.
the police had no idea.
- had?
- well, they still don't have
anything solid.
But they're starting
to ask questions.
- no.
- dad.
- you put yourself
at risk...
For me.
- i'd do anything
for you.
More than your other kids.
They would never do
what i did for you.
- it's gonna be okay,
baby.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you, i promise you.
- okay.
- you've always been
so special to me.
Dad.
- now go home.
- no.
- i'll drop by tonight,
And we'll figure
all of this out, okay?
Go on now.
- it's gonna be fine.
Stupid fucking cunt!
- no wonder none
of those missing boys
Has ever been found.
- encase a body in cement
And it's preserved forever.
The four walls build.
- you were already there.
- arthur wasn't ready then.
He is now.
Burying a child in cement.
that's not very christian.
- no closer.
- i'll take that to mean
the boy is still alive.
- walk away, kyle.
this doesn't concern you.
- there's no way
i can do that.
- i need to do this.
I can't stop this.
- i can.
Alive.
Arthur!
Daddy.
- hey, you.
- hey, you too.
- long day?
- oh.
The longest.
- mm.
- they found that boy.
- well, do the police have
any idea what happened?
- if they do,
they're not saying.
Those parents must be
so relieved.
Do you hear that?
- crickets.
For once,
the house is quiet.
- mm.
- jinxed it.
- hmm.
- i got this.
i got it.
- no, but you're so tired.
- it's okay.
I want to.
- yeah, it's okay,
big guy.
It's okay.
Mm.
I'm sorry you're in pain.
Yeah.
I promise you, no one's
ever gonna hurt you again.
Especially me.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com