Good morning.
Didn't I paint your condo
a couple weeks ago?
No, a bunch of workers painted my condo
while you hit on me.
You know what? Those workers
are living the american dream.
You show up on time, you work hard,
and just maybe your boss will get laid.
OK. Let's go take a shower.
You know what?
You go take a shower.
I'm going to lay here
and try to put a name
on some of those positions
I invented last night.
Honey, half those positions aren't new,
and the last one,
I think you stumbled into.
I might have stumbled into it,
but I'm pretty sure I stuck the landing.
You were great.
Last night was unbelievable.
There's plenty more
where that came from...
If I can ever walk again.
My back.
What's up?
- You got any shampoo?
- Yeah, just
grab one of the empty bottles, put
some water in it, and just shake it up.
Please let that be a
door-to-door chiropractor.
- Who is that?
- That's my ex-wife.
If we're quiet,
she'll probably just go away.
Gary, believe me, you need to
have a civil relationship with your ex.
So just go downstairs,
be pleasant, and see what she wants.
I know what she wants.
She already has my left one.
- Hi, dad.
- Hi, Cutie.
I love you. What's going on?
Why aren't the kids at school?
We had to stop by here to pick up
everything you forgot
- to drop off with them last night.
- What are you talking about?
I put everything they had into their
backpacks. What did I forget?
Their backpacks.
And I got a speeding ticket
on the way over here, too.
You got a speeding ticket?
What's the matter?
Your two lady friends couldn't
help get you out of it?
No, Gary.
I'm not going to sink to that level.
Why not?
They have.
You know what, Gary?
If we were at Mardi gras,
you would get way more beads,
my friend. OK?
- That's right.
- It's not in my room, mom.
We still can't find Louise's cello.
How do you lose a cello, Gary?
I don't know.
I've looked everywhere for that thing.
Get in the car.
I'll be right out. All right?
- Bye, dad.
- Do you have any tests today?
Je vais fais une exam du francias.
That's fantastic.
Too bad we're never going to Germany.
- Why are you walking like your father?
- What? I hurt my back.
My gosh! You're the only one alive
that knows how to fix it.
- What?
- Come on. You can do it.
I'll get on the ground.
You fix it.
In order to fix your back,
I would have to get on
the floor and climb all over you.
It's crossing a line.
Come on. Help me.
Help me! Just do it!
All right, but no unnecessary wiggling.
How'd you hurt it this time?
What? With lifting something?
No, I wasn't lifting weights.
What, are you painting ceilings?
Allison, I did not hurt my back
doing anything you warned me about, OK?
I hurt my back having super-amazing
hot sex with my new girlfriend.
- And I'm done.
- What?
You never even touched me!
I don't want to hear about your sex
life, OK? Learn some boundaries, man.
Boundaries?
You're engaged to our marriage
therapist. Don't you think
that's crossing a boundary?
Dr. Walter krandall did everything could
to save our marriage, including me.
And I only said that because
I knew you were going to.
I bet if Dr. Walter krandall
hurt his back
and couldn't ride his dumb little bike
around town, you'd fix it.
I would fix walter's back
because he is my fiance...
And he's also a published author
and has appeared in "Time" magazine,
and he was on the "Today" show.
Yeah. What?
Willard scott was wishing
him happy birthday?
- Are these your keys?
- Yes, they are.
Come on, tom.
We're gonna be late.
See you, dad.
That's your phone that's been buzzing?
It's just danielle.
She called me 11 times this morning.
So I stopped answering it.
I didn't know danielle
was being so possessive.
A little bit.
You know, she insists on holding
my hand all the time, even during lunch.
I can't eat.
And I think my left hand is
getting smaller from all the squeezing.
Hold it out. Let me see that left hand.
Let me see, with that left hand,
if you can pick up daddy's keys.
There you go. You're a good guy.
Listen, I got to tell you something,
Tommy, this is a good thing, OK?
This girl likes you. Right?
Plus, you're getting hand.
I am the first of my friends to get it.
That a boy!
But if she wasn't so hot,
i'd think she was crazy.
Yeah. It's a good thing
the hot ones are never crazy.
-= Gary 102 =-
"Gary Gets Boundaries"
[Subs-Addicts"]
[Sub-Way.fr]
Please. Just do this thing for my back.
Come on. You just...
you get my hand up over my head,
and you sit down on my hips,
and then you straddle me,
and you just kind of rock my hips around
like this until you hear something pop.
Yeah. I'm not going to
be doing that to you, man.
Help me up.
Give me a hand.
Give me a hand here.
All right. That's good.
Gosh. My hand.
My back.
I just put my hand on my back!
If I was in my old house, forget it.
Would have cracked my back,
I would sit in my hot tub,
and I would be as good as new.
This nonstop sex with
vanessa is killing me.
That's terrible.
Did I tell you my wife
just gained 60 pounds?
Look, here's the thing with Vanessa.
You saw her. She's beautiful.
And for some reason, she thinks I'm
incredible. I've got keep up with her.
She used to having sex with
these hairless, bendy,
flexible abercrombie & fitch guys,
you know, and... You know what it is?
It's like every time, I have
to prove myself over and over again.
I got to be honest with you, Dennis.
I've never felt so vulnerable.
Remember when we used
to talk about football?
Have you found the cello yet, Gary?
Louise has practice tonight.
Who is this?
Are you even looking for it?
No, I'm not looking for it. I'm on
my way to work. I'm on the freeway.
What do you want me to do?
Hey, Buddy!
I only need a little
bit of the road, OK?
This guy almost killed me. It's amazing.
Holy smokes. Honor student,
my ass. You know what?
Yeah? That's real classy
with your kid in the car.
I don't have any beer, Gary.
Not even in the downstairs, my god!
What are you doing?
You're never home at this time of day!
What? I skipped a class to come
home and, you know, study for a paper.
OK, you know what? I don't need
to tell you why I'm in my own house.
Were you in my hot tub?
No, I was in my hot tub that
I built with my hands on my patio.
That my lawyer was able to get from
your friend who went
to law school on the internet.
Look, Gary,
I mean, i'm sorry about your back. I am.
But really, seriously, coming over
here and. What are you doing?
- I'm changing out of my trunks.
- In my kitchen?
Yeah, because you always
used to get mad at me
if I would track water
through the house.
Gary, you just.
I can't believe you would
just undress in front of me. God.
All right. Big deal.
I don't see what the big deal is.
I mean, getting undressed
in front of you, it's like
it's like getting undressed
in front of a dude.
A dude?
I gonna say dog, but I knew
it would rub you the wrong way.
You know what, Gary?
You've got to get your suit back on
and go. And from now on, new boundaries,
OK? You are not allowed in my house
or anywhere outside of my house.
OK? And I am not going to go in your
house. And why are you still naked?
Because my back just locked up.
I can't bend down and pick up my shorts.
- For god's sakes!
- I need your help.
Help me pick up my shorts.
All right.
All right, give me your right foot.
OK.
- Your right foot. Jeez, what are you 3?
- I'm sorry.
I can't believe you, Gary.
You come into my house,
you dig through my fridge, you drop your
pants. You know what? Do it yourself!
- OK.
- God, it's just...
Right. I don't know why you're making
such big deal out of such a tiny thing.
That's because the tiny thing
is in my kitchen.
You are cranking the air conditioner,
I was just standing in frot
of a cold refrigerator.
You know what, Gary?
This is my house!
I know it's your house,
Allison, and I respect that.
I was only using the hot tub because
of my back, and that's the truth.
Burgers are ready.
My gosh.
This is heaven on my back.
I knew that was going to happen!
And yet...
i did it anyway.
- Dad?
- Over here, honey.
- Hi, dad.
- Hi. How are you? Sorry.
I didn't find your cello yet, OK?
Hey, where's your brother?
Right behind me.
Tommy, puberty hit you hard.
- Hello, Gary.
- Hello, Krandall.
Allison asked if I could pick
Tom and Louise up from school.
Great. Where's Tom?
Unfortunately, I only had
enough room on my bike for one.
He made me run behind him!
That's not the definition
of being picked up at all!
- What's going on here, Krandall?
- Every light in the house apparently.
I understand there was an
incident between you and Allison.
She prefers not to
speak to you for a while.
Really? She's punishing me by
not coming into my house?
I hope she doesn't get really mean
and stop cashing my alimony checks.
I don't know what's going
on between the two of you,
but if you'd like to talk about it,
i'll put on my therapist's hat.
OK. Does it come with
a chin strap like that one?
Deflective humor. That's very healthy.
But if you give me your version of it,
I will offer my keen insight.
Yeah. No offense, Krandall.
I don't think so. I mean, come on.
You're going to marry my ex-wife.
You can't be much smarter than I am.
I tried talking to her,
but she wouldn't share with me either.
Me, of all people.
I'm a professional.
Do you know that one of
my clients is sir ben kingsley?
You're not supposed to tell me that.
I know. I know. I got an earful about
that from parker posey.
Listen, Danielle,
OK, I have homework to do.
OK? I really need to go.
Can't we watch each other do homework?
Did you just minimize me?
No, no. There's something
wrong with the computer.
I bet any minute now, it's just, rrr!
I like that one.
This girl's really getting to you,
isn't she?
She's driving me crazy, dad.
She calls me all the time.
She stuffs notes in my locker.
You know, today she made me
hold hands with her during the assembly.
Both hands.
It was like we were figure skating.
All right. So, Tommy,
why are you putting up with all this?
Because I'm just an average guy, OK?
- And she's a totally banging girl.
- OK. Tommy, let me tell you something.
You show me a banging girl, and
I'll show you a guy that's tired of...
Holding her hands.
OK. So... so what should I do, dad? OK?
- I don't want to break up with her.
- You just have to be honest with her.
You have to take her for a walk and
tell her to ease up a bit. That's all.
A walk?
Really?
Women respond to honesty.
I mean, if this girl is wearing you out,
you can't just act like nothing's wrong.
My gosh.
- Are you all right, dad?
- Nothing's wrong...
It's Danielle.
My god. She's calling
from inside the house.
Listen,
be strong, OK?
- Thanks.
- All right. You got it.
Hey, Louise.
Hi, honey. What's up?
- My ride's here.
- Look.
You don't have to go to cello practice.
You have nothing to play.
I'm in band, dad.
If I had anything better to do,
don't you think i'd be doing it?
- Hey, I'm taking off dad. OK?
- Wait. Where are you going?
Danielle and I are going
to go on that...
- that walk.
- When are you gonna be back?
I don't know. I've got to go over to
her house. So I'll just. I'll see you.
There you are, slowpoke.
Yuck. This is awful,
all these bendy,
flexible,
hairless men.
Which one is abercrombie?
- Hi. Hi, Vanessa.
- Hey, handsome.
Who was that little blonde
girl pulling your son like a wagon?
That's his girlfriend.
She's crazy... about him.
Where's parker?
Don't you have him tonight?
I did, but his dad wanted to
take him to a game, so we switched.
- Thought you'd want to hang out.
- Yeah, sure. What...
- What did you have in mind?
- I don't know.
Drink some beers,
watch some football, just be mellow.
Really?
That's fantastic.
You have no idea how good that sounds,
because I've been meaning
to tell you that my back.
- Hello, boys.
- My back is very horny.
- Would you look at this?
- Hello, my dear. Hope you don't mind.
- I let myself in.
- Not at all. What am I smelling?
The Chateau Briand, and it's going
to burn unless I find a set of tongs.
Walter, you are so wonderful.
This is exactly what I need tonight.
Hope your day's getting a little
bit better. I spoke to gary earlier.
Please, don't say that name. I'm having
a nice moment. Let me enjoy this.
Absolutely. That's exactly my plan.
If you want to share anything with me,
as sir ben kingsley does
each wednesday...
No, Walter.
Walter, I love you.
I just don't want to talk.
I want to relax.
Then I have something
very special for you.
- Close your eyes.
- I like the sound of that.
Keep them closed.
Oh, my god!
Beautiful, isn't it?
Walter, where the
hell did you find that?
It was in the laundry
room under a pile of clothes.
Why didn't you tell me
you had a cello in the house?
This is awful.
Admittedly I haven't played
in a while, but
why am I defending myself?
What instrument do you play?
Are you OK, sweetie?
You kind of sound like you're in pain.
Pain? Me? No.
Non. Mal?
No, I'm doing, you know, like, primal...
Like grunting noises, you know.
I don't know if you know anything
about the Silver-Back Gorilla.
- I do, actually.
- Well, then never mind.
- Just sit down.
- OK. You know what?
Speaking of gorilla colors,
i'm going to go downstairs and make
an emergency paint order.
- An emergency paint order?
- Look, don't break my chops, honey.
You knew what you were getting into the
minute you started dating a painter, OK?
OK. All right.
Cello, Allison.
- Gary, what are you doing?
- What am I doing? What are you doing?
Just dropping off the Cello.
Yeah, it turns out it was...
It was in my laundry room the whole
time. Isn't that funny? All right, bye.
No, wait.
So you just bring it in my house,
sneak it in here and act like
it was here the whole time?
I thought you were out,
and you, you broke into my house today.
I had to use the hot tub
because you would fix my back.
Look, I don't care what it was, Gary. We
need to stick to the boundaries we set.
No, no, no. The boundaries
that you set that I don't understand,
because I don't really care who
comes in whose house. It doesn't
make sense to me. And I'm not even
sure why you're so mad. Oh, my god!
My back, Allison!
Please help me!
I can't even move!
You don't know why i'm so mad, Gary?
All right.
Where do I start?
I couldn't flirt my way out
of a speeding ticket
for the first time in my life!
And then when the cop looked
at my birth date,
he asked me if I might
know his mother... and I did.
And then my stupid ex-husband
whose back is sore from
having too much sex with his
young girlfriend
undressed in front of me
and said it wasn't any different from
undressing in front of a dude!
That's it?
That's what you're so fired up about.
The dude comment?
My gosh!
I feel better!
All right!
What do you care what I think about you?
I'm your ex-husband!
Exactly, Gary.
We were married.
You had 2 children with this dude.
I don't want you to want me.
Just acknowledge that
i'm still wantable. No?
I mean, my god. You don't know
what it's like. It's different for men.
Different? I don't know what it's like
to get old? I'm like the tin man!
You had to oil-can me down there,
for crying out loud!
Look, Allison,
don't whine about this.
I mean, you're almost 40,
sure, but you're still banging.
What is...
banging?
Look, I'm sorry about today.
I shouldn't have been in your hot tub.
I'm sorry I was in your house.
I'm sorry I said that it was
like being undressed in front of a dude.
I was just being an idiot. I'm sorry.
Banging like...
like how?
Banging, like, if we had met
in a bar and I didn't know you at all
and you were wearing the red
dress and you had your hair up...
Anything else?
If you weren't talking so much
or criticizing what I was wearing
or complaining about the service...
I would go up to you in that bar,
and I would ask you to dance,
and I would do everything in my
power to get you to go to bed with me.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
Thank you.
Assuming it was last call
and there was no one there younger.
Come on. I thought it
would make you feel better.
You know, it did. A little, and then it
didn't, and then it almost did again,
and then, you know
the whole thing was over.
Got to tell you,
a lot like having sex with you.
Hey, I'll have you know, I've
invented some new positions since then.
Goodye, Gary.
- All right.
- Look...
i'm sorry I assumed you lost the cello.
I was certain I lost it, OK?
I do look good in that red dress,
don't i?
Banging.
Hey, sorry about that.
That paint order took a lot
longer than I thought it was gonna.
- So you called her a dude.
- Yes, I did.
And what's the deal with your back?
Look, OK.
I have a confession to make.
My back is really messed up from years
of playing football and surfing AND
painting houses,
and apparently my back locks
up after nonstop acrobatic sex.
What made you think you
had to do that in the first place?
Because I didn't want you to think
I was one of these old guys
that, you know,
couldn't keep up with you.
Keep up with me?
I was trying to keep up with you.
You know, I know that all divorced
guys go through a crazy time,
but most of them at least
spread it around.
You are too much of a job for one woman.
If you ever want to write
that on a bathroom wall
or maybe send out a mass e-mail
to all my friends, that would be great.
Hey, pal,
- how did it go?
- Good. You know, really good.
I told her to lay off a little bit,
and you were right. Women like?
- it you say what's on your mind. Great.
- That's great.
Tommy, your lips...
They look glossy.
And you've got...
You've got glitter all over your face.
Really?
You were making out
with her this whole time!
Yeah!
I got lip!
That's fantastic, buddy!
You know, the more I told her to,
stop holding my hand,
the more she wanted to kiss me.
I'm really considering telling her to
stop kissing me and see where it goes.
All right. Why don't you
slow your roll there, partner?
Maybe just take a little time and enjoy
smelling the lip gloss for a while.
- All right. Good night, dad.
- I'll see you in the morning.
My back is killing me.
VO By :
¤AkaZab¤
Team Subs-Addicts"