Kids, wake up! Oh, my gosh!
I overslept! Guys!
I overslept! If I ever meet the guy
that invented the snooze alarm,
i'm gonna slap him in
the face every 5 minutes.
Come on, you guys. Come on, hurry up! We
don't want to keep your mother waiting.
So. So, that, concludes our
drill on what to do in case
we ever oversleep. So...
Just go back into your rooms
and put your school clothes on.
Don't keep your mother waiting.
That's good. Come on, guys.
You know, dad, I'm tired of
being woken up like a fireman,
without the thrill of the job.
Come on, We'll be out of here in 5 min.
I'll pop in some toaster waffles.
- Don't make a big thing about it, OK?
- Don't make a big thing about it?
Why are you suddenly acting like
the woman I wish I'd married?
We'd better not be late. I'm the tardy
officer. How would that look?
Hey, why don't you set your alarm,
Louise?
And then you can wake me up every day.
For the same reason I'm not going
to give myself away at my wedding:
because it's not my job.
Hey, Tom, honey, don't forget to
bring some nice clothes tonight.
I can't believe you're still
making me do that, mom.
Do what?
Mom told the new neighbors
I would ask their friendless
- daughter to the school dance tonight.
- Come on, Tommy, be nice.
Be nice. They just moved in. It wouldn't
hurt you to introduce Marjorie
to the people she'll be
going to school with.
Fine. But we are officially even.
After this, I don't ever want to hear
about how my big head ruined your body.
What's going on around here?
I mean, you're being nice,
you're cleaning up for no reason.
What's, my gosh,
the doctor called, I have cancer.
Is it in my head or in my butt?
Can't I just be nice
and easygoing for no reason?
Based on my 15 years of research, no.
Don't run the dishwasher. It's broken.
What's going on with you?
Walter and I may 16.
- That's great! Allison, that's great!
- I know. Isn't it? I'm getting married.
No more Allison money!
No more alimony?
Hey, maybe that's where they got
the word "alimony" from.
- Allison money. Alimony.
- What?
- It is exciting though. I mean, really.
I feel like I finally know
where my life is headed.
I feel like I just passed a 120-pound
Kidney Stone that says she's 110.
You know, I wonder what it's
gonna be like to be married
to a man who doesn't smell
his q-tips after he uses them.
- Come on, Louise! You guys ready?
- Yep! Let's go!
I got to get going.
I have to be in long beach by 9:00.
What a happy day.
Remember in "the wizard of oz"
when the movie went from black and white
to technicolor?
I don't know how they did that.
- I am so sorry.
- "Don't start the dishwasher."
There's really only one way to
screw up those instructions.
-= 113 =-
" Gary Moves Back In "
VO :   ¤Aka & YaYa¤
Subs-Addicts"
[Sub-way. fr]
I am so sorry, Gary.
What. What is this?
Well, remember my dad gave me that
newspaper when man landed on the moon
and you told me it would never be worth
anything? Well, now you're right.
- So, how bad was it?
- How bad was it?
Are you kidding me?
The water ran for 7 straight hours.
Every floorboard buckled.
The neighbors gathered around the house.
They thought the house was weeping
and it was a miracle from god!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Gary.
I am so sorry.
Stop saying you're sorry.
You sound like me when we were married.
You sure you want me to stay here?
Well... tch!
I don't want you to stay here,
but after what I did,
I can't make you go to a hotel,
because you...
- You'll hold that over my head forever.
- Forever.
Right, so... I... i got you,
some beer.
And I'm gonna make you a steak.
And I insist that you stay
in the master bedroom.
Oh, my old bedroom.
Great, you know. That'll be like...
It'll be like when they show a prisoner
the cell he lived in for 15 years.
- Hey, dad.
- Hi, sweetheart.
Louise, honey? Your dad is gonna
be staying with us for a couple days.
And I don't want it to
be confusing, but...
Your father and I are not getting back
together, OK? In a few days,
everything'll go back to the way it was
before, but, you know, not "before" when
we were married "before,"
before the flood "before."
I wasn't confused until you
tried to explain it that way.
Yeah. I'm with Louise. I'm...
We're not back together, right?
Right. Yeah.
Hey, son,
when you leaving for the big dance?
As soon as Cowzilla rips
the roof off and plucks me out.
That's a lousy attitude Tommy. You don't
even know what this girl looks like.
Yeah I know, but it's just not fair,
dad. Mom should have asked me first.
What's the big deal?
You take her to the dance,
you stiff-arm her through
a couple of numbers, you
let her graze over the buffet and fill
her 4 stomachs, and you bring her home.
- She's here. She's here!
- How bad is it?
OK. Look. Try not to stare.
- Hi, Marjorie. How are you?
- Nice to meet you, mr. Brooks.
It's nice to meet you. Come on in, OK?
I'm gonna say something now.
That may have been it.
Hi, Marjorie. Look at you.
You look so pretty. I love that dress.
Isn't that a pretty dress, Tom?
You know, thanks for doing this, Tom.
Total drag taking out
the new girl, right?
Hey, at one time or another,
we've all been the new girl.
You know what? Honey, hair is starting
to fall in the back. Let me help you.
Let me. Let me talk to you.
Tom, Let's go. Come on.
- Are you OK?
- No, I'm not OK.
My heart's beating so fast,
my tie is moving.
All right, look. OK.
Here's some money. OK?
OK. Do I give it to her
now or when we come home?
That's for snacks at the dance.
Sorry. I'm just...
just a little nervous, you know?
It's a pocket. OK. You all right?
Let me help calm your fears
a little here, OK?
You don't have to change the oil
in your car every 3,000 miles.
It's OK to do it every 5,000 miles.
That's fine.
What does that have to do with my date?
Nothing. I'm just trying to get
your head out of it, OK? Let's go.
Hey, Tom, come on.
Marjorie's mom's waiting.
Nice to see you, mrs. Brooks.
Nice to meet you, mr. Brooks.
Let's go, Tom.
I just want to let you know that
I am completely unprepared for this
and I blame both of you.
Are you aware that Tom just left
the house with a grown woman?
She's 15, Walter.
Was she sent from some
Island to protect mankind?
She and her family just
moved here from iowa.
Of course. Corn.
Congratulations taking over
the reins of team Allison.
Yeah. I hope you do a better job with
the franchise than I ever did? Come on!
Can we just settle for a high-five,
whatever it is your people do?
I brought over the cds of the potential
wedding bands you asked for.
We got Dixieland, Disco...
I even threw in some Country-Western
for the Texas Krandalls.
The texas Krandalls.
So when they say, "rember the alamo,"
you do.
Very funny, Gary.
I rember that joke fondly the next time
I'm lying on top of your former wife.
I'm gonna go put my bag
in your room, OK, Allison?
Wait a minute.
Why is he going to your bedroom?
I flooded his house.
The least I can do is
put him up for a couple days
and let him sleep in the master bedroom.
- And you'll be sleeping...
- In the guest bedroom.
Walter, wait a minute.
You're not jealous, are you?
Of Gary?
How long is he gonna be staying?
Allison. I forgot to tell you,
I might have exaggerated
a little bit with this girl
that works down at the coffee shop.
So if the phone rings, please answer,
"senator Brooks'office."
Two days, tops.
So, I'll see you tomorrow at school?
Promise me you're gonna have lunch
with me. I don't want to eat by myself.
Tomorrow's meatloaf day,
so I'll bring a Beaujolais.
- Dad! Dad!
- Hey, son, how are you?
Well, I think it's safe to say
that I'm in really over my head here.
Why, what happened?
I don't know if you've noticed or not,
but Marjorie's kind of hot.
The law doesn't really let me have
this conversation with you, but...
I understand the words you're saying.
I mean, we were the center
of attention all night,
and people were staring
and snapping pictures.
And then the coach slapped
on the shoulder and told me
he can use someone like me on defense.
I'm starting next week, and I don't
even know what sport I'm playing.
All right. Calm down.
When you're with a girl like Marjorie,
you're gonna draw a lot of attention?
All right. It's like driving a Ferrari?
When you're next to something
that's sleek and beautiful.
Again, I have to go with the car
metaphor for legal purposes.
People are gonna notice, you know?
I don't think I can handle that.
You know,
I'm an under-the-radar kind of guy.
Didn't a part of you
tonight like that attention?
Come on. Let me hear it. You liked it.
Yes. OK? I loved it. I felt like a god!
You felt like a god! Yes! All right!
Now go upstairs and put on
your pajamas and get ready for bed.
And tomorrow,
you sit with her at lunchtime,
and you're gonna be
the coolest guy in school.
You know,
I'm finally cooler than Randy Wilcox.
And he brought his own
son to health class.
Hey, Roomie. You know I forgot
how much I loved living here?
Gary, did you shave in
the kitchen sink a while ago?
Yes, I did. Don't worry, though.
It was mostly my face.
What are you doing?
I'm planning a wedding, Gary,
and I'm on hold with a realtor.
I'm thinking about selling
the house once I move in with Walter.
It's Allison Brooks. I spoke with
you last week. I have this wonder...
Yeah, and we saw your ad
on the bus bench. Very nice smile.
- You can't sell our house.
- No, but I can sell my house.
No. In this economy? You'd be crazy.
Let me rent it from you.
OK. What?
You don't want to uproot the kids.
They live in the house.
They have all these
great memories here.
Think of all the dead pets
buried in the backyard.
You know? Some family comes in,
they want to put in a pool, they start
digging. Next thing you know, there's
a hamster with a badge
asking a lot of questions.
I... i don't know. I mean, Gary,
I would be your landlord.
Yes, you would. You'd be my landlord,
and if I fell behind on the rent,
you could just throw
me out in the dead of winter.
- You would love that.
- I would love that.
It's perfect! So? So?
OK. Yeah, you can rent my house.
Jessica, i'm back!
You named our house "Jessica"?
When you're in prison, you get lonely,
Allison. You start to name stuff.
This is perfect. It's just
like old times. Except good.
Allison, your llama got loose.
What are you doing out there?
When I was here earlier,
I think I left my keys.
Yeah, there they are,
right where I left them.
So, what are you two doing?
Well, I am planning a wedding,
Gary is bothering me,
and you're obviously here
because you're jealous.
All right, so what if I am? I think it's
inappropriate that Gary is staying here.
There are hotels and hostels.
I could even make room at my place.
There's a pull-out
couch in the train room.
You know, Walter,
I don't like this side of you.
We're getting married,
and then you don't even trust me?
- I mean, what does that say about us?
- Wait a min, you two. Knock it off
OK? Let's just slow things
down for a second here.
Krandall has a train room?
But I know what this is.
It's just pre-wedding jitters, OK?
Let's not lose sight of
what's important here, OK?
And that is me moving out of
my dump and moving back here, OK?
Walter, you know how I feel about Gary.
I mean, I would not sleep with
Gary if it would save his life.
Which, by the way,
I think that was the way he tricked
me into doing it the first time.
All I said was,
I didn't know how much time I had left.
- And in all fairness, do any of us?
- Yeah. Well...
if I was planning on sleeping with Gary,
I would express my disgust
as vigorously as you just did.
Oh, my god. I can't believe
you are acting so irrational.
I can't deal with this right now.
I'm gonna run a bath,
take a sleeping pill, and go to bed.
If we wind up sleeping together,
you should know
I'm a man that likes to be held.
- Good morning.
Mango.
Bear claw?
Walter, what...
What are you doing here?
I came over with a box
of apology bear claws.
The question is,
what are you two doing here?
Yeah. Gary, what are you doing here?
You told me to sleep in here!
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I took a sleeping pill.
I just I must have, you know,
stumbled in here by accident.
- Why were you spooning me?
- Why were you backing up into me?
Hey. You know what?
When you get spooned, you back in.
That's the way I was raised.
And to think you accused
me of being overly jealous.
What, were you just...
You just walked into my house?
- You're in bed with another man.
- Please. It's not a man. It's Gary.
Exactly!
She's right, Krandall. Nothing happened.
It was just like when we were married.
Mom, where...
- What is everybody doing in here?
- Bear claw, Louise?
- Can i, mom?
- Yeah, grab one for your brother.
Thank you, dr. Krandall.
Our ride to school is here.
Have a great day.
Tommy, I have no clue what's going on in
here, but we get sugar for breakfast!
Remember, honey,
family stuff is private!
Look. Walter, I know what this must
look like, but you have to believe us.
This was an accident.
I know exactly what it looks like,
and it was no accident.
Wait a minute.
Don't throw away your marriage
with Allison. And most importantly,
you're gonna blow my shot at
getting back together with Jessica.
- Who is Jessica?
- It's the name he calls the house.
It's a prison thing.
I'm sorry to disappoint you and Jessica,
but there isn't gonna be a wedding.
Allison clearly isn't
ready to be my wife.
Walter, wait a minute!
You can't leave like this!
I believe I can, and I will!
My god, walter fell down the stairs!
Jessica, what have you done?
Walter, are you all right?
No, I'm fine.
I've never been good at storming out.
I have small feet
and a high center of gravity.
Excellent save on the bear claws,
Krandall.
Here, let me. Let me help you up.
No, leave me alone.
I'm gonna sit here and say my piece.
OK. Look. Walter, why would you
say I don't want to get married?
Because every one of your actions,
starting with flooding Gary's house,
is explainable on a subconscious level.
May I elaborate?
No. I don't think it's good
to elaborate after a fall.
Gary, come on. Walter, go on.
Gary told you not to run the dishwasher,
yet you did,
knowing it would flood his house
and he'd need a place to stay.
You're saying I did all
this deliberately just
so I could get him over here
and get into bed with him?
- Exactly.
- You're wrong.
The only reason Allison flooded
my house is because she lives
to make my life miserable,
and the only reason i'm here
is so she can make my life
miserable and save on gas.
No. Walter's right. I did this all
subconsciously knowing that Walter
was so jealous that if he
caught us in bed together, he would
call off the wedding.
God, it was all so deliberate.
Right down to the sleeping pills.
What is this,
an old episode of "quincy"?
You can say it, Mango.
You're not ready to get married.
No. No, don't say it, Mango.
- Don't say it.
- No, he's right.
I don't want to get married.
Sure, you do! Yes, you do!
Look how handsome this guy is.
You love him, he loves you,
and he's just.
He's two titanium hips away
from walking down the aisle.
It's like our whole relationship
was just a reaction
to my marriage with Gary, wasn't it?
Kiss her, Krandall. Kiss your woman.
Walter, you are a loving
and kind man, but I cannot marry
you just because you're, like,
the complete opposite of Gary.
I understand, Mango.
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't heartbroken.
But I'm gonna let you go,
and I'm gonna do it with dignity.
Starting now.
Cranberry, I'm gonna get you some ice.
Gary, would you help this wonderful,
sweet man to the sofa?
- Man, I can't believe it.
- No, I'm afraid she's gone, Gary.
This is where they've been
sending my "sports illustrated."
The baseball cards are done.
Well, let's see them. Let's see them.
What have we got? Harmon killebrew.
He's hot.
For what it's worth, you know,
i'm sorry you couldn't move
back into your old place. But, hey,
at least Allison didn't marry a guy
she wasn't in love with?
You see my crockpot?
It's over there.
Hey, dad. Hey, Dennis.
Your dad tells me you're
driving a Ferrari.
- I was driving a Ferrari. Was.
- What do you mean, was?
We were sitting outside
the lunchroom, and
I went inside to grab some milk, and...
she's gone.
Couldn't have been more than 30 seconds.
Whoever took her must have
known what he was doing.
You know, I never had to worry
about that with my old girlfriend.
I could leave Danielle anywhere.
You could leave my wife
on the front lawn with her robe open,
no one would take her.
Look. Son,
it's better to have driven a Ferrari
and lost than to have
never driven a Ferrari.
It's Danielle.
Looks like I'm back to riding the bus.
Team Subs-Addicts"