Hi, Gary.
Hi Dad.
Hi sweetie.
Oh, wow. Reading the newspaper.
I'm impressed.
I'm just seeing what's on TV.
Oh, my gosh.
Jon Cryer documentary.
"from duckie to emmy."
Hmm.
Uh, listen,
Gary, we have to
talk to Louise,
But first we have
to deal with Tom,
Who, if he
would stop pouting
in the car,
Would come out
and tell you
what happened.
Uh, Louise,
would you get daddy
a beer, please?
Yeah, sure.
Gary, do you
really think
it's a good idea
To have Louise get
your drinks for you?
Yes.
Um, I used
to get them myself.
This way, I don't
have to get them myself.
It's totally bogus.
Take it easy, man.
What's goin' on?
Well, I tried out for
the Lakeside wrestling club.
Lakeside wrestling?
Hey, just like
your old man, huh?
Yeah.
All right. How'd it go?
I'll tell you
how it went.
Ok, I wrestled
the coach's son,
And I totally pinned him,
but then I got cut,
And he had
a spot on the team.
Well, that doesn't
make any sense.
If you pin, you're in.
That's how it's
always worked.
Who's the coach
over there?
Uh, Joe Campbell.
You remember him
from high school?
Soup? I remember
soup Campbell.
I'm pretty sure
he likes to be called Joe now.
Ah, well,
that's too bad for soup,
Because unfortunately
in the real world,
You don't outrun
a perfectly good nickname
Just 'cause
you wanna go back
to your real name.
Works both ways, too.
I went to school with
a kid named Wang Chin.
He begged
for a nickname.
Yeah. Well, I totally
pinned him, and it's not fair.
Don't worry. I'll talk
to soup Campbell.
He owes me a favor.
We wrestled together
in high school.
Let's just say, uh,
I did him a solid, ok?
You do your homework.
I'll straighten it out.
All right?
Here, daddy.
Ah, daddy's little girl.
Look at that.
I hope you're happy
when Louise decides
To tend bar
at Dublin's Pub.
Are you--
is that someth--
Is that something
she's shown interest in?
No. No. Man.
On that note,
Louise, I'm gonna
Show your father
your history test.
Ohh. Wait. You got a "d"
on your history test?
You're the smartest kid
in the class.
I don't know
how it happened,
But it was bound to
eventually,
Just like when you say Tom
is due to get an "A" someday.
Law of averages, right?
It's what we're
all countin' on.
Here. Look, uh,
honey, it's--
It's unfamiliar
territory,
But I guess we're
supposed to impose
Some--some kind
of a punishment, right?
But how do you
punish Louise?
Take away her books?
Make her play?
Hey, Tommy, if you
came home with a "D,"
How would we punish you?
Uh, probably
somewhere
in the area
Of no video games,
phone, tv until
my grades improve.
But that depends on
how much sass I'm
dishin' your way.
Uh, ok, Louise,
So you're
gonna get
the Tom special.
Uh, you can dish
a little sass,
Because that
comes with
the package.
[sighs] that sounds
very appropriate. Thank you.
Ok...
Something is
going on with her.
I'm really worried.
I don't know.
Drugs? Pot?
I shouldn't. Uh-uh.
Gary Unmarried 2x15
Gary's Big Mouth
Original Air Date on March 3, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Hey, soup.
Hey, guy, name's Joe.
No one's called me
soup since--well, well.
Gary Brooks.
How you been, man?
Me? Not bad. Not bad.
You got your own
sports radio show.
Yes, I do.
Dream come true.
You listen to it?
Yeah, really not my thing.
I'm all about coaching here
And holdin' down the fort
at Valencia Public Storage.
You lookin' to streamline?
I can put you in a 10-by-12
for 75 bucks a month,
And that's climate controlled.
I'm divorced, soup.
I, uh--I own nothing.
I came by to talk to you
About my son Tommy,
Tommy Brooks.
He said he tried out
for the wrestling team.
I was wondering
what happened.
Yeah. I want you to know I did
everything I could for him.
It broke my heart
to see him fail.
Uh, fail. That's--
that's the thing.
He--he said
he pinned your son.
Heh heh heh heh.
Pin's an exaggeration.
It's more like he
held him down for 3 seconds.
However you want
to explain it, soup,
My son beat your kid.
He deserves to be
on the team, you know?
Yeah, I just felt
in the long run,
My son donny
has more potential.
All right,
for the sake of argument,
Let's not go by your feelings
and go with maybe--
I don't know--logic.
My son beat your son.
He deserves to be on the team.
Sorry. 12 spots,
12 wrestlers,
one broken heart.
Tough nuts, huh?
I didn't wanna
bring this up, soup,
But, uh--ahem.
You owe me.
How do I owe you?
Senior year,
I let you beat me
So you can
come to states
With the rest of us,
remember?
You're crazy.
I straight-up beat your ass.
What?! I let you win.
You begged me.
Y-you said your dad
would kick your ass
If you didn't
get to state.
Sorry. I don't
remember it that way.
I guess we just
agree to disagree.
Uh, yeah. No. No.
We--we don't.
We don't agree to disagree.
I completely
threw that match for you.
If we wrestled in real life,
You wouldn't score one point
against me. You know it.
My son Tommy deserves
to be on the team.
He beat your kid.
Well, he didn't beat him
enough to make the team.
I'm sorry. Donny's just
a better wrestler.
Dad.
I'm tired. Can I go home
and watch tv now?
That depends.
How many'd you do?
3.
You did 3 push-ups?
Candy bars.
You "did"
3 candy bars?
Get out of here.
Don't come back
Until you've done
20 push-ups.
It's not fair.
I hate wrestling.
Look, this is ridiculous.
My son beat your son.
He deserves to be on the team.
You're not gonna
get away with this, soup.
Wait. We have soup?
You know why
he's doin' this, right?
Because every time
he looks at you or Tommy,
It's gonna remind him
of that moment in his life
when it counted most
And he couldn't get it done.
He's feeling shame, man.
Well, you know
how I feel about
shame, Curtis.
I think as soon
as something happens
in your life,
You just let it go,
forget about it
Like it never
even happened.
You're on.
I wanted to talk
about something
That happened
20 years ago.
I let this guy win
a wrestling match
'cause I was being
nice, and now he
resents me for it,
So he's taking it
out on my son.
'cause I was being
so we're talkingw he
about unfairme for it,
Coaching practices
in children's sports.
Who's got a take?
Let's hear it.
We got Aaron in Chino.
Aaron,
you are on the air.
What do you got for me?
Yeah, a similar thing
happened to my kid
in little league
Because I stole
the coach's wife.
You know who gets hurt?
The kids do.
Yeah, that's
exactly right, Aaron.
Except in my case,
where the coach got hurt
When I showed up
to the game with a tire iron--
Ok, thank you, Aaron.
All right, let'so
to another call.
We have s.C. In--
what is this?
Wine country?
Soup: Yeah, as in
stop whining about your kid
when he doesn't make the cut.
Well, well, well.
Looks like we got soup Campbelll
on the line,
Aka the weasel
who blackballed my son
From makin'
the wrestling team,
even though I let him
Beat me in high school
so his sorry rear end
Could go to state
with the rest of us.
I thought you didn't
listen to my show, soup.
I'm sick of you
claiming you let me win.
Not only did I beat you then.
I'd be glad to give you
another beating now.
Soup, as much
as I'd love to drive
your face into the mat,
I hate to break it
to you, but I'm
a grown man now, ok?
A grown man now would
strap on his singlet and dance.
What am I supposed
to do with this guy?
The man is
callin' you out.
You can't host
a sports show
And then back down
when someone steps to you.
Soup: What's it
gonna be, Brooks?
You gonna sac up?
You gonna change
the name of your show
To "the score
with fairy Brooks"?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Timeout, soup.
You callin' me a fairy?
Hey, if the wings fit
and the wand's tiny...
Ok, soup,
you wanna go,
we'll go.
But after I pin
your ass,
My son Tommy is
on that wrestling team.
You follow me?
You got it.
Bring your "a" game,
'cause this soup's
about to boil over.
Good! I hope
it does boil over,
'cause I'm gonna
bring the spoon,
And I'm gonna eat you
like you're
The most tastiest soup
that ever existed.
Ok, Louise, there was
a famous division
Between the north
and the south
In the civil war
called the...
No clue.
Uh, Mason...
Mason-dix...
Mason-dixie chicks.
No!
Louise, no. I--
I don't get it.
You--you're
a straight-a student
in every other subject.
Mom, maybe we just found
the one thing I'm not good at.
Maybe we all need
to accept the fact that
I'm not the perfect kid.
No. Louise, you are
the perfect child since
the day you were born.
Your head was shaped
like an oval,
And you pointed your
toes on the way out.
Hey, is Tom home?
Uh, no, not yet.
Honey, could you
Excuse us just
for a second?
Yeah, sure.
[sighs] ok, something
is happening with her.
I mean, she doesn't
know her history,
But I--I actually think
she's just pretending.
Why do you think
everybody has an agenda?
Maybe she
doesn't know her stuff.
Not everyone's
workin' an angle,
Like, uh, the salesgirl
at Victoria Secret
That you said was
trying to hit on you
'cause she liked
the way your bra fit.
Ok, I'm sorry.
I didn't imagine that, Gary, ok?
She slipped a wine cooler
in my dressing room
And told me that
my bra would look better
on the floor of her Miata, ok?
Look, Louise,
she knows the stuff,
But she's faking it,
and I don't know why.
I don't know.
Maybe she's, uh,
tired of the pressure
Of trying to be perfect
all the time.
I--I know the feeling.
I'd love a day off.
I'd love to see
a day on, gar.
Hey, thanks a lot, dad.
You completely
humiliated me at school.
Wait. Honey, hang on.
What's wrong? What happened?
Dad went on the radio
show and said he would
wrestle my coach
And if he wins, that I
get a spot on the team.
Now everyone at school's
saying the only
way I can get in
Is if my dad fights
my battles for me.
This is
a good thing, Tommy.
I beat your coach,
I settle an old score,
Plus you get
on the team.
It's a win-win.
I'm just tryin'
to help you out.
Yeah, well,
I don't want your help.
If you fighting my battles
is the only way I can get in,
I don't wanna be on at all.
Whoa. What's up
with that guy?
He was full
of thank-yous
When I helped him
pull his head out
of that pumpkin.
Ok. Look, I know
this is the last thing
you wanna hear right now,
But I think
you have to back down
from this fight, Gary.
Tom's feelings are
what's important here.
I can't back down,
allison.
I'll totally
lose my rep.
I can't lose my rep.
Gary, I know backing down
is the hardest thing
in the world for you.
Oh, you're dead wrong,
And I'll never
admit to that.
All right,
I'll back down.
All right.
I'll go talk to soup.
I'll take care of it.
Good. Good.
You're doing the right thing,
and you're a good father, Gary.
By the way, how did,
uh, Tom's head end up
in a pumpkin in the first place?
Ha! I dared him.
Hey, soup,
we gotta talk.
What do you want, Brooks?
All right.
You here to beg for mercy?
No. I'm here
to back out of the match
for my son's sake, ok?
Oh, that's so touching.
I think I just
lactated myself.
All right, knock it off.
Here's the thing.
I know every single
resentment you have
about high school
A-and me,
you're taking it out
on my son. It's not ok.
I'm gonna go on the air.
I'm gonna tell
all my listeners
That I'm backin' out
of the match,
And I'll take
whatever repercussions
come with it,
As long as you let my
son try out for the team
fair and square, ok?
All right, I'll do that.
As long as you announce
to all your fans
That not only are you
a quitter, you're a liar.
You tell 'em I won
that match in high school
fair and square.
But you didn't.
Duh.
That's why
I want you to say it.
Fine. I'll do it.
Ok. I'll give Tom
another tryout,
But this time, it's not
gonna be against
my load of a son.
He's gotta beat
the best wrestler
in his weight class.
All right.
It's a deal.
Oh, uh, hey, soup...
Remember junior year,
we had that crazy
outbreak of jock itch?
The one that kept us
out of divisionals.
You know
who that started with?
Who?
Your mom.
Gary: Look, there comes
a time in every man's life
Where he has to bite
the bullet and he
just has to admit
That he's been wrong
about something for years.
This better be
about me.
I said on the radio
that I let soup Campbell
Win a wrestling match
against me in 1988.
The truth is soup Campbell
beat me, Gary Brooks,
Fair and square.
Wow. I can't believe
how well he's handling this.
So the match is off,
Because I am both
a liar and a quitter.
[no audio]
Daniel, don't chicken out
on me now.Liar and a quitter.
If you lock in a "c"
and I manage a "d,"
Everything will go
according to plan.
Do I have your word?
Good.
Did you see
"Jersey Shore" last night?
Snooki is a hot mess.
Ok. Gotta go. Bye.
Hi, Louise.
Oh, hi, mom. I'm gonna
go do my homework.
No, no. No, you're not.
Listen, um...
I need some help
with some U.S.
History questions,
So, uh, can you sit?
Yeah.
Um, so Lewis and Clark,
They died
in the Alamo, right?
Uh, I--I think so.
Yeah. Yeah. And you know
George Washington,
When he
freed the slaves,
Was that before
or after he invented
the light bulb?
Um, I- couldn't tell you
one way or the other.
Hmm.
Ok.
Hey, you--you know
who was a pretty
good president?
Nixon.
Yeah, if you like a leader
who escalated a questionable war
By launching
an offensive into Cambodia
After winning the election
on a secret plan to end
that very war.
But you might be right.
Oh, gosh!
Come on, Louise. I know
you know your history.
Why are you
pretending you don't?
We're trying to help
our friend Marjorie.
Our class is on a curve,
and some of our grades
Are so high that she
might fail and get held back.
Honey,
you're a good friend,
Ok, but you can't
let your grades suffer.
If you wanna help her,
Why don't you
offer to tutor her
after school?
That's not going to be enough.
She's a terrible test taker.
You know what?
That's the only way I'm
gonna let you help her.
Ok? She's gonna
have the same
problems next year.
What are you gna do,
tank your tests again?
Uh, no way.
Next year, colleges start
looking at transcripts.
I'm going to drop her
like a hot rock.
Oh. Good.
All right, so let me
teach you some
takedowns, ok?
Hey, dad, if I wanna get
on the wrestling team,
I wanna do it myself.
Ok, but you
gotta be prepared,
'cause you don't know
what I went through to--
You're gonna
make the team.
You just gotta win.
Let me show you
some takedowns,
show you some moves,
Show you what it's lik
to be real man.
Be a real man.
Ok. Curtis, get down
on your hands and knees.
You...
Just a reminder. We have
to see each other
at work on Monday. Ok?
Just help me out here.
I'm gonna show my son
some moves.
All right, son,
the key to establishing
dominance in a match
Is you gotta really
ride your man.
Ride him good, all right?
Control his hips.
Make sure you're
the boss of his hips.
You stay back
behind his bottom, where
you can control everything.
Don't be afraid
to throw the cross-face.
Really get it in there.
You can feel his lips
right up against your skin.
Take your knuckles.
Dig it into his hips.
Aah! Come on! Hey!
Man, I might wanna
have kids someday.
All right.
Wait. You're gonna
have kids with your hips?
Yeah, man.
I--I need my hips
To do the thing
to get the kid.
All right.
All right, get up.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's just go over
what we learned, ok?
Yeah, I got it, dad.
Hand control,
stay off my back,
And if I'm doin'
the fireman's carry,
Don't be afraid
to shoot the crotch.
You gotta shoot
the crotch, right?
Bump, bump.
Both: Shoot the crotch!
You gotta shoot it
in there.
Go do some homework
or somethin', ok?
He doesn't understand.
It's killin' me
That I had to backut
of that match with--with soup.
It's makin' me nuts.
Yeah, but you don't want
Tom to win for you.
You want Tom
to win for him.
I understand that,
But let me
tell you somethin'.
I would love a piece
of that soup guy.
I know.
All right.
See you later.
Thanks for helping out.
No problem, brother.
Hey, just for the record,
When my hand slipped
off your hip, I was
goin' for your ankle.
We don't need to talk
about it. It just--
it never happened.
All right, son, don't forget
that fireman's carry.
Shoot the crotch, ok?
Ok, yeah.
'cause whenever
you're in there,
keep your back straight.
Shoot the crotch.
Ok.
Just shoot it
right up there, all right?
Allison, why don't
you come on over here
and help us out?
Hasn't my crotch done
enough for this family?
Uh, honey,
uh, no pressure,
But here comes
a very pretty girl.
Hey. I'm Jessica.
Are you wrestling next?
Uh, yeah. I'm Tom.
Are you, uh--
you gonna watch?
Yeah, I got
a really good seat,
on top of you
In the middle
of the mat.
Oh.
Well,
that sounds awesome,
But I gotta wrestle
someone first.
Um, honey,
I think you're
wrestling her.
Oh, god.
Dad, I'm wrestling
a girl?
Ok, you didn't
train me for this.
How am I supposed to shoot
the crotch, all right?
In health class,
They told me to ask
permission before
I shoot the crotch.
Soup,
what the heck's
goin' on here?
You tryin'
to embarrass my kid
or what?
You said you wanted him
to do it on his own,
So I put him up against
the best wrestler on the team.
That's Jessica. But now
that I think about it,
If he loses to a girl,
that'd be pretty embarrassing.
Oops.
All right, Tommy, big deal.
You're wrestling a girl.
Just one thing.
Don't let it
get in the way, ok?
Ok, dad,
I don't know how much
you know about girls,
But there's
more than a few things
that can get in the way.
All right, shake hands.
And wrestle.
Gary: Easy.
Easy, guys.
All right,
shoot it, Tommy!
Shoot!
Ok!
Take it.
But be
a gentleman,
honey.
Ow. Ow.
You're hurting me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry. Oh, god!
No!
[blows whistle]
Winner!
No!
Uh, honey, honey,
Uh, why don't we get
some sweatpants on you?
I think Jessica
realizes how much
You enjoyed the match.
There you go.
That didn't take long.
Ah, I'm sorry, dad.
I know how much
You humiliated yourself
for me to get this shot.
Plus I, uh--I totally
got to second base without
even touching first.
You know what I mean?
Don't worry
about it, Tommy.
Some people
just don't know how
to play fair, ok?
All right,
you be a good sport.
You go over there
and shake Jessica's
hand, ok?
For what it's worth,
Gary, um,
I'm proud of you.
Proud of me
for what?
No matter what
I did, I couldn't
help Tommy.
Look, you know what?
You did.
You let him know
that it's ok for a man
To swallow his pride
when someone else's
feelings are on the line.
I mean,
that's a much bigger deal
Than getting
on any team, Gary.
Besides, look.
He doesn't look like
he's suffering too much.
Hey, uh, dad,
Jessica just told me
About this ballroom dancing
class she takes after school,
And she wants me
to be her partner.
Oh, instead
of wrestling?
Yeah. Well, I mean,
ballroom dancing with Jessica
Sounds like a lot more fun
than holding some sweaty guy
between my thighs.
Yeah. Tell me about it.
Another Brooks
gets pinned.
The dynasty
of failure continues.
Heh heh. Ok, soup.
That's terrific.
Look, Tommy, if it's
all right with you
And if your mom
doesn't think
I'm setting
a bad example,
I think
I'd like to really
Kick soup Campbell's
ass on this mat
once and for all.
I'm good.
Go for it.
Let's go, soup.
You and me
right now.
I'm havin' soup
for dinner.
Dad, can we
have soup for dinner?
Shut up, donny.
All right, I got
30 seconds to spare.
You on top
or me on top?
I'll start on bottom.
All right.
I figure you could use
all the help you can get.
Do us a favor, allison.
Count us in.
Uh, 1, 2, 3.
Wrestle.
Ohh! Ow!
I think you broke my ribs!
Oh, really?
No, not really.
Yes. Ha!
How's that feel, soup?
Not so good. I think
I fell on my keys.
Gah! You ready to give up?
Are you kidding me?
I got you right
where I want you.
I think you sat
in some gum.
That's not my ass, soup.
That's yours.
You think
I'm letting go,
you're high.
I will die on this mat.
You will be pinning
my corpse.
[cell phone rings]
Ah, that's my phone.
Do you mind?
Nah, I don't mind.
Wh-where is it? Right here?
Wait. No funny business.
Ok.
Joe Campbell's phone.
Oh, hi, Robin.
[whispering]
it's your wife.
tell her I'm not here.
Ok.
Uh, Robin, Joe stepped out
for a minute.
It's Gary Brooks.
I'm good. Thanks.
Uh, can I take
a message, though?
Pick up, uh,
skim milk and eggs
And remind him to take
his lipitor. You got it.
Bye, Robin.
Don't forget
to take your Lipitor.
Cholesterol?
Yeah. Ah, they think
it's genetic,
But what
do they know?
Doctors, right?
Yeah. Uh,
they're closin' up.
How long have we been here?
I don't know.
I'm starvin'. You wanna
order a pizza or something?
Aw, I can't.
The cheese.
Oh, right. Sorry.
Don't let it
stop you, though.
If you get me
a salad,
I'll be fine.
Salad? I'd rather
have the pizza.
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --