My friend Miranda was dating
Thomas John Anderson...
an up-and-coming
New York playwright.
Oh, God.
That was wonderful.
Things were great
except for one thing.
I'll be right back.
Immediately after sex...
he'd hop out of bed and shower.
- Be right back.
- Night after night, the same thing.
- I'll be right--
- Yeah.
She decided to confront Thomas John
Anderson as soon as he dried off.
- So, what's with the showers?
- What do you mean?
You always get up and shower
right after we're done.
I'm starting to feel like it's me.
No, it's not you.
It's just--
- What?
- It's just a habit I have.
Growing up, the nuns told us
sex was a sin.
So I just got into the habit
of taking a shower after l...
you know, came.
Oh, the nuns.
Miranda suddenly realized
she was dating "Catholic Guy."
So you thing the water serves as
a retro baptism kind of thing?
Beats me. If I'd known
he was Catholic...
I never would've gone out
with him in the first place.
- They should make them wear a sign.
- Single people in New York...
rarely ask about their dates'
religious backgrounds...
for the same reason they don't ask
the number of former sex partners:
- too scary.
- I mean, he's a rational...
Iogical guy
in every respect but this.
Clean. You forgot clean.
He's a clean guy.
Leave it to me to find the only
religious guy left in Manhattan.
New York is a city
filled with places to worship.
But it recently dawned on me...
the only time I ever heard
anyone mention going into one...
was for a singles mixer.
Are relationships
the religion of the '90s?
Having been raised in the church
of "be nice to people...
and don't talk
with your mouth full"...
I decided to check out some more
traditional religious types...
in their natural habitat.
As I watched people leaving church,
I was amazed at how they looked.
Valentino, Escada,
Oscar de la Renta.
What is it about God and fashion
that go so well together?
And suddenly, there he was
wearing Armani on Sunday.
Mr. Big.
I admit it was kind of a shock.
Up until that moment, I thought
he only believed in the Yankees.
Hello there, churchgoer.
- What are you doing here?
- Research.
I'm doing a column on closet
Presbyterians. You know any?
Actually, I'm an atheist,
but don't tell the minister.
Who's the mystery woman?
My mother.
- I take her to church every Sunday.
- Really?
I'm so loving that.
How come you never told me?
Well, you write every Sunday, so--
So every Sunday-- church.
Right.
I've got 20 minutes
before my racquetball game.
- Why don't we have coffee?
- I can't. I'm on deadline...
and this cappuccino
just kicked in, so--
So?
God bless.
It was one of those awkward
relationship moments...
where you feel like you know
nothing about the person...
you thought you knew
everything about.
He goes to church
with his mother?
- That can't be good.
- Don't listen to her.
A man who cares about mother
makes a wonderful husband.
- I think it's sweet.
- All religions are sweet...
until you get to that
shower-after-sex phase.
- Is he still doing that?
- It's amazing he has any skin left.
Have you tried
taking a shower with him?
I'm afraid he'll pull out
garlic and a cross.
So, which church
does his mother go to?
- Park Avenue Presbyterian.
- It's one of the best on the East Side.
What, are you rating churches?
ls there a Zagat guide for that?
Four stars, great bread,
disappointing wine selection.
The thing is, I'm dying
to meet his mother.
Can you imagine?
Getting on the good side of his
mother is like closing the deal.
- I'm sorry I'm late.
- It's about time.
I just had a five-hour lunch
with James.
Five-hour lunches.
I remember those.
Ladies, I have an announcement.
- Please don't laugh.
- What?
- I'm in love.
Samantha uttering
those words to us...
was an event as unfathomable...
as Moses parting the Red Sea.
It all started
a couple of weeks ago...
on a particularly blah
Wednesday night.
Samantha decided to treat herself
to a night of great music.
I couldn't help but notice
how you move to the music.
It's beautiful.
Well, I love jazz.
That's pretty clear.
Are you a musician?
Yeah.
Trapped in the body of a lawyer.
Well, we won't tell anyone.
May I join you?
Sure.
After they closed the jazz joint
they walked and talked for blocks.
You have to at least
try one of the glazed.
It's a little bit of heaven.
Heavenly.
And I never thought I'd get there.
Why not?
An angel like you?
And then Samantha did something
rather shocking for a first date--
she didn't ask him home.
Thanks, James.
I had a wonderful time.
Can I see you again?
I'd love that.
And with that one touch,
Samantha...
who was never a believer
in relationships...
suddenly became a convert.
I'd totally given up on the idea
that you could actually talk to men.
- Don't spread that around.
- Before James...
all my conversations
consisted of two sentences--
"give it to me" and "go home."
And I owe it all to Charlotte.
Me? What did I do?
All that bullshit you spout...
about not sleeping with men
right away actually paid off.
If I'd fucked James already,
who knows where we'd be.
Wait. You haven't had sex yet?
Soon.
You know...
I think he's someone
I could actually marry.
Samantha, that's great.
The idea that Samantha could possibly
get married before she did...
shook Charlotte's beliefs
to the core.
She took some drastic action.
She made an appointment
to see Noanie Stine...
psychic to the stars
and a cosmic connection...
who lived in a brownstone between
Central Park West and Columbus.
- Is this you and Madonna?
- Yeah.
We go to the same Cabala class.
Now...
pick three cards, face down
with your left hand.
Charlotte had heard about Noanie
through a sorority sister...
whose marriage she had
very accurately predicted.
Now, is there one question
in particular?
Well, no.
Just--
There is.
When will I get married?
"Ace of wands." Prosperity.
"Nine of cups."
Strength and independence.
"The Hanged Man."
A new awakening.
You're a strong,
independent woman...
with great success in your future,
but I do not see marriage.
- Excuse me?
- I don't see it.
- What?
- I don't see marriage.
Well, how can you just
say that like that?
I mean, what about my feelings?
Honey, I'm a psychic.
I'm not a shrink.
So, who is the fabulous mother
in the hat...
and when do I get to
go to church with you two?
You want to go to church?
You say that like I'm
the antichrist or something.
It's just I never thought of you
as the church type.
Oh, really?
What type am l?
The incredibly beautiful
and intelligent type.
What religion are you?
I'm no one religion in particular.
I'm open to all.
- Kind of like a 7-Eleven?
- Come on.
I want to go to church with you and
your mommy. How about this Sunday?
Well, it's just
a private little thing...
my mother and I do,
just the two of us.
You want to go
to the Caribbean next week.
Sure. I'll go pack my jet ski.
No, I'm serious.
We could both use a vacation.
The sun, the sand, you and me.
You waiting on me.
- Can you get away?
- Yeah, but I can't afford it.
I'll tell you what.
I'll buy the tickets.
When we get to St. Barts,
you can buy me one big margarita.
Wait. I want to hold you.
- I'll be right back.
- Stay here a second.
Isn't this nice? Us together?
Yeah.
I'm just gonna go jump in the shower,
and then, boom, I'm all yours.
There's nothing sinful about sex.
Oh, really?
Well, thanks for clearing that up.
And what is that?
The gospel according to Miranda?
And next you're gonna say
that God made the body...
and if God made the body and sex
is an expression of that body...
how could anything made by that
God-made body be considered sin?
Well, yeah.
It's a miracle! I'm healed!
You're free to go work
with the lepers now.
I guess this means
I'm not going to hell.
Great news! Thank you, Miranda.
Thank you
for saving my immortal soul.
In her effort to help...
Miranda had accidentally detonated
some kind of Catholic guilt bomb.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
When I come out, I'd kind
of like it if you weren't here.
You got it.
Six months later,
that exact same speech...
would find its way into
Thomas John Anderson's...
hit Off-Broadway play
Shower of Shame.
Meanwhile, downtown...
Samantha was preparing
to see God.
I know it's only been
a couple of weeks...
but I love you, Samantha.
I love you too.
Oh, honey,
I can't wait any longer.
Just unzip and get over here.
Okay, I'm ready.
Put it in.
It is in.
Samantha said a little prayer
that he was kidding.
He wasn't.
Sunday morning. A time for rest.
A time for relaxation.
A time for spying.
The plan was simple.
Just get a look at the mother...
then Miranda and I
would go for eggs.
Look at how crowded it is.
What a sham.
Will you lighten up? It's a Presbyterian
church, not a Catholic one.
Catholics, Episcopalian,
Buddhists, Shakers, Quakers.
All the same, all designed
to fuck up our sex lives.
Here, pray.
There they are.
- Where?
- Right there.
As I watched Mr. Big standing
quietly next to his mother--
tall, proud, respectful--
I think I fell a little bit
more in love with him.
Let us pray.
- We come together--
- We're out of here.
Here they come.
Let's make a break for it.
No, they saw me.
I have to say hello.
I can't pray and run.
There they are.
Go. I'm fine.
Aren't you the young lady
who made all that noise?
Slippery gloves.
- 'Morning.
- Good morning.
- It's a lovely church.
- Yes, isn't it?
- Don't you think it's lovely?
- Mother, this is my friend Carrie.
I searched her face
looking for the light of recognition.
But there was nothing.
I'm going to say good-bye to the pastor.
It was lovely meeting you.
"My friend Carrie"?
You show up at church
after I asked you not to.
Are you testing me? Why all the
interest in meeting my mother?
- Has she even heard of me?
- She doesn't need to meet...
another girlfriend.
I didn't mean--
I mean...
I'll introduce you
as my girlfriend when I'm sure.
Look, I have to do things
on my time frame.
"Time frame"?
We've been going out for months.
I really don't know
what else to say to you.
We'll get there. You just
have to have a little faith.
- "Faith"?
- Yeah. Look.
In a couple of days we're going on
vacation. We can talk then.
Right now, I've got to get
my mother home. Okay?
Well, go.
Just go.
Move over.
I didn't leave.
You didn't seem fine.
He introduced me to his mother
as a friend.
She never heard of me.
That isn't a good sign.
- Maybe they're not that close.
- Don't lie. You're in a church.
I can't get inside.
I don't know what else I can do.
Late that night
in the Church of Disco...
Stanford invited everyone he knew...
to a party to introduce
a new fragrance--
Fallen Angel.
Also, he wanted to show off
his new boyfriend...
Allanne.
Isn't this fun? It's like hell
with a cover charge.
Carrie, this is Allanne.
- Hi. Nice to meet you finally.
- You too.
Did I tell you that Allanne
designed the Fallen Angel bottle?
Yes. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Excuse me for a second.
I just saw someone
I want to say hello to.
You know what we did today?
We shopped for Deco
cabinet handles for his armoire.
I turned into one of those
couples we hate and I'm loving it!
Stanford and Allanne
worshiped the same God--
style.
You all excited for the big vacation?
I don't know.
I can't help feeling...
Iike it's some sort of consolation prize
for not letting me in his life.
What is going on
with you two?
- We're not in the greatest place.
- What happened?
He wouldn't introduce me
to his mother.
Thanks.
Skipper. Hi.
It seems Stanford had invited
everyone in his Rolodex.
I was hoping I'd see you here.
I've been totally thinking
about you since we broke up.
- You have?
- Totally.
You look great.
Thanks. So do you.
Miranda looked at Skipper.
The months apart had shed
a new light on him.
Actually, they'd shed a new light
on his shower-free feelings about sex.
Later that night, the three of us
tracked Samantha to the ladies' room...
to get the lowdown
on her love life with James.
Here you are. We've been
looking for you everywhere.
So, how is everything?
She means have you and James
done it yet?
And?
- It's nice.
- I'm so happy for you.
Sweetie, what is it?
Nothing.
What's going on?
Why are you crying?
James has a small dick.
- It's not the end of the world.
- It's really small.
- How small?
- Too small.
- Size isn't everything.
- Three inches?
- Well--
- Hard?
- Is he a good kisser?
- Who the fuck cares?
His dick is like a gherkin!
I feel so terrible.
Listen to me. I'm a bad person.
Don't beat yourself up. You had certain
expectations and you're disappointed.
Why? Why?
Why does he have to have
a small dick?
- I really like him.
- I thought you loved him.
- We've all been there.
- That's for sure.
I was once with a guy the size of one
of those little miniature golf pencils.
Couldn't tell if he was
trying to fuck me or erase me.
I'm sorry. It's just-- It's funny.
Let's not lose perspective.
- There are ways to work around this.
- I don't want to.
I love a big dick.
I love it inside of me.
I love looking at it.
I love everything about it.
When I blow him, it's like...
nothing.
- Can you talk to him about it?
- No.
It's the only thing
we can't talk about.
- What am I gonna do?
- How is he with his tongue?
Charlotte left us all behind, telling
us she had another party to go to.
She took a cab to a part of town
never mentioned in the New Yorker.
Will I ever get married?
I call the power of all the saints.
St. Lazarus.
St. Rosa. Send me your guidance.
Send me the truth.
Send me an answer.
No yolk.
What does that mean?
You'll never be married.
You are cursed.
But do not worry.
For $100 dollars, we can remove it.
The entire way home, Charlotte berated
herself for being so foolish.
She simply refused
to give in to the idea...
that she would never get married.
Sorry.
All she had to do was keep
believing, and it would happen.
It was 3:00 a.m.
in the Church of Disco...
and Miranda couldn't believe
what she was about to say.
- You want to spend the night?
- The night? The whole night?
Yeah, the whole night.
- I knew we'd get back together.
- You did?
Yep.
Every night I'd light a candle
and say a little prayer.
You're a freak.
Samantha tried desperately to believe
that love was stronger than sex.
Why are you crying?
I'm just so happy.
I stayed up all night
questioning my faith in faith.
I mean, hadn't I had faith
in us all along?
Faith that all the withholding
would stop.
Faith that he's say "I love you."
Let's go!
Hey, hurry.
We're gonna miss the plane.
Wait, wait.
Put them down a second.
Just put them down.
What?
I need a sign.
I mean, you told me
to have faith, but, see...
I'm kind of losing mine, so...
I need a sign.
What, like in those old religious
movies? A voice from above?
Just tell me I'm the one.
You don't have to tell your mother
or the whole world, just--
Just tell me.
I can't do this.
Just get in the car. Please.
I can't.
I love you, but I can't.
So that's it?
After he left, I cried for a week.
And then I realized I do have faith.
Faith in myself.
Faith that I would one day
meet someone...
who would be sure
that I was the one.