Previously on "Desperate Housewives"...
Hi, Maisy
Are you having an affair with my husband?
Mistresses were confronted..
Very good to be back
What's that?
I'm on house arrest
It's a condition of my bail
How are you going to work?
I can't. I can't do anything
The tables were turned
Good lord, that's Angela
And secrets from the past
I'm afraid you're mistaken
My wife's name was mary alice
Caught up with everyone
I'm such an idiot
And you're such a liar
Oh, and apparently,
a killer
Throughout even the most respectable
of neighborhoods,
you can hear the sound of scandal
Some scandals announce
themselves with a shout
Ida! Ida greenberg,
that is not your paper!
Some with a whisper
throw me a $20, and I'll hook you up
with free porn
And some with a bang
Get the hell off my lawn!
And once in a great while,
there comes a scandal so deliciously sordid,
its roar drowns out all other noise
its roar drowns out
all other noise
So your husband -- does he have any idea how many men
pay for the privilege of sleeping in this bed?
There's not a lot
of sleeping going on --
- not if I'm doing my job right
- Ha ha ha
So how do you want
to get started?
With these ?
Well ... that's going to cost you extra
Maisy gibbons, you're
under arrest for solicitation
What?
Please turn and place
your hands on the bed
I'm sorry I'm -- I'm going
to have to ask you to leave now
Hey! Aah! You get off me!
- This is entrapment
- Right
You all are making
a gigantic mistake
Yeah, yeah Hey, fellas,
here's one for your memoirs
- Come on
- No! No!
No, don't you touch me!
- Would you get your hands off me!
- Take it easy, mrs Gibbons
Yes, the scandalous arrest
of maisy gibbons
would soon prove to be the shot
heard 'round the world
Take it easy, ma'am
Don't you put me in here!
It is often said that good news
travels fast,
but as every housewife knows,
bad news moves quite a bit faster
Tish? Hey, you are not going
to believe this
Maisy gibbons was arrested
- You cannot be serious
- Yes
- Hey, did you hear about maisy?
- I let my son spend the night at her house just last week
- She ...
Maisy gibbons running in handcuffs --
I'd have killed to see that
Stay put. I'll be right back
Ladies, please calm down, ma'am
This is just a precaution
If you'll just take a flyer
hey, guys. What's going on?
Oh, there's been
an outbreak of head lice
Head lice ?
These flyers detail all the important information
concerning the situation,
including the recommended
delousing combs
Delousing? Do they have to
make it sound so disgusting?
Does anybody know
where it started?
I'm sorry
That's confidential information
Barcliff maintains
a strict no-blame policy
Hey, guys, over here
I think parents have a right to know
who brought this into our school
Please calm down, ma'am
Our position is that there's nothing
to be gained by pointing fingers
To identify the child
who initiated the outbreak
might result in him or her
being subjected to ridicule
I, um, excuse me¡K¡K
- If you'll just take a flyer...
- stop scratching, stop scratching
Now, now, stop it
Guys, let's go, okay?
Stop scratching. I mean it Stop, stop
- Hey See you later
- Bye
Glued into the hair shaft,
and can only be removed ...
What the hell?
- Gabrielle!
- What?
Hey, gabrielle, I think
we got a problem here!
I can't hear you!
I said, I think we got a problem!
- The water's backing up here!
- What?
- Is that sewage?
- Aah!
Yeah, that's sewage
So, uh, mike, the suspense is killing us
Why don't you
just tell us the bad news?
Well, your outtake pipe's completely corroded.
That's why it collapsed
I'm going to have to
tear it out and repipe the whole system
And how much
is this going to cost?
I'll do the job for you at cost,
but you're still looking at 6, 7 grand, minimum
Okay, well,
we'll let you know
Look, um ... if money's an issue
oh,  no, no, no,
it's not the money
It's just, uh, carlos and I are trying to prioritize
some little things we need to do around the house
All right And, uh, you don't consider
sewage backing up in the house a priority?
It's definitely on the short list
I'm kind of surprised
you called me
Why?
Well, um, ever since my arrest,
nobody around here seems to want to
have much to do with me
Innocent until proven guilty, my man
Hope he's more innocent
than you are
Hey,  it's lynette
I know you're down about this mike thing,
but you got to come to poker
It'll be worth it.
I got dirt on maisy gibbons
Hey, susan, it's me
I really wish you'd return my calls
We need to talk
I know I messed things --
you okay?
Hi
You know, I can stay home
if you want
No, no, no
Now, I know how much you were looking forward
to this weekend with your dad
I'm fine
You don't look fine
Well ... a little sad
Mike and I were just a fling
And not even a full fling
Sort of a borderline fling
Mom, anyone can see
how much you loved him
Well, I also loved junk food,
and I gave that up, and I survived
There's your father
Go have fun
Last chance. You're sure?
I'm sure. Now go
You'll find someone else, mom
someone great. I know it
What's wrong, rex?
Didn't you enjoy your golf game with dr Wallace?
I didn't play
I'm still feeling sluggish
Still? Did you talk
to him about that?
Yeah, of course. He doesn't understand
why the medication isn't working,
and he wants me to come in
for a checkup tomorrow
I can see that tish
is making the rounds
She must have
some juicy new anecdote
Yeah, get her over here
I could use a funny story today
Tish, Tish
Oh, I can tell by that look on your face
you've got something good
Now, come on, don't be selfish
Well, first off,
you're not friends with maisy gibbons, are you?
No
Thank god,
because this is too good
Maisy was arrested
While harold was at work,
she was having sex with men
in her house for money
Can you imagine?
No, I can'T
And that's not even the best part
Word is she had a little black book
with all her clients' names
So, uh... you think that'll get out?
Of course. These things always do
- Nancy, wait up.
- I can't wait to tell you this. Wait, wait
Well, you heard
your funny story, rex
Why aren't you laughing?
I go get it
Hello
Hi, tami, yeah
- Can we see one of the bugs?
- Yeah, here. See?
It's this little white thing
Look... It looks like a -- aw, jeez
It looks like a sesame seed
That's cool
Yeah, well, there's lots more
where that came from
No, I'm -- I'm so sorry
He must be so disappointed
But, look, we'll get all the boys together
once topher's back on his feet
Bye
What'd tami want?
She's canceling
topher's birthday party on sunday
He's come down with the measles, so...
Measles, huh?
Yeah. What?
Tami brennan spent
a fortune on topher's party
She'd call in specialists from switzerland
before she'd let it be canceled
Okay. Why would tami lie to us?
Because she saw porter scratching
his head at school
They all did, and now word's getting around
Why is everything
a conspiracy theory with you?
Lots of kids get lice
They're not that big a deal
- Well, it is for the rich b-I-t-c-hs at barcliff academy
- Lynette
It's been one day, and they've been disinvited
to a birthday party
If rumors start flying, these boys can kiss campouts
and pool parties goodbye
Uh-oh
Yeah, not so cool now, huh?
It's all here
Appraisal, title search,
and escrow documents
Again, I'm sorry
Again, I'm sorry about changing my mind,
but this just isn't really
a good time to sell the house
Zach's going through a lot, and he wants to finish
high school before moving
Ah, forget it
It's part of the business
I expect to get screwed over
Now,  where is your house key?
Oh, I must have left it at home
I'll bring it by tonight
No one will be here
Zach's away on a school trip,
and I'm going to mount pleasant
on business today
Just drop it by tomorrow
Or I could just keep it
What?
It's a joke, paul
I know your wife's dead and all,
but it's been six months... lighten up
Hello
Felicia
Oh, hi, felicia
Edie, I found this
in my sister's things
It has your name on it
Oh... my necklace
Oh, you know
I lent this to martha three months ago,
and she said that
it went down the drain
Oh, I miss how we used to
steal things from one another
So, felicia...
I heard they have a suspect
in your sister's murder
Mike Delfino ?
Oh, he didn't kill her
But they found her jewelry
in his garage
But his fingerprints
weren't on any of it
Well, that just means
he wore gloves
So he's smart enough
to use gloves,
but he leaves her blood-spattered jewelry
lying around for anyone to find?
Please ...
Is that what you'd do if you killed someone?
I don't know what goes through
the mind of a murderer
I'm just saying I wouldn't
trust him if I were you
Edie, that is lovely
Is it an antique?
Yeah, I think so
You know, I know a store you would love
It specializes in antique jewelry
It's in salt lake city.
Have you ever been to salt lake city?
No, I try to steer clear of utah
It's a little too
conservative for me
Too bad
Have you ever been, paul?
No
It's lovely
I used to live there
when I was a nurse
You should definitely
go sometime
Bye
With no indoor plumbing,
gabrielle was now forced to improvise
when it came to her personal hygiene
wherever and whenever
she had the opportunity
Sorry
That's okay. I was just about
to give a maisy gibbons update
Guys, we should be ashamed of ourselves
for reveling in that woman's misery
That being said,
Edie, please continue
Well, I hear from a very reliable source
that maisy's going to cut
a deal with the prosecution
Apparently, she has some high-profile johns,
and the DA'S looking for a second term
I don't get it
I don't get who would
pay maisy for sex
Obviously, someone who's
not getting it at home
So the upshot is maisy is going to turn over her little black book
with all of her clients' names
- Really ?
- Yep
I mean, can you imagine the fallout
when this goes public?
blood on the walls
I'm all in
I'll call
Bree?
Uh, what just happened?
The stakes were raised
Yes, yes, they were
I fold
I can't believe
how lucky you were today
Luck had nothing to do with it
I had crappy cards
I was bluffing the entire time
Really?
Wow, you're good
Oh, that's the only nice thing
I could say about my first husband --
he taught me how to bluff
He played poker?
No, he was lousy in bed
I had to fake
a lot of orgasms
You don't have to respond
Thank you
So, uh... where was susan today?
Uh, I'm not sure
- Wow, tom must be great in bed
- Huh?
Well, obviously, you have
no idea how to bluff
Okay
She's going through something, and I'm sure
she'd prefer it to be private
She's upset with mike,
isn't she?
Well, come on...
I'm going to find out sooner or later
She's devastated
about the breakup,
and she hasn't
left the house in days
Well, why didn't you
just tell me that?
Because it's personal
It's the kind of thing
she would only want me to tell her friends
I'm susan's friend
Well, I don't hate her
Edie, if you want me to share stuff with you,
you're going to have to start being more supportive of susan
Okay. How?
What do friends do?
They call, they're sympathetic,
they ask about the pain the other person
is going through,
and  then they listen
What if you want to be supportive,
but you just can't stand
listening to people bitch?
Then it's good
to know how to bluff
God, I have to go to the bathroom again
Go to bree'S
I've been to bree'stwice today
Then go to Susan's
I hate Susan's
She has all these weirdscented candles
Her house reeksof apricot Hose
- How about lynette's?
- No, you don't understand
I don't want to go to anybody's house anymore
I'm tired of knocking on doorsand making up excuses
as to why we haven't fixed our plumbing
Why are you yellingat me?
Because it's your fault ?
My fault?
Yes. If you hadn'tgotten yourself indicted,
we would have pipes right now
I got indicted trying to make enough money
to keep you happy
In case you hadn't noticed,
you're a little materialistic
Oh, I'm materialistic?
When the johnsons bought their new 7-series, you were the one
who went right in and traded in his car for something better
Who ended up driving it?
You know what?
I don't have time to fight right now
I have laundry to do
Nurse abigail?
Mrs Scavo, right?
The twins' mother?
I just wanted to tell you that
the boys are now, ha ha
... lice-free
Good to hear
I just can't figure outhow it happened
They get a bath every night
Trust me,
it's the ugliest 15 minutes of the day
I believe you
I keep thinking that
maybe it was the petting zoo
that I took them to last week
That llama was really iffy
Mrs Scavo, it doesn't work that way
Lice only spreads from human to thuman
Even the cleanest kid in the world can get it
if he gets too close to the wrong kid
Really?
Yes. So don't be so hard on yourself, huh?
I guess
Still, I can't help but feel a little guilty
After all, my kids started
an entire lice outbreak
Look, your, uh, your kids didn't start it
They didn't?
No. I know for a fact that patient
zerowas another little boy
This is his fourth time with this particular problem
Oh. That is a load off my mind
Well, thank you
So which kid is it?
I can't tell you
You know we have a no-blame policy
We have to protect the children
You understand?
Of course
No, I don'T
You're going to have to give me a name
Mrs Scavo --
here's the thing
acting like parents won't assign blame is like pretending
they don't keep score at pee-wee league games
It's human nature
If you don't give the moms
someone to blame, they'll pick a scapegoat
I can't let my boysbe the scapegoat
Please don't put me in this position
I'm begging you
They've already been uninvited
from a birthday party,
a really big birthday party
with a bouncy house
and a hot dog stand and a clown
I wish I could help you, but --
for god's sakes, there's going to be a magician
Tami brennan went all out
Tami brennan?
Topher's mother?
Yes
Well, isn't that interesting?
Have a seat
Meanwhile, at the fairview county prison,
maisy gibbons was delighted to
find out she had a visitor,
but she was soon reminded
one should always beware of visitors
bearing gift baskets
You've gotto be kidding me
Hello, maisy
Stuff like this is why I love you
So... what brings you here?
I need a favor
I thought as much
I heard that there's a, um, little black book
with the name of your clients in it
There is
I was wondering if, perhaps,
you could remove rex's name from that little book
Wow, that's a big favor
Those muffins better be really good
I have some money that I've been
putting aside for emergencies
It can be all yoursif you just
keep my mouth shut?
Continue to be discreet
Gosh... I don't know
I don't think it's asking that much
All you need to do is remove one little name
But if I do it for you,
then I have to do it
for all the other wives
That wouldn't be fair, now, would it?
Maisy, please
I mean, we used to be good friends
Ah. Where were you when harold lost his job
a year ago, huh?
Did you stop by to see if there was
anything that you could do?
Did you bringa big basket of baked goods
when you knew we couldn't even pay our bills?
If you did,
those displays of friendship
seem to have slipped my mind
Maisy, I didn't mention it when you were
having financial troubles
because I thought it would embarrass you
Yes, I would have been embarrassed,
but it would have been a whole lot better
than the silence
I have $14,000 in that account
It can all be yours
I'm not interested
But you do get credit for one thing
You came to visit me,
even if it was for an ulterior motive
None of the other girls
from the club even bothered
I've been abandoned
Guess that's what happens
when you become the town whore
Oh, sweetie
They didn't abandon you
because you're a whore
They abandoned you because you weren't
all that nice to begin with
Who is it?
It's edie!
Oh, edie, not nowI'm kind of busy
Hi
Or just come on in
What are you doing?
I decided that my life
is way too complicated,
and so I'm simplifying
I am getting rid of the clutter
Ooh
I was on vacation.
Made sense at the time
Okay, not to be rude,
but is there a reason you're here?
Look... I'm feeling badly about
what you'regoing through with mike
And don't worry I'm not going to date him
Doesn't matter anymore
Well, don't get me wrong,
I still have every intention of sleeping with him
Some mountains are just meant to be climbed
I got to learn to keep my doors locked
How long have you been sitting here?
I don't know
Five minutes, give or take three hours
That's i. Get up
Get dressed
Why?
'Cause you're coming with me
It's time to get wasted
Happy hour started 45 minutes ago
Why would I go anywhere with you?
Because that's what normal women do
when they get depressed
They put on short skirts,
they go to bars with their girlfriends,
maybe have one too many and then make out
with some strange man in the back of a dark alley
Wow
Oh, come on
It'll be fun, I swear
Come on. Come on
Why do you even care?
I never said I cared
It's just... well, I I guess I know what it's like
to have your heart stomped on
Okay. All right. Give me a minute
I'll go change my clothes
And don't forget to do something
with that skanky hair
You're a little scary-looking
Oh, what about him?
Not my type
Oh, look, I know the pickins are slim,
but isn't there someone here that you're attracted to?
I hate them all
Look at them just leering at us
They're so damn cocky, like they know they have the upper hand
What are you talking about?
We have the upper hand
Without us, they have nothing
Maybe 15 years ago
Not anymore
Now we're just lonely and desperate,
and they know it,
and they just sit there ready to pounce, you know,
waiting for us to take any crumb
they're willing to throw our way
I don't want crumbs
I want mike
Hi, Um.... I'm going to be spending
the whole night with her,
so I'm going to be needing
a lot more of these
I'm sorry
It's just so hard to find a guy like mike
I know in my heart he didn't kill mrs Huber
Okay, let's say mike's a peach
and he didn't kill martha
Who did?
I don't know
Obviously, a bad guy
Somebody really awful,
somebody like -- somebody
like Paul Young
Paul? Ha ha
Are you serious?
I'm telling you, he's hiding something
He clams up every time we try
to ask him about mary alice
And then when we found out about dana
Dana. Who's dana?
Paul and mary alice had a baby that died
You're kidding
Zach killed her
Holy crap. Who told you that?
Paul. He said it was an accident,
but I'm telling you,
I think that's why mary alice was being blackmailed
Mary alice was being blackmailed?
Yeah
The girls and i found a threatening note
in her stuff
What the hell kind of street
do we live on?
I don't know
Come to think of it, the other day,
paul was talkingto felicia,
and he was working overtime
trying to make mike sound guilty
See? Shifting blame onto someone else --
that's classic criminal behavior
Oh, I'm telling you, he's up to no good
Zach and paul are out of town
Maybe we should sneak into their house
and do some snooping
I have a key
Oh, my god, yes
We should do that
Oh, come on. I was just kidding
No, edie, this is our chance
We should just go infor 10 minutes
Susan, that's breaking and entering
Martha huber was your best friend
If we could find out who really killed her,
wouldn't that be worth the risk?
- Have a nice evening
- Thank you
Serena, hi. How are you?
- I talked to Dr Wallace today
- Oh?
He still has no idea why
the medicationisn't working
He told me he's thinking
of running more tests
I told him I'm thinking about
getting a second opinion
Rex, this might sound silly,
- but are people staring at us?
- Yeah. What's going on?
Well, I could be wrong,
but I suspect that maisy gibbons' client list
has been released
You think they're laughing at us?
No, I think they're laughing at you
I think they feel sorry for me,
which is just as mortifying
- What are we going to do?
- Oh
We're going to act like nothing is happening,
and then, when we finish eating,
we're going to walk out of here with all
the dignity that we can muster
Please, let's go now
Oh, no I refuse to give them
this kind of satisfaction
Open your menu
Everybody's staring, bree
It's humiliating
Well, you should have thought of that
before you left a personal check on maisy gibbons' nightstand
All right, you stay here
if you want to I'm leaving
Rex, if you walk out of this restaurant,
I will scream
- Bree¡H
- I will scream
about your cruelty
Then I will scream about your infidelity
And then just to make sure it really hurts,
I will scream about your distasteful sexual habits
You want to know what true humiliation is,
you just take one step
So, what are you having?
The veal looks good
So what are we looking for, exactly?
An embroidered pillow that says
"I killed martha huber"?
I don't know
Just something suspicious
Mmm, smells expensive
Do you believe in evil, edie?
Of course I believe in evil
I work in real estate
I'm serious
There's something about this house
that's just so cold
and creepy
You couldn't tell when mary alice was alive
She just brought so much warmth and light
Now there's something
I can just taste it
Can't you sense it?
The only thing I can sense
is that you've had too much to drink
Oh, something happened in this house,
something so awful we can't even imagine it
Ow! Son of a bitch
Are you okay?
I just stubbed my toe
- Oh, my god -- angela
- Huh?
Angela -- that's what mary alice
used to call herself
What are you talking about?
We heard it on this tape
that bree stole from her the rapist's office
It's a long story I'll tell you later
Oh, we got to put this in
What was that?
I think it's paul
You said he was going to be gone
Well, I guess I was wrong
Hurry
I got to get the tape
Hide!
Paul
Oh! Oh! Oh! Edie
God, you scared me
I'm sorry I see that you, uh,
made it back from mount pleasant
Yes. What -- what are you doing here?
Well, I came by to bring you your key
I was just about to leave you a note
You're returning my key at 11:30 at night
What the hell's going on here?
You're right
- We're too old to be playing games
- What?
My note was goingto tell you that I, uh...
I-I wasn't kidding this afternoon
I really would like
to keep a key to your place --
to use if the mood strikes me
Ha ha. You've been drinking
Just enough to get up the courage
to tell you how I feel about you
Okay, well. obviously, you're
uncomfortable about this,
so I-I'm really sorry if I embarrassed you
Here, here's your key
I'll see you around
Edie, um...
I'm not embarrassedHuh?
If anything, I'm flattered
Susan, Susan, talk to me
Mike, it's not a good time
I'm a little drunk and a little freaked out
Why haven't you returned
any of my messages?
We're broken up
I thought I made that pretty clear
Oh, come on
Can't we work this out?
You lied to me
When? When did I lie to you?
The police showed me your rap sheet
You killed a man
You can't believe I'm some cold-blooded killer
Well, of course I don't believe that,
but I also didn't believe that karl was going
to cheat on me,
and I didn't believe that mary alice
was going to kill herself
I mean, let's face it, mike --
blind faith is not my friend
I was going to tell you
There just wasn't a right moment
See? Now that's a lie, too,
because there were plenty of right moments
- Susan¡K¡K
- every time we went out for pizza,
you could have said,
"oh, and by the way, I once killed a man"
Or when you said, "hey, let's go jogging,"
you could have said,
"well, by the way, I once killed a man"
Every time we went to the movies
and the hero shot the bad guy,
you could have turned to me and said,
"oh, and by the way,I did that once" You didn't
Do you want to hear what happened or not?
It doesn't matter,
because I will never believe
anything you say ever again
Well, at the very least,
you can believe that
Occupied
Carlos, I have to go
Well, you're going to have to wait
Why should I have to wait?
It's my port-a-potty
What do you mean, it's yours?
I'm the one who stole it
Babe, I'm sorry
You're just going to have to wait
Thank you so much, bree
Seeing your tile has really
helped me make my decision
Next time I remodel, I am using limestone
Gabrielle, is everything okay?
Sure, why?
Well, it's just that you've been acting
kind of odd lately
In what way?
Well, you keep coming up with excuses
to use everyone's bathroom,
and then two days ago, mr Cowley looked into your back yard
and saw you and carlosdoing your laundry in the jacuzzi
Well, uh, there's a simple explanation for that
I, um¡K¡K
are you and carlos having
some sort of money trouble?
Gabby, it's okay if you are
- Is that so?
- Yes, and....
and to tell you the truth,
I'm a little insulted I am a good friend
Why would you feel like you
have to hide that from me?
I don't know
Probably for the same reason
you didn't tell me rex was one of maisy's clients
That is obviously different
Why?
Because it happened to you?
Bree, this is how I see it --
good friends support each other
after they've been humiliated
Great friends pretend nothing happened
in the first place
Well, then, good luck on your remodel
And please tell rex I said hello
Hey, tami
Lynette
I see topher's made a speedy recovery
Can we go play?
Yeah, sure, boys
Have fun
Whoo! Let's go play in the bounce house!
Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
All right, you caught me I lied
But, uh, you sure have some nerve,
crashing a 6-year-old's birthday party
Just so you know,
I got topher a set of bongo drums
I know you'll love them as much as he will
Charlie, come on out of there!
I don't want you playing
with those scavo boys!
Uh, mona, please I'm sure they're clean
You are not ruining my party
All right, porter, preston, okay, out, out, out
Come on. Porter, preston, let's go
No, not -- not --not quite yet
Boys, keep bouncing.
That's right. Keep bouncing
Oh, by the way,
I spoke to nurse abigail
I know who patient zero is
All right, that's it, kids get out
Out, out, out
Go, go
How could you do that?
Look, this party meant everything to topher
I couldn't risk people not showing up
He would be devastated
I had to do something
And the best you could come up with
was letting my kids take the fall?
Hey, I hardly had to say anything
People were already suspicious
- Oh, please
- Yeah, it's true. Let's face it --
your boys aren't the cleanes
tkids on the planet
That was not a smart thing to say
Where are you going?
I'm going to tell the truth
to every mother out there,
and then I'm going to take back the bongos
No, wait, okay, all right
Look, I wa--I was wrong
I admit it.
I am really, really, really sorry
Too little, too late
Okay, okay
No, I'll -- I'll tell everyone that I was wrong,
that your kids aren't the ones
Please, I'm begging you
Well, why are you standing there?
Get to it
- Bree, hi
- Hi
What's up?
Well, um, I've been doing some thinking
Rex and I have been members of the
fairview country club for years, and
well, lately, it seems to have
lost some of its exclusivity,
and so I've decided not to renew our membership
I'd rather see the money
go to someone I care about
Oh, bree, I-I can't take that
Gabby, this is the way I see it --
good friends offer to help in a crisis
Great friends, don't take no for an answer
We're going to pay you back
every cent
I promise
Take your time
Yes, everyone loves a scandal
no matter how big or small
After all what could bemore entertaining
than watching the downfall of the high and mighty?
What could be more amusing than the
public exposure of hypocritical sinners?
Yes, everyone loves a scandal
And if for some reason,
you're not enjoying the latest one
well the next one...
is always around the corner
Transcript by Raceman, Synchro by ITTiger
www.forom.com