이 이야기는 허구이며
특정 인물과 사건을 묘사하지 않습니다
Jaunary 14, 1984
- Suction.
- All right.
More suction.
- You okay, kiddo?
- Is he gonna make it, dad?
Just as soon as I finish
cross clamping this aorta.
Boy's not much older than you.
Does he need more blood?
I can give. / Nope.
'Cause that just about does it.
- Need a hand.
- What's going on?
55-year-old, needs a stent, angioplasty.
All right, close up.
I'll see what's what.
- Talk to mom?
- Yeah.
Got through all her blue books.
- She give out any A's?
- No.
Grant!
He's in repack, Seth.
Better get a perfusing rhythm
before sending him up to the cath lab.
Paddles.
Charge 200.
Clear.
Charge.
- Your dad's got the touch.
- Yeah?
Doesn't miss a trick.
Raises them from the dead.
Don't believe it, Jase.
I'm just a glorified electrician around here.
Okay, let's send Mr. Lee
up to the cath lab.
Let me through.
I want to see my husband, please.
My husband, Tong Lee,
is he going to be all right?
- Yes, he's stable, ma'am.
- Oh, thank god. Thank you.
Oh, we, we can pay.
We have money. Cash.
Just think about your husband
right now, okay?
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
Is that a squirrel?
Japanese crane.
Looks like a squirrel.
Hey, Nick.
Nick Vera, this is David Cage.
- You're the new ADA, replaced Danner?
- Yes.
But trying to live that down.
I'm here to mend fences.
This is Edwina Davis,
just came forward with new information.
Miss Davis witnessed the murder
of Dr. Grant bowen back in '84.
- Call me Edie.
- Okay.
I was on the streets back then.
Scared of cops.
But all that's changed.
Making amends.
- Tell us what you saw?
- The man that got shot.
The doctor, he was walking
and talking to a white guy.
The guy who was arrested
for the killing was black.
Homeless, history of mental illness.
- You see this white guy shoot the doc?
- Right in the heart.
- You hear anything they were saying?
- No.
But I think your shooter
might've been another doc.
- Why's that?
- Because he had a cap
with the hospital logo on it,
you know, with the hands.
- Anything else you can remember, Edie?
- No.
But I could use a soda.
Sure. Come on.
- So?
- Good new direction.
I'm glad.
Like I said, trying to reach out.
If we take this job, I'd like to
get my detective off desk duty.
- The one who clocked Danner?
- Will Jeffries.
Up to my boss to drop
those charges, not me.
- You putting a good word in couldn't hurt.
- That's true.
- I could make a call.
- Could?
Will.
Cold Case
3x22. The River
딕테이션
김철균((kim1047@nate.com)
싱크편집
최자앵(ashaa@nate.com)
한글번역
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
번역수정
캐서린 모리스(릴리 러쉬 役)
대니 피노(스카티 발렌스 役)
존 핀(존 스틸만 役)
제레미 래치포드(닉 베라 役)
톰 배리(윌 제프리스 役)
트레이시 톰스(캣 밀러 役)
한글교정
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2006/05/07
- Just don't take her there.
- He's harmless.
Go to the library instead.
You spend too much time with criminals.
You think everyone's doing wrong.
- Hey, Kat.
- Hey.
Hello.
- Scotty Valens, this is my mom, Dina.
- Hi.
- And Veronica.
- The ballerina, right?
Do you have a gun like my mom?
- I do. Yeah.
- Anyway. The library.
See you tonight.
Family drama?
There's this guy at Finley park,
where she likes to play.
He up to something?
I don't know.
He just sits there, reading.
But you don't like how he looks.
He doesn't have a kid there.
Just bothers me.
- Want me to check him out?
- You mind?
Nah.
Grant Bowen, 40,
ER doc at st. Walter's.
Theory in '84 was a mugging gone wrong.
Killed on his way home after his shift.
- St. Walt's is in a rough part of town.
- Shot with a 38.
The slug was recovered,
weapon was never found.
Homeless guy they arrested
had on the doc's top-siders.
But he could've taken them
after the doc was killed.
Jury didn't think so.
Guy was convicted.
Died in jail two months later.
The only physical evidence was a red,
heart-shaped sticker found by the doc's body.
- Valentine's heart?
- Murder was in August, not February.
According to this witness,
doc was chatting it up with the doer.
- Who had a hospital baseball cap.
- Huh, something personal.
Will's on his way to Drexel.
Widow's an English professor there.
You could still catch up
with him if you hurry.
- He's off desk duty?
- Boss brokered a deal.
I had to. The man was playing
with a flying squirrel.
I met Grant when he was a resident.
Broke my ankle ice-skating,
he put on the cast.
And the rest is history?
And we were such opposites.
Opposites how?
I come from a family of academics.
Grant was a steel worker's son.
He sure made good,
becoming a doctor.
And he could've worked anywhere,
but he wanted to give back.
That's why st. Walter's.
We have new information that your husband
may have been shot by someone he knew, Anne.
- A white guy, possibly from the hospital.
- Oh, my god.
Anyone that fits that description
that may have wanted to hurt grant?
Maybe.
- Another doctor in the ER.
- What's his name?
- Seth Garvey.
- They didn't get along?
They did, but Seth envied Grant.
- Professionally?
- For starters.
We were at a medical convention in Atlantic
city eight months before Grant died.
- Here comes the river.
- What's that?
Last common card dealt.
It's called the river
'cause your hand's fate depends on it.
- Very existential.
- I love that.
- Yes! Yes!
- Damn!
Fate is with me.
Well, I'm in the middle of a great book
about sir Francis Bacon, so I'm going up.
- Coming?
- Another half an hour.
Come here.
You got beginner's luck
like I've never seen.
Yep, my father used to say
better to be lucky than smart.
Adios, boys.
Hey, let me walk you up, Anne.
A lot of shady characters about.
Podiatrists and the like.
You know, I never heard grant
mention his dad before.
- Usually doesn't.
- Why's that?
He was a drunk. Deadbeat.
And Grant's perfect.
Overcompensating I guess.
He's not perfect.
But almost.
Must be fun to live with.
So where to?
What?
"She is beautiful,
therefore to be wooed"
"she is a woman,
therefore to be won."
Henry the Sixth.
- Are you hitting on me, Seth?
- Yes.
Well, don't.
He take the hint, stay away?
Asked me to marry him,
few months after Grant died.
Guess that'd be a no.
Kinda had the fever for
Anne Bowen, huh, Dr. Garvey?
No kinda about it.
Didn't matter, she was
married to a fellow doc?
Not saying I was proud of it.
But the heart is a lonely hunter.
Were you lonely enough to try
and get rid of Grant?
Whoa, whoa.
- Left field.
- New angle on his murder.
He was shot by someone he knew.
From your hospital.
You think I killed him
so that I could be with Anne?
- Did you?
- That's crazy.
Not really, happens all the time.
All right, look,
I admit I was jealous of Grant.
He was one of these guys that had it all.
- But then he started falling apart.
- What was going on?
His past was catching up to him.
- Specifically?
- His genetic past.
- Like his dad, he was an addict.
- Drugs?
Cards.
Got the bug in Atlantic city.
Then we went to a local game
near the hospital.
- Last hand.
- You said that two hours ago.
- Gonna get lucky this time.
- Said that two hours ago, too.
Crap.
Let me make a call.
- Got a lie cooked up, doc?
- A lie?
Car trouble.
Friend in need.
Why don't you just go home to her?
Or considering that you're a doc, though,
I'd go with a pileup on the expressway.
Lot of casualties.
Hey, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe half an hour.
It's been so busy down here.
Actually, there was a pileup
on the expressway.
Yeah. Terrible.
Maybe an hour more.
Okay.
Bye, honey.
That's the spirit.
- I'm putting everything in.
- Whoa, doc, that's a lot of money.
- You sure about that?
- Nothing's sure.
That's what so great.
You bluffing me?
That doesn't cover it.
Then I'll throw in my wedding ring.
- What do you say?
- See the river.
Showtime, doc.
Pair of bullets.
You bet everything
on a stinking pair of twos?
- You lousy river rat.
- I knew my luck was turning.
I'll take you down, doc.
Do you hear me?
You're going down!
- Who was this guy lost his wedding ring?
- Cy Tisdale.
He hung around the hospital,
getting paid to be in medical trials.
Think he was dangerous?
He had a pretty shady existence,
degenerate gambler.
Which takes money.
Money a rich doc like Grant had,
and Cy needed.
Anna Kournikova.
What's that?
Ace, king.
Looks good but never wins.
You guys want in?
- Like a bunch of roaches.
- Where are you going?
I ain't the ringleader here.
Why are you pick on me?
'Cause you knew Grant Bowen.
True. Okay?
He was shot, not long after you
made a threat against him.
Said you'd take him down,
so maybe you did.
Aw, that was just card talk.
- Besides, a mugger killed him.
- No.
New witness says it was a guy
in a st. Walt's baseball cap.
Like the one you took
right of of Grant's head. / Nah, I...
I gave that back to the doc,
same night I took it from him,
same night we became friends.
Recall where you were
when Grant was killed?
Playing poker at Skinny's tavern.
- Ask Skinny, he'll tell you.
- Will do.
Besides, I never would have hurt the doc.
He was my protege.
No offense, Cy, but...
you don't seem like the mentor type.
I tried to teach him the game,
but the guy...
was torn between two lovers.
Good evening.
Can you check this off?
That's okay.
- Here you can.
- Yes, of course.
Well, a toast to Jason's
future alma mater, Cornell.
I hear you've been shadowing
your dad in the ER, Jason?
But he's surgeon material.
I like the ER.
People need your help right away,
- and then, you save them.
- And they're forever grateful.
Like Mrs. Lee who brought another
angelfish for our aquarium today.
'Cause that's how she thinks
of you as her angel.
Oh, boy.
- You sure?
- I'm afraid so.
- What's wrong?
- Credit cards aren't working.
I didn't bring my purse.
Uh, I'll just have to write a check.
I'm afraid we don't take checks.
Well, you just might have
to make an exception tonight.
I'm sorry, sir.
Uh, that's the ER.
Damn it. Uh...
- Um, I'll take that check, waiter.
- No, no, we invited you.
I'm so sorry, but...
I'm on call.
- Sara's dad is not paying.
- No, he's not.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
Please, order dessert.
What is going on?
I don't know.
It's a bank snafu.
- It's really embarrassing.
- Anne, I have to run.
You can't just walk out on
your son's graduation dinner.
It's work. / And stick his girlfriend's
parents with the bill.
It's the hospital.
Look, I have to go.
Why are you on call tonight, anyway?
I'm sorry.
It was the game or the lady.
And the lady lost.
You think she knew
what the competition was?
My experience?
Wives always know.
I hear you.
Did some checking, Anne.
You got $1.5 million in life
insurance, after Grant died.
Yes. So?
Well, so it must have come in handy,
considering you were broke.
If you think I'm some
kind of black widow...
I know there were money problems.
Grant was screwing up your life,
humiliating you.
He was in trouble.
But you didn't mention that.
What does that have to do
with him dying?
Maybe everything,
because maybe you did
something about it. / I tried.
I tried to save him.
- Any luck?
- None.
What are you doing?
Uh, just, uh...
looking for a pen.
You're trying to steal from me?
- That's ridiculous.
- Yes, it is, but that's what you're doing.
Cornell called today.
Tuition check bounced.
- Bank snafu.
- Another one? / Must be.
Grant, you're a doctor. I'm a professor,
and both our bank accounts are empty.
- What the hell is happening?
- Okay, uh...
I've been playing poker.
You gambled away our money?
- But I'm gonna win it back.
- Grant.
When I'm at that table,
it's like I'm playing with fate.
It's dangerous and exhilarating.
It sounds like you're talking about a drug.
But you can't get good at a drug.
Do you hear yourself?
I'm getting good, really good.
- That's the ER.
- No, it's not.
It hasn't been the ER
in a long time, has it?
- I'm gonna win it all back.
- Grant, stop. Before Jason finds out.
Don't tell him.
It's just a temporary problem.
He's gonna find out
when we can't pay his tuition.
Just trust me!
We'd been married 18 years.
And suddenly I didn't know him anymore.
- Did your son find out?
- Yeah.
'Cause we couldn't afford Cornell.
That must have crushed him.
He had to go to community college.
Work two jobs.
It turned him against Grant forever.
So when Grant died,
he and Jason were estranged.
At least with the insurance money,
Jason got to transfer
to Cornell the next year.
He's a doctor now.
Just like he always wanted.
You know that witness, Edie?
The ex-junkie?
- She called me.
- And?
That's it. Just saying.
Saying what?
Saying that maybe I'm not a 100%
totally washed up in the dating world.
Because a crack-ho called you?
Why you have to say it like that?
I got something on Jason.
One of his two jobs?
Was working at the blood
bank at st. Walter's. / That relevant?
According to the web site,
each time you donate,
you get juice, a cookie,
and a red, heart-shaped sticker.
- Like the one at our crime scene.
- That's the trifecta right there.
Knows the victim, associated
with the hospital, and that sticker.
And a million and a half reasons
to see his dad dead.
Which one's yours?
Oh, none.
- You like the boys or the girls?
- Excuse me?
Seems like you're watching
the kid in blue pretty close.
- Don't know what you mean.
- He's weak, no friends.
- He's a good pick.
- I'm trying to read.
You'd rather have the blonde kid.
He's popular, athletic.
You move on him,
he'll tell you to go pound sand.
Guess you know something about it.
I know what you are.
I make a study out of people like you.
I'm not doing anything.
You're thinking about it.
No law against that.
You're not gonna read here anymore.
You're gonna walk away right now.
And if you come back,
I'll find you,
and I'll wreck you.
We have to talk, Jason.
Who asked you to open
my dad's case again?
We don't need a formal invite.
I'm just wondering who the hell cares.
I know I don't.
That's pretty tough.
I have surgery in six minutes,
and I'm punctual, so...
So where were you
when your dad was killed?
- You're talking to me like a suspect.
- Picked up on that, huh?
We're down to five minutes now.
He embarrassed you
in front of your girlfriend,
made you pull out of Cornell.
All 'cause of his gambling.
I'm not denying he was a bum.
Did you always think that?
No. I used to worship him.
I watched him raise people
from the dead.
Can't see something like that
and not want to be just like the guy.
- But then he let you down.
- Yeah, well...
that's the way it goes.
So that night?
I was at a bar, Clancy's.
Got drunk, first, only time in my life.
Why that of all nights?
Because I'd just seen first-hand
what my dad had become.
- A bum?
- And a menace.
Dr. Bowen, my husband is back.
Really? Sorry. / He's in the OR.
Will you check on him?
- You're the only one...
- Can't just now, Mrs. Lee.
Start a line.
2 million units of penicillin, 500 of gent.
- Dad!
- Quiet, Jason.
- But, dad, the chart...
- Jason, you watch, I work. Understand?
Dr. Garvey!
He's giving him penicillin.
- Stop! He's pen allergic, Grant.
- What?
Clindamycin.
And get Dr. Marsh.
You, come with me.
You could've sent him into
anaphylactic shock. / I missed it, sorry.
"Sorry" is for when you show up
to work a zombie.
"Sorry" is for when you borrow
thousands of dollars and never pay back.
Spare me the lecture. / But "sorry"
doesn't cover nearly killing a patient
because you're so distracted and tired
that all you think about is gambling.
This has nothing to do with the cards.
- You have a problem.
- That's crap.
Admit it. / I need sleep.
I worked two shifts.
- Stop lying.
- He's right.
- What?
- Mom knows it, too.
You lie about everything now.
Now you're both lecturing me?
- What the hell is this?
- End of the line, Grant.
You're coming with me.
End of innocence, huh?
You could say.
Where was Dr. Garvey taking your dad?
I never asked.
Something you forgot to tell us,
Dr. Garvey? /  I don't think so.
You hauled Grant out of the ER,
day he died.
- Makes you last-to-see.
- And maybe the shooter.
- I didn't shoot Grant.
- You did something you tried to hide.
Yeah. I covered for Grant
when he almost killed a patient.
The hospital could have been sued.
Fact remains, you're
the last guy seen with Grant.
You had it bad for his wife,
and you were jealous of him at work.
Not at that point.  I wasn't jealous
of him in any way. / No?
I pitied him.
And, yes, I interfered.
I did it for her.
- Anne.
- You did what?
I took him to a gambler's anonymous
meeting...basement of saint Michael's.
- He sit still for that?
- Far as I know.
I stayed a few minutes,
but I was working.
Anyone see you leave the meeting?
Yeah. That mutt Cy Tisdale.
Those food stamps you're playing for?
Lot of bazooms.
Got some new information, Cy.
What now?
Witness put you and Grant at a gambler's
anonymous meeting the day of the murder.
Want to tell us why you
failed to mention that? / Not really. No.
Went to talk to your old pal, Skinny.
- See about that alibi of yours.
- Oh, yeah? How's he doing?
- Not so good.
- Been dead a decade.
But that's no surprise to you, is it?
I got feelings, you know.
- That's hurtful.
- Quit bluffing, Cy.
Tell us what happened
to Dr. Bowen that day.
- The birds is what happened.
- Birds?
Pigeons, to be exact.
I almost killed someone today,
right in front of my son.
And now he hates me.
And it's not even an hour later,
and all I can think about
is how to get to a game.
I've lost my wife, my son, my job.
But I keep thinking my luck will turn.
That's the beauty of chance.
The beauty I couldn't resist.
I'll try, though.
Try accepting I'm going out a loser.
What the hell are you doing here?
- I come here sometimes.
- To quit?
To remind myself
why I don't want to quit.
Look at these sad sacks.
Put a c-note in any of their hands,
they'd be out the door.
Not me. Not anymore.
- Had a dream last night, doc.
- Oh, yeah?
Had the ten, jack, queen
and king of spades. And the river...
- it dropped me the ace of spades.
- A royal flush.
I think it's a premonition
that our luck's about to change.
That's your dream, Cy.
Mine are all nightmares.
Look at that, would you?
A buck says the gray flies off first.
- I'm quitting, Cy.
- Tell you what.
You take the gray,
I'll take speckles.
- I'll take speckles.
- That's the spirit.
You see? Now, that's a hell of
a good omen if I ever saw one.
Even if I wanted to play,
there's no way to get money.
- No one left to hit up.
- There's got to be someone.
- There's always someone.
- Yeah.
Maybe one person.
So who was gonna stake him?
Said there was a wife
of a guy he saved.
Owned a store that sold fish.
He was going to borrow from her?
He was past borrowing.
He was gonna rob her.
So you were right
about that guy in the park.
He was trolling.
I had a feeling.
I talked to him.
He ain't coming back.
Really?
- 'Cause...
- What?
My mom said he was gone yesterday,
but back today.
No kidding?
This is it.
Mrs. Lee?
Yes? / We need to talk to you
about Dr. Grant Bowen.
Dr. Bowen is dead.
That's why we're here.
Your husband was a patient of his?
My husband is dead now, too.
Did Dr. Bowen come to see you,
Mrs. Lee? / Try and rob you.
Dr. Bowen was a good man.
We know you told him
about having cash on hand.
And how indebted you were to him.
He saved my husband's life.
But he wasn't himself that day.
- So he did come see you?
- After closing.
And I tried to give him luck.
But it didn't work.
- Dr. Bowen?
- Mrs. Lee.
I thought you'd be at the hospital
with your husband.
- How did you get in?
- I, uh...
- the back door was open.
- Is my husband okay?
Yes. Yes, he's fine.
It's, it's the bill that,
that's the problem. / The hospital bill?
Yes. There, there were some
additional charges.
Uh, central line kit, anesthesia.
Uh, I remember when you said
you could pay in cash?
And you're here for the money now?
Yes, yeah. $1,000.
This isn't all your money, is it?
You saved my husband.
Wait...
I can't do this.
I'm going to take, uh,
three hundred...
and twenty-four dollars.
And I'm not gonna be paying you back.
Whatever it is,
it can't be that bad.
It's funny, what a life
ends up being worth.
Wait, Dr. Bowen.
Take this for good luck.
I'm beyond luck.
Everyone needs luck.
So he left with $324.
Pretty specific amount.
And my not-so-lucky luck charm.
Dealt you hands,
but took a peek.
You got a gay waiter.
A queen with a trey.
Where'd you get this, Cy?
Won it in a game.
Way back. / Wrong.
You took it from Grant
when you killed him.
Guess you thought
you could use the luck.
I'm gonna need a lawyer.
Except I can't afford one, so...
I guess I'll just clam up.
Being a guinea pig at st.
Walt's wasn't the only way
you were making money back then,
was it, Cy?
You also got paid for giving blood.
That's 'cause I got the lucky blood.
O negative. Universal donor.
You donated the day Grant died.
And got yourself a red heart sticker.
Which you must have dropped
when you shot Grant.
I'm a poker player, lady.
I ain't folding my hand just 'cause
you got some good face cards.
Witness who saw Grant's murder is coming in.
She's gonna ID you, and you're gonna
go down without a friend in the world.
I don't need friends.
I got 52 of them.
Right here.
We know you did it, Cy.
We just don't know why.
- They let you play cards in jail?
- Sure.
Been a prisoner to this deck so long...
bars instead of a door
won't make much of a difference.
What made you do it?
I thought Grant was your friend.
He was.
That's why.
Thought we were gonna meet
a half hour ago?
Had to go to Western union.
Send a money order.
Priorities, doc.
Money order can wait.
We got a game to go to.
Paid off my life insurance.
$324.
- How much you got left?
- Change of plans, Cy.
What the hell?
That skinny's gun.
Yeah. I took it from behind the bar.
No one saw me.
What do we need a gun for?
I think I know a way
to go out a winner, Cy.
Keep my promise to my wife.
You need a gun for that?
You're gonna kill me.
You're bluffing.
My wife and son can't think
I killed myself.
Don't be stupid.
Dying isn't winning, doc.
You remember back to when
you were married, Cy?
When you had kids?
You would've done right
by them, if you could've?
I ain't shooting you.
I go and my family gets
a million and a half dollars.
And what do I get?
You get to know you did right by me.
I'm a louse, doc, remember?
Selfish through and through.
And that's where I'm headed.
To where you're at.
To a wasted life.
You want that for me?
It ain't so bad.
Now who's bluffing.
So what?
I ain't pretending
my life ain't wasted.
But I ain't telling anybody
to shoot me either.
That's 'cause you got
nothing to die for.
And I do.
Please, Cy.
I got a ten, jack, queen,
king of spades here.
And all you got to do
is deal me that ace.
Here, take this for luck.
How do you know you're not gonna be
needing it where you're going?
I don't.
- That's what I loved about playing cards.
- What's that?
The not-knowing what the river
was gonna bring me.
It's gonna be aces for you, doc.
All aces.
♪ Asia's "Only time will tell" ♪
♪ You're leaving now ♪
♪ it's in your eyes ♪
♪ there's no disguising it ♪
♪ it really comes as no surprise ♪
♪ to find that you planned it all along ♪
♪ I see it now ♪
♪ becomes so clear ♪
♪ your insincerity ♪
♪ and me all starry-eyed ♪
♪ you think that I would
have known by now ♪
♪ now, sure as the sun
will cross the sky ♪
♪ this lie is over ♪
♪ lost, like the tears
that used to tide ♪
♪ me over ♪
♪ only time will tell
one thing is sure ♪
♪ that time will tell
only time will tell ♪
♪ if you were wrong ♪
♪ the brightest ring around the moon ♪
♪ will darken when I die ♪
♪ now, sure as the sun
will cross the sky ♪
♪ the lie is over ♪
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
♪ You're leaving now ♪