Previously on Lost...
- We're gonna have to take the boy.
- Dad!
I'm going after my son.
I'm going after my son,
and nobody is gonna stop me.
We need him!
One of our people
was captured by yours.
- So go get'em back.
- We can't do that,
but you can, and if you do,
we'll let you and Walt go free.
I'll do it. Give me the gun.
I'll kill him.
You lived up to your word.
We live up to our word, too.
You're gonna take this boat
and follow a compass bearing
of 3-2-5,
and if you do that exactly,
you and your son will find rescue.
Who are you people?
We're the good guys, Michael.
- Daddy!
- Come here.
Thank you all for your patience.
I know
it's taken me a few days to...
Figure out our next move
but I didn't wanna do anything
until I knew more
about our situation.
You deserve to know everything
that I do,
so...
no more secrets.
As you all know, Miles here,
and three of his people
came to the island about a week ago.
So I brought him up from the boathouse
to share with us
exactly why they're here.
We're here for him.
We kind of, like,
knew that forever ago.
OK then. Problem solved.
How soon do we turn him over?
- We can't turn him over.
- And why the hell not?
'Cause once they have me,
their orders are to kill
everyone else on the island.
Wait. So what, he's one of us now?
You're gonna protect him?
He tried to kill you, John.
And he won't tell us
who his spy on the boat is.
It's Michael.
What?
My spy on the freighter is Michael.
I'm sorry.
The same guy who killed
two women in cold blood
to set this little bastard free?
And then sold us out to get off
the island? That Michael?
That Michael.
The rules of desertion...
Still apply to everyone.
Nobody leaves this ship
without my say-so!
I'm not beating these men
to scare you.
I beat them to save your lives!
You remember what happened to the last
2 men who took off in this boat?
You remember what happened
to Minkowski?
As soon as we get the engines fixed,
we're back in the hunt.
In the meantime, everybody
just hold on!
- Johnson!
- Yes, sir.
Clean this mess up.
Sir.
- Hello, Michael.
- Not now, man.
Yes, right now.
Why are you on this boat?
I'm here to die.
www.soustitreslost.com
That was a nice meeting but I thought
there wasn't gonna be any more secrets.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about the 3 million bucks
your buddy here asked for.
Miles offered his loyalty
in exchange for the money.
But I haven't seen a bank on the island,
so I didn't think it worth mentioning.
Something funny?
Linus will find a way to get it.
And how will he do that?
He wants to survive.
And considering a week ago
you had a gun to his head,
and tonight he's eating pound cake...
I'd say he's a guy
who gets what he wants.
- It's fine.
- Okay, thanks.
Bye, guys.
May I have a word with you?
We've heard enough from you
for one night.
- You have to listen to a little more.
- It's okay.
What do you want?
This is a map to the temple.
It's a sanctuary.
It may be the last safe place
on this island.
- Why don't we know about it?
- It wouldn't be a sanctuary
if I told everyone, would it?
All our people are already there.
You'll get there in a day and a half.
If it's safe, why don't we all go?
Hurley, Claire, the baby?
Because the temple's not for them.
It's only for us.
The people that are coming
know who I am.
They're here to capture me.
They'll kill anybody in their way.
If they knew who you were,
that you were my daughter,
they would use you to get to me.
We don't have much time.
Maybe he's right.
I agree. We should go.
These people...
you said they're dangerous.
More dangerous than you?
But your mother will protect you.
Okay, now go.
Where is he?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
He's in the engine room.
I don't understand.
It should be working.
Gaskets are all corroded.
- Can I help you?
- The captain sent us down
to help with the repairs.
Thanks. We're okay.
Jeff, man, you know what?
We need a pressure valve.
You mind go grabbing one
from the supply room?
Not at all.
You shouldn't be here.
- What you doing?
- Why are you here?
- If they see me talking to you...
- Then talk quickly!
- You won't understand!
- I'll understand perfectly.
You just start from the beginning
and explain how you came
to be on this boat.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you, Mr. Dawson.
It's...
- What happened to me?
- You were in a car accident.
It's a miracle you're alive.
How badly am I hurt?
You just need to rest now.
It's a cold night.
I brought you some extra blankets.
Let's get some light in here.
Now I thought I heard someone shout,
and something tells me it wasn't him.
You okay?
You're lucky to be alive.
EMTs say they found you in a wrecked car
with a note pinned to your chest.
You didn't have any ID on you.
You want to tell me your name?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
You want me to call Walt?
- What?
- The note pinned to your chest.
It was written to "Walt."
You want me to call him?
No.
Okay, then.
Hey, ma.
Can I... come in?
No. You know the answer to that.
- I wanna see him.
- No.
- Just let me talk...
- I don't know what you said to him,
But whatever it was,
he doesn't want to see you.
Please, ma. He's my son.
- I have a right!
- I thought you were dead.
They said your plane crashed
in the middle of the ocean,
but you show up here fine and dandy,
only I can't tell anybody
but you or Walt,
I can't call you by your real names.
He barely talks to me,
But he does wake up screaming
in the middle of the night,
and I'm the one who got to tell him
it's gonna be okay.
So until you can explain to me
where you were for over two months,
and what happened,
you gave up your rights.
Will you...
Will you tell him I love him?
Yeah.
What can I do for you?
How much can I get for that?
Why is there Chinese writing
all over it?
A Korean guy gave it to me.
You don't look like you speak Korean.
- I'll give you $300 for it.
- I'm not looking for money.
What are you looking for?
I want a gun with bullets.
Come on. Let's just get this done.
Help me just get this done.
Excuse me, sir, you got the time?
No, man. no.
Come on, Michael.
How about for an old friend?
Manhattan?
We let you leave one island,
you just go to another one.
Will you just relax?
I just came here to...
Now are you ready to talk like adults?
Enough!
- Do it. Go ahead, do it!
- You'd like that, wouldn't you?
How did you find me?
We're the ones who sent you home.
Did you honestly think
we weren't gonna keep tabs?
- What do you want?
- Your help.
Why would I help the son of a bitch
who kidnapped my son?
We gave him back to you in one piece.
You're the one who lost him.
You told him, didn't you?
You couldn't carry the guilt
of what you did
so you shared it with a 10-year-old.
Is that why you wanna kill yourself?
Because that's the way
he looks at you now?
- Because he knows you're a murderer?
- Go away!
Bad news amigo, you can't kill yourself,
the island won't let you!
- What'd you say?
- No matter how bad you want to,
No matter how many different ways
you try,
it won't happen.
Give it a shot
if you don't believe me.
You got more work to do, Mike.
When you figure that out,
I'm in the penthouse at the hotel Earle.
The wreckage of oceanic flight 815
has been found.
This footage confirms
the airplane did, in fact, crash at sea.
At these tremendous depths,
there is little hope
of recovering any remains.
Investigators are equally skeptical
about the chances of retrieving
Oceanic 815's black box.
The real story behind what happened
to this fateful airliner
may have been lost along
with the 324 passengers onboard.
But even with this tragic discovery,
the victims' families
were hoping today...
I didn't expect you that fast.
Is this the guy who hit you
with a champagne bottle?
Yeah, but I had it coming.
Arturo, Michael and I
have some business to attend to.
- Would you get some air?
- Of course.
Help yourself to the chow.
I don't make it to the mainland
too often. So when I do,
I like to indulge myself.
So you people can just...
- come and go?
- Some of us.
- Want a drink?
- What I want is for you to tell me
what my plane is doing
at the bottom of the ocean.
That's not your plane. It's a phony.
A man named Widmore put it down there,
and he staged the whole wreck.
Staged? Why would he stage a...
Because he doesn't want anyone else
finding where the real plane ended up,
except for him.
I'm supposed to believe this?
Did the bullet bounce off your skull,
or did the gun just jam on you?
Prove it.
- Sorry?
- Prove that this Widmore
did what you say he did.
That's the cemetery in Thailand
where Widmore dug up
the 300-odd corpses he needed.
And the purchase order for the old 777
he bought through a shell company,
and the shipping logs
for the freighter he used
to drop the whole mess
down a trench deep enough
to guarantee that no remains
are ever gonna be identified.
Do you have any idea what it would cost
to bring those bodies up?
What you want from me, man?
In a few days,
a freighter is porting in Fiji.
It's Widmore's boat.
We have reason to believe
he found the coordinates of the island
and he's heading right for it.
So congratulations, Michael.
Your shore leave is over.
You just got a job on that boat.
Meet Kevin Johnson.
You're joining the crew in Fiji
as a deckhand.
You want me to go undercover?
Why the hell would I go back
to work for you people?
Because if Widmore finds the island,
it's good night for everybody on it.
He'll kill them all
without thinking twice.
You wanna redeem yourself
for what you did,
this is your only chance.
You can save all their lives.
No. I can't.
I can't go back to that island.
I didn't say you were going back
to the island.
You're going on that boat
so you can swab decks.
You're going
so you can kill everyone onboard.
You are engineer?
Just a deckhand.
We're all equals on this boat.
As long as you play decent hold'em.
I'm George Minkowski.
- Kevin Johnson.
- Nice to meet you, Kevin.
Go check in with Naomi over there.
I'll be seeing you. Welcome.
I'm reporting for duty.
Kevin Johnson.
Naomi Dorrit. Pleasure.
- So you're from the States, yeah?
- New York.
- Yeah, I could tell from the accent.
- Manchester?
How'd you guess?
You can head onboard.
One of these crates
was delivered for you.
I'll have it delivered to your berth?
- Yeah. thanks.
- Welcome aboard, Kevin.
Your name isn't Kevin.
Don't worry.
80% of the people on this boat
are lying about something.
Orange?
No, thanks.
- Yeah?
- How was your trip?
I figure flying can't be
too much fun for you.
- What do you want?
- You get your care package?
Wait until you're out in the open sea,
then you're good to go.
You can stow your gear downstairs, OK?
Welcome aboard, Keamy.
You met some of'em now.
Got some names and faces,
- and you're gettin'cold feet, huh?
- Yeah, actually, I am.
Here are a few more names for you:
Sun,
Sawyer, Jack,
Claire, her baby.
and your only way to save their lives
is if you man up
and get on that boat.
Or maybe you wanna come back
and explain to your kid
how you let all of them die, too.
It's game time. Are you in or out?
I'm in.
Then ditch your phone
and go do your job.
No offense but I was flying these things
when you were still at school.
- I should be the 1st to go.
- I need you here
- to transport the science team.
- What you gonna do?
That's need-to-know. You don't.
So much for the fairer sex, huh?
Frank Lapidus, chopper pilot.
Kevin Johnson.
Deckhand.
- So what's your story, Kevin?
- Sorry?
How'd you end up on this tub?
Looking for a little adventure.
Adventure...
Well, how do you like this
for adventure?
You ever hear about Oceanic 815?
What would you say if I told you
the plane they found in that trench
wasn't Oceanic 815?
Then what is it?
You know those nuts that think
the moon landing was faked?
Well, this is like that...
Only real.
That's why I signed up for this trip.
The owner of this boat believes me.
Charles Widmore.
He believes that 815
is still out there somewhere.
I mean,
can you imagine what would happen...
if we'd found
some of those people alive?
Pull!
- Another clip.
- Good job.
Kill shot!
What are you guys doing?
What's it look like we're doing?
We're shooting things. Pull!
Thought we were going
on a rescue mission.
Don't you have something to mop up?
Come on, let's go.
You can do this, OK?
You can do this.
Seven, one...
seven, seven, six.
Don't do it, Michael.
I love you, Walt.
- What, are you going Nicholson on us?
- What?
Jack Nicholson in The Shining,
when he's bouncing that ball
against the wall?
Next thing you know, you're gonna go
after your wife with an axe.
I'm not married.
Sorry to interrupt but you got a call.
- A call?
- Yeah. From the mainland.
They patched it through
to the radio room.
It's gotta be a mistake.
Nobody knows I'm here.
You're the only Kevin Johnson onboard,
so somebody knows you're here.
Said he really needs to talk to you.
His name's Walt.
Yeah, here you go.
It's kind of personal.
Mind if I take this alone?
Take your time, Kev.
You just push this yellow button
and turn this knob on the console.
Got it.
I'm so sorry, Michael,
but he's still in New York.
So I'm afraid you're stuck with me.
Are you still there?
You put me on this boat,
talked me into blowing it up,
and when I push the damn button,
a flag pops up.
- You actually activated the bomb?
- It's not a bomb! It's a...
It's a joke.
There are people on your boat
who are innocent.
They have no idea
hat the man they work for is a monster,
a killer without conscience
or a greater purpose.
I had to show you the difference
between him and me.
When I'm at war,
I'll do what I need to do to win
but I will not kill innocent people.
Ana Lucia and Libby...
They were innocent.
You killed them, Michael.
No one asked you to.
I don't blame you, Michael.
We did you have your boy.
And what wouldn't a man do
for his son?
What do you want... from me?
I want you to compile
a list of names...
Every person on your boat.
When I call again,
you'll give me that list.
Then you will disable
the radio room you're sitting in.
When the crew is disoriented
by their lack
of communication,
you'll take out the engines too.
That way,
the boat can never get to this island,
and your friends will be safe.
Will you do that for me, Michael?
Then consider yourself
one of the good guys.
So you're telling me...
that you're working
for Benjamin Linus?
Yeah, that's what I'm telling you.
Guys!
Hold it!
- Let me go! What are you doing?
- Shut your mouth.
What the hell is this?
This man is not who you think he is.
He was a passenger
on Oceanic flight 815.
I spent two months with him
on the island before he betrayed us.
This is the man who sabotaged
your radio room.
He destroyed the ship's engine,
and his name isn't Kevin Johnson.
It's Michael Dawson.
And he's a traitor.
We'll stop here and drink.
Two minutes, then we keep moving.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I don't know.
I just have a bad feeling about this.
What if your dad is... playing us?
Look, I don't like taking orders
from my dad any more than you do.
But I know he doesn't want me
to get hurt.
At least we've got something
in common.
Promise not to tell if you won't.
Come on, he's gone!
- No, we have to get Karl!
- He's gone, he's gone!
Listen to me.
I need you to take my hand.
On the count of three,
we're going to run.
Can you do that with me?
I love you.
I love you very much, Alexandra.
You ready?
One...
Two...
Three!
Wait, wait, don't!
I'm Ben's daughter!
I'm his daughter!
soustitreslost@gmail. com