These are the last two eggs.
From my own bookshelf?
- Help you pass the time.
- I've already read it.
You might catch something you missed
the second time around.
Why did you move me
from the rec room down here?
I wanted you under my own roof.
Where are you keeping
your other prisoner? Miles, is it?
- You don't want to share.
- Well, I was hoping you would share,
seeing as you claim
to have a spy on his ship.
I feel for you, John. I really do.
You keep hitting dead ends.
You couldn't find the cabin.
You can't make contact with Jacob.
You're so desperate to figure out
what to do next,
you're even asking me for help.
So here we are, just like old times...
except I'm locked
in a different room.
And you're more lost
than you ever were.
I know what you're trying to do.
It's not gonna work.
- Excellent, John. You're evolving.
- Done with your breakfast?
What was that all about?
Who knows? It's Locke.
Mornin', ladies.
Good morning.
Mornin'.
Coffee smells good.
Well... Why don't I go make you a cup?
Kinda weird, ain't it?
Sitting on porches,
drinking coffee out of mugs.
Anyway, I found some clothes
about your size.
Hung 'em in a closet.
- So after I kick out Hugo...
- I'm not moving in with you.
Well... Then why did you stay?
That's none of your business.
You got a secret agenda?
- If you're spying for Jack...
- I'm not spying for anyone.
- So why don't you tell me...
- Because I don't trust you.
This is about the pregnancy thing.
Go home.
Okay, fine.
See you later, then.
You ready?
Is there a back entrance?
Yeah, but you're going in the front door
with your head held high, okay?
Let's do this.
Why'd you do it, Kate?
Coming through.
Folks, we're not making any statements
or answering any questions right now.
Excuse us.
The people
versus Katherine Anne Austen.
The honorable
arthur galzethron presiding.
The bailiff will read the counts.
Will the defendant please rise?
Katherine Anne Austen,
you are charged with fraud,
arson,
assault on a federal officer,
assault with a deadly weapon,
grand larceny,
grand theft auto,
and murder in the first degree.
Miss Austen, how do you plead?
Not guilty.
Thus entered.
I'll now hear argument on bail.
Your Honor, we are requesting
that the defendant be remanded into
custody for the duration of the trial.
Your Honor, my client was free
pending arraignment.
- Now, she's a flight risk?
- She's the very definition of it.
She has one of the most
recognizable faces in America.
Where will she run?
Based on your prior history,
I'm inclined to agree wh the people.
You're hereby remanded into federal
custody for the duration of your trial.
- Your Honor, my-...
- Take the defendant into custody.
Sorry.
Subtitles: www.soustitreslost.com
Albuquerque?
Too hot.
- New York?
- Too many people.
More than Seoul?
What's wrong with Seoul?
Sun, we're going to leave this island
any moment now.
I learn english...
for you...
to live... in... America.
I want...
to raise my baby at home.
In Korea.
You mean our baby.
This is, Charlotte and Dan.
Their helicopter already took Sayid
and Desmond back to their freighter.
They can make arrangements
to get all of us off this island.
Where's Kate?
She stayed with Locke.
Is that blood?
I just...
killed a chicken.
What can I do for you?
I wanna talk to Miles.
Where you keeping him?
Why do you need to talk to him?
Well, that's personal.
- What gives you the right to decide?
- You may think this is a democracy
because of the way
Jack ran things, but it isn't.
Then I guess
that makes it a dictatorship.
If I was a dictator, I would just
shoot you and go about my day.
Dinner's at six if you're hungry.
Wait.
You bringing that to Miles?
- Yeah, Locke asked me to do it.
- Cool. That dude creeps me out.
- He's still in the rec room, right?
- No, I moved him to the boathouse...
You just totally
scooby-doo'd me, right?
Sorry.
- You're not gonna let him go, are ya?
- No. No, I promise.
Don't tell Locke it was me.
So the arab traded you too?
- Do you know who I am?
- Excuse me?
Do you know who I am?
Do you know what I did?
What did you do?
Answer me.
I'll tell you what you want to know,
but you gotta do something for me first.
- I'm not letting you go.
- I don't want to be let go.
I'm exactly where I wanna be.
What I want...
is one minute...
of someone's time.
You bring him to me,
and I will tell you
everything I know about you.
Who?
Who do you think?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
The D.A.'s decided
to try this case herself,
So they'll do the full court press,
and we need to talk
about cutting a deal.
What kind of deal?
Honestly, my best guess,
I'd say she'll take a 15-year sentence,
- and you serve seven.
- No way.
If you go trial, you're looking
at 20 years on each count,
not to mention a life sentence
on the murder charge.
You confessed to your mother
that you killed your father,
and now she's their star witness.
What am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to win this thing?
Put me on the stand.
And take a chance
with the D.A. crossing you? No.
Way I see it,
we've got one shot at this.
What?
We make it about character,
not about what you did or didn't do,
but about who you are.
What do you mean, who I am?
- I want him in the courtroom.
- Absolutely not.
- It'll generate tremendous sympathy.
- Duncan, listen to me.
You are not bringing him in here.
You wanna make this about me,
about my character? Fine.
But you are not using my son.
Maybe we should try a number
other than the boat, like... 9-1-1.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
- We can't contact their boat.
- You haven't heard from Sayid?
You said they left yesterday.
And I'm sure they're fine.
What if Locke was right?
What if they are here to hurt us?
Locke has no idea what he's doing.
Then why is kate with him?
You sure he's got Ben
in his basement?
I saw Rousseau
take him in there last night.
- Does Locke ever go out?
- He's been in there cooking all day.
He invited us all over for dinner.
Can you get Aaron for me?
Just pick him up
and rock him a little bit.
Yeah, I'm just...
not very good with babies.
I wouldn't want him
to get more upset.
Here, I got him.
It's okay.
Here we go, muffin.
Yeah. There we go.
You're so good with him.
What?
Just the last thing I ever thought
I'd be good at is being a mum.
You should try it sometime.
Hey, Aaron. Come on, sweetie.
Please rise.
Court is now in session.
Please be seated.
Don't fire me, okay?
What?
We got killed in the opening.
I had to do this.
Does the defense have a witness?
Yes, we do, Your Honor.
The defense calls Dr. Jack Shephard
to the witness stand.
Your Honor, I renew my objection
to this witness. He's irrelevant.
And I renew my overruling
of your objection.
Be aware that this witness
did not meet the defendant
until after the alleged crimes
she's being charged with.
He's to be viewed
as a character witness only.
- Proceed.
- Please raise your right hand.
Swear to tell the truth, the whole truth
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
Could you please tell the ladies
and gentlemen of the jury,
if there are any of you who don't read
newspapers or the Internet or watch TV,
how you met the defendant?
On september 22, 2004, Kate...
Miss Austen and I were both passengers
on Oceanic flight 815,
which crash-landed
on an island in the South Pacific.
Were you aware that Miss Austen
was a fugitive being transported
by a United States Marshal
on that flight to Los Angeles for trial?
- I did learn that eventually, yes.
- From the U.S. Marshal?
The Marshal died in the crash.
I never spoke to him.
Miss Austen told me.
Did you ever ask her
if she was guilty?
No. Never.
Seems like a reasonable question.
Why not?
I just assumed that there'd been
some kind of mistake.
And why would you think that?
Only 8 of us survived the crash.
We landed in the water.
I was hurt pretty badly.
In fact, if it weren't for her,
I would have never made it to the shore.
She took care of me.
She took care of all of us.
She gave us first aid, water,
found food,
made shelter. She tried to save
the other two, but they didn't...
Miss Austen, please, sit down.
This has nothing to do with...
With anything.
It's my trial, and I don't want him
to say anything else.
It's fine.
I have no more questions, Your Honor.
Miss Dunbrook, your witness.
That was very moving, Dr. Shephard.
I only have one question for you.
- Do you love the defendant?
- Objection!
You opened this door, Mr. Forrester.
I'll allow it.
Dr. Shephard?
Do you love Miss Austen?
Not anymore.
So what do you want to watch?
Xanadu or Satan's doom?
I'm reading.
- Turn that thing down, damn it!
- Sorry.
Can I come in?
Sure. I believe you know my roommate.
Got something in your eye, Hugo?
Why don't we talk in the kitchen?
I know it's in a box, but...
It's pretty damn good wine.
I tested it.
So how's the life at casa de Claire?
- Baby Aaron keeping you up all night?
- No, he's a good sleeper.
Good for you.
You're terrible at this, Freckles.
- Terrible at what?
- You said you didn't stay for me.
So at least be woman enough to tell me
you wanna use me for something.
I wanna use you for something.
See? Wasn't that hard.
- For what?
- For Ben.
I want you to help me bust him out.
- You wanna play some Backgammon?
- You're on.
Do you think I know what I'm doing?
Do you...
regret following me out here, or are you
worried about what we should do next?
All I know is I'd be a lot more worried
if I was sitting on that beach.
And the rest of the group,
what do they say?
I think they're saying,"baa."
That's the nice thing about sheep.
They're predictable.
But I ain't so sure about Kate.
What do you mean?
I need your word
you'll do nothing to her.
- Why would I do anything to her?
- Just give me your word.
- You know what? Forget it.
- No. All right.
You have my word.
She came to me about an hour ago.
Said she wanted my help busting Ben
out of your basement.
Why?
She talked to that guy...
Bruce Lee from the freighter,
the guy you got locked up.
He told her to bring Ben to him
to chat.
It's impossible.
She doesn't know where Miles is.
What? The boathouse down by the dock?
If Hugo knows, everybody knows.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yeah, sure.
- Where you going with that?
- Whatever Miles has to say to Ben,
he can say to me.
Son of a bitch.
Come on.
You got one minute. Go.
- How about some privacy?
- 55 seconds.
You know who I am?
You know who I work for?
Then you know he's put a lot of time
and energy to find you.
So now I found you, and I can tell him
exactly where you are.
Or I can lie and tell him
you were already dead.
And I'd be willing to do that
for $3.2 million.
You've arranged this meeting
so you could blackmail me?
- It's extortion, technically speaking.
- 3.2? Well, why not 3.3 or 3.4?
What makes you think I have access
to that kind of money?
Do not treat me like I'm one of them!
Like I don't know who you are
and what you can do.
- Your friend Charlotte knows I'm alive.
- I'll take care of her.
Just worry about getting me the money.
You have two days.
My present situation is a little bit
restricted. Can that be amended?
- One week, in cash.
- Time's up.
- Don't even think about...
- I said time's up!
- This is hot.
- You got your chat. I want my answer.
We got your name
when you called the freighter.
Of course, we know about you
and everybody else on the manifest.
- Then prove it.
- Your name is Katherine Anne Austen.
You're wanted for murder,
fraud, arson,
a whole bunch of other stuff
I can't remember.
You're a fugitive.
You got caught in Australia,
and the feds were bringing you back.
So, yeah, we know.
If I were you,
I'd stay right here on the island.
Who knows?
Maybe you didn't survive the crash.
Come on.
Go back to your house.
- This has nothing to do with you...
- Go back to your house!
You okay?
I couldn't sleep.
Yeah.
The beds take a little getting used to.
- I didn't wake Aaron, did I?
- No.
Aaron was born on this island.
He can sleep through anything.
- What are you doing?
- I'd like a moment alone with Kate.
Would you excuse us, please?
It's okay.
I don't need to know
why you did what you did.
I just need to know
what they said to each other.
Miles told Ben th he would lie
to the people he works for on the boat,
tell them that Ben was dead
for $3.2 million.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I asked you where he was...
You're not welcome here anymore.
I want you gone by morning.
You two can have a few minutes
of privacy.
- I don't need any privacy.
- You need to talk to her.
I'll be outside.
Hello, Katherine.
Was it true, what he said,
Dr. Shephard? That you're a hero?
- Why won't you talk to me?
- Because the last time I tried,
when you got sick,
when I risked my life to see you,
- you screamed and called the police.
- Please.
I don't wanna fight with you.
Why are you here?
Because...
It all changed
when I thought you were dead.
My doctors have given me
6 months to live for the last 4 years.
I don't know how long
I'm going to last.
I came here to tell you that I...
I don't want to testify against you.
Then don't.
I want to see my grandson.
You came here to make a deal?
I just wanna meet him.
I don't want you anywhere near him.
We're finished.
Hey, Freckles.
You okay?
I'm sorry I couldn't do nothing.
I wanted him to think
that you fooled me, too.
No sense in him
not trusting both of us.
He wants me gone by tomorrow.
What, he... banished you?
Well, I un-banish you.
You can stay...
right here.
This is my house.
Okay, me and Montezuma's house.
You're gonna be all right.
I'll keep you safe.
Time. OK, tell me.
What do you remember?
Okay... Queen of diamonds.
Then we... Six
of...
clubs! Sorry.
And we have the red ten of...
hearts, maybe?
It's two out of three.
It's not bad. It's progress.
Three cards, Charlotte?
Is that progress?
Been calling your boat all day.
Why isn't anyone answering?
We're here. How should we know?
- If they're not answering...
- Are you saying
there's only one line on that boat?
There is another number we're only
supposed to use in emergencies.
It's an emergency.
Put it on speaker.
- Regina, it's Charlotte.
- Why are you calling me on this number?
Minkowski wasn't answering.
The people on the island want to talk
to their friends, make sure they're OK.
What friends?
They left last night.
- Frank took 'em up in the helicopter.
- What do you mean, they took off?
I thought the helicopter was with you.
Morning.
Listen, I don't know
what you think you're doing,
- but you're wasting your time.
- Open your mouth.
Open your mouth. Wide.
Don't talk. Bite down, bite down.
I realize that when I tied you up
in here the other day,
I made the mistake of failing
to introduce myself. I'm John Locke,
and I'm responsible
for the well-being of this island.
Eventually, Miles,
you're gonna tell me who you are,
who are the people on the boat,
and why you're so interested in Ben.
In the meantime, however,
you're gonna keep your mouth shut.
I learned something yesterday.
No use having rules if there's
no punishment for breaking 'em.
You'll be fine
if you bite down on the trigger.
Enjoy your breakfast.
Wait. Wait a minute.
- Just slow down.
- Come on.
It's not like we ain't never done it
before.
Yeah, I'm cool
we didn't go all the way last night.
I get it. You were sad.
But, I mean,
how can you resist after that whole
"I'll keep you safe" thing?
What?
- What did I say?
- Just... forget it.
Oh, right.
You still think you might be pregnant.
I'm not worried.
And I'm not pregnant.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
I mean...
Would it have been
the worst thing in the world?
Yes, it would've been!
- What would we have done with a baby?
- I'm going back to the beach.
Beach?
What, you're leaving because of this?
That's that?
You crawl up in my bed one second,
- the next, you...
- Good-bye.
Don't make this about me. You didn't
want a baby any more than I did.
You're just looking for some excuse
to split, and now you got one.
That's all right, Freckles.
I ain't gonna hold it against you.
I'm just gonna sit right here
in my comfy bed,
because in about a week, you'll find
some reason to get pissed at Jack
and bounce right back to me.
Miss Dunbrook.
Are the people ready to proceed?
- May we approach the bench, Your Honor?
- Please.
Unfortunately, Your Honor,
our chief witness, Diane Jansen,
the mother of the defendant, is unable
to testify because of medical reasons.
How long will you need?
- I can't say right now.
- I'll grant a recess for lunch,
but be prepared to proceed
with your case after we return.
- This court is now in recess.
- All rise.
We have to talk.
My key witness spoke to her daughter
yesterday, and now she's got cold feet.
Quit posturing, and let's get to it.
What are you offering?
Four years in.
No jail time.
Kate Austen is a worldwide hero
who saved 5 other peoples' lives
after a plane crash,
and nearly starved to death
on a deserted island and after all that,
you put this woman on trial for rescuing
her mother from an abusive husband.
If you think that jury
is gonna give her actual time, then...
you must have a hell of a closing,
Melissa.
All right.
Time served, plus 10 years' probation
and agreement not to leave the state.
- What does that matter? She can go...
- I'll take it.
No. Wait.
Give me something to sign, I'll sign it.
And then I walk out the back door.
I just...
want this to be over.
I can do that.
10 years' probation,
and you stay put.
I have a child.
I'm not going anywhere.
How did you know I'd be here?
Your lawyer gave me the heads-up.
He owed me one.
Thank you.
For saying what you did.
You're welcome.
You know, I've heard you say
that story so many times.
I'm starting to think you believe it.
I just wanted to tell you
that what I said in there...
I didn't mean it.
You wanna follow me?
Come by for a visit?
I actually have to get over
to the hospital,
but maybe you and I could grab
some coffee together or something?
I know why you don't wanna see
the baby.
But until you do,
until you want to...
there's no you and me
going for coffee.
But...
if at any time you change your mind,
come and see us.
Hello?
Kate! I'm so glad you're back.
- He missed you so much.
- Did you keep him away from the TV?
Absolutely.
I put him down for a nap.
Hey, buddy.
Hi, mommy.
Hi, Aaron.
soustitreslost@gmail.com