Previously on Lost...
Now talk.
Think of the island like a record
spinning on a turntable...
Only now, that record is skipping.
Whatever Ben Linus did
down at the Orchid station
it may have
dislodged us.
Dislodged us from what?
Time.
Come on!
It's not stopping!
We have to go back to the Orchid.
That's where all this started.
Maybe it's where it'll all stop.
This is all happening
because they left.
I think it'll stop
if I can bring them back.
- Bring who back?
- Jack, Sun, Sayid,
Hugo, Kate.
Don't you want her to come back?
Sure you don't want us
to lower you down?
Where would be the fun in that?
John! Damn it, hold on!
I think you can let go of that now.
James, don't.
Come on! Help me!
Stop.
We can't help him.
Wherever John went, he's gone.
And wherever we are
is before that well was ever built.
Yeah, I'd say way before.
What makes you...
Can you hear me?
Can anyone hear me?
What the hell was that?
That one was different. It was...
That was more like an earthquake.
Wait!
Great.
My headache is gone.
Yeah, mine is too.
And my nose isn't bleeding anymore.
I think it's over.
I think John did it.
Now what?
Now we wait for him to come back.
For how long?
As long as it takes.
Are you kidding me?
I'm gone 10 minutes,
and you have a hootenanny?
Don't be such a bummer, man.
Rosie was just droppin' off brownies.
You should thank her.
She shouldn't be here, Jerry.
We're on the clock, man.
Mellow out, Phil.
What's gonna happen?
The polar bears are gonna figure
a way out of their cages?
That's not the point.
- If Lafleur finds out...
- He's not gonna find out anything.
- I'm gonna have to answer to him.
- Relax, man. Nobody's gonna find out.
Guys?
What...
- Is that a hostile?
- I don't know.
Is that...
Horace?
He's got dynamite.
- Get her out of here now!
- Rosie, you gotta get outta here.
Don't tell anyone you were here.
Just go. Go!
Okay, this is bad. This is bad, man.
- We gotta get Lafleur.
- 3 AM. You want to wake him up?
- Of course not...
- We can handle this ourselves?
And maybe Horace blows himself up,
and Lafleur kills us for not waking him.
We gotta go now!
- Do you wanna knock?
- You knock.
Fine.
What?
Mr. Lafleur, sorry to bother you, but
we got a situation out at the pylons.
What kind of situation?
It's Horace.
He's got dynamite,
and he's blowing up trees.
Son of a bitch.
Subtitles:
www.sub-way.fr (1.00)
Relax! I'm comin'!
- Hey, boss.
- Evening, Enos.
- You got your zapper with ya?
- Yep.
You wanna tell me why I need it?
'cause our fearless leader
is out blowing up trees.
Why's he doing that?
'cause he's loaded.
Since when does Horace drink?
He doesn't, so we're gonna
keep this on the down low.
Oh, man.
All right.
You put out that fire. Pack up
this dynamite. I'll take him home.
Why don't you put out the fire,
pack up, and I'll take him home?
You wanna tell Amy
where we found him?
Help me get him up.
Oh, my God. Is he okay?
- You tell me.
- Bring him inside.
The couch. The couch is fine.
- Where'd you find him?
- By the Flame,
blowing up trees with dynamite.
Wanna tell me why?
We had a fight.
Must've been a doozy.
Please, Jim.
- It's personal.
- Personal?
You think this isn't gonna get out?
It'll be on the coconut telegraph
by breakfast.
It was about Paul.
Go on.
What's the matter? You okay?
The baby... it's coming.
Oh, hell.
I'm not gonna tell her.
Don't even tell her. I won't.
- Where's Red?
- I don't know.
- I won't do it. Won't...
- Daniel?
You okay?
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna tell her.
Daniel, where's Charlotte?
She's not here.
She's gone.
Where?
She's... Dead.
She's dead.
There was another flash, and...
And she was...
She was just gone.
Her... Body just...
disappeared.
She moved on, and we stayed.
I'm so sorry.
Hold on. Wait a minute.
We "stayed"?
We're not traveling through time
anymore? You saying it's over?
Of course it's over.
Wherever we are now...
Whenever we are now...
We're here for good.
I won't do it. I won't.
Okay. Swell.
Until Dan checks back in,
I say we head back to the beach.
When Locke gets back with everybody,
that's where they'll be looking for us.
The beach? What, you didn't get
enough flaming arrows shot at you?
And your camp is gone.
Why bother?
Sawyer's right, Miles.
We should go back to the beach.
We survived there before.
- We can do it again.
- Or maybe when we get there,
You'll wanna go back
to the Orchid again.
When that gets boring,
we head back to the beach.
It's the only two plans
you people have.
Hey, zip it.
I'm heading back to the beach.
If our stuff's there, great.
If not, we build new stuff.
You don't like the plan, good luck.
Who put him in charge?
Thanks for getting my back
for that whole beach issue.
You should thank me.
It was a stupid idea.
Well, what does that say
about you agreeing with me?
Any plan is better than no plan.
Besides, if I hadn't agreed with you,
we'd still be arguing
about where to go next.
I just hope you figure out
something better before we get there.
Well, I'm open to suggestions.
Oh, no! No, Paul!
Oh, God! Oh, God! No, no, no, no!
No, please! We didn't know!
Paul, please,
please do something. No, no.
No, no, no.
We were just touring this park.
We didn't mean anything.
We were just having... Paul, please.
Oh, my God! No!
No, Paul, please. Please.
Who do you think they are?
Who cares who they are?
We don't even know when they are.
We don't get involved, right?
That's what you said.
It doesn't matter what we do.
Whatever happened, happened.
Yeah, thanks anyway, Plato.
I'm going over there.
- You still got my back?
- Absolutely.
- Talk to me, Paul!
- On your feet!
- No, I can't! I can't!
- Come on, get up! Now!
All right, drop the gun!
It's all right.
It's okay. You're safe.
It's over.
Who are you?
Her friend's wearing
a Dharma jumpsuit.
That put us '70s, '80s.
- The guys with the bags... Others?
- Beats me.
- What, y'all don't know each other?
- Before my time.
Walkie.
We need to go.
I'm on it.
Listen, sweetheart,
we gotta get moving now.
Who are you people?
Our ship wrecked here
on the way to Tahiti.
But that ain't important right now,
'cause whoever's
on the other end of this...
Those two might've given 'em a call
before we saved you.
We have to bury them.
Bury them?
We ain't got time to bury nobody.
We have to. The truce.
Oh, God. We have to bury them.
And we have...
And we have to bring it...
him back home.
We have to bring Paul back with us.
Please.
I'll carry him.
We'll put these guys in the ground
and carry your friend back,
but we better do it fast.
He wasn't...
my friend.
He was my husband.
All right, listen up.
When we get there,
there's gonna be a lot of questions.
Keep your mouth shut.
Let me do the talking.
You really think you can convince them
that we were in a boat wreck?
I'm a professional.
I used to lie for a living.
Daniel! Stop!
Turn it off.
Turn what off?
It looks like some sort
of sonic fence or something.
Where did you say
your ship was going?
Listen, sister, we're the ones who just
saved your life and hid those bodies.
So how about you trust us
and turn that damn thing off?
Okay, fine.
"Sonic fence"?
- Didn't I say let me do the talking?
- Dan would've fry his brain.
His brain's already fried.
Okay, it's off.
You first.
See? It's fine.
All right, let's go.
And going forward, we should all
do a better job of trustin'...
It hurts!
You're gonna be okay, Amy.
Just try and relax.
Where's Horace?
Does he know his wife's in labor?
He's unavailable.
Amy's in a very dangerous situation.
The baby's breech.
- What does that mean?
- It's upside down.
- She needs a cesarean.
- Don't tell me about it. Just do it.
I'm not an obstetrician.
Our women deliver on the mainland.
Amy was supposed to leave on Tuesday.
The baby's two weeks early.
Can you deliver this baby or not?
I don't know.
Hey, man. Where is she?
- What's up?
- Amy's having her baby.
What?
Did you hear me?
She's in trouble.
Doc says she needs a cesarean.
We had an agreement.
Screw our agreement.
He ain't never done one.
I'm guessing you have.
Don't you understand
that every time I try to help a woman
on this island give birth,
it hasn't worked?
Well, maybe whatever made that happen
hasn't happened yet.
You gotta try. You gotta help her.
You're the only one that can.
The baby's breech.
Did you try
an external cephalic version?
It's probably too late.
I'm gonna need a number 12 scalpel,
14-gauge sutures,
half-round if you've got them,
and an epidural anesthetic.
You're gonna need?
Where is Horace?
I'm speaking for Horace now,
and I say she's delivering this baby.
- I don't think it's a good idea.
- I want her.
I want her to do it.
You heard the lady.
Listen, you're gonna do great.
I know you are.
Is everything okay?
Amy went into labor.
I know.
Is she okay?
I don't know. There's a problem.
I pulled her out of retirement.
Any luck?
We finished grid 1-3-3 today.
No sign of our people. No one.
1-3-4 then.
How long do we look, James?
As long as it takes.
What happened?
It's a boy.
He's okay? She's okay?
Everyone's okay.
How's your head?
It hurts.
- Where are my people?
- They're fine.
Amy told me what happened in the jungle,
and I really appreciate what you did.
Well, y'all got a funny way
of showing your appreciation.
Look, we have
a certain defense protocol.
There are hostile indigenous people
on this island,
and we don't get along with them.
Why don't you tell me
who the hell you are?
My name's James Lafleur.
You can call me Jim.
How'd you get to the island, Jim?
If my friends are safe,
why are you asking me all the questions?
They told me I need to talk to you,
that you're the boat captain.
We got caught in a storm.
Our ship wrecked.
Must've hit the reef.
Thankfully, we washed up on shore.
- What kind of ship?
- A salvage vessel.
Searching for a famous lost wreck.
It's an old slaver
out of Portsmouth, England,
called "the black rock."
You heard of her?
Can't say that I have.
Once you got washed ashore, why were you
then wandering around in the jungle?
Some of our crew were missing.
We were looking for them.
That's when we came upon
your girl instead.
I tell you what.
If your crew shows up,
we'll send 'em along with ya.
Send 'em where?
There's a submarine that leaves
this island first thing in the morning.
You and your friends,
you're gonna get on it.
It's gonna drop you off in Tahiti.
You can find your way home
from there.
Hold on a minute, chief.
We just saved that woman's life.
Doesn't that earn us a week or two
to find the rest of our people?
Only people that are allowed
to stay on this compound
are members
of the Dharma Initiative.
And look, I don't want you to take this
the wrong way, please, Jim, but
you are not Dharma material.
We're screwed.
He's probably trying to explain
time travel by now.
- Sawyer's gonna be fine.
- What are you looking at?
I lived here for over three years.
That was my house over there.
You were in the Dharma Initiative?
The others took over these barracks
and wiped out most of the people
living in them.
They brought me here on a sub
a long time after that.
Well... Welcome home.
No more flash?
No more flash.
The record is spinning again.
We're just not on the song
we wanna be on.
- Where's dad?
- Come on, luv.
Charlotte.
Somebody will be along shortly
to show you to your rooms.
In the meantime, Mr. Lafleur here
can fill you in on the situation.
- "Mr. Lafleur"?
- It's Creole.
- I improvised.
- What happened in there?
He believed my story.
But we're getting punted.
Bastard's putting us on their sub
tomorrow and shipping us off to Tahiti.
How's that bad news?
- You guys, come on! Now!
- Let's go!
Get in! Get in! Move!
Come on! Inside! Move! Now!
Heather, keep an eye on them.
Hello, Mr. Alpert.
- Hello, Mr. Goodspeed.
- I wish you would've told me
you were coming.
I would've turned the fence off.
That fence may keep
other things out, but not us.
The only thing that does keep us out,
Horace,
is our truce...
Which you've now broken.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Where are my two men?
You know what?
Getting on that sub
is starting to sound like a great idea.
- What do you say? Sub anyone?
- Hold your horses, Banzai.
No one's getting on a sub.
Okay, Lafleur, how well
did you bury those bodies?
That depends on how hard he looks.
Call the Arrow.
Tell them we're at condition one.
Take the heavy ordnance,
and make sure
- the fence is at maximum.
- Yes, sir.
- Let me talk to him.
- Excuse me?
Your buddy with the eyeliner,
let me talk to him.
We had a truce with these people.
You don't understand.
I understand I'm the one
that killed his men,
- and I'm gonna tell him why I did it.
- I can't let you do that.
It's a good thing
I ain't asking your permission.
James, are you sure
you know what you're doing?
Not yet.
But I'll figure something out.
I'm sorry. Do we know each other?
I'm the guy that killed your men.
Heard some gunshots, saw two men
throwing a bag over a woman's head.
Gave 'em a chance to throw the weapons
and walk away,
but one of them took a shot at me,
and I defended myself.
- Is that so?
- That's so.
Your people know
that you're telling me this?
They ain't my people, hoss.
So if you got some kind of a truce
with them, it ain't been broken.
If you're not a member of the Dharma
Initiative, then what are you?
Did you bury the bomb?
- Excuse me?
- The hydrogen bomb with "Jughead"
- written on the side. Did you bury it?
- How...
Yeah, I know about it.
I also know that 20 years ago,
some bald fella limped into your camp
and fed you some mumbo jumbo
about being your leader.
And then poof...
He disappeared right in front of ya.
Does it ring a bell?
That man's name is John Locke,
and I'm waiting for him
to come back.
So... You still think I'm a member
of the damn Dharma Initiative?
I guess I don't.
But no matter who you are,
two of my men are dead.
And my people need
some kind of justice.
What are we gonna do about that?
How are you doing, Amy?
Is he gone?
- Alpert?
- No, he's not gone.
- We told him where the bodies were.
- You told him? Why?
We had to.
It was the only way
to maintain the truce.
Jim here worked it out
with him, but...
He's gonna need
something from us now.
He needs to take Paul's body
back with him.
Listen, we've been friends
for a long time, yeah?
So,
this is completely your choice.
If you don't wanna give him to them,
then we will suffer
the consequences.
They can take him.
He would want to keep us safe.
Can I have a minute, please?
I'm sorry.
You need some help?
Nah, I've got it. Thanks.
The sub leaving tomorrow morning...
It returns in two weeks.
Until then,
you can stay
and look for the rest of your crew.
I bought us two weeks.
Horace said we can wait
for the next sub.
Any luck, Locke'll be back by then.
And then what?
What do you mean, "then what"?
Locke said he was leaving
to save us.
The flashes have stopped.
They're over.
No more bloody noses...
We're already saved.
That sub behind you brought me here.
I've been trying to get off
of this island for more than 3 years
and now I've got my chance.
I'm going to leave.
You do realize
it's 1974,
that whatever it is
you think you're going back to...
It don't exist yet.
It's not a reason not to go.
What about me?
You really gonna leave me here
with the mad scientist
and Mr. "I speak to dead people"?
And Jin, who's a hell of a nice guy
but not exactly
the greatest conversationalist.
You'll be fine.
Maybe...
But who's gonna get my back?
Come on.
Just give me two weeks,
that's all I'm asking.
Two weeks.
All right. Two weeks.
Something smells good.
Hey there.
Is that for me?
You were amazing today.
Thank you for believing in me.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Wake up, boss.
How's your head?
It hurts.
I got good news and bad news.
What you want first?
Good news.
You're a daddy.
Bad news is you missed it.
Gosh.
Amy... She had the baby?
It's a boy.
A boy?
Now how about you tell me why you're
too busy drinking and blowing up trees
to see him be born?
I was...
I was looking for a pair of socks,
and all of mine were dirty, so I went
to grab a pair of Amy's, and...
I found this...
In the back of her drawer.
It was Paul's.
- You got in a fight over a necklace?
- I know.
But...
It's only been three years, Jim.
Just three years
that he's been gone.
Is that really long enough
to get over someone?
I had a thing for a girl once.
And I had a shot at her,
but I didn't take it.
For a little while,
I'd lay in bed every night, wondering
if it was a mistake.
Wondering if...
I'd ever stop thinking about her.
And now I can barely remember
what she looks like.
I mean, her face is...
She's just gone,
and she ain't never coming back.
So...
Is 3 years long enough
to get over someone?
Absolutely.
What?
Wait. What?
Don't bring 'em in.
Just meet me in the north valley.
Who was it?
- What's going on?
- It was Jin.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah...
I gotta go.