Previously on "lost"...
some lawyers came to see me.
They wanted to test to
see if aaron's my son.
You need to take care of them.
Wouldn't you do anything you
had to in order to keep aaron?
- Hello,kate.
- He's with me.
He's the one who's trying to take aaron.
It was me.
Sorry.
charlotte!
We have to go back the orchid.
That's where all this started.
Maybe it's where it'll all stop.
This is happening because they left.
I think it'll stop if
I can bring them back.
un homme a la mer!
What is your name?
Jin.
I am danielle. Danielle rousseau.
**********
*******
***********
********
**********
************
*************
*********
**************
*******
***********
why don't you leave me and my son alone?
Because he's not your son,kate.
- Move away,
kate. - Sun--
- I said,move away! - S-sun!
What are you doing? Where's aaron?
He's in the car.
Sun,listen. I know you
think you're helping--
if it wasn't for you,
jin would still be alive.
I didn't kill your husband,sun.
- Yes,you did.
- No,I didn'T.
Neither did anyone else,
because he's not dead.
- You're lying.
- No,sun.
Jin's still alive,*********
8,15,16,23,42.
8,15...
are you all right?
You rousseau? Danielle rousseau?
YeS. Th-that's right.
Where you from?
- We sailed from tahiti.
- When?
- November 15th.
- No. What year?
- Why?
- what's the matter?
I... I-I need go find my camp.
W-what camp?
You were on this island before?
You see helicopter?
***********
********
**************
*******
************
********
*************
is there an antenna on the island?
Hey,jin! Is--uh,please. Is
there,um... ra--a radio tower?
okay. Like that.
Is there a-a radio tower here?
Yes.
But I-I must find my camp because
maybe,uh,helicopter go there.
Do you know where
your camp is from here?
- no.
- How about from the radio tower?
Yes.
Then go with us to the tower.
Then we'll find your camp.
Okay.
************
Are you ready to go?
Yes.
Who are you hoping to find?
My wife.
8,15,16,23...
**********
*******
***********
*************
******
**********
*****
************
********
**********
******
nadine?
nadine? nadine!
************
*******
did you hear that?
What is that?
Monster.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Lost
Season05 Episode05
************
*******
**********
- we go find her.
- No. We must go.
You shut up.
AlleZ.
nadine!
Nadine!
**********
********
nadine! Nadine!
run!
what was that thing?
**********
******
****
********
no!
Do not leave anyone behind!
*********
No! No. You don't go.
With baby. No.
what wrong?
*************
*******
************
**********
**************
*********
*************
**********
********
***********
*********
***
*****
********
*********
- you!
- No!
- You disappeared!
- No! Please,wait!
- You're sick,too! You're a carrier!
- No!
turn around slowly.
Jin?
Sawyer?
Jin!
you gotta be kiddin' me!
I thought you were on that
boat. I thought you were dead.
No. No.
I--in water.
well,what do you say?
where is sun?
where did that guy come from?
I thought he was on the boat.
The blast must've
thrown him in the water.
He's been moving with
every flash,just like us.
every time the sky lights up,we...
move through time.
translate. Please. Translate.
You heard the man. Translate.
Uh,he's korean. I'm from encino.
he wants to know how you're
sure his wife is off the island.
You speak korean,red?
Obviously.
Tell him I'm sure,but none of it will
matter if we don't make it to the orchid.
*******
*********
*****
**********
*******
********
**********
bring sun back?
Why you bring her back?
Because she never should have left.
I've spent the last
three years thinking...
believing that he was dead.
You say you have proof that
he's not. I want to see it.
Why don't you put down the
gun? No one wants it to go off.
How do you know he's alive?
there's someone...
someone here in los angeles.
Let me take you to them,
and I'll show you the proof.
"someone"? Who?
The same person that's gonna shous
how to get back to the island.
Is that what this is about?
- You knew about
this? - No.No,I was--
and that is why you were pretending to care
about aaron,to convince me to go back there?
- I wasn't pretending anything.
- This is insane. You guys are crazy.
- Kate-- -
jack,don't!
Sayid,where areou going?
I don't want any part of this.
And if I see you or him again?
it'll be extremely
unpleasant for all of us.
30 minutes,sun.
We can be there in 30 minutes.
And you'll have proof--
proof that he's alive.
Or you can shoot me and never know.
Let's go.
how far?
It's just over the next ridge.
How you will leave the island?
I'm not sure yet.
I go with you.
No,no. It doesn't work
like that. It's a 1-man job.
- Why?
- I don't know why,jin. It just is.
But I promise I'll bring sun back.
you okay? You wanna take a break?
- let's just get there.
- Yeah.
So,uh... you speak any other languages?
Just klingon.
dan,is this gonna work?
It--it does make empirical sense that if this started
at the orchid,then that's where it's gonna stop.
But as far as bringing back people who
left in order to stop these temporal shifts,
that's where we leave
science behind. You okay?
oh,no!
come on!
charlotte!
Charlotte.
Juliet. You have a little...
you,too.
charlotte! Can you hear me?
Charlotte?*******
what'd she say?
don't let them bring
her back,no matter what.
Don't let them bring her back.
This place is death.
you said we'd be there in 30 minutes.
I didn't account for traffic.
Sun,I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
For leaving jin behind.
When we landed that
chopper on the boat...
everything was just happening so fast.
I knew he was down below,but I...
should've waited for him.
Why are you telling me this now,jack?
Are you going to ask me not to kill
ben if he's lying about my husband?
After what he just did to kate,
if you don't do it,sun,I will.
what are you doing?
What I'm doing is helping you.
And if you had any idea what
I've had to do to keep you safe,
to keep your friends safe,
you'd never stop thanking me.
You wanna shoot me? Then shoot
me! But let's get on with it.
What's it gonna be?
Drive.
Why can't daddy come with us?
Charlotte,can you hear me?
You know what my mum would say
about me marrying an american?
Yeah,I know more about ancient
carthage than hannibal himself.
What the hell is she talking about?
Have no idea.
Let's go. We have to keep moving.
All right,somebody help me with
charlotte. We're gonna have to carry her,.
no.She's gonna hold us up.
We--we can't
just leave her.
The flashes are getting closer together.
Maybe when your nose starts bleeding,
you'll realize we tta get out of dodge now.
We'll come back for her
just as soon as we can.
No. No way. We're not
gonna leave her behind.
Let them go without me,daniel.
No,charlotte. No. I'm not
gonna leave you behind.
the hell?
- We have to move now!
- He's right. Go.
- Charlotte-- -
just--no,just go!
charlotte... Oh,turn it up.
i love geronimo jackson.
we're running out of time,dan.
Go.
I'm gonna stay with he
let me ask you something,john.
If we don't even know
when the hell we are.
What happens if the orchid
ain't around anymore?
Look for the well.
You'll find it at the well.
Yeah,we'll be sure and do that.
Let's go.
we're here.
Thank god.
What are the odds that we would end
up in the same time as this thing?
you just had to say somethin'.
How the hell did charlotte
know this was here?
- daniel?
- Yes?
I've been here before.
You've been... you've been here before?
I grew up here,on the island.
mm,there was this thing...
the dharma initiative.
And then I moved away with my mum.
Just my mom,and I
never saw my dad again.
And then when I got back england,w-when
I would ask my mum about this place,yeah?
But she would say that it wasn't
real and that I'd made it up.
that's why...
I became an anthropologist--
to find this island again.
It's what I've been
searching for my whole life.
Charlotte...
why are you telling me this?
Because I remember something now.
when I was little...
living here,there
was this man--
a crazy man-- he
really scared me.
And he told me that I
had to leave the island...
and never,ever come back.
he told me that if I
came b-back,I would die.
Charlotte... I don't understand.
daniel. I... I think that man was you.
You're going down there?
What exactly e you hoping to find?
A way off the island.
You expecting a subway?
good-bye,james. Juliet,miles.
I'll see you when I get back.
No. Stop.
You don't bring sun back.
No,I have tobring them all back.
That's--that's how it works.
How you know?
I-I... I just know.
I will cut this.
N-no. You do that,you'll
kill every one of us.
This island is bad.
You don't bring sun back. You promise.
You promise you don't bring my baby!
All right. All right. You have my word.
Promise,john.
I promise.
I won't go to sun,jin,
but she might find me.
If she does,what do I tell her?
You tell her I'm dead.
You say I wash up.
You bu me.
Proof.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
you sure you don't want
us to lower you down?
Where would be the fun in that?
john.
If whatever you're attempting
to do actually works?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
what?
John! Damn it,hold on!
I think you can let go of that now.
No. No! No!
- James,stoP.
- No! No!
James,stop
come on and help me!
JameS.
we can't help him.
hold on. Hold on. It's
okay. Okay. Okay,hold on.
you gotta hold on. stay. Sta
stay with me. just stay,okay?
You're gonna be fine.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I've got a plan. I've got a plan.
When we were back at the
hatch,I talked to desmond.
I told him to find my mother.
She can help us,charlotte.
She will help us.
How can your mother help us?
She can.
She--
- Listen,listen.
- Yeah?
What?
I'm not allowed to have
chocolate before dinner.
charlotte?
Charlotte?
Charlotte.
no.
james!
Can you hear me?
Can anyone hear me?
who's there?
hello,john.
You?
what are you doing down here?
I'm here to help you
the rest of the way.
I don't-- I
don't understand.
You came to see me in the cabin.
You asked me how to save the island,
and I told you you had to move it.
I said that you had to move it,john.
but ben said he knew how to do it.
He told me that I had to
stay here and lead his people.
And since when did listening to
him get you anywhere worth a damn?
The good news... is
that you're here now.
Are you ready to go?
I-I d--I
don't know...
what to do once I get there.
There's a woman living in los angeles.
And once you get all of
your friends together--
and it must be all of
them,everyone who left.
And once you've persuaded
them to join you...
this woman will tell you
exactly how to come back.
who--who
is she?
Her name is eloise hawking.
What if can only convince
some of them to come back?
I believe in you,john.
You can do this.
richard said I was going to die.
Well,I suppose that's-- that's
why they call it sacrifice.
All right. okay.
oh,yeah,I'm ready.
good.
Now...
On the other side of this column here
is a wheel that slipped off its axis.
And all you have to do
is give it a little push.
could-- could
you help me
*******
say hello to my son.
Who's your son?
May I?
Take it.
how do you have this?
John gave it to me.
You said john never came to see you.
That's true,jack. I went to see hiM.
Jin gave it to him
before he left the island.
Why didn't locke tell me himself?
I don't know.
Maybe he never had a
chance before he died.
I'm sorry I had to bring you
here before I gave it to you,sun.
But all those people back on the
island,jin included,need our help.
There is a woman in this church,and she
can tell us how to get back to your husband.
But we're running out of time,
sun,I need you to decide right now.
Will you come with me?
Yes.
what are you doin' here?
I assume the same thing you are.
You're looking for faraday's mother,too?
Hello,eloise.
Hello,benjamin.
I thought I said all of them.
This is all I could get on short notice.
well,I suppose it'll have to do for now.
All right. Let's get started.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
www.tvsubtitles.net