???
It looks like we have some
breaking news out of Highway 894.
Terry Gillman, our traffic reporter,
joins us live with the latest. Terry?
Hello in the studio.
Are you guys getting this?
This guy's hauling through traffic,
heading southbound on the 894,
doing at least 100.
The real problem is he's driving on
the northbound side of the highway.
Well, Terry, we can see that a
police copter is in hot pursuit,
but are there any ground
units pursuing this guy?
No. Ground units broke off
when the suspect decided to use
a freeway exit as a freeway onramp.
This guy is crazy.
Whoa! Oh, my God!
Did you guys just see that?!
Oh, man. Oh, let's, uh...
hope, uh, uh, whoever
is-is in in the, uh...
is-is in the other...
other car lives-lives to, um... Oh...
There's something wrong with him.
TV News Helicopter, this is
Milwaukee Police Air Control.
You are dropped into restricted airspace.
Request you immediately climb
to 10,000 feet and hold.
Oh, I can't...
There's something wrong with Terry.
Uh, Terry, can you see anyone
moving out of either vehicle?
Are there any signs of life down there?
I can't... I can't see. My eyes...
There's something wrong
with my eyes. I can't...
I can't... I can't see.
I can't... Um....
Help me.... Uh...
I'm... I'm blind!
Did he just say he was blind?
Terry, are you okay?
TV News Helicopter, this is
Milwaukee Police Air Control.
You are on a collision course
with Police Air pursuit.
Turn immediately and vector 3-0-0-7
- and climb to 10,000 feet.
- Keep talking.
Repeat: turn immediately and climb.
- I can't see. I-I can't see!
- Turn immediately and climb.
Cut the feed!
I said, cut the feed!
Are you looking for someone?
The director assigned a trainee
to cover preliminaries and provide
support for this investigation.
An agent by the name of Lee?
Lee.
Kind of big guy?
Enthusiastic?
You know him?
Think I'm about to.
Hey. Dr. Hood.
Agent Young.
Hi. I'm Felix Lee.
Uh-oh.
I know what both of
you guys are thinking.
Really? Tell us.
Dr. Hood,
you're wondering why
the director would burden you
with some rookie agent at the
head of a very serious case.
Well, why would he?
Funny you should ask.
I know I don't have
much field experience.
And science-- not exactly MIT.
The whole tactical training
bit wasn't really my bag.
- So, what do you do?
- Recon.
I'd have to say recon.
It's easy for me
'cause I'm real good at blending in.
I'm like a mouse.
A 6'6" mouse.
Exactly.
What was Agent Young thinking?
Why I didn't flash my FBI badge until now.
Okay, so, what do we have here?
Well, the pilot's name
was Terence Gillman.
Reportedly suffered a loss of vision
right in the middle
of a live news broadcast.
Anyone on the ground when he crashed?
No. That's the only
good news, actually.
The pre-crash footage
was all over YouTube.
Think that where the director saw it.
Yeah. Prior to joining
the, uh, news team here,
Gillman flew for the FBI as part
of the Hostage Rescue Team.
The director served with HRT.
Yup. And Gillman saved his
life not once, but twice.
Well, that explains why we're here.
Solving this case just became personal.
So, Gillman was in perfect health,
and without warning,
his sight goes.
Yeah. I'm thinking river blindness.
Caused by those nasty little nematodes
that can live in the
human body for up to...
15 years.
Wikipedia.
River blindness?
Um, those nasty little
nematodes are fairly common in,
uh, Western Africa.
But not really likely Milwaukee.
Did we get anything from the autopsy?
Body was toast.
It was practically cremated.
Oh. So it will be pretty hard
to identify any other symptoms.
Oh. There was this.
Yeah. He was married.
I found it in the crash sight.
- We need to talk to his wife.
- Yeah.
Here.
She would want that.
I know I would.
Let's hope she's the only widow
we have to speak to while we're here.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@¥Û±¶
Sync:FRS@”Ó“‚
eleventh hour s01ep14
Terry loved that job so much, so much.
For the last five years,
he never missed a morning commute.
You know, it's funny.
He wasn't even supposed
to be working last night.
They just called him in
to cover the chase, and...
We're sorry for your loss, Mrs. Gillman.
I need to know what happened, please.
We believe Terry suffered
from something called,
uh, rapid onset blindness.
It's a very rare condition.
Need to ask you.
Did he complain recently of, uh,
poor vision or headaches?
Nothing.
He would have told me
if something were wrong.
Maybe he didn't want you to worry?
Terry took the responsibility
of being a pilot very seriously.
And he would have never flown
if he felt that he were impaired in...
...any... Oh!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Just... pregnant.
I never thought that I would
be raising a baby by myself.
It's not fair.
I want to have my husband back! I...
You'll let me know
if you find out anything?
I promise.
Thank you.
What now?
We find out from Mr. Gillman
if he had any more symptoms.
You can talk to dead people?
Remarkable.
He was on TV every day for
the last five years, remember?
Well, eastbound I-94 is
really gonna put a wrench
in this morning's commute...
What exactly are we looking for?
Any, uh, indication that he was sick...
Well, good luck.
In the three years I knew Terry,
he never caught so much as a cold.
It's gonna be a rough
one out there, folks.
In a bizarre twist, a few
lanes are blocked by chickens
who apparently fell off a delivery truck...
How long were you Terry's assistant?
Three years.
Couple months ago, I got
promoted to junior reporter.
It never would have
happened without Terry's help.
God. His poor wife.
She must be heartbroken.
You and Erica are friends?
Yeah.
We got thrown together
at a couple of office parties,
but we decided we liked each other.
She must feel so alone right now.
This is really helping.
Thank you, Debbie.
So, if I were to give you any advice...
That's the third time he's adjusted
the volume on his headset in two minutes.
Maybe the roar of the engine was too loud?
Well, why's he turning the volume down?
Could be, uh, hyperacusis.
It's, uh, extreme noise sensitivity.
Scratching his neck.
Why is that odd?
Well, it's odd if you have an itch
in the same place for three days.
Could be, uh,
dermatitis.
Deie, was the cabin,
uh, climate-controlled?
Yeah.
That's why I never flew with him.
He liked it arctic.
He kept the air conditioning at 65.
Freeze that, please.
Well, you can add
hyperhidrosis to the list.
Sweating when it's cold, right?
Yup.
My God.
Why didn't I notice this?
No. If he didn't notice,
why would you?
Um, what was the date
of the first broadcast
where we see Terry's symptoms?
The Monday before last,
so, two weeks ago.
- It narrows the timeframe.
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
I was the first person he told.
About them being pregnant.
He was so thrilled to become a dad.
911 just dispatched an ambulance
to Erica Gillman's house.
- Terry's wife?
- She's blind.
Dr. Nayar, I'm Jacob Hood.
This is Rachel Young.
We're with the FBI.
Oh, Dr. Hood, yes.
Hi.
How's, uh, Mrs. Gillman and her baby?
They're doing okay.
I-I have to say,
I've never seen this before.
She suffered spontaneous blindness,
but nothing in her medical
history relates to it.
Her husband had the same thing,
and it cost him his life.
What tests did you run?
Every diagnostic panel I could think of.
They're shots in the dark, huh?
Exactly right. So far,
we just can't make the connections.
Oh, you should know that
there's been a flurry of patients
with really strange combos of symptoms.
Really? Such as?
Pins and needles; numbness
in their hands and feet;
a lack of muscle coordination.
Skin rashes?
Memory loss?
Yeah.
What are you thinking, Hood?
Can you give me
uh, a specific example?
Well, um, this morning
a traffic cop came in.
He was having trouble writing tickets.
Also had a bad rash.
And this afternoon a woman was
complaining of numbness in her feet.
We're testing her for Buerger's disease.
- Minamata.
- Minna who?
All the symptoms point to it.
Minamata-- it's a...
it's a city in Japan,
and it's kind of where the real
dangers of heavy metal poisoning
were first discovered.
This chemical plant,
they dumped a load of
methyl mercury into the bay,
and it poisoned the sea life,
which was the town's main food source
and it devastated the population.
I'll begin targeted
hair and blood analysis.
If it is mercury poisoning,
we'll know within the hour.
- Thanks. We appreciate that.
- Yes.
Where would people be
exposed to mercury here?
I don't know.
That's what we're here to find out.
- Before this town ends up like...
- Minamata.
Yeah, that place.
???
Hey!
Oh, hi.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, how you doing?
Not good.
You know what that does
to the ecosystem around here?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You will be.
Once I give you a $500 ticket.
- $500? Come on, man!
- 500 bucks.
You're killing me.
Maybe next time you'll think about
what you're killing, "man."
Analysis of Erica Gillman's hair
indicated a mercury level
of 2.9 parts per million,
almost six times the normal range.
My other patients have
similar mercury levels.
Certainly enough to
prove mercury poisoning.
- Is it treatable?
- With chelation therapy.
We inject a binding compound
to collect any heavy metals,
then the body excretes them naturally.
The treatment should work.
For the other patients, maybe,
but not for Erica Gillman.
I don't understand.
If you know what's making me blind,
why can't you fix it?
In most cases,
the chemical used in
chelation therapy is safe.
Most cases?
It's not safe if you're pregnant.
Erica, right now the
mercury in your system
is being passed through the
placenta to your developing fetus.
With every minute that passes,
the danger of serious
complications multiplies.
My baby is sick?
The sooner we stop the, uh,
baby's exposure to the toxins, the better.
Erica, I need your permission
to perform an emergency C-section.
I'm in my second trimester.
My baby won't survive.
Preemies as young as 23 weeks have
gone on to live normal healthy lives.
Give me a percentage.
Every case is different.
I don't care about every case.
What are the chances
that my baby will survive?
10 to 15%.
Erica, before you make your decision,
you need to know that
without intervention,
you and your baby will
get much, much sicker.
The only way to treat you effectively,
is to treat the two of you separately.
I've lost my husband.
I won't lose my child, too.
You understand?
We're bringing in a
diagnostic team from the EPA
to help with this investigation.
Well, we're going to need it.
Identifying the mercury
was the easy part.
Finding the source--
that's gonna be difficult.
Any ideas?
Ah, well, the upside of
what happened in Minamata
is it was fairly contained.
But nowadays, the way
the food supplies are,
it could be up and down
the country very quickly.
Then how serious a health
risk are we talking here?
Well, I think from a few isolated
cases to a full-fledged epidemic.
Well, with only four cases so far,
let's keep our fingers crossed
that it stays that way.
Excuse me, I had a
mercury advisory issued to
all the local hospitals like you asked.
And every patient with the
appropriate symptoms is being tested.
It's not pretty.
They've already identified 25 new cases.
Six in the last hour alone.
So much for keeping
our fingers crossed.
We have to find the source.
Otherwise, what happened in Minamata's
gonna be like the best case scenario.
Where do we start?
I'm thinking,
a little of something the science
community calls immersive garbalogy.
Oh, yeah... Cool.
What's that?
Gillman on the address.
Got another one.
Hood, you can tell your friends
in the science community
that immersive garbalogy sucks.
Hey, Doc, isn't mercury
used in thermometers?
Used to be.
They don't use mercury anymore.
I'm pretty sure as a kid,
my mama put those things in places
mercury definitely should not go.
Yeah, well, even if they
didn't have toxic mercury
in their house as a permanent fixture
maybe they just had
to pass through it once.
Something they already ate
or drank in large quantities?
Yeah.
Yeah, but those other 25 victims
weren't all hanging out
at the Gillmans, were they?
No, probably not.
But, uh, there's got to be
some kind of common thread.
You Officer Walter Barrett?
Hi.
The traffic cop who had
trouble writing tickets.
And had the weird rash.
Uh, yeah, that's me.
Nice to meet you, Officer.
I hear your toxicity levels aren't
as high as some of the others.
But if you start to feel
nauseous or sick in any way,
- just let us know.
- Will do.
So, how can I help?
Well, as we go through this trash,
if you see anything
that you ate or drank
in the last couple of weeks,
you just tell us, okay?
Peanut butter?
No, I'm allergic to peanuts.
My head swells up
like a watermelon.
Mayonnaise?
Ew, never touch the stuff.
All those preservatives
give you Alzheimer's.
Well, the Gillmans
sure like their milk.
Lake Fresh.
I use that in my coffee.
How many times a day?
Breakfast, lunch, dinner,
and every hour in between.
Prevents gout.
Well, if there is toxic
mercury in this milk,
the compound on the swab
should find it pretty quickly.
It's positive.
Felix, call the Health Department,
have them issue an immediate recall
on all Lake Fresh dairy products.
I'm on it. Officer Barrett.
Doesn't the milk industry
have safeguards in place
to stop something
like this from happening?
Yeah, sure it does,
but it doesn't normally
include testing for heavy metals.
We can get the remaining
stock off the shelves
but what about the milk
that's already been sold?
- I don't know.
- Do it, okay.
Lake Fresh has, uh,
two local bottling plants.
They're shutting down production.
We need to investigate both.
We should split up.
This guy's all through traffic
heading southbound on the 894
doing at least a hundred.
The real problem is
he's driving on the northbound
side of the highway.
Ground units broke off...
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
How you doing?
All right.
I'm just putting together
a memorial segment for Terry.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sure it'll be amazing.
Oh, um, I know I told you I'd be done with
that wetlands pollution
piece by the end of the week,
- but it's just...
- It's okay, honey.
- I can't.
- Don't worry about that,
all right.
This is way more important.
Thank you for understanding.
I just wish...
I just wish there was
something I could do.
Something I could say.
I'll be okay.
I just, um...
I just miss my friend.
I know you do.
Agent Lee.
- ???
- Thank you.
It's Agent Lee.
We could use some good news, Felix.
Sorry, Lake Fresh East is clean.
The equipment is anyway.
Some of the milk is
testing positive for mercury,
but it is not coming from this plant.
Lake Fresh West is negative, too.
So, the milk was tainted
before it got to Lake Fresh?
Where does that leave us?
Well, the victims that drank
the, uh, poisoned milk,
they're the final link in the food chain.
Processing pnts--
they prepare their raw product for
distribution-- they're in the middle.
But it all begins with the dairy farms
and the cows that supply the fresh milk.
There have got to be, what,
at least a dozen dairy
farms in this area.
26, actually.
But according to the Wisconsin
Department of Agriculture's database,
only one supplies milk to
both Lake Fresh facilities.
???
All right, I'm forwarding the coordinates
to your onboard GPS, Agent Young.
Thanks, Felix.
I didn't know you could do that.
Afternoon.
Something I can help you with?
I need a refrigerator.
Something old.
Right this way.
I got a bunch of 'em over here.
How much for this one?
Uh, you don't want that piece of junk.
The compressor's shot and
the coils are rusted through.
Better to repair it
than buy a new one, right?
I'm big on recycling.
A sale's a sale.
Come on back. I'll write you up.
Cash or charge?
Oh, I prefer cash.
Works for me.
I already told you,
my girls are healthy.
This is quite a large barn
for such a small amount of cattle.
What happened to
the rest of your cattle?
I sold off some head to raise cash.
The ones I kept produce more
than enough milk to make my quota.
You expanding your dairy
to something more agricultural?
Looks like that field's just been plowed.
Rachel...
...will you give Felix a call.
Something I need him to grab for me.
??
???
Did I tell you I come from
a family of farmers?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, third generation.
And with the economy the way that it is,
it's impossible to
not cut corners, am I right?
So, uh, you understand.
I understand.
You did what you had to do, right?
Right?
They were losing weight,
staggering around a lot.
I figured it was mad cow disease.
I was really scared.
I euthanized them last week.
Your cow didn't have mad cow disease.
They had mercury in their systems,
which went directly into the milk.
Well, how could I have known that?
You knew they were sick,
and that's when you're supposed to
call the health department.
But instead, you just covered it up.
I was protecting my livelihood.
I was looking out for my family!
Really?
What about the families
who drank the milk?
Look, I don't think I should say
anything else until I talk to a lawyer.
You're going to need one.
Take him into custody.
??
Three generations of farming?
Well, now we know how the mercury
found its way into the milk.
But not how it got into the cows.
Every inch of this farm
has to be tested--
the feed, the grass, the water.
Turn everything over.
??11 inches.
Does everything look okay?
The baby's heart and lungs
are developing normally. So far.
It's your heart I'm worried about.
The longer you wait to treat this,
the more stress is put
on all your vital organs.
Erica, I don't want to lose both of you.
But you said the baby looked good.
Unfortunately,
there's no way of knowing whether the
mercury is affecting him at this time.
But, Erica, with the levels
in your system,
the chances are, it will affect him.
The question is how much.
Wait a minute.
You said him-- affecting him?
Is... is it a boy?
Yes...
you're having a baby boy.
Okay, so far we've run
trace metal screens
on the storage silos, feed troughs,
and the cattle feed itself--
all negative for mercury.
Jacob Hood.
Yeah, did you run the simulation
with a lower dose?
Okay. Well, thanks for trying.
What was that about?
It's the head of obstetrics
at Johns Hopkins.
I thought maybe a low-dose chelation
regimen might help out Erica's baby.
That didn't sound like a yes.
No, it wasn't.
You know, Doc,
when you're behind a desk,
??victims are just names
on a computer.
Out here it's different.
How do you deal with people
who've lost so much?
to tell you the truth, Felix, I haven't
really worked that one out yet.
Hood.
We checked out
Breen's remaining livestock.
All clean.
Well, that means the infected cows
ate something the others didn't.
Well, the remains have been sent out
for stomach content analysis,
but it'll take time.
Well, till we get the results,
all the local dairy farms are
going to have to be quarantined.
Isn't there a faster way to
figure out what those cows ate?
Faster?
Yeah.
Oh, don't tell me we're
dumpster-diving again.
??We don't really have to.
You're kind of standing in it.
Oh, crap!
You know, contrary to popular belief,
cows do not have four stomachs,
but they do have
four digestive compartments.
Girls must love you.
I do all right.
This is interesting.
??What's that? What? Let me see.
What the hell is that?
It's fish bones.
- Fish bones?
- Yep.
I thought cows were vegetarian.
Well, they may think they are.
But farmers have been
supplementing their feed
with meat by-products for years.
And the cheapest one is fishmeal.
Well, we need to find out
the name of this fishmeal distributor.
If other farms are still using it,
dairy products could be
just the tip of the iceberg.
Nailed it!
Tests confirm the fishmeal Breen
got from here is our source.
This is what his cows were eating.
Blue Fleet's wastewater
is laden with mercury.
Notify every cattle farm and feed house
that bought from them in the last 60 days.
I've already got disposal
teams out handling collection.
Agent Lee, exactly what kind of fish
does Blue Fleet process?
mostly menhaden and lake herring.
Herring?
I don't really like fish.
You know that, uh,
Three Stooges movie, where
Curly swallows that fish whole,
in the X-ray you can it
swimming around his ribs?
Freaked me out.
Anyway, there's, uh,
not really many kinds of fish that
can carry dangerous levels of mercury.
It's only really predators like,
um, swordfish, and sharks.
Big fish that eat other big fish.
I doubt we'll find swordfish
or sharks in the great lakes.
So, how'd the mercury find
its way into the little fish?
Lake Michigan is huge.
It's bigger than some countries.
There's no way we can search all of it.
You don't have to.
Someone's done it for us.
Let's see if we can find more seagulls.
The handy thing about gulls
is they'll eat anything.
So, if they've been feeding on
tainted herring
there's going to be signs.
What kind of signs?
Tremors, ruffled feathers,
droopy eyelids, um...
...violent behavior.
??
??Roll your window up!
You folks okay?
Yeah,
thanks to you.
Rachel, I think we really
need to get to the source
before it turns up somewhere
else in the food chain.
Oh, thanks for the, uh...
by the way, it's...
How long have you been with
the Department of Fish and Wildlife?
Long enough to see
the number of species facing
global extinction raise to 16,000.
The evidence that we're killing
our planet keeps piling up
and we keep ignoring it.
It's frustrating.
The only time the federal
government takes notice
is when their bottom line is threatened.
We're not the enemy, Officer.
- Is this your transmitter?
- Yeah.
We use them to track the bird's
breeding and migratory patterns.
Rachel...
this is why we're here.
If these sick gulls are
feeding from tainted herring,
we can use this
to lead us to the source.
So the GPS data from the bird transmitter
narrowed our search to five square miles.
This sonar will find any, uh,
foreign debris on the lake floor
that could be poisoning the herring.
What was that?
Only one way to find out.
Gas masks on.
Yeah, that's, uh,
that's liquid mercury.
Are those maggots?
Yeah.
Well, that'd certainly have the effect
of luring the fish toward the mercury.
What's the glass from?
It's a barometer.
yeah.
Old barometers had glass servoirs
filled with pounds of liquid mercury.
That's right--
Wikipedia?
??
This sure as hell wasn't an accident.
Someone could be out there
right now dumping more of this.
I think I know how to find him.
Liquid mercury is classified
as a hazardous material.
So if you wanted to buy this much
of it without a license, you'd...
Just get a truckload of
mercury-filled antiques with cash.
From a dealer who won't ask
too many questions.
Exactly.
yeah.
That was... that was a beautiful thing.
Okay, let's get every available
field agent from here to Detroit
canvassing antique stores
and local online dealers.
Felix...
find out who those
barometers were sold to.
It's the hospital.
Erica suffered a generalized seizure.
The uterine contractions triggered
a drop in the fetal heart rate.
Well, if nothing is done,
she'll lose the baby and her life
will still be in jeopardy,
so delivery is now the only option.
Yeah, she still won't give consent.
Well, can you blame her? She's facing
the toughest decision of her life.
And she can't even
ask her husband about it.
Then if I, I don't induce,
my baby will die? Is that for sure?
There's always exceptions, but, uh,
no, it doesn't look good.
If I make the choice and I fall on
the wrong side of the percentage,
I'm always going to wonder if I...
Not a great bet, is it?
No...
no.
Can I ask you something?
Sure, anything.
What would you do?
If it were your wife?
If it were my wife.
You know what...?
I think I'd say to hell with
the science, just go with your heart.
Agent Young.
How is she?
About to make the hardest
decision of her life.
She's having the baby.
They've got to induce.
I'll tell Dr. Nayar.
So what now?
We wait.
Excuse me, ma'am, official FBI business.
So, in the last six weeks,
local antique shops have sold
more than 30 mercury-filled barometers,
thermostats, and thermometers.
The parts recovered from the refrigerator
account for only half of them.
So that's over 200 pounds
of mercury unaccounted for.
Who bought the antiques?
A man using the name
of Lars Saunderski.
He left a phone number
with several dealers
so they could call him
when more barometers came in.
The phone number traced back
to a disposable cell phone
and the name doesn't exist.
actually, yes, it, it does, uh...
Larus saundersi-- it's the
Latin name for the Saunder's gull.
It's an endangered species.
Okay, so who in the hell uses
an endangered bird as an alias?
Sorry, do you mind me asking...
your, um, necklace.
Couldn't help noticing it's, uh,
it's beginning to oxidize.
There isn't a chance that
anyone, uh, been handling...
mercury could have, uh,
touched that, is there?
I mean, uh,
you don't know anyone
who works for the Department of
Fish and Wildlife or anything?
my husband.
He gave me this necklace last week.
Your husband.
??That would count.
Debbie.
You, you shouldn't be here.
What's in there, Ben?
Tell me you didn't
poison all those people.
It was the only way
to get their attention.
The toxic effects of mercury--
they're reversible.
Terry died...
and his wife could, too,
and their baby.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
Oh, my God.
Ben.
What did you do?
I did this for us,
for the baby we're
going to have someday,
and for, for their children, too.
My God, Debbie, th...
Th-This planet is under
attack and nobody cares!
But I do.
I mean, I'm...
I'm actually trying to fix it.
Do you know how crazy you sound?
No, aren't you the one
who's always telling me
that the only time people
sit up and take notice
is when something tragic happens?
that's what I give them, honey.
This is front page news.
Debbie, come on.
Debbie.
Let me explain.
There's nothing more
to explain, Mr. Finney.
You're coming with us now.
I did what I thought was right,
and when there's no fish
and no forests...
you'll wish you hadn't stopped me.
You killed someone.
I'm not sorry I stopped you.
??
??Ben Finney, you are under arrest.
How's the baby doing, Doctor?
Strong.
Like his mom.
Hey.
So...we recovered the last of the
antiques from Finney's storage unit.
You add to that
what we got off his boat.
Looks like we got it all.
Okay, so, um,
the lake should clean itself
within a couple of months,
and that's, uh...
Well, thank you very much
for all your help, Felix.
Please, don't mention it.
Oh, so I guess that's it.
Yep, this is it.
Okay, Agent Young.
Agent Lee.
- Dr. Hood.
- See you around.
You know, uh, I could hang
around if you guys wanted.
That's something that
I would consider if you asked.
But just know there are
several other posts at the Bureau
who have expressed interest in what it is
that I bring to the table and what I do.
Really?
That's weird 'cause
I spoke to the director
and he said that you begged
for this assignment.
Yeah, he did say that.
- Director said that?
- Quite specifically.
Okay, well, I'm just going to
be honest with you guys, then.
I think that the work
that you guys do...
...is awesome.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I just had to see it for myself.
Can I stay?
I don't know.
Rachel, what do you think?
It's your call.
I guess I can deal with him.
You're not going to make me
regret this, are you, Felix?
??Doc, please.
It's the Three Musketeers,
one nation under a groove, baby.
That's kind of what I mean.
welcome to www.1000fr.com