Previously on Alias:
Tonight at 2200 hours, the CIA will conduct
simultaneous raids on all Alliance facilities.
And tomorrow morning, God willing,
the Alliance will no longer exist.
- Let's move in.
- Go. Go. Go.
- Three agents down at SD-2.
- SD-9 has four down.
We've gotten reports
from all team leaders.
We appear to be in control
of all Alliance facilities.
So congratulations, sir.
The Alliance is gone.
I just wanted to let you know
that Phase One is complete.
Good. Move on to Phase Two.
I've been asked to confirm
that you are in position.
Yes.
Everything's in place.
Maybe when we're done here,
we should go back to Fiji.
Yeah, we should.
It was so great.
I'm gonna take a shower.
- You're early.
- I've been compromised.
How?
Something I said.
How do you want me to handle it?
Use her to send a message.
Make it public.
I heard you were here.
I couldn't sleep.
I was afraid I'd wake up
and find out this was a dream.
I went for a run to clear my mind
and I ended up here.
- Any word on Dixon and Marshall?
- They'll be in debrief for a while.
Meanwhile, Sloane's been put
on Interpol's most wanted list.
- About last night...
- Is this gonna be about Alice?
- I know it's complicated.
- We're not together any more.
- Since when?
- Since this morning.
The truth is,
we'd been over for a long time.
I was thinking...
I can actually go to the CIA
through the front door.
And I can actually give you a ride.
Folks, this is Christine Phillips,
our new Clandestine Services graduate.
Langley's approved her observing
our operations over the next few months.
- Hi.
- FBI Assistant Director Kendall.
This is Agent Michael Vaughn.
Agents Jack and Sydney Bristow.
I've read your operational file.
It's a real honour.
Thanks.
Sir, we got a situation in Berlin.
The networks are carrying it live.
- I'm putting it through to central display.
- This is all that we know so far.
A woman apparently has been shoved out
of a van, a speeding white van, we're told.
This is in a public square...
- Oh, my God.
- Sir, that's Agent Wallace.
- You know her?
- She's one of ours.
Give me a better look
at those explosives.
- Looks like C-4.
- If the C-4's wired with a remote trigger
any radio communication
could cause detonation.
You're doing fine, Emma.
Just do what I told you and you'll be fine.
Patch me through to the federal office
in Berlin. You speak German, right?
We'll have satellite coverage
in the next 30 seconds.
KH-11 coming on line now.
Bump up the resolution.
Sir, I've got the federal office
on the line now.
Tell them to put you through to the ranking
agent on site. Tell them the woman is CIA
and any random radio communication
could detonate the explosives.
All around the cobbler's bench
The monkey chased the weasel
The monkey thought it was all for good
Pop goes the weasel
A penny for a spool of thread
A penny for a needle
That's the way the money goes
- Pop goes the weasel...
- Come on, come on, come on, come on.
I speak English.
No patience to wait till time goes by
We're monitoring the situation. Instruct
your agents to cease radio communication.
This woman may be wired
with a remote detonator. I repeat...
Agent Bristow,
I have already ordered radio silence.
Pop...
Excuse me.
Are you all right?
- Hi.
- Are you OK?
Sorry, I just wasn't ready for that.
Don't be sorry.
The CIA lost an exemplary agent today.
Those of you who knew Emma Wallace
may find it difficult to focus,
but I'll ask you to try.
For the last two months, she was tasked
with a deep-cover assignment.
Her objective was to gain
the trust of this man.
Dr Renzo Markovic,
a former R & D scientist
who's been developing
a new classified technology
under the project heading "Helix".
He's already received preliminary bids
from several terrorist organisations.
- Weapons?
- We don't know.
That's the question that Agent Wallace was
trying to answer before she was murdered.
Agent Wallace may not be the only
casualty in our effort against Markovic.
She was sent undercover
with a partner, another CIA operative,
whom we now presume
to be captured or dead.
His final satellite transmission indicated
he was proceeding to Cayo Concha,
off the coast of the Dominican Republic.
Markovic leases one of the lower floors
in the Sirena del Sol resort,
where he conducts his research. If our
operative's still alive, he's being held there.
Agent Bristow, you're on point.
Agent Vaughn, you'll be assisting.
Conditions for success are twofold.
Acquire what intel you can on Project Helix.
- And bring our man home.
- Who is he?
He's one of our most decorated agents.
Here's his file.
James Lennox.
You leave tonight.
- Hi.
- Ready to go?
- Yeah, come on in, I'll get my stuff.
Nice place.
- I'm gonna get a new couch.
- Yeah?
I don't know.
So this is where you live?
- This is where I live.
- I love it.
I'm ready.
OK, we should go right now.
- Hey.
- Francie.
- This is Michael, from the bank.
- Hiya, Francie, nice to meet you.
- Nice to put a face with the name.
- Same here.
- We should catch our plane.
- Another business trip?
Just a finance conference
in New York, just overnight.
- Have a good trip, you guys.
- Thanks. It's nice to meet you.
- You too.
- Bye.
I'll see you later.
It's so easy to blow up your problems
It's so easy to play up your breakdown
It's so easy to fly through a window
Arden Jezek. He's Markovic's
chief of security at the resort,
which means he's got access
to Project Helix
and probably knows
where Lennox is being held.
Why aren't we going
after Markovic directly?
Our surveillance teams say
they lost track of him four weeks ago.
Jezek's our best shot.
It's so tough to get up
It's so tough
Hi.
I've injected you with a cardiotoxin.
You'll have a heart attack within the hour
unless you do exactly as we say.
- Then you get the antidote. Are we clear?
- Yeah.
- Is Agent Lennox still alive?
- Yes.
Where is he?
Sublevel, room 47.
You'll escort us down there
and you will help my partner download
everything you have on Project Helix.
Smile.
They are with me.
- I'll see you at the exit point.
- Yeah.
Sydney.
If Agent Lennox is still alive,
he may have undergone
psychological reconditioning.
You could be walking into a trap.
- Let's start over, from the beginning.
- I've already told you everything.
My name is Sydney Bristow. I'm a CIA
agent. I've come to take you home.
I can't see. I can't see.
I can't see.
They used metachlorazine on you.
It's a photoreactive acid.
I'm covering your eyes with a bandage.
Keep this bandage on or you could be
permanently blinded. You're OK.
You're sweating because the poison's
taking effect. Type and you'll be fine.
You're in the system.
- You're doing great, we're almost out.
- My partner, has she reported in yet?
- What happened?
- Stay here.
Thank you. Shut your eyes.
Shut your eyes.
OK, one more.
Oh, man.
Your eyes should normalise
in a few minutes.
OK.
Thank you.
You OK?
What do you think?
No signs of any
post-traumatic stress disorder
or symptoms of behaviour modification.
He was holding his own
with the interrogators
and he risked losing his sight
to get us out.
I don't know.
We'll know more after the psych eval.
- How are you doing?
- I could've sworn you were a blonde.
I was.
My hair's usually brown.
Hard to keep track.
It's nice to see the face
of the person who saved my life.
So, um...
where is, uh, Emma?
Is she, uh...
Is she back in LA?
Jim...
Emma's dead.
I'm so sorry.
We know that you've been through hell,
Agent Lennox,
and I apologise that your homecoming had
to be celebrated with a psych evaluation,
but you've been given
a clean bill of health
even though I'm sure
it doesn't feel like that.
Agent Wallace's death has left several
questions unanswered.
Can you tell us how you infiltrated
Dr Markovic's organisation?
We were hired on as freelance security
experts at his villa in Berlin.
Emma... Agent Wallace gained Markovic's
trust enough to become his driver.
In that capacity,
she was privy to a phone conversation
between Markovic and someone
she believed to be his superior,
in which they indicated Project Helix
was ready for testing.
Are you saying that Markovic
answers to someone else?
That was Agent Wallace's impression
based on the conversation.
They didn't use names,
it was just a voice on the speakerphone.
- And you never heard this voice yourself?
- No.
How's your eyesight?
- It's better.
- Can you tell us what led to your capture?
When we reported to Langley
the project was proceeding,
we were ordered to break into
the facility in Cayo Concha
and hack the central database. I knew
there was a good chance we'd be caught.
I decided to go in alone so I could transmit
the data to Emma in Berlin
if I were trapped.
They moved in before I could do that.
Do you have any idea
how she was compromised?
No, I don't.
OK. I think we have a pretty
comprehensive picture here.
There's a driver waiting
to take you to a safe house nearby.
Is there anything you'd like to add?
We were engaged.
In a case like this, we start by digitising the
news footage that covered the bombing.
Uh-huh.
You, uh, you like Italian food?
I have a boyfriend.
- Yeah. Me too.
- Hey, Weiss.
Excuse me.
I think the new girl has a thing for me.
I was going over
Agent Wallace's contact log.
Now, she phoned in
every two days like clockwork.
I mean, the slightest
discrepancy in protocol
and she contacted us for verification.
- Your point being?
- The day Lennox says he was captured,
we have no records of anything from her.
No warning, no extraction request, nothing.
Why didn't she make contact?
Agent Weiss.
Roll it back.
That flash of static right before the blast.
An RF transmitter would account
for the interference,
but all radio signals were shut off.
Wait, uh, run it back.
Slow it down a little bit.
- There.
- So if the signal interrupted the feed,
it had to have come
from our triggerman's detonator.
Which would place him
within a block of this camera.
All right, find out where the news van
was parked. Check all ATMs, traffic cams.
All right? We may just have
this guy's face on video.
Lennox?
Jim?
Beware of the grieving man
and his bottle.
Emma used to say
that she had spent so much of her life
pretending to be other people
that she was afraid she might disappear.
I have been sitting here
trying to remember all her aliases.
You're right.
It's hard to keep track.
I lost my fiancé last year.
And I know we were trained
to compartmentalise
things that hurt too much,
but I still haven't been able to do that.
And as hard as it is, I...
I would rather feel it
than to not feel anything.
Hey.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
Agent Bristow?
Agent Lennox?
- What's going on?
- Back up against the wall.
- What is this?
- Why?
- What...
- What are you doing?
- All right, stay down.
- Lennox. Lennox.
Stay down.
Sydney, go.
- Hey, hey.
- Sydney, go.
- OK.
- Stay down.
Go, go. Sydney, go.
OK, take it easy.
Take it easy. What is it?
He's gonna be placed
in federal custody.
What's going on?
We've decrypted the specs on Project
Helix that you and Vaughn obtained.
The data describes a breakthrough
in next-generation molecular gene therapy.
It refers to a new procedure whereby
a patient's face and body are reshaped
to identically resemble someone else.
Agent Lennox was
the first test subject to be doubled.
- Doubled how? Like cloning?
- Not exactly.
So you're saying the man
that we rescued isn't Agent Lennox?
- It's possible.
- So who is he?
Based on our intel
the procedure's first recipient
was the man who created
the technology - Dr Markovic.
There is no way the man we have
in custody is Dr Markovic.
I know it sounds insane. But as
we were analysing the news footage,
Phillips noticed the interference of an RF
signal, which helped narrow our search.
We got this from a traffic camera.
Over the last few years,
it's become common practice
for wanted terrorists
to employ men who look like them.
Decoys designed
to mislead intelligence agencies.
With this new procedure,
that would no longer be necessary.
Men like Osama Bin Laden could simply
be made to look like someone else.
Clearly, that is not something we can afford
to have advertised on the black market.
How is this possible
without obvious scarring?
The procedure isn't surgical.
The patient's genetic code is altered
to reshape their physical attributes.
- Is it reversible?
- It's unclear.
It only works on people
of a certain genetic disposition,
and the recipient must be induced
into a comatose state for several days
while their cells regenerate.
The data indicates the only way to
distinguish the real person from the double
is by an ocular scan.
A flaw in the iris was deliberately built
into the procedure to tell them apart.
Even if Lennox is who he says he is,
there is no real way of guaranteeing
that he's not the man in that video.
I'm telling you, the man we rescued just
had his life destroyed. He's on our side.
He is who he says he is.
What the hell do you mean,
I've been doubled?
- The project you were investigating.
- Project Helix, what about it?
- A prototype surgical gene resequencer.
- All right, meaning what?
Markovic created a technique that allows
people to change their appearance.
That's why we gave you the ocular scan -
to make sure that you were really you.
Do we know who it was?
The man who took my identity?
Dr Markovic.
Now I know why Emma
didn't call for an extraction.
She had no idea I was captured.
We had a hotel room in Berlin.
She thought she was with me.
Markovic had the Helix prototype
taken off Cayo Concha.
- We tracked it to a freight yard in Poland.
- He's trying to hide it.
What's the next move?
I've been ordered to find the prototype,
download the schematics, then destroy it.
I'm coming with you.
This is Mountaineer.
We're in position in the train yard.
Copy, Mountaineer, we've got you
on satellite. We're reading five guards.
One on the north side of track two.
One between tracks one and two.
Two on the southern perimeter.
One on top of the centre car.
Wait, we just lost the last guard.
Hold while we reacquire his signal.
Do you have the drill?
Drill.
All right, I'm having trouble
seeing the third tumbler.
- OK, the borescope's jammed, hang on.
- Do you have the audio?
All right, here we go.
All right, all right, all right.
- We got it.
- OK.
I'm gonna rig the explosives.
All right, Boot Camp,
I'm into the data log.
Copy that. Standing by
to receive the schematics.
All right, wait a second. According to
this, the sequencer's been used twice.
What?
I'm not the only one
who's been doubled.
Who else?
It doesn't say.
Agent Vaughn. A call was routed through
the PBX you need to take right away.
- Who am I talking to?
- My name is James Lennox.
The man you rescued
is Dr Renzo Markovic.
I know that sounds impossible.
He's developed some kind
of genetic doubling prototype.
- We know.
- I was captured trying to infiltrate
his medical lab on Concha Cayo.
They knew the CIA would send in a team
after me and they set you up.
I just escaped 12 hours ago while they
were trying to transport me off the island.
- Where are you now?
- I'm in Poland.
I've tracked the prototype
to a freight yard here. I'm gonna destroy it.
I got him. He's two miles away
and travelling alone.
It could be Markovic.
A guard may have alerted him
and he's now trying to prevent us
from sabotaging the prototype.
There's no way to be certain.
I'd like to believe you, but we conducted
a test confirming Lennox's identity.
The ocular scan?
The ocular scan doesn't work.
That was disinformation he wanted you
to download, so you would trust him.
The ocular scan is a joke.
Listen carefully:
do not approach the train yard.
I'm losing you.
Hello? I can't hear you.
Hello? I'm losing you. Hello?
Put me through to Sydney on a separate
channel. I only want her to hear this.
Got it.
Sydney, don't react, just listen. Do not
take your eyes off the man you're with.
We just got a call from someone claiming
to be the real Agent Lennox.
He's on his way to you now
and it looks like he's alone.
Clear your throat if you copy.
Backup copy.
Sydney, there's no way for us
to verify the identity of either man.
Disarm the man you're with,
then take cover
so you can do the same
to the man heading your way.
Once they're both secured,
lead them to the extraction point.
We'll figure this out
when they're in custody.
Don't move.
What are you doing, Sydney?
Against the wall, on your knees,
hands behind your head.
Put your hands behind your head.
On your knees.
He's secure.
How far away is the other man?
What other man?
You think I'm Markovic.
Cloud cover's moved in over your position.
We're blind, but he's gotta be right there.
- Sydney, Sydney, you have to trust me.
- Cuff yourself to the rail.
All right. If someone is headed this way
claiming to be me, it's Markovic. All right?
- I'm telling you, he is setting us up.
- Then why's he travelling alone?
Because he knows if our satellite picks up
a security team headed this way,
we won't hesitate
to destroy the prototype.
All right, it is his only play
to get his face back.
Sydney, he killed Emma.
He will kill you.
Hold it.
Drop the gun and turn around.
You don't work for Markovic.
You're CIA.
- I'm Jim Lennox. I'm CIA too.
- Drop the gun. Drop the gun, now.
- Put the gun down.
- Markovic's men are on their way here.
Drop it or I'll shoot.
We have to trust each other.
Get down.
Sydney?
- Drop it.
- You son of a bitch.
- He's lying. He has to say that.
- I was tortured for four weeks.
- He knows enough to pass as me.
- Don't listen. He took my life.
You're not walking out of here.
Neither of you can drop your guns.
What are you doing?
I hope you like your face,
Dr Markovic.
You're gonna have it for a long time.
Don't!
Yeah, all right.
Appreciate it.
Four weeks off.
The least they could do.
Yeah, well, they offered me counselling,
but I haven't not worked in eight years.
Where are you headed?
Fiji. I've never been there before.
Emma and I were gonna go
for our honeymoon.
She was from there.
I know.
I knew her.
You knew Emma?
One thing about my fiancé.
I was lucky to have known him
for as long as I did.
Thank you.
Where do we go?
Nobody knows
I've got to say I'm on my way down
God give me style and give me grace
God put a smile upon my face
Where do we go to draw the line?
I've got to say I wasted all your time
Oh, honey, honey
Where do I go...
You're so beautiful.
Dinner's ready.
We do have an oven, you know.
We can reheat.
Yeah
And ah
When you work it out
I'm worse than you
Yeah, when you work it out I wanted to
And ah, when you work out
where to draw the line
Your guess is as good as mine
Where do we go?
Nobody knows