OK, I'm in.
Agent Bristow works undercover with her
father, Jack Bristow, also a double agent.
Get down.
I guess we'll just have to
learn to trust each other.
Bristow's CIA contact: Michael Vaughn.
My guardian angel.
Her current assignment:
to infiltrate and destroy SD-6,
a secret organisation
dealing in espionage, extortion,
weapon sales, posing as the CIA.
SD-6 has made over $400 million
in arms sales alone.
The sanctity of this agency requires
the sacrifice of some personal freedoms.
This is not about cutting off an arm of the
monster. This is about killing the monster.
Bristow's mother:
formerly Russian intelligence,
recently turned herself in to the CIA.
Mom?
Intel indicates she may still be
an enemy of the United States.
The true loyalty of Agent Bristow's mother
remains unknown.
Previously on Alias:
I want to make something
very clear to you.
If Sydney in any way becomes victim
to your endgame...
I will kill you.
You haven't told her what you did to her
after I disappeared, have you?
Mom says there are no explosives
or anti-intrusion devices.
- She says the building is clean.
- We obviously can't trust this information.
Unless she wants to prove herself.
That kind of hopeful thinking
will get you killed.
We're sending you to Madagascar
to retrieve the Bible.
You too.
Prepare to leave tonight.
Let's move it.
Jack, I owe you.
But why 30 pounds of Semtex?
I need you to make sure that if anyone
enters that building no one will survive.
Sydney, hold your entry.
That building is wired to explode.
I need you to take a look under the house.
Is there a crawlspace?
She lied to me.
Another child is born
Another race is won
Another dream is shattered
Another day's begun
Five weeks ago, Irina Derevko
surrendered herself to the CIA.
She claimed that
she wanted to cooperate,
to seek restitution for the crimes
she committed against the United States.
During the next several weeks,
Irina Derevko provided meaningful
intelligence to the CIA.
- On several occasions...
- Pardon the interruption, Agent Bristow.
Let's talk about last week,
the incident in Madagascar.
Before Derevko turned
herself in to the CIA,
as leverage, she concealed
her organisation's operations manual.
Last week, the CIA
discovered where it was hidden.
When I told Derevko that I was going in
to retrieve the manual,
she informed us that
the building was safe to enter.
In truth, it was a trap.
Derevko had rigged it with explosives.
Just as we were about
to enter the building,
an agent spotted something
on the satellite imagery.
- That agent was your father.
- Yes.
He saved my life.
I wanted to stand in this cell.
Just once.
You tried to warn me about her
so many times.
I'm so sorry that
I didn't listen to you.
Some things you need
to experience for yourself.
I imagine every parent tries
to protect their children from that truth.
I never said thank you
for saving my life.
We're due for a briefing at SD-6.
We should go.
Niels Haider, the so-called "Austrian
Connection", was murdered yesterday.
The bold nature of the hit, the complete
disregard for civilian collateral damage
indicates the work of the Triad.
Haider was Triad.
They killed one of their own?
Yes. We believe so.
The Triad?
You never mentioned them.
It's a loose coalition
of organised-crime entities.
They deal mainly in drugs and prostitution,
but over the last couple of years
they've made a significant foray
into weapons.
OK. So why did they kill Haider?
Because he was selling Intel to SD-6.
In his last communication
to our sources in Vienna,
Haider informed us
that the Triad was engaged in a plot
to deploy and develop
16 next-generation weapons.
Any idea what
"next-generation" refers to?
No, which is
a major source of concern.
According to the communiqué, testing
of the weapons was ahead of schedule,
which means they may soon
be put into the field.
Do we know
where these weapons are now?
Budapest. During the Cold War,
the Russians built a massive bomb shelter
underneath the magistrate's bureau.
The Triad has been using that shelter
to serve as a testing facility.
Your mission is to gain access to that
facility, identify the nature of the weapons,
retrieve the specs and test data
off the central server,
then proceed to the R & D lab
and photograph the weapons.
So that SD-6 can engineer the weapons
for themselves.
- Which we won't let happen.
- OK.
I'll confer with your father
about your countermission.
My father?
He didn't tell you?
Based on your father's instincts
in the Madagascar incident,
Devlin gave him operational approval.
When you and I were
approaching that building
Ops was monitoring our progress
via sat radar scan.
Now, at the last moment,
your father switched to infrared,
which is how he saw the explosives.
We don't have routine satellite coverage
over Madagascar.
One had to be retasked. Now,
the closest one was over the Indian Ocean.
Yet your father specifically requested
the one over the South Atlantic,
which of the two is the only one
that has infrared capability.
He wanted to account
for every possibility.
Probably.
Or it's possible that he already knew
there would be explosives at that entrance.
I don't see how.
He never trusted
my mother's motives, but he...
You think my father
wired that entrance?
To set up my mother?
We were nearly killed.
- I know.
- If there'd been comms interference...
- It wouldn't be the first time.
- Meaning what?
- Russek.
- Russek?
- Your father set him up.
- I was a prisoner.
- Sloane was about to have me executed.
- I don't know why you deny this possibility.
I understand that your authority
has been superseded by my father
and that maybe you feel irrelevant.
But he saved our lives.
Remember that.
I will wait to hear from you.
- Hey.
- Hi, you look fabulous.
- So do you.
- I am so proud of you.
- Thank you.
- Where did you find all these people?
- Can you believe it?
- I invite a hundred, thinking 70 will show.
- You said you were worried.
- He tells his entire NA meeting.
- They're good people.
I'm sure they're fantastic. But we make
90 per cent of our profits from the bar.
They don't drink.
Baby girl, where you at?
Got no strings,
got men attached
Can't stop that feelin' for long, no
You makin' dogs wanna beg
Breaking them off your fancy legs
But they make you feel
right at home now
See, all these illusions
just take us too long
And I want it bad
Because you walk pretty, because
you talk pretty, cos you make me sick
And I'm not leavin' till you're leavin'
Oh I swear there's something
when she's pumpin', asking for a raise
Does she want me to carry her home...
Your plane leaves for Budapest in an hour.
You'll meet Dixon at the airport.
When you get into the Triad's testing
facility, you'll log onto their computer.
Sloane expects you
to disable the firewall
so SD-6 can hack in and directly download
the specs for the next-gen weapons.
Once you've accessed the computer, you'll
contact the CIA and give us the IP address.
We'll download the specs.
Here. Memorise this number.
This is the IP address
you'll give Dixon.
He'll think he's accessing the Triad's
computer, but he'll be on a CIA server.
We've set up some dummy files
for him to download.
Anything else?
Sydney, Washington has made a decision
regarding your mother.
What she did to you invalidated
her agreement with the CIA.
The government is pressing charges.
They're going to seek
the death penalty.
- Hey, Daddy.
- Hey, Craig. What're you doing in LA?
Madagascar customs picked up
a US national transporting explosives.
They brought him to LA
and I'm baby-sitting him to New York.
Listen, I heard about Weiss.
How's he doing?
It was rough,
but they say he's gonna be OK,
which is more than I can say
about the nursing staff.
Wait till he gets home.
He's gonna be insufferable.
- Listen, I have to...
- Yeah. Yeah. Go. Go.
I'll be back next month.
I wanna play some ball.
- Why? You think you're ready for this?
- That's cute, that's cute.
Craig. The guy with the explosives,
was it Semtex?
- Yeah.
- Vintage Russian stuff?
- Yeah, that's right. How'd you know that?
- And he's here in LA?
- For the next two hours.
- I have to talk to him.
He's with me.
Manolo Desouza.
I'm Agent Vaughn.
Has anyone offered you a drink?
I'm sure I could find you a soda.
This is not a good time
to be a terrorist, Manolo.
Now, a couple of years ago and you
would have had some civil rights.
Now we just throw you in a cell.
No attorney. No due process.
So who were you working for?
OK.
In that case we'll just let
the pictures tell the story.
The satellite photos from four days ago
showing you rigging a plantation building
in the jungle near Sambava.
Those photos are all we need
to put you away for the rest of your life.
So I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Do you want that soda?
I was working for you,
you son of a bitch.
CIA.
- Through what office?
- My contact was Jack Bristow.
You tell that bastard
I'm not taking the fall on this.
- Test. One, two, three.
- Good.
Once you disable the network firewall
I'll download the database
while you access the viewing room
and take photos of the weapons.
The guards change shift at noon.
That gives you ten minutes to get in place.
- How do I look?
- Lip gloss.
What I have here is
a ordinary tube of lip gloss.
Let's say that you're at the beach
and your lips are feeling a little...
"My lips are chafed." Or you're possibly
on a date, it's the end of the night,
you're doing some smooching,
you want your lips to be supple and you...
Pistachio.
Now, that's my favourite flavour.
But you flip it over, and it's a miniature
camera with compressed-air injector.
Take a look. Go ahead and smile
cos you're on TV. And...
Anyway, this... I...
There's three cameras inside the tube.
I wanted to make four, but then there
wouldn't be room for the actual lip gloss.
You know,
I'll make you a fresh one.
- So, you're making a family tree?
- It's a present for my grandparents.
They're both from Budapest,
but they lost everything in the war.
Well, I'm certain you will find
the documentation of their marriage.
And you should be able to find
their registration of birth.
Our records are very complete
dating back to 1895.
Older than that,
unfortunately, not so thorough.
Good work, Syd.
Birth records are here. Over there,
documentation of marriage and death.
The correlation is unintended.
Please.
Eight. Two. Four.
One problem.
All documents are in Hungarian.
How do you expect
to know what they're saying?
- That's good.
- My grandparents taught me.
All right, Syd, you're clear.
The combination is eight, two,
four, zero, two.
- Stand by, Dixon, I'm going radio silent.
- OK, Syd. Standing by.
Mountaineer in position.
Come in, Boot Camp.
Copy that, Mountaineer.
Stand by for IP address,
Boot Camp.
IP address is 199.181.134.104.
I've opened port 47.
Good work, Mountaineer. Go ahead
and give the dummy IP to Dixon.
- See you at home.
- Copy that.
Dixon, I've disabled the firewall.
The IP address is 259.10.3.179.
Good work, Syd.
Now go get some pictures
of the weapons and we're outta here.
The viewing room is around
the corner to your left.
Door marked "kutatoterem".
Copy that.
Clear to exit.
OK. Go.
Sydney, you've got company.
Two guards coming on your left.
16 next-generation weapons.
We had no idea that the 16
next-generation weapons
would turn out to be children.
They're training as sleeper agents?
That appears to be the case.
See, the best spies have certain traits.
Proficiency with numbers,
three-dimensional thinking,
creative problem-solving.
These abilities are all in evidence
as early as five years old.
This is footage that we downloaded
from the Triad computer.
Every first-grader in the European Union
takes a standardised test.
A few years ago the Triad acquired
the company doing the testing
and added a series of questions designed
to locate children with these traits.
This year, 28 children were indicated.
Their parents were sent letters
inviting them to participate
in a month-long achievement programme.
16 accepted.
Six-year-olds acquire knowledge
at an incredible rate.
So the basic skills of marksmanship,
linguistics, visual-verbal cue recognition,
it can all be taught
in a matter of weeks.
- Who is he?
- We're still working on that.
So what happens to these kids
at the end of the month?
Triad sends them home
with the intent that, when they're grown,
they will contact these kids
and send them out in the field.
There was a rumour that the KGB
began developing a similar programme
back in the '80s,
but we never confirmed it.
Before these kids are sent home,
their memories are reset?
Yeah. That's right. They remember nothing
except that it was extremely satisfying.
Someone forged my wife's name in the
registry at her favourite bed and breakfast.
Weeks after her death.
My concern is that
it's intended to be a message.
You have enemies, Arvin.
Clearly one of them is trying
to leverage your grief.
It's not my grief.
It's my guilt.
Cancer didn't kill Emily, Jack.
Emily's doctor told us
that her cancer was in remission.
That very day, the Alliance told me
that I was being considered for partner,
but that there was a problem.
Somehow Emily had learned that...
Well, she learned about
my association with SD-6.
She didn't know the truth.
In fact, she assumed the lie
that we're a branch of the CIA.
Despite that, the Alliance decided to make
my promotion contingent on Emily's death.
My choice was an easy one.
I wasn't about to kill my wife.
Emily was not a bargaining chip.
Then I talked to her doctor,
and I was persuaded that...
despite this temporary remission,
that Emily's lymphoma would return
and that it would slowly
and painfully kill her.
She had already
suffered so much, Jack.
The thought of her succumbing
to this merciless illness
or being killed by the Alliance...
So I dissolved sodium morphate
in a glass of red wine.
The wine put her to sleep.
The sodium morphate
then caused a heart attack.
She didn't suffer.
I will find out who's doing this.
Jack.
See who else was being
considered for partnership.
I was given a seat at the table.
That means someone else was not.
Well, I have this new friend
on my work detail - Tommy Marijuana.
We call him that because there's Tommy
Marijuana and Tommy Crystal Meth.
Tommy Marijuana thinks that we're always
the person that we were in sixth grade.
Sixth grade was
an awkward phase for me.
- Oh, come on. You, awkward?
- Yeah. I had big teeth and little eyes
and I was always a foot taller than
everyone else, so I sort of hunched over.
I wish I could have seen that.
I don't know, when I was in sixth grade,
I was just sort of anonymous.
You know, you had the smart kid
and the funny kid and the good athlete.
And I was just Will.
They're putting my mom on trial.
They're gonna ask
for the death penalty.
The only way I'm able to deal with it
is to tell myself
that woman was never really my mother.
The irony is, since she's been back,
my father and I are closer
than we've ever been.
It's Vaughn. I have to go.
Hey, Vaughn.
That guy with the Semtex, Desouza.
- Are we supposed to be looking into that?
- Excuse me?
I'm just wondering, is that our case,
or were you pursuing it independently?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Daily situation report says the guy was
here yesterday on a transfer order.
You're listed as visiting him.
Vaughn?
No, it's not our case.
- Hello, Sydney.
- Dad. Hi.
- Agent Vaughn contacted you?
- Yeah.
Have we identified the man
from Budapest with the children?
Yes. Valery Kholokov.
- It's Kholokov?
- You've heard of him?
Yeah. He used to run
KGB's psych ops division.
Mind-control experiments, psychoactive
drugs. I thought he was dead.
Well, so did we. But apparently after the
KGB dissolved he went over to the Triad.
A facial-recognition scanner at the airport
in Buenos Aires identified him yesterday.
- What's he doing in Buenos Aires?
- He has a house there.
The project in Budapest is completed.
- A team is raiding that facility as we speak.
- The children have all returned home.
We have surveillance teams
monitoring each of them.
If the Triad ever makes contact,
we'll intercede.
We need to grab Kholokov.
See how many other kids he's
done this to - who they are, where they are.
- There's a team prepping now.
- Good. I wanna go with them.
No. Sending you to Buenos Aires
would be an unnecessary risk.
Kholokov has a private security detail.
External and internal alarm systems...
Dad, when I signed up with SD-6,
I wanted to join.
When I found out the truth...
I mean, these kids...
I know what it's like to be used.
I'm going to Buenos Aires.
The team leaves in 12 hours.
OK. Anything else?
That's all.
I'm going to pack.
I saw Desouza.
He told me that you hired him
to rig those explosives.
Irina Derevko would eagerly destroy
all of our lives.
I'm not a big fan either.
It still doesn't justify what you did.
You do good work,
Agent Vaughn.
But your consistent shortcoming,
and you should know this,
is your naive sense of morality.
Evil must be eliminated
by whatever means necessary.
- I don't think Sydney would agree.
- Sydney...
will never know about what I've done.
You betrayed her trust.
I won't.
Now, she should hear it from you.
But if you don't tell her,
I promise you, I will.
- Yes, sir?
- Why is my security system disabled?
It was disengaged on site, sir,
ten minutes ago.
I'll put the system back on line, sir.
Sir, is everything OK?
I'm going in.
- The guard's been sedated.
- Copy that, Mountaineer.
I make four guards in the courtyard.
Kholokov just went inside.
Get into position.
I'm heading to the junction box.
You take the guards.
I got Kholokov.
On my signal.
And that's in three.
Two. One.
Go.
- You good?
- Yeah. It's him. It's Kholokov.
Good work. Nice job.
- You want me to hypnotise you?
- I want you to take me back
to whenever it was I first saw that puzzle.
But you say you don't remember
seeing that puzzle before.
- I must have.
- Agent Bristow, I've seen your profile.
Your spatial intelligence is stellar. It's no
surprise that you could solve the puzzle.
But I wasn't solving it. When I was
standing there, staring at that puzzle,
it was like I remembered
where every piece belonged.
There wasn't any thought involved.
You said the KGB developed
a similar project.
It's possible that my mother knew
the techniques and maybe she...
Agent Bristow.
If you are looking to uncover a trauma,
then I need to warn you.
Hypnotic regression can trigger severe
nightmares, flashbacks, acute depression.
Understand that to do what I do -
maintain my cover at SD-6 -
I compartmentalise a lot.
But the idea that I might have been
programmed to be a spy -
I can't tuck that away.
I need to know what happened to me.
Excuse me, sir. I analysed the wine.
Is this a good time?
There's no fingerprints on the glass.
The wine is a '99 Hadley Cabernet Franc.
An unremarkable vintage.
What is remarkable is what I extracted
from inside the wine.
I was so surprised I redid the test.
But I'm certain it's VTX.
A calcium-based antidote -
extremely scarce.
Antidote to what?
Mainly heart-attack-inducing toxins.
Kurtotic acid, sodium morphate.
VTX simulates death.
It slows the lungs, nearly stops the heart,
which is how it prevents the poisons
from causing cardiac arrest.
And then when the VTX is metabolised,
the body returns to normal.
So if someone who was poisoned
by sodium morphate were given VTX,
they would appear to die.
Yes, sir. Well, assuming
they had no other heart conditions,
in eight to twelve hours,
they would be just fine.
I'm going to count back from three.
When I get to one, I want you
to tell me where you are.
Three.
Two.
One.
Where are you, Sydney?
It's me.
In my room,
when I was little.
Tell me if you see anything that resembles
the puzzles we're looking for.
I'm taking...
I'm taking care of her...
I'm taking care of her for Christmas.
That'll be soon.
Christmas... Christmas...
Christmas is all set.
Yes, I see it.
Nothing can happen to you now, Sydney.
You're safe.
Sydney, I want you to listen to me.
Just breathe.
Breathe. Focus on the puzzle.
Focus on the puzzle.
Good, Sydney.
Very good.
Look around you.
Tell me who else is in the room.
Good work, Sydney.
Sydney, get in.
What is it?
I have this memory
from when I was six years old.
My mother had just died
in a car accident.
I felt so scared. You were never home,
so who was gonna take care of me?
Then I overheard you talking.
You were in your study, on the phone.
You were talking
about Christmas, about me.
You were taking care
of my Christmas presents.
Suddenly, I felt so safe.
You were taking care of me.
That memory is a lie.
- You weren't talking about that at all.
- Sydney...
I've seen the footage,
mom's briefings with her KGB handler.
She was sent here
for one specific purpose.
To steal information from you about
a project you were developing for the CIA.
An operation to train children
to be American spies.
Project Christmas.
Ever since Mom came back, you were
afraid she'd figure out what you did to me.
You weren't trying to protect me from her.
You were trying to protect your secret.
So the first opportunity you had,
you set her up.
- In Madagascar.
- Sydney.
- Understand something...
- No, Dad, you understand something.
You took away my choices in life.
You programmed me to be a spy.
I will never forgive you for this.
I would teach my feet to fly
Oh, I wish I had a river
I could skate away on
I made my baby say goodbye
It's coming on Christmas
They're cutting down trees
They're putting up reindeer
And singing songs of joy and peace
I wish I had a river
I could skate away on