Sheriff Tom Underlay.
I protect the community.
There's a little work camp
down in the glades
that an old friend of mine
runs-a mr. Szura.
I want to find out why
the air force is down here,
and if there's a cover-up,
who's involved.
According to my contact,
they were after
a missing weather plane.
How many crew members
from that weather plane
you have locked
in this place ?
All of them.
What are you doing with them?
Testing them. They really are
amazing creatures.
They aren't creatures.
I'm worried about Jesse.
They're hybrid bastards, mom.
- You wanna go?
- Come on, bring it.
Jesse, give me the gun.
No way. The gun's mine.
Invasion
1x19 - The son also rises
Transcript: RaceMan
Adaptation: Ez, Keno83,
RonanaSplit & Lucile76
www.forom.com
Dad.
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was you.
It's not loaded.
Where are the bullets?
In the tackle box.
- Hey!
- Hey, nothing!
- What are you so pissed about?
- This!
Well, I've had it
for a while now!
Why is it bugging you?
Because you shot it-
while you were drinking.
You were shooting
at pictures of your mom?!
What is wrong with you?
Why are you sneaking
in my room?
You got no right
to come in here and do that.
That gun is mine! My other
father gave that to me.
Your other father
is a sick bastard!
And the only reason
that i let you keep this gun
is because you promised you'd
keep it in the display box!
I better not ever hear about
you shooting any gun again.
- You understand me?
- How are you supposed to hear about it
when you're not around?
I haven't seen or heard
from you in two days, dad!
And if you're so concerned
about our family,
then why don't you check in
on us once in a while?!
I've been out of range.
Oh. Oh! And now
that you're in range,
your wife tells you that
I've gone all columbine!
And isn't that nice-
now I got another stepparent
I can count on!
She is worried about you, Jesse.
We all are!
You got bigger things
to worry about than me, dad!
In case you haven't heard,
the town has gone
"night of the living dead."
Half the people
aren't even human anymore!
And from what I understand,
my stepfather likes it that way!
So if you want to be
pissed off at somebody,
why don't you be
pissed at him?!
I am.
Where you going now?
I'm going out.
Russell, you just got back.
Russell!
Mariel...
what are you doing?
Cleaning.
- It's 2:00 in the morning.
- I couldn't sleep.
You know, this could be
a really useful space for us.
Besides your guns, we could keep
all kinds of supplies in here.
Never hurts to be prepared.
Prepared for what?
Rainy day?
Instinct is everything.
Instinct is the key
to survival.
Most people
distrust their instinct.
They discount
their inner voice
because they allow their brain
to rationalize that voice away.
Well, we're not
"most people" anymore.
I didn't ask any of you
to meet me on this beach,
but here you are.
Because you knew something
was amiss tonight.
You're feeling anxious.
You should be.
The threat from the outside
that I've repeatedly
warned you about
is upon us now,
and now is the time
for us to take advantage
of this incredible gift
that we have been given...
for us to rise up
and act as one!
Has the whole world
gone insane?
It's the middle of the night,
and I can hear
my hybrid stepmother downstairs
scrubbing the closet floor
while my hybrid father
hands her dishrags.
Is this urge to disinfect
part of your D.N.A. Now, too,
or is it just that my family
is still crazier than everyone else's?
All families
are crazy, Kira.
Some just hide it
better than others.
So you're not in your bathroom,
secretly fighting soap scum?
No.
though... I have been feeling
a little restless tonight.
I feel better now, though,
talking to you.
I miss you, Lewis.
How's, uh, school?
Weird.
All the kids
are different now.
Like me?
No, not like you.
They're not as nice.
And a lot of them used
to be my friends.
Oh. I'm sorry.
It's like you can really feel
these two totally separate groups forming.
And I'm worried that my stepbrother Jesse's
going to a dark place with it all.
Who is that?
I have no idea.
Russell.
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
Tom?
I don't think your wife's
gonna like what I have to say.
Russell,
what are you doing here?
Are the kids all right?
Yeah, they're fine.
We're just-we're having
a little problem in the park.
I was hoping
that Tom could help
before things
really get out of control.
Your buddy Szura
is a murderer.
He's killed at least
four people that I know of,
two of whom
you sent to his island.
I know all about
the place, Tom.
And tomorrow, the world's
gonna know about it, too.
Who has he killed, Russ?
Christina Conrad,
Derek Cooley...
probably father Scanlon
by now.
I sent them to the island because
he promised me he would protect them.
- Do you ever get tired of lying?
- I'm not lying!
What, do you think
you know it all?
Maybe Szura was trying to
protect himself. I don't know.
I wasn't there.
Is that the same reason
you gave Jesse a gun?
So he can "protect" himself?
This has nothing
to do with Jesse.
Those people
needed to be contained.
The priest tried to kill me- what are you doing?
Maybe you deserved it.
You know, I'm sick of your games!
This is no game!
You are destroying my family,
you son of a bitch!
I'm trying
to save your family,
you stupid bastard!
You may be stronger than we are,
but i know you can die.
Go ahead, kill me.
Come on, Russ, do it.
Do it, come on. Do it.
You wanna do it, do it.
Do it.
- I can't!
- Why not?!
Because it's not loaded!
I am done keeping
the big secret, Tom.
I mean,
people are dying.
You may not be
killing them yourself,
but you are party to it.
You really don't get it,
do you?
I'm not your problem!
Do you realize
the military knows
about those creatures
in the water since '96?
Since my plane crash.
I've seen the pictures.
- What pictures?
- From hangar 42.
Szura with the N.T.S.B...
Szura with the wreckage.
Szura with all the air force
brass-I've seen them all.
Your partner's
a very popular guy.
- Szura... with the military?
- Come on, Tom.
You can't keep denying it.
Where are you going?
- Find out what the hell he's doing.
- You're too late for that.
I already have a team going out
to that island to pick him up.
And when they do, you're gonna have
a lot of questions to answer.
This doesn't end
with Szura, Tom.
This ends with you!
Are you sure you don't wanna
bring anyone else along, sir?
No, no, the fewer people
who know about this, the better.
But this island's
pretty isolated.
- What if mr. Szura-
- Hey, outside. Come on.
What if mr. Szura doesn't
want to talk to us, sir?
I don't give a damn
what he wants.
Is he really capable
of murder, sir?
We're all capable, Lewis.
We all have the potential
to go to our darkest place,
but most of us manage
to leave a light on.
It's all in here-
the hybrids' master plan.
Everything-it's in here.
Thought it was
Szura's master plan.
Well, he wrote it,
but he had a lot of help.
"The appearance of new forms
and the disappearance
of old ones are bound together."
- You know who said that?
- A magician?
Charles darwin.
Who's he?
He's a dead english guy.
Listen to your music.
Did you know that
95% of all the species
that once lived on this planet
have died out?
That blows my mind.
Basically, the overriding
message of this whole plan
is that the hybrids
are the chosen people,
and our extinction
is inevitable.
And who knows what
the fourth element is? Rose.
Water. W-a-t-e-r.
Excellent.
Okay, so there they are.
Those are the four elements-
earth, air, fire and water.
So what do you guys
think they represent?
Balance.
The balance between
all things in nature.
For the world
to function effectively,
you must always have balance-
economic balance,
ecological balance,
the balance between
life and death.
Ms. Wade, some of us don't know
what you're talking about.
Who can tell me
what this word means?
- How's life, man?
- Beautiful.
- You still living in your car?
- Nah, I moved up.
My grandmother's house
got red-tagged,
so now I'm sLeeping
in her rubble.
Sweet.
At least I went a whole morning
without getting my ass kicked.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
That's good, man.
That's real good.
Nice face, man.
You're looking good.
What's so damn funny?!
Come on. Come on, man.
Well, that was real subtle.
Screw 'em, man. I feel like
I'm in occupied france.
The trains are rolling, man,
and nobody is doing anything
to stop them.
My sister was almost drowned
yesterday.
They pulled her into the pool
and held her under
until she passed out.
Was my girlfriend
a part of that?
Oh, yeah, she's
one of 'em, too, now.
Looks like I'll be looking
for a new prom date.
They're not all bad.
Everyone's just scared 'cause they don't know
what's going on right now.
And you do?
Not completely,
but I'm not afraid.
Maybe that's 'cause
your boyfriend's one of 'em.
He's not my boyfriend.
Really?
She hangs out with this guy
who's my stepdad's deputy.
He's 26.
This isn't
about Lewis, Jesse.
Why don't you mind
your own business, okay?
Then why don't you?
We can't just let this
keep happening.
'Cause pretty soon, there's not
gonna be any of us left.
What about talking
to your stepdad?
Are you kidding me?
The guy is one of 'em, too.
Well, you said he's been
this way for a long time.
Maybe he knows
how to stop it.
He doesn't want to stop it.
He took my mother to the water
and made her the way
that she is.
And your dad, man-he probably
took him to the water.
And maybe he took
your girlfriend. Who knows?
He may have done this
to everybody.
Frank.
- Hey.
- Hey, Russ.
Hey.
I thought we were gonna meet
down at the chief's office.
Mona, could you give us
a couple of minutes?
Thank you.
¿Que pasa? How are you?
I've had better days.
I've heard, um, Mona said you
were pretty stressed out lately.
What's up, frank?
Well, um, after I got
your call last night,
we went through the whole mess
with the coast gard.
And this morning, the chief
talked to the sheriff about-
He talked to underlay?
Why?
- Because he's the sheriff, Russell-
- He's also a murderer.
Mira, the chief doesn't
quite see it that way.
Matter of fact, he thinks
you've overstepped here.
He thinks i overstepped?
And this relief worker Dennison
that you want arrested?
His name is Szura.
Whatever. He's very close
to the chief.
What?
Yeah, and apparently,
underlay knows and respects the guy as well.
Oh, no, no...
Frank, come on, man.
Don't do this to me.
Not you, too.
Underlay said he's willing
to go to this island
and check things out for us.
Underlay is the reason
Szura is on the island.
He's the reason
all of this has happened.
All of what?
All of what, Russell?
Yeah, I'll go talk
to the chief myself.
- He won't see you.
- He doesn't understand the situation.
You don't understand!
The chief is not gonna
talk to you! ¿Me entiendes?
In fact, he doesn't wanna even
see you around here anymore.
What are you saying?
He's placing you
on administrative leave.
He just thinks that you should
take some time and go home
and be with your family.
Frank...
you listen to me, okay?
None of us will have any family
left if we don't do something.
¿Me entiendes?
I'm sorry.
Did you sell me out?
Did you tell Vargas you thought
I should be taken off the job?
Of course not.
Well, then what did you say?
That you've been working 24-7
since the hurricane,
and that you've been having
some issues at home.
What issues?
I work with you every day.
The kids, your ex-wife,
the sheriff, your wife.
I've seen every side
of the equation.
None of that has affected
my ability to do my job.
I didn't say
that it did, Russ.
I think you're the best person
I've ever worked with.
You've got knowledge
and character both.
And I respect the hell
out of you.
Then what'd you say to him?
That I love you
and I'm afraid for you, Russ.
I'm afraid for you
and your family.
Why?
Because I know
what's happening in town,
and you can't stop it.
It's the way things
are supposed to be, Russ.
You can't stop change
like this.
You can only live your life
the best way you can
and hope that whatever you
leave behind has some value.
Are you... one of them?
Does it matter?
Can I put my stuff
in your locker?
Sure. Why?
I got about ten hybrids
blocking mine.
Maybe we should talk
to your stepdad, Jess.
What for?
He'll do what you said.
He'll try and stop this.
- Dude, he's not gonna talk to us.
- Maybe we can make him talk.
Look, I know some guys.
They might want to help us out.
- What kind of guys?
- Guys who can make people talk,
even when they
don't want to.
You know where he is?
Yeah, he went on
some boat trip.
He's gonna be back
around 6:00.
Where's he keep his boat?
Black point Marina.
Look, Brett,
I don't like the guy at all.
And I don't trust him at all,
but, I mean, he is my stepdad.
And he's the sheriff.
Yeah, the sheriff
that killed your mother.
Look, my father finally
kicked my mother out last night.
I knew it was coming,
but...
come on, man,
she called me crying.
Crying like crazy...
wanting to know
if she could stay with me.
What am I supposed
to do with that, man?
What am I supposed to do
when she calls me,
crying on the phone
because my hybrid father
kicked her out on the street?
I just want
some answers, man.
Are you sure he didn't know
we were coming, sir?
Yes.
I just searched
those bypasses again.
Everyone's gone.
Place is completely deserted.
Do you have any idea
where they could have gone?
Yes, Lewis, I do.
I do.
"God said let the waters
bring forth abundantly
the moving creature
that hath life."
That's Szura.
And he's quoting
the old testament.
So he's using all of the big ideas
to rally the troops, right?
Yeah.
But to what end?
I mean, his book definitely
supports the notion
that evolution is inevitable.
And the book is called
"robin hood and the cambrian explosion."
And robin hood says the best way
to get the job done is guerilla-style.
Robin had sherwood forest
to do all his dirty work in.
What does Szura have?
The island.
The water.
When Russell and i
were in Szura's bunker,
we found a downlink station
where they were monitoring
the temperatures in the ocean.
We thought maybe they were
checking up on the lake creatures.
But what if they were actually tracking
the currents for themselves?
Yeah, but for what purpose?
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe to ride into
town on the crest of a giant...
wait...
look.
There's a storm developing
in the southern caribbean.
Okay. The lights came in
during the hurricane, right?
And hybrids
are basically amphibious,
so wouldn't it stand to reason
if you were a hybrid psychopath
planning an invasion,
you might do it under the cover of a storm?
Hey.
Front door was open.
Oh, thanks.
Tom is not here.
I know.
I got suspended
from my job.
Apparently, somebody at the top
thinks I've become a liability.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, well...
I... I'm thinking about
going out of town for a while,
and I want to take the kids.
What about school?
I'll get their books, their homework.
I'll work with them.
- Where are you gonna go?
- I don't know yet.
Okay, um...
well, just tell me...
when you're going,
when you'll be back.
I'd like you to consider
coming with us.
Mariel, whatever's happened
in this town,
I'm certain that
it's not accidental.
These changes have a purpose,
and I'm afraid that that purpose
is about to be realized.
Did you ever tell Tom
what's inside of you now?
That you're basically
carrying enough eggs
to spawn an entirely
new species on your own?
- Not yet.
- So what if you get pregnant?
- That is really not your problem.
- I disagree.
You saw Christina.
That girl had a litter
growing inside of her.
You think
she could have survived?
- It's not your problem!
- I think it's all of our problem!
And for our kids' sake, just
think about what I'm saying.
So does larkin
know you're here?
No, but she will.
What about my husband?
Is he invited to come on this
little trip you're planning?
I suspect he'll have
other plans.
I don't understand why you keep
doing this to me, Russell.
He's my husband!
Whether you like it or not,
he is my husband!
- I know, Mar-
- Get out of here.
- Mariel-
- Get out of my house!
Just think about
what I said.
So you told Mariel everything and
she wouldn't listen to you ?
No.
Your job...
is this permanent?
I don't know.
They're all in on it.
Szura, Underlay, the chief,
the air force...
You're Silkwood, man.
You're Karen Silkwood-
blowing the whistle the nobody wants to hear,
you know what I mean?
- Where's Jesse?
- He's at his friend's.
He called.
He said he wasn't gonna
be home for dinner.
- What's he doing?
- Daddy?
Which state do you go to
when you die?
What?
Our teacher told us
that when we die,
we leave our bodies
and go to another state.
Which one is it?
Your second grade teacher
taught you this?
Yeah.
- "The balance of life and death"?
- It's my homework.
- Who's this teacher?
- She's new.
Well, maybe it's time for a little
parent-teacher conference, eh, Russ?
Did Jesse tell you
where he was going?
No, but he promised
he wouldn't be late.
- Russell, where are you going?
- I'm gonna go find him.
Russell, come back here!
You're not doing this again!
You can't just keep leaving
without giving me an explanation
for what's going on.
You know what's going on.
Yeah! And it's affecting
all of us.
Me, dave, your daughter,
your son-
we're all feeling it.
So stop acting
like you're the only one
trying to hold things
together.
You're not.
I'm sorry.
It's just a lot,
you know?
I do.
Look, when Jesse called,
he was with his friend Brett.
I think I have
his parents' number
if you wanna try
to call them.
Okay.
They got him about ten minutes
after the boat came in.
He was tying it up.
Got him how?
They said they knew
what he was,
that they just
wanted to talk.
- And he was cool with that?
- I guess so.
He's waiting for us.
- What is this place?
- It's my grandmother's.
Nice, huh?
You could thank F.E.M.A.
Yo, man, what's up?
Where is he?
Swimming.
What?
Yeah, he was cool
till we got him here,
then he wouldn't
give us his gun.
So we took it from him.
Oh, man!
Oh, my god.
Now I know
he's not the sheriff.
But a deputy's
almost as good, right?
Oh, come on, Lee!
Man, what'd you do?
I told you we just wanted
to talk to the man,
and this ain't even him.
Oh, chill, man, he's fine.
Hey, deputy.
If you can hear me,
raise your hand.
Honey!
Kira!
- Is anybody here?
- Back here, dad.
Hey, Kira.
Have you seen your...
- stepmother?
- She's at work, I think.
What is all this?
Does she know something
we don't?
We gotta get him
to the hospital!
Hey, Lee,
this is messed up, man.
Where's his radio? His radio's not here!
What'd you do with it?
- Beats me.
- Damn it!
- We don't need a radio.
- Don't need a phone, either.
hey! Hey! Stop!
Hey, man, stop it!
You stop it!
Jeez, man, what the hell's
wrong with you?!
Oh, you want some? Huh?
Back up, monkey.
Back it up!
Where's the radio?!
Hey, man...
- hey! Hey! Hey!
- Where's the damn radio?!
Put it on channel one and call
my dad or stepdad, anybody!
You come here!
- Where?
- Move!
- What the hell are you doing?
- You're going swimming!
You wanna
push people around?!
You want to
take over the world?!
- I'm not one of them!
- I don't care!
Jesse!
Jesse !!
How much of this
was Jesse?
According to the other boys,
he tried to stop it.
How are they?
One of them
has a few broken ribs,
but he'll be all right.
Russell may have
saved them all... Tom.
Is he still here?
Yeah, he's in my office
with Jesse.
It's gonna get worse
before it gets better.
I know.
Water and batteries
won't help.
They help me.
Kira.
Everyone's gonna blame me
for this, aren't they?
I can't speak
for anyone else.
Do you?
What did you think was
gonna happen tonight, Jess?
I don't know.
I guess...
- I didn't care.
- Do you care now?
I'm sorry that
I haven't been around
as much as you
need me to be.
And I'm really sorry about
what's happened to your mom.
But she's still your mom.
And I'm still your dad.
And no matter what,
nothing's ever gonna change that, Jesse.
She is still your mom.
Okay?
I don't wanna
live here anymore, dad.
Okay.
Okay?
Yeah, I pretty such
got fired today, so...
I'm up for anything.
I was actually thinking that
we should all take a trip.
Where?
Someplace dry.
Hey, Russ.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Hey, Tom, I'm, uh...
sorry about Lewis.
I know you are, Jess.
Is he gonna be all right?
Uh, that may be up to us.
Russ?
My turn to take you
for a ride tonight.
- Where are we going?
- Gas station.
I want to show you something.
It's been like this
all day.
They're all hybrids-
the people,
not the cars.
I got home tonight
and discovered
that Mariel had packed the place
to the rafters with emergency supplies.
So I called a few stores
around town,
and all the major outlets have run out of
water, tarps and batteries,
so I drove to one of them.
All hybrids there, too.
Is there
another hurricane coming?
But nobody knows it.
People...
are just feeling it.
These people
are feeling it.
But it's the rest of the people
that I'm worried about.
Szura's gone, Russell.
I went out to that island
this morning,
and he and his group,
they're just gone.
Now I don't know
what he's planning.
But if we get hit
with a storm-
it's anything like eve was,
everyone is
gonna be distracted.
Why are you
telling me all this?
Because I'm gonna
need your help to stop him.
What happened to Lewis
is gonna happen again
till we find a way
to coexist.
And right now...
I'm just a little short
on people I can trust.
Yeah?
Tom?
It's him.
where are you?
In transit.
There's some issues
I need to discuss with you.
Yeah, well, I got some issues
I need to discuss with you, too.
Put it on speaker.
I had to leave the island.
That ranger
is a real pain in the ass.
Where have you
taken everyone?
I'd rather discuss this
in person.
Could we meet
for breakfast tomorrow?
Eli...
and, Tom...
I know you're with him.
All right.
What do you want to do?
- Thank you, miss.
- You're welcome.
- Is yours still not working?
- Afraid not.
But it's nice to know
if I get in trouble again,
you're always nearby.