The hurricane creates chaos.
Mariel, look out.
We thought it was gonna hit further north,
but it hit right over Homestead.
Szura was supposed to be training these people
to reenter society.
So basically we're dealing with
an armed hybrid militia.
Everyone's really freaked out.
I know some guys who can make people talk.
He's my stepdad.
He's the sheriff.
The sheriff that killed your mother.
Hey, deputy, if you can hear me,
raise your hands.
- Let me go!
- Mommy!
- Let her go!
- Jesse!
He's got a whole operation.
Genocide under the cover of a hurricane.
Tonight you are going to deliver
what is inside of them.
Oh, my god.
There's a major emergency at the wharf.
A lot of people are gonna die.
They're watching everything.
Invasion - Series Finale
1x22 - The last wave goodbye.
Transcript : RaceMan
Adaptation : Ez, Keno83,
RonanaSplit & Lucile76
www.forom.com
Just keep moving.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Keep moving. There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Why are they doing this to us?
I don't know.
Just hold tight to me, okay?
Look, it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Jesse?
- Get under those stairs.
- I have to find my mom!
No, not now.
Just meet us under those stairs!
Mom, it's gonna be all right.
- Brett!
- Hey!
What are you doing here?
Man, they just pulled us out of our house.
Man, we didn't even have time to pack a suitcase!
What about your dad and your brother?
They separated us when we got off the truck.
Is this messed up or what?!
Get off of me!
My god, they're pushing them
into the water.
I have to find a way out of here.
How many women are up there?
At least 30.
- Are they all hybrids?
- And all pregnant.
God. Here, give me the gun.
All right, stay here.
I'm gonna try and find Larkin
and the kids.
- Russell!
- Just stay in this area.
We'll be back for you, I promise.
Go.
You don't understand, colonel.
There is a major emergency at the wharf.
And if we don't get some soldier
down there A.S.A.P.,
a lot of people are gonna die!
I'm sorry, deputy,
but we just don't have the manpower right now.
Most of our people went up north.
Well, you must have someone!
Just tell her to look out the window!
Is this request coming directly from the sheriff?
Yes! From the sheriff and from me!
- I'm a veteran...
- Just look out the damn window right now!
Look!
It's me, honey.
Dad, what are they doing out there?
I hear people screaming.
I want you to lay down on the seat
and don't get up.
We're moving.
- Now?
- Now.
Now!
- Where are you going?
- To find a safe place to have our babies.
- What about the other women?
- They didn't want to leave.
- Can you get us to the hospital?
- I don't think that's possible.
I gotta get you away from this window.
We're gonna go downstairs.
Just come with me.
You're gonna be okay.
Keep breathing.
Just keep walking.
Mom! Mom, where are you?
Mom!
Hang on to me, Rosie!
Hang on.
Are you all right?
Crawl under here.
I want you to stay under here, okay?
And don't move.
Okay, mom.
Jess!
Jesse!
Larkin!
- Jess, I'm here!
- I'm coming!
You're almost here!
Come on! Come here!
- Stay under here.
- Okay. Okay.
Stay with Rose.
Don't move.
It's okay. It's okay.
Anyone tries to run away, shoot 'em.
Throw their bodies in the water.
What if they're already dead?
There may be some life left in 'em.
No! No!
No!
Please! No!
No! No!
Mom!
Get off of me!
No! No! No!
Bring her back!
Larkin!
Larkin, they took Rose away!
Rose!
Rose !
- Larkin!
- Put her down!
- Stay here!
Rose!
Larkin!
Stay down!
Just stay down, baby.
Larkin!
Rosie!
Tom, don't shoot!
It's me!
I found Mariel!
She's in the storage house just up the pier.
- Is she all right?
- For now.
Come on.
Move! Get out of the way!
Get out there!
Stop those men!
Move that truck!
It is air force security.
This area is being secured.
All personnel stand fast.
Stand fast. Cease fire.
Cease fire.
Put your weapons on the ground
and put your hands in the air.
I repeat, this is air force security.
This area is now under air force command.
Do not move!
This area is now under air force security command.
You are to stand down immediately. Stand down.
All civilians remain in the way.
Remain in the way.
You okay, baby?
Stay with Russell.
I'm going to find mariel.
2- story building just up the pier.
Larkin!
Jesse!
Kira!
Hey!
Hey.
You all right?
- Hey, where's Larkin and the kids?
- I don't know.
She said that they were here,
but you haven't seen them?
No. No, no, no.
Larkin!
Jesse!
- Russell!
- Hey!
- Russell! Russell!
Oh, my god.
- daddy!
- Hey! Hey!
You okay?
- Hey, pop.
- What's up, Jess?
You all right?
oh, my gosh, give me this one.
The baby? The baby's okay?
Everybody's okay?
We're all okay.
We're okay.
Okay, ladies, settle in.
- Where are you taking us?
- Just get in the car!
Mariel!
Go!
- Tom!
- Go!
Mariel!
Mariel...
Szura and the hurricane are gone,
but their collective damage is everywhere.
Lots of people are missing.
Many more are dead,
and Mariel has been kidnapped.
The military has secured the area,
rounded up all the hybrids,
interrogating everybody all night long.
Not surprisingly,
the guy they spent the most time talking to
was sheriff Tom Underlay.
I have to admit,
the lights in the water don't seem so scary
when you compare them to the looks
on some of these people's faces.
When half of the town thinks
that the other half tried to kill them,
how do you recover?
Anyway, all I'm saying is
if we don't do something
about this guy now, who will, huh?
He's the sheriff,
so who's gonna stop him?
He's the most connected guy
in town, Brett.
Come on, man.
You've lost people,
I've lost people.
How much more are we gonna take?
I need to find my wife.
You have to let me out of here.
Your wife is not
the only person missing, Tom!
Lots of people went
into the water last night,
and we need to know why!
I've told you Szura wants to create
a majority.
- He wants to make everyone like him!
- And like you.
Come on, you really think
that I'm involved with this?
Why would I have them bring you here?
Why would I be shooting at them
from some damn truck that you gave him?
Those trucks were sent to a relief group
- run by a man named Dennison.
- Dennison is Szura!
- And somebody on your team obviously knows it.
- Not me.
Well, then someone above you,
someone who wanted this to happen.
Come on, Tom. Nobody wants to see
innocent people killed.
Nobody wants to see war, either,
but when it comes to national security,
we're pretty good about justifying everything.
You yourself have six hybrids locked up
at the base
that you're testing like lab rats,
and you think it's all for the greater good?
One small step for man,
one giant leap for mankind?
Think again, colonel.
Because if Szura has his way,
there may not be any mankind left.
We'll find him.
Yeah, before or after he murders my wife?
You have to let me out of here.
Hey.
Okay, you guys are all clear to go.
Listen, Sirk's gonna take you back
to Tom's.
Stay there until you hear from us,
all right?
- What about Mariel?
- We're going after her.
Russ, be careful.
- Okay, so I'll see you guys soon?
- Please find mommy.
We will, honey.
We will.
- Where do we start?
- Battery park.
Why would Szura be there?
It's remote, it's secure,
and it's where I originally set him up.
Oh, I don't suppose you've shared this
with colonel Lopez.
No, I kept that part to myself.
Cover this area.
- This area, at the top.
- Yes, sir, right away.
Lie down.
I'll be right back.
Just lie down.
It's okay.
We have to get these women to a hospital,
or they're not gonna survive.
I don't care if they survive.
- Where are my children?
- They're fine.
- And my husband?
- He's fine, too.
He's probably out saving the world somewhere.
Now do your job.
All of these women are carrying
multiple fetuses.
- I'm not sure that I am capable of-
- Oh! God!
Oh, Mariel... help me.
Help. Help.
- She's bleeding.
- Well, then do something.
I...
I have to go to the water.
Yes, yes. Can you take us
to the water?
Please?
P lease.
The water's what we need.
Jesse, you can just get in the back seat here.
Kira, put Rose in the middle.
Here, take this radio.
I'm gonna go ahead
and make sure the roads are clear.
- Thanks, Lewis.
- You're welcome.
Bye, guys.
Bye.
What's Pettis doing here?
Shouldn't they be in Iraq
profiting from all their misery?
Probably here to help with the cleanup.
Yeah, but this quickly?
That's what they do.
The government contracts them
to help rebuild places all over the world.
Yeah, I know what they do.
But this storm wasn't even supposed
to hit here.
This hurricane was supposed to hit
a hundred miles up north.
That's where every other relief group is.
So what are they doing here?
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
Could I trouble you guys for a ride?
- I don't mean to impose.
- Uh, yeah. Yeah, sure, man.
- Where you going?
- Sheriff's house.
Come on.
Get in the car.
Go.
All right, look, man, I can't drive
with you pointing that gun at my head.
Go!
We have to get them to the water.
Why?
It's what they're telling me they need.
And it makes sense.
Their blood...
our blood is much closer to
that of a marine mammal's now.
In order for them to survive,
- I think they probably need to be in the water.
- I told you I am not concerned about-
Well, then for their offspring!
To survive, they may need to be in the water.
Every other species instinctively knows
where and how to give birth.
Why should they be any different?
Get down!
Mariel!
Oh, my god.
- Stay with her.
- What?
- I gotta find szura.
- No! Tom!
I gotta find him.
- Come on, we gotta get out of here.
- We have to take them with us.
What?
- I need to get them to the water.
- No, we don't have time for that.
- Szura's people could be here any minute.
- No, russell, I'm not leaving them.
What's at the water?
I think it's where
they need to give birth.
Mariel, we may not want them giving birth.
Well, if they don't go there, they'll die.
They may die anyway.
I am not leaving them.
We don't know what's inside of them.
It doesn't matter.
Tell me, Tom...
How many bullets did you take
and survive, huh?
You're done here.
I'm afraid that's not possible.
Thousands of people were taken
to the water last night...
to see the lights,
like you did with your wife.
These hybrids...
they felt compelled to change
those they loved the most.
I don't believe you.
Turn on your radio.
It's a brave new world, Tom.
Evolution swallows us all.
Why didn't anyone answer?
- 'Cause maybe nobody's home.
- His door was unlocked.
Call somebody.
Hello?
Where'd that deputy take everyone else?
Hey.
We saw them get into his car.
- Maybe they had trouble on the road.
- We didn't.
Shut the door and lock it.
- What's upstairs?
- We don't actually live here.
- Bedrooms, I think.
- The sheriff's bedroom?
- No, that's in the back.
Then that's where we're going.
- I'm gonna go out there.
- No, Lewis.
Kira, you heard them on the radio.
That man has a gun.
- Can't you just wait for my dad?
- No.
I want you to try yo stepfather again.
Don't anyone move.
Didn't anyone ever tell you it was rude
to eavesdrop?
Just give me your gun.
We just want to talk to your boss.
Jesse, is that you?
Tom, you gotta get back here.
There are guys in the house with guns,
and I'm afraid that they're gonna kill us.
Brett?
Jesse?
Jesse!
Damn it!
Mariel.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Would you just let them die?
I am not sure that what's inside them
is like you.
What if these hybrids are just
a bridge species,
and it's their offspring that we really have to worry about?
Just to save a few lives,
are you willing to risk millions more?
Whatever's inside them may be different,
but it doesn't mean that it's bad.
And it doesn't mean
that it's dangerous.
It's just... different.
And the man I used to be married to
would have understood that.
God help us.
Come here.
You okay?
All right.
Alma.
I can't find her pulse.
What happened to you, man?
We're on the same side.
- You know that.
- No, I don't.
I get why you're angry.
I really do.
My dad saved you.
- Didn't you see that?
- He didn't save my mom.
- It wasn't his fault.
- Look, hey!
Look, you said everything was his fault!
So stop trying to change the story now,
all right?
I said I was angry,
and I told you a lot of things
that I was wrong about!
Sit down.
Sit down!
Where's my family?
I don't know.
Where are they?
Ms. Groves and her brother
are in here with me, sir.
I think
everyone else is upstairs.
- You all right, Lewis?
- Yes, sir.
But the other man has my gun!
That's right, and he'll use it
if I tell him.
So how about you hand me yours?
- Now, or your kids are dead.
- Who are you?
I'm a revolutionary.
And I'm here to take back my town.
- Who's this?
- My mom.
- Where is she now?
- Dead.
Mine, too.
She could come back.
Mine did.
Yeah?
What is she like now, huh?
She still the same person?
No.
Right.
But she's still my mom.
There weren't any guns in that closet.
Where do you keep 'em?
That's the only gun I've got.
Hey!
What are you doing, man?
You were supposed to call me
when he got here.
- Yeah, I was going to.
- No, he wasn't.
He's blowing you off.
He just wants to rob the place.
Shut up.
- Where are the kids?
- Up here. They're fine.
Damn it, Brett,
why are you telling him that?
- Come on, man, we're leaving.
- What?
This was a mistake, all right?
We're going home.
Are you crazy? This son of a bitch
killed your family!
- He tried to kill us all!
- Yeah, but killing him won't fix it.
Look, I'm done!
And I'm leaving.
No, you're not.
Tom?
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah, we're fine.
Everybody's fine.
Oh, no.
Hey, Lark, you okay?
Larkin.
Oh, my god.
Larkin, look at me!
Priority, this is unit seven.
We have a female victim down.
She's been shot.
- Squeeze my hand, squeeze my hand.
- Priority, response, please. This is an emergency.
Priority, respond, please!
This is an emergency!
We're not gonna get anyone out here, sir.
- The channels are jammed.
- Get some towels. Come on.
Towels!
Come on, come with me!
Larkin, stay with me.
Look at me.
- The baby.
- I know.
- I know. I know, I know.
- The baby.
- I know. Just look at me.
Honey, take Rose upstairs,
okay?
Go on, sweetie.
I know.
Just stay with me, all right?
I think the bullet hit her lung.
Help me turn her over.
Help me turn her over!
Careful, careful.
Oh, my god.
Bullet's out, but she's bleeding badly.
Give me the towel!
- Coming!
- Go! Go! Bring 'em!
She's gonna need a chest tube, sir.
- We've gotta get her to the hospital!
- There isn't time!
- Russell?
- He's coming, he's coming, all right?
- Just stay with me.
- Stay with me right now!
Her lung's collapsing.
Get her up.
Get her up. Let's go.
What? What? No, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Stay with them, Lewis.
Lock that guy up and stay with them.
- I wanna come with you.
- Stay here!
Don't let anybody leave this house
until I get back.
- That's my sister!
- And I'm trying to keep her alive!
Tom, where are you going?!
Tom's not here.
But Szura's dead.
Come on. Let's go.
I really appreciate what you did today,
Russell.
I know we've had our... issues.
But today I was reminded of
how much good there is...
or was... between us.
I'm sorry if I made you do something
you don't feel comfortable with.
You didn't make me do anything.
- What?
- You're a good man.
And I told your wife that, too.
Thanks...
I think.
How are the kids?
They're good.
They've got a good mother.
Is that Tom's car?
Tom?
Tom, what is it?
What happened?
Tom, what happened?
What happened?!