Yes!
My name is Professor Nick Cutter.
Eight years ago,
my wife Helen disappeared.
I discovered
she had stepped into the past
through ruptures
in time called anomalies.
Now creatures from the past
threaten the future of the human race.
There's only a small group of people
who know the truth: my research team.
Stephen Hart,
Connor Temple...
Abby Maitland,
government officials James Lester
and Claudia Brown.
I returned from the past to find
something has gone terribly wrong
and Claudia Brown has vanished,
as though she was never even born.
I've come back to a different world.
And Helen and I are
the only two people who know it.
Transcript: evarin - Synchro: MNk
Oh, my God!
It's closing!
No, I have to go!
I have to make things right!
Don't be stupid!
You'll get marooned there.
Something's happened.
Something happened while I was in there,
something's changed.
The world's evolved differently.
On my way.
I think we're done here, aren't we?
No, no Claudia Brown...
Claudia Brown.
She was in charge of the day-to-day
running of the operation.
No, that's Leek. Oliver Leek.
You can't have forgotten him.
You saw him at the ARC today.
- The what?
- The ARC. The Anomaly Research Centre.
No, you mean the Home Office?
No, we moved from that place ages ago.
Is he having a nervous breakdown?
If someone can call an ambulance...
He's fine.
You're getting a little old
for imaginary friends, Professor.
A quiet night?
What the...
Spoke to soon, probably kids.
All right, fun's over.
I need back up. We've got an intruder.
Don't make me come in there and get you.
Evening, Professor.
- What have we got?
- A new creature report.
Erm, intercepted emergency call
at the Castle Cross shopping mall.
A security guard screaming
something about a monster.
A shopping mall. God help us.
I've instructed the police
to stay out until we've investigated.
Ah Professor,
glad to see you back well and safe.
Though I gather your...
wife won't be joining us?
Who the hell are you?
Ah, yes, Professor Cutter's
suffering from some kind
of stress-related amnesia.
He seems to have forgotten...
Pretty much everything, really.
No, I haven't forgotten a thing.
I wish I could.
And now he's being enigmatic as well.
What a vivid repertoire.
Are you really telling me you
don't know who this man is?
Nah, course it's Leek.
Oliver Leek. I know exactly who he is.
Is this industrial action
or did no-one hear that
we have a creature in a shopping mall?
Guys, I'm on it.
Cutter's always been eccentric
but I now think he's just deranged.
I suppose all very brilliant men
are a little bit... unusual, sir.
I'm brilliant, Leek,
and I'm not the least bit unusual.
You didn't have a clue
who Leek was, did you?
OK, you're officially freaking me out.
Let me get this straight.
You're saying something's
changed because of what
happened in the Permian anomaly?
Like evolution has just what,
altered course?
I'm glad somebody was listening.
You believe me?
All right. I'll buy it.
I could kiss you, Connor.
That's very sweet, but maybe not
while there's people watching.
One thing, though.
How do I know how I'm different
when I don't know
what I was like before?
Apparently some people never change.
Is that a bad or a good thing?
- What are we using?
- Ketamine for now.
But it would help if I knew what
size creature we were dealing with.
- I've had to guess the dosage.
- Where's my gun?
- Abby's got one.
- She knows how to use it.
- How many animal have you tranquilized?
- I've played darts.
Well, sometimes I think you
don't trust me with firearms.
I don't know what gives you that idea.
You ready?
So what now?
We go in.
- Who are you?
- Duty manager.
What happened?
We got a call from
one of our operatives.
We haven't been able to raise him since.
What did he say?
He didn't really say anything.
He just sort of...
screamed.
Did you see anything in there?
I want you to close
these shutters behind us and
I don't want you to open them again,
until I tell you it's safe.
Because whatever happens,
it mustn't get out.
What mustn't get out?
Hang on, who the hell are you lot?
- Are we OK?
- About what?
We can't ignore what happened.
Oh, you mean the fact
that you slept with my wife?
Stephen, if you're looking for closure,
I'm a little bit busy.
I don't blame you for being angry.
Helen never cared about either of us.
She's mad.
Mad?
She took off through
an anomaly for eight years.
Does that strike you as well-balanced?
Just forget it.
I'm finished with the past. It's just...
I don't know if it's finished with me.
Don't you hate it when people
bring their personal lives to work?
Can you get any closer?
Come on, show us what you are.
What's that?
Not sure.
A Cretaceous era therapod dinosaur.
- The genuine article.
- A raptor.
I always hoped we'd get one someday.
It's beautiful.
I said it was beautiful.
I didn't say it was friendly.
Oi, where are you going?
I'm gonna get a slushy.
It gets me every time.
Do you think the raptors
have gone back through?
When was life ever that simple?
- I hope you're going to pay for that.
- Yeah...
if you can lend me a fiver.
Thank you, Abby.
- Abby...
- What?
Close the shutter!
Really quickly!
Connor, run!
- I hate that.
- What?
Brain freeze from the...
slushy.
Right go check the atrium,
make sure we can contain it.
We need more firepower.
This is a raptor.
I've just lost a friend because
we disrupted nature once too often.
I don't intend to let it happen again.
You're sure you're OK?
Under the circumstances
I'd say I was doing well.
Abby, give me your gun. Stay here.
You good?
Don't shoot.
Abby, Connor...
get this guy out of here.
Come on, you'll be fine.
Lester wants to know what's going on.
We've got a confirmed anomaly
and one very angry raptor.
I'll put armed back-up on standby
and say there's a security scare.
They'll stay closed as long as it takes.
Leek, has the concept of personal
space ever been explained to you?
Sir, it's from the Ministry
and is marked top priority.
Private sector PR Manager?
What am I supposed to do with them?
The minister thinks that
we need more help with the media.
He feels that the situation
is kind of getting out of hand.
His words, not mine.
The last thing I need is some greasy
PR supremo sucking up to the press.
This isn't a reality TV show.
Let me know the minute
it's safe to re-open.
Keep in touch. You know how
I worry when I don't hear from you.
A raptor in a shopping centre.
How can I explain that to the owners?
I think a PR person might
not be such a bad idea after all.
I haven't got my jacket.
- You can get it later.
- I need my wallet and my keys.
Smashed clean off its hinges.
It's big.
Cutter!
In your own time!
Just shoot the damn thing!
Shoot it!
You all right?
The gun jammed.
Wait. Did you leave that door open?
I don't remember.
Give me the gun.
- What?
- Come on.
- Please.
- No.
Just for a minute.
What, do you want to go first?
Thank you.
Clear! Clear, guys.
- You're ridiculous.
- What?
I said you're ridiculous.
Ridiculous? I'm just doing my job.
- Is that it?
- Shoot it!
All right, fine.
Got it, got it. It's fine.
Come on!
It's not exactly staying
still for me, is it?
- Shoot it, Connor!
- It's fine, I got it.
You idiot.
Abby, I'm sorry... Sorry.
OK, I'm just gonna have to just do this.
I'll be back with you in a minute,
all right?
Now, hold on.
So you think that
I would just have stood
by and watched you get torn to pieces?
That depends on how much you resent me
for what happened with Helen.
Yeah, you're right, I do. I resent you.
But if I wanted you dead...
I'd have shot you myself.
- Run!
- It's jammed.
Go!
Stephen, wait here!
You all right?
Look at it.
Just the perfect killing machine.
Do you know, in a fair fight,
mammals wouldn't stand a chance.
Well, speaking as a mammal,
I'm all in favour of cheating.
About the gun,
I was wrong.
Never mind.
Listen, you could have gone with Helen,
you could have left, and you didn't.
And right now...
that's all that really matters. So...
so just...
forget about the rest.
- Do you think she'll be back?
- Is she finished messing with us?
I seriously doubt it.
Helen never handled
rejection particularly well.
Professor! Stephen!
- What happened?
- I shot her.
Collateral damage, though,
cos I got the raptor too.
You brought down a full
size raptor on your own?
He's nearly full size.
Is she gonna be all right?
She will have a nasty headache
but she should be fine.
She'd better come around soon cos
I need all of you to
get the raptors back alive.
- Alive?
- Yeah.
These things are
trying to make sushi out
of us and we have to play nice.
That doesn't seem fair.
The cleaner was attacked,
he was badly injured.
I don't get it - he was right there.
He was in a really bad way.
Well, he must have
recovered and got himself out.
One raptor is a problem. Two means
we've got an infestation and God knows
how many running around down there.
I want you to take this to the bowling
alley and meet us in the store.
On my own?
It's unconscious.
You've got nothing to worry about.
What if it's just playing dead?
- Playing dead?
- Yeah.
You know, as Cretaceous era predators
go, this creature's pretty smart.
So...
yeah, you probably...
Watch out for that.
Really?
Interference.
Seems odd.
She's gonna kill me when she wakes up.
The first Security Guard was
attacked here. The second one here.
Both attacks happened within seconds,
Which means there's at least two.
- And we've only found one.
- And a baby.
What are you doing here? You're
supposed to be looking after Abby.
I thought you were doing that.
Look!
Oh, God! Abby!
Stay here, tell us where it's going.
Right, stay here,
tell 'em where it's gone.
Where's it gone?
Come on, come on, where are you?
I can see it, Cutter.
It's on the level beneath you.
I repeat, on the level below.
I can't see it, it's disappeared again.
Where's it gone?
Oh for crying out loud,
how hard can it be to see
a raptor in a shopping centre?
Oh, my God!
Guys it's heading
towards the bowling alley.
It's going towards Abby. Be quick -
it's moving pretty fast.
Come on, come on, you can do this.
Connor she's fine.
Oops, she's coming around again.
- I'll just give it a quick...
- No, hang on, just wait a minute.
There are three raptors,
one of them's a baby.
So the chances
are they're a family unit.
So maybe we don't have
to go looking for daddy.
Maybe this little fellow
will bring him to us.
That's right, you shout for your daddy.
Now, let's just hope
they're a close family.
Where do you want me?
I want you in there with Abby.
Give me that. Go.
What's going on?
Tell you later.
What happened?
That's two doses of tranquiliser.
We have to up the amount.
They're too dangerous.
We can't keep taking stupid risks.
Stephen, everything we do has an impact.
We've killed them before.
Nothing happened.
How do you know for sure?
Maybe the strain of going through
the anomalies has got to you.
Maybe you only think
these changes took place.
What, do you think I dreamed
Claudia Brown?
The whole pattern of evolution changes
but just one person disappears?
One person who happens
to be a friend of yours.
No, it's not that simple.
The Arc didn't even exist before I left.
There's a whole team of people
in there I've never even met.
There might be countless other things,
big and small! I don't know!
I'll only use it if I have to.
- Have you seen an animal pass this way?
- A dog? A polar bear? What?
No, trust me,
you'd know if you'd seen it.
We've got to get it back to the mall.
What the hell was that?
A radio controlled
Cretaceous era raptor.
Probably be in the shops by Christmas.
You've got to admit,
that's pretty awesome.
Pretty cool,
but you could tell it was a model.
Yeah, course.
Oi, what about my bike?
Connor! Where the hell are you?
We're on our way up to the second floor.
Professor! Out of the way!
Bet you boys are glad
you gave me a gun now?
- How are you feeling?
- Terrible.
Do you want me to get you something?
I could get you a glass of water.
Stop fussing, Connor, I'm fine.
Abby, I want you to know something.
If I wanted to shoot anyone
you'd be the last person I'd shoot.
Apart from my mother, obviously,
but you'd be way down
the bottom of the list with her.
I don't think I'd shoot either of you.
Can we stop this?
Can you move the gun...
out of the Abby area.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
I've got your back.
What can you feel?
It's strange.
It's bone structure feels more like
a bird's wing than anything reptilian.
So, guys, let me get this straight.
All we have to do is drag two
of the angriest creatures in the known
universe through a hole in time,
back into an ancient world where
we don't know what's waiting for us.
- Put like that, it sounds so easy.
- I'm going to do this on my own.
- We'll help.
- Who's "we"?
I didn't say I wouldn't.
I just prefer to do my own volunteering.
I'm doing this on my own.
I don't want any arguments.
Connor...
How long have I got?
I don't know.
You know, it's so hard to say.
90% of the anomalies
are gone within hours.
This one's been here most
of the night already.
Come with me.
OK, what I want you to do is...
I want you to tune every
one of these radios...
to 87.6 on FM.
Now, doesn't that sound strange to you?
Interference.
- Why?
- Come on.
You think it's something
to do with the anomaly?
It could just be a technical
problem at the radio station.
Well, then, I want you to get
on to that and find out.
But if it is the anomaly
that's causing this,
that means there could be
interference anytime one opens.
Which would explain why Helen
was always one step ahead of us.
She must have some
receiver to spot them.
We could build a detector.
Something that traces
the anomalies within seconds.
If the interference stops
when the anomaly disappears,
then maybe we're onto something.
Now, if I don't make
it back this time, Connor...
it's down to you.
Cutter, I've been meaning to ask you...
This Claudia Brown. What was she like?
What does it matter?
I mean, to you she never even existed.
Tell me anyway.
Well, she was OK.
She...
Good at her job.
Loyal.
Team player.
But not as tough as she pretended to be,
but she was strong when it mattered.
She meant a lot to you?
Yeah.
Sorry.
What for?
That I didn't know her and...
cos you lost her.
I want to believe you.
I really do, but it's hard.
I know.
These two won't be
asleep for much longer.
OK...
this is as far as you go.
I thought you might try something
like this. So I followed you through,
just in case you had some crazy
idea about not coming back.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
OK. I know what you're talking about.
But so what? Maybe it's for the best.
What? Dying out here in
this Godforsaken place?
I figure if I travel through enough
anomalies, then maybe I can fix it,
maybe I can change things
back the way they were.
What if there's no way back?
What if this world
is the only one there is?
I mean look, it's suicide.
I don't want to die, Stephen.
I just want to try
and make things right.
OK, well, let's suppose
that you do change things.
How do you know that this time round
we're not all just
going to get wiped out?
I don't.
You could change a million things
and still not get Claudia back.
All you know is what's
happening right here, right now.
You know, for once in your life,
forget about the past.
Cos you've got a job to do.
Yeah, all right.
Just don't overdo it.
You haven't been right for a while.
Is it just me or
is that anomaly closing?
- You all right?
- Where's Stephen?
The anomaly's closing!
Pull!
Come on!
Pull, pull!
Well, you were right.
It was the anomaly
causing the interference.
Yeah.
We don't have to sit around
waiting for the creatures any more.
We'll know the anomalies
are open before they do.
Now all we have to do is find out
what's causing
the anomalies in the first place.
That might take a wee bit longer.
Yeah.
The place is clean
and the anomaly's gone.
You can give the all clear.
Excellent. We'll handle it from here.
Oh, good work, by the way.
- That could have been very nasty.
- Indeed.
You know you deserve a rest
and a chance to recover.
Take an hour.
No, let's not be mean, take two.
I'll see you back here at nine.
Forget it. I'm going home to bed.
Well, there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
A new member of the team.
- Who?
- Some sort of PR wizard.
Basically,
he'll be our cover-up specialist.
Protecting the public from what
they don't need to know and so on.
An unpleasant job but it has to be done.
Fine. Whatever.
What's this?
Revised details on the new recruit, sir.
Seems that the new man
is not actually a man.
Well, her qualifications
seem impressive enough anyway.
Morning.
- You're late.
- So fire me.
We can all dream.
Now you're finally here,
perhaps we can get going.
Hello.
I'd like you all to meet
your new colleague.
This is Jennifer Lewis.
Claudia Brown.
Jenny.
Nice to meet you.