Lucien, you fumbled the ball, man.
Go get.
Yeah, yeah. Right.
Aw, man!
Help!
Someone help!
What's that idiot doing?
Help! Help! Someone!
Transcript: evarin - Sync: MNk & Golgi
- OK, where is it?
- Identifying location now.
- In the river?
- Trying to confirm coordinates.
- What's happened?
- The anomaly must have closed.
- Well, did you get the location?
- We didn't have enough time.
Give me the coordinates!
- Do you want something, Caroline?
- Nothing.
I notice you do a lot of scissor kicks.
They won't to be enough
to disable your opponent.
Really you should be looking
to catch them, excuse me,
really you should be looking
to catch them in the throat area.
Like...
that.
Your way he gets a few bruises,
but mine, he's totally on the floor.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Good.
Dinner is served.
That's...
Amazing!
- Is that all for me?
- Yeah, you and...
Where to start?
It's Cutter. He's been calling.
- No. I've had no call.
- It must have.
I think I'd know if
Cutter was calling me.
We've got to go.
I could have sworn this was switched on.
What's so important
you have to leave everything?
Turn the lights out when you leave.
I'd like to...
Sorry, Caroline.
They just left.
- You were supposed to delay them.
- I put them off as long as I could.
The boy's name is Lucien Hope.
His friends said he seemed
to be struggling with something.
- Did they see anything?
- No.
- Maybe he just lost his footing.
- No, the lid's been lifted clean off.
Water pressure?
Could be.
Rainfall's been below
average for the month,
and floods don't happen for no reason,
which means the anomaly's under water.
- Where does this drain go?
- Back to the canal.
Seal it off and tell Abby and
Connor to meet us at the other end.
- Do you think he's still alive?
- I don't know.
But I ain't giving up on him
until I know for sure.
What the hell is that?
Lucien?
Stephen, it's not human.
Lucien!
Stephen!
It can only get out into the canal.
I'll have to say something to Caroline,
you know.
It's weird, us rushing off all the time.
Here's what you can tell her.
"Stop coming to my flat
every five minutes."
Our flat.
All right, your flat.
- Why is she at mine so much, anyway?
- Don't be naive, Abby.
You're looking at the reason,
aren't you?
- Not much going on there, is there?
- We're taking it slow.
She is.
You know what, you don't know
what you're talking about.
Why don't you stay out of it?
I don't care what you think. All right?
Is there any way out of this canal?
The locks are closed.
It's completely sealed.
- Then it's still in here.
- What is?
I'm not sure,
but we have to find out fast.
It'll be dark in a few hours.
Go in the boat with Abby and Connor.
You see anything, call us.
Let's go.
We've searched for hours.
We'll never see anything in this light.
What's that over there?
- There?
- Where?
Can you get us a bit closer here?
Looks like skin.
Yeah, from a mammal.
Looks like whatever it
is just shrugged it off.
- Back up. I saw something.
- Where?
That way, port, about 20 metres.
- I said port!
- This is port!
Starboard, then!
Just go, before it disappears!
How can he steer if
you don't know which is which?
- I've lost it now!
- Oh, great.
- Give me a go.
- What can you see that I can't?
Maybe you've...
For heaven's sake, you two argue
like a couple of kids over a toy!
Look, out of the way. I'll do it.
What just happened?
I don't know.
We must have hit something.
Come on, we'll get you out.
That's it, Jenny - swim.
What the hell is that?
You have to get out of the water.
Quickly!
Come on, Jenny! You'll be OK! Swim!
I can't swim!
Come on! Swim, Jenny!
Move your feet! Swim!
Hurry up, darling!
Come on! You're going to be fine.
Help me!
Swim quicker. Swim quicker!
Come on!
You can do it! Keep swimming!
- Come on, you're nearly there!
- Swim!
Jenny, here. Quickly.
- Stop, Stephen!
- Better late than never.
Get the body back to the yard, ASAP.
Roger that.
What was that thing?
How are you doing?
Three months ago,
my idea of a life-and-death issue
was getting front-row seats
at London Fashion Week.
- How d'you think I'm doing?
- You don't have to do this.
You know, you can quit.
I think I'll take my chances.
Look, Claudia...
So sorry.
- Jenny.
- You know what?
You saved my life.
So just for tonight,
you can call me anything you like.
For the record, I really hate that name.
Does your fiance know what you're doing?
He knows I'm working for the government,
that's all.
Luckily he's not very...
curious.
Not about my work, anyway.
So what about you?
Do you have... someone?
No.
I'm not particularly good at that.
My wife left eight-and-a-half years ago
to travel through the anomaly,
and the next woman that I liked, she...
She left.
I don't seem to be a particularly
romantic proposition at the moment.
And on that note, if you'll excuse me,
I have a date with a dead shark.
Do you think this is what took Lucien?
What a terrible way to die.
Poor kid.
But we have to know for sure.
Wait a minute.
God.
- Muscle spasm.
- It's some kind of proboscis.
It's a tongue covered in teeth.
Probably used to grab his victims
and then pull them into his mouth.
Unless I've missed my guess, this is
the future evolution of the shark.
Let's get this done.
We're going to have to cut it open.
Wow, that's strong.
God.
There's nothing else
left in its stomach.
It's not him.
He can't have been digested by now.
Exactly.
A shark takes days to digest prey.
Lucien went missing hours ago.
Not guilty?
So it was another one?
Maybe.
- Give me some good news.
- We still haven't found the boy.
No, that's bad news.
Good news makes people happy.
Keep trying.
We found the shark.
Now you're getting the hang of it.
So then!
- Problem solved?
- No, not quite.
There's another predator.
Abby saw something.
- Another shark.
- Or something else.
All the evidence points to
a marine mammal that sheds its skin,
like a seal or a walrus.
And the boy was taken above ground,
so even if the shark swam up
the flooded drain, how did it grab him?
- Using that proboscis.
- That wouldn't explain the singing.
A shark can't make that sound.
It doesn't have vocal chords.
So to sum up,
we're looking for a deadly,
skin-shedding aquatic predator with
a line in Charlotte Church impressions.
Well, the marketing
possibilities are endless.
- What do we do?
- Drag the canal.
- Whatever it is has to be in there.
- If it's a mammal,
it can leave the water,
so we should widen the search.
Start the search of the
canal again in the morning.
If nothing turns up, then,
and only then,
we'll consider the options.
Good decision, sir.
Exactly what I was going to suggest.
Really?
How terribly reassuring.
Come here.
What's she doing?
She stayed up for me!
She didn't stay up, did she?
She's asleep.
It's the thought that counts.
What are you doing?
You should have gone home to bed.
Rex?
Could you just...
- What were you doing in there?
- Oh my God!
- How did this happen?
I have no idea.
- Maybe...
- I'll get some towels. I'll get towels.
Maybe he crawled in when
I was putting things away.
- I'll call a vet.
- No!
- Get me some tinfoil.
- Tinfoil.
- Right.
- I should go.
- Yeah, good idea.
- Abby!
I'm sorry.
I hope he makes it.
Look, you don't need to go.
He's going to be OK?
Don't touch him!
You don't know what you're doing.
Keep your girlfriend away
from him in future, yeah?
Sorry.
Look,
something about this doesn't add up.
We should widen the
search to the canalside.
This is another of your hunches?
We can't just drop everything, you know.
- There's a plan in place. A good one.
- When have I ever been wrong?
Except about women, generally.
Look at the odds,
it's got to be in the canal.
Just give me a few
minutes to look over there.
- What am I meant to tell Lester?
- Cover for me.
No, cos you're wasting time.
Ten minutes.
So what's going on?
I know you.
You know that guy that hit you?
- What if he comes back?
- He won't.
I've seen him before,
in the mall. He was the cleaner.
I've seen that guy too.
I saw him at the ARC.
- He was dressed like a soldier.
- Are you sure?
Something's going on.
We're being watched.
Maybe.
We should get Stephen, yeah?
Are you recording this?
- What does it sound like to you?
- Dunno.
A bit like something I once heard
in Glastonbury, in a chill-out tent.
- Glastonbury?
- Yeah.
- Like you've been there.
- How would you know?
What's going on with the pair of you?
Connor's dating Cruella de Vil.
For crying out loud.
It wasn't an accident.
How many times do I have to...
Right, grab the recordings
and let's get back in the boat.
OK, here'll do.
Play back the recording.
See if we can't invite
them to come and see us.
Guys?
Nothing...
Maybe no one's home.
I think this is silly.
We should be helping
Stephen search the canal.
It's not in the canal.
Something's taken her!
Put that down! You could kill Abby!
I can't see her!
Get help! Now!
- Now!
- OK, OK!
No. What are we doing?
We have to keep looking!
We can't, we can't just stop!
This is Abby!
We can't just give up!
I'm not stopping looking!
Connor, we're doing all we can.
We told you and you didn't come!
Why? Why didn't you help?
- How did this happen?
- I was following up a lead.
And who did you tell about it?
Did you know about this?
No.
- And now the girl's dead.
- Not dead! She's not dead!
We could just go out there,
we could find her!
We need to get back in
the boat and do something!
Why is nobody doing anything?
- Take him home.
- Please! Don't do this!
I suppose teamwork,
for once in your life,
- was completely beyond you?
- I take responsibility for this.
- How very gracious of you.
- It's still out there.
We are very close,
and we still have to finish the job.
It's finished, for you.
Go home.
You're in charge.
Don't look at him. Look at me!
Come on! What do you want?
Something better than sonar.
We have to go over
every inch of canal again.
- A remote control submarine can do it.
- Get it for him.
You're looking in the wrong place.
- Do you agree?
- No.
Whatever took Abby is in the canal.
Straight down and we go straight for it.
- How deep is it here?
- About ten metres, sir.
Help!
He-e-e-elp!
- Help!
- Lucien.
- I thought you were dead!
- What is this place?
I don't know.
They took us down here, those things.
Don't waste your time.
- I already tried that.
- We have to try.
Come on, help me.
We're going to die, aren't we?
My friends are looking for us.
- They're going to be here soon.
- They don't even know we're alive.
They'll find us. I promise.
You're not supposed to be here.
- Where else am I going to go?
- I could have you thrown out.
Yup. You could.
Thought you might be interested in this.
A local builder lodged a complaint.
He can't get in to demolish
an old warehouse,
because the basement
flooded in the tidal surge.
Maybe you're right,
and we're looking in the wrong place.
At the very least,
it's definitely worth checking out.
As petty-minded bureaucrats go,
you're the best.
I know how you feel.
But I need your help.
I think I know where to look.
Listen to me.
It was my fault.
I should have asked for backup,
and I didn't.
I reckon that's cost
the life of a very brave,
very beautiful girl.
And you're...
you're right to blame me.
But surely,
if there's even half a chance
we can stop this happening to somebody
else, then we owe it to Abby to do it.
And this time,
I'm asking for backup, so...
will you come and help? Please?
If you change your mind,
Jenny Lewis knows where to find me.
Help!
What do you think they are,
those things?
I don't know.
If they were going to kill us,
they would have.
There's a reason we're still alive.
Don't tell my mates, will you?
That I was scared.
You're not scared.
Seriously now.
Who'd be frightened
of an overgrown tadpole?
You're fine. Honestly.
We've swept the whole canal.
Sweep it again.
Back it up!
- There! Try down there.
- The opening's too small.
- We'd smash the sub.
- I'll buy you a new one.
Just keep going.
Would this help?
Yeah.
Yeah, that'll do the trick.
Thanks for coming.
Well, with respect,
I'm not doing it for you.
It's what she would have wanted.
We had an argument.
The last things we said to each other
were mean and...
stupid.
She knew how much you cared about her.
- You think?
- Yeah. I know.
Yeah...
You right?
Yeah.
The anomaly... it's reopened.
- You'll crash it!
- Sue me.
- Cutter, the anomaly's reopened.
- I know.
This way.
The water!
It's getting deeper.
- Help!
Someone!
Help!
What are we supposed to do now?
It's just a wall.
Help me!
I can hear shouting.
Somebody's in there!
It's okay.
They're going to get us out.
You'll see. We're not gonna drown!
It's okay.
Help!
Hello? In here!
Quickly! The water's rising!
Help!
Lucien, hang on...
we're going to get you out of there.
You all right?
You've got to help Abby.
- What?
- Abby!
Abby's still alive?
- They took her.
- Where did they take her?
- Down the pipe.
- The pipes down here?
They took her down.
Lucien, what did it look like?
That!
I ain't going back in those tanks again.
What the hell is that?
Lucien, stay where you are.
Yess! Two points.
Who says I can't play?
Nice shot.
What was that?
What the...
Give me your gun.
Give me your pistol. Come on!
It's OK! You're safe now!
No, Connor!
No!
I'm coming!
Stay there, Lucien.
Stay there.
Get down. Get down!
Abby! Come here, grab my hand!
Come on!
Just climb up. You can do this.
That's it. I've got you.
Grab hold of this.
That's it. You're nearly there.
You're so nearly there.
Connor, I'm slipping!
OK... you need to come up now.
I can't!
I'm pulling you over, Connor.
- Just leave me.
- No. I'm not letting you go.
I lost you once, Abby.
I'm not losing you again.
Now, come on. We can do this.
It's pointless we both die.
Just let me go.
Let me go.
I can't.
Please!
I love you.
I'm not...
I'm not leaving you here.
No!
Time to go.
- Right. Get these two, take 'em out.
- Sir.
I'm just gonna run a few more tests.
Then we'll get you back to your parents.
They've already been informed
that you're safe.
Your mates! They came! No bother!
I reckon your boyfriend did a good job.
He's not my boyfriend.
- Has the anomaly closed?
- No.
It's still there, and likely to recur.
You know what, Leek?
The area could benefit from
a government redevelopment grant.
We'll start by sealing the anomaly site
with a few thousand tons of concrete.
That should do the job.
- Shall I see the contractors?
- No.
I'll get a shovel
and a cement mixer myself.
- Of course see the contractors, idiot.
- Yes.
Next time I sack you,
you might at least pretend to stay
sacked for more than five minutes.
Still, it's just as well you decided
to disobey my orders.
If it'd been left to Stephen, we'd
still be looking in the wrong place.
Jenny, would you like to join us?
That's unfair.
No.
No, I called it wrong.
- I was lucky.
- Yeah...
You were.
- So is that it?
- What?
Is that what our future looks like?
No. Not ours.
The earth, humanity,
is going to be long gone by then.
Or, perhaps, we do survive,
and just evolve back
into the world we came from.
You mean those things could be
our descendants?
It's possible.
Don't fancy yours much.
Maybe you should have a lie-down.
Yeah...
Back there,
on the other side of the anomaly,
you said something.
Yeah...
I said a lot of things, didn't I?
Mainly "aaargh!"
Maybe I didn't hear you right.
I thought you said something
about how...
you felt about me.
Did I?
Abby, I...
You're not even dressed!
Not dressed? What do you mean?
The theatre, remember?
Yes. The theatre. Of course.
Yeah, I am... I'm ready.
We should go.
Yeah?
- I'll see you later, Abby.
- Sure.
Abby, you look absolutely exhausted.
You really must let me talk to you
about makeup some time.
You realise you might
have compromised this whole...
- project?
- It was a mistake.
Cutter wasn't meant to be there.
Won't happen again.
Well, I hope not,
because the consequences for you
could be very bad.
Now,
please try and stay out of sight
in the future.
It would make life easier for everyone.
Hopefully Cutter won't remember him.
Nick has an excellent
memory for faces.
I hope this isn't
going to go wrong, Oliver.
I'd hate to think I'd put my faith
in the wrong man.
Now that I see people very rarely,
it's hard to know if my judgement
is as good as it used to be.
I hope you can deliver
what you promised.
I can.
Remember,
I have a lot riding on this as well.
Then I'm sure everything
is going to be just fine.