Hi, Clark.
Lana. I didn't think anybody else
was out here.
Well, it looks like we had
the same idea for cooling off.
Yeah, it's a scorcher.
You know, I'll come back.
Oh, no, why? It's a big lake.
There's enough room for both of us.
I'm game if you are.
No peeking.
Your turn, Clark.
I promise I won't peek.
Clark?
Clark!
Boo.
Don't do that.
You're...not funny.
I always said there should be
nothing between us.
Now there's not.
Help!
Help me!
What's wrong?
He's here. Run.
Run!
No!
No! Don't let him take me!
I dug holes. I used my x-ray vision,
but it's like she just vanished.
Was anybody else out there with you?
No. Just me.
You were skinny-dipping alone?
Well, it was kind of
a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing.
All right, son,
I'll give the sheriff a call.
Maybe I should skip school
and look for her.
Clark, it's not your
responsibility to save everybody.
Besides...
...right now, we have a surprise for you.
Outside.
Wow, I didn't know
you got a new truck.
It's not mine, Clark.
It's yours.
What? Oh, my God.
Wait till I tell Pete.
It's not just for fun, son. We needed
a new truck around here anyway.
Well, how can we afford it?
Well, the extra money
Lex gave us came in handy.
Considering the source,
I'm surprised you used it.
Yeah, I know. But I finally realized
that I wasn't giving him a fair shake.
After all you've been through
the last couple of months...
...we're really happy to have you home.
I don't know what to say.
Say that you will take good care of her?
I'll take good care of her.
-Thanks.
-All right.
You better get to school. If Sheriff Adams
finds out anything about that girl...
-...we'll let you know.
-Okay.
Hey, Clark.
Lana.
-Look, about yesterday....
-Oh, it's okay.
You're not mad?
About you running off?
No, I had a good view when you left.
So who was screaming?
-Some girl.
-ls she okay?
I don't know.
She just kind of disappeared.
I'm really sorry I just left you.
Again.
Well, it's not like we had a date
or anything.
But I had fun.
So did l.
Our relationship has always
been about pain and angst.
I guess a little levity is refreshing.
Maybe after a while, you'll stop
torturing yourself and realize...
...that there's no reason
why we shouldn't be together.
It's okay, Clark.
I'm willing to wait as long as you want.
Hey.
Hey, wait.
Hey, who are you?
What happened? I saw
you get pulled into the ground.
At least tell me your name.
Sara.
Sara Conroy.
Okay, Sara, what's going on?
-He's after me.
-Who?
He's always after me.
-Clark. Where were you?
-Pete, did you see that guy?
-What guy?
-How could you miss him?
He had a big red cape on.
He was standing right there.
Sara, you must--
Who's Sara?
She was right there.
The insanity defense.
It's working. I get it.
I'm not insane.
What do you call skipping an exam
worth 50% of your grade?
-That's today?
-That was today.
You flunked.
Chloe, I need your help.
Something came up
at the lake yesterday.
Yeah, I heard.
You are referring
to the Blue Lagoon moment...
...with a certain
former girlfriend, right?
-You know about that?
-This is high school. Everybody knows.
The only--
Did Sara Conroy tell you?
Doubtful, since I've never
met anyone with that name.
Well, she's a new student.
I think.
I saw her in the woods,
and I just saw her in the hallway.
She's definitely a candidate
for Wall of Weird.
Well, that's too bad,
since the Wall of Weird has been retired.
-Chloe, who did this?
-I did.
It's time to leave childish
pursuits behind.
You're not the only one who grew up.
Besides, the Daily Planet was beginning
to frown on my obsession.
-But we know these stories are true.
-Do we?
-People have died because of that wall.
-And people have been saved too.
I'm done chasing windmills, Clark.
From now on, it's hard news
that can be backed up with facts.
Lex, your message sounded urgent.
Is something wrong?
I'm not really sure.
I'm having a rather strange day.
Join the club.
I was hoping you could help me
with a problem, Clark.
What do you need?
Would you hand me that sword?
-ls this new?
-Depends on your definition.
It was a ceremonial weapon used by
a group of 1 6th-century samurai warriors.
The Katai.
Ever heard of them?
Japanese history
really isn't my strong suit.
Let me give you your first lesson.
Legend has it this sword was forged
in the fires of Mount Fuji.
The blade can cut through anything.
The Katai never took it into battle.
They never had to.
Till the day the strongest Katai
turned on his own.
One by one, the Katai fell at his hand.
Nothing left to lose...
...the last of the Katai lunged
at the warrior with this sword...
...the blade cut him clean in two.
But when the warrior's armor fell away...
...the Katai saw he wasn't even human.
Just like you, Clark.
See, I've always been honest with you.
But it turns out you've been lying to me
from the first day I laid eyes on you.
-No, Lex, I can explain.
-Too late!
The irony is, all you had to do
was come to me, Clark.
I was your friend.
I would've protected your secret.
I would've protected you.
But I couldn't be trusted.
I'm a Luthor.
-No, that's not it.
-I don't care!
I'm going to dedicate myself
to ensuring...
...the whole world knows
who Clark Kent really is.
Life as you know it is over.
Lex.
Lex!
Mom! Dad! We got a big problem!
Sara?
What are you doing here?
Lilacs. I haven't seen lilacs in years.
They're my favorite.
My mother used to grow them for me.
Where is your family?
Listen.
Please don't let him
take me again.
Who?
The Traveler, Clark.
How do you know my name?
Sara, you cannot escape me.
No matter where you hide,
I will always find you.
No! Please! No!
Clark!
No!
Clark. Thank God,
we've been so worried.
-What happened?
-You fell asleep...
-...studying for your history exam.
-That was a day ago.
-We've been trying to wake you since.
-You must've been dreaming.
It was so real.
I met this girl Sara Conroy,
and she was in trouble.
Conroy. That's the name
of our new next-door neighbor.
He has a teenage daughter.
They moved into Lana's old house?
There's been a moving truck
there since yesterday.
How could I dream about someone
I've never even met?
Wow.
-Somebody's sure up early.
-Clark, have you been up all night?
I was kind of afraid to go to sleep.
I can't get over
how real that dream was.
-I feel like checking on the Conroys.
-What would you say?
-Sara was in danger in your dreams?
-Be careful.
-Yeah. I gotta be careful when I'm sleeping.
-You weren't just asleep, son.
You were out for 36 hours.
That just happens to coincide
with that girl moving in next door?
-You think she's keeping me asleep?
-I don't know, Clark.
But with all the weird things going on,
you need to be careful.
So, look, I'm asking you,
you stay away from the neighbors.
Missed you at school
the last few days.
I haven't been feeling so good.
To be honest,
you look a little tired.
-Maybe you should get some sleep.
-No.
-I'll be fine.
-Okay.
Well, I brought you your homework.
Mr. Blair said that you could
make up your history exam...
...as long as you have
a note from your parents.
You're the best.
-Can I tell you something?
-Sure.
I had this dream,
and it's really freaking me out.
What was it about?
A lot of things. This girl.
No, Lana, it's not like that.
She needed help.
Let me guess.
You had to save her.
Except I couldn't.
Her name's Sara,
and she moved into your old house.
-When did you meet her?
-That's the thing. I haven't.
How could I be dreaming about her?
Maybe if you walked me
through the dream...
...we could figure it out together.
You don't think I'm nuts?
Clark, I think you have a lot of issues...
...but I do not think
you have lost your mind.
-Okay, so where did you see her first?
-Crater Lake.
-You were there.
-Really? What were we doing?
Nothing.
It's really hazy.
Okay. Well, I have a better idea.
Why don't we go see Sara in person?
Wow, she seemed so....
Do the doctors
think she'll come out of it?
Well, there's always hope.
It must be really hard
to see your daughter like this.
Oh, Sara's my niece.
So this is your old house, Lana.
And you're the boy from next door.
-What exactly happened?
-Clark.
It's okay. It's no secret.
It was a car accident.
Sara and her parents
went off the Loeb Bridge...
...on their way home
from a soccer game.
The paramedics say Sara was asleep,
which is probably why she survived.
-Sara's from Smallville?
-Grandville.
Just over the county line.
Lilacs. Those are Sara's favorite.
Yes.
How did you know that?
They're my favorite too.
It must be kismet,
living in the same house.
That's an interesting medal.
This?
-Well, it's just good old St. Christopher.
-The patron saint of travelers, right?
Yes, I say his prayer every night
in the hopes that Sara's journey will end...
...and she'll come back to us.
Look, I'm sorry.
You'll have to excuse me.
It's time for Sara's medication.
Thank you for stopping by.
Dad, I thought I made it clear...
...that I'm back, fully committed
to LuthorCorp and to you.
And I'm delighted...
...to hear it.
Now, what's the problem?
I've been blocked out of half
the computer files I need to do my job.
Insufficient security clearance?
Thank you, Meli.
These...
...security measures, Lex, are a necessary
evil. You should know that.
-We have to protect our assets.
-From me?
I applaud your renewed commitment
to LuthorCorp.
After what you've been through,
it's remarkable.
But you think I might betray you again.
Betray me?
That's an interesting notion.
Might you?
I want this to work.
I want us to be a family again.
You have nothing to fear from me.
Why have you refused to complete
the psychological profile?
Come on, Dad. You've never believed
in that psychobabble, and neither do l.
I believe that personal,
emotional problems...
...may affect day-to-day decision-making.
I think that dreams can often reveal
hidden dangers, serve as a warning--
Spare me the Jungian cliff notes, Dad.
It's five sessions, Lex. That's all.
I thought you wanted
to reestablish our bond.
I do.
Then do it. Prove that my total
confidence in you is justified.
Clark Kent dreaming of the girl next door.
Isn't it nice to know
some things never change?
Now I'm just trying to stay awake.
Yeah, even Red Bull has its limits.
Trust me. I've tested them.
I think Sara's reaching out
to me for help.
Entering your dreams to communicate?
How else would I know these details
of her life? Like the lilacs.
There is a theory that telepathic
receptivity is increased during REM sleep.
It has to do with frontal lobe activity.
My frontal lobe is acting as a beacon.
Well, I've never seen a case this dramatic,
but we all know that your brain...
...is wired a little differently
than the rest of ours.
Add that the river where she crashed
is a source for our favorite green stuff...
...and you have the perfect Smallville
cocktail for weirdness.
You think the meteor rocks
gave her this ability.
Once she's in, she can keep you asleep.
It certainly explains
the day-and-a-half snore-a-thon.
I didn't wake up
until the Traveler appeared.
And I think it's her uncle.
Or a manifestation of fear
that she has for her uncle.
Sorry. I didn't mean to get
all Freudian on you.
No. Her uncle is all-powerful in her life.
-Why wouldn't he be in her dreams?
-You're not buying the altruism angle?
My faith in human kindness
is not what it used to be.
Wanna go to the courthouse to see what
public records say about Uncle Nicholas?
I have a deadline for the Daily Planet.
And a Wall of Weird story doesn't
take precedence in their mind.
-No time for childish pursuits anymore.
-Hey, that's not fair.
You know that if I had a choice...
...I would definitely be down there
pulling dusty records with you.
I doubt that.
It's okay, I'll grab Lana.
Yeah, at least she can provide
a constant source of caffeine.
Now I know why
public records are public.
They're incredibly boring.
Not all of them.
Take a look at this.
Wow. Sara's parents were rich.
When they died,
she inherited everything.
One guess who's in control of the money.
Uncle Nicholas.
As long as she stays in a coma,
he controls the wealth.
But he still hasn't done anything wrong.
I mean, taking care of your niece and living
a nice life isn't exactly a smoking gun.
Then why is Sara so scared of him?
-I just don't get it.
-Hey, you're tired.
I'm afraid to close my eyes.
I'll go put on another pot of coffee.
You don't have to stay.
I want to, Clark.
That was fast.
-Sara.
-Hi.
I must've fallen asleep.
-Yeah.
-How do you get into my dreams?
I don't know, Clark.
This has never happened to me before.
I mean, just the other day...
...suddenly I was in the woods and then
at school and then at your house....
I realized what happened when
you and Lana came to see me.
You can hear us?
Yeah. It's like being
in a long, dark tunnel.
I mean, sometimes it's open,
but sometimes it's not.
I tried to reach out to you.
You don't know what it's like
to be locked in your own body...
...never any contact.
Sara, who's the Traveler?
Oh, we shouldn't talk about him.
He'll find us.
Is it your uncle?
Why are you so afraid of him?
What does he do to you?
I don't know. I used to be able
to hear the doctors talking...
...and they said I should've woken up.
But every time I do feel just
a little bit better, he does something...
...and I get sent back to a deep,
dark place...
...that's like the bottom of the ocean.
I almost woke up once.
That's when he moved us here.
Sara....
God, he's here.
Interesting theory, Clark.
I know it sounds crazy,
but that's what happened.
Now you're saving people
in your dreams too.
A shrink would have
a field day with that.
-You don't believe me?
-I believe you believe it...
...and that's enough for me.
You'll have to forgive me. I have
a personal bias against psychotherapy.
You don't like
letting people in your head.
Something like that.
Well, this girl's in my head
until I figure out a way to help her.
I made a few calls to Metropolis General.
It's true. Sara was supposed to wake up.
So her uncle is drugging her.
They didn't have evidence of foul play...
...but they've only performed
routine blood tests.
Maybe the drug's untraceable.
It doesn't appear
he's done anything wrong.
We both know appearances
can be deceiving, Lex.
Hearing it in a dream
won't get him arrested.
I appreciate your help.
Anytime.
I always liked this sword.
What is it, some sort of legendary
samurai antique?
Hardly. It's a prop
from my favorite Kurosawa movie.
Throne of Blood.
I bought it at auction.
Relax, Clark.
It can't hurt you.
It's not real.
Right.
You've got to learn the difference
between reality and fantasy.
Get some sleep.
Clark. This is a pleasant surprise.
I thought I'd bring Sara
some fresh flowers.
Come in.
This is real nice of you, Clark.
Would you mind
if I sit with her for a while?
Not at all.
Can I get you something to drink?
Anything with caffeine.
I think I might have some soda.
-Clark.
-Sara.
He's so angry.
Wait, if you're here, that means I'm....
-Hello?
-Lana, hi. Come on in.
I was looking for Clark.
I brought him a pick-me-up.
He's not back from Lex's,
but you're welcome to wait.
Thanks.
-So you finally have new neighbors.
-Yeah, not as good as the old ones.
Mrs. Kent, could I ask you something?
Of course, Lana.
Do you know why
Clark pushed me away?
Metropolis changed Clark.
He's not the same boy he was
when he left this spring.
Jonathan and I are trying
to figure it out too.
I guess I just feel like...
...if I stay in his orbit long enough...
...he'll finally decide to open up.
Martha! Come quick, it's Clark!
Oh, my God!
Jonathan!
-What happened?
-He must've fallen asleep at the wheel.
I'll call an ambulance.
No, I think he just hit his head.
He'll be fine.
Where was he coming from?
Lex's mansion is the other way.
Oh, Clark, I told you
not to go to the Conroys.
He was worried about Sara.
He kept seeing her in his dreams.
It's my fault.
I took him there.
Sweetie, don't blame yourself.
Clark will be fine.
-What about Sara?
-I'm worried about her too.
Sara, wait!
-Sara!
-No!
-We have to get away from him!
-You can't keep running.
-I just want to be free!
-You can.
In the real world.
You just have to face him.
-I'm afraid.
-Sara, you're keeping us in this dream.
I can't help you until I wake up.
I have no power.
I'm sorry, Clark.
Sara!
How did he know about this?
How did he know about the lilacs?
I don't know what's going on
in there, but it's gonna stop.
Don't put that needle in her.
How did you get in here?
We know you've been drugging Sara.
Really.
You and your boyfriend are a little
too neighborly for your own good.
if you kill her, there's no more money.
Who said anything about killing her?
Sara, are you okay?
I'm all right, Clark.
She's in trouble.
-Who?
-Lana.
No.
I warned you, Sara.
This is a fight you'll never win.
-It's too late.
-Sara, we have to save Lana.
He's too strong.
You can't stop him.
Death will follow those who trespass.
Sara! You have to help me!
Sara, you cannot escape me.
-Return with me.
-No.
You're stronger than he is, Sara.
You know you are.
-He cannot save you.
-Fight it!
He did this to you.
-Get angry. He took six years of your life.
-I control your destiny, Sara.
Close your eyes
and return to your slumber.
Don't be afraid, Sara.
The more you resist, Sara,
the more you will suffer.
I will not warn you again.
Clark.
Mom. Lana' s in trouble.
Lana.
Looking for this?
Lex?
What's so urgent?
-I decided to do it.
-Do what?
Meet with the psychiatrist,
submit to a full battery of mental tests.
Curious.
Tell me, what changed your mind?
Because I was dealing
from a position of fear.
If there's one thing you can sniff
out like a bloodhound, it's that.
It's a gift, Lex, and it's useful.
I know the only way I'm gonna
prove to you that I'm your rightful heir...
...is to deal from a position of strength.
I have nothing to hide.
That would mean a lot to me, son.
I figured, you're my father, and you
only have my best interests at heart.
-Who's the good doctor?
-Claire Foster.
Highly credentialed.
She's published a couple of books.
She'll be able to help you
work through any problems.
-That island didn't make me crazy, Dad.
-Crazy? No.
Of course not.
But it'll be good to have that
in writing, won't it?
Lex.
When you're rich, you're not crazy.
You're eccentric.
-Hi, Sara, how you doing?
-Hi.
I brought you some fresh lilacs.
I know they're your favorite.
It's Clark, isn't it?
I didn't think you'd remember me.
Yeah. We've been through
so much together...
...even though we've never officially met.
I still don't know
how I got in your dreams.
The important thing is, you're safe.
And you're awake.
You're obviously a special guy.
I saw some of the things
you're able to do.
Well, in our dreams, we're all super.
I just....
I know it's none of my business.
I know dreams are usually private.
No.
I'm curious to hear your perspective.
What did you see?
Someone who's clearly in love...
...but who resists it.
Lana, right?
Clark, take it from someone
who's been trapped for six years.
If you love her that much,
don't push her away.
It's a long and complicated story, Sara.
I only know what I saw.
I may have been there...
...but Lana's the girl of your dreams.
Burning the midnight oil?
I finally got some sleep.
My makeup history exam is tomorrow.
-How are you feeling?
-Pretty stupid.
Why?
What you did was really brave.
You saved Sara's life.
Yeah, and it almost cost me mine.
It's lucky you got there.
You believed in me when I thought
I was losing my mind.
It was the least I could do.
So I finally met Sara.
All she could talk about was you.
I told her I'd love to switch places.
You know, find out what goes on
inside your head.
It's not that exciting.
Still, you know, maybe it would explain
why things between us....
Lana, if I had the answers up here,
you'd be the first to know.
You know, it's just the last few days
I felt like the girl next door again.
And it was nice.
Even though it almost got you killed?
Lana.
You'll always be the girl next door.
So any chance we could
do something this weekend?
You know, as friends?
What did you have in mind?
Well, it's been like an oven outside...
...so I was thinking we could
go swimming at Crater Lake.
I really don't think
skinny-dipping is a good idea.
Who said anything
about skinny-dipping?
Maybe in your dreams, Clark.
---------------------------------------------
-**- English Subtitles by jondon -**-
Smallville Taiwan Fans Site
---------------------------------------------
www.tvsubtitles.net