- I'm going to throw up!
- This is ridiculous!
Hold on, I've lost lateral control!
This is really not going well!
I know!
No lift.
I can't get any altitude!
Bloody hell!
Try hitting it with more sedation!
I'm already doing that!
What the hell is wrong with...
Magnus, pull up.
I can't!
Pull up now!
Dammit!
This is going to be nasty.
The Team Projet-SG
presents:
Sanctuary - Season 2 Episode 8
Next Tuesday (v. 1.00)
Timing by: Arrow,
nitrogenc, Salomon.
http://projet-sg.net
Just come on.
Just say it with me once...
Reykjavik.
- I love that word.
- You've told me a dozen times.
But I'm talking vodka, good food,
fresh-faced women
with names like "Goodmansdottir"...
Stimulating conversation
under intricate ice sculptures...
Will, I've already told you,
you can't go to the conference.
- Why?
- Some things have come up.
- Things? What things?
- Well, for starters,
our sensors have picked up a very rare
abnormal in the gulf of Mexico.
And?
Mutated Vampyroteuthis Infernalis,
a vampire squid,
incredibly shy. I've only ever
encountered one once before,
60-odd years ago
in French Polynesia.
Okay, so a shy vampire.
There's a first.
Actually, the name is misleading.
They're amazingly intelligent
and very docile.
They're called vampire
not because of a violent predilection,
but more because
of their superior intellect.
- This is fascinating, it really is...
- The beacon is coming from
an abandoned oil rig
off the Louisiana coast.
So one of our retrieval teams
will pick it up, bring it back, boom.
They're all in mission mode.
I'd rather not interrupt them
for something as simple as this.
We will charter a helicopter
in New Orleans and fly out there.
Take Kate.
Kate can't dive. I need you.
I'll miss the opening reception,
but I still can give my presentation.
- Fine, I'll go.
- Actually, no.
I need you here
for the next few days.
Why?
I have a meeting in Berlin
with my U.N. security council liaison.
- Very time sensitive.
- Henry?
- He's in Tasmania surfing.
- The Big Guy?
Is with him.
Is not ready for an extended period
of being in charge.
No, because I told you
about this trip months ago, okay?
I'm a guest speaker.
They're giving me a nice hotel room.
- I'm touring fjords.
- There's always next year.
Which is next year.
I'm sorry, Will.
This is not a request.
You all right?
I don't know.
My door kind of gave way
when we... stopped.
What about you?
Any landing
you can swim away from...
What is it with you
and flying, anyway?
Two crashes in 158 years,
that's not bad.
They only invented flying
110 years ago, so...
Great.
We lost our air tanks
and half our scuba gear.
And our friend as well.
- You think it's still around here?
- I'm sure it's long gone.
This bore well leads to open water.
- Another rare abnormal stays rare.
- Dammit, and we had him.
I've never seen something so big
fit into such a small container.
Cephalopod.
Thankfully, a very
passive one at that.
This one doesn't seem too pleased
that we captured it.
It's much safer with us, believe me.
These creatures are so passive,
they're often killed by other species
very early in their life cycle.
Welcome to your new home...
Squidly.
We will not be calling it that.
There are far more inappropriate
nicknames I could give it.
- I'm sure there are.
- Good, there's still time.
For what?
The red eye, New Orleans.
Connecting through Halifax,
landing in the lovely city
of Reykjavik,
the capital of Iceland.
Come on, Magnus.
I know Kate
is not your first choice,
but can't she just
hold the fort down for a couple days?
I'm not gonna be gone that long.
I'm sure she can.
See, that's the Magnus
I know and love.
But the answer is still no.
Prep it for flight, please.
The radio's broken or there's far
too much concrete and steel in here
for us to get a transmission out.
Meaning nobody can pick up
the chopper's transponder signal.
How deep do you think this goes?
70 feet, maybe more.
- Without scuba gear...
- It's much too far for us
to try to dive to the bottom.
Okay, here's what I think.
Once we don't check in for a while,
those people we rented the chopper from
will come looking for us, right?
Isn't that
how it's supposed to work?
And if they follow
the bogus flight plan that I filed,
they'll be looking for us
200 miles west of here.
It's how we keep
our work private, Will.
According to the mission plan,
we're due back tomorrow night.
Once we don't show up,
Kate's got to get suspicious,
she'll just probably...
Right, right, you're right.
We're totally screwed.
I'm sorry about
your trip to Greenland.
Iceland.
It's Iceland.
I'm sorry your trip
to Iceland was scuttled,
but obviously we have a far more
important problem on our hands.
We always do.
What's that supposed to mean?
What does it mean?
It means whatever you want it to...
It's all right.
It just shifted position.
You think it'll hold?
If the crash didn't bring it down,
I doubt we can.
All I know is
the deposit you gave
the rental company's history.
Maybe everything you heard
about this creature is wrong.
Maybe they're not
as docile as you think.
Nonsense.
We captured it easily enough.
It offered no resistance.
Something freaked it out.
Flying,
or the vibrations from the rotors,
different altitude.
Its container was specially designed
to mimic its preferred atmosphere.
It should have been fine.
How did it go
from happy-go-lucky Cephalopod
to air-rage squid
in a matter of a minute?
I don't know.
I should be learning
Icelandic phrases right now
and discussing psychoanalytic theory
over cocktails.
Yes, instead, you're
stuck here with me.
You know what I mean.
Actually, I do.
This isn't about conferences
or ice sculptures.
It's about some immature tryst
with a woman you barely know.
Excuse me?
Dr. Halstrom, or should I say Sigrid,
your Internet chat friend?
Internet chat friend?
She happens to be
the foremost authority
on deviant psychology in Scandinavia,
thank you very much.
- An attractive element in a woman...
- She has a PHD!
Really, it's about priorities.
My priorities? What is this,
an employee training seminar?
Why did you want me to stay, anyways,
other than to ruin my fun?
Do not pretend that this is
some giant intellectual loss.
This is about your libido.
Come on. If you think that this
is all about me chasing...
- Do not get self-righteous with me...
- Hold on.
What?
Something just swam past my leg.
Maybe that unhappy vampire squid
- that we have in here with us.
- It's miles away by now.
No, I'm telling you...
Something is in here with us.
Something just swam past my leg,
and it's slimy...
You all right?
I'm miles away from all right.
You said it would break
for open water.
It should have.
- Then why is it still here?
- I don't know.
And why does it hate me so much?
It might have marked this
as its territory.
Wonderful news.
I've never seen such aggressive behavior
in this species.
You might want
to get out of the water.
Good idea.
I'm gonna fry you up...
A little tartar sauce...
I think those tentacles
gave me a rash.
I've got an idea.
Why don't we just shoot it?
- I'd prefer not to. It's a very...
- Rare species of abnormal.
Right.
What we need to do
is send it a clear message,
at least until we figure out
why it's behaving this way.
Incoming!
- It's really pissed now.
- Do not touch the water!
Okay, do it!
Clear!
You okay?
That seemed to have worked.
For now.
It'll be back, and...
Battery's pretty much dead.
Thanks for...
Of course.
So what now?
Well, we can't send an SOS.
Eventually someone will notice us
missing and start a search.
In the meantime, I want to know
what turned this creature violent...
Come on, we should change.
Otherwise, we'll freeze to death.
I'll change somewhere else.
Maybe...
Maybe it's environmental.
Something from the rig
is poisoning its food supply.
No, scans didn't indicate
any sea water anomalies.
Fine, then it's just
a crazy giant squid.
Honestly, they are one of the most
docile creatures in the entire ocean.
You got to stop using that word
to describe it, because it's not docile.
It feeds on plankton,
it lives in coral caves,
it can create entire Mandelbrot
mathematical patterns
on the floor of the ocean.
I have never known one
to attack another life form.
Really? What about
bringing down a chopper?
Because this one did.
40 MINUTES PLUS TÔT
Delegates from around the world
are going to be there!
Plus, there's an intense discussion
group on amygdaline mutation!
I think it would really
benefit our work!
Would you tie off
the other side, please?
Anyway, I think my being there would
expand my knowledge of
cutting-edge psychological theory!
The cross-over in treating abnormals
would be endless!
Could you sit in the back, please?
Just in case it needs sedation!
Really?
It seems fine.
Better safe than sorry!
Sea creatures rarely like flying!
All right.
All set?
Let's go.
Fuselage is intact.
- What the hell made us crash?
- I remember a loud noise
and then the Squidapus went insane,
maybe it just really
didn't like flying.
Possibly,
though why it's still upset
is anyone's guess.
Antenna's broken.
Means the radio is definitely out.
I should have come clean to you
about Sigrid. I'm sorry.
What you do in your own time
is your own business,
just so long
as it doesn't affect our work.
Granted, but...
What's wrong with taking
a little time off?
Things have been pretty hectic
around here.
What's your point, Will?
Don't you ever want to take a break?
Not really.
Stranded.
We've got some flares.
We could wait till night,
fire them off.
Flares only work if there's
someone in the vicinity to see them.
This rig is miles
from the nearest shipping lanes.
You must have been
stranded at sea before.
Only once.
April 14th, 1912.
Really?
I wonder how they serviced
the drill apparatus when it was in here.
Do you see right up there,
right up by the lights?
I bet you those air vents
double as maintenance portals.
And the pattern continues
down below.
How far do you think down that is?
30, 40 feet?
That's doable as a free dive, right?
We take the transponder
from the helicopter,
we swim down to the portal,
out to the surface, and signal for help.
Unless, of course,
the docile squid
attacks us before then.
If it attacks both of us,
we don't stand a chance.
But...
- if one of us were to stay here...
- What, like as a distraction?
It seems to hate you more.
Yeah, it really does, doesn't it?
- All right?
- Hold on a second.
All right.
You're good to go.
All right,
if I make it out...
Throw me down a sandwich.
And an Uzi.
Sure you're all right?
Okay, so when you say priorities...
Does that include drowning?
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
The system purged itself.
You got lucky.
Of course!
What?
Why didn't I think of this earlier?
If we can salvage enough wiring,
we run an extension
from the radio's internal antenna...
Right to the wall.
We can use the entire rig
to boost the signal.
But isn't the battery almost dead?
We should be able
to get one last transmission out.
All right.
Bring on the Hail Mary.
What?
It's worth a shot.
All right.
Start with the avionic wiring.
We definitely
don't need that anymore.
All right.
Rip as much wire as you can.
Start splicing.
- So you never go on vacation?
- I travel all the time. You know that.
Yeah, on missions or for research.
I'm talking about...
flopping down on a beach
with a good book,
a never-ending supply of mojitos.
I own a villa in Italy,
on Capri, near Naples.
I go there every seven years.
Seven years?
For a long weekend.
I take it back.
You really do know how to unwind.
That's about as long
as I can stand doing nothing.
British, remember?
Wait a second.
Let me get this straight.
You own a villa in Italy,
and you never told me about it?
I own a lot of things
you don't know about.
Really?
What about a working helicopter?
Yeah, several.
She's nice, you know.
Sigrid.
She's friendly and charming.
She's chair of advanced psychology
at Stockholm University.
She sounds lovely.
Ever since Clara,
things have been kind of...
Lonely.
Goes with the territory, I'm afraid.
Doesn't it make us all
more productive if we have,
normal healthy relationships?
You're not being serious, are you?
What am I talking about?
Nothing we do is normal.
I don't think
that occasional loneliness
is too high a price to pay
for what we do.
Maybe you do.
You just should have told me about it
when you recruited me.
But you never would have
taken the job.
- Probably not.
- And you'd be miserable.
So, what's your cover with Sigrid,
greeting card salesman?
Fire insurance.
Oh, God...
All right, ready?
Hang on a second.
You think this'll work?
It should do. I've never been
stranded for too long.
The Titanic?
I was fished out of the water
by Molly Brown.
She hauled me into her life raft.
I was very lucky.
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
This is A-Star 350,
N-0-X-1-7-J.
Aircraft down.
Requesting immediate assistance.
We are at
27 degrees North by 89 degrees West.
Two souls onboard.
Mayday, mayday, mayday...
Come on...
Battery's gone.
You weren't kidding
about the Hail Mary.
We've any food?
There's MREs in my gear bag.
Did you move it?
It was right there.
Maybe it got knocked into the water.
You don't think it took it, do you?
What, the squid?
After the shock we gave it,
highly unlikely.
Besides, it wouldn't be remotely
interested in our emergency rations.
They're kind of a last resort
for me too.
What is this?
Some kind of residue the squid
left behind when it attacked?
Adult vampire squid don't secrete
anything remotely like this.
Then, what the hell...
Quiet.
Holy crap.
Don't tell me it's another squid.
Maybe one of its young.
It explains why it gave us such
a hard time when we tried to take off.
Now,
we have to be extremely careful
not to hurt or frighten it.
That is definitely not
a baby vampire squid!
Southern hemispheric sea scorpion!
Very rare.
Extremely dangerous!
How the hell did it get
inside the chopper?
I knew I wasn't that bad a pilot.
- I think I'm gonna throw up!
- This is ridiculous!
Hold on, I've lost lateral control!
Okay, this is really not going well!
Looks like it climbed onto the tail
as we took off.
Crawled inside the exhaust louver.
It must have got trapped
in the engine compartment.
That's why I lost flight control.
I thought vampire squid
weren't aggressive,
that other creatures
killed them off.
Yeah, ordinarily,
they're the victim.
It could be that the sea scorpion
is one of the species
that triggers its fight response.
Both these creatures must have claimed
the rig as their territory.
They'll fight to the death
if we let them.
So it's a turf war?
- Wonderful.
- It must have sensed
its adversary was nearby
when we loaded it into the chopper.
But see,
if the scorpion hates the squid so much,
why doesn't it just jump into the water,
and they can, you know, do battle?
It's a bottom-dwelling
arachnid amphibian.
It can't swim. The squid can.
So it needs solid ground
to settle the score.
They're actually very well suited
as enemies.
The sea scorpion is also
more intelligent than it looks.
It's just incredibly vicious.
It's the vicious part
that I'm worried about,
not so much the smart.
It unlocked the hatch?
How did it know how to unlock the hatch?
I told you it was intelligent!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Will, you have to load the harpoon!
What is it about me that makes
these things hate me so much?
- Where is it?
- To the other side! I can't see it!
It's coming 'round this side!
Hello, beastie.
The other hatches are sealed.
This should hold it for now.
I now officially...
hate seafood.
We have to get these two creatures
as far away from us as possible.
Agreed.
But how?
We drop the chopper.
Scorpion can't swim,
the squid won't leave
until it gets the scorpion.
We cut the helicopter loose,
squid will follow it down.
How are we gonna do that?
The acetylene torch
from my diving kit.
It should be able to cut the wires.
Hold on a second.
We're gonna use...
a torch on top of
a fuel-soaked chopper
that has a sea scorpion
trapped inside
so the giant vampire squid
will follow it down?
Sounds like a plan.
No beaches.
No mojitos.
No fancy villas.
These cables are really thick.
It'll take me forever
to get through.
Just try weakening
the major stress points.
So the UN.
Yeah, what about it?
Why does the liaison
want to meet with you?
He wants to talk about how I exposed
Emma Correia as a mole in our network.
In person?
You averted a major security breach.
Couldn't you just do a teleconference?
I don't mind.
Munich's lovely this time of year.
You mean... Berlin.
Right.
Yes, of course, I mean Berlin.
- Because you said Munich.
- Yeah, both are in Germany, Will.
But isn't Munich where...
Olaf lives?
Who?
You think I don't know about you
and Olaf Von Ausburg?
Super-rich guy,
he owns the Bremen soccer club.
I haven't seen him in decades.
You look me in the eye,
and tell me that you were
gonna meet the UN liaison
and not Olaf.
I appreciate the offer, Olaf,
but it's not a good time right now.
It never is, Helen.
I don't know why you keep asking.
Because even you need
some time off once in a while,
especially after everything
you've been through.
Please.
Let me be there for you, hmm?
You need this.
He offered me a weekend away.
I was considering going.
I knew it!
It was a romantic getaway,
wasn't it?
It's my prerogative
how I spend my personal time.
But when I try to get away,
I get the speech about priorities?
Double standard much?
- I'm doing this a lot longer than you.
- Which I respect,
but just don't give me a hard time
when I try to take care of myself.
Please. With Sigrid?
You can do much better than that.
And Olaf is some prize catch?
The guy looks like
a Maserati salesman.
It doesn't matter anyway.
I'm not going.
Why?
Far too many things going on.
That clears the air.
Well...
I think you should have taken him up
on his offer.
Look out!
Will, hold on!
Don't move!
I know.
Any sudden movement,
and it will strike!
Will, look out!
Get out of there!
That's not good.
As long as the chopper's above water,
the squid can't win.
We have to end this, and now!
Well, that thing ain't coming down
any time soon,
not without something stronger
to cut those cables.
Stay here.
Where are you going?
How deep can you dive?
Light it up!
You just blew the whole thing!
It's just gone!
You're crazy, you know that?
You're absolutely certifiably insane.
That was pretty cool.
Cool, yeah!
That was, like,
James Bond, Die Hard cool.
Better than room service
in Reykjavik?
Way better.
Never let it be said that I don't know
how to show someone a good time.
You got it, believe me.
Tuesday is Ashley's birthday.
That's the reason
I wanted you to stay. I just...
I didn't know how to ask you.
I guess it didn't help that I was...
desperately trying
to get away to Iceland.
It's hard, isn't it?
To find someone worth a damn.
You're kidding, right?
There's plenty of fish in the sea.
You didn't just make that joke.
You didn't just make
that joke right here.
- You laughed.
- No, I didn't.
It was derisively, out of pity.
A laugh's a laugh.
I was just choking
on helicopter fuel.
You know...
We sent up
a pretty good flare just now.
I think so.
You think anybody'll see it?
I don't know.
With my luck...
Seriously, how are we gonna
get out of here?