Sanctuary One to Lophelia,
do you copy?
Still no answer, mom.
Take us down.
- You see anybody?
- Let's hope they're below.
What did the message say exactly?
Just that Eric was bringing back
something we'd never seen before,
and we were to meet him
in the harbor.
Only they never made it to the dock.
It's Eric.
Make sure Will is covered.
Come on.
Six dead.
They weren't just killed.
They were half devoured.
Whatever it was, it was powerful.
Whatever specimens
were in these are long gone.
Makes you wonder
what was in these cages.
You think they could've
broken their way out?
Looks more like something
clawed or chewed its way in.
Mom,
come check this out.
- Tranquilizer rounds only.
- Are you sure?
Eric paid with his life
to bring it back.
- We owe it to him to preserve it.
- I think we owe it to him to kill it.
The Team Projet-SG
presents:
Sanctuary - Season 1 Episode 06
Nubbins (v. 1.00)
Timing by: Arrow, nitrogenc,
Ricana, Salomon.
http://projet-sg.net
Now I know why Eric was
so excited about these creatures.
Their hyper camouflage
makes them all but invisible.
Plus the fact that it's present in both
the predator and the smaller abnormal.
The Nubbins.
- You gonna make me ask?
- Ashley's name for them.
Scientific name Nubina Atelerix,
according to Eric's log.
Do we know
what triggers this camouflage?
It seems to be a function
of both fear and aggression.
That makes sense.
Hide to avoid being stalked,
and as an aid to the hunt.
So obviously it was the predator who was
responsible for killing Eric's crew.
Track wounds of each of the victims show
biological evidence of both species.
Come on, there's no way those adorable
things could have attacked anybody.
I'm not saying that they did.
So how could they have left
trace on the bodies?
I'm theorizing that some of
the Nubbins might've escaped
and survived by feeding
on the dead crew members,
hence the mingling of the DNA.
Well, that's creepy.
What's creepy
is that a bunch of them
were eaten by
that nasty-ass monster.
All but our two little survivors,
probably on their way to becoming
the carnivore's next meal.
I'm gonna go see how they're doing.
You okay?
Eric was one of the world's
great hunters of abnormals.
He called them
"evolution's experiments".
Am I reading
a personal relationship?
I don't want to see
his sacrifice go to waste.
Have you had a chance
to check out my Nubbins?
Oh, you mean the...
No, but I would like to.
Oh, guys, come on,
there's nothing to be afraid of.
Oh, man, I think I'm allergic.
You better get used to them. They're
the coolest thing we ever brought back.
I got to admit,
your Nubbins are pretty amazing.
Don't you just want to squeeze them?
You find anything out
about our predator?
I'm still running the DNA.
It'll take a few days before
we can complete the analysis.
So what's going on?
We have a rather odd situation
on our hands.
Isn't "rather odd"
sort of your stock in trade?
A gentleman by the name of
Maurice McRae, recently deceased,
stipulated in his will that I perform
the autopsy on his remains.
Why?
He spent the last years of his life
in a psychiatric institution,
convinced he was an abnormal.
- And how did he know about you?
- That's a question I have as well.
Well, I guess
it's too late to ask him.
True, but his granddaughter, Sophie,
has accompanied his body.
I was hoping you could talk to her,
put her at ease,
while I examine her grandfather.
What does she know about us?
Only the rumors that
her grandfather passed along.
Everyone was convinced that he was
a few cups shy of a tea service.
Everyone but Sophie.
- You're gonna go with the postmortem?
- Of course.
If his claims are unfounded, well...
there's no harm in fulfilling
the man's final request.
You must be Sophie.
I'm Dr. Zimmerman.
You work with Dr. Magnus?
I do.
My condolences.
Thank you, Doctor.
- You mind if I ask you some questions?
- I already know what you're gonna say,
that my grandfather was
an eccentric old man.
Actually, no,
I don't know anything about him.
Sorry.
It's just, all the doctors said
he was suffering
from advanced dementia,
and my parents, it's all my relatives
think he was crazy.
But you didn't.
He just felt so strongly.
I loved him very much.
How did he come to this decision?
Well, he always talked about
a private research facility.
He called it "the Sanctuary",
a place where what he called...
"abnormals", were given refuge.
'course, no one took him seriously.
Is that what goes on here?
Well, we are
a private research facility.
Research into what, exactly?
A range of things.
A "range"?
Why don't you tell me more
about your grandfather?
My grandfather could see things
that other people didn't,
that other people couldn't.
When we spent time together,
it was...
it was like the world would open up.
Sounds like an inspiring man.
I mean, he showed me
what people were thinking,
what they were feeling.
So he actually imparted...
these thoughts or sensations?
Are you humoring me?
- I'm not. I'm just asking questions.
- It's fine. I'm used to it.
Dr. Zimmerman, look, I'm sorry,
if you're going to be so evasive,
I really don't see any reason
to tell you more than I have.
Dr. Magnus has made arrangements
for you to stay here,
as long as you're comfortable with that,
until the autopsy results come in.
Thank you.
You have something
against sleep, don't you?
Just doing some reading.
There's a recurring legend
amongst equatorial rainforest cultures
about Nubbins.
Nubbins?
I thought Ashley made that name up.
She did.
They're most often called "Amoratas".
Apparently the species
is highly prized
as harbingers of fertility
and a bountiful harvest.
In some societies,
they were a common wedding gift,
to promote connubial bliss.
Before the age of self-help books.
When they vanish,
it's considered a portent of discord.
How did the...
the autopsy go...
on Sophie's grandfather?
Sorry?
The autopsy?
There was a...
significant anomaly
to the frontal lobe.
I'll need to do more tests to determine
if it's a tumor or...
something else.
So it's...
it's possible that he's an abnormal?
Too early to tell, really.
I'm...
I'm gonna go to bed.
Sweet dreams.
Don't forget to put out the fire.
I never do.
All right.
Are they okay?
He said the female kept going
in and out of camo mode,
and then swelled up like a blimp.
She gave birth just after dawn.
They're all fine,
all 14 of them.
It took them only minutes
to adapt their camouflage.
The juveniles are
putting on weight so fast
I'm projecting they'll reach
maturation within a day.
That rate of metabolic growth
is scary.
We should find a way
to discourage their mating.
Not yet.
I want to document
a full reproductive cycle first.
I'm keeping this one as a pet,
just so you know.
In the throes of a breeding cycle,
they may not be as docile as they look.
Oh, come on, I can handle
a baby Nubbin, mom.
Right, little guy?
You're so cute.
What about the predator?
He showed marked signs of agitation
throughout the night.
Only came out of camouflage
for all but a few moments.
I don't think he likes the Nubbins.
But you can't say for sure?
No, not yet,
but I can say
that I've never seen brain structures
quite like your grandfather's.
Sophie, the blood I took from you
as a control sample,
I should tell you,
I found similar biochemical
anomalies to your grandfather's.
Oh, my God.
It would be premature
to read anything into it.
Yeah, but if he was an abnormal...
In 24 hours,
all this will be much clearer.
Okay, well, look,
since I've gotten here,
no one has told me squat
about what this place actually does,
and now you're telling me
I'm some kind of freak of nature, too?
You guys are hiding
something from me,
both of you!
Why should I believe
a single thing you tell me?
Sophie, we find ourselves
in a very rare situation.
I'm about to do something
that I normally wouldn't even consider.
I don't understand.
What?
You will shortly.
Will, would you be so kind
as to show our guest around?
Yeah, sure.
Watch yourself there, Big Guy.
You don't want to get between them and
their breakfast. You could lose a digit.
I've never seen
an animal with such...
a big appetite.
It's not just food.
They're not pairing up
for square-dancing.
Oh, man.
Maybe you shouldn't be
exposing yourself unnecessarily.
Yeah, the allergy pills
aren't working.
I just hope these little dudes
aren't permanent guests.
You look as queasy as I did
when I first walked this floor.
Actually, you're taking it
better than I did.
I sensed all of this
before I got here.
I mean, not the specifics, but...
Even though your granddad was gone.
Maybe...
he passed on his gift.
Or maybe the feelings that
you always saw as coming from him
were coming from you.
You okay?
Yeah, just light-headed.
It's all.
I tend to get these dizzy spells.
- Why don't you sit down?
- I'm all right.
You might be having
a mild panic attack or something.
I just get like this.
Well, we'll be sure to have
Dr. Magnus check it out.
What is it?
The new creatures...
They're upset.
I know it may be hard to believe,
but those aren't tricks of the eye.
Those are flesh and blood creatures.
Of course they are.
It's okay.
They seem to be drawn to you.
You okay?
Is it coming back?
I think I should lie down
for a while.
Come in.
The Nubbins came out of camo-mode,
and we did a head count,
and one of them was missing.
Yeah, I just couldn't stop myself.
What time is it?
It's almost 2:00.
Weird.
I must have fallen asleep
or something.
That is not very nice.
Will is a friend.
Co-worker...
slash... friend.
That's all.
Maybe you should...
Maybe you should put him back,
- just to be on the safe side.
- Okay, little buddy, let's go.
- Oh! Oh, man!
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
Get back in here...
Oh, let me...
let me get that for you.
This...
Here.
Just... toss it in here.
Let me...
do that.
You wouldn't have a...
man's shirt lying around, would you?
Medium, right?
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Have you been feeling...
I don't know, odd?
- How do you mean?
- Well, I'm not sure,
but ever since we got back
from the ship, I've felt...
- Woozy?
- Is that how you're feeling?
Yeah, kinda.
I think sometimes I can...
be a little stand-offish.
I mean, I know I can be snippy.
No.
No, not at all.
I don't want you to think
that I'm...
unappreciative,
or unapproachable.
I've been accused of that by guys.
Yeah, me too.
Not by guys, but...
You know what I mean.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's just these new contacts.
I'm just getting used to them.
I really like you...
Really?
Without glasses.
Where's my Nubbin?
At first I thought
they were just camouflaging,
but I swept the entire cell
feeling for them.
Don't tell me they've escaped?
Something gnawed
through the ventilation grate
from the outside.
Mayday.
I'm going to err on the side of caution.
I want the building sealed.
- Nobody goes in or out.
- Threat level "holy crap". Check.
These creatures
escape the Sanctuary,
and we'll have much more than
a pest control problem on our hands.
Can we not turn this
into a planetary crisis just yet?
- They're 14 little furballs.
- Invisible furballs.
We'll round them up, okay?
If they reach sexual maturity
as fast as they've reached full size...
Do the math.
But they haven't overrun
their native habitat, right?
Camouflaged or not,
they wouldn't be much of a secret
and that's the one saving grace.
Something must control their number.
What about the predator
Eric brought back?
That's one of a number of theories
I'm working on.
Though their shared
trait of camouflage
doesn't necessarily define
their relationship on the food chain.
We could try to draw them out,
if we could just figure out
what they crave. You know,
besides other Nubbins.
We know
they're hungry little suckers.
I'll make sure
our food stores are protected.
Too late for that.
They've already wiped out the pantry
and the walk-in.
What?
There's nothing left?
Right.
We go floor by floor.
Snares, tranquilizers,
whatever it takes.
Hey, little guy, it's okay.
Here you go.
That's gouda.
Nobody's going to
hurt you, little fella.
Nobody's gonna...
I lied! I'm going to hurt you!
Your mother was a sewer rat!
I'm going to schedule
a full rabies series,
unless we can confirm its absence
in every Nubbin out there.
Isn't that, like, super painful?
I'm not going to lie to you.
No, it's okay, please.
You can lie to me.
Those poor things
must've been pushed to the limits.
Listen,
I know you're all about
saving the whales and everything,
but these guys just happen to be
a pack of vicious, over-sexed,
hyperthyroid, invisi-rodents.
Stop demonizing them.
They were just afraid!
We have no history
with this species.
We cannot take this attack lightly.
Now, how many have we
re-captured so far?
Three,
- Or so.
- Three?
Almost four.
Out of 14?
Actually, I'd go up about five...
Times.
What did you see?
I'm not sure "see" is the right word,
but by the way they rippled,
I'd say we're looking at
several litters of newborns,
but, they won't be doing
the horizontal tango for, like, hours.
We need to corral them all
as quickly as possible.
I'm taking you off the front lines.
I want you working on a more...
- technological solution.
- I'm good with that.
Tell me you're not talking
about exterminating them.
I'd like nothing more than to see them
all back in their cell unharmed.
We wouldn't be having this discussion
had you shown better judgment.
Come in.
- Could you give us a moment?
- Yeah,
- sure.
- Thank you.
Dr. Magnus...
Hello, Sophie.
Will said you might
be able to help me.
Please, have a seat.
He told you about the headaches,
and the spins and all that?
If it's all right with you, I'd like...
to conduct a few simple tests.
Simple, like brain scans?
Probably prudent
under the circumstances.
I know you have
more important things to deal with.
You're in the middle of a crisis.
Actually, by Sanctuary standards,
this is just another day at the office.
What did my grandfather die of?
A brain aneurysm.
And you said that
we have similar anomalies.
Let's just see what's happens
before we anticipate, all right?
Okay.
It's going to be okay, Sophie.
Okay, here's my idea.
We capture a male Nubbin,
use it as bait
and wait for the females to swarm.
Or we use a female as bait
and watch the males swarm.
Well, want as many of the child-bearers
back in captivity as possible.
As if the girls are going to go all
weak-kneed over the right Nubbin.
- I'm sorry, the "right Nubbin?"
- You know, smart, handsome,
good sense of humor, go-getter,
dedicated to the same things you are,
loves long walks on the beach...
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Johnny Nub in the crosshairs.
There's nothing that threatens
your health. You're fine, Sophie.
- But you did find something.
- It's completely benign,
similar to what we found
in your grandfather's brain,
a tissue structure that bridges
your frontal lobes.
- Like a tumor!
- No, no, nothing like that.
There's a nerve bundle that links
this unusual organ to the thalamus.
I think it may be used
in pre-verbal communication.
Oh, this is unbelievable.
I suspect it's some sort of
empathic ability.
In my world,
it's a genetic expression
that may well preview
an evolutionary advance.
I just always
attributed it to Maurice.
It only ever happened
when I was with him.
He wanted to bring out
your gifts, no doubt.
- That's what the will was about.
- This condition that I have,
assuming that you're right, what...
what does that mean I can do?
That's for you to explore.
With our help, if you'll trust us.
Maybe this isn't going to be
as tough as we thought.
I'm not so sure about that.
Well, I'm telling you, we have
a Nubbins explosion on our hands.
I've found something that may explain
their popularity as a wedding gift.
Wait, don't tell me.
They can be returned?
Actually, they have scent glands
that emit powerful pheromones.
It explains their
overactive mating instinct.
In fact, it may well extend
beyond their own species.
You're not saying
that they're affecting us?
Haven't you noticed it?
Are you asking me
if I've been feeling...
Randy?
- I've made you uncomfortable.
- No, as a matter of fact,
you've...
you've aroused my curiosity.
Turnabout is fair play.
Awkward.
Poor thing.
What the hey?
What's going on?
We've got problems.
You mean plus the fact these things are
spilling out like popcorn at a matinee?
Our systems are degrading.
We got surges, reboots...
Must be the step-down transformer.
Well, clearly that wasn't good.
All right, is it me,
or does it smell like fried Nubbin?
Dude, I haven't been able to smell
anything since they got here.
Oh, man...
We have Nubbins in four
out of five infrastructure systems.
Computer, cooling,
electrical, air purification.
They're not in the water. Yet.
I don't think it was an accident
they brought down the computer system.
Come on, they're smart,
but not that smart.
I don't know.
A couple get sacrificed to bring down
the entire server? Air vents clogged?
Drones sent out to protect
the survival of the hive.
These aren't bees.
- They just reproduce as fast.
- Hive mentality
means tradeoffs between individual
survival and that of the group.
We've seen it in higher orders.
Like every time soldiers
go into battle.
What does that tell us
about what they'll do?
Everything they can
to ensure inter-species domination.
You know, this "catching them
one at a time" is not working.
The more I watch our predator,
the more I begin to think
that it is what controls the Nubbins
in their native habitat.
You're not talking about
turning that killer loose?
Not loose.
We can implant it with a device
so we could track it and control it.
The vast majority of the Nubbins
would be stampeded into the open,
- and we could herd them to safety.
- It's just not fair.
I mean, Nubbins are only doing
what their instincts tell them.
All we'd be doing is replicating the
predator-prey dynamic already exists.
Of course.
Like the lions and the Christians.
We have them contained right now,
but if they get out
and this expands
beyond the Sanctuary,
we could be Ground Zero
for a plague of furry locusts.
We have to act, and quickly.
Tracking device is active.
It's all right, Henry.
He's quite sedated.
- Would you rather I do it?
- No. It's okay, I just...
Much better with computer bytes
than animal bites.
There.
See? What'd I tell you?
Easy peasy.
- Wanted to see how you were feeling.
- Did Dr. Magnus tell you?
- I told her it was okay if she did.
- Yeah.
Yeah, she did.
She...
gave me this bio-feedback device
to use so I know when the supposed
powers are working, and...
I guess you're pretty used
to dealing with freaks.
That's... not how I see you.
I guess I'm just feeling sorry
for myself.
Well, I'm sorry
that you're stuck here
in the middle of
a level-three bio-hazard.
The beast...
The one the Nubbins are afraid of.
It's waking up.
How do you know that?
I don't know, I just...
I don't know.
Listen, Sophie...
These feelings that you're having,
the connections with the creatures,
you should trust them.
It's a...
It's a very special thing.
Well, I wouldn't wish it on anybody.
I don't...
feel special.
I feel like
I should be in a sideshow.
This sense,
it doesn't happen to tell you
where the Nubbins are, does it?
But...
I can...
feel their hearts racing.
Their fear...
Their desire.
Nature abhors a vacuum.
That's because
she's never seen mine.
Easy there, little Nubbin...
I've got suction,
and I'm not afraid to use it.
Releasing the predator...
Look at him go.
Team One,
predator moving from Utility Five,
herding Nubbins toward
residential corridor.
- Shut down air vents.
- Copy that.
Predator 3, Nubbins 0.
Where's he gone?
I'm not seeing him.
Track the device.
Level 5, north corridor.
He's moving fast!
Checking level 5, north corridor,
primary and secondary cameras.
Nothing on the primary corridor.
Negative on B and C.
Nubbins on the move.
Wait a second.
Predator's stopped.
- A dead stop.
- Where?
Just outside the library.
- We're losing power on the main grid.
- Go to auxiliary.
And we have lost auxiliary.
Okay, women and geeks first.
Oh, no, wait, that's all of us.
See what you can do, Henry.
Will, let's go.
They're tranquilizer rounds.
One shot won't do it.
Looks like our predator
just became prey.
Why do I have the feeling
that we're next?
I guess we can skip
the midnight feeding.
So we were wrong
about our predator keeping the Nubbins
in check in the rainforest?
Not necessarily.
I mean, sometimes
predator becomes prey.
Hyenas, for example,
have been known to kill lions.
Apparently we underestimated
the Nubbins' strength in numbers.
Can you imagine what ten times
the number of Nubbins will do?
- Or a hundred times?
- If they can rip a creature the size
and strength of the predator to shreds,
I've no doubt they'd give us no quarter.
We may have sealed ourselves in
with our executioners.
Their hive behavior
isn't just intelligent,
it's strategic.
Sooner or later,
they're gonna find a way out.
And they're reproducing faster
than we can capture or eradicate them.
- Doesn't anybody have some good news?
- I've got wood.
You know...
For the fire.
When we were aboard the Lophelia,
do you remember the hold
- where we found the Nubbins?
- The refrigerated dry hold.
Although it was either turned off
or malfunctioning.
A cryogenic transport's fairly common
for a bioresearch vessel.
Yeah, but the thing is, is...
The setting on the control panel...
It was for 50 degrees,
which is cold,
but well above freezing.
So maybe it was their intention
to slow their metabolism,
moderate their growth
and mating cycles.
Ashley, you and Henry round up
as many fire extinguishers as you can.
On it.
Still, even if we are right about
the cold, unless we can drive them
into the open, I don't see how that
by itself will do the trick.
You are right about the cold.
They don't like it.
Can you tell
what they're feeling now?
Crowded...
Afraid...
Threatened...
They're sending warnings.
They're sounding an alarm?
What are you thinking?
That we try and mimic the frequency
of their distress call.
If we're successful,
we could strategically place emitters
powerful enough to flush them out,
stampede them,
and funnel them towards capture.
- What are you getting, Henry?
- Just over 19 kilohertz.
Ultrasonic. Beyond the range
of human hearing.
19.5...
20...
21.5...
and stabilizing.
There's your distress call,
21.5 kilohertz.
Time to chill, guys.
So what'll happen
to the Nubbins now?
Now that low temperature has slowed
their reproductive cycle to a crawl,
they can live out
their days in relative peace.
- They're not thrilled about the cold.
- Thrilled Nubbins is
what got us into this mess.
It was very brave of you
to share your gift.
In the end, Henry's allergies
were a better detector
than any of my paranormal abilities.
The difference is, is that you can sense
a lot more than Nubbins.
I'm still not sure
how I feel about that.
I think we know
what your grandfather wanted for you.
Yeah. I guess, in a way,
he'll always be guiding me.
And so will we.