Previously on Sanctuary...
I promise to make you happy, Helen,
for all eternity.
Let me help you
before you make things worse.
And how is that possible?
I've already murdered,
what, seven whores?
It's amazing to me,
Jack the Ripper, Sherlock Holmes,
the fact that you two
can sit here together...
Time is a great healer.
Redemption...
That requires a little more.
The shield is working.
If it's him, we're safe.
It's a modified EM bubble.
It protects outside interference
from jamming devices.
- Is that what she told you it was for?
- What is it for?
Me. Your mother did
indeed leave me close to death.
Forgive me.
Tesla found me, revived me,
and the rage that once
fueled me is gone.
Tesla may have shocked you
into your senses, John,
but nobody becomes what you were
without a predilection for killing.
No doubt you'd return
to your murderous habits one day.
I wasn't asking you out on a date.
You're doing a great job.
How do you say,
"it's all going to be okay" in Zulu?
What she said.
That's right, keep it light.
They're panicked enough
without picking up on our fears.
Remember, they're empaths.
They feel what you're feeling.
- Neomycin?
- The intakes have second-degree burns.
Did you contact
the Mumbai Sanctuary?
Told them the empaths are safe.
Their ship, on the other hand...
How's it looking?
Not so good. Celine Dion should start
singing about now.
Sorry. Disaster joke, not funny.
What the hell is keeping him?
Fire's spreading, smoke everywhere!
It's okay, just come with me.
- The rest of the crew?
- Dead.
One of the empaths is still missing.
Did you check the sleeping quarters?
Without detailed knowledge
of the vessel, arrivals can be tricky.
- I need a known destination...
- Yes.
On my way.
Be careful.
- Any idea what happened to the ship?
- Best guess?
About two hours out of Maputo,
the boiler exploded,
tore a hole in the hull.
All right.
I may need your help
bandaging the new intakes.
Come on, doc.
You know about me and blood.
All right,
get the guest quarters ready.
- We're going to need beds tonight.
- Check.
- Metal fragment in her abdomen!
- Dear God, her pulse is weak.
Get her to the O.R.
I need to operate immediately.
It's quite a day.
Thank you for answering my call.
It seems business
is never finished with us,
despite our losses.
I couldn't have done it without you.
All hands on deck.
Besides, I've missed this place.
Vengeful killing sprees
are good for the soul, but...
there's no place like home.
Quite a lot of teleportation
for one day.
You feeling any worse for wear?
Right as rain.
In fact, I've...
I've never felt better.
The Team Projet-SG
presents:
Sanctuary - Season 2 Episode 11
Haunted (v. 1.00)
Timing by: Arrow, Salomon
http://projet-sg.net
I can't imagine what would have happened
to them had John not answered my call.
There was no rescue craft
close enough to have saved any of them.
Lucky.
That she is. One more centimeter
to the right, this would have lacerated
her descending aorta.
- Cardiac arrest.
- Dammit! Get the cart!
One milligram epinephrine.
Alive.
For now.
She's not out of the woods yet.
Let's close her up.
Man, Kate needs your help
with the intake database.
- Can't you do it?
- I tried,
but it looks like
the system's fried.
I'm a little busy here.
Tell that to Mumbai.
They're screaming for our rescue
and recovery logs asap.
Molly's primed for a charge.
I can't exactly bail on her right now.
Molly?
Modified o-wave linear expeller.
Doesn't that acronym spell "mole"?
Molly's hotter.
Dude, it's a weapon, not a woman.
Clearly you and I
have not dated the same girls.
Are you going to do this thing,
because...
Okay, fine.
You're gonna have
to take over for me.
Molly needs to be charged
and assembled
before the seams
on the pulse magazine degrade.
You just made that up.
That means nothing to me.
All you got to do is open the stock,
remove the power core and charge it,
then you re-insert the power core
back into the stock,
you seal the magazine,
vent the shaft,
secure the laser sight,
and presto.
You realize you're talking to a guy
who flunked Allen key, right?
Relax. You'll be fine.
Don't overcharge the power core.
You'll blow up the lab.
Okay, so no pressure, then.
You're welcome.
I feel nothing for you people.
It was a favor,
a task, nothing more.
What did you say?
I urge you not to trifle with me.
You should have said nothing.
You should have left
well enough alone.
Why did you come to me?
It's up to her now.
We've done all we can.
- Recovery in the infirmary?
- I want her monitored.
Today could have gone
a lot worse than it did.
I'm sorry. I don't speak Zulu.
Nozipho, one of the other empaths.
She's like you.
You can't...
You can't see her.
Is she lost in the Sanctuary?
God, I'm so sorry,
I don't understand.
You can't...
You can't sense her anymore.
Come with me.
What did you do to this thing?
Come on, so now it's my fault?
I'm just saying, you see this?
- Who designed the database?
- It is not the database.
Says you.
Are you...
Who does this?
What?
- What is this?
- I use my computer.
- The Craven Throng?
- It's experimental garage acid.
Come on, you're telling me
that my music screwed up your database?
Your freeware media player created
a conflict in the com port access.
Why is it whenever you talk,
all I hear is, "blah, blah"?
I did not create this
to be your personal stereo system, okay?
Is that...
Blood's fresh,
20, maybe 30 minutes.
Her throat's been cut.
Get the security camera footage.
I want to know everyone who was
on this floor in the last half hour.
All right, you got it.
- Gather our guests.
- I don't get it.
These guys are so gentle.
They're no threat to anybody.
Exactly.
They're the perfect target.
Beautiful...
Isn't it?
Turn around
very slowly.
How long?
Long enough.
Habits are...
hard to break.
Perhaps you're not
trying hard enough.
I am who I am.
It's high time
you did something about it.
I take it the EM shields are up.
Indeed.
I heard shots.
Is he...
He's dead.
Tell me again why you're trying to bring
a homicidal maniac back to life.
It's more about compulsion
than murder.
I set him up for this,
letting him loose on the Cabal.
He knew I'd find out about
his activities sooner or later.
- He wanted me to kill him.
- No offense,
but you guys got a seriously
messed-up relationship.
It's complicated.
Charge the defibrillator.
Second button there to 200,
and clear!
- Nothing.
- 300.
Clear!
360.
What the hell?
I'm downstairs.
The lights are flickering.
Yeah, I know, I know.
- We took a power surge.
- He's breathing again.
The infirmary.
We got a problem.
The empath on oxygen, Musa.
She's gone offline.
We have to get her back here.
Bring the patient from the infirmary
to the O.R. now.
On it.
I need to do a major system reboot.
Can you live without your med servers?
Do it.
We need to check for any breaches
in abnormal containment.
We won't have full security
until Henry's reboot is complete.
You're cool hanging
with Jack the Ripper?
He's no danger to anyone right now.
I don't know why...
I feel so strange.
I know you wanted this...
to end more quickly.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
Why did you bring me back?
Main server's
coming back online now.
I'm gonna head to the O.R.
and check on the bio-techs.
Keep me posted.
The EM shield is at full strength.
Attempt to teleport,
and you will die.
I understand.
This is my fault, John.
I should never have believed
that you could change,
that you had changed.
How many have there been since...
Since you let me back in?
Does it matter?
You've been killing again,
and not just Cabal remnants.
Does it matter that I never
wanted it to begin again,
that I tried to stop?
Helen, I tried.
This is Whitechapel all over again.
You're gonna be okay.
I'm going to get you to the O.R.
Your lungs are hurt,
but you're gonna be okay.
You need to put this on.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
I'm sorry. I'll get you to Dr. Magnus.
She'll understand you.
You're gonna be fine. I'm gonna get you
going. I don't speak any Zulu, sorry.
So was I right?
You think the boss still has the hots
for tall, bald and deadly?
Man, I thought
I had relationship issues.
What about you, Big Guy?
Anyone special in your life?
I mate every five years.
With who?
What the hell happened?
Someone plug the microwave
and the toaster in at the same time?
You got me. I'm still trying to get
all systems back online.
- How's she doing?
- Her life support is fried.
She's on back-up.
Magnus wants to keep her close.
All right, we are back up
and firing on all cylinders.
Now, tell me, who's your daddy?
I'm gonna go
check on the other patients.
What?
I'm arranging for your transfer
to a secure facility out of the country.
You are far too dangerous
to ever be free again.
What happened now?
Stopped.
Great.
Seriously?
I know, I know,
we're in auto lockdown!
I'm getting an override going now.
Come on!
Will, this is not good...
Oh, man.
- What was her name again?
- Magnus said something like... Bosa.
Antlers...
Musa!
So just talk to her
and calm her down.
It's very important.
Hey, Musa...
What?
No signal?
Since when?
Something's jamming it.
Come on.
- This is nuts.
- Stop doing that.
Don't you update
your safety equipment?
Constantly.
Yeah, then,
why isn't anything working?
Where's the disembodied voice saying,
"chill out. Help's coming?"
I'm that voice.
Is help coming?
This shouldn't be happening.
Can we go out the top,
climb up to the next floor?
Yes, we can, but we're not going to.
Not safe.
Okay, Biggie,
this whole speaking-in-code thing
is really not working for me.
Something's wrong.
Need to know what
before we do anything rash.
Wouldn't want to do that.
That is some old-school radio shack.
Is that an original phone system?
From when this wing was built.
Looks like it hasn't
been used in years.
It hasn't.
- Do you really think it's gonna work?
- If you stop talking.
Stay exactly where you are.
Will, come in.
Do not even think about teleporting.
The EM shield stays active
in lockdown mode.
- I have no intention of escaping.
- Really?
I will answer for my actions.
- Don't try me, John.
- I'm quite serious, Helen.
Something has changed.
- Stop!
- If you'll let me, I'd like to help.
Stop talking.
On your knees,
hands where I can see them.
Better?
Okay, just sit tight.
We're gonna get some help.
Dude, I need help in here.
- But you got to get me in the room.
- Yeah, I know.
What the hell is going on?
Dude, I'm completely shut out.
- This is very serious.
- Come on.
I've tried every
override command I can.
I have no control.
What about the...
Hello?
Check?
- Nothing?
- I got nothing.
- Yeah, I know.
- Hang on.
Anyone!
You've got to be kidding me.
Surveillance feed.
There.
Will somebody please tell me
what the hell is going on here?
"Gunama," what's that mean?
I had no idea
you were a techno whiz.
Don't know why.
So how old is this building?
Elevator was new when I moved in.
When was that, 1950?
'51.
Here, hold this.
Hello?
Big Guy?
Where are you?
In an elevator.
No, I know, but where are you?
Will, it's the original
room-to-room intercom.
Man, I can't believe
that thing still works.
What's going on?
The phones are dead. Nothing works.
Yeah, I know.
Henry's locked in the O.R.
with a patient. I'm stuck on med level.
We've gone into
some weird lockdown mode.
- What for?
- I was hoping you could tell me.
Something's going down.
Still, it shouldn't kill the phones,
or lock us out of the computers.
At least I can see you.
You're on the surveillance cam.
Magnus is locked in with Druitt.
- Is she all right?
- Yeah, she's fine.
He seems quiet for now.
Wait. If audio's down,
why is video still running?
I mean, shouldn't
everything be fubar?
Why am I talking to you
on the oldest intercom ever made?
Good point.
Can you connect with anybody?
We need some help here.
All right, I'll give it a shot.
We good?
We're still locked out.
Come on.
This really is none of my doing.
Otherwise,
why would I still be here?
Accidental or not,
I will shoot you
if you give me reason.
That is very clear.
None of this makes any sense.
Lockdown shouldn't cut off
our communications
or jam our radio and phone signals.
Henry's overrides
must not be working.
Helen, I know there's no good time,
but I need you to understand something.
What is this?
It's as if a part of me
has been severed.
Can anybody hear me?
Yes, I can.
Where are you?
Elevator.
There's been a malfunction
in the security system.
- I need assistance.
- Not the only one.
Try that one, the black wire.
- Found her.
- Boost the signal if you can.
You're connected.
We got a patient
in major distress here.
- Where are you?
- In the O.R. with Henry. It's Musa.
- She's having a seizure.
- Doc, her heart rate is rapid,
but her blood pressure's really low.
I don't know about her physiology.
How do we proceed?
First priority, stop the seizure.
Can you find a vial of diazepam?
Back cabinets, bottom left.
Two milligrams in an IV.
Can you set that up?
Yeah, we're on it.
Let me know
when that's up and running.
It should calm her convulsions.
I'm doing it now.
Oh, boy.
So, what the hell happened?
I've already tried everything I can
from a remote terminal.
This isn't a glitch, believe me.
We're locked out on purpose.
We're all cut off from each other,
but elements from the security system
are still active.
It's got to be a targeted attack.
No way. Since we got hacked,
our remote security protocols all have
triple redundancies now,
it's totally not possible.
And no perimeter breach
detected, no data theft,
- and these odd power fluctuations?
- I know.
None of it matches the patterns
of a remote hack.
And yet we're all
at a perfect disadvantage.
So we got hit by something.
Any theories on how to undo it?
This all started right after Henry
rebooted the entire system.
- Everything was fine, and...
- The system overloaded.
It must've damaged the automated
commands running the Sanctuary.
All the security
cameras are working,
but I can't get into a system
that I created.
It's like someone's running all this
in real time.
You think somebody's controlling things
from inside the building?
- One of the abnormals we rescued?
- Impossible.
They're here seeking asylum,
and it's not their way.
When you revived me...
The overload.
A massive energy surge.
Yeah, but from what?
I feel different.
I feel...
purged,
purified.
It came from you.
I think so.
How's Musa doing?
The convulsions have stopped.
She seems to be stabilizing.
Good. Henry, take the defib paddles
and charge them to maximum.
All right.
Okay, max power, ready.
Juice the electrical panel.
Something just came out...
What the hell was that?
It's not anyone inside the building,
it's the building itself.
What does that mean?
That something very much alive
is in control of the Sanctuary.
What,
like as in an electrical being?
This one appears sentient,
even natively intelligent.
It's found a way
to cut us all off from each other.
The fluctuations.
- It's testing its new environment.
- Exactly, and it won't be long
before it has full control.
Okay, time out.
Are you guys sure
this thing is hostile?
It's a trapped creature.
Maybe it'll just...
I don't know, hang out and chill.
It's violent,
remorseless, relentless.
It won't give up ground without a fight.
Think of it as facing me.
Once it has full control
of this facility,
it will be unstoppable.
It could easily spread
to the city and beyond.
- So how do we fight it?
- Henry, we need...
The defense protocols, you got it, doc.
I just need to feed it into the network.
Which won't be easy.
Fill me in.
Energy creatures
often behave like viruses.
They forge a parasitic relationship
with whatever host environment
they can invade.
4 years ago we had something like this
caught in our back-up generators.
It caused a lot of craziness.
- How'd you do that?
- This one's got me locked out, but...
If we can restart the main power,
do a cold start, I might gain control.
We've to get into the catacombs,
shut down the power.
- Which we can't do, can we?
- Well, we have to find a way.
Can you get out through the top,
climb to a different floor?
I've already thought of that,
but opinions are divided.
I don't like it, not with something
monitoring our every move.
It's watching all of us,
which is kind of creepy.
Come on,
it can't know what we're up to.
All of you,
knock out your security cameras
as politely as possible.
All right, done.
Henry, are you able
to log onto the network?
Yeah, but I'm locked out.
It's like playing Xbox
without my joystick.
Keep trying to hack in.
As it adjusts to its new environment,
it may give you an opening.
All right, I'm on it.
Will, do you have any access to the old
duct system from where you are?
Yeah, I guess there must be.
Why, what are you thinking?
The old heating system's obsolete.
We switched to radiant years ago.
Meaning it's probably outside
of Electro's field of vision. Nice.
Get down there, reboot the system.
It should give us control
of some of the key sections.
All right.
One of you should climb up
to the next floor,
see if there's another way
to the catacombs.
We're on it.
Are you sure?
I can go.
I'm lighter.
- I'll get there faster.
- Faster's good.
Here, I'll help you.
Watch where the hands go, wookiee.
Hey, I think I found a way in.
All right, you should go.
Just be careful.
See you in a few.
You said you feel...
Different.
What do you mean by that?
The darkness within me is...
gone...
Completely.
Far more than when Tesla shocked me.
That was appeasement, but this...
This is...
So peaceful.
It must have happened
when I restarted your heart.
The creature jumped from you
into the facility itself.
But how did it end up inside me?
I have no recollection
of ever encountering it before.
You wouldn't have to.
God, it actually makes sense.
Every time you teleport, you convert
your molecular structure to pure energy.
The creature could have latched onto you
during one of your jumps,
integrated into your being
when you re-materialized.
And now...
That its influence is gone...
Is it not possible this entity
was the sole cause of my bloodlust?
That it's been polluting my soul
since I began using my power?
I want to believe you, John,
but it's too easy to blame everything
you've done on something else.
You're right.
My mind is so...
Clear.
As it was when we first met.
That thing was my rage.
I'm sure of it.
{\There's danger! Can't you feel it?
The darkness is growing}
You're okay here. You're okay.
{\It's making something...
Poison in the air!}
I so don't understand
what you're saying right now,
but I can tell it's not good!
Something's bugging you.
You're an empath, and that's...
Oh, god.
Hang on a sec, what the hell is that?
Hang on.
It's looking for something!
It's scanning
our chemical directory.
How could it actually access
those compounds?
Using the robotic assist mechanism.
It is possible.
What else could it be after?
Well, it could just be doing
an inventory diagnostic.
I don't know, I'm still scanning.
I'm trying to find a way to break in.
If it shifts focus for...
We lost the intercom!
So fix it!
John, what's its agenda?
Chaos, death, suffering.
Sound familiar?
Once it learns everything it can
about its environment,
the violence will escalate.
Come out to the coast,
we'll get together,
have a few laughs...
Right is east...
Right?
All right, fine.
You want to play, let's play.
Here we go.
You...
zap me again,
And I'll kill you...
Somehow.
Hallelujah!
Oh, man...
Found the furnace.
Thought these were
out of commission.
Defunct, my ass.
Oh, crap.
Come on.
Elevator, too?
A little slack, please!
Oh, not good.
- Dammit.
- Get down here!
Get out of the way!
- We've got power again.
- Yes, but no control.
It's always something, isn't it?
I'm writing a damn symphony here.
Come on.
Just a tiny little command.
Nothing to threaten you.
Come on...
Come on!
Suck it, Electro!
This is my town!
- This thing has brakes, right?
- Used to!
Next, elevators.
Right, emergency brakes are...
Active! Okay!
See? See? What'd I say?
Okay, what else you got for me?
It's gonna kill us all.
Did I mention I hate rides?
Really?
It's stripping the emergency brakes.
And taking us higher,
so that when we reach the top...
We drop.
You son of a...
Come on, Will, cut the power.
Yebo, damn right!
- They have risen to the occasion.
- Of course they have.
Hey, doc, it's Henry.
Will did it.
Communications are back,
so's most of the rest.
- Most?
- Yeah, I'm working on it.
Doc, the toxins it was scanning?
It's making something very bad,
very fast.
It's using the automated assist.
- Can you override it?
- Yeah, that's the problem.
I've reclaimed everything else,
but I'm locked out of the main lab.
I can't make it stop.
Mr. Foss, can you open the door?
- It's all right, Henry.
- All right, hang on.
Nice.
Sarin gas nerve agent.
We've got about 90 seconds.
It'll release the compound
into the vents.
It won't end here. It will grow,
consuming whatever it can
and never stop killing.
- Henry, we need more time.
- We don't have it.
Okay, power's been reset.
We should be good.
What's happening now?
My entire body is geared
to being its home.
Let me go.
- Don't do this. We could find a way...
- I love you.
Remember that...
Always.
Would you be so kind as to...
deactivate the EM shield?
For all eternity.
I need a med kit right away!
Get away from me!
Let me help you!
I don't need your help!
It would have killed a lot more
if it weren't for you.
You kept it at bay.
- I need to leave now.
- Where are you going?
I have no destination in mind.
Wait.