- Hey, honey.
- Hey, dad.
What’s going on with the unibomber look?
I was going for George Clooney.
Go further.
That’s right, you’re not used to seeing me like this.
See, when I’m on the job I usually let it grow then I shave it off right before I come home.
Kind of a ritual for me.
Well, make sure you find a razor day after tomorrow.
And after that, I’m gonna be shaving a lot more often.
Okay.
Hey Brooke. Hey rake boy.
I see nobody uses the doorbell still.
Papa Peyton, the scruffy thing’s working for you.
What are you guys up to so early?
- I don’t know. Peyton just asked us…
- Oh no, you know what? You’ll find out when you get home.
Not even a little hint?
Uh Uh. Not even. I love you
You better. Love you too, honey.
Bye.
So, what’s the surprise?
I need your help with something. Come on.
Damn, that’s nice. Is this your dads?
Yeah, he hasn’t driven it in like a year though.
Do you think you can get it to run?
Of course he can.
And he’s going to look good doing it too in a tight little wife beater,
maybe some grease smudges.
And I was thinking maybe you could help me wash and wax.
Glad to help.
I just want to do something nice for him. Since he’s coming home.
Alright,
I’ll go get my tools.
Surprise!
You answer the door in your underwear?
Grandma, Grandpa. What are you guys doing here?
Royal, May, oh, what a surprise.
Well, thanks for the warm welcome. I told you this ambush was a bad idea.
- He’s dragging me to another one of those auto conventions.
- Nobody’s dragging anybody anywhere.
I told him that the only way I’d go is if we came by here for Danny’s birthday.
Oh, Dan’s birthday, of course.
Yeah.
Well, you going to leave us standing out here all morning freezing our asses off?
- Oh…
- Come on in.
Kiss Granny.
Looks like you put on a few there, Deb. It looks good on you.
Dan.
You remembered. I’m touched.
Oh I’m not here to wish you a happy birthday. But your parents are.
What?
Yeah, they showed up at the house.
Apparently, you never told them that you’re not living there right now.
How’d they take it?
You think I told them? I’m not going to be on the receiving end of that. That’s your job.
Well, how long are they here?
Just tonight. But it gets better. Your mother is cooking you a big birthday dinner.
Oh perfect.
Alright, so what are we going to do?
We are not going to do anything. You are going to go to the house right now,
- and tell them we’re separated.
- No, we’re doing the counseling.
We can work this thing out, right? Isn’t that the whole point?
- It is.
- Well, you know how they are.
Do you really want them weighing in on the state of our marriage?
Do you remember when we told them we weren’t going to have any more kids?
How many times did my dad call you? And now you don’t even have the option of hanging up on him.
Go on, Dan. Just say it.
We go through the motions tonight. Get it over with.
Send them on their way. Go back to working on us.
Besides, it might do us some good to try and remember what its like to be a normal family.
Fine, just for tonight.
Just for tonight.
Good morning, Sir. Table or counter?
Um, actually, I’m looking for Karen.
Oh you know what? She’s in Italy right now. Cooking school.
Good for her.
How’s that boy of hers doing?
Lucas is great.
She calls in every once and a while. You want me to leave a message?
No, that’s alright. I’ll just catch her the next time I’m passing through.
Okay, can I tell her who stopped by? Mr…
Just an old friend.
Well, it’s not the battery. It’s probably the starter.
Well, you can fix that, right?
Yeah, it shouldn’t be a problem.
It’s an amazing car.
It’s an amazing guy.
Is that what you got me in this thing for?
Yeah…
I was, just getting started.
Sadly, so was I.
What’s wrong?
I’m just worried about my dad.
Okay, I just checked online and now they’re saying it’s a category 3 hurricane.
Alright, and you already checked on the web cam, right?
Yeah, its out.
Well, maybe he turned it off.
Or the storm did it for him.
Yeah, but storms knock that kind of thing out all the time, right?
Anyway, aren’t dredging boats huge?
He wouldn’t be on the dredging boat.
Right  now, if there’s a storm headed his way, he’d be on this little tiny transport
heading back to shore and that’s what worries me.
Okay, Peyton, just stop. Don’t do this to yourself, alright?
Just because he hasn’t checked in doesn’t mean something’s happened.
Doesn’t mean it hasn’t either.
So this dinner thing’s gonna be pretty bad, huh?
Massacre.
My Grandma’s okay. It’s just my Grandpa’s pretty intense.
You’ve met my dad. Just imagine where he comes from.
- Scary.
- Yeah.
You  should come tonight. Maybe it will make everybody behave.
I’ll come if you want me to.
No, I wasn’t serious. I wouldn’t put you through that.
No I mean, if you’re asking, of course my answer’s yes.
Well, then I’m asking.
Well then I’m coming.
Let me get this right, the charcoal finish, custom leather package,
and what you want is a champaign interior.
I’m here to see the manager.
Excuse me
Hey fellow, you ought to know who you’re doing business with.
Is there a problem?
Well, you’re buying from Dan Scott. Basketball legend.
Still holds the all time scoring record for Tree Hill.
Made all-state his Senior year.
- No kidding.
- My dad.
- I figured. You play college too?
Would have, but he blew his knee out in his freshman year. He got robbed.
Would have been one of the greats.
Dad, Mr. Miller’s really not interested.
I’ll tell you what, meet me in my office. Okay? I’ll be right in.
- Yeah.
- Champaign interior, right? Alright.
What? Somebody’s got to brag on you.
And you’re not going to close that sale without your old mans help you know that, don’t you?
You know you always were my biggest promoter.
Yeah well.
Hey still in shape. Good for you.
Oh you’re home. Listen, I called Nathan. I told him not to tell Dad that he’s not going to practice.
You mean that he quit the team?
You know what I mean.
I also told Keith to avoid the subject.
Any other lies I should remember to tell?
I’m trying to protect our son from my father, okay?
You don’t even see the irony, do you?
Mom, you look beautiful as ever.
God bless you for a liar.
When I compliment you, you call me a liar.
You look tired.
Hey, son, what’s the deal? No more Charlotte hornets?
Yeah, New Orleans can have them. You think they have playoffs hope?
No, no.
- No sports talk.
- Oh, come on.
Yes ma’am. I just became head of the table then, huh?
- Keith!
- Mom!
You look great.
Well, look what the cat dragged in.
It’s good to see you too, dad.
Happy birthday, Danny.
Yeah, thanks.
Come on, have a seat. Dinner is almost ready.
Hey Deb.
Danny will you pour some wine, please?
- I’m on it.
- Amen to that.
Uh, listen mom, we’re going to need another place setting, I invited a guest.
A date! Oh my goodness, well you get that chair over there…
Grandpa, Grandma, this is Haley.
- Oh Haley.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
Well, Nathan, you’re looking more and more like your old man every day.
We all know where he gets his good looks, don’t we? Well, come on in.
- You sit right here next to me, hun.
- Thank You.
I’ll get it.
Oh my goodness, Whitey!
- Good to see you.
- Good evening everybody. Sorry I’m late
Glad you came?
Yeah.
Alright, try it again.
We got power!
Whooo.
Peyton, come check it out.
What is it?
I just got a phone call.
Um, it’s the storm.
My dad’s transport is missing.
There were three guys on it.
They recovered a body.
What’d they tell you?
I have to go see if it’s him.
Alright, you sure you shouldn’t call your Grandma?
No she’d freak out. I’d rather not upset her. Besides, its not going to be my dad.
Of course its not.
Let’s go ahead and get this over with. We have a 4 hour drive ahead of us.
A 4 hour drive into a storm?
Well the storms passing through. By the time we get there it should be gone.
Okay, wait a second. Shouldn’t somebody stay here by the phone? I mean, incase your dad calls.
I will. You go with Peyton.
You sure?
Yeah. Lucas you’re good in crisis, not that there’s going to be one.
But I would probably end up falling apart and you’d end up taking care of me which is not the point, so…
I love you.
It’s  going to be okay.
You’re the best.
I’ll call you guys if I hear anything.
So, how’s the team doing this year, Whitey?
Oh we’re still undefeated actually.
Dad, you still rooting for the Magic these days?
Please! No talk of sports until after dinner, okay?
Good idea mom.
Sorry.
Well, Nathan, what are you averaging these days?
You know your dad had 27 and a half a game. You beat that yet?
- Royal, we just said…
- I’m asking the boy a question, May.
Uh well maybe you should ask the old man.
24 points a game I think, isn’t it?
So, 24 a game huh?
You’re gonna have to get that up if you’re going to beat the old man.
Yeah, your dads star would have risen through the roof at Carolina
if it wasn’t for that damn knee of his. How’re your knees?
- No worries.
- Oh, he’s got great knees.
Uh huh. Of course Danny takes after his old man. Never let adversity stop him.
Too bad Keith takes after his mothers side of the family.
Lucky for him.
I’d drink to that, but I have to get a refill.
Well, I should see about the cake.
I’ll go do that, Mrs. Scott.
- Want to come help?
- Yeah, the cake, right.
I warned you, it was going to be intense.
Oh, insane is more like it.
You know, there’s a door right there. We could sneak out, nobody would even notice.
Tempting.
Um, so how often do your grandparents come into town?
Couple times a year. Why?
Haley, you’ve got that look.
What look?
The look you get when you want to tell me something but you don’t really want to tell me.
No I don’t, and you shouldn’t know that look yet.
What is it?
Your grandfather came by the café today. And he asked for Karen.
- He did?
- Yeah.
I just kind of got the feeling like they’ve been keeping in touch.
Does Lucas know?
No, they’ve never even met. But your grandfather asked about him.
That doesn’t make any sense.
My grandpa acts like my dad’s a second coming, why would he visit Karen?
I don’t know, I don’t want to start anything, I’m just telling you.
You know what? My family’s so screwed up,
nothing new would make a difference right now. Don’t worry about it.
You warm enough?
I’m okay.
I should probably get the heater fixed in here, huh?
You know, I could have Keith take a look at it for you. I mean he’s really good at that stuff.
You want me to stop and get some coffee?
I’m fine. Thanks.
Thanks for doing this for me, Luke.
It’s what friends are for, right?
Yeah.
Now what?
What’s going on?
Bridge is up cause of the storm. It’ll be open in the morning.
Alright, we have an emergency, we have to get across the bridge.
I’m sorry Miss, but it’s not safe.
Okay, um, is there another way through?
Only the ferries, but the channel’s too rough so they’re not running.
Well, what are we supposed to do?
Hopefully they’ll be able to open the bridge in the morning. 6 a.m.
There’s a motel right down the road.
Might want to grab yourselves a room before they’re all gone.
There you go!
So, Nate. How’s your game this year?
Here we go again.
Just cover your ears, May, I just want to know how my grandson’s doing on the team.
- Well I already told you, dad.
- No you didn’t, you didn’t tell me jack.
And every time I mention it you change the damn subject.
Now will somebody around here tell me what’s going on?
Nathan?
Whitey? Anybody?
Nathan, I think you better take this one.
I quit the team, alright?
You quit the… what do you mean you quit the team?
He didn’t quit the team dad, he’s just taking some time off.
No, he’s not. Please stop lying, Dan.
Were you ever going to tell me this? I mean that’s a hell of a thing to keep to yourself.
Yeah, you’re one to talk.
What’s that supposed to mean?
I know you visit Karen at the café, alright? What’s that about?
- Nathan!
- That’s none of your damn business.
- I guess somebody’s got a big mouth.
- You shut up, Grandpa
- Don’t you talk to me like that.
- Back off, Royal.
I’ve had enough of your crap. Nathan is not the problem.
Would someone please explain?
Dan has been riding Nathan for the past 6 years about that damn game.
Deb stop.
Riding him so hard, that Nathan took drugs so that he could measure up.
Drugs?
Until he had to be rushed to the hospital.
He could have died because of this insane pressure to put a ball through a hoop.
But none of that is my sons fault, Royal.
It’s your sons.
Danny. You of all people. How dare you!
You know how much you hated it when your daddy bullied you to be better.
I  never bullied him.
And when you wanted a way out, I gave you one.
All these years. I protected you. I lied for you.
And now you’re doing the same thing to your son?
What lie? What are you talking about?
In college. His knee injury. It wasn’t permanent.
Danny quit. And I helped him.
- What do you mean, he quit?
- It’s not like that, dad.
Oh stop it, Dan. It’s time the truth came out.
Will somebody tell me what in knee hell is going on here?
You were on the road when Danny hurt his knee.
So we lied.
- You told me it was degenerative knee condition…
- It was Dad, it was...
You looked me in the eye and told me that.
Don’t you see, Royal? He was never going to be the star that you wanted him to be.
You just couldn’t see that.
The boy had two choices.
To fail in front of you or to quit.
Either way he lost.
So you just quit.
Without even being man enough to own up to it.
There’s more to the story, dad.
- You don’t know the whole story!
- I’ve had enough.
Me too. Come on, Haley. I’ll take you home.
Thanks for dinner.
Well, I can show myself out. Thank you, May.
Deb.
Happy Birthday, Danny.
- Danny, don’t you…
- Why?
Well, I guess I’ll do the dishes.
Alright, lets just try to get some sleep, then we’ll be at the bridge as soon as it opens up.
What did he say? 6 a.m.?
We’ll be there at 5.
What?
We’re in a hurry to find out if my dad’s dead.
It’s just kind of surreal.
Yeah, it’s pretty messed up.
You know how in dreams, you’re always trying to get to some place you need to be
but you never really get there?
Yeah.
I wish I could wake up.
Maybe we should try to get some sleep.
You think you can?
Okay.
I’ll just sleep on the floor, alright?
Don’t be stupid.
Look, Peyton.
I just wish there was something I could do, or say to help you through this.
You already have.
Thanks Lucas.
Goodnight.
Sorry you had to see that.
Oh, it’s okay.
It helped me understand you.
You know, growing up, there were just certain things that were just carved into stone.
And the main one was that Dan Scott would have been a pro if he didn’t blow out his knee.
So, all this time, he just has been feeding me this line of crap about how great he would have been.
And how I’d never be as good as him.
Bastard.
At least you know the truth though, right?
I just don’t know what to do with it.
Okay, goodnight.
Goodnight.
I’m here if you need me, okay?
Hey, remember how I said “My family’s so screwed up,
nothing new would make a difference”?
Yeah.
I was wrong.
- You want to hear my side of it?
- Why should I believe it?
This whole time you’ve been riding me you’ve known exactly the way I feel.
Now that that’s in my head it just makes it that much worse.
I was a great player, Nathan.
In high school.
But when I got to Carolina, I knew it wasn’t going to be the same.
My dad couldn’t see it though.
It was hard on your grandmother too.
So when I got hurt, she came to me and pleaded with me to walk away.
She said it would be better for all of us.
So I did.
Worst decision of my life.
It felt good to get out from underneath my father.
And after a while I realized I wasn’t playing for him at all.
The game meant the world to me.
I just never took the time to stand back and realize that.
So I tried to get back into it. Rehab, running, weights.
But it was too late.
My knee never responded.
It was over for me.
So you think that somehow gives you the right to hammer me all the time.
I know I push you. I know I’m hard on you.
But I’m trying to save you from a life of regret. And Trust me, you don’t want it.
So then you make me feel like crap all the time.
That really helps, dad.
I could have been stronger. But I push you so you will be.
So things will end up better for you than they did for me.
Then you’re safe, dad.
There’s no way I’m ever going to end up like you.
Hey.
What you got?
‘To my heart, love Dad’
He gave it to me on my last birthday.
What if it’s him, Lucas?
- It’s not gonna be.
- Cause I don’t know what I’d do.
It’s going to be okay.
I just keep trying to picture walking into that room and seeing him lying there.
But I hit a wall.
Why does it seem like every time things are finally going to be okay, something terrible happens?
You don’t know that it has.
Keep him close to your heart, Peyton.
Get some sleep, okay?
You can sleep in the bedroom, I’ll stay out here tonight.
Has it ever once bothered your conscience that our entire relationship is based on your lie?
When you were forced to walk away because of your so-called injury, I dropped out too.
We both dropped out to raise Nathan. Don’t rewrite history.
Oh, so you’re the only one who can play that game?
I thought I knew the man I was choosing to spend my life with.
The injury was real, Deb.
And yes, I decided not to rehab it, at first.
By the time I changed my mind it was too late.
I did it in service to you and Nathan.
Now I know how you’d hold it against me for not telling you, but...
did you ever think that maybe I did it...
to protect you from it all?
If that’s what you need to believe.
It’s the truth.
The truth.
In this house?
What’s all this?
Oh, sorry, I didn’t mean to wake you.
I wasn’t asleep.
I hit the vending machines.
Hungry?
You should probably eat something.
After my mom died, my dad couldn’t cook.
So, we lived on frozen pizzas for the longest time.
I could live on pizza.
He’d buy these cheese pizzas, and then put his own toppings on.
Pickles, bologna, pineapple, whatever.
That’s nasty.
No actually they were really good.
I think he did it mostly just to make me laugh.
You know it would help me forget for a little bit.
You ready?
No.
Let’s go.
Morning.
Scrambled or fried? What do you think?
I think nobody’s going to be that hungry.
I’m glad you stood up to Royal the way you did, Deb.
I didn’t mean to hurt Dan but, this lying over the years has gotten so tiresome
I did what I thought I had to do to save my son.
That’s what we do.
I’m glad you spoke up.
Dan.
Son, you know, someday you’re going to realize I did you a favor.
Your daddy’s going to get over this eventually.
But if you let history repeat itself, your son may not.
I’m going for a run.
Oh well. I think I’ll scramble the eggs.
Yeah.
Listen, Nathan,
whatever you’re going through,
I’m sorry about your dad.
I understand why he did it, grandpa.
He must have really loved you, you know that?
Cause anything seemed better than disappointing you.
It’s not him.
You did good.
I felt like my chest was going to explode.
- Peyton’s place.
- Hey, its me.
Hey I was just dialing you, that’s freaky.
Well it’s good news.
Yeah I know, I just got off the phone with the coast guard, they made contact with his boat, he’s fine.
They found your dad, he’s okay.
Alright, we’re headed home.
Okay, I’m waiting. Love you.
- Alright you too. Bye.
- Oh my God, that’s… wait.
What?
My bracelet, I must have left it in the motel.
Alright, lets go.
- Hey.
Grandma’s making breakfast. Show starts at 9. You in?
Um, as fun as last night was, I think I’m going to pass.
You know, I’ve been thinking.
Now that you know the truth about your dad, you’re free, right?
I mean, he’s been lying to you all this time. You don’t have to listen to him anymore.
There’s no more pressure.
Yeah, I wish that were true.
What do you mean?
My dad walked away, and his father will never forgive him for that.
I have to go back.
- Nathan, I…
- I have to beat him, Haley.
It’s the only way I’m ever going to be free of my dad.
It has to be in here.
Got it?
Hey, it’s okay.
Everything’s okay now, okay?
- Ow. Ow. My hair.
- Sorry.
There.
Brooke.
What?
Brooke gave me that necklace.
You know, we…
we probably should get going.
Yeah.
Okay.
How’s business, Keith?
It’s pretty steady.
Good.
I know I rib you a lot son, but I hope you know I think you’re a good man.
That’s great, dad.
The first nice thing you say to me and its really just to dig at Dan.
- Now son…
- Please, could we just eat our breakfast?
Dan, you forgot to open your presents.
This is from your dad and me.
Oh, okay.
What’s this?
It’s a quilt. A lady in Orlando made it.
We still had all your old basketball stuff and I just couldn’t bring myself to throw them out.
You see son, you still have a lot to be proud of.
It’s almost over, Deb.
Thank God for that.
Look, after all that has happened I want to thank you for not throwing gas on the fire.
You okay?
No, no, Dan I’m not. And we’re not.
All this pretending and lying, I can’t really hold it against you.
- Deb…
- Because I realized all these years,
I’ve been doing it too.
- Peyton, I…
- Don’t.
It was stupid. Okay? You’re with Brooke now.
Yeah.
We just got carried away. It didn’t mean anything.
It didn’t?
Of course it did.
See you later.
It’s okay.
Hey you.
Synchro : Amariss
- www.foromfr.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net