Come to my family again
and you and I are at war.
How soon can we bring him in?
We can't just pull him off the streets.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry,
I thought you were Tom.
Daddy! Daddy!
You can be anything
you want to be, Mr Hyde.
Jekyll and Hyde. The comparison
has occurred to me, but this is fiction.
Any idea who might be bribing us,
Dr Jackman?
Or who might be following
you in a black van?
He's got a knife. Minimum necessary
force. You understand me?
OK, OK, a quick half, then.
I've got to go home and change.
Unscheduled change, he's coming.
What triggered it this time?
You might at least have had the decency
to be having an affair.
I'm not sure how strong he is.
Strength isn't usually a variable.
- Sorry?
- In cases like this.
There aren't any cases like this.
Good luck, Miss Reimer.
Goodnight, Dr Jackman.
Who are you?
You know who I am.
You brought me here.
No I didn't. Who are you?
We were just talking.
That wasn't me. Who are you?
Ooh, nice.
It's not your usual perfume,
there's another one.
Special scent for today, then?
For him?
For me?
The woman sitting
opposite you is Katherine Reimer.
She's a psychiatric nurse...
...with experience in related areas.
# It's raining, it's pouring
Jackman is boring #
He was talking about me.
I'm Katherine Reimer.
- Is he doing you?
- No.
- Can I?
- Then what are you for?
- I'm your new nanny.
Oh, Mary Poppins, I love Mary Poppins!
I could eat Mary Poppins!
I'm here to work for you.
For both of you, if you approve.
You have a vote too.
- What, we're getting in help now?
- I have references
and I can start immediately
if that suits.
If you have any questions,
I'd be happy to answer them.
- Am I interviewing you?
- Yes.
- Why do you want this job, Ms Poppins?
- It's interesting. Clearly unique.
It's an opportunity...
# She's talking, she's lying
She's telling a tale and she's dying #
- Why do you say I'm lying?
- Your heart rate just went up.
Pitter, patter, pitter, patter!
I want this job because it's
a unique opportunity. Next question.
Why is it unique?
When I spoke to Dr Jackman,
I assumed this was a simple case
of split personality.
But there's a physical change too,
isn't there?
You've got darker hair,
a different hairline.
Your eyes are darker too, very dark.
Hard to tell, you're sitting down...
...but I'd say you're, what,
a couple of inches taller?
A few pounds lighter too,
that's got to be handy.
Oh, and you've got a slightly
different jaw line. Next question.
- Why did you lie to me?
- I'm sorry?
When I asked you why you wanted
the job, why did you lie?
I'm sorry, I didn't...
Rule one. Don't ever lie to me!
I can smell lies.
Thing is, darling, I don't care
why you want the job,
don't mind if you've got secrets
or if you don't answer my questions.
Don't answer many questions myself.
But don't...
...don't ever...
...lie to me.
Now. Why do you really want this job?
Don't open your mouth unless
you're telling me the truth.
Good girl.
Good girl, Mary Poppins,
you're learning.
- Love a girl with secrets.
- Next question.
- Can you release me from this chair?
- I can.
- Will you?
- Do I have a job?
- Release me.
- What happens if I do?
- Find out.
- Going to need some assurances.
The lights and cameras on.
You're safe if the lights are on
and Daddy can see me.
Look away.
Keep going.
So here's the deal.
Here's the "job".
As long as the lights
and cameras are on, you're safe.
Lights out...
...you're dinner.
What do you think?
I think you must have quite an appetite.
Tee hee hee.
Gonna watch telly before I go out.
There's beers in the fridge,
bring several.
Welcome to the company, Mary Poppins!
How many times?
You feel an unscheduled change coming,
you tell me where I am!
Yes, no problem at all.
I'll speak to you later. OK, bye bye.
Sir?
She left, sir.
Fine, good. Well, um...
can I have the bill, please?
You've already paid.
Yes, yes, of course I have.
Ah, you go to the gents, you come back,
you're a changed man.
We've all been there.
Right.
Happen to know where I parked?
You could have told me
I was seeing someone.
- Lose your keys again?
- Where does he leave them?
So who is she?
He's left-handed. Why can't
either of you check the other pocket?
- Who is she?
- I keep your secrets, I keep his too.
- I know he sees lots of women.
- "Sees" is a nice word.
I need to know if he's got
a relationship.
- Why is this one a relationship?
- Dinner, no sex.
Oh. Have you been drinking?
Don't tell me you took the car.
He drank. He took the car.
Why am I getting the look?
- How was your driving?
- Expressive.
I gave you a breathalyser.
You don't know where you've been.
- Ta.
- It's enough to have the curse.
You don't need to lose your licence!
- Is this the tea I like?
- It's the same tea.
- Tastes like the other one.
- There isn't another one.
I wasn't due this evening,
I owe him the time.
He can have it any time,
but not tomorrow.
I'll tell him.
Can't believe
he's calling himself Hyde.
- He read the book. He liked it.
- Liked it? Read it?!
Made him laugh.
So what's she like? Have you met her?
Has he brought her home to Mummy?
That information's off limits,
Dr Jackman.
- I'll listen to the audio logs.
- He asked for 3 hours off the recorder.
The GPS shows he didn't
change location during that time.
All within the terms of your agreement.
He's entitled to a private life.
I'm not allowed to know
who I'm dating?!
- You didn't tell him he was married.
- I'M married!
- HE'S dating someone.
- He's met my wife and kids.
I can't get equal rights with myself!
He saw your family.
He's kept away since.
He made a promise and he's keeping it.
Only because I kept him
in the chair for a week.
He does get angry, doesn't he?
Yes.
You're safe here, Katherine,
the cameras.
He's capable of anything, but only
if he thinks he can get away with it.
I know what he's like, Dr Jackman.
I've met him.
- Definitely tastes like the other tea.
- There's only one tea.
Excuse me.
Hello? No, you're early, but it's fine.
I told you, there'll be no
after effects, it's a low dosage.
It causes amnesia, he won't remember
a thing since he got back here.
Later.
It causes amnesia, he won't remember
a thing since he got back here.
I still don't understand
why you had to drug him.
Because I've got every key
in the flat except one.
Still trying to take down the security.
It's like Big Brother in here.
He's got too many safeguards,
I'm cutting the power.
- Is that safe?
- Of course it's not safe.
He won't be under for long, and I don't
know who he'll be when he wakes up,
so no offence...
You win. I believe you.
Your letter was in the box.
Did you hear me? I believe you.
Hello, Katherine.
Mr Hyde?
Jackman's in bed now. Hyde is awake.
And you're dead now.
You knocked him out, didn't you?
Silly little Katherine,
silly little dead girl.
When the Doctor is out, I'm in.
Oh, Katherine, alone at last!
Mr Hyde, you don't play these games,
not with me.
You've always had more sense.
You know what I've got now? You.
Ohh...
I've also got the main fuse.
Yep. Took your keys.
Yep, took my keys too.
Well, lookee here, Katherine!
Everything you need
for the perfect night in.
A beautiful woman,
a locked door and soundproofing.
- You won't hurt me.
- I'll eat you.
You know the rules. You hurt me,
anyone, he turns himself in!
- You turned off the cameras.
- Anything happens to me,
you think he won't know it was you?
- You're guessing.
- I know how he thinks.
I am how he thinks.
Then you've got a problem.
Because you like me.
Bet your life.
Are you messing with me?
- Ten.
- What?
- Nine.
- What is this? What are you doing?
Eight.
Seven.
What are you doing?
Six.
Five.
- No!
- Four.
Three.
Two!
Come to Daddy!
# She's running, she's crying
# She's turned out the lights,
she's dying #
No!
If I tell you who I am,
you won't kill me.
Are you listening? If I tell you
who I am, and who sent me here,
you'll turn the lights back on,
the cameras, you won't hurt me.
Go on, then. Try me.
Ask me who sent me here.
We need to do this.
We need a slam dunk.
This is the slam dunk. All respect,
but we're running out of time.
Mr Lennox, we have already
waited over 100 years.
That's awesome, truly awesome.
100 years, respect!
Love those numbers. But if we don't
move now, we're gonna lose him.
- We'll be waiting another 100 years.
- I've reviewed your proposal.
What if the child dies?
He's got two kids, he's got twins.
He's got like a kid and a buffer kid.
He's got a margin-for-error kid.
The children are potentially important.
Both of them.
Hearing that,
but we are managing our risks.
We are gonna contain and control.
And if you can't?
My neck on the line. My personal neck.
Love my neck, won't
let anything happen to it.
Contain and control, listen to the neck.
What's the hurry?
Tom Jackman is 41.
Now, I've got a floor full
of people running numbers,
telling me shit about genetic damage,
about what the change is doing to him.
None of them thinks he'll make 43.
Some of them don't think
he'll make Wednesday.
That, with respect, with all respect, is
what the hurry is. We need to do this.
You can...
Thank you.
Yeah, I appreciate that. Thank you.
She said yes. Buy the zoo!
Feeling a bit weird. Don't really
remember getting home last night.
He hasn't been
taking drugs again, has he?
Don't think so.
OK. Tell him next time I wake up feeling
like this, I'm peeing in a bottle.
Yes, Dr Jackman.
- You OK?
- Yeah, sure.
- What's wrong?
- Sorry. Jumpy today. It's nothing.
Time of the month?
Bit rich, coming from the wolf man.
- See you later.
- See you.
Daddy! Daddy!
Uncle Billy!
- Hello, boys.
- Where did Uncle Billy go?
Sorry, no Uncle Billy.
He says he'll come another day.
But I saw him,
he was sitting right next to you.
No, he wasn't.
- I did, I saw him!
- He's not there, stupid!
- I saw him!
- Come on, boys, in you go.
- Tom!
- Peter.
What are you doing here?
Oh, you know,
I just thought I'd drop by.
- What, socially?
- What's wrong with that?
You.
Heard there was a zoo trip, thought
I'd help look after the boys.
That all right?
Extra pair of hands.
Didn't think you'd mind.
Well, that's all settled then. Come on,
you two, let's get you strapped in.
Am I being set up for a man-to-man?
Well, you don't have them
with me any more.
Peter at a zoo?! He's wearing a suit.
Who wears a suit to the zoo?
Have a good time.
Sorry. Rules of estrangement.
Do we kiss now? I've forgotten.
- I'll have them back by six.
- OK, no kissing. Filed.
Eddie, be careful.
Come on, Harry.
Daddy, I want chips.
In you go, help Daddy find a table.
Eddie, wait for me.
Eddie, wipe your nose.
- Why?
- It's running.
- But I'm eating.
- And not just food, wipe your nose.
Is it always like this? The... eating.
Sorry. It wasn't on purpose.
No, no, no. Just sharing
your food at speed.
Will you for God's sake
wipe your nose?!
What's wrong?
Eddie, what's wrong?
- You shouted at him.
- No, I didn't. Of course I didn't.
I didn't shout at anyone.
Are you awake?
- Something wrong?
- No.
So, since when have you
been an animal lover?
I hunt every summer.
That's not exactly loving them, is it?
That's more shooting them.
Well, it's a brief relationship.
Right, out you come.
Harry, you go with Uncle Peter.
Eddie, you come with me.
Come on, Harry, careful now. Good boy.
That's it.
Tom. What's wrong?
Nothing, probably nothing.
Just being paranoid.
Right you lot, let's go to the zoo.
What's paranoid?
When you think everyone's
out to get you.
Wolf! Wolf...
Wolf, wolf!
What's wrong with it?
The meat wasn't fresh. There's really
no excuse for that in a zoo.
Daddy, Eddie's nose is running.
Eddie, not your jumper, use a tissue.
In your pocket there's a tissue.
Which child?
How about the snotty one?
Eddie, use the tissue.
If you had to lose a kid,
I'd guess you'd choose the snotty one.
Let's make this work, people.
Our last and best chance
for a long time,
according to our man on the inside.
I'm on my way, but, listen, I'm not
sure about any of this any more.
It's too late now Katherine.
I'm at the café.
It's like a leaky tap, your nose,
do you know that? It's like a leaky tap.
We'll to have to send you
back to the factory, get it mended.
Yeah, the man'll come and take him away,
won't he, Daddy, to the factory.
Now, use the tissue, OK? Not your coat.
But I don't want to go to the factory!
No, no, you're not going to the factory.
There is no factory. I'm joking, OK?
Big, silly Daddy joke. All right?
So. You walk out on your wife.
Now there's an Uncle Billy.
Good-Iooking young man, I hear.
You don't think? Claire doesn't think?
- Claire thinks he's your relative.
- People have relatives.
You don't.
You were found at a station
at six months old.
- I know.
- No family, no relatives,
you didn't even have
a bloody train ticket.
So, who is Uncle Billy?
I've been your friend for years.
More than your friend.
- My boss, in fact.
- Your benefactor.
Got you a job, a life.
So I'm obliged
to tell you everything?
No, no, no.
I think I'm obliged to listen.
Tom, you have to trust someone.
Eddie, stop it. Daddy. Daddy.
- Is that yours or mine?
- Is what?
- It's mine, hang on.
- Hello, who is this?
- Dr Jackman, it's me.
- Katherine?
Hyde's awake.
I'm sorry?
He's awake, Hyde,
in your head right now.
What are you talking about?
Can we talk? Are you alone?
I'm at the zoo, I'm with my kids.
Go somewhere we can talk.
I have to take this call.
You'll keep an eye on the boys?
Sure.
- OK.
- Are you alone?
I'm at the zoo.
What do you mean, he's awake?
He can't be if I am.
That's not what you thought
when you shouted at Eddie.
You thought it might have been
Hyde then, didn't you?
- How do you know?
- And when you arrived at the house,
Eddie thought he saw Hyde
in the passenger seat, remember?
Could have been some kind of
psychic impression? Sensitive child?
- Katherine, how do you know about that?
- He's awake in your head, right now.
- He can't be.
- He's awake. Look at your phone.
- My phone?
- Look at it!
It's not connected.
So the question is, Dr Jackman,
how can I be phoning you
if your phone isn't connected?
How is that physically possible?
How is that possible, Dr Jackman?
How is that possible?
How is that possible...
... Daddy?
How can you be phoning me?
Jesus, I'm not phoning you,
I'm in your head.
Keep the phone at your ear,
people will think we're schizo.
What, schizo? Do you think?
I just took a call from my own id!
Wh... why aren't you asleep?
There's something in our bloodstream,
keeping me awake. Something new, a drug.
- Ooh, tickles.
- You can feel your blood?
- You can't do that?
- Who drugged us?
- That's not why I called.
- You had a reason?
I'm your dark side,
it's not like we chat.
- What was that?
- Pulled it from your memory.
- Who are those guys?
- Which guys?
THOSE guys.
- How do you do that?
- You can't do that?
- They're following me.
- Not you.
- Eddie!
- Yeah, 'cause remember...
"I don't want
to go to the factory."
"I don't want to go to the factory."
What is this? What's happening?
Daddy! Daddy!
Stop doing his voice, stop it!
- I have.
- Daddy! Daddy!
- Eddie?
- Daddy, Daddy!
Eddie.
Stay there. Don't move.
- Daddy, where are you going?
- My son's in there.
My son's in there with the lions.
We've got to get him out!
My son's in there! Please, you've got
to help me! I need your help!
My son's in there!
Wh? What are you doing?
Who are you? What do you want?
What do you want?
Me. They want me.
OK, take me! Take him, take Hyde,
Just get my son out of there!
- They took the snotty one.
- Eddie!
That shows consideration.
Eddie! Eddie!
It's OK, son.
Oh, God! Eddie...
Daddy!
- He's gone in.
- Has he changed?
I don't know!
I take responsibility
for any mistakes today,
which means I fire everybody!
You said this would work!
Has he changed?
- What the hell was that?
- Jesus!
Oh, my God! Shit!
I'm going out on a limb here,
he's changed.
What's he doing?
He just threw a lion over a wall.
Anything he likes.
Give it up for a ballsy song choice.
- There's a note.
- What?
On the lion, there's a note.
- Well...
- What?
Get the note from the lion.
#... the lion sleeps tonight
# Oh-we-oh-we-oh
We-um-um-a-way...
- It's for you.
- What, me?
"Dear Benjamin,
meet me in the lions' den."
He can't be serious.
He sent a note with a dead lion. How
much more serious do you get?
"PS Alone."
Well, I've got several clear lines
of sight. I'll get my best shots on it.
Don't kill him, or me.
In that order.
Clean up the van.
#... um-um-a-way
# In the jungle, the mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
# In the jungle, the quiet jungle
The lion sleeps tonight...
Mr Hyde.
#... Oh-we-oh-we-oh
We-um... #
Ever killed anyone Benjamin?
Not personally, I have people.
You're missing out.
It's like sex, only there's a winner.
Thought you might be here somewhere.
Come in.
You know what,
I'm doing fine just here.
You nervous, Benjamin?
Ner? Not nervous,
no, no, I'm just a little... lion aware.
Not nice to turn down
someone's hospitality, Benjamin.
I've got my pride.
- You can control them?
- They're just lions. Can't you?
Kid seems a little freaked.
Yeah, what can you do?
Somebody tried to feed him to a lion.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Just an experiment.
A what?
We wanted to precipitate the change.
As we understand it,
placing your child in danger,
especially the primal kind of danger,
the threat of a savage beast,
would create exactly the right chemical
conditions to bring us, well, you.
Why should I care if the kid's
in danger? Have you seen his nose?
- Well, you did just save his life.
- No! I killed a lion.
There's a difference.
You know what?
You don't have to care about him.
Tom Jackman cares. So you came.
So you took over a whole zoo
for an experiment?
It's our zoo.
What?
We didn't have to take it out,
it's ours.
- Since when?
- This morning.
Tom Jackman bought tickets,
we bought the zoo.
What, you thought we sent
in a SWAT team?
Money is the new war.
That's who you're talking to.
That's what we can do.
Which of your guys put my son in here?
- Why do you want to know?
- I don't. Tom Jackman does.
He's awake, I can feel him.
Tickles.
Sorry, I can't give you
that information.
OK, the big guy
I put through the window.
What's his name?
You mentioned his name...
Christopher!
That's amazing. What you can do,
all of it. Amazing. Look at you!
The most powerful creature on
the planet, that's what I'm looking at.
Fastest, smartest, the best.
And you're British, so it's even funny.
We have waited and you have come.
Forty years ago, a baby
was left in a railway station,
six months old.
But we knew who he was,
who he had to be.
And we have cared
for Tom Jackman ever since.
More, more than cared,
controlled every step of his life,
waiting for you to emerge.
And here you stand. Mr Hyde, reborn.
The second coming, with balls.
- Who left me at the station?
- Who knows?
You don't.
We know more
about Dr Jekyll's experiment
and your creation than anyone.
We can help...
# You don't know who left me
at the station #
Let's find out together. Work with us.
What do you say?
- What if I say no?
- People don't say no to us, Mr Hyde.
Not even you. I mean sure you can kill
a lion with you bare hands, that's cool.
But when it comes right down to it,
we can buy the fucking zoo.
Give me an answer, Mr Hyde.
We've got a man down, Med team here
now, Mr Lennox is on the roof...
Shit!
That's not me on the roof.
Start up, we've gotta get out of here!
Sorry, that's enough zoo for today.
My daddy wants a word with you.
Wakey-wakey.
Dr Jackman?
Who are you? What's your name?
Christopher Browning.
You put my son in a cage with lions,
Christopher Browning. Why?
- I was ordered to.
- Why?
- To make you change.
- I don't know why.
- One last chance. Why?
- I don't know!
- Don't lie to me. Don't annoy me.
That's not a good way to go.
Heard of good cop, bad cop?
This is the movie!
Look, I'm nobody, me,
I'm nothing and I don't know anything,
and I'm not lying.
Please don't let him
in here again, eh?
Forget Hyde! I don't need Hyde.
All I've got to do, pick up the phone.
You tried to kill a child. Do you
want to go to prison as a child-killer?
Think about that.
That phone there, all I need.
- Do you want me to phone the police?
- Yeah. Yeah, go on phone them.
I mean, you've got me, ain't you.
You've got witnesses.
Go on, phone them.
Turn me in, please!
Otherwise he's gonna come back.
For God's sake just phone them!
- Still can't sleep?
- He's telling the truth.
He's nothing,
just a little man taking orders.
So?
They've got a lot of men like him, so
many men are coming for your family.
Send them a message.
- What message?
- The only message they'll understand.
- "Look what happened to the last one."
- I can't do that.
Of course you can't. You're weak.
Just be weak a moment longer,
- close your eyes and let me fly.
- No.
I hope you're strong enough
to bury your children.
You don't care about them.
I love children, me.
Snack-sized people.
Always leave you wanting more.
I'll tell you what, you're the one
who doesn't care,
if that man walks out of here.
What is that? Eh? I mean that
phone's not even connected.
What is it?
- Bad news!
- No...
- Hi.
- What's that?
Well, it's up to you,
of course, but I'd say...
...the front of the queue.
Oh, my God!
- You're still shaking.
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not.
- I'm getting there.
- You told him who you worked for?
- I had to.
- What did he say?
- He laughed.
- Which saved your life.
- Yes.
- Did you think he wouldn't attack you?
- We had an understanding.
- You do. Keep the lights on.
- I thought we had better than that.
He's a wild animal.
Never forget what you're dealing with.
- Or you lose a limb. Or your life.
- It was your idea.
- Not turning off the power.
- It was the only...
- Don't fall in love with Tom Jackman.
- I'm not in love with Dr Jackman.
It's appealing. A man so determined
to beat his own demons.
But he never can. Hyde is
a savage beast, stronger every day.
Jackman is a man who wakes up every day
wondering what he's done this time.
- Hello?
- Are you with Claire?
Hi.
Tom, where are you?
If you're with Claire,
don't tell her it's me.
Of course I am.
Where did you go to?
Guess. How's Eddie?
Bit confused.
He doesn't seem to remember much.
Keeps going on about Uncle Billy.
For God's sake, Tom,
what happened? Can't get
sense out of anyone at the zoo,
and then you go and disappear!
- I need to talk to you now.
- Where are you?
Sherringham Hospital. Intensive Care,
head for the visiting area.
- Don't tell Claire.
- I'm on my way.
If you hear anything,
anything at all...
You'll be the first to know.
- You were asking about Mr Browning?
- Yes.
I'm afraid you're going to
have to speak to a doctor.
He's here.
OK, people, let's move it!
Let's everybody not screw up.
Sherringham Hospital, what you got?
Who owns that? Do we own that?
It's NHS.
Speak English!
You were asking
about Christopher Browning.
I heard you with the nurse.
Yes. I'm a...
I know him.
He's never going to walk again.
Or speak, or eat,
except through a straw.
Blind in both eyes, deaf in both ears.
Almost every bone in his body broken.
Who does that to a person?
What kind of man?
You're his mother, aren't you?
Katherine?
It was in the tea. You drugged me.
You're working for them.
No. She's working for me.
I'm not that poor man's mother,
that's not why I'm crying.
I'm yours.
There's a team on the way.
We'll have him here in an hour.
- I'll meet them there.
- Good work, Mr Syme.
You're welcome.
The order's in, then?
Oh, he knows we're coming after him now.
We can't leave him on the loose.
No more kids and lions.
We're done being nice.
So. You're my mother.
- I'm the nearest thing you've got.
- What does that mean?
It means I left you in a station
forty years ago.
With a letter and a photograph.
- What about my father?
- He died many years ago.
What did he die of? Was he like me?
Did he have what I have?
Is that what killed him?
In a way. It's a long story.
- Did you tell Hyde?
- I didn't tell Hyde much of anything.
I know what he is.
I just wanted to meet both my boys.
He wasn't very interested
in me anyway, you know your brother,
anything he can't fuck or eat...
Why did Katherine drug me?
You advertised for someone
to work for you.
I made sure you found someone
you could trust. Once she met you,
she didn't trust me.
Wanted proof I was who I said I was.
But you keep your secrets so close.
Drugging you was the only way
she could get to them.
We didn't know there'd
be side effects, I'm sorry.
I think she's a little bit in love
with you, but I'm sure you know that.
I let him loose today.
On that man. Hyde whispered in my ear
and I let him tear a man apart.
That's how Hyde works.
He reduces you, piece by piece,
all the easy options.
He's evil, that's what evil does.
The nearest thing I've got to a mother.
- What does that mean?
- It's complicated.
Either you're my mother,
or you're not.
You are a direct descendant of
Dr Henry Jekyll of Edinburgh, correct?
- Yes.
- Yet Dr Jekyll had no family, correct?
Yes.
Then how can anything be simple?
- I need to know where I came from!
- Of course you do.
- Are you going to tell me?
- That's why I'm here...
Dr Jackman!
- Did you tell anyone where you were?
- No. Well, a friend.
- Who?
- Peter Syme.
Peter Syme isn't your friend,
he's your keeper.
If they've decided
to pull you in, you've got to disappear.
- Who's going to pull me in?
- I'll delay them.
- How?
- Don't go home, don't contact anyone.
Just for God's sake,
please, disappear.
How do I control Hyde?
You can't.
- Who are you?
- Official business.
- Whose official business?
- Sorry, boys, you've just missed him.
Oh, come on, Mr Syme,
you must have seen photographs of me.
Have I really aged that much?
Dear God!
- Hello?
- I've been told
there's no one I can trust,
but I've decided to trust you.
Dr Jackman!
There's a woman called Katherine,
she'll contact you. Help her.
Dr Jackman, where are you?
Gone away.
That was him? Phone him back!
I'm phoning him back.
Mrs Jackman?
Good morning.
They'll be down in five minutes.
Do you want a coffee or anything?
No coffee. Tell them five minutes
will be fine.
Then what's going
to happen to me? The truth, please?
He'll get stronger,
you'll get weaker.
It's always the same,
every Jekyll, every Hyde.
- Not this time. I'll fight him.
- You can't.
- I won't ever stop fighting him.
- Then he will kill you.
Then I won't die.
How's Mom this morning?
No trouble. Didn't even want coffee.
- I'll fight him.
- You can't.
- I won't ever stop fighting him.
- Then he will kill you.
Then I won't die.
I have a family.
I have a wife and children.
I won't die, I don't have the time!
- Nobody in or out?!
- Nobody.
- But you offered her coffee?
- I used the com.
Two minutes ago
I spoke to her. She was fine.
Then where is she?
Nobody in or out! One door!
Where is she? Huh?
Shit!
Tonight is everything this organisation
has worked towards ever since it began.
Tonight is the culmination of over
100 years of planning.
- It's me.
- It's him.
It's him.
Dr Jackman is coming home.
Let me dream for you.
Get away from me!
I do declare, I'm all a-flutter.
I won't let you tie me up with Hyde.
I know how dangerous he is!
Hyde's an animal, I'm dangerous.
You're locking me in with Hyde?
Yes.
You wanted to know
where your husband goes.
This is where he goes.
Oh, dear, Mrs Jackman. It's going
to take a bit more than that with me.
Fine!
There's been a murder hasn't there?
Fantastiche!