Come to my family again
and you and I are at war.
- Eat your children!
- No!
Hyde's an animal, I'm dangerous.
Hi Honey, I'm home.
- Where's my husband?
- Tom's gone Honey.
Tonight is everything this organisation
has worked towards ever since it began.
Tonight is the culmination
of over one hundred years of planning.
There now, Benjamin,
it'll be over in a moment.
Dr Jackman is coming home.
No, for God's sake, no! Please! No!!
You won't be needing
this any more. Sorry.
Claire! No!
Peter, for God's sake,
he has claustrophobia.
I know.
Sorry, dropped the phone.
What time did you say?
You OK in there? Need a refill?
No, I'm fine, thanks.
That'll be Claire.
Hey.
- Hey. Am I late?
- No.
- Can I try again?
- Come on, I'm still cooking.
Yeah, well, I was trying to be late.
Oh, shit!
Sorry, no offence.
OK.
See ya!
Who asked you to set me up?
Uh, whoever asked you to do that?
- You did.
- Apart from me.
- Good-Iooking, isn't he?
- Didn't notice.
Not my type. Not interested.
And those glasses
are going to have to go.
- Damn it!
- Gotcha!
I'm going to have to drink now.
I brought my car.
Take these through, talk to him.
- God!
- And Claire, don't, you know...
- What?
- You know.
- Men like a sense of humour.
- Yeah, theirs. And don't scare him.
Don't be scary,
don't be funny, gotcha.
Don't get onto what he earns.
- I don't do that.
- You always do that.
No funny, no scary, no money.
How hard can it be?
I give her one sentence.
So, what do you do?
Rich men.
Sorry, it's a joke. Sorry.
OK?
Yes, er... just, er...
...admiring the patio.
Did you have that last time?
Yes.
OK.
It's nice, though, it's a nice patio.
All right?
- Need any help?
- Do you?
No, no.
All your own work?
The garden?
Except the patio.
So, Tom, how's work?
Oh, you know.
Same as ever.
- Tom's a research scientist.
- Ah, a scientist, right.
What do you do?
About 250,000 a year.
Sorry, hang on a minute.
- Your cab, I said five minutes.
- So early.
Yes, sorry, got a meeting first thing.
What's wrong?
- I've lost my shoes.
- How can you lose your shoes?
- Did you take them off?
- Obviously.
You check the bathroom,
I'll look next door.
Do you always take
your shoes off when you eat?
- Yes. Did you hide them?
- Mm-hm.
Why?
You were leaving.
- Oh, my God!
- I know.
- You barely spoke.
- We still haven't.
- Tell me everything. Disgust me.
- Who's that?
- Nobody, my mother, go away.
- OK.
He's up. Later.
We've still got his shoes.
Do you want me to send them round?
No hurry.
Tom?
Yeah?
Is there a man's dressing gown
in there?
Yes.
I was hoping you wouldn't notice it.
Was specifically pointing it out
part of the plan?
Old boyfriend?
He is now.
Ah!
Twins in the family either of you?
No.
Well, there's news on that.
It's twins.
- But we had scans.
- Tom.
- The scans were wrong.
- There was one heartbeat.
Now bring it to me, that's it,
nice and slow. Careful. Good.
Tell him he's here.
Gemini has landed.
"Gemini"?! For God's sake
who thought that one up?
Is that supposed to be clever? And let
go of her, she's not going anywhere.
Claire, I'm sorry, we have
some questions, it may take a while.
Some questions?
I apologise in advance for the coffee.
- You have some questions?
- A few, yes.
You have my husband in a box!
Don't let them hear you call it a box,
the tech boys.
Total self-contained
life-support system.
It's the safest place
in the world, apparently.
As long as the batteries don't run out.
Let her go, it's fine.
What's that? What's that noise?
He's having a sort of...
Well, a sort of panic attack.
Get him downstairs,
let's get him stabilised.
OK. To me guys, come on.
Be careful, though. Slowly.
Uh, Claire, this way.
Mrs Jackman.
Maybe you should call me
Mrs Jackman now, what do you think?
Mrs Jackman.
- Morning, Dr Jackman.
- Morning.
- Mrs Jackman all right?
- Fine.
- How was your weekend?
- Twins.
Twins!
Sorry, could you do that
again for me, please?
Did I bring the wrong thumb?
How long have they kept you here?
- Idiots.
- Is there a problem?
Only with our equipment.
They'll fire someone.
It's an American company,
they like to feel dynamic.
You haven't been down here.
I'll show you to the lift.
I didn't know there was a down here.
- Who's that?
- Oh, for God's sake!
- Who is that?
- Another American. Hard to keep up,
they keep sacking each other.
I don't know their names.
There are women here
you haven't slept with?
- Why so many rumours about me?
- Probably all the sex.
- Oh, here, use mine.
- That's OK. We have to use mine here.
- I thought I'd clearance everywhere.
- You're down the rabbit hole now.
Everything you think is wrong.
- Sorry, can I take the stairs?
- What's the problem?
I'm sorry,
it's just I have claustrophobia.
I know.
You know where we are I suppose?
- Where Tom worked.
- Where you thought Tom worked.
- Where he thought he worked.
- Where are we going?
Down the rabbit hole,
where everything you think is wrong.
Whatever my husband is, putting him
in a box doesn't make you his friend.
I'll tell you what it makes me,
what it makes a lot of people, rich.
Very, very rich.
- Oh, Sally.
- Um, I'm... I'm leaving.
- Yeah, well, it's late.
- Yeah, no, I'm... I'm leaving
and I'm... I'm not working
any notice either.
- What... what are these supposed to be?
- Just some notes for tomorrow.
Is it a joke?
Is it... Is it... s-sexual?
If it is s-sexual,
l-I can sue you for... for harassment.
Wh... I didn't write these.
It... it's your handwriting.
Yes. Yes it is.
Yes it is.
Mind not on the game, is it?
Fantastic, let's keep going.
I need to talk to you.
- So what do you think?
- Of what?
- My symptoms.
- Look 'em up on the internet.
- You're a doctor.
- Yes, I'm a doctor.
Know what I do with symptoms?
I look 'em up on the internet.
It's open.
OK, hair on my arm out of nowhere.
How do you explain that?
Easy, you imagined it.
Because it's impossible.
OK, my thumb print?
Fault in the machinery,
like they told you.
I don't think
they were telling me the truth.
You imagined that too.
Just push, it's open.
OK, so why am I writing pages
of rubbish to my PA?
- Pages and pages of...
- Yeah, that's... that's my favourite.
"I'm coming." Talk about repressed.
- Who cracks one off in print?
- Could you take this seriously?
Stress, common or garden stress.
- I prescribe a holiday.
- For Christ's sake!
Where did they go?
- Where did who go?
- The door knocked.
- It didn't.
- I heard them.
Tom, nobody knocked.
Three words, ho-li-day.
I'll be with you shortly
and there'll be somebody
on the door if you want anything.
I warned you about the coffee, didn't I?
Remember you said "rich"
on the day you took my family,
on the day you took my children
and put my husband in a box.
Remember you said "rich".
I apologise for the coffee.
Hello?
- A handful, isn't she?
- Who's this?
And attractive too,
I'm sure you've noticed,
but you have an eye
for the ladies, don't you, Mr Syme?
Pot, kettle.
Although I'm not sure I'd trust you
with the wife of a friend.
- Pot, kettle.
- Who is this? Who's speaking?
Miranda Callendar, private investigator.
Mrs Jackman paid me
to follow her husband,
your organisation paid me to stop.
- Peter, could I have a word with you?
- Sorry, just... Sorry, just one second.
And you are Peter Syme,
lifelong friend of Tom Jackman
and his principal betrayer
and abductor of his wife.
Abductor? What on earth
are you talking about?
I've watched her
being driven into your offices.
I'd say it was a pretty
full-on abduction.
Although maybe you just lock women up
in your basement, recreationally.
- Pot, kettle.
- Min!
I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
There's some woman
called Miranda Callendar,
check her out.
Claims to be a private detective.
- Says we paid her off.
- On it.
- Peter...
- What is it?
- Excuse me...
- Meg...
- Peter.
- Take my coat. Thank you. What is it?
- Can we go outside?
- Why?
Mr Syme, she says
that she wants to speak to my boyfriend.
- Yes?
- She's very attractive too.
I am impressed.
What is your secret?
Money or conversation?
Is there a point to this?
I'm outside,
I'd like you to let me in.
And why would I do that?
Because you're a bad boy
and I'm a good detective.
- Hello?
- Oh, you are a busy boy, aren't you?
- I hope you're taking vitamins.
- What are you doing?
- Open up.
- Are you serious?
- Hello?
- You can phone everyone
I've ever slept with in the entire
building, you are not coming in here!
Go home, this doesn't work.
I know, but this will.
I want to speak to Winston Churchill.
Oh, and I don't mean that dreadful MP,
I mean the real one, the war leader.
I want to speak to the real actual
Winston Churchill.
I'm such a fan.
Winston Churchill?
If you're lucky, I'll introduce you.
It's the best holiday ever.
Your kids are having
a good time too, since you ask
Kids? We have kids?
So that sea air's working
its magic, then?
Mm, nightly. Sometimes afternoonly,
couple of times morningly.
You hear that sound?
That's me going green with envy.
That's the sound of green.
- Want to know a secret?
- Nah, secret? Course not.
Yes, I want to know a secret.
- You won't believe me.
- Sounds brilliant.
- I turn his eyes black.
- What?
Seriously. His eyes,
they go jet black every time.
Like mine.
- Dead sexy.
- What do you mean, they go black? When?
- Every time.
- Tom's got brown eyes.
- Am I good, or what?
- That's not possible, is that possible?
- I don't think that's possible. David?
- Yes?
- Don't ask David.
- Nothing, never mind.
OK.
My name's Jake.
Claire, are you all right?
- Like my bike?
- Claire? Who's that speaking?
Nobody, it's OK. I've got to go.
Do you want a go on it?
- My bike. There's room for a small one.
- Sorry, no. No, thank you.
She said no.
- Well, her skirt says yes.
- I'm her husband, she said no.
Her husband? Did you lose a bet?
We're just out for a walk,
we don't want any trouble.
Oh, you don't, that's good.
We just want to go back to our hotel...
- He's not your husband.
- Yes. Yes, he is.
I am her husband and we'd like
to go now, so if you could...
I'll prove it. OK. Watch this.
Are you watching me now?
Now, would your husband let me do this?
Well, come on.
Would your husband let me do that?
Please. Just leave him.
But you can see what I'm saying.
Would he let me do that?
What do you think?
- Yes, he would.
- Oh, OK.
So how about this?
Would he let me do this?
Please, stop.
No.
Tom?
Just...
Just let him.
- It'll be OK.
- Yeah, just let me.
There.
Tom!
It'll be over in a minute.
Finishing touches.
Very nice.
Help yourself to the other one.
You're her husband.
Let's go.
Only me. You all right?
Yeah. Yes, of course.
- Drinks on the way?
- Yeah.
Come on, lover, let's sit.
We could eat here tonight,
what do you think?
I haven't booked.
I'll flirt with the maître d'
- Kind of late, isn't it?
- What for?
- Ice-cream van.
- There isn't any ice-cream van.
Tom, there were too many of them.
I know.
And anyway...
I don't want the kind of man that
gets involved in that kind of fight.
- Don't you?
- Of course I don't.
OK.
I'm off to flirt with the maître d'
Lighten up or I'm going all the way.
- Is someone coming?
- What?
Why have you brought three?
You asked for three.
Do you want me to take it away?
- Yes.
- No problem.
Right, I'll go and see
what I can do about a table.
Don't wait up.
Oh, sorry. Um...
I was just, er... Sorry.
No problem, sir.
Could you sign for the drinks?
Yes.
Thank you, sir. Have a good evening.
# A heart of stone, a smoking gun
# I can give you life...
- Where you off to?
- Slash.
Tom?
I told you. I think he went out
the window.
Why would he go out the window?
Where would he go?
It's funny,
just don't know why I want to hurt you.
Don't even know your name.
Don't know my name.
Please...
Just woke up wanting to hurt you.
Please, don't.
I was born to hurt you.
Please...
And do you know what?
It just never gets old.
What do you say, lover?
Ready to go again?
- Please. Please, don't...
- Just let me.
No, please...
Now, now,
it'll be over in a minute.
Finishing touches.
# I wanted to bite not destroy
# To feel her underneath
# Turning into the light
# Cos I'm on fire
- # Cos I'm on fire...
- Oi, look at this.
Oh, please!
Oh, God!
What?
- She'll be here any second.
- Oh, jolly good. Do sit down.
Thank you.
Just to remind us why we're all here.
I hope your hand's
as strong as you think it is.
No, you don't.
Ah, Claire.
Mrs Jackman.
Miranda Callendar, I think you know,
the detective you employed.
She's been a little unforthcoming
on what she found.
Do I get a refund?
And this is, er... Min, her assistant.
- Actually I'm a detective too.
- No, she isn't.
- I'm on the cusp.
- You're not.
- It's a grey area.
- Min!
And this is Katherine Reimer, of course,
I'm sure Tom's mentioned her.
I've heard a lot about you.
I've heard bloody nothing
about you, dear.
I work for your husband.
Do you dress like that
or do you wear clothes?
- I wear clothes.
- Does he notice?
Half the time.
Everyone here is aware of your
husband's... interesting condition.
Great! You all knew. Fantastic!
No one think it was worth telling me
I married a werewolf?
You didn't marry a werewolf,
Mrs Jackman, you married Dr Jekyll.
Dr Jekyll?
Dr Henry Jekyll died
in Edinburgh in 1886.
- Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde?
- Yes.
Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde was a story.
- No, it wasn't.
- No, it isn't.
OK...
Sorry.
Just, um...
just trying to catch up here,
just trying to be clear.
- I married Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde?
- Yes, you did.
Come on, seriously?
I'm Mrs Jekyll and Hyde?
Yes, you are.
That's so like a man, isn't it? There's
always something they're not telling you.
- "Sorry, should have said, I'm Dracula!"
- This is not a joke.
- This is not serious!
- Henry Jekyll died without issue.
- He's the last of the Jekyll line.
- Sorry?
- That means no children.
- I know what it means!
Tom can't be Jekyll's descendent,
because Henry Jekyll had no descendants.
- But that doesn't make any sense.
- No, none whatsoever.
Um, what has Tom told you
about his parents?
He was fostered.
His mother abandoned him.
On a railway platform
in Belfast in 1967,
six months after he was born.
I don't believe that.
- You don't think he was abandoned?
- I don't think he was born.
Yes? Excuse me.
But please,
I don't want to miss anything.
- Ready?
- As soon as you say.
- Is she there?
- Yeah.
- How's she been?
- Well, in fairness, she's jet-lagged.
I shudder to contemplate.
Might as well get started.
I'm just going to say this again,
you know that there's no guarantee.
I know, good luck.
Thank you. OK everyone, it's a go.
We're going to have to clear the room.
Miss Utterson,
we're clearing the room now.
Of course.
Where are you?
I went to the hospital.
I don't know, I feel, I feel...
You've been gone a whole night!
Where have you been?
I don't know. I woke up on the beach.
Claire, it's weird, I feel... I feel...
You feel what?
Fantastic. I feel fantastic.
- What have you been doing?
- I don't know, I just, I feel...
- I don't need my glasses.
- What?
I don't need them,
I don't know where they are.
I can see perfectly. 20/20 vision,
it's like being a kid again. I can see!
- Do you... do you have your wallet?
- My wallet?!
Have you had a bang on the head?
You're not making any sense.
How could that fix my eyesight?
I don't know!
Something bad's happened to you,
and it hasn't fixed your eyesight.
Just... just check your wallet.
For God's sake,
I'm telling you, I can see.
Tom, where's the hospital?
I'm coming over.
Tom? Where's the hospital?
Tom?
Come on, come on.
Shit. Shit.
Shit.
- No, get down.
- Everything OK?
- Are you all right in there?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Go!
Jesus!
Who are you?
What are you?
OK, this way.
Sorry about the lights.
Here you are, watch your step.
I mean you've got to think fixer-upper.
But there's a lot of potential here,
there's a lot of... rooms.
OK. I can read a face, me.
There's a couple of rentals
in Hammersmith,
they'd probably be more up
your street.
I mean this place... I know
I shouldn't say it, but quite honestly,
I wouldn't lock up
my worst enemy in this place.
I would.
Dr Henry Jekyll died
in Edinburgh in 1886.
Six months after his death,
his research notes,
plus whatever survived
from his various experiments,
passed into the ownership
of a newly-formed company,
Klein & Utterson.
Klein & Utterson
still survive to this day.
And how do you find them
as an employer, Mr Syme?
- American.
- Ooh, and initially Scottish.
A frightening combination.
Klein & Utterson also took possession
of something else,
the body of Dr Henry Jekyll.
- How am I doing?
- Fascinating fairy tale.
There's a copy of this fairy tale
with my lawyer.
I hope that's enough to secure
my safety for the evening?
Oh, absolutely.
You should definitely hope that.
In the 70 years following
Henry Jekyll's death,
and in total secrecy, there were, I think,
16 attempts to recreate his experiment,
resulting in sixteen deaths.
And then in 1965 Winston Churchill died.
In the papers a few months later,
a silly season story
about our old friends Klein & Utterson
and how they were going to
bring good old Winston back.
How?
Cloning. A clone. Created from the DNA
harvested from his body.
A brand new grow-your-own Winston.
How is that going, by the way?
Is he done?
You were going to make a clone
of Winston Churchill?
Of course not. Just some bloody idiot
mouthing off in a pub.
Trying to impress a girl from Hull,
according to the records.
Unfortunately, her father worked
for one of our more esteemed tabloids.
You weren't trying to clone
Winston Churchill,
you were trying to clone Henry Jekyll.
After all those years of failing
to recreate his experiment,
you finally decided
to throw in the towel
and recreate the man himself.
How am I doing now?
It took until 1997 to successfully
clone a sheep.
Do you really imagine in 1965
we were able to clone a dead Victorian?
Klein & Utterson were successfully
cloning farm animals in the 1950s.
Anyone that tried to speak about it
ended up very rich or disappeared.
- Which are you hoping for?
- Neither.
You think Tom Jackman is a clone?
A genetic experiment, grown in a lab?
Yes.
I see.
Tell Colonel Hart we'll be needing him.
This is over.
- Why?
- Because Tom Jackman is not a clone.
You have nothing.
You have walked in here with nothing.
I'm sorry.
- Why are you sorry, Peter?
- Mr Syme?
So soon? Vital signs?
- All normal.
- What have you done to Tom?
I told you we had a cure,
what do you think we've done?
- You're going to cure him?
- No, we've already cured him.
- We should take Mrs Jackman with us.
- Why?
- Because she's entitled.
- What about them?
- They'll have to stay here.
- Why?
No, it's OK, you go, see your husband.
We'll see you again shortly.
Yeah.
Yeah, see you.
Bloody shame, actually.
You should have been working for me.
- You said I had nothing.
- Oh, nothing at all, really,
but you were so close.
But... if... if Henry Jekyll
had no descendants,
if Tom Jackman isn't a clone,
then where did he come from?
I was hoping you were going to tell us,
because we don't have the faintest idea.
Daddy?
Is that you, Daddy?
Are you my daddy?
Did you want to know
what I look like, Daddy?
You did, didn't you?
What do you think? Are you proud?
What do you look like, Daddy?
Are you old? Are you really, really old?
You feel old. I can feel you in here.
Feel your thoughts. Old, dusty thoughts.
Old and scared.
Always so scared.
Why are you so scared, Daddy?
Are you scared of me?
Are you married?
Do I have a mummy?
Or are you alone?
You feel alone.
You think alone.
I can feel what you think.
Think of a number.
No, do it Daddy, think of a number.
A big silly number, go on, it's a game.
Say it out loud, a big fat number,
any big fat number.
- 103.
Oh, God!
I was right, wasn't I?
Bet I was.
Waaah!
I'm in your head.
I know what you think.
I am what you think.
Scared now, aren't you, Daddy?
Scaredy Daddy.
I'm not scared of you!
Yes, you are.
I'm coming to get you, Daddy.
I'm coming to eat you, Daddy.
Oh, you've got
a vivid imagination, Daddy.
I've been there.
You, shut up.
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Just a moment.
- Who is it?
- Delivery, sir.
- I didn't order anything.
- 6 Stadler Street? Dr Jackman?
You phoned yesterday,
said it was an emergency.
New television, sir.
Do you want some help opening the box?
Why is he in that box?
It's the only way to keep him stable.
They'll be ready for us in a moment,
uh... Coffee?
- Could someone get some coffee?
- Why now?
You've had a cure
for over 50 years, you said.
Because your husband...
Claire...
Tom's dying.
Every change is shredding his DNA.
He won't see 45.
He may not even see the end of the
month. We couldn't wait any longer.
- We wanted to.
- Why?
- He's all yours in a minute.
- Thank you.
- Why did you want to wait?
- We know how to stabilise him
and we've always known
how to stop the changes,
but we didn't know
in which form he'd stabilise.
- It's Hyde we want.
- I don't want Hyde.
I know.
- Watch out, it's hot.
- Go away.
It's all right.
Who is he now?
How do you know which one he's...
stabilised as?
We open the box.
And then what?
Either you take Dr Jackman home,
or Mr Hyde stays here.
- They're both my husband.
- No, no, no, Hyde is ours.
I see.
Well, then.
I'll have that coffee, thanks.
I'd wish you luck,
but you wouldn't believe me.
It's not an even chance, is it?
You wouldn't be doing this if it was.
You think it's Hyde in there.
- They do.
- You don't?
At every stage of this, Tom's been
stronger than anyone ever expected.
- I'd never bet against him.
- You sound like you're proud of him.
- He's my friend.
- Yes.
He's your friend.
- How hot?
- Very hot.
- Thanks.
- Arrgh! Jesus Christ!
- I apologise for the coffee.
- Well, then, what are you waiting for?
- Get my husband out of that bloody box!
- Shit!