Previously on The O.C.
Articulating your feelings
to your girlfriend
kind of a challenge.
How do you feel?
I...
I see the great
love of your life.
It's George.
George?
I'm here to offer you a job.
He heard about my work
with the sea otters
and invited me to travel
across the country
and talk to college
kids about voting.
Why don't you give
Jason Spitz a call?
You're always saying
how funny he is.
I don't have that many
guy friends anymore.
Who does? Who's got the time?
Where the heck's your mom?
I know I asked you
to be my stepdad.
Do you mind being
my friend instead?
Tell me what it is
that you love about Julie.
We're just
from the same world.
I'm not buying you
lingerie for your birthday.
That's just weird.
Okay, that's fine.
I told you, you don't
have to buy me anything.
You and Ryan are throwing
me a birthday party
and that's enough.
Look, I know you've never
had a birthday party before,
let alone been to one,
but usually people get
presents for their birthday,
so will you please
tell me what you want?
Okay, honestly,
I want Ryan
to ask me to go to
Berkeley with him next year.
Okay, I was thinking more
along the lines of a cute top.
I know, I know, it's just,
I'm a planner,
and I've already seeing
that day six months
in the future when we
all go our separate ways.
And I just know
that if Ryan goes
to Berkeley and I go to...
Harvard or Princeton
or Oxford, then it's over.
Don't you have to apply
to Berkeley first
in order to...
You already applied to Berkeley?
Does Ryan know this?
No.I applied before we
even started dating.
I just got back from
France and I figured,
well, I had to go somewhere,
so I reapplied to Princeton,
Oxford,Yale, Harvard
and the Sorbonne,
and I figured why not
throw Berkeley in?
Hmm.
Um, hi.
Can we get two coffees, please?
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
So you want to get
Ryan to tell you
that he wants you
to go to Berkeley,
without knowing that
you already got in to Berkeley?
Exactly.
And how're you going to do that?
Easy.I just need to get him
to tell me that he loves me.
Mm-hmm, Ryan talking
about his feelings.
Now that would be an
earth-shattering event.
Careful, they're hot.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Did you see this about earthquake weather?
You know, it's exactly
this kind of voodoo science
that lets politicians
deny global warming.
Oh, my God, I know.
And how many times
have they predicted the big one,
and it never happens.
It almost makes you wish that it would.
Hey.
Good morning.
What's the occasion?
Just you're being so sweet
throwing me a birthday party,
and I wanted to thank you, so...
Oh, my gosh, did I ever
tell you about...
How you've never
had a birthday party
and you've always spent every
birthday alone in your room
watching Sixteen Candles
and talking to a gypsy
on the psychic hot line?
Yeah, I know,
I'm a broken record.
Just, you know, it really
means a lot to me
that you're doing this for me.
Well, Taylor, I'll tell you,
planning your birthday
party is not easy.
I expect something in return.
Oh.
I expect to have
my way with you.
Ryan!
Well, all that time and energy.
Clowns, balloons, a magician...
Oh, oh, well,
if there's a magician.
It's kind of strange to think
about all of this ending isn't it?
Hmm?
You, going off to Berkeley,
me, whichever way
the wind blows.
Well, it's still six months away.
Right, yeah.
If only I had
a crystal ball, huh?
Maybe I should call Esmerelda
from the psychic hot line.
Th is a really good croissant.
Don't you have the feeling that
we're on the cusp
of something and we just need
to leap into the void?
Did you get these at Joe's?
Ryan, don't you have that feeling?
What?
That life is telling us
to take a wild,
impulsive jump into the unknown?
Not really.
So, you're good?
You don't have a need
to just let something
explode out of you,
consequences be damned?
What are we talking about?
Well, I was...
I guess it's just my birthday
and I'm getting sentimental.
All right, well, don't worry.
It's going to be great.
Okay?
All right, I've got to go.
Thanks for this.
Hey, tonight, you want
to do something? See a movie?
Yeah, sure, okay.
All right, great.
Oh, my God.
Oh, hi, honey.
Sorry, I didn't
hear you coming down.
Mom, do you mind?
Because I still
have to eat in here.
What can I get you?
You want some scrambled eggs or
I could whip up some pancakes.
You cook, too? That's amazing.
It's just a talent I have.
Yeah, one of many.
I'm seriously never
going to stop barfing.
Caitlin, don't be gross.
Me? Gross?
What's gross is Frank's dirty...
germy convict bag
is sitting on the counter.
I mean, what,
did the warden give that to you
as a going-away present?
Caitlin.
It's okay. It's okay.
It shouldn't be on the counter.
Though I actually
got it at REI.
Well, why bother with a bag?
You can just move in.
You spend enough
time here anyway.
Young lady, apologize.
I'm sorry, Frank.
Feel free to have as many
conjugal visits as you'd like.
You know, I... I
should get going.
I've got a job interview.
I'll walk you out.
Okay.
And we'll talk later.
Mrs. Cohen?
Holly.
I went to Harbor with Seth.
Oh, hi.
Hi, are you here
for prenatal yoga?
Oh, yes, I am. And you?
Yes. I just found out.
How far along are you?
Oh, not-not very.
I just found out, too.
Well, this class is great.
I told Missy, the instructor,
I have worked way
too hard for this body
to just let it turn
into some dumpy baby factory.
I mean, who says I can't
have a baby and a six pack?
I should probably
stretch before class.
Well, hold on just a second.
Hey, hos, come here.
This is Mrs. Cohen.
She just found out
she's pregnant.
Oh, my gosh!
Congratulations.
And you're not
even showing.
So...
should we let her in?
Oh, yeah.
Totally. She's ripped.
We formed a club.
Promised ourselves
we wouldn't turn out like Molly
the Mammoth over there.
Eww.
In nine months
I'm wearing my bikini.
I don't care what anyone says.
And I told Jerry
if I get too big,
I'm inducing at eight months.
It's much easier
to lose the weight.
So do you want in?
We call ourselves the
Six-Pack Pack.
Isn't that like so cute?
Don't you just want to barf?
All the time.
Summer, what's up?
Hey.
I am just picking up Seth.
Taking him to an art exhibition,
sponsored by GEORGE,
the Global Environmental Organization
regarding Greenhouse Emissions.
Seth's going to an art show.
Well, yeah, I mean,
he's going to art school,
and I like the environment,so
I thought it was the perfect date.
Sure.
So are you ready
for Taylor's party?
Oh, yeah, party's all set.
Even got her a present.
Really. Mind
telling me what it is?
Well, you know,
she likes translating
those French love poems?
I collected a few.
Had them bound for her.
Atwood, that is so romantic.
You know, nothing is as romantic
as the first time you tell
someone you love them,though, huh?
I, uh...
haven't told Taylor I love her.
You haven't?
Has she said something?
No. No, I-I just assumed.
You guys have been together
for a while
and you seem pretty happy.
I thought,"Why wouldn't you
have said I love you?"
I have an idea. Why don't you?
What?
For her birthday.
You should, because...
the book of poems is awesome, but
add that special little "I love you."
As as girl,I don't know, me personally,
I got chills.
Does Taylor expect me to tell her
that I love her on her birthday?
What? No. I don't know.
I've got to go.
I can't stay, okay?
Well, thanks for meeting me.
I wanted to talk to you alone.
You're not going to do
anything pervy are you?
Caitlin...
I care about your mom.
And considering my past,
I understand
why you're suspicious.
Look, I really don't care that
you went to prison, all right?
I mean, the Bullet went to prison
and he was awesome.
You're just boring.
I'm sorry, but it's
just the way it is.
Well, I have to say
I don't think that's fair.
You hardly know me.
Then say something funny.
What?
Make me laugh.
Fine.
I don't know what interests
a 15-year-old girl,
but your mother
doesn't think I'm boring.
Well, that's because
you're sleeping with her.
Can you not say
that kind of thing?
Well, what do
you want me to say?
I mean, is it true in prison
on your first day,
you got to make someone your bitch?
Or what about the whole
dropping the soap thing?
I mean, really,why don't you guys
just install soap dispensers?
Hey, I make your mom happy.
I'm just asking
for a chance here, Caitlin.
Of course.
If it makes my mom happy.
Oh, my God.
Oh... my God.
It's so beautiful. Just forget how the ocean ties us all together.
You know, he's so right.
If we aren't good custodians for our planet,
what right do we have to be here?
Don't you think
that was amazing?
Mm-hmm.
I give it a three.
A three?
He put a radio transmitter
in a piece of trash,
threw it into the ocean,
followed it around for six years
just to show how pollution travels.
And you're giving it a three?
I'm gonna give it a three-and-a-half, then.
What about the part where
he followed it
through the oil fires in the Persian Gulf,
and he got third-degree
burns on his arms?
I know, but the camera work was terrible,
and what kind of film
stock was he using?
The oranges and reds
totally bled together.
He was just making a point
to show the health of our planet.
Yeah, but he's also
making a movie,and as a movie,
it sucks.
Well, what about that one?
Where the turtle adopted the hippo
who was lost in the tsunami?
Mm-hmm.
That's pretty much the nature film
equivalent of a chick flick.
Okay.
What about that? Where the family giraffes habitat was destroyed.
Yeah, shot like a perfume ad.
God, what is your problem,Seth?
I just want you to get excited
about something.
I am, about things
that are good.
But I could do one of these
doughnuts with both hands
tied behind my back.
Really?Prove it.
What?
Make a movie.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I want see you do it better.
I want to go watch the penguins again,
and don't you dare say anything.
Hey, I didn't know
you were coming by.
I was just at Spitzy's office.
You should have called.
Is everything all right?
The people in Newport are awful.
Honey, you're
a little late to the party.
I've been saying that
for 20 years.
Has it gotten worse?
I mean, I know Julie and
some of the othersare bad, but...
What happened?
I was at this prenatal
yoga class and these young women,
they're monsters.
They wanted me to join the six-pack pack.
The what?
And then they talk about
inducing labor at eight months
so that they don't have
to gain weight.
Can we raise another child
around this?
Oh, honey, Newport's always had
that element,
and still we managed
to have life.
And not everybody's like that.
You know what?
Spitz has been wanting us
to meet his wife.
How about we do
dinner tomorrow?
Restore your faith in humanity.
All right.
But more importantly,
do you think they'll let me
join the six-pack pack?
I've been doing my sit-ups.
Come on, hit me with your best shot.
Go ahead, come on, wind up.
I'm not a beast!
Oh, God, he really loves her.
And she is never going
to know how he feels,
because he can't tell her.
Isn't that tragic?
Yep.
I mean, how could you do that?
How could you just let the love
of your life slip away
because you were too afraid to
tell them how you really felt?
Well, maybe she's better off.
Uh-huh.
Did you get that from the scene
where she was about to be
burned at the stake?
No, she's a beautiful woman,
he's a hunchback
who lives in a bell tower.
The chances of it working out...
Yeah, but he doesn't know that.
If he at least told
her how he felt,
then maybe there would be
a way to work things out.
You know, they could
have a life together.
Or you know,
at least four more years.
Why did you save me?
But the archbishop...
Ryan, I'm not talking
about the movie.
It's... There's just moments
in everyone's life,
and if you just let them
slip away, then...
then they're gone forever.
And that's the tragic
thing about life.
Don't you feel that way?
Taylor.
I...
...missed the last
part of the movie.
Would you mind
rewinding it a little?
Sure.
Thanks.
Lonely, huh?
Better get used to it, buddy.
Good morning.
If you say so.
What's that?
This is the obituary for mine
and Ryan's relationship.
A rose, plucked
before its time.
Uh-huh, English?
I wrote a letter to the Dean of Berkeley,
telling him that I must
respectfully decline the scholarship,
and he should offer it to the next candidate.
So you're saying no?
What happened with Ryan?
I tried, Summer, I really did.
The moment was upon us.
We were staring
into each other's eyes,and...
And he just didn't say it.
You know, sometimes I just want
to grab him and tie him
to a chair and shoot him full
of sodium pentathol
and see what spills out.
Why don't you?
You don't think it's too crazy?
Because I was thinking
if the two of us just tackled him
and then we could
tie him down...
I wasn't talking literally.
Oh.
Do you love him?
Yeah, I really do.
Do you think he loves you?
Well, sometimes he grabs my hand
and he squeezes it
for no reason.
I mean, what else could that mean?
Okay. So we just need to loosen
his tongue a little.
But how are we going to...
Summer Roberts, you bad thing.
Okay, you know what,
a trip to the Robert's
wine cellar is in order.
What the hell is he doing?
Morning.
Hey, are y all right?
Yeah, it's just a cramp.
How far did you go?
Mm, nine, ten miles.
Oh. Wouldn't it be easier
if you just said,"Sandy,
there's something bothering me.
Can you give me some advice?"
Yes, it would,but where's the fun in that?
Let me guess.
You're trying to decide
if you love Taylor
so you can tell her
on her birthday.
Huh?
You've been dating for a while,
things are good,
birthday's tomorrow.
Bingo.
Yeah. You're good.
So? Do you love her?
Uh, honestly I'm scared.
Good, you should be.
That's reassuring.
Well, it might be the most
powerful thing
you can say to another person.
It changes everything.
Now for heaven's sake,
if you don't feel it,don't say it.
Yeah, it's just I think
she's expecting it.
And to not say it...
It's like saying
you don't love her.
Exactly.
Well, do you care about her?
Of course.
Do you enjoy being with her?
More than with anyone.
Tell her that.
It won't be exactly what she wants
to hear,but it'll be honest.
All right.
Can you tell me something?
Sure.
Do you have any idea
why Seth is filming the pool?
Hey, check it out, man.
Summer challenged me to make
this pretentious art film,
so I'm making one called
Six Hours In The Pool.
Sounds great.
Yeah, I'll tell you
about it later.
Uh, Taylor called.
She wants you
to go over there for dinner.
Oh, okay.
Yeah. Okay.
Ah, it's perfect.
Look, Frank, I get
that men have urges,
and I imagine prison is
one of those places where
those urges get twisted, but...
Julie...
I've never even heard of clown porn.
I mean that photo where they're all
stuffed into the little car...
It's not mine.
Oh, really?
It was just in your bag,
along with... this?
I mean, which one of us
is supposed to wear this?
Julie, none of this is mine.
So someone just went
into your bag, planted a wig
and some really bad clown porn.
Who would...
Oh... Caitlin.
Julie, it's all right.
No, Frank, it's not.
My daughter is trying to
sabotage this relationship.
And where would she get
her hands on clown porn?
She's just hazing
me, you know?
It'll be good for me to show
her that I can take it.
Itll blow over.
It's not serious.
Did you see  50?
How much more of this is there?
Five hours and 58 minutes.
What are you doing?
I'm not going to sit here
and watch six hours of the pool.
I told you to become
engaged in something.
Instead, you just set up a tripod.
It's a satire.
It's a comment on the lack
of artistic rigor...
No, it's you being lazy.
How many naps did you take
while you made this?
I took two to res...
Do you feel like you're
overreacting a little bit?
I mean, what does
it really matter?
That's the problem, Seth.
You did this because you chose
the path of least resistance.
You know, you could have
made a movie about anything
in your life,
and instead you chose this.
So what am I supposed to do?
Follow Ryan around with a camera
until he punches someone?
Yes, anything that engages
you in the world.
What is the point?
Well, if nothing else,it's important to me.
Thanks.
Mr. Spitz.
How are you?
Kirsten, how's it going?
Hello, Jason.
Listen, you guys, I want you
to meet my wife, com.
No way, really?
Well, then what did she say?
Honey, honey.
Oh, my God.
What a complete ho-bag.
Honey.
I got to go.
Call me back.
Love you, bitch.
Hi.
I am so sorry.
Kirsten and Sandy Cohen,
this is Carrie, my wife.
So nice to meet you.
You, too.
That was my girlfriend.
She's having trouble dating this guy,
and the guy's wife is
all like, uh, "I'll kill you."
Wow, I imagine that could
be a little hard to handle.
Oh, whatever.Not my problem.
So, Carrie, you're from Newport?
Oh, yeah, born and bred.
Really. Interesting.
Oh, now, Sandy,let's get to it.
How can we convince Jason here
to get out of that soup kitchen
he calls an office
and get a real job?
Oh, thanks, that's good.
For luck.
Uh, actuylor, I'm not
that big a wine drinker.
I know, you can't have
coq au vin without the vin.
Well, that's true.
Okay.
You know, I feel kind of bad, you making
dinner the day before your birthday.
No, it's my pleasure.
Absolutely.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
I'm nervous 'cause I've never
cooked for you before.
Okay, cheers.
Oh, yeah.
Whoo, bottoms up.
Mmm.
Tasty.
So, uh...Oh, that's...
So, Taylor, there's something
I want to talk to you about.
No, let's save all the serious
conversation for after dinner.
We don't want it to get cold.
Okay.
Hmm, I think I need another sip.
Wow, do you detect
a hint of blackberries?
Mm, no, I don't.
Try it.
It's fun, come on.
Uh...
Okay.
Mm.
Nope, no blackberries.
I think you need
to take a bigger sip.
You still go to your sorority rush?
Sandy, sisterhood doesn't
just end with graduation.
A Tri-Delt once,
a Tri-Delt forever.
Oh, but last year,I got so sick.
Totally embarrassing.
I can only imagine.
And I thought,"Carrie, what gives?"
Can't you hold
your liquor anymore?
Ugh! And then I realized
it was just morning sickness.
Was that a relief.
You know, I'm afraid it's getting
a little late for us.
Oh, no, no,no, no.
You are not running away.
This great bar
just opened up on Ocean.
When was the last time
you two did tequila poppers?
Maybe another time.
Oh, tell me you're not bailing
because you're pregnant.
I mean, no offense,
but that is lame.
Carrie, no.
What?It's lame.
Actually, I'm an alcoholic.
Oh, God.
Me, too.
Hey, after you have that thing,
we should totally go out.
You know, without
the two dish rags.
Oh, God!
Can you just take
that thing outside?
Oh, don't freak.
I'm not a psycho.It's our baby.
When we go out with the baby,
Carrie likes to have the nurse
sit nearby,a few tables away.
Oh, you know,Sandy,
I'm-I'm, uh, suddenly...
I'm, I'm not feeling well.
I'd better get you home.
Thank you both for
an unforgettable evening.
Jason, I'll talk to you Monday.
Yeah. Well,good night,and...
Hey, Kirsten,uh, remember,you can
call me for baby advice anytime.
Sure.
Losers.
I don't understand
how you're not drunk.
Oh, it's the Atwood genes.
We're built to withstand
massive quantities of alcohol.
Ooh.
Here we go.Here's the bed.
Okay, all right.
Now we're just gonna...
Whoa. That's good.
But if I can't get you drunk,
you'll never tell me you love me.
Oh, Taylor.
I know, I know.
Bad Taylor.
I shouldn't have tried
to get you drunk.
Just like I shouldn't have
pretendedto be your sleep therapist,
or rented Roger the homosexual,
or stalked you wearing
a Groundhog costume, or...
What else did I do?
I-I think that's it.
I'm going to go to sleep now.
Oh.
Good-bye, Ryan.
It was nice.
Taylor.
Taylor?
Are you pretending to go to sleep,
thinking I'll tell you I love you
while you're unconscious?
Maybe.
Don't laugh at me.
I'm not.
It's hard dating someone
who doesn't tell you how they feel
and always having to
interpret hand squeezes and...
I love you.
What?
You do?
Uh, yeah.
I can't believe
you just said it.
Neither can I.
Oh, I love you, too.
Oh, good.
Yay!Yay!
Now we can go to Berkeley together.
What?
Yeah.Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got into Berkeley.
I applied, and I got this letter,
and put it on my desk and...
Ryan Atwood.His face
betrays no emotion,
but what passions lurk
behind those eyes?
Answering that is the purpose
of this film.
Come with me, my friends.
I thought the movie was about the pool.
Summer didn't really take
to six hours of the pool.
She wanted me to make a movie
in which I engage with people.
What is Ryan Atwood
wrapping so intently?
Taylor's birthday present.
Ah, Taylor Townsend,
the fast-talking Eve Harrington
who melted Ryan Atwood's heart.
Tell us, Ryan,how does it feel
to have Dean Hess's sloppy seconds?
Or what did you get her?Either one.
Um...
well, uh, one of her hobbies is
translating French love poems,
so I had them bound for her.
Wow.That is really romantic.
Well, it's,it's not that romantic.
Are you kidding?
You may as well tell her
you love her.
It's, uh, it's actually
a little late for that.
What?
Yeah.
And then what happened?
Well, we finished dinner
and he still wasn't drunk,
so I suggested a drinking game.
I called it "Drink."
Whenever I said "drink,"
we drank.
Simple but effective.
Yeah, a little too effective.
I ended up on the coffee table
singing "Part of Your World"
and telling him he was my Prince Eric.
Uh, did he say it?
Yes.
He did?!
Yeah!
Oh, my God,that's amazing.
Ow.Ryan told you he loved you.
I know.
I mean, I think he said it.
Yeah, this feeling just kind of
came over me and...
I couldn't stop myself.
So why the long face?
You regretting it?
Well...
it turns out she applied
to Berkeley without telling me,
and now...Your spur-of-the-moment
"I love you" issuddenly committing you
to four more years.
The plot thickens.
I'm not saying it'd be bad.
It just seems like all of
a sudden we're going mach five.
You'd like to turn down
the heat a little.
He definitely said it.
Absolutely.
I think.
Well, don't you
think you'd remember?
I don't know; it hurts.
Summer,what am I going to do?
I can't just ask him,by the way,
"did you tell me you loved me last night?
Because I was too plastered
to remember."
Right.
Okay.
Today's your birthda right?
And I happen to know
that he got you a crazy,
romantic present.
So when you open it tonight,
why don't you just be like,
"Oh, my gosh,Ryan, I love you,"
and if he said it last
night, he'll say it again.
You're a genius.
Yes, I am; it's all up here.
It's just there might be
one other tiny little thing.
I'm not saying take it back,
but today's her birthday, right?
So she's going to be interpreting
every little thing.
So maybe you send her a message.
For instance,
that sends the message "You're the only girl in the world for me.
Let's move to a co-op in Berkeley."
Is that what you want to say?
We go off Ryan Atwood.
What will he do?
How will this situation
resolve itself?
You said something
about Berkeley?
I'm not sure.
Maybe I was just talking
about him going to Berkeley.
That would make sense, right?
Morning, girls.
Happy birthday, Taylor.
Thanks, Julie.
Oh, I gave the mailman
that letter from the counter.
What letter?
The letter to Berkeley?
Yeah, I think so.
Oh, my God.
Uh-uh! Mister!
Mail carrier, sir.
Excuse me, please.
Um, could you wait?
Hi.I'm sorry.
Um, a woman in that house where
I live just gave you a letter
that she shouldn't have,and, uh,
I kind of need it back.
Ma'am, once the letter goes in the pouch,
it's the property of
the Federal government.
Okay, and I totally understand that,
but if you take that letter,I am going to lose
my place at Berkeley and the
chance to be with the man I love
and who I think loves me,
and, and 15 years
from now,when he is trapped
in a loveless marriage
and I have become
a cold, hard ice queen
for whom love is no more
than a distant memory,
it will come down to the fact
that on this morning,
which coincidentally happens
to be my birthday,
you obeyed the letter of the law at
the expense of simple, human charity.
Wow, that was amazing.
Can I have my letter now?
Yeah, sure.
Hey.
I didn't know you were a runner.
Yeah,it helps me
to work stuff out.
You should try it.
Maybe I will.Everything okay?
Yeah. No, I was just,uh, nearby.
I figured I'd stop in and say hello,
ask your advice on winning
over a 15-year-old Newport girl.
Caitlin giving you trouble?
Well, things with Julie are great,
and I-I'm so grateful
to you and Taylor,but Caitlin, she just--
I don't know,she just seems to
want to shut me out.
And I know that you have some
experience with the Cooper women,
so...Well, a Porsche would
probably do the trick.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's not
really in my budget.
Well,Caitlin's had a tough year.
You know.Once she sees that her
mom's happy,she'll come around.
Just be patient.
Ah... suddenly a Porsche
sounds like a bargain.
Right.
Uh, look,I, I got to get going,
help set up Taylor's party.
Oh, sure.Is that,
is that her present?
Oh, yeah, it's, uh--
she translated these French love poems
so I had them bound in
leatherfor her.
Oh, my son the romantic.
Yeah.
So I'll, uh, see you tonight.
It's not that romantic.
Taylor, it's going to be fine.
Ryan's going to give you
a really romantic present,
tell you he loves you,and you guys are going
to wind up going to Berkeley
together.Don't worry.
Okay, yeah, I know.
Do you think I should act
surprised when I go to the party?
But it's not a surprise party.
Well, I know, but it might
make Ryan feel good.
Okay, it's a great idea.
Ah!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday.Happy birthday.
Oh, my God, what a surprise.
Oh, I didn't know it was
a surprise party.
Just go with it, okay?It's Taylor.
Happy birthday.
This is a-amazing.
Yeah, well, you deserve it.
You got a lot of
birthdays to catch up on.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, absolutely.
Let me get you a drink.
Okay.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
We can move.
I mean it.
Ryan and Seth will be gone
in six months.
We could put the house on the
market, throw a dart at the map.
Maybe it's time.
But this is our home.
So? We'll make some place
new our home.
You know?
We'll still have our memories.
But when Ryan and Seth
come home for the holidays,
I want them to come
home to that house.
It was an idea.
Well, thanks, Sandy.
I just don't think I can.
Oh, my God.
It's a replica of the green
destiny sword from Crouching Tiger.
Oh, my God, thank you so much Seth.
Glad you like it.
It's so neat.
Open Ryan's present.
Okay. Where is it?
Oh, no, no, no.
It's okay.
Ryan's embarrassed.
No, it's just,
it's um, personal.
Well, I hope so.
Oh, my God.
It's a...It's a dictionary?
That is practical.
Yeah, the guy said that it,
um, had more words than others.
Well, that's good, being
as it is a dictionary.
It's red-- that's a cool color.
I still love him,you know?
I'm sorry, I shouldn't be
telling you this.
No, I understand.
I worry about him a lot.
You know, I know making this
movie just seems so stupid,
but I just wanted him to get
excited about something, you know?
Anything.
Just give him a chance.
Seth will find his way.
I hope so.
He just seems a little lost.
Those are mine.
What do you think you're doing?
What? The guy likes clown porn.
I think everyone should know.
Do you have any idea how
humiliated Frank would be if he saw,
or if Ryan saw it?
It's his father,Caitlin.
Whatever.
Do not walk away from me.
I've tried to be understanding.
I'm sorry if Frank isn't as
hilarious as Bullit was.
It's not even about that.
Then what is it?
Is it the money?
Mom, look at us.
In the past year we've lost
Dad, we've lost Marissa,
we had Dr. Roberts and we lost him.
And then we got
the Bullit, lost him.
What makes you thinkthat this guy'
sgoing to stick around any longer?
Caitlin, am I crazy,
or did you say that it
was okay for me to date Frank?
Yes, to date him.
But it's been a week and he's
practically living in our house.
Like he's family.
He is not family.
You and I are.
I mean, why can't we just act
like that for a little while?
Hey.
They're about to
bring out the cake.
Everything okay?
Yes, everything's fine.Caitlin,
why don't you go back inside.
Taylor.
Taylor, I'm sorry.
I'm not crazy, right?
Last night, you did
tell me you loved me.
Yeah, I did.
Okay, then what?
Are you trying to
send me a message?
Do you wish you
hadn't said it?
No. Last night when I told you...
You mentioned going to Berkeley.
God, I knew it.
Ryan, yes, I applied to
Berkeley months ago.
Before you and
I ever started dating.
Oh.
And then, this, you and I
happened, and I thought,
I don't know, maybe.
And I guess I should have told
you, but I really needed to know
exactly how you felt first.
I just think our planning
to go to college together,
it's a big decision.
Would you have said you loved me
if you'd known I'd
gotten in to Berkeley?
Great.
Wow, okay.
I'm just going to go.
Taylor.
She's coming.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Taylor
Happy birthday to you.
Come on.
This is where you blow out
the candles and make a wish.
Don't worry.
Kirsten and I will
square up things here.
All right, great. Thanks.
And I gave Seth the car
to help carry the presents.
So where you going now?
Uh, I don't know.
I'll see you later.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah. Sure.
But by the looks of it,
you and I aren't going
to be brother and sister
any time soon.
Oh, no.
What happened?
Honestly? It was me.
I mean, look, Ryan, I have
absolutely nothing against your dad.
It's just I really didn't want to
rush into an insta-family again.
I mean, how long
would this one last?
Like a month?
Well, you never know.
I, uh, moved in with the
Cohens and I gave it a week.
Here I am.
I just wish there was a way
you could tell if it was
all going to work out.
Yeah, but there isn't.
But I promise you, I will
always be your brother,
in a completely, non-creepy way.
Caitlin, honey, could
I talk to you?
Yeah.
Wait, Ryan, as your sister,
if you don't tell Taylor that
you love her, you're an idiot.
Oh.
She's right.
I just wanted him to get excited
about something, you know?
Anything.
Just give him a chance.
Oh, no.
Seth, I'm so sorry you
had to overhear that.
No, it's all right.
I mean it's true.
What I was going to say is, I think
what you made is really good.
Yeah, there's no
coherent theme.
Most of the shots are
too wide and the Dogma
thing has been done to death.
But you know, I get that you
wanted me to find something
that I'm passionate about,
the way you're passionate
about the environment.
But you love movies.
I do.
I love going to them
and then telling people
what's wrong with them.
What is it?
I could be a critic.
You mean spending your
whole life watching movies
and telling people
how terrible they are?
Yeah, that sounds awesome.
I just want you
to find something
that you really care about.
You want to go rent
An Inconvenient Truth?
Yes, I love that movie.
I just want to count the number
of gratuitously soulful shots
of Al Gore staring out an airplane window.
Do not insult Al Gore.
So what did you tell Frank?
I told him we needed
to slow it down.
Mom, if you really like him...
I do.
And he's not going away.
But I told him that right now
I need to be spending
some time with my daughter.
Does that include
buying me ice cream?
Absolutely.
The hermit?
My soul card's the hermit?
Are you kidding me?
Okay, Esmerelda, I'd better go.
I guess I'll call you next year.
Come in.
Hey, I hope I'm not interrupting.
No.
I got you something.
Okay...
Wait, these are all poems
that I've translated.
I collected them,recopied them,
had them bound.
Ryan, this is amazing.
Are you sure this is from you?
Taylor, I'm sorry.
I-I freaked out.
What I said last
night, I meant.
Really?
I love you.
And I don't want to lose you.
So let's put it all on the table.
Berkeley, Paris,
Oxford, anything.
I don't know what to say.
That's a first.
Oh, my God, Mom.
It's okay, it's just...
It's an earthquake.
Get in here.Mom!
Seth.
Kirsten!