Oh, hey,
I thought you were
hanging Christmas lights.
Oh, I took a coffee break,
union rules.
Well, you better hurry up,
it's going to start
raining any minute,
and you know how Seth
loves his rooftop reindeer.
Yeah, don't worry,
it'll be up by dinner.
Oh, speaking of dinner,
are you going to bring a guest?
That's pretty subtle,
Kirsten.
I'm not saying
you'd bring Taylor,
I'm just letting you know
that she's welcome.
Uh-huh.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know,
it's, uh, it's just...
Oh, you think that if you invite
her, she's your girlfriend.
Boy, so predictable.
Hey, now, inviting a girl
over for Christmas Eve,
that's like making
some sort of announcement.
It's Chrismukkah.
We make our own rules.
Fine.
Set a place for her.
I'll invite her today.
Great.
Okay.
Oh, my ham guy.
Can't believe we're spending
Christmas in the ghetto.
It's not the ghetto.
It's Riverside, and it's
where our family is from.
I thought we were
in denial about that.
Kaitlin, in case
you hadn't noticed,
we're a little short
on family these days.
I think we should
take all we can get.
TAYLOR:
* God rest ye merry gentlemen,
let nothing you dismay... *
Oh, God, now it's caroling.
Happy holidays.
Hello.
Is that a gift for me?
'Cause I forgot to get you one.
No, this is for Ryan.
I got him a George Foreman grill
because he likes lean meat,
obviously.
Lovely. So, Taylor, uh, Summer's
having dinner with the Cohens,
but you're welcome
to come with us to Riverside,
unless of course you're doing
something with your mother.
Oh, no, no.
She sent me a mass E-mail
last week.
She's spending Christmas
in Cabo.
She would've
invited me,
but she knows that I don't like
Mexican food.
But it's not a problem because
I'm having dinner over at Ryan's.
Oh, I didn't know you
were invited over there.
I'm not...
well, yet.
But I'm sure he's
going to ask me.
Well, I mean,
I hope he does.
Well, he will.
So I better go over there
and give him his gift.
Last chance to come
to Riverside.
You want to watch my Aunt Cindy
do whippets underneath the mistletoe?
Uh... no, thanks.
But you guys have
a good time.
Bye.
Feliz Navidad.
I know, where's
the mistletoe, right?
But don't worry,
we can kiss anyway.
Uh, Taylor, I'm a
little busy right now.
Well, don't you want
your present?
Just leave it right there.
I'll open it later.
You know I just ran into Kirsten
in the kitchen,
and she was talking to some guy
with a huge ham.
Are you guys having dinner
or something?
Uh, yeah.
Poor Ryan.
All of his muscles are so developed,
except for the ones in his mouth.
You want to invite me
to Chrismukkah,
but you don't know how,
so I will save you the trouble.
I would love to come.
Taylor, look, I don't know
what's going on between us,
but it's only been a few weeks.
And you think if you invite me
to Chrismukkah,
then that makes me
your girlfriend.
I don't want to hurt
your feelings, but yeah.
Hurt my feelings?
Why would that hurt my feelings?
Just because I spent
time and money
getting you the perfect gift--
which, by the way, happens to be
the deluxe version
of the George Foreman grill--
and in return you give me
a hot, steaming pile
of rejection.
Well, you know,
I think that's just fine.
(sighs)
Because I'm used
to it, okay?
So here, here it is.
Grill away.
Taylor, I don't want this.
No, I took your gift--
the holiday-themed
rejection--
so you should take it.
No, you take it.
I bought it for you.
You take it.
It's yours. I...
Taylor!
Whoa, it's going to pour.
Are you sure this
is a Virginia ham?
Taylor?
Taylor, are you...
are you hurt?
Only my heart, Ryan.
Only my heart.
Come on up,
I'll get you some ice.
Oh, you're
offering me ice?
Hmm, I guess I should
jump at that.
Here.
The receipt's inside.
I hope you grill
your face.
Oh, so, I was just
in the pool house...
What are you doing in there?
I told the supervisor that
this is off-limits to the staff.
What?
Where is your supervisor?
Uh, Kirsten, what are
you talking about?
Excuse me, do I know you?
O.C 07
-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:Allen
-=www.eastgame.net=-
I said do I know you?
Uh, look, I don't know
what's going on, but...
I was up on the
roof with Taylor...
Is this one of your guys?
Nope, never seen him before.
Oh, great.So now I just have
strangers wandering around my house.
No, no, no.
Where's Seth?
Oh, you're a friend
of my son's.
He's at the comic
book store.
If you run into him,
will you tell him
that I need him home by 5:00?
Uh... I have a meeting.
Now shoo.
I don't want you wandering
around my house.
Hey, kid,I got the feeling
the dragon lady wanted
you out of here.
You see, this is why I feel
so strongly about this issue.
Take Daryl here.
Last week he was homeless.
But because of the money
we've raised, he has a future
to look forward to
in the new year.
Well, you're quite the
philanthropist.
Yes.
And I help people.
Julie.
I love it when they call
me by my first name.
What are you doing?
What is all this?
Take this, it's a voucher
for the mission.
Tell them I sent you.
You don't know me?
I know your pain.
See, people think that
Newport Beach is a cold city,
a place of privilege.
But even this poor street urchin
has found hope here.
Now you just run
along now, honey.
You heard the lady.
You guys, come on.
Would you...
would you give me back...
Would you give me back
my wallet?
(mockingly):
Would you... would you
give me back my wallet?
Seriously.
Hey, hey, give me that.
Why, is this
your boyfriend?
You guys should get a room.
Yeah. So you can
make love in it.
(scoffs)
I make love to ladies.
Hey, man, thanks.
Do I know you from Brown?
You go to Brown?
Yeah. Who are you?
You don't know me either?
I can't believe this.
Hey, dork,your girlfriend's
across the way.
Which one?
You should check her out.
She looks good.
How does Sandy Cohen
have such a loser for a kid?
Wait, Sandy Cohen?
You know where he is?
I think I heard he's
at a press conference over at the yacht club.
Press conference?
Oh, just... just
look at her.
Oh, I shouldn't be watching.
Why, bad luck
to see the bride?
Yeah, totally.
Oh, God.
You okay?
Oh!
MAN:
So what are your plans
for the holidays?
This holiday,I think my wife and I
are just going to take it easy.
Your wife?
I thought she
never rested.
True, she's
a very busy lady.
All right, Joe,
thanks very much.
Thanks for your
time, Mr. Mayor.
And thanks for
all your support.
As I always say,
I am mayor of the greatest
city on earth.
Vote Sandy Cohen!
You're the mayor?
Why, you want to call
for a recount?
Happy holidays.
Uh, Sandy, Sandy.
Something terrible is happening.
And if anyone can make it
make sense, it's you.
This guy bothering you,
Mr. Mayor?
Uh, no.
It's fine.
All right, kid,
slow down, tell me
what the problem is.
Okay. So, uh, I fell off
the roof this morning,
and ever since then
nobody recognizes me.
Even Kirsten threw me
out of the house.
You saw Kirsten?
And Seth doesn't know
who I am either.
And he's marrying Summer?
I see that you're
having some trouble
and I sympathize
with that.
But stalking me
and my family
is not the answer.
Come on, and don't make a fuss.
Oh, the poor kid.
What's the matter?
Can't find your boyfriend?
Kirsten.
What happened?
Taylor and Ryan,
they were hanging decorations,
and I guess the ladder fell.
What did the doctors say?
Well, they said apparently
there's no serious injury,
we just have to wait
for them to wake up.
Ryan?
Is that you?
Taylor.
You know me?
Oh, my God.
I found you.
We're in a parallel universe.
Exactly.
Okay.
And I'm so grateful
that if I have to be
in a parallel universe,
that you're here with me.
Oh, that's...
Of course
you probably wish
you were with someone you
actually wanted to date.
That would be nice,
wouldn't it?
Oh, even in a parallel
universe, she never stops.
But I mean, we could also
be asleep, right? Or dead?
Ow.
You're awake.
As for being dead,
I'm guessing if we were,
there would be some kind
of white light situation,
maybe a guy
with a beard.
Process of elimination,
parallel universe.
How do you know all this?
Oh, tenth grade I had
a little sci-fi phase.
Alt-universes are huge.
Clearly, you and I
have entered a world
where we don't exist.
But don't despair.
I know the way back
to the real world.
Yeah? Does it involve
me dating you?
Well, well, look who's
funny in alt-world.
I know.
No, Ryan,
we have been sent here
to fix something.
It's the only explanation.
Someone or some ones
we know are in trouble.
Summer?!
Hi!
Kiss-kiss.
Oh, my God.
Let me see
the hardware.
What, you mean
this old thing?
(squeals):
Oh, my God!
Four carats.
Oh, my God, it's so pretty.
Can I get a...?
* Ice, ice... *
* Baby! *
(humming bass line
to "Ice, Ice, Baby")
* Ice, ice, baby *
Hey, babe.
Whoo!
Alt-Summer is
a mindless bimbo.
Get it started, Newport!
Whoo!
I'm so excited.
So where's the groom?
Oh, you know him,
he's parking.
He won't let any of
the valets touch his Hummer.
Right.
Because that's my job,
bitch.
Right!
Hey, Holly, looking ripped.
Hey, Chester.
What's up, Mrs. Me?
Mm-hmm, that's me.
Okay, wait a second. I thought
you said she was marrying Seth.
That's Che, or Chester,
I guess, in alt-reality.
What's he doing here?
I thought he goes to Brown.
Okay, what if three years ago
his family had planned to move here
but you did instead,
taking the last spot
at Harbor?
So without quality education for their child,
his family moves to Connecticut.
But in a world where
you don't exist,
the Harbor spot was open,
so his family moves here,
thereby allowing Che
to fulfill his alt-destiny
as a Newport bobble head.
Well, obviously this is what
we've been sent here to fix.
So, Summer, I saw the most rocked out
chairs at Bergdorf.
You have to come with me.
Ooh... baby.
Do you mind?
Um, no, I'll just
go get pumped.
But that's my job, bitch.
Oh, yeah, give it up.
Whoo!
Ooh...
(gasps):
Hey, bitch!
Okay, we need to get
started right away.
You go to Seth, find out
where it all went wrong.
I will follow Summer
and do some recon.
Uh, where do we meet?
It's alt-universe.
We'll just find
each other.
Their MRIs came back normal,
no brain damage,
no cause for alarm.
They'll wake up soon, I'm sure.
Is there anything
we can do to help?
Talk to them.
Make sure they're surrounded
by familiar voices,
music, even smells.
Anything that you think
might stimulate them.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Well, somebody should
find Taylor's mom.
I guess I'll do that.
Ew, signing up for
the suicide mission.
Oh, my ham. I have to go home
and turn off the oven.
Seth and I will take
care of the ham.
In fact, she just said we should surround them
with familiar sounds and smells.
So I say we bring Chrismukkah
to the hospital.
KIRSTEN:
That's a great idea.
And I'll look after
Taylor and Ryan.
And you be careful
with my ham.
I'll be very careful.
We're still getting it checked
if it's real.
Uh, baby, this is business.
I've got to take this.
Okay.
Hey, baby.
Yeah.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
I'll walk it.
You wearing that thong
I bought you?
Whoo-hoo.
Not for long.
All right, love you, too.
Bye.
Bye, baby.
Hello?
Oh, it's you again.
Looking for Seth?
Uh, yeah, they told me at the
comic book store he came home.
Well, I haven't seen him yet.
You might want
to try him upstairs. Honey?
Could you bring
me my glass?
Here you go, sweetheart.
Oh, thank you.
Jimmy?
You know my husband?
I don't believe
we've actually met.
Oh, this is
a friend of Seth's.
Oh.
I know, it must be
a Christmas miracle.
Well, you should come
to the party tonight.
All of Newport's
going to be there.
Well, they better be,
if they want to keep
doing business with
the Newport Group.
Seth!
JIMMY:
He's not home.
He's probably out
stalking Summer Roberts.
(Kirsten chuckles)
I'm going to go.
Well, you should stop by,
it starts around 7:00.
Interesting.
SANDY:
Oh, and "philanthropist"
means you help people.
Oh, well, you learn
something every day.
Listen, are you coming
home before the party?
You know how you sweat
through your shirts.
SANDY:
Can't we make some excuse?
Listen, honey,
as long as you're mayor
and she is head of
the Newport Group,
you're gonna have to
deal with each other.
Honestly, I don't know how
you were ever married
to that ice queen.
Well, we were different
people back then.
I'll be home
in a couple hours.
Bye.
Joinx!
(Chester barking)
(Julie squealing)
Double-O joinx.
Oh!
CHESTER (groans):
Oh, give it to me!
Oh! Daddy like!
Daddy like!
I'm a bad kitten!
Mima?
Hi.
No?
Yes, you don't know me.
Uh, I was just...
You come visit Missy Cooper?
Yes,
yes, that's
exactly what...
She come home 3:00.
Plane from Berkeley.
Triple-O joinx.
(laughing)
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, move over.
Taylor, why don't you
just sit over...?
Ryan, don't worry.
It doesn't mean we're
boyfriend and girlfriend.
I have huge news.
Yeah, well, me, too.
Sandy and Kirsten are divorced
and she and Jimmy are married.
Ew, yikes, that is huge.
I can beat it, though.
Sandy Cohen
is married to Julie.
What?
And she's having
an affair with Che.
Whoa.
Okay, all right,
so this means we need
to get Sandy and Kirsten
back together
and Seth...
Ryan, there's
something else.
Yeah, what else?
Um...
In this world, Marissa's alive.
I was in her room
and Mima said
her plane lands
at 3:00 from Berkeley.
Now it seems like everyone
is going to this party
at Kirsten's, so I think
that we can use
this opportunity
to reunite the Coopers
and the Cohens
with their
rightful partners.
Uh, Taylor,
can you let me out?
Why? Do you have to go
to the bathroom?
I haven't had to go.
It seems like it's not
an issue in an alt-world.
Taylor, seriously,
let me out.
Are you going to the airport?
Ryan, she won't even know you.
It doesn't matter.
Even if Marissa is fine
in this world,
which, thank God she is,
we need to focus on
fixing what is broken.
Because that's
what's going to get us
back to the real world.
But if she's alive...
Then you don't want to go back?
Okay.
I get it.
You... you got to go.
Sorry.
I can't believe we have to drive
to Riverside in this.
Oh, no, honey,
I told you.
My family only drinks
wine coolers.
We're having a very
Britney Christmas, Mother.
Yes, watch out.
I might put you on my lap
while we drive
out there.
Oh, thank God
you're still here.
Ryan and Taylor
are in a coma,
but we're not
supposed to worry.
What are you talking about?
They fell off a ladder.
But the doctor says
they're fine.
We just have to wait
for them to wake up.
So it's a coma light?
Exactly. I have to find
Veronica Townsend.
Do you know where she is?
Taylor said she's
flying to Cabo tonight.
But she may have
already left.
I really don't
think that Veronica
is going to care if
Taylor's in a bogus coma.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Her daughter's in the hospital.
She needs to know.
Come on, I'll drive.
You don't have to.
Taylor is my
responsibility.
She's living in my house.
Come on.
So no Riverside?
Sweet.
I mean, I hate comas.
Let's go find Veronica.
Oh, Mrs. Cohen.
The EMT just came by.
He found this
in his ambulance.
Thought it might've fallen
out of your son's pocket.
Oh, thank you.
I've been talking to them
and reading to them
out loud.
I know the doctor
says not to worry...
I know, it's hard.
But in these situations,
a lot depends
on the patients
healing themselves,
mentally and physically.
When they finish whatever
they need to finish,
they'll wake up.
Thanks.
Marissa?
Who are you?
Uh, I'm sorry.
I thought, uh...
What, you knew my sister?
I thought she was coming
home from Berkeley.
No, that's me.
The youngest in
my freshman class.
Sort of a prodigy.
Uh, what... what
did you mean "knew"?
She died three years ago.
What?
She OD'd in an alleyway
in Tijuana.
Well, that's really the way
I want to start
my Christmas vacation.
Wait, who are you again?
No one.
Oh, okay.
Well, Merry Christmas.
I'm sorry.
Ryan, you gave her
three more years.
She got to
fall in love.
She got to graduate.
And then she still died.
Which just means that you
weren't meant to save her.
So if there's
any part of you
that's still
blaming yourself
for what happened,
you have to let it go.
You've done so much
for everybody.
Yeah, like what?
Ryan, haven't you been
paying attention?
You saved the Cohens.
Without you, Seth is
the next unibomber,
Sandy is married
to Slutty McSlutterman,
and Kirsten probably
hasn't had an orgasm
in, like, a year.
Uh, all right,
all right.
And if you think that I'm just
gonna let you give up,
you're crazy.
Taylor, I said
all right.
Oh. Oh, good.
Okay.
Has anyone ever
said "no" to you?
Once.
And I pushed him off the roof.
Kidding.
Let's save the Cohens
and go home.
All right.
Okay.
An alternate universe?
It's the only
obvious explanation.
"Obvious" might not be
the word I would use.
They both got knocked out
at the same time
and neither is waking up.
Like Dorothy in Oz.
And just like Dorothy
had to go see the wizard,
they've got some mission
to accomplish
before they can return.
Like what?
Uh, anything.
Could be like our world,
only messed up.
They've got to
reset the balance.
Or could be a world ruled by
giant vegetables,
and they've got to topple
the vegetable despot
before they can come back.
You had me till
vegetable despot.
It makes perfect sense.
Hello.
Sandy,
I think I know why Ryan
hasn't woken up.
Hi.
Okay, now before we can reunite everyone
with their rightful partners,
we need to
prep them first.
So I will take Kirsten
duty and you can...
Ooh.
I already told you, I'm not
going to your stupid party.
Because Summer Roberts
is going to be here?
Since when are you
avoiding her?
Since she got engaged
to that burly ding-dong.
You have fun.
I'm on it.
Taylor, what
are you doing?
I told you not
to wear that suit.
Your ass looks like
the back of a truck.
Oh, my God.
In alt-world, I'm a boy.
Maybe I should try Pilates.
They say it elongates you.
Outside.
Go stand against the wall.
Go, come on.
And my mom is still a bitch.
Veronica.
Thank God,
we caught you.
Oh, Julie, please don't tell me
you're going to Cabo, too.
Veronica, you can't
go to Mexico.
Taylor is in the hospital.
Anorexia?
No, she fell off a ladder.
Oh.
The doctor says
she'll be fine,
but she's not waking up.
Maybe if she
heard your voice.
Summer has a car
outside...
I'll call from Cabo.
Veronica, listen.
I know you're not
the warm and fuzzy type.
But it is Christmas Eve
and it would mean so much
if you could be there.
And if you get on
that plane right now,
I'll tell security
you have a bomb.
Wow, very
Jack Bauer of you.
All right.
All right, come on,
put this on.
No, hate my life!
I hate my life...!
I hate my life!
Yeah, no wonder Summer
doesn't like you.
See?!
Even you think so.
And no offense,
but it's kind of weird,
you having such a vested
interest in my love life,
considering I just met you
this morning.
All right.
You want the truth?
Huh?
I know the truth.
You know the truth?
Yeah.
I'm from an alternate universe
where your dad adopted me
and you and Summer are in love.
And unless I fix
things here,
which means
getting your parents
and you and Summer
together,
I can't go home.
I always knew this would happen.
Doesn't surprise me.
Put this on.
Okay.
Now, I'm going
to tell you exactly
what you need to know
to woo Summer.
Have you ever heard of
a show called The Valley?
Hey.
It's a great party, huh?
Yes.
I'm so glad that the mayor
let me off so that I could come.
You work for the mayor?
Mm-hmm.
How... well,
what's that like?
Honestly, it's amazing that
anything ever gets done.
What with the mayor moping
and crying all day
about how he's still in love
with his ex-wife.
But I probably shouldn't be
airing his dirty laundry.
I mean, she must be around here
somewhere, right?
Well, I better mingle.
Ta.
Good, you got
a jacket from Seth.
Yeah.
Did it go okay?
Great. He's going over
stalking points right now.
Well, I am doing some serious
Jedi mind tricks on Kirsten.
(Chester barking)
RYAN:
There's couple number two.
Ho-ho-ho, Merry Christmas.
Oh!
That's my man.
Okay, so what we need to do
is get Kirsten and Sandy
and Seth and Summer alone
together for ten minutes.
Which means removing
the obstacles.
You take Julie,
I've got Chester.
Hey, wouldn't this
actually be fun,
you know, if you were actually
doing it with somebody
who you wanted to date?
Go.
Okay, I'll stop.
Hi.
Good grub.
Yeah.
So, listen,
a red-haired lady wanted
me to give you a message.
She's in
the master bathroom
and she needs help
with something.
A little thong removification.
Charming.
Well, uh, she's waiting.
Hey, I have a good idea.
Hmm?
Why don't you come with?
Wow, really tempting.
Um, I'm going to pass.
Ew.
Good to see you again.
Thanks for coming.
Hi.
Hello.
Do I know you?
There's some guy
who wants to meet you
in the master bathroom.
Something about
getting a thong on?
Oh.
That's charity talk.
"Thong" is an acronym for
The Homeless of Newport...
Go... or something.
Excuse me.
Just do me a favor,
and don't get caught.
Mr. Mayor.
Yes?
Hi, I was wondering,
do you have time for
a quick question?
I'm hoping it's about
the new hospital.
Because Dr. Henry Griffin
and I have some big plans.
Actually, it's about
relationships.
You see, you and I are kind
of in the same position,
because I just broke
up with this guy,
and he refuses
to move on.
I'm not sure how
this applies to me.
Mr. Mayor, come on.
I mean, your ex-wife will
tell anyone who listens
about how much she's
still in love with you.
I work at
the Newport Group.
And it is amazing that
anything ever gets done.
Young lady, I don't know you.
But I do know
that this is not
an appropriate conversation.
So please excuse me.
Uh, mail truck.
What?
Uh, yeah, um...
from the old days at Berkeley,
when you guys
first fell in love.
She won't shut up
about it.
Mail truck, mail truck,
mail truck.
It's just crazy, huh?
Bye.
SUMMER:
So, wait,
you're saying that you ride
horses in the valley?
No, no, I like plastic horses
and the show The Valley.
Hey, I like that show, too,
and plastic horses.
What's yours' name?
Uh, Princess Sparkle.
Wait, no, no,
I mean Captain Oats.
I just said
"Princess Sparkle,"
'cause I think that's
a really cool name.
No way!
You are not going
to believe this.
How's it going?
Well, I read lips,
and in the past
two minutes, the words
"mail truck"
have come up nine times.
We might actually
pull this off.
Mm-hmm.
VERONICA:
Lots of teenage boys get lipo.
It's no big deal.
And stop picking
at your man girdle.
But, Mom?
What?
You have
something to say?
No.
You know what?
I think it's time
I talk to her as an adult.
Okay, you can do this.
Do what? Eat?
Well,
that's apparent.
Shut up.
Why do you have to be so mean?
Neither he nor I
are remotely fat.
We are smart and attractive,
and interesting
and people like us.
And we are not going to let you
make us feel bad
about ourselves anymore.
No?
Well, I imagine the mirror
does that for you.
You bitch!
Oh, my God.
You all right?
I just can't believe
I just said that.
I mean, I've been
waiting for so long.
I can't believe
I finally did it.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks, Ryan, I...
Whoa.
What is it?
What's wrong?
I don't know,
I ju...
Do you hear something?
Almost like rain?
Stay here, I'll get you
a glass of water.
Okay.
JIMMY:
In my own house?
In my own bathroom?
I have to brush
my teeth in there.
So do I, but I don't
use a toothbrush.
(laughs):
Yeah, dawg.
Oh, Julie, you haven't
changed a bit.
Maybe you should learn to knock.
What's going on in here?
Well, Mr. Mayor,
let me just tell you what
I found your wife doing.
Jimmy, don't.
Whoo...
Well, suffice to say,
her thong was
in his mouth.
Shut up!
Baby, it was stuck. I was only
trying to help her out.
Oh, but that's what you said
with Holly.
How come all these women
around you
keep getting their thongs stuck?
I'm starting to get suspicious.
Geek, move it or lose it.
Then I will lose it,
whatever it... is.
Mm-hmm.
All right, well,
it's your funeral.
All right.
(whispers):
Oh, snap.
Thong emergency.
(growls)
That was, like, so brave.
Oh, Julie, how
could you do this?
Please, Sandy,
we both know
our marriage is a sham.
JULIE:
You only married me
so I could mastermind
your political career.
What are you doing with Miss
Queen of the North over here?
Don't you know?
He spends all day crying
about me at the office.
What are you
talking about?
Everybody knows, Sandy.
In the same way that everybody
knows how you go on and on
about the mail truck?
I never told anybody
about the mail truck.
Well, not according
to her.
Well, she's the girl that told
me you spend all day crying.
Uh-oh.
Sorry.
Apparently, people don't stock
clean glasses in the alt-world.
What's up?
Oh, it's the street urchin.
I knew not to trust him.
I think you two
better start talking.
Absolutely.
Taylor?
Oh, don't worry.
I know exactly what to say.
Okay, people,
I can explain everything.
(startled gasp)
Sorry.
What?
TAYLOR:
Just feel a little dizzy.
I...
Oh, no.
Ryan, I think I have to go.
What?
What do you mean?
It must be because I stood up
to my mom.
That's what I was here to do.
Ryan?
Yeah?
You have to get everyone
together.
No.
It's the only way back.
RYAN:
Taylor, no,
I can't.
Taylor...
What?
Huh?
Just hold on.
Taylor?
Taylor, honey?
You need to be with Sandy Cohen.
I'm going to get the doctor.
SANDY:
So?
Are you going to explain
yourself?
The truth is,
things the way they are now
are completely wrong.
SUMMER:
Who's this random guy
we're all listening to?
And why am I not drunk yet?
Okay, look, none of you know me.
But, uh, the truth is
that each of you saved my life
just by being who you are.
And right now none of you
are who you are.
Like Summer, for example.
What are you doing?
What?
I mean, Che, Chester, he's, he's
completely wrong for you.
You should be with Seth.
Kirsten, all right, you don't
want to run the Newport Group.
That place makes you miserable.
And you may like your
Chardonnay, but
I got news for you, it doesn't
like you back, and Sandy,
you don't want
to be mayor.
You're all about saving the
little guy, not holing up
in some mansion,
giving orders.
What you two are best at is
being married to each other.
There he is.
Get him out
of here.
Um, okay,
before I go,
Sandy, Kirsten, Seth and Summer,
promise me you'll be together.
KIRSTEN:
Hey, Veronica, good news.
Taylor's awake, and the doctor
said she's going to be fine.
I stay home from Cabo
and she's fine?
Hi, Mom.
And you're walking even?
Geez.
Veronica, your daughter is okay.
You should be happy.
Oh, Julie, it's okay, I got it.
Mom, why don't you go to
the airport? I bet you could
catch the last flight to Cabo.
Well, I guess
I could still make it,
but I'll probably
have to fly coach.
Merry Christmas, Mom.
Yeah.
You okay?
I don't know why,
but I feel just fine.
Huh.
Julie?
Hmm?
You should see this.
I haven't read it.
Oh, my God.
You, uh, you seen my hat?
You threw
up in it.
Right.
Atwood, there's someone here
to bail you out.
(weary sigh)
Thanks.
I don't know who you are,
but a lot of what you said
back at the house made sense.
So why do you care so much
about getting a bunch of
strangers back together?
Well, I guess I thought
it would get me back home, too.
But I was wrong.
Can I ask what happened?
How'd your family fall apart?
Hmm.
I think it all goes
back to when Marissa Cooper
died three years ago.
She was Jimmy and
Julie Cooper's daughter.
I knew Marissa.
Well, after she died,
it was like
everybody got stuck.
Didn't know how to say good-bye?
Maybe you're right.
What are you doing
for dinner?
How about you come
over to the house?
There's someplace
I gotta go. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Oh, I was just
calling you.
Julie, Summer
and Kaitlin
are with Taylor.
She's awake.
Oh.
What'd you find out?
This.
It's from Marissa.
She sent it to Ryan
the day she was leaving.
I guess it got lost
in the mail.
Oh, that's odd.
Well, it's Chrismukkah;
stranger things have happened.
What's it say?
Well, that she had
to leave Newport.
That it was the only way they
could get on with their lives.
She loved him,
but she had to say good-bye.
Is that food?
Oh, thank God.
Between you and me,
Taylor in a coma
is kind of a nice break.
How you doing, Julie?
I'm okay. Thanks.
(sighs)
Ryan, are you awake?
Hi.
I just had the weirdest dream.
You were in it, I think.
That's so funny.
I think you were in my dream,
too.
I can't remember what it was,
though.
Huh. Me, either.
I'm really glad you're here.
Look, the rain stopped.
Hey!
Look who's back in the land
of the living.
Oh, Ryan, we were
so worried about you.
(Ryan sighs)
Everything is going to be okay.
Yeah, I know.
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
http://tlfsub.eastgame.net