(music from TV)
(dialogue from TV)
Hold it, buster.
- Find the prisoner.
Hannah, whoa!
Hannah, there's been a mistake.
Get me a lawyer.
- Where is the king?
- In the Great Hall, Sire.
- Enough. Thy post.
- Aye, Sire.
To the Great Hall.
(TV static)
(whimpers)
(dog growls)
I can't breathe!
No, no!
Not again!
(screams)
(screaming)
- (man) Been thinking about what to do.
- (woman) It's him.
Gotta change. Gotta change. Gotta be soon.
Hello, Duane. Nice to see you.
Nice to see you too, Doc.
- How are you feeling today?
- Pretty good.
Why don't we sit down, Duane?
- I wanna go over a few things with you.
- OK.
Now, uh... it says here...
...that you've been refusing
to take your medicine.
- I don't like the way it makes me feel.
- OK. All right.
Let's talk about that. Because we give you
that medicine for a reason, Duane.
- Because of your behaviour.
- I know. I know.
Because we don't want you
to hurt anybody again.
Are you still hearing voices?
I'm not crazy, Doc.
Duane Barry's not like these other guys.
No, everybody here is different.
They're coming again.
They're coming again. I can feel it.
They're gonna take Duane Barry to the place.
Nobody's coming, Duane.
Nobody can stop 'em.
I'm gonna give you a shot.
I think you just need some rest.
This'll make you sleep.
And when you wake up, you'll see
we didn't let anybody hurt you. OK, Duane?
Duane?
Duane!
Get away. Get away.
- Put down the gun, Duane.
- Gimme the keys.
- Duane.
- Gimme the damn keys!
(alarm)
No! No!
Either way, Doc, we're getting
outta here together. You got it?
Let's go, now! Go! Go! Go!
Agent Mulder.
Krycek. What's up?
There's a situation going down.
They want you right away.
What kind of situation?
A hostage negotiation.
- And they want me?
- Yeah.
- What for?
- The guy escaped a mental institution.
He's got four people at gunpoint in an office.
Claims he's being controlled by aliens.
- Krycek, Mulder. Where's the commander?
- Right that way, sir.
- OK, I got it right here.
- Lucy.
(man) You can put people
on the third and fourth floor.
- Agent Mulder?
- Yeah.
Lucy Kazdin, negotiation commander.
- This is Agent Krycek.
- Let me show you what we've got.
His name's Duane Barry. He's armed with
a 9mm Smith & Wesson handgun...
...one 9-round magazine.
We believe that he's prepared
to use the gun and not afraid to die.
- What does he want?
- Safe passage for him and his hostage...
...a shrink named Hakkie.
- Passage to where?
He's bent on taking the doctor
to an alien-abduction site.
He can't quite remember where the site is,
so he stopped at a travel agency.
- Is he lucid?
- Yes, but off his medication, so he's manic.
Ranting about scoop marks, scars on his
body, homing devices and other nonsense.
Like what?
This alien-abduction business,
which I guess you know about.
Yeah, but I've never been
in a hostage negotiation before.
We'll take you through it.
Agent Rich is advisory commander.
- He and I will be coaching you.
- What Mr Barry needs is a friend.
Someone who appears to understand him
and can appeal to his sense of reason.
Do we know anything about
his abduction experiences?
You really believe
in this stuff, Agent Mulder?
Is that a problem?
We're here to save lives.
You'll begin negotiations immediately.
Every three hours
we'll re-evaluate your progress...
...and let our tactical commander
advise and update on the use of force.
If this man is an abductee,
I need to know more about him.
His personal history.
Each abduction case is different.
That material's not been made available to us.
Nobody's thought to call
the hospital for records?
Look, Agent Mulder, the guy's a psycho.
Your object is to keep him on the phone.
The longer you do, the more chance
he's not gonna kill anybody.
We stop to do a Freudian analysis, next thing
we know we've got four dead hostages.
So, whatever crap you gotta make up
about spacemen or UFOs...
...just keep him on the phone.
Are we gonna have to sit
on the floor like this all night?
I told you to shut up!
We all have families, for God's sake.
Duane, don't hurt anyone.
- Please?
- I'm not gonna hurt you, Doc.
Because this time
you're going with Duane Barry.
So you can see what it's like.
That it's real!
(phone)
- Duane?
- Yeah.
This is Special Agent Fox Mulder.
- Look, I wanna try to help you.
- Yeah?
Well... we're just sitting here
waiting for, uh... travel plans.
I think I know what
you're going through, Duane.
I just wanna make sure
you get what you want and that Bob...
...Kimberly, Gwen
and Dr Hakkie don't get hurt.
You know what I'm going through?
You think you know what Duane Barry's
going through?! You don't know jack!
I know you're scared, Duane. And that
you'd like to see this all come out right.
Yeah, right.
So they can put me back in the nuthouse...
where I belong.
We're only concerned about your safety,
Duane. You and the others.
Hey, what's your name?
Mul-dore?
I know the routine.
Honesty, containment...
... conciliation. Am I missing something?
You need someone to trust, Duane.
I know a lot of people
who've been through similar experiences.
You wanna do something for me, Agent
Mulder? You keep your dogs on a leash.
You try to gas me out or do
anything stupid, these people die.
They're not taking me again. You got it?
They can take somebody else!
- Nobody's gonna try anything, Duane.
- (hangs up)
Who is this guy? He's FBI, isn't he?
- Former FBI.
- And you didn't think to mention that?
He's been institutionalised on and off
for over a decade. It's beside the point.
The point being that the Bureau
wants to minimise its embarrassment.
That we can police our own.
They would like it done
as neatly and cleanly as possible.
- Well, you're off to a hell of a start.
- Negotiation is a process, Agent Mulder.
If you just wanted somebody
to read the script, you didn't need me.
This method has proven successful
in winning the hostage-taker's trust.
No. That man is afraid, and the only way
you're gonna win his trust...
...is by trying to understand
what he's afraid of.
Have you ever spoken
to an abductee, Agent Kazdin?
Heard them talk about having their brains
sucked out through their nostril?
- Wanna know what they do to your ovaries?
- Not particularly.
Well, then, understand that you might
have to alter your approach a little bit here.
Is there anything I can do?
- Yeah. What's your name again?
- Krycek.
- Krycek. Have you got your notepad?
- Yeah.
Grande, two per cent cappuccino
with vanilla. Agent Rich?
As you can see, the SWATteam has taken
positions on all the surrounding buildings...
- Scully.
- It's me. I'm in Virginia.
I know. I've been watching it on TV.
What's going on?
What's the media saying?
An escaped mental patient is holding
people hostage in a travel agency.
What they're not telling is he's former FBI
who claims to be an alien abductee.
- Seriously?
- His name's Duane Barry. I need your help.
Find out what happened to him.
Transcripts from therapy sessions...
...hypnotic regressions,
anything about his abduction.
- Mulder?
- The lights just went out here.
- (man) We're losing power.
- What the hell is goin' on?
(woman screams)
- Tactical Unit, what are you guys up to?
- Absolutely nothing, sir.
What the?
- (gunshot)
- Get down! Everybody get down!
Tactical Command, shots have been fired.
Locate and report.
(gunshots)
Negative. I've lost communication.
Waiting for orders, sir.
- We've lost our captured line.
- We have either four or five shots fired.
- What's the number in there?
- 5552804.
We have either four or five shots fired.
An electrical substation blew.
We've got no power.
- Duane?
- I told you.
- Is everyone all right, Duane?
- You didn't believe me.
No, I believe you.
I just need to know if anybody's been shot.
I need towels. Kimberly?
Kimberly? He's going to bleed to death.
I guess we're gonna need a doctor.
You'll have almost full ambient hearing loss
and your sense of balance may be affected...
...particularly if you have to move quickly
or get into a physical situation.
If you get trapped or held in the building...
...we'll be able to warn you
if there's a tactical assault.
And remember, he's either got
four or five rounds left.
There's a wireless mike
in the top of this flakjacket.
Speaking in a normal voice, we should hear
anything you say up to a hundred yards.
Attempt to keep these devices concealed.
If you put a telephone to that ear,
it'll reveal that you're wired.
- You really wanna do this?
- Yeah.
Your job will be to deliver medical help
to the hostage. Anything else is a bonus.
Get in and get out. You are not to risk
your own life. And whatever you believe...
Don't jump into his delusion.
I can't negotiate if he thinks I believe him.
Right. This is Agent Janus.
He's a trained medic.
He'll work on the hostage.
You're to keep Duane Barry talking.
Like I said, if he's talking, he's not gonna
shoot anybody - including you.
I've got three snipers out there.
Anything you can do to get him to the door...
All we need is one shot
to the medulla oblongata.
Tact Command, this is rooftop zero two.
I have them in sight.
They're passing the fountain and
approaching the front entrance now.
(Duane Barry)
Just unlock the door. Move back.
- Duane?
- Hands in the air.
- Put the kit on the floor slowly.
- We're unarmed.
- We just wanna help the injured.
- (woman) Over here.
Face the door!
That's right.
Not armed, huh? You're FBI, aren't you?
- Got a gun in the kit?
- No.
- Are you wearing a wire?
We're just here to help.
OK.
- Nobody's gonna try anything, Duane.
- That's right. You wanna work with him.
We just wanna make sure
no one else gets hurt.
Just do your business and get out.
- How's he doin'?
- He's bad.
Hi, my name is Janus. I'm a paramedic.
Hold on. We're gonna take care of you, OK?
They wanna work with you, Duane.
But you gotta work with them.
- Why not let the others go?
- Doc's going with me.
Then let the women go.
Were they here, Duane?
The light. Was that them?
- Don't try and BS Duane Barry.
- We lost time.
I checked my watch.
Isn't that what happens? Time stops? Isn't it?
Duane?
(screams)
(screaming)
- You're making it up.
- Isn't that what they've been saying to you?
- That you're making it up?
- They say it's all inside my head.
- All they wanna do is give me more drugs.
- I hear you, Duane.
- You hear me cos I got a gun.
- No, I believe your story.
No, you're feeding into his psychosis.
I know you're afraid.
I know the pain and the fear you must feel.
Just listen to me.
Don't try and identify with him.
I've talked to people, Duane. People
just like you who nobody wanted to believe.
This man's gonna die
unless we get him to a hospital.
Why don't you let him go, Duane?
There's no reason this man has to die.
Come on, Duane.
You've got the power. Let him go.
OK.
Good. You made the right choice. Now, we're
just gonna move him carefully to the door.
No! Baldie can go.
But you stay.
I'm trading the bald man for you.
Dammit!
They're coming out. Get him.
You're gonna be all right, sir.
Keep moving.
Now let's see how good a liar you are.
I'm telling the truth, Duane.
How could you ever know
what Duane Barry's been through?
How could anyone know?
It happened to my sister.
Don't you think you can lie to save their lives.
I want some honesty!
I want some respect!
I'm tired of all the BS!
How does it happen, Duane?
Driving in your car? Alone in bed at night?
When do they come to you?
You're paralysed, aren't you?
Unable to move.
Sometimes you can't even breathe.
You feel an electric shock
and then they're there.
He's gonna push him right over the edge.
I need a clear picture
of what's going on in there.
Right away.
You're choosing
a dangerous course, Agent Mulder.
There are beings, aren't there, Duane?
Are they tall? Or small?
- No!
- Diminutive?
They take you, Duane, against your will.
- He's gonna kill us.
- You're powerless.
Sometimes you can't even speak.
It's always the same. Nobody can help you.
Where do they take you, Duane?
Is there a ship?
Do they take you to a ship, Duane?
How do you get there?
Are you conscious of being transported?
(Duane Barry) They're, uh...
They're talking to Duane Barry...
... but they don't speak.
He can hear what they're saying.
They can... read his mind.
That's right. Abductees call it "mindscan".
It's a kind of telepathy.
I'm telling 'em I don't wanna go...
...but they never listen.
They know what I'm sayin'.
But they just...
...go right on about their business.
Tell him what their business is.
Tell him.
They take you aboard the ship
to perform the tests.
They... drilled my teeth.
They drilled holes in my damn teeth!
(whimpers)
(whirring)
(screaming)
(phone)
Yeah?
Who here can talk to an Agent Scully?
Agent Scully, it's Alex Krycek.
- Where's Mulder?
- He traded himself for one of the hostages.
- What?
- He's in with Duane Barry.
- Get him out of there.
- They're working on it.
No, get him out of there now
or he's gonna be killed.
- How can you be sure?
- Duane Barry is not what Mulder thinks he is.
How old was your sister when they took her?
She was eight.
I've seen kids sometimes. Young girls.
What are they doing to them?
Doing tests.
You know...
...testing 'em.
They tell 'em not to cry.
Are they hurting them?
Oh, yeah.
Sometimes...
...sometimes it hurts real bad and, uh...
...you just wanna die, you know?
You know what's it's like, sir?
It's like living with a gun to your head...
and never knowing when it's gonna go off.
You can let the others go, Duane.
Let the others go and take me.
Oh. They heard you talking like that,
they're gonna have your ass.
I don't care about that, Duane.
No. I wouldn't do that to you.
Besides, Doc and I got an appointment.
Ain't that right, Doc?
We got a picture.
Mulder is here, opposite the doctor.
The women are on the north wall. We can't
see the east wall. Barry must be there.
- Hold on a second.
- No. I don't think you understand.
- I just flew down from...
- We've got a situation...
- Let me talk to someone in charge.
- Calm down, Scully.
I'm not gonna calm down until I can talk to
someone who will listen to what I'm saying!
What's the problem here?
I'm Special Agent Dana Scully and I have
information that is vital to your negotiations.
- What information?
- I think there has been a misjudgment here.
This man who claims to be
under the control of aliens...
...his mental health history
describes a rare state of psychosis.
As you see from his medical records, in 1982
Duane Barry was shot in the line of duty...
...the bullet piercing his bilateral frontal lobes.
The injury left him nearly incapable
of functioning in society.
It effectively destroyed
the moral centre of his brain.
Almost a hundred years ago
there was a famous case.
A man named Gage had
a blasting rod pierce the same region.
And what effect did it have?
He became a pathological liar,
suffering from severe delusions.
His behaviour was characterised
as bizarre and violent...
...with a tendency to act out his fantasies.
How did you get involved in this case?
Agent Mulder called me.
We used to work together.
Well, if this is true, he's got
your former partner completely fooled.
Is there a way I can reach him
with this information?
The government knows about it, you know.
They're even in on it sometimes,
right there in the room when they come.
They work together.
With a, uh... secret, uh... corporation.
Who in the government?
A man. Military. They're all in it together.
The government knows why they're here...
... but they wouldn't dare let the truth out,
so they cooperate.
You're gonna have to deal with resolving
this situation, Duane, sooner or later.
I'm tired.
There's no other way out.
You've got to tell them what you wanna do.
- I just wanna go back to the place.
- What place?
Where it started.
Where they first came and got me.
Where is that?
A mountain.
We went, uh... up and... up.
Ascending...
...ascending to the stars.
I'm not going again.
- No.
- Mulder, it's me.
Listen to me. You cannot trust Duane Barry.
He is a psychopath who took a bullet
in the head. He is not what you think he is.
What?
How do they find you each time?
Implants.
My gums, sinus cavity...
...here in my bellybutton. Tracking devices.
Mulder, he could snap at any time. He has
a history of irrational and violent behaviour.
Now you have to work
towards resolving this.
Now, you have his trust.
You have to try and negotiate with him.
Why not let the women go, Duane?
They'll deal with you if you let the women go.
That's good. That's good, Mulder.
Now, keep him talking.
HRT is moving into position and unless
you can get him to free the hostages...
...they are going to execute a tactical plan.
The women are of no consequence to you.
Let 'em go.
It's the right thing to do, Duane.
OK, but he stays.
Go on. Get outta here.
Get up. Go on.
Get outta here. Go on.
I... I just want to say that I believe you.
OK, go!
Are we safe now?
- The women are clear.
- I got him. Standing, centre room.
Moving.
This is a countdown, Mulder.
They're coming at you.
- Position one, ready.
- Coming at you.
- We're gonna need transportation.
- What do you want, Duane? A car?
- I don't know.
- Do you know where you wanna go?
They're gonna tell me.
Duane, you can't leave here
if you don't know where you wanna go.
- Duane!
- What?
- Come here.
- Hold your fire. You lost your line.
- There's something I wanna ask you.
- What?
You didn't believe me.
I had to earn your trust.
Now there's something I gotta know.
Are you making any of this up?
You, uh... calling Duane Barry a liar now?
No.
You think I'd make it all up?
No, I don't. I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?!
- Duane, will you listen to me for a second?
You're like all the others.
You say you believe me.
- I do believe you.
- You're lying just like everybody else!
I believe you, Duane!
- I trusted you! I trusted you! I was a fool!
- Can I... Can I say something?
Duane, can I say something?
I know you're tired, but there's
something you've forgotten to do.
When you let the women leave,
you left the door unlocked.
Go and lock the door, Duane.
Go lock the door.
Go lock the door, Duane. Go lock it.
They can get in here. Go lock the door.
(man) He's down! He's down!
(distorted sounds and voices)
Code three. Repeat. Rolling code three.
Medical unit two zero. We're rolling.
You OK, Mulder?
Yeah.
Whatever you're feeling,
you did the right thing.
I know. It's just that, uh... I believe in him.
Sometimes when you wanna believe
so badly, you end up... looking too hard.
- Agent Mulder. Thanks for coming.
- No, I was surprised to get your call.
Yeah, well, as it turned out, whatever
your impression of the way it was handled...
...I didn't get to thank you for going
out there and putting it on the line.
What?
I don't know. I guess I thought maybe
you'd called me down here to chew me out.
- How's he doing?
- Duane?
They almost lost him, but he's stabilised.
They've got him listed on critical still.
I checked on his record with the Bureau.
It was exemplary.
His accident was something of a mystery.
Shot by his own weapon in a drug stakeout,
left for dead in the woods.
He was never the same.
Lost everything - wife, kids, house.
The fine thread of sanity.
I actually called you down here
for another reason, Agent Mulder.
Uh...
In the X-rays, the surgeon
found several pieces of metal.
In his gums, in his sinus cavity
and one in the abdomen.
I had them checked. I felt you'd wanna know.
And there were tiny drill holes
in his left and right rear molars.
A dentist said they could not have been done
with any of the current equipment in use.
Not without chipping or damaging the tooth.
Anyway, I thought you oughta know.
This could just be a piece of shrapnel.
Duane Barry did a tour of duty in Vietnam.
It was right where he said it would be. Along
with the ones in his gums and his sinus.
And you think this was implanted?
Well, if it was, that would mean
Duane Barry is telling the truth.
Or some version of the truth.
Look, I'll take this down to ballistics.
We can have this cleared up in a second.
Let me just make a slight adjustment.
What do you think?
Could be a shell casing
or a small artillery refragment.
The edges are dull,
but it could've been white-hot.
That would make sense.
But look at this.
- What?
- These small markings. See them here?
Mm. Looks like some kind of a stamp.
Like it's been tooled or etched.
Pretty fine work too.
This square we're looking at
is only ten microns across. Strange.
Eleven fourteen.
Thank you.
- (woman) Can I get some help here?
- I'll be right with you.
I'm just gonna cash up my drawer.
(bleeping)
- What happened? Did you touch something?
- Uh... I don't know what happened.
(bleeping)
(continuous bleep)
(phone)
Hello, this is Fox Mulder.
Leave a message, please.
Mulder, it's me. I just had something
incredibly strange happen.
This piece of metal they took out of
Duane Barry, it has some kind of a code on it.
I ran it through a scanner
and some kind of a serial number came up.
What the hell is this thing, Mulder?
It's almost as if...
It's almost as if somebody
was using it to catalogue him.
(thud)
(glass smashing)
- Come on!
- (Scully) Mulder!
- (Scully) I need your help!
Mulder!
Subtitles by Visiontext
(child) I made this!
ENGLISH HOH