They're not paying you enough
for this.
Well, it's the same each term.
My room.
Oh, there's this. Sorry.
Dr Graham?
Sorry!
# Who's cooking monsters
in the kitchen
# Who keeps a knife tucked in
her garter
# Who keeps you nervous
# Like screaming motorcycles
# You keep the fires burning
# I'll keep the water running
# We'll know it's over
when they turn out the lights #
There's been a break-in
at his high school.
Type Three, I'd say.
The secretary must have
disturbed it.
Well, she didn't say. She's dead.
We're compromised, we're compromised
to hell. They know where he lives.
OK. Gotta go.
Show time.
Welcome to the Dark Ages.
Mum?
Oh...
Well, hi. You must be Luke.
- What are you doing?
- Did I wake you?
I can't get the damned
ice machine to work.
Sorry. I'm Galvin. Rupert Galvin.
Can I get you anything?
There's no word in the English
language
to describe the correct
state of the perfect omelette.
It's all to do with internal
temperature.
Neither raw nor cooked.
Like this. See?
The French...
Thanks.
... have a word for it.
Baveuse.
Don't you love it?
Do they have a word for
someone who stays away
for years and years and
doesn't even write?
Idiot. The same in English.
What can I say? I'm sorry, Jenny.
Well. It doesn't matter.
You're here now. And it's
a wonderful surprise.
- How long are you in town?
- Oh, a while.
You know, I haven't slept
in 36 hours.
Where are you staying?
You could stay here. Rupert...
could stay here, couldn't he?
No, it's fine.
I have a reservation at Compton's Hotel.
Have you heard of it?
Ah... yes, I have. It's down by
Southwark Bridge.
OK. I need some sleepee.
I would drive you over there but
school's
in the opposite direction,
I'm afraid. Sorry.
Maybe Luke could take me.
Yes. Why not?
Good idea.
Go to the corner. Grab a cab.
Let him finish his breakfast.
He never eats breakfast.
Mum!
I've got stuff to do.
Who is this guy anyway?
Mum?
- Something you want to tell me?
- No.
He's your boyfriend.
Rupert is not my boyfriend.
Yeah, yeah!
Who is he, then?
He's your godfather.
You're kidding.
You know, I knew your father.
Did your mom tell you?
Yeah, we were good friends.
Yes, indeed. It was a bad time
when we lost him.
A very bad time.
Do you ever see things, Luke?
Do you ever see things?
- What kind of things?
- Oh, I don't know.
Out of the corner of your eye.
But when you look...
they're not there.
How about, you and me...
tonight, boys'night out.
What do you say?
I can't. Sorry.
- I've got to be somewhere.
- Cancel.
She'll understand.
- I assume it's a she.
- It's not like that. It's a party.
But you're not planning
on going home alone, right?
I like you.
Tonight, my friend,
the ladies can wait.
Your godfather has spoken.
7:30, Royal Festival Hall.
Meet me.
Good.
Oh, and, ah... Luke.
Don't open it until you get home.
And if you do see anything...
take care.
Remember - they bite.
- Hiya.
- Ruby.
- Can we talk?
- Yeah?
You know this party?
- The one we're going to tonight.
- Yeah. I've got a problem.
Oh. OK.
What's happened?
This guy turned up. He was a friend
of my dad's.
Apparently, he's my godfather.
He wants a boys'night out.
- You're joking.
- Listen... I've got your art folder.
- Do you need it?
- Bring it into college with you.
No, I'll stay here to work,
I have the place to myself.
Well, I could come to yours
and get it?
- OK. Cool.
- See ya.
I thought we had rats,
but it was big.
More like a monkey.
You've got monkeys!
Wow. Well, there goes
the neighbourhood.
It ate our mop.
Mmmm. You should call the council.
They have men in vans to deal with
this kind of thing.
Forget it. Listen.
I'm sorry about tonight.
It's OK.
No, it's not. It's Amber's birthday.
I said I'd go.
She'll be off her face by half 10.
She'll never know.
You won't be missing much anyway.
It was rubbish last year.
"Abraham V.H."
- Who's he?
- No idea.
And what about J and R?
R's Rupert. My godfather.
J's my dad.
See? 1990. The year I was born.
The year he died.
Old Abraham was the look of him.
See a family resemblance?
Er... maybe. Apart from the beard.
"The new V.H." The little sprog.
Is that you?
I suppose - so.
I'll find out.
Pardon me. Thank you.
Excuse me, ma'am. Thank you.
Mina!
- Rupert!
- Mina.
- You were amazing.
- You didn't tell me you were coming.
No, I'm a wild, impetuous guy.
Somebody I'd like you to meet.
Mina Harker, this is Luke.
Luke Rutherford. Hi.
Mina, your fans are waiting.
We got to move along here.
Seeing is believing, Luke.
You must believe even when it seems
impossible.
Thank you, Mina.
You were fabulous. As ever.
Through here, come on.
Beautiful girl, huh?
I didn't realise she was...
Blind? Don't let that fool you.
Mina's unique.
Very special.
I've been seeing really weird stuff.
I was attacked...
by a... a monkey thing.
And there was a creepy-looking guy
watching the place.
And who is Abraham?
You know you asked me what I did?
Well, the truth is...
I'm a warrior.
You're a warrior?
You're joking, right?
So was your old man
and so was Abraham.
All of us warriors in the coldest
of cold wars.
The struggle between human
and inhuman.
Us and them.
It's people like us keep the freaks
in their place,
down in the half-lif
where they belong.
Freaks?
What are you talking about?
Who are these people?
They're not people. What I'm
talking about are inhumans.
A different species.
Supernatural beings.
You know, in most cities you're
never more than 20 feet from a rat.
They outnumber the human population
seven to one.
How often do you see them?
Inhumans are the same.
- Whether you see them or not.
- They exist?
Oh, they exist all right. You know
they exist. You've seen them.
Like vampires and werewolves?
We don't care to name them.
We just grade'em and smite'em.
You smite them?
Oh, yes, sir. With extreme
prejudice.
Swiftly and surely.
Like the wrath of God.
Cheers.
You asked about Abraham.
Abraham Van Helsing, of Leyden,
Holland.
Rutherford is Jenny's name.
Your daddy's name was Van Helsing.
Come on, you are taking the piss.
You're saying I'm related to some
character from a book.
Identity theft. Bram Stoker
stole your name.
Now if it was me, I'd be mad
as hell.
I think I'm going home.
I have stuff I could be doing.
You think he invented Van Helsing?
I'm guessing no?
Abraham Van Helsing was real.
Come on, drink up. I'll show you.
Is everything all right, sir?
Do you want your bill?
- You know this place?
- Smithfield. It's a market.
Meat market.
It had a cold store
deep underground.
In 200 years, the ice never melted.
Perma-frost.
It took the construction guys
months to thaw it out.
- Do you know what they found?
- McDonald's?
Rivers, boy.
Rivers.
The Flaxman and the Hawk.
People thought they'd dried up
in the Middle Ages.
But nothing changes.
The old waters still flow.
Will this take long?
Not long.
Why, you got someone
waiting for you?
- No. I've got revision to do.
- Schoolwork.
Well, sorry.
That's what goes on.
You know,
up there in the real world.
What are you doing?
- Pulse gun.
- You could have killed me!
Works on microwaves. Everything has
its perfect internal temperature.
Like an omelette.
Exactly.
For an entity, it's about 30 below.
Warms'em up pretty good, huh?
Anything from a Type Seven,
Eight, maybe.
- Then what?
- Then we're after big numbers.
What was that monkey thing?
Type Three. Small potatoes.
Forget about it.
Is this an entity?
No, Luke, that is a rat.
What?
The locket.
Ready?
- You got it?
- No.
One more time, it locks us out.
Use the force, Luke.
Yeah, very funny.
Ready.
Did you get it that time?
- I think so.
- Good.
Shazzam.
The library of Abraham Van Helsing.
The world's number one authority
on inhuman life forms.
We call them the Stacks.
It kinda works, doesn't it?
What?
Built for keeps. State of the art
in the early 90s.
Hello, Luke.
This is very strange for me.
I'm talking to you out there
and yet I'm got you right here
in my arms.
But if you are watching this,
it means we never really
got to know each other.
And I can't tell you how sorry I am.
Everything you see
around you is yours.
Use it wisely.
Good luck, Luke.
The time has come to act.
What happened?
Mum said it was an accident
on a business trip.
It was business.
There is no accident.
The freaks got him.
Were you there?
Yes.
- Does Mum know about any of this?
- No, and she never will.
Not from me anyway.
It was a car smash. End of story.
Me and your daddy, we tried
so hard to...
... to keep you both out of it.
Is that why you went away?
You said you had your reasons.
Yeah, believe me it wasn't easy.
I know Jenny was hurt, but...
Well, it would have made you
a target too.
Me?
Luke...
Last night your school
was broken into.
Today a Type Three shows up
at your apartment.
Now I don't think that's
coincidence.
Now they're on to you.
They know where you live.
So I'm supposed to drop everything
and join the struggle,
start smiting entities?
Is that what you want?
It's not what I want.
Your cover's been blown wide open.
Like your old man said. The time
has come. You have no choice.
Everyone has a choice.
No. Other people have a choice,
you have a destiny.
You're the last Van Helsing.
Denial is not an option.
Incredible.
Did you ever ask yourself
how you do that?
Other people, they can't do that,
Luke.
It's in here.
In the genes. Talk tomorrow.
I don't think so, Mr Galvin.
We've talked enough.
You can't just hijack
someone's life, OK?
I have plans!
Hey! You came.
- Yeah, better late than never.
- How's the godfather?
Weird.
Deeply weird.
I'll tell you later.
How's the party?
Hi, Luke.
Hello, Amber.
Where have you been hiding?
He just got here.
Then you've got some
catching up to do.
Urrgh! Great!
Bet you wish you'd stayed
with Amber.
Forget it, we'll get a cab.
- I've got no money.
- Ruby!
Oh, God!
Listen to me!
What's up? What's up? What happened?
Down there, there's a freak.
Grabbed at me!
What sort of freak?
I dunno - tall, teeth. Does it
matter? What are you - an expert?
All right...
Lads?
Can you turn the lights on?
Come on.
I'm so proud!
What a hero!
Luke!
Someone wants to have a word
with you, Luke.
So be nice.
Come quietly.
Let him go.
Do it now or I will most surely
smite thee, you freak.
Watch out!
I'm getting way too old for this.
Hi. I'm Rupert, Pleased to meet you.
Are you OK?
How about you?
He knew me.
Whatever it was.
He knew my name.
He'd been sent to find me.
- What did I do?
- Nothing
It's what you might do
that worries them.
Oh!
Terrific.
And what about you? Did you just
happen along or did you follow me?
He wants to thank me.
He just can't find the words.
Were you following me?
Protecting my assets
by saving your ass.
Like I said, denial is not
an option.
- Excuse me
- Just a minute, Ruby.
- Do you know who sent them?
- Not exactly.
The hoodies were Type Four.
The big one a Type Five.
So you have to figure it wasn't
their idea.
- Why not?
- Type Fives don't have ideas.
And Type Fours can barely keep track
of their own saliva.
But you're wanted by just about
every freak in the Half-Life, so...
Excuse me, wha -
Who is she?
Who am I?
Who is SHE?
Ruby's a friend of Luke's.
Friend.
Is that entirely safe?
Where he goes...
I go.
Sweet.
So, Luke, you opened the Stacks.
Were you impressed?
The point is...
they're no to us. Luke and Ruby
were attacked.
And Ruby wants to know
what is going on?
So would someone please be kind
enough to explain?
Let's see.
Luke is the last Van Helsing.
The Inhuman want to kill him,
and you don't tell anybody.
Clear so far?
Luke is way under-prepared.
This is where you come in, Mina.
Go back with him to the Stacks.
Mina will find the weapons you need.
Excuse me. Another dumb question
I suppose, but...
how?
How will she?
Just leave it, Ruby.
I mean, I'm not being funny,
but I wouldn't have thought
she was the obvious choice for
finding stuff, that's all.
Luke is not the the only one
with an illustrious family.
Jonathan Harker...
Van Helsing's assistant, first
curator of the Stacks.
If it's in there, Mina will find it.
While you're gone, I'll do
some digging.
We need to find a name.
We have to know who we're up
against here.
Luke, don't go.
- Come on, Ruby, I have to.
- You so don't.
Luke, I have a really bad feeling
about this.
Don't go. Please.
I'll call you. OK?
You got your car, Mina?
- Of course.
- Oh(!) Is that entirely safe?
And my driver.
And what am I supposed to do?
Not a thing. You've had quite
a night. I'll take you home.
You don't need to patronise me,
you know. I'm not stupid.
Hmmm!
Halfway up at the back.
I can see it!
Careful. It's heavy.
Well?
Weird ammo.
Glass. Two liquids.
One silver, one green.
Not glass, actually. Soluble
plastic.
On a human target, you'd get a bump.
- A bump.
- Knocked down but no tissue damage.
No long-term effects. Fire at a
freak, and it's a different story.
They vaporise.
The original magic bullet.
Not magic, science.
And I'm supposed to use this?
I don't think so.
Maybe you'll feel differently
when the time comes.
Is this it?
Sorry it's not up to Luke's
standards.
Will you be OK?
Yeah.
No self-respecting freak'd
be seen dead round here.
Wait.
Any time, day or night,
if anything happens...
you call me.
Give him time to adjust, Ruby.
It really has been quite a night.
Yeah.
You could say that.
Thanks for the lift, Rupert.
Errrgh.
Ahhhh!
Thanks.
Rupert, it's Ruby.
You know what I said about freaks?
Boo.
Rupert, it's Ruby.
You know what I said about freaks?
Do you think I should call Ruby?
Won't she be tucked up
in her little bed by now?
You don't like her much, do you?
I don't know her.
Anyway, that's irrelevant,
She's your girlfriend.
No, she's not.
Ohhh, she thinks she is.
She wants to be.
Come on. You don't know that.
How do you know that?
Ohhh, it's this spooky sixth sense
that only blind people have.
Yeah, well, you're wrong.
We're just friends.
I've known her since she was four.
- We were at nursery, for God's sake.
- Whatever you say.
It's not my business.
But... your life is changing.
Do you really want
to get her involved?
She's not involved.
We were attacked.
It happened.
And it won't happen again.
- Look, it's late. I should go.
- Don't forget this.
I'm not good with stuff like this.
I'd probably'bump'my foot off.
You'll be just fine.
Hi, love. Good time?
- It was different.
- Different's good.
Come and tell me all about it.
Mina, Rupert.
Yeah. Luke's friend, Ruby...
She never made it home.
I know it's my fault. Whatever,
just meet me at the Stacks now.
So, you liked him?
Got on OK?
Sure. He's, um...
interesting.
Had an interesting life.
Loads of colourful stories, I bet.
Oh, yes. He tells a good story.
Well, they were young.
Travelling the world.
It was great for them really.
Then it was all over.
Yes.
Did Rupert... talk about it?
Not really.
He mentioned the trip,
when Dad died.
I didn't realise he was there.
Oh, yes. Rupert was there.
He was great then.
Brilliant, really.
Dealt with everything.
Then he disappeared?
Yes.
Well...
We all have our own ways
of dealing with things.
I won't disappear.
I know.
We're a team, right?
- I'm going to go to bed.
- You go. I'll do this.
Not too long. You've got that test
tomorrow, remember.
Ruby?
What's the matter?
I don't know what he wants.
He won't tell me.
Who? Ruby, where are you?
Baltic Stairs.
You got that?
Let me speak to her.
I want to know she's all right.
She won't be. Unless you come
on your own.
I want to talk to her!
And that means without... Galvin.
Ruby!
# Ruby, Ruby, Ruby
- What?
- On his way. Guvnor.
# Ruby, Ruby, Ruby, Ruby #
Do you know who I am?
(GROWLING)
Do you have... any idea
what has befallen you?
You have entered a world of sorrow.
Dark streets,
rain falling on cobbles.
All...
Comfort...
Fled.
The thin taste of anguish
and despair.
In short, girly...
you have entered my world.
Gladiolus Thrip...
at your service.
Are you getting anything?
Don't you just hate that?
How can you respect an individual
who doesn't use the john,
just hawks it all up?
It's an old building.
Somewhere near water,
down by the river, I think.
- Anything else?
- Yeah.
Another face, a shadow,
right near the end.
I think I know who it is.
His name's Thrip.
- Hmmm.
- You know him?
Yeah. Type 12, bounty hunter.
Do you think you can locate him?
I think so.
Thrip is nasty but he's not stupid.
Ruby will be OK until he gets
his hands on Luke.
Luke is safe home, right?
Of course.
Don't worry.
You're safe. I've got you.
I'm sorry, dear boy, forgive me.
But your face.
It's a picture.
Gladiolus Thrip, at your service.
Where's Ruby?
- What have you done with her?
- Oh, quite safe. Quite safe.
Just had to make sure you'd do
as you were told.
The smiter smit, eh, Mr Redlip?
Well?
Is he on his own?
There's a thing.
Good boy.
You said if I came on my own,
you wouldn't hurt her.
No, I think we said if you didn't
come on your own, we would hurt her!
Subtle distinction, but I'm a bit
of a stickler.
Where is she?
You want to know where she is?
Hold out your hands
and I'll show you.
Come along.
My word is my bond.
We're only going to cuff you.
Cuff him, Mr Redlip.
Like taking sweetbreads from a baby.
She's right... beneath you.
Put the gun down or forever
know my wrath, you freak.
Whoopee.
Well done, Mr Galvin.
That's more like it.
Forever know my wrath, eh?
Marvellous.
Oh, shut up, Gladys, you cancerous
piece of garbage.
Sticks and stones, Mr Galvin.
Sticks and stones.
So have we come to negotiate?
Is that the style of the thing?
Oh, I don't negotiate with freaks.
I just grade 'em and I smite 'em.
And very well you do it,
if I might say.
Mind you... that said,
we all have a trick or two
up our sleeves.
Ohhh.
Scary.
My turn.
Where's Ruby?
Thrip said she was down there
under the grate. Come on!
Come on.
Let her go.
Of course. It's you I want.
Put - the - gun - down!
I don't trust you.
Trust?
This isn't about trust, matey.
It's about me stabbing her in the
neck if you don't do as I tell you.
Shoot, Luke. She'll be OK.
What?
Shoot her,
and then shoot him.
You must believe, Luke.
Even when it seems impossible.
Bring it on, laddie.
If you think
you've got the oomph, that it.
Oh dear.
Smiters aren't what they were.
Ruby.
Get off! You shocked me.
She's fine.
She's OK.
Thanks, Mina.
- No problem.
You shocked me with
a sodding raygun!
- You did well last night.
- You think so?
Yes, I do.
How's Ruby?
She yelled all
the way home because I shot her,
And make me buy a pizza
for the breakfast.
You know what i'm saying?
Very good.
Here, I....
I have something yours.
Where did you get this?
***
you have been diagnosed with
very rare condition
*** syndrome,
When you made it to be
released at the moment
and notice your private psychisian.
And who is he?
Professor Rubert E. Galvin
What "e" stands for?
Expensive.
Tell****or i'll may wich to find***
keep it with you at all times.
Oh, and... Rubbish Smiler.
Check under the bed, don't forget,
they bite!
777. You dream very well note.
Mr. Rutherford.
Did you actually do any
revisions for your test?
Yeah
- Some.
- Congratulatons, you hid it well.
- Have you considered extra tuitions?
- No,
- I haven't thought...
- Well you should.
Sorry.
Hello? I have to take this.
This is real life, you do.
Do you hear me?
Transcript: chocolate
Sync: innuit