All this training you're making me do...
did you have to do it?
Don't be ridiculous.
I like to focus on my mental agility.
I guess that's what happens when you get old.
You have to hand it to them.
They've got balls.
Sadly...no brains.
And there's no way they can get in here, OK?
You ready?
After you.
After you!
This is quite a gathering. Who sent you?
Say what?
You heard me correctly.
Play nicely. You ain't playing nicely, man.
No kidding. Who sent you?
What did you do that for?
You got an attitude problem, you know that?
My boss told me - "Rupert
Galvin, he's twisted."
Boss?
You disrespect my tail, you disrespect me.
You're damn right I disrespect you.
OK, let's start again, huh?
Who sent you?
Tibbs.
Mister Tibbs to you.
Where is he?
I ain't telling you that.
Three, two...
I didn't quite get that.
Liberty Hall.
He's at Liberty Hall.
You...said you wouldn't kill me if I told you.
No, I never said that. Luke, did I say that?
I don't think so.
Shame.
What was all that about?
Who's Tibbs?
Nobody important.
Deal with it tomorrow.
You got a concert to go to?
What are you going to do?
Nothing. Research. Go on. Have a good night.
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:FRS@»®¿Õ¹â½£
Demons S01 EP03
Hiya.
An evening of culture wouldn't kill you, you know.
Sorry, I got caught up.
??Where? The pub?
Would I rather be with a beer than
my two favourite ladies?
Three favourite ladies.
I wouldn't go that far.
Mina, this is my mum, Jenny.
It's a pleasure. Luke has missed a real treat.
I didn't realise you had such talented friends.
Oh, thank you!
You missed the action.
I wouldn't say that.
Well, why don't you walk me to the
car? You can make up for it.
Lovely to meet you, Jenny.
She's very beautiful in the part, isn't she?
So, what happened? I thought
Chopin was your favourite.
You know he is. He's just not quite as
appealing as a run-in with the Noisy Boys.
Oh dear.
They were trying to break into the Stacks.
Quite a mission for a Type Four.
It wasn't their idea.
Is Galvin concerned?
We've got a name and address. We'll
deal with it tomorrow. Tibbs or something.
What did you say?
Tibbs or something.
Where exactly did you leave Galvin?
In the Stacks.
Doing what?
Research.
I'll be back in a minute.
Hey. Listen...I know I said we'd
get a drink, but I've got to go.
Oh, Luke! We haven't seen you all evening.
I know, sorry. Mina's invited me clubbing.
- I'll come.
- Oh, Ruby!
Well...if it's all right? Well...
Great.
Oh, dear. Is she crashing your date?
I'll see you soon.
OK. Bye.
I don't know what you're so worried
about. Galvin was fine when I left.
He was going to potter round the Stacks.
Galvin, potter?
Please. Do you have any idea who Mr Tibbs is?
No, I haven't been told.
Mr Tibbs is the half-life
that killed Galvin's wife.
Where are the guns?
How long has he been gone?
Dunno. An hour, two maybe.
Great.
What time is it?
Five minutes since you last asked.
??Should I have a gun?
Not now, Ruby.
No. Not now.
When we get there.
- I've got it covered.
- He's got it covered.
Well, what is the problem?
You're not trained.
And you're in the SAS now?
Children!
I want to be able to cover your back.
You can cover my back.
With what? Marmalade? Luke, I need a gun.
You cannot have a gun.
Why not?
Because I've only got one.
What?
Galvin took the rest.
Right, let me get this straight.
We're about to go and fight one of the most
dangerous creatures in the half-life
with a blind woman, two teenagers, and...one gun.
You got a problem with that?
Get back.
Ruby, hold them off.
- What?
- Just point and shoot.
Ruby, shoot!
What did you think you were doing?
Taking tea, obviously.
Is that what Maggie would have wanted?
For you to be killed by the
same low-life that got her?
I'll forgive you your rational mind, Mina.
Yeah, well, I won't forgive you your
balls. Too often they rule your brain.
You want a drink?
It's a bit early for me.
That rule doesn't apply when
you've been up all night.
Are you planning on getting any rest?
No.
Ever?
Until he's dead.
I'm sorry, Rupert.
Why are you sorry? You were right.
I know how you feel.
But Maggie wouldn't want you -
You know, it's been 20 years since Maggie died,
and there's not a day goes by
that I don't think about her.
What will you do if you find Tibbs?
If you kill him, will you be happy -
Hey. How are you feeling?
I didn't think so.
He's not here. You're going to be fine.
You're safe.
Luke, Ruby.
OK, this is what we're up against. Tobias Tibbs.
A Grade 11 entity.
These don't look too hot.
So what's his quirk?
Psychopath.
He's a rat that experiments on
humans. He thinks it's funny.
It's hilarious. Is that what happened to - ?
Grace? Presumably.
Have you managed to get
any information out of her?
Her name.
Maybe we should push her a bit.
I think she's been through enough.
Yes, well, I need to go back to
the factory to get a reading. Luke?
Will you be all right?
Are you looking after me now?
Sometimes I wish I could turn these visions off.
Here, take my arm.
You don't get flashbacks
when you touch me, do you?
Why? What have you been up to?
Do you think Grace was a normal person once?
A missing person.
That's exactly what she is.
The police keep a database of missing persons.
A fair percentage - casualties of the half-life.
And the rest?
Well, humans can be pretty nasty too.
Yeah.
Is that what happened to your wife? Tibbs took her?
Is that why you became a smiter?
What happened?
I don't know. By the time
I found her, she was dead.
Yeah, well, you should be freaked out, Ruby.
You could have been killed last night.
You could have got us all killed.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
And your luck is going to run out eventually.
Maybe you should jump ship before it does.
And go back to what?
I don't know. Play netball.
Whatever girls of your age do.
Have a normal life.
I don't want a normal life.
I know what you want, Ruby.
But it's not going to happen. You can't
just smite your way into Luke's heart.
The sooner you realise that, the better.
I've never seen Galvin so angry.
I mean, it's not like
he's a relaxed kind of guy.
I suppose this is different.
You're not old enough to have enemies, Luke.
Not...real ones.
But you will, one day.
There's something to look forward to.
What were you hoping for? Wife, kids?
Not yet.
Not ever.
You don't mean that.
Why not? Families aren't exactly
compatible with our life style.
I think I've proved that. Galvin's proved that.
Life could get a bit dull on my own.
I'm sure it will. But you'll
find something to fill the gap.
Is that why you play the piano?
That's why Galvin drinks.
Maybe you could become addicted to exercise.
Great.
Now you understand why Galvin's so angry.
He had someone.
Give me your hand.
I'll see you later.
Luke...
Sorry if I upset you earlier.
It's cool. I understand.
I'm looking forward to a lifetime
of Saturday nights down the gym.
I'll see you later.
OK.
What you doing here?
I need to ask you something.
I've got to get back.
Do you want me around?
What do you mean do I want you around?
Galvin...thinks I'm better
off out of the action.
That you need to do this on your own.
Yeah, a lot of people seem to think that.
Well...I don't care about them.
What do you think? Just...
You just say the word and I'll be off.
You know I like having you around.
- ??
- It's dangerous.
What if something serious happened to you?
You're even starting to sound like him.
Yeah? Well, maybe he's right.
I don't want any of this,
but I don't have a choice.
You do.
Why would you want to hang around?
You really don't know?
No.
Take care.
Hello.
You all right?
I'll make you something proper, if you like.
No time.
How was the club?
What club?
The club you spent the entire night in with Mina.
Yeah, it was good, you know.
Yes, I think I know.
I do vaguely remember what it was
like to be young, free and single.
You are free. You are single.
You have lunch when you want.
You can date who you want.
What exactly is so difficult about your life?
Luke!
I'm sorry.
I've had a long night.
I've got a bad feeling about
this. Something is not right.
What do you mean? You got
the location, didn't you?
What are you worried about?
It's too easy.
You know sometimes, Mina,
you love to create problems.
I'm going after him and I'm going to kill him.
I'm not trying to stop you,
just be patient. We need more time.
We have no more time.
OK, I want you to stay here with Mina.
When I get back, we'll think of a better plan.
Please don't leave me. He'll come.
No, he won't. You're perfectly safe.
He's not stupid. He'll find me.
I can't go back there!
Grace, listen to me.
I'm going to kill him. But for
that to happen, I need to leave -
No, you can't leave me!
You'll be fine, trust me. Mina -
Mina's blind! How can she help me?
Please, take me somewhere safe.
Come on.
OK. No half-life has ever penetrated these walls.
You'll be perfectly safe.
Hell, we've even got a coffee machine.
I can't work coffee machines.
Well, apart from refreshments...
you'll be just fine, OK?
Thank you.
Galvin, I don't like this.
You ready?
Let's go catch us a rat.
Let's go kill us a rat.
He'll be back soon.
And this will all be over.
I'm not so sure.
Grace, I know you've been through a lot.
But it's time to move on with your life now.
I'm not thinking too much about MY life.
Well, you should.
Right now...
I'm thinking about yours.
Mine?
Oh, absolutely.
Tobias!
MISTER Tibbs.
No half-life has ever penetrated these walls!
Well, I am privileged.
And so are you.
After all, few people...
get to witness such a... momentous occasion.
Poor Galvin.
He'll be very cross when he finds out.
Very cross. And then very dead.
Such a shame. Ah!
This is mine, I fancy.
I'm done.
Yes, my dear.
I rather think you are.
He's not here, I'm afraid.
It's OK, I don't need to speak to him.
Will you just give him this, please?
Right. No message?
No.
No love left between you two?
No love left.
Ruby.
Coffee?
Is this what I think it's about?
I dunno. Probably not.
I know you and Luke... have been friends forever.
There was always going to come a time
when... other things intervened.
Things that...come into
conflict with that friendship.
What do you mean?
Well, just because Luke's going
down a different path...
doesn't mean he thinks any less of you.
A different path?
What's he told you?
He doesn't have to tell me anything.
- Oh, in that case
- I just know.
Right...
Are you...sure you know?
Mums have a sixth sense about these things.
I see.
What do you mean...by a sixth sense?
I don't think I need to explain that, do I?
No, I guess not.
Wow. I'd really no idea.
Does Luke know? I mean...
Does he know that you know?
Ohhh, he's worried.
He snapped at me earlier.
He snapped at me too.
Ah well, it's difficult for him.
Yeah, I guess.
I know it's not an ideal situation, and...
well, maybe the whole thing will
fall through of its own accord.
Are you sure?
Well, it can't be easy dating someone...
with a disability.
Sorry. What did you say?
Mina. Luke's worried about
Mina's blindness, I know he is.
He gave me this whole speech earlier
about how easy my life was,
and how I didn't have anything
difficult to deal with,
and well, I suppose when you
compare my life to hers, he's right.
Right. Let me get this
straight. Your sixth sense...
tells you that Luke is worried
about dating a blind woman?
Yeah.
Nothing else?
No.
Why? He's not on drugs, is he?
No, he's not.
He hasn't been eating much recently.
I'm not sure that makes you a smack-head.
I wish you'd have told me
it was going to be like this.
These are my best trainers.
What exactly did you think it would be like?
It's a sewer.
I know you have the body beautiful, but, ah...
surely it functions like everybody else's,
or do you pass pure perfumed piss?
Yeah, I bottle it and sell it down the market.
It's not like there's any money in smiting.
That is true.
I understand why you do what you
do, Galvin. I know what drives you.
What's supposed to drive me?
My boot up your ass if you don't keep moving.
I love these conversations we have.
Luke...I ma cross with you, but...
I just have to tell you about this
conversation I had with your mum.
She is a legend.
You see, that's the problem...
Things...happen, and I always just
want to talk to you about them.
We should...talk, there are...
things I have to say.
Things I probably should
have said a long time ago.
I'm going to come find you, OK?
It doesn't make sense.
This is where Mina said.
This is it exactly.
Did we take a wrong turn?
There are no other turns!
All right. Calm down. We'll find him.
Hopefully before he finds us.
That is unlikely.
Mina doesn't make mistakes.
Unless...
Unless?
Yeah, Tibbs is here.
Or he wants us to think he's here.
He wanted us to find the handkerchief.
Shoot.
Luke...
Luke.
You see, the thing is...
I'm an alien. I've been meaning to tell you.
It's no use. It's completely blocked.
It's completely blocked off
because he knew we were coming.
It's a trap, Luke.
A rat trap, one might say.
Good evening, Mr Galvin.
Have I got you flustered?
What a predicament.
Still, as the saying goes,
things could only get worse,
Or is it better?
Well, I've planned for them to get worse.
These London sewers may be old,
but they really are rather sophisticated.
This chamber you're in, for
example, is COMPLETELY isolated.
Really? You don't say?
There you've already worked that out.
But what you may not have realised is
that little pool of water you're standing in
is about to rise.
You see, at peak times down here in the sewers,
all your little human friends
are scurrying home from work,
going to the toilet, taking a shower.
All 11 million of them. That's one big shower.
Yes, very amusing, Mr Rutherford.
You're a welcome addition to the team.
One big shower - as you
so rightly point out -
is exactly what you're about to experience.
I don't think so. We've got friends.
People who know where we are.
Friends?
I'm not entirely familiar with the concept.
Oh! You mean that nice blind girl.
No. Sorry. She won't be arriving to help -
- You so much as put a fin
- I haven't! I promise!
Relax.
But...in 18 minutes and 32 seconds, she
and the Stacks will be blown to smithereens.
It's a very impressive
library that, by the way.
It won't be nearly so easy to
catch half-lives without it.
But wait.
There won't be anyone left to catch half-lives.
Oh dear.
He's lying, right?
No, I fear Grace may not be as
virtuous as the name suggests.
Oh, she was once.
After being stuck in your company for
so many years, and locked up in a cage,
well, you managed to reduce her to
what -a low-life, stinking little rat?
Just like yourself.
That hot-headed, sharp tongue of
yours will get you killed, Mr Galvin.
As it did your wife!
Good night, children.
Sweet dreams.
Luke. You see, the thing is,
we've been friends for ages.
Too long. I mean...
well, not too long, but...
just friends for too long.
And it's the just friends thing that I wanted...
Luke.
I want your body.
Mina?
Mina!
Mina! Mina!
Great. The only time I actually want you awake...
Mina!
Hi, it's Luke, Please leave a message.
Luke! I...
I think we've learnt one thing.
Mina's second sight is rubbish.
It's not entirely her fault.
I mean, what's the point if this is what happens?
If we ever get out of here...
Yeah, and she's still alive.
Here, hold this.
Think, Ruby.
Think, think, think.
Genius.
That's...
'Bingo'.
Bingo?
Keep calm.Keep calm.
Genius!
Explosive Devices. Bingo.
I take it there's nothing down there.
There's plenty down there.
All she had to do was check the facts.
It would have taken five minutes.
- It's not Mina's fault.
- Then whose?
It's mine, OK?! It's my fault!
Mina was worried about what she was seeing.
She wanted more time to do
research. I wouldn't let her.
She knew it was a trap?
Well, she didn't know.
She was suspicious.
Why did she let us come down here?
She didn't. I did.
I didn't take her advice.
I had to find him, Luke.
I just wanted him dead.
Yeah, well, it seems like
the feeling's mutual.
Only he doesn't let his heart rule his head.
Your turn.
It would be a really good time for
some scientific consensus, people!
??
"Extricate the bomb casing."
Done.
"Isolate the timing device." Done.
"Locate the power source."
Locate...the power source.
"There many different types of
explosive..." blah, blah blah.
???
"Two wires...or four wires?"
Two wires...or four wires?
Two wires! We're cooking on gas.
"In the case of two wires...
isolate and sever the red wire."
Since you came into my life,
everything has gone wrong.
I'm 18 years old, Galvin, and I'm about to drown.
Does that mean anything to you?
Did you think about me when
you decided to come down here?
No.
You never do.
You think I'm some kind of weapon.
Send Luke in.
We don't need to tell him what's going on.
I'll be the brains.
No, you're right.
I got Maggie killed and now
I've done the same thing to us.
It wasn't Maggie's death
that made me a smiter.
It's because I'm a smiter
that she got killed.
We were on a mission. Me and your dad.
We were after a Type 15, a Loup Garou.
The closer I got, the more obsessed I became.
Some things don't change.
He led us around town but...
we couldn't get a finger on him.
Maggie never even entered my head.
When I got home, she wasn't there.
There was a monogrammed handkerchief on the bed.
Tobias Tibbs.
It wasn't your fault, Galvin.
It was entirely my fault.
I took my eye off the ball.
Now I've done it again.
Luke, ah...
I've only got time to make one phone
call, so I'm making it to you.
I want to be cremated.
I...I don't know why I'm telling you that.
I'm about to be blown to smithereens
and the chance of there being any...
Anyway...
there's something I want to tell you
and there's only 30 seconds left.
Luke Rutherford, you're a prat.
You're a prat, but...
I love you.
Ohh, yes!
Yes! Yes!
Ruby, keep it down.
Mina, we're alive.
This - was a bomb.
Where's Galvin?
I've no idea.
And Luke?
Oh, Luke.
I have a horrible feeling
I know exactly where they are.
Caught up in one big rat trap.
What do you think will happen?
What, to the world?
No. Forget the world.
To us.
We're going to drown.
Yeah.
Yeah, but...what will actually happen?
I've no idea.
You know, Luke, um...
I know you don't think too highly
of me right now, but, ah...
If we're going to die...
there's one thing I want you to know.
We probably haven't got that long.
I do care about you.
It may not seem that way, but it's true.
You just have a funny way of showing it.
What do you want, birthday cards?
Little chocolate rabbits at Easter? What?
You know, your whole life I've been
watching you. Soccer matches, judo bouts...
Even choir practice.
Oh no.
Yeah, that was a mistake.
You've been following me for 18 years.
I lost count. I hoped it would come
across as caring rather than creepy.
It doesn't.
I knew one day that they'd find you.
If they were going to hurt you,
they'd have to hurt me first.
When they turned up at your school...
I was there.
I know.
I made a promise that, ah...
I'd never let anything happen to you.
It's kind of ironic then.
Yeah, well, we're...
we're not big on irony back home.
Sorry, am I going too fast for you?
Ruby...
I wanted to say thank you.
You saved my life.
I just smiled at you, by the way.
In case you couldn't tell.
???
This is going to have to be
a pretty swift vision, Mina.
What can you see? Can you feel anything?
Mina, really, really, we need to hurry up now.
Tibbs was here.
Yeah, I could have worked that out for myself.
Mina, I...I really need
you to do something...??
I'm trying.
He was here...
- ??
Have you got it? ??
Exactly here.
??
What's happening?
Oh, we did it.
Now give that damn signal.
Well, you guys really are in the sh...
Yes, thank you, Ruby.
OK?
Right.
What?
Nothing...
Good night?
I'm sorry I snapped at you before.
I had stuff on my mind.
It's what I'm here for.
You are just like your father, you know.
Handsome? Witty? Intelligent?
No.
You smell...
strange.
He used to do that. He used to rock
up in the middle of the night,
smelling strange...with no explanation.
You don't want an explanation.
That is exactly what he used to say.
Why did you put up with it?
It wasn't a case of putting up with it.
It was just him.
All part of the deal.
You didn't want him to change?
I wouldn't go that far.
But you loved him anyway?
Yeah.
And whatever he did to make him smell that bad...
He loved you too.
Yeah.
Do you miss him?
Of course.
But you're glad you had him. I mean...
even though he was never there and...
he put you in danger, and he smelled bad.
I don't think he ever put me in danger.
You never knew?
What?
Then it didn't matter.
Luke...
Then it is possible.
Thanks, Mum.
Luke...
Are you on drugs?
No.
Are you OK?
I'm glad he didn't do that to
Maggie. I'm glad she died quickly.
Does that sound strange?
No.
So are you going to let this go now?
Is he dead yet?
I've had enough of vengeance.
For now, anyway.
Are you sure you showered properly?
Like 10 times.
Well, maybe take a bath or...
get a new layer of skin?
Here. I got you a new phone.
Thank you.
Well, Ruby...
I guess you saved the day.
It was nothing.
OK then.
Well...obviously, it wasn't entirely
nothing. I did rescue you all.
You did a good job. I'm very proud of you.
'I just have to tell you about this
conversation I had with your mum.'
Hey, Ruby.
So does that mean that you'll
be happy to have me around?
Let's not get carried away, huh?
Hey, Ruby.
Have you been talking to my mum?
- What?
- You left me a message.
What's my mum been saying?
Oh, wait, I've got another.
'Luke Rutherford, you're a prat.'
You called me a prat.
- '...I love you.'
- Really?
Well, I always think clearly under
pressure. That's why you need me.
There are vampires in town.
Why would I lie to you?
Why are we watching Mina?
She's been here longer than you think.
I need to know what it says about Mina.
She's a boring bitch we can do without.
He's the last Van Helsing. He'll
have to fight vampires sometime.
Join me.
Galvin! Galvin!
welcome to www.1000fr.com