Here's Joe.
Joe, nice to see you.
Nice to see you. Good to see you.
- Commander, how are you?
- How are you?
And that's why men like Joe are
the future of British policing.
No pressure there then.
Keep back.
Do not come any... closer.
Listen, you've been told once.
I don't want to tell you again.
We need bold initiatives
in community partnerships
to ensure good practice
within a management framework.
This is about the effective delivery
of sanctions to the stakeholders.
Stakeholders?
Five years ago we simply
called them criminals.
Excuse me, excuse me.
- Night.
- See you tomorrow.
My God!
I've got you, love.
You're going to be all right.
PCSO Bousfield to control.
Receiving, over.
Receiving you, Mary. Go ahead.
Immediate assistant
and an ambulance required
at the old board school
off Commercial Street.
There you go, love.
Christ have mercy.
Fitz, coffee no sugar.
- Two teabags, Skip.
- Thanks.
- Usual, McCormack.
- People can't die at a decent time?
Got your own crappuccino
there, Kent?
Right, what have we got?
Let's get suited and booted, boys.
All impressed with you in there.
The good money's on you
making commander in three years.
- That's very generous.
- All part of the plan, Joe.
- Yes, sir.
- No need to be formal.
It's what your father wanted.
He'd be proud.
We've got a dead woman
in Whitechapel.
Probable domestic. No DI.
- Bit of a rough squad.
- I'll take it.
- Ready to head up your 1st murder?
- Absolutely.
Good lad.
Once you've ticked that box
we can move you on.
Get you out of the trenches and up
to headquarters where you belong.
- I don't know what to say.
- How about thank you?
Thank you, sir.
Excellent.
Commander Anderson's
sending us a new DI.
Good.
- Cos we don't know what we're doing.
- Another fast-tracker.
Had I've have known,
I'd have made vol-au-vents.
I'll tell the others.
Now that's a good look.
- DI Chandler.
- DS Miles.
We'll get you suited up. This way.
The victim's name was Cathy Lane.
43 years old. Mother of three.
Separated from her partner.
She was found around 2 am
by a community support officer.
Cathy was still alive
then but by the time the emergency
services got to her she was dead.
- Who identified her?
- We all did. Let's go.
Have you worked
a murder scene before?
I'm not a virgin, you know.
I've had my fair share.
Oh, well, you'll be laughing then.
Streak of piss.
- Hello, Ray.
- We've got to stop meeting like this.
Wouldn't be the same
without a dead body between us.
- Morning.
- DI Chandler.
Can you see the cuts to her throat?
On the side here
we have the first incision.
There is a second cut,
more decisive, right round.
This is a deep one. Seems to go
all the way through to the vertebrae.
- Do you want to get a look at this?
- No, I'm good, I'm good.
- There's not much blood.
- No, it doesn't look like much.
I know what you're thinking,
she was dumped but you'd be wrong.
It's all here. It's soaked
into her clothing. She's sodden.
It's Interesting,
there's no struggle.
There's a bruise here
and more on the other side with...
small petechial haemorrhages
around the eyes,
suggesting asphyxia.
I think she was strangled first
and this is how he dropped her.
Just a snapshot
based on obvious injuries.
Patience.
I want a plan of the area.
Fitzgerald and McCormack
are doing that.
Witnesses.
Mary Bousfield, Community
Support Officer. This way.
I saw a man with a long knife.
He was over 40. Dark coat.
About 5'10".
Posh but shabby.
- Had a funny hat.
- Funny, how?
Funny, unusual.
- Had flaps.
- Did you see his face?
I'm really sorry. I know police
aren't supposed to cry.
I cry all the time, Mary.
You should see my mascara run.
Thanks.
Let 'em get her off to hospital.
Cathy Lane was a battered woman.
She split from her partner 6 years ago.
Always arguing about money for the kids.
He wouldn't pay
while she lived with other men.
They'd have too much to drink,
have huge rows.
We were constantly banging him up
in the cells for the night.
Once he stuck a potato peeler
in her head. Bang, like that.
- I knew we'd find her dead one day.
- Who is this guy?
Rob Lees.
He's a butcher.
- Works with long sharp knives.
- Let's go and talk to Rob Lees then.
Don't you have a desk to go to?
No... I don't.
Let's go.
- There you go, guv'nor. Lovely.
- Cheers, thanks.
Police.
Can I have a word, please, sir?
- Hello, Jim.
- Got a new boy?
You'll get me into trouble.
He's the boss.
Can I help you, sir?
- Rob Lees.
- Rob's not here.
- Do you know where he is?
- Nah.
His mobile's switched off
and he's not picking up at home.
Has he been at Cathy again?
- Is she all right?
- She's dead.
Has Rob got a woolly hat?
- A woolly hat.
- No, he wears one of those...
furry Russian things with flaps.
Get Rob Lees' flat watched.
Can we find out
where his mobile is right now
and get someone down to his local?
He is, I know. But what can you do?
We'd better get a move on.
Before we go anywhere can we get
something straight?
- I'm in charge of this investigation.
- I'm just showing you the ropes, son.
I didn't expect this.
Welcome to hell, gentlemen.
I think the killer knelt by her head,
held her with his left hand,
then cut her throat left to right
with his right hand.
The blood would've
run away from him.
There are no cuts to her clothing so
I assume her skirt was pushed up.
The community support pulled her skirt
down but she thought she'd been raped.
Take swabs but I haven't seen
any physical signs of rape.
And here's the surprise.
It's as if he's tried to gut her.
On the left-hand side, two inches
in, we have a deep, jagged wound.
On the right-hand side there are
four more cuts.
The stomach has been
cut in several places, and
the intestines have been exposed.
I think he stayed at his position
at her head,
stabbed down, then draw the knife
towards himself quite violently.
These cuts were done quickly.
I'd say the whole attack
would have been over in a few minutes.
- She wouldn't have known what hit her.
- Rob Lees is what hit her.
- What can you tell us about the weapon?
- It has a strong blade.
Long? Like something
you use for butchering meat?
The thing is, skin stretches and
soft tissues compress
It's hard to talk about knife size.
- I can only speculate very generally.
- So speculate for me.
Something like a hunting knife.
- Or a boning knife?
- I can't rule it out.
Thanks, sweetheart.
And there he is. Half the division
out looking for him,
Rob Lees turns up on his own doorstep
looking like ten kinds of shit.
Been up all night,
smells like a pub.
- Tell your mum you'll be home for tea.
- Excellent.
- What are you doing?
- Going to interview the suspect.
Why? DIs are supposed to sit behind
their desk and drink herbal tea.
I'll treat it as an office outing.
Look, I know this guy.
He's a liar, he's a manipulator.
And what's worse,
he knows his rights.
So sit in if you have to,
that's your prerogative.
But I'm asking you to let me do
what I'm good at.
OK... sir?
Fine. But I want this resolved
as much as you do.
So we do this together. We get it
right and we get it over with.
OK, boys, phones off.
That's my seat.
And that's my seat in there
but we're all making sacrifices.
This interview is being recorded and
conducted at Whitechapel police station.
The time is 10:15am.
The date is 31 August 2008.
I am Detective Sergeant Ray Miles.
The other officer present is...
Detective Inspector Joseph Chandler.
- The solicitor present is...
- Lydia Hart.
Please state your full name
and date of birth.
Robert Lees. 11 March 1972.
You do not have
to say anything but...
Sanders, shut up.
- Do you understand the caution?
- Yeah, I understand.
Where were you this morning at 2am?
Drunk tank. Charing Cross.
I got a ten-copper alibi.
It checks out. They were looking in on
him every half hour for the whole night.
Where's the new DI?
Probably with the commander begging
for a transfer.
Arts and Antiques Squad.
Never got the chance to know him.
Well, we won't miss hello.
Got to be a record that.
Shortest-serving DI.
Rob Lees is no longer a suspect.
Everybody. Listen, everybody, Rob
Lees is no longer a suspect.
Now that we...
Now that we no longer
have Rob Lees as a suspect...
Now that Rob Lees
is no longer part of this...
Is no longer a s... Yeah.
Now that Rob Lees
is no longer a s...
We've got to start over.
We've got a description of the suspect,
so let's find him on CCTV.
He's wearing a hat with flaps, so he
should stick out like a sore thumb.
- Sanders, you're good at watching TV.
- I am.
You take first shift on that.
Fitz, draw up a rota.
Right, Rob Lees has been
eliminated from this inquiry.
We start afresh. Consider this
a new investigation.
I need some chalk.
I might have some.
I can wait.
As long as it takes.
Teacher's pet, arse licker.
- Thank you... Kent.
- Kent.
Thank you, Kent.
Right, our suspect is in his 40s,
average height and build.
Dark complexion,
wearing a hat with ear flaps.
It's a distinctive look so...
let's start with CCTV opportunities
and find this guy.
- Great idea. We'll start tomorrow.
- No, we start now.
End of shift. Unless you're
authorising double time.
Oi.
Sorry.
Oh, dear God.
What's his name? Spell it for me.
Phwoar. Who's let off?
You're a detective. Work it out.
Tell him to wait upstairs.
Got a bloke upstairs, says he knows
everything about the murder.
Miles.
I beg your pardon?
In your own time, Mr Buchan.
She was lying on her back...
skirts pulled up.
She looked like she was drunk.
Her throat was cut and her stomach
had been mutilated.
- You saw the mutilation?
- Not exactly.
Where were you standing
when you saw her body?
I wasn't there.
Mary Ann Nichols was the first
canonical victim of Jack the Ripper
and she died on 31st August 1888.
So? Jesus Christ.
31 August. Same date,
same time of night.
She also died next
to a board school.
- I was describing her injuries to you.
- I don't bloody believe this.
My book.
It has all the canonical murders and
some other events I think were linked.
I think the man who killed your lady
was copying Jack the Ripper.
I'll bet she was lying on her back,
head pointing east, eyes open,
hands by her sides, palms open,
legs out straight, slightly parted.
- A perfect re-creation.
- You're a Ripperologist, aren't you?
Why, yes, I am. And I also host
an excellent Ripper tour.
A lot of the tour operators promote
inaccurate theories.
I pride myself on my strict
adherence to the known facts.
Here's a fact. You're a loser.
Now get out before I nick you
for wasting police time.
Keep the book. It'll help you predict
what the killer will do next.
There are at least 4 more deaths
to come if I'm right.
Out!
You should be grateful.
I'm giving you a head start.
They never caught the Ripper. Time and
history have spirited his identity away.
- Get out.
- Thank you for your time.
Every time there's a stabbing
in Whitechapel
they come crawling out
of the woodwork.
I hate Ripperologists.
Right.
- Forensics.
- There's nothing.
No prints, no fibres,
no DNA. Nothing.
- Witnesses.
- Nobody heard anything.
Well, they all knew there was a fire,
they heard the fire engines.
No one heard a scream,
a struggle, nothing.
Well, Mary Bousfield's a witness.
Talk to her, see if she remembers
anything else. Friends and family?
Well, everyone I spoke to
was very upset.
There were no enemies. No motive.
Right, so we've got no physical
evidence, no witnesses,
no known... no known motive.
Right.
I want everything done again.
Knock on every door,
talk to Cathy's friends,
go through CCTV again.
How can you conduct
an inquiry like this?
Look at the state of you,
look at your desks.
There could be actions here.
Clean it up and log it in.
I want paperless desks.
Use your bins, you see?
Use your bins.
And empty them
at the end of every night.
Who's the office manager here?
Well?
- I am, sir.
- Sort it out, McCormack.
It's a disgrace!
And haven't... haven't you
heard of showers?
Or irons. I mean, where are your ties?
Where's your tie?
- Get your feet off. Where's your tie?
- I'll get one.
It's no bloody surprise
that potential witnesses aren't talking.
You don't look professional.
And it smells in here!
Get yourselves organised.
Self-discipline, self-respect,
Deodorant. Go!
This is what real policemen
look like.
This is what real policemen smell like.
I wouldn't expect you to understand.
Your courses may look good on paper
but they count for nothing here.
We're not paper policemen!
This is a murder investigation,
not a beauty contest!
I think he's got obsessive
compulsive disorder.
Never known a man so obsessed
with cleanliness in my life.
Must be gay.
Do you think?
- I've got gaydar. I can tell.
- Going to have a shower then?
Am I going to have a shower?
Fresh as a daisy.
Oh, my God. I've found him!
I've found him!
This is from the camera at Puma
Court just before the murder.
There's the hat.
Looks like a deerstalker.
He looks like Sherlock Holmes.
- Or Jack the Ripper.
- Shut up, you nonce.
What's he wearing under his coat?
It's an apron.
You can keep the book.
It'll help you to predict
what the killer will do next.
There are at least four more deaths
to come if I'm right.
The Star's headline read
"Leather Apron".
The only name linked
with the Whitechapel murders.
A noiseless midnight terror.
A strange character who prowls
about Whitechapel after midnight.
Universal fear among the women.
There was a great fire the night
Mary A. Nichols died,
only streets away from where she had
her throat cut and body mutilated.'
Shit.
Hello!
Are you all here for the world-famous
Buchan's Guider Ripper Tour?
Good-o. If you'd all like to step in,
please. Save the old voice.
Now, we will be visiting all the
sites of the Ripper's murders
as well as some
of his regular haunts.
So I must ask
if everyone here is over 18.
- Are you over 18, young lady?
- Yes!
Good-o. Now...
This is a two-hour walk.
And it is not suitable for those
of a weak or squeamish disposition.
It will be dark.
It will be frightening.
And maybe tonight
we shall see someof the ghosts...
of Whitechapel.
OK, that's £10 per person, please.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, sir. Enjoy the tour.
We're going off-piste tonight.
None of the other tours come here.
They don't appreciate its significance.
This passageway was known
as George Yard
and it was here on a first-floor
landing on 7 August 1888
that a terrible discovery was made.
A woman, stabbed 39 times
and left to die.
Her name was Martha Tabram.
And she may have been
the Ripper's first victim.
Some Ripperologists discount her
since her throat wasn't cut,
nor was she mutilated.
She's not a Ripper victim, they say.
Doesn't fit the pattern.
A serial killer does not emerge
fully formed.
Even he must learn his craft.
And Jack learned quickly.
Let us visit the place where he
killed his first canonical victim,
Mary Ann Nichols!
I think this man has killed before.
I want to look for...
previous in the last
few months or so.
A murder with overkill. 39 stab
wounds to the torso and legs.
- And this is from where?
- It's an idea.
- 39 stab wounds is very specific.
- It might be nothing.
- It is. The Ripper's for tourists.
- You're ignoring the possibility...
- There was no murder like that.
- Are you sure?
Course I am. It's my job to know.
- Serious assault. Maybe she survived.
- You are kidding.
You've been given a job, will you...
just do it?
Sir.
Kent, there was a fire on the night
of the murder. It might be connected.
- Find out all you can.
- Yes, sir.
And it's not Father's Day, you're not
the world's greatest lover and...
What does IOFB mean?
I Only Fire Blanks.
The wife got it for me
after I got the snip.
Get them off.
No sense of humour,
that's his problem.
He don't want to be one of us.
He's like a wife who wants
to change all your bad habits.
Another plastic copper.
- Not a real detective.
- Sarge! I think you should see this.
Emma Jones. August 7.
She was found with a lump on her head
and 39 stab wounds.
- Spot on, sir.
- Did she identify her attacker?
She said he was young,
around 5'9" with dark hair
and she reckoned he was a soldier.
- Why?
- She saw tattoos.
- Thought they were regimental.
- Which regiment?
Sir, she was stabbed 39 times.
She couldn't really say.
A murder in a school yard,
an attempted murder by a squaddie.
- A connection?
- I want to talk to her.
- She's in hospital.
- Kent, come with me.
I've got to pack this in, buy a nice
wee pub in the country or something.
He doesn't look well.
I hate hospitals.
What do you think's wrong with him?
Excuse me, Dr Phillips, please.
I'm looking for Dr Phillips.
Are you sure?
Maybe I could help you?
Dr Phillips, please.
He's not here. I think he swapped
shifts with Dr Cohen.
- Maybe he can help you.
- Thank you.
I didn't treat Emma Jones
but I am aware of her case.
Does this account look familiar?
22 stab wounds to the trunk.
Left lung penetrated in five places,
the right lung in two.
Heart penetrated once.
Liver penetrated five times.
Spleen twice
and the stomach six times.
The wound on the breastbone
made a long instrument,
possibly a bayonet.
This is the attack on Emma Jones.
No, it happened over 100 years ago.
Yes, heart penetrated once. I see.
In Emma Jones's case
the knife glanced off the ribs.
- The heart was not pierced.
- Is that why she survived?
- That and the ambulance.
- I'd like to speak to her.
That's not possible.
She's in intensive care.
- Even so...
- In a coma.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Why would somebody copy
a hundred-year-old murder?
They never caught the Ripper.
Did they come close? Perhaps.
But we'll never know.
The real Jack probably committed
suicide after the last murder.
Maybe he plunged into the icy Thames
taking his secrets with him.
And we are left with his legacy -
the birth of the serial killer.
My book. An encyclopaedia of facts.
All the clues you need
to start your own hunt for Jack.
Will you be the one
to find the Ripper?
- Thank you very much.
- Oh, thank you.
That was very interesting.
Thank you. Good tour.
Guten Abend.
I normally get a few bites.
Wasn't on song tonight.
Too many Germans.
They don't give much back.
I like the Yanks. Great enthusiasm.
And they like a souvenir.
- Can I have a word?
- Absolutely.
You can buy me a drink.
So, I suppose you're
the Ripper's biggest fan.
I don't think fan is the right word.
I don't admire what he did.
You seem to enjoy the murders though.
All the details.
- You pretty much live it every night.
- Oh, dear.
I am a performer for the tourist
hordes, that is true, but...
in my heart I'm a detective,
like your fine self.
You know what's it's like,
the irresistible siren call
of a mystery, the...
delectable twist of a conundrum.
We are slaves to that delicious
eureka moment
when the scales fall away
and everything is laid bare.
There's no eureka moment
in what I do.
I follow the bloody footprints
and arrest the man holding the knife.
But that is tragic.
To be a detective
and not have the fire.
So you're more interested in being
a detective than a Ripper.
I'd be a poor man's Ripper.
Only able to dispatch small dogs
and ladies under five foot.
On the night of the murder,
I was watching my mother sing
with the church choir in aid
of the roof restoration fund.
I fell asleep and disturbed everyone
with my snoring.
Can you help me?
Yes.
The man who murdered Cathy Lane...
will kill again.
This is the pattern.
Emma Jones, stabbed 39 times.
7 August. Survived, just.
Martha Tabram, stabbed 39 times.
7 August 1888. Died.
Cathy Lane, throat cut, mutilated.
31 August.
Mary Ann Nichols, throat cut,
mutilated. 31 August 1888.
The man who attacked and killed these
women in 1888 was Jack the Ripper.
The man who's attacking
these women in 2008
is his biggest fan.
- We have a copycat.
- Here we go again.
Come on. This is your patch.
You should have spotted this.
You should be ashamed that it's taken
a plastic like me to work this out.
All right, all right.
- The Ripper only killed prostitutes.
- Correct.
So you think Emma and Cathy
were on the game?
- No.
- There's nothing to suggest
- either of them were toms.
- Good point.
Were they attacked
in the same place as his victims?
Those places no longer exist.
Theslums were cleared
and the roads changed.
With the greatest of respect,
these women were attacked
in unconnected locations
by different people.
A soldier in his 20s, about 5'9"
and a 40-something man
wearing a deerstalker hat.
Different people,
different location.
You had a theory but...
you're new to this and it's easy
to get carried away
with all the history in the area.
- Game over.
- Right, who's hungry?
The killer could be dressing up
to match the historical suspects.
Dressing up? So he's a perv then.
No. No, no, no, no.
So that the witness descriptions
match what the police had in 1888.
The police looked for a soldier
after Tabram's death.
The prime suspect with Jones's
stabbing is a soldier.
Prime suspect with Mary Ann Nichols,
a man in a leather apron.
Think about it.
The guy in the CCTV had an apron
under his coat.
I thought Jack the Ripper
had a black bag
a top hat and walked through smog.
I think that'd draw attention
in Brick Lane, don't you?
September 8th 1888, the next victim
was Annie Chapman.
I think on 8 September we'll have
a murder on Hanbury Street.
We need to be there to stop it.
- I've heard it all now.
- Total crap.
Joe, what you're proposing
goes against all procedures.
You gain nothing by chasing bogeymen
and you stand to lose everything.
- I can see a pattern emerging.
- You're ambitious, that's good,
but you're letting your ambition
cloud your judgement.
You want this murder to have meaning
because death should be significant,
but in truth most murders are banal.
- I'm not imagining this.
- Take my advice.
Step back a little. Detach yourself.
And if another woman dies?
Then we never had this conversation.
This obbo's a waste of time.
No one will get murdered tonight
by a copycat Jack the Ripper.
So eat up.
If my mother could see you now,
do you know what she'd say?
She'd say you shouldn't go
chase any suspects
till at least half an hour
after you've finished eating.
Half an hour? We'd be here
all night, mate.
Our historical murder
won't happen till 5am.
I thought I could eat
but you take the biscuit.
Come on. This is a farewell meal for
our good friend DI Chandler.
He gambled and he lost.
This is his last supper...
on expenses.
Can we have more beers?
When I eat curry I can smell it
on my pits the next day.
- Do you want one, sir?
- No, thanks.
You should. You look like
a copper on an obbo.
What he means, sir,
is that you need to relax,
Blend in. Make it look like.
Nothing remains
of no.29 Hanbury Street.
And this is as close
as we can get...
to where the body of Annie Chapman
was found in the back yard
on this very night in 1888.
And it was a terrible sight.
He didn't just cut her throat.
He tried to cut her head off.
He split her open and threw her
intestines over her shoulder...
like a grotesque scarf.
Not much left of poor Annie Chapman.
Just a few sad belongings
at her feet.
Moving on.
Good luck to you, sirs.
We should check him out.
He just seems to know
a lot about it.
It's his job.
Funny job.
Bloody waste of time,
resources and my patience.
I told you nothing'd happen.
As soon as we're stood down
I'm having a word with the commander.
I'm having a slash.
5am, Skip.
That's it for the DI then.
Not so much fast track
as bus fare home.
You going to call it then, sir?
I tried, didn't I?
- You did save a life tonight.
- Yeah.
I'll put it on my CV.
Where is he?
Number four, round the back.
Establish the perimeter.
Get Dr Llewellyn.
Get Miles and then follow me.
- DS Miles, come in, over.
- Skip.
- Skip, we're up.
- Oh, Jesus.
He took hold of her by the chin
and commenced the incision
from left to right.
An attempt had been made
to separate the bones of the neck.
The abdomen had been
entirely laid open.
The intestines lifted out
of the body...
and placed by the shoulder
of the corpse.
It's the Ripper.
- He was right, weren't he?
- Yeah.
Congratulations, you were right.
All you have to do now
is solve the unsolvable
and catch the most famous
serial killer that ever lived.
Good luck.
The double event is imminent.
The night he killed two women,
a soldier has been beating up girls
and threatening to gut them.
We've got a prime suspect.
You'll be the man
who captured the Ripper.
Transcript: Chocolate