(man) Even all these months
after Katrina ravaged New Orleans,
human remains are still being found in
devastated neighbourhoods across the city.
Cadaver dogs are being used to search
for 2300 people still unaccounted for.
Makeshift morgues still exist in warehouses,
schools, and churches throughout the area.
Officials are finally beginning to admit
what many people have known
since the levees broke long ago.
Many of these people will never be found.
- You look tired, Mike. Late night?
- Oh, yeah. Late and nasty.
- Same kinky creature?
- Doc, the girl carries a serious perv swerve.
Feeling wrong feels so good.
- Sorry, Dr Brennan.
- No, it's fine.
Males often bond
by exaggerating sexual conquests.
Mike's not exaggerating. This girl is turned on
by coffins. Mike'll take her into the cooler...
(Zack) Some libidos
are inflamed by proximity to death.
- Who's that?
- My assistant Zack, back in DC.
Congratulations on your coffin sex.
I've got work to do.
Some of the information you've sent seems to
have come from remains already embalmed.
Bodies were unearthed by the flooding.
They have to be ID'd and reburied.
I could fly down there to help.
A, tomorrow's my last day,
and B, the sex-on-the-coffin thing
is not guaranteed.
You know, there are reasons they call this
the Big Easy. Even after Hurricane Katrina.
Dr Brennan... meet John Doe 361.
Found him in the Ninth Ward,
sticking out of the mud.
Good afternoon, Detective Harding.
Male, 40s.
- Badly decomposed, looks pretty banged up.
- Yeah.
Be nice to know if it was hurricane, flood,
or foul play that killed him.
Detective, have you been
into the cooler lately?
Apparently some libidos are inflamed
by the proximity to death.
God, Graham, thinking about sex in this place
should be illegal - If it ain't already.
(Bones) Oh, Sam,
I'm going to need x-rays on this one.
Looks like there's something
lodged behind his teeth.
You've been working 48 hours straight.
You need the evening off.
I only have one vacation day left.
Are you doing penance for FEMA?
Let me cook you dinner tonight.
- I don't know.
- Come on. I'm a Southern gentleman, ma'am.
- Your honour will be respected.
- Yeah.
Tell you what, Graham. We'll see what the
x-rays tell us about this one and then, maybe,
we'll get a bite to eat.
All right.
Agh!
(phone rings)
(phone still ringing)
(woman) Dr Brennan,
your airport shuttle is here.
What?
No. Um...
My flight isn't until Thursday.
Today is Thursday, Dr Brennan.
What happened to Wednesday?
Dr Brennan? Hello?
Are you there, Dr Brennan?
Looks like someone stole your earring.
Ripped it right out of the lobe.
- I don't know what happened to me.
- It's a tough town.
We don't have many cops any more, and...
they were never that good to begin with.
- Shouldrt insult the ones that stuck around.
- Detective, I didn't... know who else to call.
I need blood samples on this clothing.
Maybe we'll get lucky and they won't all
come from you. Still hazy on the details?
I'm not hazy on the details, I...
- I don't remember anything.
- Nothing?
Dr Leger knocking over a tray of instruments
at the morgue, then... nothing.
- That was the day before yesterday.
- I requested a rape kit.
No sign of sexual activity,
forced or otherwise.
- You can't go in!
- Are you OK?
- Booth, I told you not to come.
- Who's this?
- He's FBI. We're sort of partners.
- Guy flies from DC, you're more than sort of.
- Yeah, that's great. You remember anything?
- (sighs)
- Tray falling over.
- Why can't she remember anything?
- It could be the head injury.
- Hairline fracture on my right distal radius.
Concussion. Slight fever. Torn earlobe.
I lost one of my favourite earrings.
You should really be worried
about losing a whole day.
I know. It's stupid.
But these earrings were my mother's.
Amnesia caused by any traumatic event -
injury or drug -
can erase memories before the event,
notjust after.
- We'll wait for a tox screen.
- It'll be at least 24 hours.
- 24 hours?
- Most labs were destroyed by the hurricane.
We'll find out what happened.
You just take care of your, uh... partner.
Another present from the bayou.
I keep asking for a baby tee
that says "the Big Easy".
We're all hoping for that.
For you, I mean.
Does our funding allow us to do
Dr Brennars vacation work?
We're just doing what the feds didn't.
It's the yin-yang of government spending.
- So we're sneaking?
- That's what makes it fun.
John Doe 361.
Wow.
Bad things happened to Mr Doe.
(Booth) It'll come back, Bones.
(Bones) You don't know that.
Head injuries are unpredictable.
- I'm just being reassuring.
- (phone rings)
Brennan.
Regarding the x-rays of John Doe 361.
John Doe 361?
Yes. You sent his x-rays.
- I don't remember that.
- You don't remember?
- What about the x-ray, Zack?
- Male, late 40s, mixed-race.
Anomalies on his spine, which I'm
looking into. His death was not accidental.
- I sent you the x-rays of a murder victim?
- (Booth) How'd he die?
- Is that Booth?
- (Bones) Yes.
You're hopping the streetcar named Desire
with Booth? Oh, I love this.
Obviously they're working
the murder of John Doe 361 together.
Precisely. How did 361 die?
The pelvis shows crush fractures.
There's what appears to be a bullet hole
in the skull, but there's no exit wound.
(Bones) OK, keep working on it.
- You don't remember the case?
- No.
And it's a murder.
Oh, I'm hungry.
When was the last time you ate?
My bad. You have amnesia.
Booth. I think I know a place.
What is the last thing you do remember?
I told you. Graham - Dr Leger -
knocked over a tray of surgical instruments.
- I want to talk to Leger.
- He was about to examine John Doe 361.
Dr Brennan!
I thought you were leaving today.
Peter, this is my friend Seeley Booth.
- My God, what happened to you?
- I'm not certain,
but the bruising suggests Tuesday night.
- After you left here?
- I was here Tuesday?
- What time?
- In at eight, left at nine.
Don't you remember?
You had dinner with Sam Potter.
Bones. Bones.
- We have to go to the morgue, talk to Sam.
- Who's Sam?
- He's an orderly. He practises voodoo.
- Bones, wait up.
- (Sam) You invited me to dinner.
- (Bones) Why?
You found this in the mouth of a John Doe.
(Booth) Let me see that.
- That's voodoo?
- It's a grigri bag. It's a mojo.
This one is meant to silence the dead.
Usually dead people are silent on their own.
Voodoo embraces the premise that spirits
can speak to us from beyond the grave.
Voodoo is all about the balance of the forces.
That wind, the flood, this death -
it's all out of balance now.
Katrina was Armageddon
for the ones who love balance.
Some think it was Secte Rouge
that brought it on.
- What's that? Some kind of a gang?
- The ones who follow evil.
Some believe they angered the sirens
who sent the flood. This is Secte Rouge.
So that's literally bad voodoo?
It's black gum root.
There's only one place you can find it -
a voodoo shop on Pontchartrain Avenue
run by Richard Benoit.
He's a good man. Maybe he can help you.
OK. Thanks.
Dr Brennan, a lost day?
Perhaps a spell was cast on you as well.
No disrespect, Sam,
but... it's not my religion.
Come on, Booth.
- (Booth) Voodoo? Who's gonna believe that?
- (Bones) It's a religion, no crazier than...
- Well, what are you?
- Catholic.
They believe in the same saints you do,
and prayer.
What they call spells, you call miracles.
- We don't make zombies.
- Jesus rose from the dead after three days.
- (phone rings)
- Brennan.
Jesus is not a zombie.
All right? Man, I shouldn't
have to tell you that.
On John Doe 361 there's a narrowing
of the disc space on L2 and L3.
- Congenital?
- Unclear.
Extensive injuries consistent with
a body being thrown around by a flood.
Cross-reference what you know
with the records of missing Katrina victims.
Hey, Brennan.
Why haven't you come home?
Pretty soon, Ange.
- Is Booth there socially?
- Of course not.
- What's going on?
- Bones has amnesia.
A man put a spell on her to stop her
solving the murder of John Doe 361.
- That's a huge supposition.
- That's fine if you don't want to tell me.
Ha. Voodoo amnesia.
- It's a good one. Mm-hm.
- Hm. Yeah. It's great.
Brennars fighting zombies in New Orleans
and we're stuck here.
- Whoa. What's that smell?
- I imagine everything smells in here.
Whoa.
Please just tell me that that car
survived Katrina. (whistles)
- We used it to evacuate.
- Did you restore it or did you use voodoo?
Ah. (laughs)
An unbeliever.
- What can I do for you?
- Do you, uh... do you know what that is?
(Benoit) This is a dark spell, forbidden magic.
Very strong.
This is Secte Rouge.
I certainly wouldn't make anything like this.
- But you have the ingredients here?
- The individual ingredients aren't malignant.
It is how they are combined and what they
are used for that makes a spell good or bad.
- Do you recognise me?
- No. Should I?
- Anyone else work here?
- My daughter. Eva.
- What is this about?
- We're conducting an investigation.
Eva!
What kind of investigation?
Is this the only place
a person can buy black gum root?
Yes. Most places like this are all gone now.
It's not a coincidence.
Yes, Daddy?
Have you ever seen this lady before?
- No. Why?
- We need to know who's bought this lately.
Don't they need a warrant?
Eva will pull up what you need
on the computer. Eva.
What you said - what did you mean,
"a coincidence"?
Most places like this,
where a houngan, a priest,
can get what he needs...
they are all gone now.
- Because of the hurricane and flood.
- Which occurred through a lack of balance.
Mr Benoit, are you suggesting that Secte
Rouge somehow conjured up a hurricane?
Secte Rouge voodoo
is more powerful than ours.
No, Eva, not more powerful.
Destruction is easier than harmony,
but not more powerful.
There are a lot of misunderstandings
about voodoo.
Yeah, that whole zombie stuff
puts a crimp in your public relations, I bet.
These are the people who have bought
black gum root in the past month.
Graham Leger, the medical examiner.
- (Booth) I tried to get in touch with him.
- (Bones) He was scheduled to be in the field.
Graham.
- It's Temperance!
- What if he's not here?
He's probably asleep.
He's been working nights. Graham!
- Graham?
- Cracker.
Hey, that's not funny. I think he invited me to
dinner that night, or drinks. I can't remember.
You know what? Maybe he roofied you.
I'm sure he bought the black gum root
to look into its medicinal qualities.
Because we all know how effective that is.
Voodoo healing is quite effective,
no crazier than acupuncture or exorcism.
Hey, hey. Easy on the Catholics, OK?
Just easy.
Bones.
Here we go again.
Bones!
You OK?
(Bones) Something bad happened here, and...
I got away.
Oh, yeah. Something bad.
(police sirens)
- What exactly were you doing here?
- It's Graham, isn't it?
Tell you what. I'm going to ask the questions.
- Come on. She was working with the guy.
- How closely?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Answer my question, please.
What brought you here? Was it a social call?
Business? Revenge killing?
Leger bought black gum root from
the voodoo store. We stopped by to ask why.
- Why?
- That's what we came here to ask.
Want to look behind me and remind
yourselves why I'm a little low on humour?
- That wasrt ajoke.
- She's not wisecracking.
She just tends to be a bit literal.
The day before yesterday
I showed a voodoo expert a mojo
that Graham found lodged
in the mouth of John Doe 361.
This voodoo consultation,
did it occur before or after amnesia?
- The amnesia's real.
- Graham purchased a rare ingredient
at a voodoo shop on Pontchartrain Ave.
So Graham made voodoo spells,
shoved them into corpses' mouths
and acted surprised when he found them?
What's that?
Split cast, huh? More voodoo.
Just like the symbol on the wall.
- Bag it as evidence.
- Secte Rouge?
- What do you know about Secte Rouge?
- We're gonna go.
I'm gonna tear this place apart. If I find one
piece of evidence that ties you to the scene,
I will take you into custody.
Do you really think someone could go into a
trance, commit a murder, and not remember?
No, I don't. But I sure as hell
think someone can fake amnesia.
Great. Thank you, Detective.
These are what you and Graham
worked on the day before yesterday.
James, meet Agent Seeley Booth.
Dr Embry is Graham's second in command.
- Condolences on your sudden promotion.
- Um... um...
Why do you think the job had
anything to do with Graham being killed?
Bones has voodoo amnesia,
Leger is voodoo dead,
and the last thing they worked on
was a voodoo ritual murder,
so I'm thinking there might be
some kind of a connection.
Leger's body...
- Is it as bad as they say?
- How bad are they saying it is?
No matter how bad they're saying it is,
it's worse.
I just want to mentally prepare myself.
I start his autopsy in a few minutes.
The file I need is John Doe 361.
According to records, these are
the only cases you worked on that day.
Four sets of remains. Two were easy IDs -
drown victims, processed for burial.
The other two were both males -
John Does 349 and 350.
I sent 361's x-rays to the Jeffersonian.
I'll check again.
- Can I make a lifestyle suggestion?
- Go ahead.
You know, "vacation",
it's from the Latin vacatio.
It means "freedom". You might
want to consider that next time.
- Learning Latin?
- This is the opposite of vacation.
No wonder you snapped,
went insane and totally lost your mind.
- Oh, thanks for your understanding.
- Dr Brennan, there's no John Doe 361.
Then whose x-rays did I send to DC?
No, I mean the file is gone.
(chants)
- OK. Hold that.
- Got it.
- Zack Addy.
- It's me. Anything else on John Doe 361?
Yes, Dr Brennan. We found some damage
to the pubic bone - some kind of strike marks.
- Did Angela reconstruct the pattern?
- (Angela) Yeah, hi, sweetie. I'm here.
I tried to make a digital positive,
but it didn't work.
- Why?
- Voodoo, probably.
The extrapolation protocols can't resolve
the gradient fluxes in the bone shadings.
- What's that?
- Mumbo jumbo. Scientific voodoo.
- Can you do it manually?
- Off an x-ray?
- Mm, not really.
- Can't you send the actual remains?
- They don't exist.
- That makes no sense.
- Voodoo. It's probably voodoo.
- Voodoo?
- OK, quit saying "voodoo".
- Yeah, because, you know, it's not a factor.
OK, let me know what you find. Bye.
How do we know this is not the guy
shoving mojo bags into dead people?
Those spells are the work of a sorcerer.
Priests, houngans, can make healing mojos,
but I won't.
But snake shaking is fine?
The snake pulls the evil out of the soul,
freeing the spirit, the loa.
I must do what small things I can. The floods
washed away too much of what was good.
Bones, how about
while you're a murder suspect,
you act more like a normal woman
and less like Lily Munster, OK?
Bye-bye. Good snake. Bye-bye.
Call me crazy,
but I'm suspicious of snake man.
You've been inculcated
by the mainstream culture's
prevailing Judeo-Christian tradition into
instinctive scepticism of alternative mores.
Yeah. Thanks for that explanation.
- I've been over every inch of these x-rays.
- Me too.
There's evidence of particles on the bones,
but no way of knowing what they are.
- Probably dirt.
- Yes, thank you, Zack.
But "dirt" is a meaningless word.
- You can't see air on an x-ray.
- What?
I never said you could.
I'm not even talking about air.
You can see a space where air might be,
like a cavity, but not the air itself.
What I'm saying is that yes, there are flecks
on the x-ray that might be dirt,
but that doesn't tell us anything.
Is it sandy? Silty? Humusy? Is it clay?
Is it more organic than mineral?
Is it soil? Is it pulverised gravel? What
minerals are in it? Are they crystalline?
These are all details a person cannot get off
an x-ray, no matter how long he stares at it.
Sometimes a person should look for things
that aren't there instead of things that are.
You mean me? In dirt?
No. Me, on the x-ray.
I've been looking for anomalies which exist
instead of anomalies which don't.
Zack, if you are ever going to
successfully mimic being human,
you have to stop making everything about
you and feign interest in the other guy.
- Zack!
- I've noticed that you try to look taller.
- When?
- Around Dr Brennan.
- I do not.
- And Angela.
Because they're both taller than you.
You know what? I take it back.
Don't take any interest in the other guy.
Thank you for your help.
(Booth) So do you remember anything else
that could help us out?
- It could have been me.
- You remember that?
Look at it objectively.
Graham Leger was killed between
11pm Tuesday and 3am Wednesday.
Not only do I not have an alibi, I...
I can't even explain to myself where I was.
It could have been me.
- No, it couldn't.
- Yes... How do you know?
I'd bet my professional career on it.
- I already did.
- What? What did you do?
Bones, stop! This is the last time
and place that you want to be rational.
Let's be wildly emotional and assume
you didn't murder a co-worker
who invited you over for dinner.
- What's that?
- What?
That.
Ew!
It's another voodoo dumpling?
It's some kind of flesh...
and these are sea shells.
And leather, I think.
- Is that a human tooth?
- Yes. A canine.
- Put down your weapon.
- Put down yours. There's no threat from us.
- You're holding a gun on me.
- My finger is not on the trigger.
It's the best I can do under the circumstances.
Holster your weapons. I'm here to arrest
Dr Brennan for the murder of Graham Leger.
- That's not gonna happen.
- It is.
- I told you, Booth.
- Please! Just once in your life be quiet!
That's good advice as everything you say can
and will be held against you in a court of law.
- What is that?
- I... I found it on my pillow.
Bones! (sighs)
- Thank you, Dr Brennan.
- What's the probable cause?
Traces of Dr Brennars blood in Leger's
home, Leger's blood on her clothing.
- Is that it?
- All I'm prepared to share.
- Now, please, step away from my collar.
- I'm afraid I can't let that happen.
- Bones! Jeez!
- It's better if nobody else dies.
You know what? I wasrt planning on dying.
Agh! It's not you I worry about. Ow!
You're welcome to the room. It's paid for.
Were you sleeping with Graham Leger?
I don't... I don't think so.
You don't think so?
I don't remember doing so, and at the clinic
they said there was no sign of sexual activity.
- I hope you've kept your mouth shut.
- Temperance Brennan, Caroline Julian.
She's your lawyer.
She's from the US Attorney's office.
You found a prosecutor to defend her?
Interesting tactic.
I've told Detective Harding everything I know.
- You didn't tell me she's a fool.
- She's a forensic anthropologist.
I have three degrees,
I've pioneered research...
- What's that?
- A grigri bag. I found it in my hotel room.
I assume the person who left it is trying to
frame me, so the tooth is probably Graham's.
Three degrees and still a fool.
This interview is over, Rose.
I need to speak with my client alone
before she gives herself a lethal injection.
Of course. Of course.
It's nice seeing you again, Caroline.
- What the hell were you talking to her for?
- I was just trying to help.
Sew those lips together, because there is no
such thing as helping the New Orleans police.
They just want to close the case
as quickly as they can.
- You are making it Christmas time for them.
- There's no way that Bones killed Leger.
- It's just not her. Look at her!
- I am doing you a favour taking this case.
But as the lady cop says,
I'm a prosecutor, and as it stands now,
I could try this case in my PJs
and still get a conviction.
Shouldrt you get to know your clients
before you make snap judgements?
- Bones!
- Fine. Stop me when I get something wrong.
"Trained in three types of martial arts,
two assault charges."
"Registered marksman with the NRA."
- "Hunting licences in four states."
- You hunt?
- Only for food.
- "Shot an unarmed man."
He was trying to set me on fire.
Just arrange bail for us
so we can get out of here.
Sure, sure.
Don't wanna get this one mad at me.
You couldn't keep your mouth shut,
could you?
- I can identify this guy.
- Angela isn't that much taller than me.
Spina bifida. He had a shunt
from his brain stem down to his heart.
It was removed more than a decade ago.
- We both like Brussels sprouts.
- You don't like Brussels sprouts.
A man can change, Zack.
(Potter) A human tooth?
Yeah. Some kind of flesh, some fabric.
It looked like some kind of shell.
Yeah, sounds like... to make you forget.
Somebody doesn't want you
to know what happened.
- Booth, I'm not under a spell.
- Well, you forgot a whole day.
The spirits don't need you to believe in them,
Dr Brennan. They believe in you.
See you back at work, huh?
How did I get away?
Graham got killed, I got away.
How did I do that?
Bones, all those things
that Caroline mentioned,
the martial arts, the shooting, the assaults.
You're the type of woman that fights.
Maybe they didn't expect it.
Maybe they thought magic could hold you.
- I don't believe in magic.
- Exactly.
You're a surprising woman.
Sometimes that's enough for getting away.
Why are you nice to me?
- Because they think they get away with it.
- What?
They burn their victim, blow 'em up, toss 'em
in the ocean, bury them in the desert.
They throw 'em into wood chippers.
Sometimes years go by.
They relax and start living their lives
like they did nothing wrong.
Like they didn't spend somebody else's life
to get what they got.
They think they're safe from retribution, but...
You make those bastards unsafe.
That's why I'm nice to you.
I couldn't do that without you, Booth.
Yeah. So you should be
a little nicer to me, huh?
I really should.
I walk in on something?
Beignet and a café, chérie.
- (man) Yes, ma'am.
- Hospital records.
- The tox screen was negative.
- What? That's impossible.
- No Rohypnol or ketamine?
- Nothing but a touch of alcohol.
Not enough to affect a baby.
Ajury is never gonna believe
this amnesia story.
- But it's true.
- Maybe this is true too.
Leger tried to rape you.
He was a notorious horn dog.
We claim self-defence, cop a plea,
you're out in three years.
I don't care what it looks like or how
you read the evidence. She didn't do it.
Could be that's true, Seeley.
You vouch for her, that's good enough for me.
But, chérie, this looks bad.
All you've got on your side
is proof you got roughed up.
These pictures from the clinic, these x-rays.
My wrist. The doctor was wrong.
He said this was a Colles' fracture from a fall.
This break shows surface trauma on the bone.
This was either defensive or someone
slammed my wrist into something.
Maybe cos you tried
to stab him in the heart with a knife?
No, if I'd already stabbed the attacker,
he wouldn't have been able to break my wrist.
- I like this story. What else?
- There's the mojo bag.
- Someone tried to put a spell on her.
- Booth!
I can work with that. This is New Orleans.
And where is my beignet?
- Brennan.
- John Doe 361 is named Rene Mouton.
How can you be sure?
I looked for something that wasrt there -
a shunt channel.
- Good work.
- You understood that?
All Zack had to do
was cross-check with DMORT.
I only thought of it because of Hodgins.
I can discern particulates on the x-ray,
but don't know what they are.
- Some kind of dirt?
- OK, everybody,
the word "dirt" means nothing
here in the lab, scientifically.
Any progress on the design
in the pelvic bone?
(Angela) I've tried
three different computer programs.
I fed in the information into multiple impact
scenarios, but this won't work on x-rays.
- I need the actual remains.
- Booth and I are looking for them.
Or better, you could forget
the whole thing and come home.
Don't worry. I made bail.
Bail?
Bail? For what?
I told you, don't worry.
The murder charge won't stick.
Whoa! Murder charge?!
Brennan. The next plane. The next plane
or I'm coming down there to get you myself.
Everything's fine.
I'm healing up satisfactorily. Bye for now.
(Hodgins) Healing up?
You know what? This whole state of affairs
where Brennan runs around fighting crime,
it's stupid, it's nuts.
Don't you agree?
Go, go. I'll be fine.
Brennan will be fine, Angela. She got bail
and the murder charge won't stick.
- What is going on with her?
- Angela.
- She started to change the day she met you.
- What?
Well, she sees how you do it.
All fun and involvement and pizzazz.
Big, you know. A big life.
Booth came along and gave her the
opportunity, but she got the idea from you.
Brennan wants a big life, like yours.
That's how it looks to me anyway, but what
do I know? I'm a bug guy. Bug and slime.
And, you know... dirt.
- Yeah.
- So...
OK.
According to bureau files, Rene Mouton
headed a small voodoo church.
By all accounts, he was a very good man.
He rescued scores of people during Katrina,
then he just disappeared.
Some thought he was just swept away
when the levee broke.
- Why would anyone murder him?
- Chaos during the evacuation.
- It could even have been for a bottle of water.
- Or... because he was a priest.
The grigri bags,
the murder of Dr Leger, your amnesia.
This is the work of a bokor,
a Secte Rouge sorcerer.
Rene Mouton was a houngan,
a powerful and well-Ioved priest.
For Secte Rouge to claim his soul, it'd give
them influence on the people he influenced.
- Like a chain letter?
- Or somebody who wanted his shoes.
- No, Booth, it makes sense.
- What does?
- Graham and I were on the trail of a broker.
- Bokor.
And he found out. Or Secte Rouge did.
Great. Then we just toss the ring
into the molten river and blah, blah, right?
In the meantime, somebody here had
the ability to hide Moutors body and files.
- James Embry? Mike Doyle?
- Me?
Say you wanted to hide a body and didn't
want it found, where would you put it?
If I wanted to hide a body,
I'd change the name tag on the coffin.
- Not Mouton. Too young.
- He's buried and the evidence is gone.
Female. I find it hard to believe that
horny little Mike Doyle is a voodoo sorcerer.
Whoa!
- Me too.
- Speak of the devil. It's Mike Doyle.
And he's not alone.
- You said to avoid the police.
- Not cooperating is one thing.
Concealing a double homicide? We might
as well give them an excuse to hang us.
Dr Embry says that
you can identify the bag of bones.
The skeletal remains belong to a man
named Rene Mouton. His skull is missing.
Looks like Doyle was drugged,
a spike driven through his head,
during or immediately after
sexual intercourse.
It appears that Dr Brennan, Dr Embry
and Sam Potter could have pulled this off.
Sam Potter brought us to the body.
We called you in. Who does that leave?
There's no security in this place.
Anyone could have gotten in here.
You said Mike was having sex when he died.
He must have been killed by the coffin girl.
- What?
- What's her name?
- I never got her name.
- Is there a mojo in Doyle's mouth?
- I don't feel comfortable releasing...
- She's a sorcerer. She works for Secte Rouge.
Detective Harding, I know this,
you know, sounds superstitious, but...
Three murders
and a world-renowned anthropologist
who can't remember how she ended up
smeared with the blood of a skinned man
crucified to a wall with spikes?
Call me superstitious.
Excuse me.
May I scatter fwan ginea over Mr Mouton?
To purify his remains?
No more voodoo crap!
I don't want you contaminating the body.
- What is it?
- Ashes from a ritual fire pit.
Ashes from a dove's feather.
Salt mixed with holy water.
- OK, we get the idea.
- It should have no effect on the bones.
Fine. Fine, go ahead.
(chants)
- (Booth) Whoa! Did you see that?
- (Bones) Very interesting phenomenon.
The electrostatic charge of the particles
reacted with the bone.
Angela was unable to recreate that pattern
from the x-rays using top technology.
Electrostatic my ass. That was part
of an emblem of a 1959 Caddy... Oh, boy!
- What?!
- The voodoo shop guy owns a 1959 Cadillac.
He's got a voodoo daughter.
- You're taking my Caddy?
- We have reason to believe
that your Caddy was used
in the wrongful death of Rene Mouton.
You think someone did a hit and run
on Rene Mouton in my Caddy?
- Yes.
- Does your daughter have a boyfriend?
Yeah.
This him?
- Mike Doyle. Yeah. Why?
- We need to speak to...
I mean Detective Harding
needs to speak to your daughter.
- I don't know where she is.
- She's a suspect in the murder of Mike Doyle.
- Why would Eva kill her boyfriend?
- It's hard to explain.
She was involved in a hit and run.
When the body surfaced at the morgue,
she asked her boyfriend to help hide it.
He refused so she killed him.
- Also, she's a member of Secte Rouge.
- No. No.
I bet there are drugs in the shop
that could knock me out, make me forget.
Eva is downstairs praying.
Eva.
Eva, open the door.
No... No!
Eva! Eva!
Oh, no! No!
Booth.
- (Booth) Could that be Moutors skull?
- Yes.
And this could be the spike that she used
on Mouton and Mike Doyle.
This is the lair of a bokor,
someone who can call the dark spirits.
This is used for ritual animal sacrifice.
It's heated to red hot
to cauterise the wound so it wouldn't bleed.
She killed herself
because she knew we were coming?
- No. No, not my Eva.
- She drove the spike through her sternum?
Sternum, heart, through the chest cavity,
through the spine.
- Can I open this?
- Why?
This holds the soul of Mr Rene Mouton.
- I believe this holds the soul of the bokor.
- Shut up!
I'd like to release Mr Moutors soul
so no other bokor can use it.
- No. It's evidence. Don't touch it.
- I raised my Eva to be a houngan, a healer.
- How could this happen under my nose?
- Rebellious adolescent?
Do you remember how much of the spike
was protruding through her back?
Six, eight inches?
Would the fact the spike was red hot
cause it to go through the body easier?
No. It might even make it harder.
- Eva Benoit did not commit suicide.
- Based on what?
This room isn't even 12 feet wide.
Even if she ran at full speed
and her aim was perfect,
no way the spike would go through her spine,
unless she was pushed onto it.
He is the sorcerer.
He believes he can bring her back to life.
OK, everyone just simmer down, OK?
You say he murdered his daughter
so he could bring her back to life?
Then you stop looking
for Moutors murderer.
An inch or two to the left or right,
we would never have known it was murder.
It would have been hard pushing her onto
the spike, especially if she were resisting.
You'd have some wounds of your own.
There's your killer.
- I'd really like to go home now.
- Yeah, me too.
My advice, cuff Mr Wizard here
before he puts a spell on you.
No written confession?
Threaten to release his daughter's soul
and he'll confess.
Dr Temperance Brennan, you leave here,
you go home, it does not matter.
There are powers. Dark powers,
to whom distance makes no difference.
- Easy, buddy.
- (chants)
Hey!
I've noticed that very few people are scary
once they've been poked in the eye.
I got in the middle of a battle
between two religious sects.
Benoit used Hurricane Katrina as a diversion
to take the soul of a voodoo priest.
- And he killed his own daughter?
- Dark sorcerers suck, man.
Oh, but he intended to bring her back to life.
There's not really any such thing
as spells and magic.
What? He put a forgetting hex on Dr Brennan.
It wasrt the spell that made me forget.
It was the drugs - Rohypnol.
- Blood test didn't find any.
- Gamma hydroxybutyrate?
- Not a trace.
- Sodium pentothal?
- Nope.
- Severe emotional trauma?
Honey, even I think
you're too strong-minded for that.
There were too many delays in my blood test.
That, plus the adrenaline,
the drugs were out of my system.
They put the voodoo on you, baby.
- I didn't really mean to call you "baby".
- You guys, stop. Now. I mean it.
Do you believe in voodoo? Even if a small
part of you believes in it, then it has a grip.
- I do not believe.
- Maybe just a little?
- No.
- If you have any doubts,
we'll get Benoit to send you back one of those
little satanic mojo pouches from prison.
Objects have no intrinsic power. A persors
future does not depend on some thing.
Things are just things. They do not have
magical meaning or powers.
- Where did you get that?
- What does it matter?
It's just a thing, right?
- My mother's earring.
- No magical power over your future.
Does that prove something?
Yeah.
It proves something.
Visiontext Subtitles: Kerrie Slavin
What's that mean?
ENGLISH SDH