I hereby proclaim this tower of sand,
Kingdom Phoebe-ville.
You know, I don't get it.
Wait, what don't you get?
That you just spent
an hour of your life
building something that is
just gonna be completely...
Completely destroyed and disappear
in about five seconds flat.
But Phoebe-ville will live forever
in the hearts of the villagers
who came to love it.
What's with the
bah-humcastle attitude there?
What?
Well, the whole point of today
was to relax and have fun.
See, and I thought the point
was to give Piper and Leo
some alone married-people time,
since they decided to wait
on their honeymoon.
Okay, so you're sure nothing's wrong?
You know, the beach isn't exactly
my idea of a good time.
Prue, how is that possible?
Okay, well, you're too young
to remember,
but this is where Grams brought us
after Mom's funeral
to try and cheer us up.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
No, but I know that you love the beach,
and I didn't wanna ruin it for you.
But something about the sand
and the ocean, you know,
it makes me angry.
Why does it make you angry?
Doesn't Mom's death
make you angry?
It makes me sad.
Well, I don't really do sad
that well, you know?
I didn't even cry at her funeral.
So seeing Mom at Piper's
wedding and now the beach...
Yeah. So I'm sorry
if I've been a little cranky.
Say no more.
Princess Prue has spoken!
By the orders of the queen...
- That's me.
- I got that part.
Phoebe-ville and all of its glory
will be abandoned
- for greener pastures and two lattes.
- Oh, all hail the queen.
I love to be hailed.
Hey!
No, no, no. Wait.
You okay?
There was this woman
and there was a shadow next to her.
Had to be demonic.
A shadow?
Like, what do you mean?
- Like a Woogie?
- No. Spookier. Way spookier.
I think I got pictures though.
So much for the lattes.
Looks like there's
a new demon in town.
So you're new in town.
Yes.
And... And you would both
be living here?
Sure.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I'm fine with the whole
alternative-lifestyle thing.
I just don't like loud.
Well, you understand.
Don't like loud.
Got it.
Like the last tenant, Mr. Turner.
He was a little strange.
And then, of course,
he disappeared without a trace.
But he was nice and quiet,
so I liked him fine.
Without a trace.
Is that so?
There's demonic residue
all over this altar.
It's his, I can sense it.
There's what? What did you say?
Surely, you knew something
strange had happened here.
It is your responsibility to divulge
such things to prospective tenants.
Now, listen, I don't know anything...
And the fact that you failed
to show us the altar makes us wonder
what else about Cole Turner
you might be hiding
inside of that tiny,
human brain of yours.
Wait. I don't understand...
Don't try to talk.
Your brain stem
will do the talking for you.
- Is Belthazor alive?
- She didn't know,
but she knows someone who might.
Shouldn't I be wearing
white or something?
I mean, it is a whitelighter
reception and all.
Piper, what you have on is perfect.
You're beautiful.
All my friends are gonna love you,
if we could ever get there.
Fine. But I still don't understand
why my sisters can't come.
I mean, we could just do
a group hug thing, and...
I can orb you because you're my wife,
but I'm not a cosmic taxi
for the whole family.
You said wife.
All right. I'm as ready
as I'm ever gonna be.
Wait, what about Prue's
demon-Iooking, shadowy thingy?
Well, I promise
we'll be in calling distance
if any demon-Iooking,
shadowy thingy attacks.
All right, you two. Have fun.
Bring me back a cloud.
Pheebs?
Hey, I have to get to Morris,
see if he can help me
track down this woman.
- Why? What did you find?
- Nothing, that's the problem.
The shadow didn't show up
in any of the pictures.
- Really? That's weird.
- Anything in the Book?
No, nothing.
I didn't really have
a lot to go on though.
Inspector.
How can I help you?
You can tell me
where to find Cole Turner.
I know he's alive,
and I know he's in town.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
You wanna know how?
Because his former landlady
was found brutally murdered
at his address.
Mrs. Owens.
Oh, my God. That's awful.
Awful like you can't imagine.
Cole didn't do this.
The Cole Turner I know wouldn't...
The Cole Turner you know?
That just doesn't sound
like the words of a woman
who claims her boyfriend left her
without a word four months ago.
I know what you're thinking.
And I know what this looks like.
And I am...
- I am so sorry for what happened to...
- You're sorry?
Her eyes were frozen open in terror.
Her skull was punctured in two places,
and by the time the police got there,
most of her brain
had spilled out onto the floor.
Be sick, be horrified.
But don't stand there
lying to me and say you're sorry.
All right, wait a second.
You're talking to her like she did it.
If she's lying to protect Turner,
then she might as well have.
Now, for the last time, where is he?
I'm gonna find him, Miss Halliwell,
and then I'm gonna bust his ass,
and then I'm gonna bust yours.
- You okay?
- He didn't do it, Prue.
I know he didn't do it.
Well, it's not me
that you have to convince.
Oh, my God.
That's her, the woman
from the beach.
All right, look. Do you see it?
No. All I see is Inspector Davidson
and the woman.
What does this mean?
Is he having her follow us?
I'm more concerned
about what's following her.
Wait, I don't understand
why you can't see it.
That doesn't matter, Prue, you can.
Do you think this has anything
to do with the landlady's death?
Well, it would be a pretty big
coincidence if it didn't.
I'm gonna follow her
and protect her from it.
If I'm the only one who can see it,
that must mean
that I'm meant to fight it.
All right, but the way the inspector
was describing the murder...
I know, I'll be careful.
Look, you should find Cole,
tell him what happened,
and see if he knows anything
about this shadow thing, okay?
All right, bye.
I'd better get out of here.
What? Why?
Because it's getting too dangerous.
So you're just gonna
disappear again?
If that's what it takes
to keep you safe.
What about keeping me sane, Cole?
I'm not gonna lose you again.
Some demon obviously knows
I'm alive, or at least suspects it.
Why else would they
have killed my landlady?
If they killed her, they'll kill
anybody they have to to get to me.
That is exactly why you cannot leave.
We have to stop them
before they hurt anybody else,
or before they hurt you.
They're after me, Phoebe.
This is my battle.
I'll handle it.
Cole,
I love you, and if holding onto that
means that I have to fight
a couple of extra demons
along the way,
then bring them on.
Unfortunately, we have no idea
what we're dealing with.
A strange shadow
that only Prue can see.
I haven't the slightest idea
what that could be.
So we'll figure it out...
...together.
It won't bring Mrs. Owens back,
but trust me, avenging
an innocent feels pretty damn good.
I don't see anything
remotely suspicious.
Unless you consider
hot-pink pedicures subversive.
You just keep doing
what you're doing.
You really think these women
are murderers?
I'm not sure what I think.
No. See, there's something
you're not telling me.
Look, I know I'm a rookie and all,
but I think I have a right to know
what I'm looking for here.
Look, Andrea,
I've seen things on this case that...
That aren't right.
That...
Look, I don't know what
I'm looking for, okay?
But until I do, I want you
to keep your distance
and just keep following
Phoebe Halliwell.
So why don't you take
the night off, go home,
and get some sleep for Pete's sake?
No, no, no. I can't.
Not till this is over.
I'll tell you what. You drop the
photos off on my desk and go home.
And you can pick it up
again tomorrow.
- Reece.
- That's an order.
- Have a good night.
- All right. You too.
- Oh, God.
- You okay?
Try not to touch anything. You don't
wanna leave your fingerprints.
- But if I wanna get a premonition...
- Use the back of your hand.
Did you find something?
It's just this place.
It's strange to be back here.
I know. It's strange for me too.
This was the first taste
I ever had of a normal life.
There were mornings
I'd wake up next to you, and...
...I didn't feel evil.
I was just a guy in love
with a beautiful girl.
I wanted it so much...
...I started to believe my own lie.
That's not a lie anymore.
We can have that.
We can have a life together.
- How?
- Well...
...by taking out the bad guys
who wanna take it away from us.
What do you see?
Prue.
She turned her back.
Why didn't she do anything
to stop them?
Stop who?
Demons.
They sort of had vampire teeth,
and they were floating.
They were killing Davidson.
I know them. They're seekers.
They have ways
of gathering information fast.
- Really fast.
- Do you know how to vanquish them?
No.
Well, let's hope
the Book of Shadows does.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you startled me.
Are you waiting
for Inspector Davidson?
Are you expecting him?
Not tonight. He's in the field.
- Where?
- I'm sorry.
I don't know.
Are you sure about that?
- What did she know?
- Nothing.
He told her nothing.
Which means he definitely
knows something.
I'm beyond your powers.
It's time.
Who are you?
I'm Death.
And I'll be back.
Here it is.
"The seekers.
They gather information by feeding
on their victims' brain-stem cells."
- Lovely.
- Which means my landlady
must've talked to Inspector Davidson
about me. That's why they're after him.
Does it say anything about demons
taking on shadow form?
No, but it does have a vanquish.
- Do you wanna see it?
- Oh, no, no. No.
Last time I touched that book,
it electrocuted me.
Yeah, well, maybe that's because
your intentions were evil.
Maybe it knows now
that you're trying to be good.
Better safe than sorry.
Oh, all right, I need the Book.
Wait a second, what is he
doing here next to it?
Keeping my distance, don't worry.
Pardon the potential
understatement of a cliché,
but you look like
you've seen a ghost.
Yeah, among other things.
I lost my innocent.
- Davidson?
- No, his partner.
She was out of my sight
for two seconds and they got her.
Was that them?
Yeah, actually, I think so.
And they're demonic lie detectors.
Only no one survives their test.
They killed Mrs. Owens
and now they're after Davidson.
To get to you.
Yes, to get to me.
- I should deal with this on my own.
- No. You can't.
You know, it's...
You said it yourself.
You don't know
how to vanquish them.
Unfortunately, this isn't
the only evil we're up against either.
- You mean the shadow?
- Oh, yeah.
Leo.
- What's with the lamp?
- Wedding present.
- Bright, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Leo, is there such a thing as Death?
I mean, the angel of death?
Yeah, sure.
- Why?
- Because I met him.
What? Are you kidding me?
Yeah, that's how the shadow
introduced himself to me
when he took Davidson's partner.
Then he said he would be back too,
I'm assuming, for Davidson.
- He's not working with the demons.
- No, he can't be.
The angel of death isn't evil.
The hell he isn't.
And if I can see him, that must mean
that I'm supposed to stop him.
Prue, you can't stop him.
The angel of death
always gets who he comes for.
Yeah, well, not this time. All right,
I need to get ahold of Davidson.
If I can get him here,
I can protect him better.
Hold it. Davidson,
as in Reece Davidson,
the DA investigator?
He's the innocent?
- Yeah, is there a problem?
- One great big giant one.
We can't protect him
without telling him we're witches.
Yeah, I know that, Piper,
but I don't care, okay?
I cannot stand by
and watch Death take that man.
But that's what you do,
at least according to my premonition.
You turn your back
when the demons attack.
No, that doesn't make any sense.
I know, but it's what I saw.
Yeah, well, then you saw wrong.
I am not gonna let Death
take any more of my innocents.
I'm tired of losing people. So, Phoebe,
do you have Davidson's card?
Excuse me.
I thought I was
protecting her, man, but...
You all right, inspector?
I should've warned her.
Man, I should've told her everything.
What exactly should
you have told her?
Look, all that matters is I'm gonna
take down the guy who did this,
okay, no matter what.
If it's the last thing I do.
I gotta take this.
Forget about the Halliwells.
It's me you're after.
I'll tell you whatever you wanna know,
I promise. Not here, it's not safe.
Don't touch me.
You're under arrest, Turner,
- and I'm gonna personally see to it...!
- Wait.
What to you mean wait?
- Did you sense that?
- Belthazor's alive.
I'm sorry,
but it was our only chance.
They might be able to track me
but they'll have a hard time
sensing me in a cemetery.
How...? How did we get...?
What...? What the hell
is happening?
What's happening to me?
Just breathe. Try to calm down.
What are you?
Someone who just saved your life.
Try to calm down, inspector.
If I were a murderer,
I'd have killed you by now.
Just... Just let me go then.
I'll just walk away.
I can't do that.
If the demons get to you,
they'll find out the way to get to me
is to kill Phoebe,
and I can't let that happen.
When... When you
say demon, you...
I don't mean as a metaphor.
Okay, Davidson
won't answer our page.
Something must have
happened to him.
- Cole's gone.
- What do you mean "gone"?
I mean, he's not here.
I looked everywhere.
He must've gone after
Davidson alone to protect us.
Yeah, but if the seekers
get to him first...
We gotta get Cole
to bring him back here.
The mausoleum. He could've
taken him to the mausoleum.
- That's where Cole stays.
- Is there any chance
that's where you saw the
inspector die in your premonition?
Maybe. Let's go.
You know, I could
astral there faster.
But what if the demons show up?
You can't vanquish them.
- You'll need the power of three spell.
- So then I won't vanquish them.
I'll just protect Reece long enough
to get him out of there.
- Prue.
- Phoebe,
your premonition
is not gonna come true.
I told you, this is one fight
that Death is not gonna win.
Just stay the hell away from me.
I told you, I'm not gonna hurt you.
Belthazor, I presume.
I'm sorry, who?
We sensed your shimmer.
You're losing your touch.
Leave him out of this.
Why would we want him
now that we have you?
Unless the human knows something
Belthazor doesn't want us to know.
- Hi. Need a little help?
- What are you doing here?
How did you get here?
What the hell is going on?
Well, well, well.
The mighty Belthazor
in bed with a witch.
Don't make me sick.
- No.
- Prue!
Come on, fight,
you miserable coward.
Prue!
I never lose.
It's his time.
Over my dead body.
It's just so bright.
Well, of course, it's bright.
It's supposed to represent
the light of eternal love.
Wait, does that mean
we can never turn it off?
At this rate, you're gonna
turn it off in record time.
I'm just saying, I don't think
it belongs in the living room.
Or the parlour,
the dining room, the foyer.
- Pheebs?
- Oh, do you think I'm stupid?
- I'm staying out of this. Besides...
- I already told you, Prue.
I wouldn't revert to my demon form,
and I could've used some help.
I was busy saving Davidson.
No, that's what I was doing.
Hello? What happened?
Is he okay?
He almost wasn't. The seekers
were at the courthouse waiting for him.
And then they tracked Cole
to the mausoleum.
How do you know
they didn't track you here?
They retreated first. They have to be
close to a shimmer to track it.
- They retreated?
- Yeah.
- I kicked ass.
- No, you kicked air.
No, I told you that I was fighting
the angel of death,
and obviously, I won.
- Prue, that's not possible.
- Well, he's alive, isn't he?
For now, maybe.
But the seekers, they'll be back,
and they'll be out for blood,
mine and yours.
The only thing they don't know
is how to find us.
Yes, and now they know
that Davidson is the key.
If you had just fought with me, we...
You know, you're not exactly
the poster boy for teamwork, Cole.
Hey, you were supposed
to stick with us, remember?
I was trying to protect you.
All of you.
By exposing yourself?
Better me than you.
You know, the one thing
you failed to consider, Cole,
is no matter how dangerous
Davidson is to us,
- you're more dangerous.
- Now, wait a minute,
- I think that I've proven myself to you...
- No, Cole. That's not what she meant.
You're a part of our lives now.
You know almost
everything about us.
If you had lost...
The seekers could use
what I know to destroy you.
I better check with the Elders.
This is getting complicated.
- Inspector, you hit your head.
- I didn't hit it that hard.
Whatever I just saw,
it's not because I hit my head.
All right, look, I know
that this may seem hard to believe
after everything
you've been through tonight.
But we are on your side, okay?
We're the good guys.
I don't know what you people are,
but good isn't topping
my list of ideas.
Be that as it may,
we can't let you leave.
Cole.
- Try and stop me.
- Inspector, you're in a room
with three witches and a demon.
You really think that gun's gonna help?
Hey, look, I don't really
know how to tell you this,
but it's not just demons
that are after you.
The angel of death wants you too.
Now, please... Please,
if you stay here, we can protect you.
I'm not afraid of death.
You, on the other hand,
are a different matter.
Cole.
He's gonna expose you.
He'll gather evidence and...
Cole, we don't kidnap cops
and then hold them against their will.
But we do follow them
and protect them against their will.
Come on.
Not you, you stay here.
So, what, I'm just...?
I'm just gonna have to wait here?
Yeah, no shimmering,
and lock the door behind us.
- Prue?
- You guys go ahead.
- But the demons.
- Yeah, the demons are just pawns.
I'm going over their heads.
Spirits of air, sand and sea
Converge to set the angel free
In the wind I send this rhyme
Bring Death before me
Before my time
Come on.
I know that you can hear me.
Are you sure you really want me?
- I...
- Come on, I don't have all day.
There are people waiting,
who definitely don't have all day.
So, what is it?
I took your husband
and you want him back?
Your brother?
Your mother.
Don't talk about her.
Don't talk about my mother.
That should've been an easy guess
with those sad little-girl eyes.
All right, you want Reece Davidson,
and it's my job to protect him.
What do you want from me?
What do I have to do?
- That's not why you called me.
- Yes, it is.
No. That's an excuse.
You're mad at me
for taking Mummy.
I told you not to talk about her.
What were you, ten?
- I'm just guessing now.
- Just stop it.
Younger, I bet.
And now, you think by saving this...
Which is it, Davidson?
You think you'll have
beaten me somehow.
That somehow,
you'll have finally won.
- Just go away.
- No.
You wanted me, now you've got me.
- You're wasting precious time.
- I'm sorry...
It's not my time
you're wasting, it's yours.
You refuse to accept me
for what I am,
which keeps you from mourning me.
You don't know me.
You don't know anything about me.
But I've seen it
so many times before.
The anger, the pain.
You lock up your tears and
angrily steel yourself against me
as if I was the ultimate evil.
You are the ultimate evil.
No. I'm not good or evil,
I just am.
I'm inevitable.
What do I have to do
to save Davidson?
You still don't get it, do you?
There's nothing you can do.
I can't just let an innocent man die.
You have to let him die.
You have no choice.
And until you can learn
to accept that,
you'll just keep missing
the bigger picture.
What bigger picture?
I'll show you.
Oh, don't worry.
It's not your time.
Well, not just yet anyway.
"Yea, though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death,
I shall fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me."
Prue left right after we did.
She hasn't been back there?
No one's been here.
I'm going out of my mind.
Yeah, try sitting
in a car for 16 hours.
- No sign of any demons?
- No, not yet.
But Davidson led us to a...
- To a what?
- Never mind.
If Prue comes back,
just tell her to call us.
- I love you.
- Phoebe.
Phoebe.
Okay, so now what?
Well, we can't crash the funeral.
- I guess we just watch from here.
- I don't understand.
You tell a guy that Death is after him
and he goes to a cemetery?
How smart is that?
You want me? Fine.
But these people
have been through enough.
Phoebe.
Hey! Hey, Reece,
get out of there! Run!
You've been so brave, inspector.
Don't ruin it now.
Where's Belthazor?
Belthazor?
- Oh, my God.
- It's his time.
Just like it was your mother's time.
Prue.
Open the gate.
Stop fighting me.
Open the gate!
Prue?
- Are you okay?
- I don't know.
What happened?
- Did the demons do something to you?
- No.
How did you even get in here?
- Death brought me.
- I'm sorry.
You know, l... I don't completely
understand it myself.
Prue, how could you
stand there and let him die?
Because it was his time, all right?
I wanted to save him, but I couldn't.
You didn't even try.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Ever hear of a doorbell?
We thought we'd surprise you.
Hi, we're not home.
You know the drill.
Cole, if you're there,
pick up the phone.
Actually, don't pick up
the phone. Just get out.
- Should I astral there?
- I think we should stick together.
Faster.
Now, let's see what
you don't want us to know.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Prue, don't.
Knowledge gained
By murderous means
Is wisdom's bitter enemy
The mind that burns with stolen fire
Will now become your funeral pyre
Well, at least we saved one.
Did you hear that?
You just reached innocent status.
And that's good?
To Prue, no one is more important.
- Nice timing. You missed the show.
- I know. But they told me to miss it.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
What do you mean
they told you to miss it?
The Elders were behind
this whole thing?
No, but they knew
they had to let Prue
learn the lesson by herself
the hard way.
- What lesson?
- That Death is not the evil.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
She just needs some time.
And we need a maid.
You know, I was thinking...
And this lamp
is not worth fighting over.
So if you love it, then I love it.
Yeah?
Yeah. I mean, life's too short.
Now I love it even more.
You contemplating the tides?
Can't control them
any more than me.
Okay, I get that you're not evil.
But what I don't get is why
I wasn't supposed to fight the demons.
Well, you were alone
and outnumbered.
I still could have fought.
But you would have lost, Prue.
How did you know my name?
I read it off my list.
It was the next one
after Reece Davidson.
You were coming for me?
If you hadn't stopped
fighting me, yes.
That's why you were able to see me.
It's the bigger picture, Prue.
Focusing all your anger against me
leaves you vulnerable
to the real evils of this world.
You'd do well to remember
that in the future.
- What?
- I don't know.
You know, I've been...
I've been mad at you for so long...
...ever since Mom died.
I don't know how else to be.
You grieve...
...and then you move on.