Previously on "invasion"...
there's this storm brewing inside me
that is more powerful than any hurricane.
What really happened to you
that night in the water ?
Do you know ?
Mariel's not like you and me, father.
- She's afraid of losing her children.
- And you're afraid of losing her.
you did see a body, but it wasn't you.
- I was counting on your loyalty, Lewis.
- But I'm loyal to god, sir.
Lewis ?
Lewis !
Do you know what happened to you last night ?
My arm came back, sir.
It's a miracle.
What happed to him is wrong.
They'll want to dissect all of us
and I cannot let that happen.
There are people out there
who may be killing themselves
and their children.
I've been reconstructing this skull.
It's almost 10 years old.
This isn't god's plan, sir.
He gave me a gift.
Invasion
1x11-
Transcript: RaceMan
Adaptation - Ez, Keno83, RonanaSplit & Lucile76
www. forom. com
the morning after the hurricane,
when they pulled me from the water...
I felt like I had a secret to tell,
but I didn't know who to tell it to.
People don't like it when you change.
They say they do, but they really don't,
because it forces them to change, too,
and that's why I'm so grateful
I found you,
because I know that you understand
and I know that you accept me...
and to those who don't,
well, adios.
yeah, well, you stop by
anytime, Mariel.
I'm giving out free haircuts
to members of the group.
Oh, that's really sweet of you, Roger.
Well, we gotta take care
of our own, right ?
Alma !
Alma.
Excuse me.
Damn it, Alma, I've been lookin'
all over for you.
We got two sick kids at home and you're hanging out with these losers again !
They're not losers !
I'm tellin' you, we don't need these people.
You need to calm down, son.
What-
get in the car.
Get in the car.
Stop it !
Let me through.
Stop it ! Stop it !
Stop it !
Somebody call 9-1-1.
He needs an ambulance.
Call 9-1-1.
Somebody call 9-1-1.
And the good news is
if you need a doctor,
she's right across the hall.
Hey, come on, come on.
Don't be shy.
I really would be more comfortable
in my apartment, sir.
Nonsense, nonsense.
After what you've been through,
the least we can do
is help nurse you back to health, okay ?
All right ? Kira ?!
Dad ?
Hey, sweetheart.
Deputy Sirk here had a really bad accident yesterday.
He was shot in the arm,
and as you know, he never had
much of an arm to begin with,
so he needs our help.
Would you mind looking after him
for the next couple of days ?
You want me to look after him ?
Sir, that really isn't necessary.
No, no, no. We'll put him
in Rose's room
while she's out of town.
Um, dad-
uh, do me a favor. We left
his overnight bag in the car.
Can you get that for us ?
Thanks, honey.
Right... yeah.
Oh, my g-
Hey. What are you doing here ?
What's wrong ?
Are the kids okay ?
Yeah, they're still with Larkin up north.
- I need you to come with me.
- Where ?
To my house. There's something
I have to show you.
- I'm working.
- It's important.
- What's this about ?
- You.
Sir, this doesn't feel right.
You have to stop arguing
with me, Lewis.
I know what's best for you.
Why'd you tell your daughter
I'd been shot ?
Because the truth is just
a little too complicated.
I really don't feel comfortable lying, sir.
You didn't lie. I did.
Now just get undressed, please.
- How long do I have to stay here ?
- Until you're recovered.
-  The doctor said that could be weeks.
- The doctor's wrong.
- How do you know ?
- I know.
This really hurts.
Yeah, I'll bet. We gotta get you some stronger meds.
I don't mean physically, sir
When I lost my arm in the war,
I figured it was god's will,
and  the other night
when I was in the water,
I thought god had given me my arm back
to help me swim.
I'm not so sure that was the reason.
Well, either way, I'm having
a difficult time with this
because I-I feel like I've gone against him.
No, no, no, no.
God must have helped you
make the decision to cut off your arm
because he knew how difficult
things would be for you otherwise.
I don't understand, sir.
Change scares people, Lewis.
You couldn't just show up into town,
flailing around a new arm
like you were captain of the swim team.
I mean, folks would be wildly unnerved.
They would start poking and prodding at you,
trying to look for a rational explanation
for the-the thing,
and there just isn't one.
That's why we need to keep this between us.
I guess you're right, sir.
Of course I am. Besides,
I think one arm suits you.
Gives you an edge.
- Where do you want it ?
- Right by the door, honey.
That's great.
Come in, Jess.
It's too cold.
Can you throw me some quarters ?
Uh, I don't really have any quarters.
Larkin, do you have any quarters ?
Uh, yeah-yeah, I think there's a few in there. Here.
You hungry ?
Uh, no. Still recovering from the chocolate corn dog.
Hmm. Yeah, not so good, huh ?
Any food on a stick is not to be trusted.
Okay, Rose...
Throw them in the deep end !
Sorry.
Watch me.
It's too deep.
Can you get them for me ?
Jess ?
- Jess ?
- Hold on a second, Rose.
- Hey, Jess ?
- What ?
I think I'm gonna go try
to track down a salad.
Can you watch Rose for me ?
Yeah.
I'll see you back at the room, okay ?
All right.
She's good.
Yeah.
Hey. Did you tell her yet ?
No.
You sure you want to ?
- Hey, Mariel.
- Hey.
So ?
Look, I want you to know the only reason
that I'm doing this
is because if I tried to explain it, I-I couldn'T.
Just show me.
- What is that ?
- A skeleton...
Your husband's skeleton.
The head's under my bed.
We didn't think that
you'd want to see that.
- Is this a joke ?
- No.
This is Tom, or at least,
what used to be Tom...
and this-this larger carcass
that's wrapped around it,
I think this is the remains of an invasive species
that's moved into the glades.
Russell and I found it
at the plane crash site of '96,
the one that Tom survived.
We think that he may have lived
through the initial impact,
only to be attacked by this thing,
but Tom is not who you think he is, Mariel.
Hell, he may not be who he thinks he is.
Then who is he ?
We think that these creatures
take people's D.N.A.,
Add their own poison to the mix
to basically create a new being,
like a hybrid, you know ?
Half us, half them.
It's okay if you're confused
right now 'cause
a lot of people are confused right now,
like all the survivors at your church group.
We heard about this morning.
They beat that guy
really badly, didn't they ?
Like a pack.
Mariel...
look, if you can just look at
the science of this thing-
"the science" ?
What are you trying to do here ?
Protect our kids.
- I can't have them living in a house-
- Oh my god, you son of a bitch
I  can't let them stay with you. It's not safe.
- I'm their mother !
- Are you sure ?!
He told me that you saw your body in biscayne cove.
That was a girl from Florida City.
The girl they pulled out may have been,
but who was in charge
of that operation ? Tom.
Look,  the night of the hurricane,
I think Tom saw you you
after you left here,
and I think he knows exactly what happened to you
because the same thing happened to him
almost ten years ago, Mariel
If I don't have my children
back to me by 6:00 tonight,
I will have a hundred lawyers in this driveway.
Ask him.
Just see what he says.
I can't believe you're doing this.
I can't believe you'd want
to hurt our family this badly.
- I'm just telling you the truth.
- No, you're telling me your truth !
- Excuse me, mr Deputy ?
- Lewis.
Oh, uh, where would you like this ?
Um, you can just put it right here.
Um, Kira ?
I'm sorry about all this.
It's okay.
I'd really rather be back at my place.
How did you get shot ?
hey, I thought you were
gonna rest.
Hope you like the soup.
I'm gonna go out for a little bit.
You gonna be all right here ?
I'm very confused, sir.
The arm wasn't the only thing
different about me, was it ?
I'm different all over now, aren't I ?
Yeah, but in time, you'll come to realize
that it's all for the good.
Hey...
it's all good.
Baby steps, Lewis,
baby steps.
I've never seen anyone
stay underwater that long.
I've never seen anyone like her,
period.
You think she's a mermaid ?
I think she's smokin'.
Hey, Rose, you, uh, you want to
go into town with me ?
Are you going to buy
more baby stuff ?
No, I was thinking about
buying more Rose stuff.
Okay.
- Bye, Jess.
- See you later, Jess.
hey.
Hey.
- What's up ?
- Nothin'. You're, just...
you're a really good swimmer.
Thanks.
You staying here ?
No. I just like the pool.
Have you been in yet ?
No. I'm more of an ocean guy.
Chlorine kinda bugs me.
We're kind of far from
the ocean here, aren't we ?
Yeah. I live down south,
like the homestead area.
My aunt lives there.
Yeah ?
Yeah. My family and I got stuck
down there during the hurricane.
- It was crazy.
- Yeah.
Look like you got through it okay.
- What's your name ?
- Jesse.
I'm emily.
Hi. Good to meet you.
- So was that your girlfriend ?
- My girlfriend ?
- The brunette ?
- The brunette.
-  What, the little one ?
- No, the big one.
No, that's-
that's my dad's wife.
Oh. I thought she was your girlfriend.
- She doesn't look much older than you.
- Well, she's not.
- Well, where did she go ?
- She went shopping with my little sister.
- Do you have a room here ?
- Yeah. We're staying here.
- Does it have a bathtub ?
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure it does. Why ?
I just can't believe she reacted that way.
Well, how did you think
she was gonna react ?
You just told her that
she's the bride of frankenstein
and that you're gonna
take her children away, Russ.
- What are you looking for ?
- An old phone book.
Russell, when are we gonna
tell the world
what's going on down here ?
When I know it's not gonna
hurt my kids.
- Your kids are outta town.
- Their mother's not.
Wait, what ?
You're protecting Mariel ?
She's the mother
of my children, Dave.
She was the mother
of your children.
If I can find a way to stop this
without destroying her,
that's what I'm gonna do.
She might destroy herself.
Healy said that the cubans
and brazilians, these hybrids,
- they were killing themselves and their children.
- And would you just stop calling them hybrids ?!
Why ?
That's what they are, Russ.
Okay.
Damn it.
What about the other mother
of your children ?
- Have you talked to her lately ?
- No.
Well, do you think maybe
you oughta give her a call ?
Not yet.
- Why not ?
- Because I don't know what to say.
"Sorry, honey, but you know
this perfect, little town
"I asked you to spend
the rest of your life in,
"well, it's been
overrun by aliens
"and one of them happens
to be my ex-wife" ?
And the sheriff and e head
of the news station-
and the priest.
He's the guy I need to talk to.
Here, if Larkin radios, just don't say anything
about any of this, okay ?
Tell her to stay put
and I'll be in touch.
- Where are you going ?
- To see the priest.
Russell !
How did this happen ?
He wanted to take his wife home
and our group wouldn't let him.
So they did this ?
I think they liked it.
Mariel, uh, I believe
you called me down here.
What do you want, babe ?
Answers.
I want to know exactly what happened to me
the night of the hurricane.
If you care about
our marriage,
you'll tell me
everything you know.
Who have you been
talking to ?
That doesn't matter.
I want the truth.
I don't know everything.
But you know more
than what you've told me.
If I've ever withheld anything
from you, it's because...
I love you.
Well, why don't you try
giving me a little less love
and a lot more truth,
and we'll see where we land ?
Tell me what happened
the night of the hurricane.
I'll do better than that.
I'll show you.
Sorry about this mess.
- It's okay. Nice.
- It's a quality tile.
- So, wanna take a bath ?
- What, together ?
There's no chlorine.
I don't know. Maybe we should
watch tv first or something...
what ? The electricity's out at home
and I don't get to watch it that much.
oh ! sorry.
Larkin and her porn.
So how come you don't
want to take a bath ?
'Cause  I don't know.
I don't really know you.
Do you ever really
know anybody ?
Yeah.
Who do you think
you know ?
My family, mom, dad.
Bet you're wrong. Bet
you don't know 'em at all.
- Whoa. You're weird.
- So they tell me.
What, do you always walk over
to strange guys
and ask them if they want
to take baths ?
No, they usually ask me.
Where do you live, Emily ?
I was in gainesville,
But not anymore..
You go to school there ?
Mm-hmm. U.F. I was a gator girl,
a phi gamma gator girl.
Cool. You graduate ?
Come on, Jesse,
if you're not getting in, I am.
Lewis ?
Um, I'm finished.
Okay. You all right ?
Yeah.
I just, uh...
I thinI should sit down.
thanks.
Yeah, you probably shouldn't
be walking around by yourself.
I guess not.
Crazy couple days...
But I guess
we've all been tested, huh ?
What ?
You lost your mom when you were
a litt girl, didn't you ?
Yeah.
Must have really tested
your faith when you lost her.
- Faith in what ?
- God ?
you believe in god,
don't you ?
Um, I guess.
I mean, I believe there is
something bigger than us.
Shoot, trees are bigger than us,
but god's who lives in your heart.
God gives you the courage
to face each day.
God... god is everything.
I'm sure your dad
taught you that.
Actually, I think he'd rather have
people believe he was everything.
Oh, no, don't say that.
Kira, wait a minute.
I know your father
is a man of faith.
He's counseled me
so many times.
About what ?
Um, my life,
choices I've made.
Yeah, well, he doe"t talk
to me much about anything,
so, uh, for all I know,
he could be the dalai lama.
The dalai lama's a buddhist.
Whatever.
Oh, no, no.
I could never follow someone
that didn't have a deep faith.
It would go against
everything I...
Oh, lord.
What-what is it ?
I think I should go now.
Why ?
I just think I need
some time by myself.
I'm a little confused
right now.
- Do you want me to leave ?
- No, no.
It's not about you.
It's just, uh, um,
I don't know who I am right now.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know
who I am.
I've lost my way, Kira.
I've been following
a blind man.
Lewis...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that you have
to see me like this.
Sorry.
I've sinned, Kira.
I've committed
a terrible sin.
God gave me the most beautiful gift
and I threw it away.
May I...
confess my sins to you ?
- Father ?
- Russell.
We, uh, we had an incident
this morning.
I heard.
What can I do for you ?
I wanted to talk to you
about your church group-
these survivors.
Oh, it's not affiliated
with the church.
It's something separate.
- You meet at the church.
- Only because it's convenient.
Fact is our meetings
are getting so big, we may have to move.
Are you thinking about
joining us ?
I'm not sure
that I'm qualified.
Does what happened this morning
concern you ?
Of course.
Well, why do you think
it happened ?
I don't know.
Father, you know Mariel
and I have two children.
I need to know if they're safe
in her home, with Tom, with her.
Are they safe ?
You saw what happened out there
this morning.
Mariel saw it, too.
Why didn't anyone
do anything to stop it ?
She did.
Mariel protected the man. I...
and the others...
we all just watched...
but she...
she protected him.
I couldn't have walked
all this way by myself in the storm.
You weren't by yourself.
You re with me.
How did I end up with you ?
The last thing I remember was leaving Russell's house to go looking for Rose.
I called you in your car.
I told you to meet me up by the main road,
by the melaleuca trees.
Why ?
I wanted
to show you something.
The last thing I remember when my
plane went down were the lights...
orange lights in the water.
For a long time, I thought
maybe it was burning fuel,
but I was wrong because
the night of the hurricane,
I saw those same lights
right here in the sky...
and I wanted you
to see them, too.
- What are they ?
- I don't know.
Have they done something
to us ?
Kept us alive, as far as I
can tell, made us stronger.
We came right down here
in this raging storm,
and we saw those lights...
come right down into the water,
and one minute, you're by my side,
and the next minute, you're not.
And you just let this happen
to me ?
There was nothing
I could do.
I wanted to stop it,
but I couldn't.
I couldn't.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe...
you wanted to stop it
and you couldn't.
What I wanted
was to trust you.
I wanted to be...
your wife and a good
mother to Jesse and Rose,
and you have taken that
away from me.
- No, I haven't.
- Yes, you have !
You did this to me.
Mariel...
Whatever is happening to me,
I am gonna fight it.
I swear, you are not
gonna do this to me, Tom.
- I'm leaving.
- You can't leave.
- You can't leave me now !
Damn.
Are you kidding me
right now ?
How do you do that ?
I don't know, but I think
I'm ready for the olympics.
God, you're so...
- weird.
- Weird.
Yeah.
But weird's cool.
I'm cool with weird.
Thanks for coming in
with me, Jesse.
Yeah, it's no problem.
Have you ever been
with a girl before ?
I mean, like this ?
Unh-unh.
Have you ever been
with a girl at all ?
Yeah, sure. I've walked
and I've talked with 'em,
but I've never been naked
in a bathtub with them.
- It's fun, right ?
- Yeah.
Huge fan, huge fan.
A few weeks ago, none of the
people I used to hang out with
wanted to be my friends
anymore.
You know sororities, they can
be so cliquey anyways, you know ?
I mean, their whole thing
is based on "us" and "them",
so if you change, you're no
longer an "us," you're "them. "
Yeah.
I've never really felt
like an "us. "
I've...
pretty much always been
a "them. "
Nice to meet you.
- Jesse ?
- Oh, god.
Jesse, you in there ?
Hey, uh, can you go out
this way ?
Yeah.
- Are you gonna be okay ?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure ?
- Thank you.
- For what ?
- For being a "them. "
Okay.
I'm comin' !
What are you doing
in there ?
hey, guys.
What were you doing ?
Takin' a bath.
I like baths.
And you wouldn't get in
the pool with me ?
Nope. I hate chlorine.
Three sorority sisters drowned
at university of florida, fourth girl sought
Mariel ?
Lewis ?
Lewis ?!
Kira, where is everyone ?
Who's "everyone" ?
Your stepmother, Lewis ?
Um, I haven't seen Mariel,
but, uh, Lewis left.
Left for where ?
He didn't say.
You were supposed to be
looking after him.
I did look after him.
I listened to his confession.
You what ?
Yeah. He told me the story
of abraham and isaac.
Have you ever heard it ?
As a test of faith, god asks abraham
to sacrifice his only child,
but in the end,
god spares the kid
because his father
had so much faith.
I think Lewis thought
you were like abraham, dad,
and then he found out
you were just a guy.
I mean, he lost it.
I don't know
what happened,
but he's lost his faith
in you.
Oh, god.
Ted, come in.
Ted, are you there ?
Yeah, Tom,
what's up ?
You know that thing we were
talking about ? I'm ready.
Roger that.
She'll be waitin'.
Mariel ?
Mariel.
Rose needs this
for her cat.
Are you planning a trip ?
Are the kids back yet ?
No.
Are they going to be ?
Not today.
Don't touch me !
Hey, listen to me,
listen to me. Hey !
Don't !
- I know how hard this must be for you.
- No, you don't !
- Yes, I do, Mariel !
I want to help you !
You want to take
our children away from me.
You actually think
I would hurt them ?
Whatever has happened to me,
part of me is still here,
the part of me
that loves my kids,
the part of me that once
loved you is still here.
hey, where you been ?
I didn't, uh,
I didn't know what to do
with the skeleton in there,
so I wrapped it up
and put it in my crawlspace.
Is that okay ?
Well, you know,
maybe we should bury it.
Bury it ?
That's the only proof we have
that Underlay's A...
that Underlay's
not what he says he is.
Right now, I'm not even sure
what that means, Dave.
What are you doing here ?
We came home early.
I don't think that place is as
cool as you remember it, honey.
Where are the kids ?
I just dropped them off
at Mariel's.
Tom called,
said they have plans.
What ? No.
Russell ?
Kids ?
Are you here ?
Jesse ?
Mariel ?
- What's wrong ?
- He's taken them.
- Tom's taken the kids.
- Where ?
I don't know, but we have
to find them.
Mariel, hold on a second.
What did the note say ?