Invasion
1x14- All God's creatures.
Transcript: RaceMan
Adaptation: Ez, Keno83, RonanaSplit & Lucile76
www.forom.com
Russell?
Hey.
What's wrong?
There's, um...
there's someone outside.
Hey, come on, guys.
Whatever it was, they're gone now.
Sheriff, can we ask you some questions?
Do you have a minute for us?
How are you feeling, sheriff?
I feel great.
I'm happy to be getting home to my family so soon.
I'm also grateful for the excellent doctors here at the hospital.
Any suspects in your shooting?
I'm not gonna get into the investigation right now.
You know, I'm gonna take my wife's advice...
go home and get some rest.
As for the investigation, the detective here
will answer all of your questions.
- Thank you, everybody.
- Thank you.
Detective, what information can you give us right now about this case?
- I'm gonna miss having you around.
- I'll see you tonight.
All set, sheriff?
Let's go get this son of a bitch.
I'm sure it was a person.
They were watching me.
A man or a woman?
I- I don't know.
They were crouched down in the doorway, and then...
and then they just took off.
I...
I'm having a baby, Russell.
I don't know if I can stay here any longer.
Honey, I know that you're on edge with all that's happened,
and I understand,
but I'm still not sure that we have anything to be afraid of.
Hey, I will protect you, I promise.
I want our baby to be safe, Russell.
This doesn't feel safe.
I'll find it...
him, her, whatever it was...
and I'll take care of it.
Three days ago, I was shot,
and now, well, I'm almost completely healed.
Some of you seem surprised.
Well, me, too.
I did not know that my body could do this.
Like you, I'm still learning about who and what I am,
but one thing I've discovered is that none of us
will experience this transformation in the same way.
Some of us will fight it.
Others may even become violent.
I'm looking for a man who needs our help today.
His name is Lewis Sirk.
He's my deputy.
If any of you know where he is,
I'd like to hear from you.
Small town, somebody must know something.
No?
All right...
but if any of you are harboring him...
if any of you are with holding information,
you will all be held accountable.
No, don't clean it up yet.
I want to get a good look at the crime scene,
and if you don't finish by the end of the day,
don't worry about it.
Mariel and my daughter...
they'll just stay at the hotel again.
Roger that, sheriff.
Got it.
Sheriff.
Hey.
Hey, is the deputy you're lookin' for the fella with one arm?
Could you give us a minute?
Yeah. What do you know?
Well, I've been doing a lot of swimming lately.
I was out at Logan Bay,
and I saw this guy swimming with one arm.
It was quite an odd sight to see, I have to tell you.
Now I didn't get that close, but when I was leaving,
I saw him washing some clothes on the shore,
like me might have been living out there or something.
Thank you, thank you.
This is helpful.
Yeah, I'm sorry that I didn't say anything earlier, sheriff.
I just...well, I just didn't want people to think I was a snitch.
You got it. We'll keep this between us, all right?
Absolutely.
What about the military?
They could have sent someone out here, right?
Larkin was snoopin' around that air base.
They were on her tail.
They could be after her again.
In the shower?
Okay, what about Healy?
He coulda came out here to talk to one of us.
He's got my phone number.
Then what if it's that guy he told you about...Szura...
the C. I. A. Hybrid assassin?
Who said he was an assassin?
Hey, Healy said they were in Cuba together.
What do you think they were doing out there, buying cigars?
They were there to check out the lights in the water,
and Szura got taken.
And Healy thinks he shot Underlay, right?
So Szura can become the top dog, the alien king?
It's a theory.
He's not sure.
Well, if this guy thinks Underlay's a threat,
he's really not gonna like Larkin.
She almost went on the news and blew the whistle
on the entire alien invasion.
All right, Dave, we still don't know that they're aliens,
and the only reason that anyone would think
that Larkin is a threat is because you've been blabbing
about our entire family on that stupid blog of yours.
It's not stupid.
No. No more.
She's so frightened now, of everything.
I just have to figure out a way for her to trust me again.
She trusts you, Russ.
She just doesn't trust what's out there.
What's that?
What's what?
Is that...
Whoa. This is mine.
- What's it doing out here?
- I have no idea.
- Look at this.
- What?
- What is that, a footprint?
- It's hard to tell.
- Dave, give me that.
- What?
Your record.
Whoa, hey, that's my favorite Buddy Holly record, Russ.
What are you gonna do with it?
No, no, no, no.
Oh, right on Buddy's face.
- Come on.
- Don't worry about it, Dave.
- I'll call you if I need you.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir.
- Hello, Lewis.
Could you put the gun down, please?
Y- yeah, of course.
I'm sorry.
Here.
Just put it down.
Hi, dad.
You brought him to our house.
You told me to take care of him, so that's what I did.
Well, I didn't mean for you to take care of him like this.
Nothing happened, dad.
Lewis and I are friends, that's all.
He just hasn't wanted to see anyone.
I mean, he's been really upset because of you.
You lied to me.
I- I...
no, you lied to me.
You told me he got shot, but that's not true.
That's not how his arm got messed up.
What were you thinking, dad?
He lost his arm in iraq, and he...
and he goes in the water and something incredible happened to him...
his arm came back.
Kira...
I mean, his arm came back,
and you just got so freaked out by it,
that you told him to cut it off.
What happened to Lewis is very complicated,
and...and if people find out about it,
they will tear him apart.
Why?
Because they'll think he's a monster, and...and...
they will destroy him.
Dad, it was a miracle.
It had to be.
And you just didn't have enough faith to support it.
Is that what he told you?
Is that why he shot me?
He didn't shoot you.
How do you know?
Because I was talking to him when it happened.
He gave me the number for a pay phone out here,
and we were talking when Mariel called and said you'd been shot.
I want you to know that despite appearances,
Kira and I have not been intimate in any way.
We've just talked.
Lewis, you left a note in my mailbox accusing me of betraying you.
And I'm sorry about that, sir, but...
do you believe in god, sir?
Yeah.
You do? 'Cause Kira wasn't sure.
She thought you didn't.
Well, Kira's 17, Lewis,
and she's unsure about a lot of things.
I believe in god.
I believe that he saved my life more than once,
and I believe that he saved yours
when you made the decision to remove your arm.
That's very difficult to comprehend.
I know, I know.
I have to have faith in my leader, sir.
I couldn't follow you unless you were a man of faith.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
It's all right.
There's more stuff missing from up here, Russ,
my record player is gone, too.
- Why did you bring this back?
- We found it by his record.
But what is it?
- Oh, my god.
- What?
My beer.
Bastard stole my beer.
I had at least two six- packs down there.
Russell, it...it was a person that was outside the bathroom,
not a horse or a deer or whatever this is.
Larkin, I don't know what this is yet.
I'm going back out there.
Dave, wait a second.
No, I bet you it's those kids that hang out at the steel bridge.
Saw them cruising their A. T. V. S around it yesterday. Punks.
- Hey, dad?
- What?
Tom is out back and he wants to talk to you.
Yeah, daddy and Dave built it for me.
Tom?
Hey. Rosie was just showing me her tree house.
Surprised to see you up and around.
A lot of people are.
Come here, baby.
Russell, you mind if I ask you a few questions?
No.
In private.
Come on, Russ, let's take a ride.
You ever been in the backseat of one of these things?
Oh, of course you have.
That must have been pretty scary.
Arrested, young kid, lookin' at murder one.
I didn't shoot you, Tom.
Did I say you were a suspect?
Fingerprints all over my house aside,
your son owning a. 45 aside,
did I accuse you in any way?
My son owns a. 45 because you gave it to him.
What do you want?
I know you know what I am,
at least, you think you do,
but someone must have helped you with this information.
You told your wife stories of people being replicated,
mass suicides, children being killed,
stories that you claim someone else told you.
Who is this person, Russell?
Because they sure don't sound like they like me.
This person didn't shoot you, either.
- How do you know?
- I know.
Well, do you have any idea who did?
No proof.
I'm open to conjecture.
There's a guy named Szura.
He might be your guy.
Szura?
- And where did you hear this name?
- Same person.
Well, this person carries a lot of weight with you, doesn't he?
Well, I trust him.
But you're not gonna tell me who he is?
No.
Because?
He doesn't trust you,
although he does feel that your survival's important,
and he's certain that Szura's a threat...
which is interesting because...
well, he's one of you.
One of me?
Oh, one of the "hybrids"?
I heard that's what you're calling us.
That's very trendy.
How do you spell Szura?
Rosie?
Dave?
Lark! Hey!
What is it?
She saw something oufront.
By the front door.
Hey, hey.
Hey, what'd you see, pal?
I don't know, but it was big.
Want me to look for this?
- No, no, no, no!
- Hey, hey, Jesse, no.
I'll go...
I'll go look for it.
I want you guys to go wait in Rose's room, okay?
All right? Catch your breath, there, kiddo, okay?
You're all right.
Quickly, come on.
What do you think it is, Larkin?
All right, keep the door locked, okay?
All right.
Larkin?
Okay, Rosie. Why don't you sit right here, okay?
But what is uncle Dave gonna do if finds it?
Okay.
What...
Oh, god, oh, god.
Dave?
It's in the house.
Where's daddy?
When's he coming home?
He's with Tom, sweetie.
But I'm sure he'll come home as soon as he can.
I want to help him.
I want to help Dave.
We're staying here.
Dave?
I'm helping him.
Dad would want me to.
I don't care.
This is your brother, Larkin.
Are you not the least bit worried about him?
Yes, but I'm worried about you, too.
Russell.
Now that all our cards are on the table...
I'm hoping we can have a smoother, more productive relationship.
Just because someone's different
doesn't make them a monster.
Funny. I just said the same thing to my wife this morning.
Look...whoever you are, just tell me what you want.
I've got a gun!
I'll shoot you, I swear!
Dave? Dave?
shoot it!
Mariel?
Hey, Kira.
Hey.
What's up?
- Can I talk to you a minute?
- Yeah, of course.
Kira?
What happens in the water?
Something happened to you the night of the hurricane, right,
and to my dad after the plane crash?
You both came out different, didn't you?
What happened?
I don't know.
I'm trying to figure that out.
I know someone else it happened to.
Really?
Why hasn't it happened to me?
Russell, I'm telling you, it kinda looks like me.
I wouldn't get too close.
Oh, he's still conscious, Russ.
Yeah, I can see that.
Oh, man, Russ...
he does look like me.
I mean, a very messed up version of me,
but...
if you look into his eyes...
then it might not be an accident
that this thin was taking my stuff.
Dave?
Hey.
Larkin.
What is it?
Did you catch it?
Oh, my god, what is that?
We're not exactly sure.
Is it a hybrid?
Russell, this may have happened
the night that creature got ahold of my legs.
What are you saying?
The night...
after the hurricane, Dave got attacked...
in the water.
We told everyone it was a gator, but...
it wasn't a gator.
so...you're saying that you think that this...
thing...
came from you?
I was only under for a minute.
Russell pulled me out really fast.
It may not have gotten enough genetic information.
Aw, hell, Russ.
What are we going to do?
It looks really sick.
It's all bleeding, its skin's all blistered.
It think it's having trouble breathing.
I think we need to do something.
All right, look, I got a first aid kit in my truck.
Are you going to touch it?
It may be dying.
But, Russell, you don't know what that thing is.
You don't know what it's going to do.
Larkin...
Larkin, come here.
No.
No, no, no, come here.
It's...it's trying to see you.
I don't think he wants you to leave.
It's okay, come here.
If you just come down here...
oh, god!
Okay, it's okay.
What is it doing?
I don't know.
All right, back up, back up. Okay...
all right, all right, all rit, back, back, back.
What is it?
It's us.
It's...it's us when we were kids.
There are a lot of mr. Varon's fingerprints here, sir.
Do you know if he owns a. 45?
He didn't shoot me, Lewis.
The only reason I wanted to talk to him
was to see what he knew, and he knows a lot.
It may lead to something...
but he didn't do this.
Are you...
Are you feelin' all right, sir?
Better than all right.
I hope you never get shot, Lewis,
but if it should happen,
be glad you're in the body you got right now.
It's a hell of an upgrade.
Thanks.
Kira, hey, baby.
I thought I was gonna meet you at the hotel.
I need some more clothes.
I talked to Mariel.
Oh?
I had some questions for her.
She said I should talk to you.
Well, it's not really a great time right now, honey.
We're still working.
Well, when is a good time?
I don't know.
Well, can I talk to Lewis, then?
About what?
Dad, can I just talk to him, please, for two minutes?
Will you come with me to get my stuff?
I...
yeah.
Take a break. Go ahead.
Five.
How's he doing?
His breathing has slowed down a lot.
Hey, Lark, come here.
This was, uh,
this was my favorite picture of us when we were kids.
Did you know that?
He could have taken a lot of pictures,
but he took this one.
How much do you think he knows?
I mean...
do you think he remembers when this was taken?
I don't know.
Does he have your memories?
Well, Mariel has hers.
Yeah, but Mariel came back whole.
Everyone we know of, so far, anyway, has come back whole.
I'm sorry if I got you into trouble with my dad.
No, no, no, it's not your fault.
It was inappropriate for me to be sharing the things with you that I did.
But, you know, I've just never been that close with people,
especially after I lost the arm.
People were always like,"oh, poor guy."
I hate that.
I know.
People have always treated me like,
"poor orphan girl, lost her mom."
It sucks.
Look, I want you to know that
even if we don't get to see each other much anymore,
I believe everything you said.
I believe that you getting your arm back was a miracle.
I'm sorry my father didn't.
Thank you.
It's his problem.
I tried talking to Mariel about it,
but I think I just made her uncomfortable.
Lewis...
I want to know what's in the water.
Good or bad, I want to know about it,
'cause I've always felt different, too.
I mean, people have accepted me...
and I've even been popular,
but I've never really felt like I belonged anywhere...
not even in my own family.
And it's just getting worse.
I mean, I feel like they're part of this secret club, you know?
And they just don't want me to be a part of it.
Yeah.
You know, Kira, you might want to talk to father Scanlon about all this.
He runs the hurricane survivor group,
- and they've all had similar exper...
- Lewis.
- I promised Mariel that we'd finish tonight.
- It's all right. I was just leaving.
- Good night, Lewis.
- Night, Kira.
See ya.
So you two work everything out?
She's a very special girl, sir.
Yes, she is.
She's also a very young girl.
And in many ways, she's a very naive girl.
I suggested she speak with father Scanlon.
Whenever I've had questions about things,
he's always been very helpful.
But you haven't spoken to him recently, have you?
Oh, yes, sir. He's the first person I sought counsel from
after I left your house.
Really?
- He's my priest.
- No, I know.
You saw him recently?
- Did you talk about cutting off your...
- Yes, sir, but it was in confession,
so...
Sir?
- Should we take him to the hospital?
- I think it's too late for that.
I should go inside.
I promised Rose I wouldn't be gone for very long.
Hey, listen, uh, don't...
don't tell the kids about this.
Yeah, I won't.
Russ...
I hope our baby's like you.
I hope that he or she is never afraid of what they don't understand.
Oh, my god, I am heartily sorry for my sins,
and I firmly resolve,
with the help of thy grace, to confess my sins...
to do penance...
and to amend my life.
I...
- Tom.
- It's all right, father.
You're not alone.
We both know it was you.
What do you mean?
Oh, come on, what,
are you gonna make me start quoting passages of judas?
Why would you want to kill me?
You abuse the privilege of God's grace.
You...you mutilated a man in the name of your own...
twisted belief.
You misled us all, Tom.
After Lewis came to me, I was...
overcome with rage at your betrayal.
To think that I had counseled you in God's name...
How could you think you'd ever escape His justice?
How could you ever think that you'd escape mine?
Are your deputies outside?
You're not going with my deputies.
As a matter of fact,
you're not even gonna go to jail.
I'm gonna send you to another place entirely.
What sort of place?
It's a place that an old friend of mine runs.
A mr. Szura.
Have you ever heard of him?
No.
Well, he's a hell of a guy, and he runs a little camp
down in the keys for people just like you who've lost their way.
I think this place is gonna straighten you right out.
It seems to be working for others.
Szura?
Szura.
I think it's a name you're gonna remember.