Previously on "Invasion"...
There's a huge storm coming,
and he's still not home.
How was I ever married to this person ?
As a storm gathers...
My pregnant wife shouldn't be covering hurricanes.
Talk to your brother ?
He's with your kids at the house.
- I've been through hurricanes before.
- Not like this one, you haven't.
These families prepare...
I have a right to know my children are safe.
They're our children !
Rose isn't here.
Rose !
Why don't you go home and
worry about your new husband
and leave us alone ?
But can this family survive...
Rose !
What lies ahead ?
Mariel ?
What's happening to me?
Did you see the lights ?
Where'd you see them ?
Will you tell me what's going on here ?
Mommy ?
You smell different.
First days are the toughest.
Baby steps, honey.
Invasion
1x02 - Lights out
Transcript RaceMan
Adaptation Ez, Keno83, RonanaSplit & Lucile76
www.forom.com
Yeah ?
Hi, daddy.
Hey, honey.
What are you doing ?
Feeding carlita.
Nothing. I, um...
I'm just getting ready to go out back to work.
Mommy and daddy Tom aren't home yet,
and Kira and Jesse are making dinner.
So I thought I'd ask you.
Yeah, go ahead. Ask me what ?
Are there monsters ?
No.
Are you sure ?
'Cause you know those lights I saw in the sky
during the hurricane,
the ones that went into the water ?
Yeah ?
I thought they might be monsters.
They weren't monsters, Rose.
Then what were they ?
How do you explain the unexplainable ?
One family's devastated while
another gets through this without a scratch.
Hurricanes kind of havea mind of their own.
We didn't ask to be hit this hard.
Frankly, we didn't expect to be.
But we're grateful the damage
is nothing like what we saw
with andrew back in '92.
Uh, Mr. Mayor, we heard rumors of a quarantine.
We're still working on all this.
Aside from the damage to the hospital,
we've received reports of chemical and fertilizer plants opening up
as well as contaminants found in the water supply.
Now when you consider that
we still have hundreds of people missing--
no one has authorized an actual quarantine yet--
just a few checkpoints here and there.
Russell ?
Yeah, Dave ?
Have you checked out that skeleton I found yet ?
I'm on my way to do it right now.
Oh, you moved it ?
No, I took your car.
Out into the hurricane slop.
Dave, who cares ?
I do, Russ.
It's a collectible.
Good-bye, Dave.
Would you support a quarantine, doctor ?
Doctor ?
I was the one who originally suggested it.
Sheriff, will your office be coordinating the relief effort--
search and rescue, military ?
Everyone will be working together on this,
but my office will run point, yes.
Over here.
So you'll be in charge ?
God's in charge. I just handle the paperwork.
Yeah ?
Sheriff, when can we expect to have
electricity and running water again ?
You'll be the first to know.
Hey, your dad likes being on tv, doesn't he ?
He always says, "presentation is everything."
Rose, do you want some more juice ?
No, thanks.
Dr. Underlay,
We understand that you went through
quite an ordeal the night of the storm--
13 hours in biscayne bay ?
That's right.
How are you feeling ?
Under the circumstances, pretty fortunate.
Rose, aren't you hungry ?
I miss mommy.
She's right there, rose.
...operation center set up...
No. She's not.
Pretty scary night for you, too, sheriff.
Your wife's very lucky.
She's a survivor.
Dr. Underlay ?
- What is the extent of the damage in the hospital ?
- Larkin ! Larkin !
Stay back behind the yellow tape.
Dave, I'm working.
This quarantine will kill us.
We'll be completely cut off.
It hasn't even happened yet, okay ?
And even if it does, the hurricane relief groups
will still have access, all right?
The hurricane is not our problem.
Dave, you're my brother--
and I love you, but I am tired,
I'm pregnant, and you're medicated.
Will you please go back to your room ?
No.
Nurse, could you make sure he gets back to his room, please ?
You suck.
Russell will be here to pick you up in the morning.
Fight the power, Larkin.
Fight the power !
.. major roads and some major highways will have their lanes reversed
to handle the evacuation traffic.
State officials hope to avoid a repeat of the mess
that occurred with hurricane Floyd in 1999.
- You know his name ?
- No
- Any I.D. ?
- None that I could find.
- What was he doing at your place ?
- I have no idea.
Coming through ! Right over here.
Follow me. Come on.
Our temp E.R.Is right over here.
Coming through !
One, two, three.
How did this happen ?
Hey, Russell ?
Baby, you there ?
Hey, honey.
Where are you ?
I'm at the hospital.
Why ?
I just found some guy in my station who was...
who was cut up real bad.
Who is he ?
Is he gonna be okay ?
I'm not sure.
Listen, is the generator in the shed ?
Don't...
- Don't go to the shed.
- Why not ?
Because it's dark down there.
I just don't want you by the water.
It's dark in the house.
I need power. I need to work.
Can you just grab a flashlight
and go in the bedroom ?
I'll be home as soon as I can.
Flashlight's not gonna run my computer.
- Why do you need your computer ?
- Why are you being so weird ?
No, no. I'm not being weird,
I'm just being protective.
Well, if you really want to be protective,
don't introduce my brother to any more alligators.
I gotta go, honey.
She still thinks I was attacked by a gator ?
- Let me see your leg, Dave.
- What for ?
- Just let me see it.
- Ow ! All right.
Okay, easy.
- Why haven't you told Larkin the truth yet ?
- I don't know what the truth is.
Yes--yes, you do.
I was attacked by an E.B.E--
- an extraterrestrial biological entity.
- We don't know that.
Oh, okay. I was sucked under water by a bright,
orange sea blob and had my flesh branded.
Yeah, that's more plausible,right ?
What ?
What, Russ ?
Let me see that.
Oh, man.
Who is this ?
It's a guy I found in my station today.
This guy has the exact same wounds as me.
He's been prodded.
This is definitely the work of an E.B.E., Russ.
- I could show you hundreds--
- I can show you hundreds of pictures of weird fish
being tossed up by a tsunami.
- It's not a f--
- Just because something's unfamiliar doesn't mean it's an alien.
Okay. So it was a fish that I found
wrapped around that skeleton ?
Were those just fins shooting through the guy's skull and rib cage ?
Taken the time to study that ?
I was going to, till I got a little way laid by a man bleeding to death.
What's a guy in a wet suit doing
swimming around the everglades in the middle of a hurricane ?
I don't know.
You'd better find out before
someone else decides to take a little dip.
You did really great out there.
No, I didn't.
I mean, I'm trying, but I really...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come here. Come here.
After what you've been through ?
You did great.
What's up ?
I think I lost my wedding ring in the storm.
I've looked everywhere for it.
We didn't lose you.
Hey, Russell ?
Yeah, Dave ?
Hey. So what did you find out ?
- I haven't checked the skeleton yet.
- Why not ?
I'm trying to figure outwhat happened to the guy.
You know what happened to the guy.
He was attacked like me, like the skeleton.
Why are you in such denial here ?
Dave, you need to give me some time.
Yeah, while the mother ship is landing ?
Will you please just hurry up
and take a look at the damn thing ?
And try not to scratch my car.
We're gonna turn off the generator now.
And you got your flashlight and your water.
And we're gonna be right in the next room, okay ?
Why hasn't mommy called ?
Well, the phones are out, Rose.
She could call on the radio.
Even when she works late,
she always calls.
Yeah, I know. But it's different tonight.
Hurricanes make everything different.
I don't want things to be different.
Okay.
Hey, Kira ?
Night, Rose.
Are you allergic to any medication ?
No.
Deep breath.
The nurse told me that I was in the water all night.
Is that true?
That's what I understand.
And again.
I hear you had a similar experience.
Yeah.
Guess we both must be pretty good swimmers, huh ?
Oh, well, that's just it--
I don't know how to swim.
Come on, bring it through !
All right.
Don't pitch that too close to the landing zone, boys !
We don't want the choppers giving us haircuts.
Sheriff,we've got U.S. 1 cleared,
and we're almost done with Krome avenue.
Good job, Lewis. Turnpike still closed ?
Yes, sir.
Keep it that way.
5-mile radius !
Tom ?
Hey, Russ. What brings you out of the jungle at this hour ?
Did you authorize the military to enter the park ?
Why would I do that ?
A military vehicle passed by my place tonight,
and I just found a guy out there that was pretty messed up--
Air Force. I found his dog tags.
I don't control the military, Russ.
Yeah, I know.
But you are working with them now, aren't you ?
The guy's name was Paxton.
He was in a wet suit when I found him.
- He was in a wet suit ?
- Yeah.
- Did he say anything ?
- He was unconscious.
Do you have any idea why he might have been out there ?
No.
Well, as soon as he's awake, I'm gonna talk to him.
- If you hear anything, let me know.
- Will do.
Lewis ?
Sir ?
Get General Dearing, Patrick Air Force base.
You got it.
Hey, Mrs. Varon.
Where have you been ?
Oh, missing you.
I see you went down to the shed.
So ?
Thought I told you not to.
Are you my boss or my husband ?
Honey...
Baby ?
You stink.
Sorry.
No water, no shower.
Wrong.
How's our baby ?
Hungry.
Did you sleep okay ?
No. I was worried about you.
Why were you gone all night ?
Just following upon that guy I found.
Is he gonna be okay ?
I think.
I called the hospital a few hours ago,
and they said he was stabilized.
Did you get in contact with his family ?
I tried, but the D.O.D. wouldn't tell me anything.
The D.O.D.?
He's in the Air Force.
Well, when I get into the office, I can check
and see if anything's come in over the wires about a missing airman.
What do you think happened to him, Russ ?
Baby ?
Guys.
Oh, boy.
You guys walked all the way from your mom's ?
Well, I carried her part of the way,
but she really wanted to see you.
Is that right ?
Really ? You miss your daddy, huh, Rose ?
Mommy didn't come home last night.
What ?
She's fine.
Tom called this morning and said
that they both just got caught up at work.
But she didn't call, so... it kind of sucks.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I didn't come home last night either.
But if you guys want to hang around today,
maybe tonight you can help daddy do some replanting.
Replanting what ?
These were all growing on the property.
But I brought them in before the hurricane
so they wouldn't get hurt.
- You remember what this one is ?
- Not really.
It's a Butterfly Orchid.
And this one, this one's called a Turk's Cap.
And that one over there, that's a little pond Apple tree.
That's gonna grow up to be a very, very bigpond Apple tree.
And this one right here is a little Rose...
who's gonna grow upway too fast.
No, I won't.
You won't?
Hey, did you hear that, Jesse ?
She said she's never growing up.
Never, ever, ever.
She in yet, Reed ?
No. Eve hit her pretty hard.
She said she might be in this afternoon.
Could you get somebody on the satellite for me ?
What do you need ?
Officer in charge of public affairs
at the department of defense.
You got it.
Thanks.
Hey, buddy.
Just don't let them in.
Don't let them in !
What ? What ?
What ?
Don't let who in ?
What are you doing ?
Got a minute ?
Hey, Russell.
How are you feeling ?
All right.
Wanted to give you these.
They belong to the guy I brought in last night--
Paxton.
How's he doing ?
Well, I think he'll recover.
Is there something else ?
No.
This is a tissue fragment I removed from his head.
It's mostly cartilage,but it's covered with tiny,
geometric spores.
They're not fungal, not bacterial.
This was not a part of him.
I'm thinking maybe a lampreyor a jelly stinger,
but this is your area of expertise, not mine.
It was still moving when it came out.
I think it may have been ingurgitating fluids.
Like a feeding tube.
Do you mind if I take this with me
so I can run a few tests ?
No, please.
Dr. Underlay, you're needed in I.C.U. Ten.
I'll be right there.
You know, Mare, when you get a chance,
you really should radio the kids.
Why ?
They were pretty upset this morning.
They came by my house.
Your house ? Why did they do that ?
Because you didn't come home last night.
I'm sorry, Russell. I have to go.
Do you remember when
we lived here with mommy, Jess ?
I sure do, Rose.
Was I a baby ?
You were pretty little, yeah.
Was mommy different then ?
What, like, different how ?
More different than since the hurricane.
Why do you think she's different now, Rose ?
I don't know.
She just doesn't look the same.
Yes, she does.
Maybe on the outside, but not in.
Well, how do you know what she looks like on the inside ?
It's not that I didn't call the kids.
It's that I didn't even think about calling them.
They weren't even in my mind.
Russell had no right to come in here and lay this on you.
This isn't about Russell. This is about me.
I don't know what's happeningto me, Tom.
It's like part of me is here, but...
another part...
a different part...
is pulling me away.
Honey, honey, you've been up for,
what, almost 36 hours ?
Let me take you home.
Hey, how are you gonna take care of others
if you don't take care of yourself ?
Did you ever feel like this with Kira, after her mom died ?
Did you ever feel like a part of you was abandoning her ?
I don't remember.
Sorry, ma'am,you've gotta turn around.
Oh. I'm with channel 7.
Okay, I see that.
The sheriff doesn't want anyone on this road.
- Has the quarantine gone into effect ?
- Not yet.
- Then why can't I get through ?
- It's for your own protection, ma'am.
Safety circle. 5-mile radius.
Yeah, I know, but I have to see somebody in cutler ridge.
I'm very sorry.
Listen, I'm married to the sheriff's wife's ex-husband.
So...
whatever.
Sorry, Sir. You've gott ahead back.
Why was Underlay in Paxton's room?
I don't know. Maybe the military got to him.
He took my camera, the bastard.
Could have used the better photos.
- For what ?
- For evidence.
What do you think ?
Russ, do you not see what's going on here ?
This hurricane was just a cover
so the aliens could land undetected.
Then the Air Force sent out their welcome party.
Boom ! They were attacked.
"Don't let them in," Paxton kept saying.
"Don't let them in."  Who do you think they were talking about--
the Cubans ?
Okay.
We gotta do this quick.
What are you gonna examine first  ?
- The antennas or the prods ?
- There's no antennas, Dave.
- How do you know ?
- Because I've seen the thing.
Well, they could be retracted.
I'm gonna examine the skeleton
and whatever's wrapped around the skeleton
and see if it compares to the tissue fragment Mariel gave me.
Good. Ohh !
And then we're gonna take this whole thing to the coroner.
No souvenirs, you got that ?
Fine. Unless there's antennas.
Dude.
I appreciate you coming by, father.
I know how busy you must be.
Anything for you, Tom.
- He's conscious ?
- Yeah.
But my wife assures me that he won't make it till morning.
- Are you certain ?
- Absolutely.
David, I'm father Scanlon.
I'm here to help you.
If there's anything you'd like to tell me at any time,
you feel free to go ahead and say that.
Sheriff ?
Say a prayer, Adrienne.
Say a prayer.
Through this holy anointing,
may the Lord, with His love and mercy...
help you with the grace of the Holy Spirit.
May the Lord who frees you from sin
save you and raise you up.
may the Lord who frees you from sin
Uh, yes ?
Miss paxton. My name's Larkin Groves.
I'm sorry to come all the way out here without calling,
but your phones are out.
I got your address fromt he public affairs office.
If you're looking for my husband, he's not here.
He's overseas.
What ?
Is there anything I can help you with ?
Miss paxton, I'm sorry if I'm the one to tell you this,
but y-your husband's in the hospital.
He's just south of here.
I think you're mistaken.
I wish I were.
David's overseas
on a mission.
What kind of mission?
I don't think I should be talking to you.
Listen, I-I could take you to see him if you want.
- They're blocking most of the roads, but--
- No, I want you to leave.
- Ms. Paxton, please.
- Now.
He's at homestead hospital.
Underlay said there was a lot of looting going on.
People steal food and appliances, Dave,
not human remains.
Then it had to be the military.
You said you saw them out here checking things out, right ?
Patrolling the area, looking for Paxton maybe.
- Maybe they looked in the trunk of my car.
- Maybe they did.
I gotta talk to Paxton. Paxton's the key.
Look, I'm gonna check on the kids,
and then I'm goin'right back to the hospital.
All right, what if they don't let us in ?
Who, Mariel ?
Underlay.
I don't take orders from him.
Well, he is the sheriff, Russell.
Yeah, the sheriff who's working with the military.
And the sheriff who's sleeping with your ex-wife.
I'm just sayin' that you might not be as objective
about the guy as you should be, okay ?
Where the hell did he come from ?
Did you know he was gonna be here ?
No.
What the hell ?
What's goin' on ?
We're picking up the kids.
You didn't call me.
I talked to you at the hospital.
Yeah, and ?
- Hey, guys--
- No, wait. Hold on.
You left 'em last night, Mariel.
They're here because you left them alone
so they shouldn't have to go now.
- It's okay, dad.
- No, it's not okay.
Mariel, she was very upset.
Rose, it's okay. Tell her.
But I wanna go, daddy.
I miss Carlita.
We really appreciate you being here for them.
I'll drop them off on wednesday, okay ?
Go give your daddy a kiss, sweetheart.
I love you.
I love you, too, daddy.
Reed.
Did you get in touch with Val ?
Yeah, I ran your story by her.
She wants to talk to you.
Great.
Val.
Larkin.
Reed told you about this missing airman ?
Val, his wife didn't even know he was down here.
It sounds to me like the military is covering something up.
She thought he was ona mission overseas.
I-I told her that he was here in the hospital
and I offered to bring her down here,
but she seemed so scared.
Larkin, the man is dead.
What ?
I just talked to the hospital.
That's not the story I want to tell.
I-I want our viewers to see how we're coping, adapting.
How did you get out of town ?
I thought there were roadblocks.
I went around them.
You could've been arrested.
Since when do you care how I get a story ?
Val ?
This man was obviously down here
on some kind of classified mission.
Now he's dead, and no one's talking about it.
And you're concerned about my driving record ?
I don't want this story, Larkin.
Not this story.
Dave !
What ?
Paxton's dead.
- Give me your keys.
- What ? Why ?
Just give me your keys.
Uh... how do you know he's dead ?
Larkin just called.
She said Paxton's wife knew nothing
about him being down here.
And apparently the Air Force just swooped in
and took his body away.
Well, then how do you know he's dead ?
I mean, did anybody actually see him dead, Russ ?
Call me crazy...
I don't care if you're crazy, Dave.
I care about how all this affects my family.
If there's something going on here,
something bigger than the hurricane...
how can I protect my kids
when they're not with me ?
They're with you, Russ.
They're in the town.
But right now the town may need your protection
just as much as they do.
What are you looking for ?
Hair, nails, teeth--
anything to pull some D.N.A. from.
Okay.
Is this yours ?
No.
"Two become one."
That's the inscription.
What ?
Any idea who this belongs to ?
Will you marry me ?
Why'd you do this ?
'Cause you're my wife.
How's it fit ?
Pretty good.
Where'd you get it ?
Stole it off a looter.
Mommy.
Mommy, I'm ready for bed.
I'll be right there, honey.
Hi.
- You brush your teeth ?
- Yep.
- You want Mobat ?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry I didn't call you last night, honey.
- It's okay.
No, it's not.
I want you to know
I'm gonna try very hard not to let that
happen ever again, okay?
I was just kinda worried.
I know.
And you know what ?
You're not gonna lose me.
Ever. I promise.
Even when you die ?
Well, you know, that's not gonna happen
for a very, very, very long time.
I've been wanting to tell you something, mommy.
Hey, Mare.
It's the hospital.
Can you save it till tomorrow ?
- Good night, sweetheart.
- Night, mommy.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
This is dr. Underlay.
- You feelin' okay now, Rosie ?
- I guess.
Hey...
is there somethin' you wanna tell me ?
- Okay.
During the hurricane, I saw lots of lights.
They were beautiful.
They fell out of the sky and into the water.
And then...
they swam away.
Can you keep a secret, honey ?
I saw them, too.