Previously on Invasion"...
I don't want to be
a prisoner anymore, Derek.
Do you understand that?
That's why we got
away from Szura. Okay.
You know about
the lights in the water, right?
What's wrong
with the town?
- I am not an alien!
- Then what are you?
Because we know you've been
different for a long time.
Our family is never going
to be the same again, is it?
You any closer
to finding Szura?
No. But if I die
before it happens,
you'll kill him for me,
won't you?
They're supposed to start
school again tomorrow.
Wonder how that's gonna go.
I think I'm pregnant,
you son of a bitch!
Szura, don't lose anymore.
Hey, we found him!
We found Szura.
Invasion
1x17 - The key.
Transcript RaceMan
Adaptation : Ez, Keno83, RonanaSplit
& Lucile76
www.forom.com
Honey, what bag is the coffee in?
Duffel in the back.
I need the keys...
and a map.
And I don't have time
to argue about it.
- Good morning, Mar.
- Morning.
- Did you sleep okay, honey?
- Yeah, all right.
Yeah, not so all right.
It's the kids' first day
back at school today.
I know.
It'll be the first time in their lives
that I haven't taken them.
Well, I'm sure you could have.
Did you talk to Russell about it?
He wanted to take Rose.
Jesse's not talking
to me right now, so...
Ah, he's just going
through a hard time.
He'll come around.
I tried calling him.
And I wrote a little note
for Rose's lunchbox, but...
Why don't you give it to me?
I'll drop it off on the way to work.
I think they feel like
they've lost their mother, Tom.
They haven't.
And if we ever have
a baby of our own,
they'll see you're not
that different after all.
Here you go.
Thanks for the ride.
You okay?
No. I don't know
what I'm doing here.
You've got to go
to school, Jess.
I'm not talking about school.
I'm talking about here, in this town.
If we're really being
overrun by aliens,
what are we doing here?
All right.
- You ready for your first day back?
- Yup.
You might make
some new friends.
How will I know?
Know what?
When people are, you know,
like mommy.
Hey, you brush your hair
this morning?
Yeah.
You still got
a couple knots in it.
You remember we're not gonna talk about
any of this stuff with anyone else, right?
We don't want to scare anybody.
But how will I know?
You might not.
But all you have to worry about
is you right now, okay?
You just be who you are.
All right, come on.
Let's go.
Daddy Tom!
Hey, sweetheart.
Hey, how are you?
Hey, Russ.
Been workin' in the mines?
Russ, this is Ms. Wade.
She's gonna be taking over
for mr. Gonzales.
Hi. Sheriff Underlay's told me so much
about you and your daughter.
- Hi, Rose.
- Hi.
What happened
to mr. Gonzales?
Oh, I'm afraid that
this last hurricane
was too much for him,
and he moved up to orlando.
Yeah. Well,
he's gonna be missed,
but ms. Wade here
is gonna fit right in.
Can I talk to you a second?
Sure.
Excuse me.
We haven't found anything
about Christina right now.
This isn't about Christina.
Eli Szura.
You told me
you didn't know who he was.
But the man we met yesterday
from county services,
the man that you called
on the radio?
That was Szura, and you knew
exactly who he was.
Szura killed my friend.
I better not fd out you had
anything to do with it.
What friend?
What friend, Russ?
Daddy?
Hello?
Hey, Russ.
I'm still at Healy's trailer.
You forget about me?
No, I'm on my way
back to you now.
I found something...
in one of healy's coat pockets.
It's a key.
A key to what?
I don't know. It's got something
engraved on it, though.
It says, "h-p-m 2-2-8."
That's for a boat.
For a boat?
Yeah, H.P.M. Stands
for highland point marina.
Did you know Healy
had a boat?
No.
Well, why don't we go
down there and check it out?
I mean, I don't know
if it's gonna get us
any closer
to finding Szura,
but might be a computer
on board or something.
What do you say?
Russ?
Nothing around here is ever
gonna be the same again, is it?
I love this town, Lewis,
and I will not let it slip away from me.
It won't, sir.
Good always triumphs
over evil.
And which side are we?
Good, of course, sir.
Then how do you explain
Christina Conrad?
She's killed
two people already-
not exactly the poster girl
for our future.
We'll find her, sir.
Our people are looking.
Mr. Varon's people are looking.
We'll find her.
Or she'll find us.
Just keep it cool.
Get me to an exam room.
Good morning, dr. Underlay.
Good morning.
Don't stop.
- I have to check in.
- No, you don't.
Dr. Underlay?
Do you need some assistance?
No, thank you.
We're fine.
Where are we going?
The examination room
is right here. It's here.
Get in here.
So if we actually find Szura,
do you have a plan for what
we're gonna do with him?
Russell?
I'll have him arrested.
I thought you didn't want
the police involved.
Not locally.
We take him to Miami.
How do we know what's going on
here isn't going on there?
I mean, Kira got attacked
in the water.
We thought it was just going
in the glades,
but if these creatures
are in the ocean now, too,
I mean,
they could be anywhere.
Look, I don't want to think
about that right now, Dave.
I just want to find Szura,
make sure that my kids get through
their first day back at school.
Yeah, all right. Fine.
228.
Well, let's check it out.
It's filthy.
- You friends with the owner?
- yeah.
- What's his name?
- Healy.
Haven't seen
much of him lately.
I thought he might have
finally taken off for good.
You, uh, you really
friendly with him?
You know him well?
We're just neighborly.
Did he ever find that island
he's looking for?
Island?
He waslways talking about retiring
to some island in the keys.
Seemed pretty serious
about buying one.
- So he was looking for an island?
- Yeah.
Sounds like
a pretty good idea these days.
Since the hurricane, this place
has gotten too strange.
Hey, man.
What's up?
Nothing.
Where you sittin' at?
Uh, over there
with greg and will.
Well, uh...
see ya.
Jesse, right?
- Anyone sitting here?
- No.
- I'm brett.
- I know.
- Strange, huh?
- What's that?
Well, the way things
have changed.
Come on,
you see it too, right?
I mean, look at that.
Stephanie Johnson
talking to Weidermeyer?
I mean, come on.
Sunglass man?
A lot of these guys didn't hang
out with each other last year.
Yeah. It's kind of weird.
Yeah.
So your family make it
through the hurricane okay?
Because, you know,
a lot of people didn't.
Yeah. We made it all right.
What about you?
Not so much.
So are you going to abandon this child
like you did your last one?
Well, not to split hairs,
but that baby
wasn't mine anymore.
Because the body I'm in now
hasn't given birth.
Neither has yours,
by the way.
Is that hard for you-
pretending that you still love
what used to be your children?
I do love my children.
Right. Right.
You just keep
telling yourself that.
Leave it!
It's my husband.
If I don't answer,
he may show up here.
Is that what you want?
Calm and happy.
Hi.
Hey, baby.
I got your note to Rose.
You ever reach Jesse?
I, um...
I talked to him briefly
while he was on his way to school.
Talked to Kira
at the house today.
She sounds like she's doing
a lot better now.
Good. Good.
Are you, uh,
all right?
I'm actually just with
a patient right now, Tom.
Can I call you back?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
Just, uh...
just checkin' in,
tellin' you that I love you.
I love you, too.
Is this how you manage things for the C.I.A.?
You have to be flexible, Tom.
If everything goes
according to plan,
Christina will be found.
Security on the island
will be improved.
I'll continue to isolate
the bad seeds
for as long as you think
it's necessary.
I've got Derek patched up.
She tried to kill him.
Some women are fickle
that way, eh?
Russell knows who you are.
He thinks you murdered
some friend of his.
The park ranger?
Yeah, the park ranger who
shares children with my wife?
The park ranger who we're gonna
need to help contain this?
Yeah, that one.
- I can contain this.
- No, you can't.
This girl is running arod
killing people in my community.
And they're not going to hold
you accountable for that.
They're going to come to me.
I really believe that we can
all work together, Eli-
the people in this town
that have been changed
and the people who haven't-
if there's mutual trust.
Feeling better?
Um, yeah. Yeah, much.
Good. Then we should be
on our way.
Great.
- Where are we going?
- To find your girlfriend.
She's obviously
very confused right now.
She needs our help.
- No. No, she's crazy.
- No, no. She's pregnant.
Oh, god!
what is it?
I just...
it fee like
it's eating me alive.
I mean, it's only been
three weeks.
Have you ever seen anyone
this big after only three weeks?
Who's the father?
She shot me.
The bitch shot me, man.
Well, I'm sure
that was an accident.
We'll find her. We'll take
her back to the island,
and before you know it,
you'll be celebrating
the birth of your son.
My son?
You know it's a boy?
Well, no, but we can
always hope, right?
Yeah...
I really want to.
You know, I really
want to be a father.
I know.
But she's just-
she's just so nuts.
She'll be fine.
She just needs
a little support.
Come on.
How are we gonna find her?
The way every other species
finds its way-instinct.
I have no idea
what I'm looking at here.
Satellite photos of the keys
I got from our weather station-
120 miles of them.
Yeah, but Szura's here.
- He killed Healy here.
- He could be based out there.
You know how many camps
the C.I.A. set up
during the cold war?
No.
Hell, the bay of pigs alone
must have had...
What does this look
like to you?
A road.
Yeah. What's the date
on that photo?
It's november 14th.
I just saw a picture
of that same island.
There. Look at that.
This was taken in august-
three months earlier. No road.
So this is new.
This is a new road...
on what used to be
an uninhabited island.
Ready?
Fire away.
What is that?
Why is it doing that?
Is it twins?
Triplets?
What's going on?
It looks like
you're having a litter.
if it can happen to me, it can happen to you.
You and the sheriff hooked up
since the hurricane?
What is it about you
that feels the need
to hurt so many people?
I have to replace
your I.V. Bag.
It's right across the hall.
Keep the door open.
Wait.
Can't you just use this?
Sure.
Doctor?
We need another liter-
standard sux I.V.
Can I see that?
We just need to get
more fluids in you.
So show it to me.
Thanks.
What's up, guys?
Let's get in there.
Guess we can forget about making
the basketball team this year, huh?
Mariel?
Dad?
What are you doing home?
I came to see you.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, I did.
You came home from the middle
of work just to see me?
I came to check in
on you, and-
I'm your dad.
What's so weird about that?
Well, you've just
never done it before.
Oh.
Well, I wanted
your yogurt, too, so...
You feeling okay?
Am I gonna have
these scars forever?
No.
They'll go away.
But you're not gonna
do that again, are you?
No going in the water.
You want to take a swim,
find a pool.
Here, hold this, baby.
yeah?
Whoa. Hey, whoa, whoa.
Are we gonna need that?
Who knows?
I'm sure Szura's got one.
Did you tell Larkin
that we're going to do this?
I told her... that we might
be gone a day or two.
No, but does she know,
Russ?
She knows...
what's at stake.
Come on, let's go.
We didn't see my dad
for, like, three days.
Filled out police reports,
even hung his picture
on the fence
for the missing.
How did you
finally find him?
We didn't.
He just showed up one day.
Acted like
everything was fine,
but I could tell
he wasn't the same.
What about, you know,
your mom?
No, no. No.
In fact, she and my dad-
I mean, she can't stand
the way he is now-
always screaming at him,
crying.
Yeah. I stay out of it.
Rarely get home
except to go to bed.
Good news is,
is that we're not the only guys
that feel this way, you know?
Couple of guys I hang with,
same thing happened to them.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah, you know, they're afraid that
if this keeps happening to people,
we're gonna end up like-
like shut-outs or something.
I mean, I'm already a minority,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
I just think we should
stick together on this,
you know, maybe do something
about it down the road.
You know what I'm saying?
I know what you're saying.
Will you be needing
anything else, doctor?
No.
Thank you.
Hey. What did you do?
Nothing.
Just keeping you hydrated.
I'm getting...
out of here.
You've done something
very stupid.
What's in that?
What is in that?
Christina.
You okay?
Yeah.
I trusted you.
I thought you, of all people,
would understand I'm a pregnant woman.
Oh, shut up.
Hey, how many
islands are out here?
Hundreds.
Well, then how are we supposed
to find this particular one?
Well, I've got
the coordinates.
Should be close,
but I don't see a thing.
We go too far?
No, not according to this.
It's gotta be up ahead.
Speed up a little bit.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
Russ, you hear that?
Hey.
- Russ, what the hell is that?
- I don't know.
How you feeling?
A little better.
So how was it being back?
Weird.
It's a great argument
for homeschooling.
You still mad at me
for not telling you
about Mariel and my dad?
It's not just
our family, Kira.
It's a lot of people.
You know that for sure?
Well, at least we know
we're not crazy now.
And maybe my dad
took your mom to the water
so she wouldn't feel alone.
What do you mean,
"took her to the water"?
The night of the hurricane.
Wait.
He took her?
I mean, he did this
to her on purpose?
No.
No, um, I don't think he knew
it was gonna happen,
I mean, for sure.
But he took her.
He...
my mother didn't
have to be this way.
But he made her this way?
Jesse.
Jesse, wait.
I can't get it from here.
So what-what-
what do we do?
I gotta go in the water.
What?
- What about whatever's in there, man?
- I don't think we have a choice, Dave.
- You want to be stuck out here?
- Well, no.
You'll go in after me
if there's a problem, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah,
of course I would, yeah.
Come on.
Oh! Whoa! Hey!
Can you not point
the shotgun at me?
Oh, yeah. Sorry, man.
- What, did you fix it?
- Uh-huh. Look at this.
Check this out.
That looks
like a channel marker.
What's it doing way out here?
That's a good question.
- Come on, give me a hand.
- Here, take this.
Look at this.
It's brand-new.
So what's it doing out here?
Maybe to help somebody
find a remote island.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
So... plan on having
any more kids?
'Cause if not, if you're
thinking of adopting,
I may have five or six
I could throw your way.
I could just disappear,
you know...
if you'd let me.
Yeah, I've seen
how you disappear.
Christina!
What the hell?
I knew you were close.
I knew it.
See, Derek?
You're like a homing pigeon.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for her.
I was bringing her to you.
I'm sorry, Tom.
Get them both
out of here now.
Hello, Christina.
It's gonna be okay, Chrissie.
It's gonna be okay.
Hey.
You all right?
What'll happen to that girl?
She'll be okay.
Everybody's gonna be okay.
We won't be having
any children, Tom.
I don't know what's growing
inside that girl,
but...
I don't want
to be a part of it.
Whoa. Whoa. There.
- What?
- See that?
Yeah, I do.
What is that?
Pull over there
by those weeds.
Turn the light off.
That's the island.
They got a bonfire goin'.
There's a lot
of people on the beach.
What are they doing?
I don't know.
There's a boat.
Can we get
a hand here, folks?
Ladies and gentlemen,
our missing friends
have returned-
Christina and Derek.
Who's that guy talking?
Szura.
I know this has been
a difficult time
for some of you.
We've all been through
an extraordinary experience.
We're no longer
who we once were.
We've moved on
from the life we had,
left friends
and loved ones behind.
And I know that
many of you
have questions
about your future,
fears... doubts.
You all want to know that your sacrifice
has been worth it.
Let me tell you
what I believe.
I believe that we are
the seeds of the future
that no man could
ever imagine.
But this future
is not guaranteed.
There are those who will
oppose it, oppose us.
To reach this future, we will need the strength that comes from our sticking together.
Our very survival
depends on our unity,
and that's why I've brought
Derek and Christina back...
so that they can be
an example to all of us...
to show us the consequence
of going alone.
You killed her!
You bastard!