Previously on "Invasion"...
Tom is not who you think he is, Mariel.
These creatures take people's D.N.A.
to create a new being, a like hybrid.
I know you know what I am.
There's a guy named Szura.
He's one of you.
If these hybrids become the majority,
this is just the beginning.
- How is it that you weren't taken?
- I got spit out.
- I'm not a well man, Russell.
- They don't take you when you're sick.
You're on the islan of misfit toys, honey.
Once we go through basic training,
we're coming back with a vengeance.
I hate this place.
I'm gettin' out of here.
You wanna know if there's something inside me
that's gonna hurt our kids.
What is this big secret?
You all went into the water and came out different.
You really wanna know what "different" means?
Then stick with us.
We'll give you the whole show.
I think I'm pregnant, you son of a bitch!
Everything in your body is completely different.
It's not cancer.
Those are eggs.
It's like it's some kind of giant ovary.
You can tell your daddy you're just like him now.
Oh, god.
Oh, god, Kira!
Get her keys.
We're just gonna grab some stuff
and then we're gone, all right?
hey, hey, hey.
Come on.
Army food. Yum.
- Which one's the key to the boat?
- The red one.
Let's get out of here
before I start puking again.
Look, look, I won't tell anybody you were here.
Just take the boat and go. Please.
Actually, we don't really need this.
I'm gonna find them.
The people who did this are not gonna get away.
Just tell me she's gonna be all right.
She lost a lot of blood, but her pulse is strong.
We just have to keep watching her.
Bad heart valve.
She's had it since she was born.
That's probably what saved her.
Those things in the water won't take you unless you're...
unless you're perfect?
You have any idea where Derek and Christina are now?
There are roadblocks everywhere.
They won't get far.
I don't understand what you were thinking, Tom.
Sending them to an island?
Christina Conrad's a murderer.
She should be in jail.
If I'd have puher jail,
the whole world would've found out
what she was and what we are.
And I've worked too hard to protect us,
and I'm not gonna let some psycho girl
and her boyfriend just...
they're going back to that island.
This time, they're gonna stay there.
Is is the M.R.I. we took of Mariel yesterday afternoon.
At first, we thought that was a tumor.
But then we discovered it was filled with eggs.
- Like an ovary?
- A third ovary.
With tubes running directly to her uterus.
Is she pregnant?
No, but according to her blood work,
that wasn't in her when she was changed.
It's grown over the last few weeks.
I mean, it just makes me wonder what else is coming.
How many other women are like this now?
I haven't heard of any hybrids giving birth.
What if the hybrids are just a bridge species?
What if it's their offspring
we really have to worry about?
Don't discount the hybrids, Russell.
Szura's as dangerous as any creature
who's ever walked the planet.
And yes, you should be concerned about these things breeding.
But don't think that Szura, Underlay
or even Mariel aren't a threat.
They're wired to survive at any cost,
and that cost will be us
if we don't do something to stop it.
Are you any closer to finding Szura?
No. But if I die before it happens,
you'll kill him for me, won't you?
I'm sorry, Healy.
Alonzo.
Excuse me?
My real name's Alonzo.
I figure if I can trust you with my life,
I can trust you with my real name.
You mind if I still call you Healy?
Yeah, go ahead.
Russ?
Mona?
I don't know how bad she is,
but I'm on my way to see her now
so I'm not gonna be able to make our meeting.
Do you want me to cancel?
No. No, Mariel's already cleared the time,
and I'm sure the kids
are gonna have a thousand questions about Kira,
so I just don't think we can wait.
Just tell Jesse and Rose I'm really sorry
I couldn't be there
and I'll talk to them tonight, okay?
Okay. Russ... be careful.
I will.
Come on, kids.
We can get breakfast at the hospital.
- Hey, Larkin.
- Yeah?
Do they know why Kira's in there?
Larkin?
Yeah?
Why is Kira in the hospital?
Well, you know, that's what your mom wants to talk to you about.
- Did she have an accident?
- You know, I don't have all the details.
Get up there.
Up you go.
Let Jesse buckle you in, okay?
You good?
So they're finally gonna do it, huh?
- Mariel's gonna tell 'em that her and Tom are aliens?
- What?
Dave...
what?
Come on, let's go.
They took the skiff, first aid kit,
flashlights, M.R.E.S...
I don't care about any of that stuff.
Let me see.
You're gonna need stitches.
You sure you're all right?
I'll be fine.
Sorry.
It was definitely that same girl, Russ.
The one who dumped her baby
and killed her mother-in-law.
Underlay was supposed to have had her in custody.
She's certainly not in custody anymore.
And she's pregnant again.
What?
Yeah, she had to be at least five months.
That's not possible.
She wasn't even showing a few weeks ago.
Why don't you stop talking about what you don't understand?
You were supposed to have sent Christina Conrad to the F.B.I. In miami.
What happened?
Yeah, well, I guess she got away, huh?
- Oh, no kidding.
- Yeah, no kidding.
- I'll find her.
- Not in the park, you won't.
Dispatch, this is Varon.
- I need two law enforcements rangers to ranger station--
- I wouldn't do that, Russell.
- She almost killed my friend.
- She almost killed my daughter.
But if you call in the calvary,
Derek and Christina are gonna be exposed
to a whole bunch of people that will not understand what they are...
let alone what that girl is carrying inside of her.
Varon, you still there?
Standby.
Well, what is she carrying?
Look, I know the park is your jurisdiction.
If you wanna take the lead on this, fine.
But why don't we keep this between us and you work with me?
I don't need your help.
No, but your kids need their mother.
You blow the whistle on this, you know what you're gonna get?
Guys in white lab coats that are gonna take Mariel away.
Try having your kids forgive you for that.
This boat's gonna make me throw up.
We should've taken her truck.
I told you, Chris, the roads are all blocked off.
We wouldn't have gotten anywhere.
I hate you for doing this to me.
I didn't need to be pregnant again.
Hey, I didn't do it on purpose.
I don't even know how it happened. Okay?
I mean, we've only been together for a couple weeks,
and I mean, you're already so big.
Where are we going?
Camp my grandpa used to take me to.
We're gonna hang out there for a while,
let things kinda cool down.
Camp?
Like, what, archery?
No, like an old hunting camp.
Give you...
give you a chance to relax.
You've been acting...
kind of crazy, chris.
What's wrong?
I think we might be out of gas.
Oh, great.
Next time when I say, "let's take the truck,"
let's take the truck.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Chris?
Whoa, whoa! Okay, okay.
Okay, sit back. Sit back,
sit back, sit back.
Is it happening again?
What?
Well, your dad wanted to be here,
but he got called away on an emergency,
and Tom...
is working as well.
Why does everyone have to be here?
Because we have something very important
we wanna discuss with you.
Someone getting divorced again?
No.
If that's what it is,
I'd really wish that you would just tell me.
No, Jess.
Nobody's getting a divorce.
This is about Kira...
and... me and Tom.
And the whole town, really.
R ight.
What's wrong with the town?
Well...
um... you know about the lights in the water, right?
a lot of the people in the town have come in contact with them,
and it's made some of them...
different.
Different how?
Well, we're just beginning to figure that out.
I want you to remember in everything you're about to hear, that...
I am still your mom, and Tom is still your stepdad.
Do you remember the night of the hurricane
when I didn't come home?
Well, something happened that night,
- and the next morning when you found me--
- Hold on.
Are you aliens?
What?
They said at the house that you were aliens.
Mariel, we never said that.
I mean, the word may have been come out,
but it wasn't used in that--
I just--I just meant that...
that you guys had changed, that's all. Like, uh...
if they'd gone from being a caterpillar to a butterfly.
Do you understand?
Is this why Kira's here, 'cause she got abducted?
No! Kira was attacked in the water.
But she's fine, because...
Kira's not...
like...
- What, she's not an alien?
- Oh, my god.
- Well, don't leave.
- Well, I am not an alien!
Then what are you?
Because we've known you've been different for a long time.
We just wanna know what you are.
Not a butterfly.
It's out of gas.
We should be able to catch up to 'em.
Hey, Russ. Um...
you relying on some old indian
tracker broken twig thing here,
or do you actually know where you're going?
To avoid your roadblocks.
We should stay near the shore.
All right.
They could also be heading up north to big cypress trail,
but without backup, we'll never know.
Ah, we don't need backup.
Yeah. You got everything under control.
How far is this place?
Um, I don't know.
Maybe like 4 or 5 miles.
- Do you still feeling bad ?
- I don't want to talk about it.
All right.
I've never seen a baby move like that.
He's okay, right?
- He?
- Or she.
I mean, it's obviously going pretty fast.
So it's all right, right?
I have no idea.
What do you want to call it?
- What?
The baby. Have you thought about a name for it yet?
Are you insane?
Have you not heard a word I have said to you
since the day that we met?
Yeah--
I got married when I was 16 because I was pregnant.
The kid's now living with my grandparents.
The next kid--
you gave away because you lost your husband in the hurricane.
That's okay, I under--
because I felt like a prisoner.
Because I felt like a prisoner my entire life.
I don't wanna be a prisoner anymore, Derek.
Do you understand that?
That's why we got off the island.
That's why we got away from Szura, okay?
I'm not going back.
Okay.
What was that?
Derek?
Want a little decaf?
Come on,
I said I was sorry.
I'll be lucky if Mariel ever talks to me again.
Oh, give me a break.
She'll talk to you again.
Listen, the kids are just--
they're still scared because there's no logical explanation
for what happened here.
Aliens or not, there's just too many holes, all right?
Well, I'd love to fill them, but Russell made me promise
to stay away from the story.
Larkin, the hell with the story.
Why can't you and I both go out like a couple of concerned citizens
and find out the truth?
Give Mariel some real answers.
She'll forgive us both in a heartbeat.
Because the only people with real answers are the military.
And according to your friend mr. Healy,
they're just sitting back and watching it happen.
But why?
Why? Why are they just sitting back and letting it happen?
What's in it for them?
How high does this thing go?
Who's involved? Don't these questions drive you insane?
Of course, but...
what you're talking about is a conspiracy story.
No!
When was the last time you talked to your buddy at the air base?
- Vince?
- Yeah.
I don't know.
Oh, come on.
He's gotta know something.
I doubt it.
He's the facilities manager.
Oh, so he's just in charge of the buildings?
He's just in charge of the buildings
Where all the top secret junk goes on. Shoot.
It's a food packet--M.R.E.
That come from your place?
I think so.
What?
esta bien. Okay?
Esta bien.
Easy.
No somos la migra.
Okay?
¿De donde eres?
Honduras.
Somos trabajadores en las granjas del sur.
They're migrant workers.
Whs "they"?
esta bien.
he said the hurricane destroyed their housing,
and the other workers won't let them live in their new camp.
What other workers?
¿Donde esta el campamento?
- hey.
- Hey.
- How you feeling?
- Okay.
- Am I changed?
- No, sweetie.
But that's a good thing.
Hey, guys.
He's mad at you for not telling us about mommy.
They know about you?
Did you tell them because of me?
No.
I told them because of me, but...
it came out the wrong way.
Why wasn't I changed, Mariel?
Your father's gonna talk to you about that
when he gets back.
- You want some water?
- Okay.
Our family is never going to be the same again, is it?
Larkin?
Vince. I really appreciate you seeing me on such short notice.
Who are you ?
what--I'm, uh, I'm her brother.
I'm Dave. Dave groves.
I was hoping we'd be alone.
It's okay. He's here to help with--
No, it's not.
Vince, wait. What's wrong?
Right after you called me,
I got dragged into the wing commander's office.
Did something happen last time you were on the base?
Look, Vince, I'm a reporter, and sometimes...
No, no, no.
No, that does not give you the right
to take advantage of a friend.
You used me.
You used me to get on the base.
What were you hoping to find?
Hey, hey, man.
Why don't we all sit down?
I put a high premium on character,
and if you had just come out
and said you were doing a story
about corruption in the military--
corruption?
They said that you were trying to prove that
we're overcharging washington
for paper clips and pencils and whatever--
that we're crooks.
That's insane.
That's more than insane.
They lied to him.
They lied to you.
Lo--
Will you please come sit with us?
I have to go.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Can I ask you one question?
If we can prove to you that your bosses lied,
will you stay and help us out?
Why would they lie?
I did go somewhere I shouldn't have.
That hangar that you told me was run by special ops?
I peeked in there, and I saw about a hundred titanium boxes--
boxes that I'd seen earlier at a crash site
for a downed helicopter in the glades.
Yeah, a member of that crew,
lieutenant Paxton, ended up in this hospital,
but before anybody could actually talk to the guy,
the air force just swept in and took his body away.
Was he dead?
We're not sure, but he may have been taken to your base.
We think that the crew of that helicopter
may have actually encountered something in the water--
something that...
may be...
extraterrestrial.
mi familia...
estan en nueva york.
Tom.
What did they say about Derek and Christina?
He claims that they haven't seen them.
What about these guys?
I don't speak spanish well enough to understand
what they were sayin.
They're hybrids, aren't they?
Where did you get these?
¿La comida--de donde salio?
Fue un regalo.
He said it was a gift.
A gift from who?
¿Un regalo de quien?
Where did the food come from ?
We didn't give it to them.
They took it !
But where did you get it ?
From the man.
What man... the young man with the girl I asked about ?
Why didn't you tell me this before ?
Because I was afraid, you...
were like them.
What do you mean ?
Who is he ?
He's my brother.
He was starving. He asked them for a piece of fish.
But they wouldn't give it to him.
So he took it.
He only took a little bit.
And they killed him.
The all killed him !
They got them to give us some food.
where's the coroner?
We're still waiting on social services out here, deputy.
Do you have an E.T.A.?
he left over an hour ago.
He should be there any minute.
Thank you.
This is bigger than an immigration problem.
Why didn't you call the coroner?
Social services can handle it.
Did you ask them which direction
Derek and Christina were heading?
- South, along the water.
- All right, good.
This detour hasn't been a total waste.
No, actually,
it's been very educational.
This isn't my vision of the future.
Then what are you doing to stop it?
Sheriff?
Andy Dennison, social services.
Sorry I'm late.
These guys need help right here.
I've got a transpo on the way out here now.
How many are there?
Eight.
There were nine.
Oh, god.
That was his brother.
He's got family in new york.
He was hoping you could get a message to them.
Of course.
As soon as we reach town.
Cuando lleguemos a miami, puedo llamar a su familia, bueno?
Gracias, seÑor.
Si. Thank you.
What happened to them?
Ask them.
I'm sorry this place is such a mess.
It's all right.
Do you want a beer?
Actually, I would.
Okay.
There you go.
Might wanna go easy on that.
Pregnant women aren't supposed to drink, are they?
Wouldn't want little Derek getting toasty.
What's in the first aid kit?
Ah, just some tape, bandages, aspirin, stuff like that.
Take it all.
Is there a closet in here?
No.
There's a gun closet.
Open it.
Uh, I don't think there's any guns in there.
Sorry, honey, the cupboard is bare.
What are those sticks?
These? These are cleaning rods for the rifles.
Let me see one.
It's not very sharp.
A hanger would be better.
You got one?
No. For what?
Christina, what--
what are you thinking?
I'm not having this baby, Derek.
Well...
don't I have some sort of say about all this?
No.
I'm not gonna let you do this.
You don't have a choice.
Is there alcohol in here?
No.
Oh, well.
Chris, don't do this.
Christina, don't.
Don't do this.
Chris, don't do this.
- God! Ow! God!
- What's wrong?
What's happening?
My insides feel like they're being torn apart.
- Did you--did you hurt it?
- No! I didn't touch it!
Ow, god! Ow!
We may have to call this off until tomorrow.
I don't have any place to go.
Well, I have two kids who I haven't seen since this morning,
and I'm sure after talking to Mariel,
they're gonna need some support.
Boy, that must be tough on the back,
carrying all that selflessness around.
Wh, do you think you're so different than me
or those guys back there?
You're not.
That's the thing I never understand about people.
They're always so astonished when one person kills another,
but it's in our nature.
You think we're descended from the three guys sitting in the cave,
sharing their buffalo?
No. We're descended from the fourth guy that says,
"hey, why don't I pick up this club
and smack these other three losers,
and then there'll be more meat from me?"
That's our ancestor.
That's survival.
Survival's
what it's all about.
Hey.
Okay.
All right.
Who's hungry?
Oh, come on.
They're supposed to start school again tomorrow.
I wonder how that's gonna go.
I'm sorry if I scared you.
You could've... called or--
I wasn't sure that was a good idea.
Do you have something for me?
Vince, it's okay.
I love my country,
Sure Larkin, and when I think there may be people--
people that I work with, that I can't trust anymore...
What have you found out?
When I went back to the base,
I talked to the wing commander again.
I told him that I'd seen you
and that I confronted you about the corruption story.
And then I told him that you agreed to kill it.
But I was never working on a corruption story.
I know.
And I could tell by his reaction, he knew it, too.
You were right about Paxton.
He was processed onto our base
the same night they took him from the hospital.
- Was he alive?
- I-I don't know.
But they took him to hangar 42.
That's the same one that you looked in.
I don't know what they're doing in there,
but you might be able to find out with this.
That is an access code for the base's backup computer servers.
All of our operations keep copies of their files on it.
You didn't get it from me.
I can go in by myself.
That's okay.
Christina?
Christina.
You got an E.T.A. On the ranger?
He's en route.
He should be there by now.
You know, she may need an ambulance.
No, no. She won't need an ambulance. She's fine.
You're fine, right?
Are you gonna tell us where your buddy is?
I have no idea.
When was the last time you saw him?
You have not been a very good girl.
What did you do with Derek, Christina?
Christina?
Jesus!
Get up.
No, no. Get up.
No. Let her go.
Let her go, or I will kill him!
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
You see, honey?
I'm a good provider.
Well, fellas, I-I'd love to stay and hang out, have a couple beers,
but, uh, I got a family to think about now.
Right, mama?
Everything always leads back to Underlay.
Like, that's the wreckage from his plane righthere.
These pictures are from that hangar in 1996.
All types of top military brass
were investigating this plane crash,
including a certain former intelligence officer.
I'll give you 10 bucks if you can guess his name.
Szura.
Eli Szura. The guy was all over this thing. Look.
He's in a lot of other pictus, too.
His name's everywhere.
Wait a minute.
That's Szura?
Yeah.
What is it, Russ?
That son of a bitch.
Mr. Szura?
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean for anything like this to happen.
He killed someone.
Someone? A park ranger, and that's a real problem.
What about Christina?
We'll find her.
Derek will help us.
Szura?
Don't lose anymore.
Healy!
Healy, we found him!
We found Szura.
Healy?