There's a huge storm coming, and he's still not home.
How was I ever married to this person ?
As a storm gathers...
My pregnant wife shouldn't be covering hurricanes.
- Talk to your brother ?
- Yeah. He's with your kids at the house.
- I've been through hurricanes before.
- Not like this one, you haven't.
These families prepare...
- I have a right to know my children are safe.
- They're our children !
- Rose isn't here.
- Rose !
Why don't you go home and worry about your new husband
and leave us alone ?
Can they survive...
Rose !
What lies ahead ?
What's happening to me ?
- Did you see the lights ?
- Where'd you see them ?
- There are no aliens.
- Then will you tell me what's going on here ?
Mommy ?
You smell different.
First days are the toughest.
Testing, testing,
One, two, three.
Since I've been temporarily cut off from the outside world,
if friends and blog readers can get this message
out there for me.
As you all know, I believe that hurricane eve
was just a smokescreen to distract us from a larger,
far more ominous threat.
A larger, far more deadly threat.
But four days ago--
I found what I believed to be
the first alien-human remains combo.
A full skeleton penetrated by 12 prods.
24 hours later, an air force lieutenant
washed up on shore with 12 matching holes
in his body.
The holes looked eerily similar to the same ones I had
on my very legs.
Yes, that's right, folks, yours truly
had a close encounter of the painful kind.
Somebody--
most likely the military--
does not want a word of this to get out.
The skeleton has been stolen.
The lieutenant has gone missing.
And they're saying he's dead.
And the only evidence remaining
is a ring that I found in the trunk of my car.
A ring which I believe came from the skeleton.
If I can prove that, I can establish
the ongoing presence of extraterrestrials in our waters.
- Dave!
- Yeah?
- Coming in for breakfast?
Yeah, I'm on my way.
All right.
One last note--
the only other person who knows about all this stuff
is my brother-in-law russell.
And he thinks I'm nuts.
I don't understand.
Wilmore and casey can't clear the roads
because the equipment's broken?
because we don't have it.
The city's using it all.
- All right, I'm on my way.
- The air force came and took his body away.
They say he's dead, but who knows?
They told his wife he was overseas.
you're not hearing me, larkin.
Val, every reporter in town
is covering the relief center, okay?
This is a real story.
I need you in the shelter by 8:30. Good-bye.
What is wrong with her?
Mmm. You know what?
She just doesn't love you like I do.
Okay, newlyweds, simmer down.
This for me?
Just share them, I'm grumpy and pregnant
and I have to go to the relief center.
we need to talk.
russell, the roof just collapsed at lone pine.
Nobody's hurt, but they need some help.
All right, let 'em know I'm on my way.
Hey, honey, I gotta go.
You seen jesse's headphones?
He wanted me to drop him off at his mom'S.
Yeah, they're on the counter by the breadbox.
Russ, will you meet me at the jewelers later?
What's at the jewelers?
Uh, I wanna see if I can find anything out about the ring.
- It's a wedding ring, dave.
- Yeah, I know it's a wedding ring,
but maybe the inscription can tell us something.
"Two become one."
Maybe the jeweler will recognize it.
Well, how do you know he made it?
I don'T. It's just it's all we have left.
No, it's not.
I'm having tests run on that tissue fragment
mariel gave me.
If this thing is alien, we'll know by this afternoon.
Russell, your own daughter said she saw millions of lights
landing in the water during the hurricane.
So?
So what else could it be?
hey, the water's back on.
What a nice surprise.
Mommy, look at this.
Look at my shoes.
Mommy?
Mommy, you're not listening.
Daddy tom taught me how to tie my shoes.
Mommy!
That's very good, honey.
That's very good.
You probably shouldn't waste all that water, mare.
And you definitely don't want to lose another one of these.
Kira and jesse--
they still need a ride to town?
No, they decided to walk.
I'll get it.
- Daddy!
- Hey, how you doing, kiddo?
You wanna come in and have breakfast?
Morning, russ.
Hey, tom, these are jesse's headphones. He asked for them.
Oh.
Look, dad. Daddy tom taught me how to tie my shoes.
Wow, look at that.
She's a natural.
Well, that's great, sweetheart.
Hey, russell,
is everything all right?
Just dropping jesse's headphones off, that's all.
He's not here.
You can wait for him.
Oh, sweetie, I really gotta get back to work.
You know, actually, if you could stay,
that would really help us out.
Jesse should be back any minute. I'm late for work.
And I know tom would love to get in.
Yeah, daddy, please?
Uh, yeah, if you could hang around, that'd be really great.
Great, okay,
I gotta go.
- Bye, honey.
- Bye, I'll call you.
Bye, rosie,
I'll call you at lunch, okay?
Thanks.
uh, thank you.
I'll see ya.
So, daddy, wanna play in my room?
Your dad's a sheriff.
Doesn't he get free gas?
Not for your mom's car.
Boy, look at all these people who are still lost.
Yeah.
Luke hampton's missing.
He was in my gym class.
He was terrible at volleyball.
Well, they found my mom.
Maybe they can find him.
hello?
Hello, anybody here?
Hello?
Anybody in the back there?
- What do you want?
- What? Oh?
Oh, uh...
- you a looter?
- No. No.
- I'll shoot you if you are.
- No, I'm not a looter.
- I'm a customer.
- I'm not open.
well, I was just  wondering if maybe you could take a look
at something for me.
you know, uh,
you might wanna put that generator out on the street.
Why?
Oh, because, um, you know, if you leave it in here,
the carbon monoxide will kill you.
Just a tip.
How'd you know about this shortcut?
Derek culie showed me.
Oh, him.
Yeah, I know he's kind of a jerk.
But he has an awesome car.
That's always been my barometer for a friendship.
Whoa.
Look at that.
Man, that got tossed.
- Do you think anyone's inside?
- If they are, it's not looking good.
What are you doing?
I'm going in the water.
- Naked?
- I'm not naked.
Kira.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Looks like ***** okay.
Cool, everything looks like down.
What do you think their deal is?
Hey, do you wanna see what's in the refrigerator?
You can tell everything about somebody
by what's in their fridge.
These people are condiment fiends.
Kira,
you gotta see this.
kira.
Jesse!
Invasion
1x03 - Watershed
Transcript RaceMan
Adaptation Ez, Keno83, RonanaSplit & Lucile76
www.forom.com
wow, this is a, uh, very nice room, rose.
Yeah.
At your house the hurricane got everything wet.
But here, nothing happened at all.
Daddy!
Dad! Daddy!
Kira?
Your dad's not here.
What is it?
Kira?
What's wrong?
Stay in the car.
I wanna help jesse.
No, stay in the car, Rose.
Jesse!
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
Jesse!
- I wanna go see.
- Rose, wait! Rose!
- Wait, rose, come back!
- Daddy!
- Rose, wait, no!
- Let me go!
Come on!
Jesse!
Dr. Underlay? I'm looking for dr. Underlay!
This is her son.
Mariel?
- He's dr. Underlay's son.
- Multiple lacs--scalp, legs.
He's bleeding heavily.
you need to find his mother. Where is his mother?
Jesse?
Oh, my god.
Ugh. I really appreciate you taking the time to do this.
- I've had a lot of looters in here.
- I know.
- Have to be careful, you know?
- Sure, yeah.
After andrew, they tied up my wife,
emptied the vaults, left her for 18 hours.
Oh, my god, that's awful
I didn't do this engraving.
It's amateur work.
But whoever owned the ring had it fitted.
There's a metal insert in here.
Not the finest, either.
And there's a date underneath.
There is?
"2...
"14...
"86."
Valentine's day.
Not very original.
So you think that was their wedding date?
Well, it is a wedding ring.
What about this other inscription here--
the "two become one"?
You think that has any special significance?
No, we see that a lot.
Start him on crystalloid and a unit of packed cells.
Then 4 units of a/b negative blood
and a dose of unasyn.
I'm nonot sure we've got that much a/b neg left.
The hurricane's left the bank pretty dry.
- Well, get me what you can.
- Okay.
Is he going to beall right?
He's lost a lot of blood. What happened?
He and kira found a mobile home
in the water near your house.
- In the water?
- Yeah.
Are any of his wounds like the lieutenant's I brought in--
that air force guy?
Paxton?
No, why?
They're glass cuts, russell, over his back and legs.
What happened?
I mean, is this story really necessary?
Do the people of south florida really need to know
that 20,000 new diapers just rolled into town?
I guess the incontinent ones do, yeah.
Mrs. Hernandez, are you ready?
Angel, I need you to stay close to me, okay?
- Who are they?
- Military?
Why no markings?
And what's with the helicopter escort?
Hey, scott, get a shot of them.
Mommy.
Hey, sweetie.
Is jesse going to be okay?
I hope so.
I'm so sorry.
What happened?
We just--we thought it would be cool to explore
- and then jesse saw something and-
- saw what?
I told you, I don't know.
- Look, I said I was sorry.
- Kira.
How about I set you up in my office with some crayons?
Would you like that?
What do you think he saw, mom?
- Mona, you there?
- Go ahead.
I'm not gonna be able to make it down to lone pine,
but I need you to bring me something.
Well, I just want to go back to the house
to get some clothes and my grandson's photo album.
It's not safe, mrs. Lowell, but I'll tell you what,
I'm gonna send somebody out there and get it for you, okay?
Oh, my grandson's 4 months old.
But he's very big for his age--
in the 98th percentile.
Well, that's--
that's really big.
Um, would you excuse me?
All right, honey.
You still running your safety circle?
Nobody in or out of town without your clearance?
5-mile radius.
Recognize these guys?
No.
How's that possible?
Well, as powerful as I am, I'm not actually present
at every checkpoint at every second.
But they look like the military to me.
Military what?
They weren't headed towards town.
They were moving away from it towards the keys.
So?
So if you didn't give them clearance--
then I didn't give them clearance.
Look, tom, the man russell found
half dead in his ranger station--paxton--was air force.
He was down there on some kind of classified mission.
Now I'd like to know what he was up to. Wouldn't you?
Oh, and you think there's a connection with these trucks.
Yeah.
I don't think you want to go after this one.
The air force is more than capable
of taking care of their own.
Then why is paxton dead?
And why did they tell his wife he was overseas?
You spoke to his wife?
I'm gonna find out what happened to this guy.
And why the air force is down here.
And if there's a cover-up, who's involved.
Now you can help me get the story
or you can be the story. It's your choice.
- When will he wake up?
- Probably in a few hours.
I don't know how long he was unconscious.
Why did kira leave him?
She said the trailer flooded.
She tried to get to him, but he was thrown to the back.
And I guess water was pouring in.
They shouldn't have been out there in the first place.
- Are you blaming me?
- No.
Because it could've happened
while they were at your house, russell.
Why were they out there at all?
They were getting gas.
Couldn't tom have done that?
Russell, when jesse's with you,
you've got him running all over the glades.
Yeah, when he's with me, not alone.
Not five days after a hurricane.
You want to make it my fault? Fine.
I'm not making it your fault.
You going to blame kira, too?
I'm not blaming anyone. I just want to know why it happened.
It happened because they're kids.
It happened because we can't be with them every second.
It's not because of me. It's not because of you.
It's not because we're divorced.
Well, I just want him to be okay. That's all.
Mariel?
I'm gonna go check on rose.
Here, prep this.
hey! Thought that was you.
Hi.
what's the matter?
Jesse's in the hospital.
Hospital? What?
Kira, what? What happened?
- Could you just take me home, please? It's not far.
- Yeah. Uh, sure, yeah.
Uh, do you have a phone that works in your house
so I can call the hospital and make sure he's okay?
Um, we have a radio.
Right.
- hey, how's your boy?
- I don't know yet.
- I'm sorry, russ.
- Thanks.
- You get what I need?
- Yeah.
What is that thing?
It's a piece of tissue mariel pulled out
of that air force guy.
- What kind of tissue?
- It was stick inside one of his wounds.
I think it may be part of whatever attacked him.
I had the lab run some tests.
Was it a fish?
Hurricanes can sometimes throw up some bad fish.
- So who am I talking to?
-General turner with the 10th mountain.
That's army.
Yes, but he's the highest ranking
military officer in the area,
and he may know something.
After you.
- General.
- Tom.
This is larkin groves with wnkw-tv.
- Nice to meet you, ma'am.
- How do you do?
Please, show him the picture.
I saw these trucks headed south towards the keys this morning,
and I was hoping that maybe you could tell me who or what--
they're air force.
Air force?
Yes, ma'am.
Looks like a cleanup crew.
Cleanup crew? For what?
Are we on the record here?
Up to you, sir.
There was a sewage plant that got busted open down in key largo.
Nothing really serious, but there was some chemical leakage.
Air force offered to go down there and clean it up for us.
A sewage plant?
Yes, ma'am.
Well... that explains a lot.
Thank you, general.
Maybe next time you can introduce me
to someone more knowledgeable.
Excuse me?
The sewage plant in key largo closed a month ago.
I covered the story.
I must have missed that one.
yeah.
Guess the general did, too.
Look, larkin, I told you,
you don't want to mess with this, really.
Too late for that.
The operation is highly classified.
I'm only in the loop because they couldn't operate
down here without me.
I understand.
You're very important...
- no, I'm not.
- And about to be exposed as a liar.
Let go of my door.
If I tell you what's really going on,
I'm gonna put you right in the crosshairs.
These guys, they don't screw around.
They'll have you fired, blackballed... worse.
I'm a big girl.
And I'll probably be fired anyway.
They are operating out of key largo.
Prove it.
Mr. Varon, the nurse was looking for you.
What's going on?
He's running a high fever, and his breathing's labored.
- Where's mariel?
- Haven't seen her.
What do you mean, you haven't seen her?
- what's happening?
- His B.P.'S dropping.
Heart rate's rising.
Where the hell's mariel?
Mariel!
mariel!
We need more L.R.S now.
Push a bolus as fast as you can.
Pressure's still dropping.
- What's the acuity?
- B.P.'S low.
His vitals are unstable.
Give him 50 milligrams of diphenhydramine
and 125 of solumederol.
- What's wrong with him?
- I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know? You have to know.
He's having a hemolytic reaction.
Are you sure your son's a/b negative?
Mariel?
Stop the blood. Stop it.
Call the red cross.
See if they have any blood substitute
and get them to send it up here now.
- Was he given the wrong type?
- No.
- How do you know? Are you sure?
- It was mine.
- Thanks for the lift.
- Yeah, no problem.
Boy, nice digs.
Yeah. Everyone thinks my dad's on the take,
but he just got a lot of insurance money after my mom died.
The radio's upstairs.
My dad keeps it on a police frequency.
But number one's a direct line to the hospital,
so if you hit that button, it'll call mariel's office.
Okay, thanks.
hello?
Hello?
- is that your mom?
- Yeah.
she was hot.
Yeah.
She, uh, she kind of looked like an old movie star.
She had a lot of style.
Even her name grace had style.
- These are from her?
- Yeah.
They're letters she wrote to my dad
when he was in the first gulf war.
Nobody's picking up on this.
Yeah, it's pretty crazy at the hospital.
Okay.
so, uh, why did you feel like it was your fault,
what happened with jesse?
I don't know.
I guess I feel like a lot of things are my fault.
Oh, c--oh, come on.
I'm sure that's not true.
I thought it was my fault when my mom died.
How did your mom die?
In a plane crash.
That's no good.
No.
You know there's nothing you could have done, right?
Yeah, I know. I know.
But you always wonder if, you know,
maybe you'd been there, something would be different.
yeah, but you were with jesse.
yeah.
- So, uh, guess it's my fault either way, huh?
- There you go.
That's the spirit, kid.
Mariel.
- Mariel, hold on.
- He's stable now, russell.
He's gonna be fine.
No, I'm not worried about jesse.
I'm worried about you.
Why?
Mariel, what is going on with you?
I'm just overwhelmed...
and exhausted.
And...
I don't know what's going on with me.
my blood almost killed jesse, russell.
But it didn'T.
He's stable now. You said so yourself.
He's gonna be fine.
Mariel, why don't you go be with him?
Just take a break and be with your son.
Yeah, I have the results here somewhere.
It's dr. Underlay's blood, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. Hurricane kind of messed everything up.
We lost our file cabinets.
I--oh, was it your son who had a problem?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, um, yeah...
I'm really sorry.
I'm not sure that he got the right blood.
You're not sure?
Well, I'm not sure he got his mother'S.
We've had lots of donors, and her results--
they were right here.
Uh... the hurricane kind of messed us up.
Uh...
uh... yeah. Here.
Here they are.
Yeah, we're running these tests again.
Why?
The equipment must have been contaminated.
Can I see that?
We had a couple different readings like this.
I--somebody must have forgotten to clean the centrifuge,
'cause there were enormous amounts of hemoglobin.
I mean, unless the donor was a dolphin or a whale or something.
where exactly are we going?
You sound like rose.
"Are we there yet?"
Yeah, but I didn't ask when.
I asked where.
You know where.
Key largo.
This isn't the way.
It's another way.
how's your husband?
I haven't talked to him today.
How's your wife?
hey.
Hey.
He's stable now.
I'm gonna go see about moving him to recovery.
hey, bud.
Man, what were you doing in that water?
I don't want you near that water.
I just want you with me.
are you worried?
About what?
That things are gonna change when the baby comes.
Between you and Russel.
Russell and I would never let that happen.
How are you planning to do that?
I mean, change is inevitable.
Things are always evolving.
It's just a matter of how we choose to respond to it.
hey.
I'm sorry.
For what?
If it sounded like I was blaming you earlier about jesse.
I didn't mean to.
Well, I accept your apology--
if you were blaming me, which I'm not sure you were.
- How long has she been asleep?
- Half an hour.
She didn't get her afternoon nap today.
- She still takes naps?
- She doesn't when she's at your house?
Well, different homes, different rules.
- Different parents.
- Same parents.
Mariel, I spoke to the guy in your blood lab about jesse.
He said there may have been a mistake.
It may not have been your blood.
There's some problem with the equipment--
too much hemoglobin.
What?
The blood work contained massive amounts of hemoglobin.
He said it was like you'd find in a dolphin or a whale.
Of course, he thought that was a mistake.
Again, he didn't even know that it was your blood.
It's kind of a mess in there.
I'd better go find out what happened.
Hopefully this next round of tests
will clear everything up.
- Listen, I am jesse varon's stepbrother-in-law.
- I'm sorry.
I'm only authorized to give out information
to his immediate family.
Oh, how do I not qualify as immediate family?
Excuse me.
- Who am I speaking to?
- Joyce scovell.
Hi, joyce, this is kira underlay, jesse's stepsister.
I believe I qualify as family.
And if I don't, I'll make sure my father
and his wife dr. Mariel underlay,
the chief of staff at your hospital, hear about it.
Let me check with my supervisor.
Nice.
Yeah, I picked up a few things from my dad.
Yeah, don't pick up too much.
I've been to key largo a thousand times.
I've never seen this.
Yeah, well, I didn't blindfold you.
Yeah, but I stopped knowing where we were going
about 45 minutes ago.
Maybe that's a good thing.
Okay? There's your story.
- You just can't tell anybody.
- Why?
You wanted the truth?
Here it is.
But if you tell anybody what you've seen,
you burn me as a source forever,
not to mention as a friend.
So what am I looking at?
What's left of an hh-60g pave hawk.
Air force search and rescue.
Paxton's?
Took off with a 4-man crew.
Why did it crash?
I'm assuming the hurricane.
Yeah, but why were they flying in a hurricane?
Why was paxton in a wet suit in the water?
What was he looking for?
According to my contact,
they were after a missing weather plane.
A weather plane?
Then what's going on over there?
what's in the box, tom?
How long was your dad in the air force?
12 years.
Handsome couple.
kira, I have good news.
Jesse varon's condition has been upgraded to good.
Thank you, joyce.
That's great news.
do you want to go see him?
- Yeah. You sure you're up for it?
- Yeah, absolutely.
Okay, let's go.
you guys look funny.
Hey! Why's that?
You're all out of focus.
Yeah, just go with that.
It's been working for me for years.
Hey.
I'm sorry you got hurt.
You know, kira--
she saved your butt, man.
Wasn't for her, you wouldn't be here right now.
Thanks.
I saw something in the water, dad.
I know.
jesse!
Hey, baby!
- How are you?
- I'm doing.
I drew this for you.
- Mariel.
- Thanks, rose.
did you get a chance to talk to the lab?
It was a mix-up.
The tech told me he ran complete panels
and C.B.C. Makeups on my blood,
and everything's fine.
Jesse got somebody else'S.
It's not gonna happen again.
So you think he can come home tomorrow?
Which home?
My home.
I'll make sure he gets his naps.
Sure.
Thank you for being here for him, russell--
for both of them.
Thank you.
- Hey, you make sure you get some rest, okay?
- Okay
russell? Honey?
Are you there?
Hey, baby.
Hey, blog readers.
It's me again--dave.
Unfortunately, my search for the owner of the ring
has not yielded anything yet.
But I haven't given up.
Something is out there.
Whatever it is, wherever it is,
I'm going to find it.
But until I do--
until we do--
russell and me--
just a tip--
stay out of the water.