Previously on "Invasion"...
Do you think anyone's inside ?
Kira, you gotta see this.
Dr. Underlay ?
I'm looking for Dr. Underlay !
I saw something in the water, dad.
Who are they ?
Military ?
Why no markings ?
I'm gonna find out why
the Air Force is down here
and if there's a cover-up,
who's involved.
If I tell you what's really goin'on,
I'm gonna put you right in the crosshairs.
Mariel...
what is going on with you ?
Invasion
1x04 - Alpha male
Transcript Raceman
Adaptation -Ez-, Keno83, Ronanasplit & Lucile76
www.forom.com
There are no accidents, Lewis.
Everything happens for a reason.
Look at our town.
Yeah, it's a shame.
On one level, maybe.
But I think it's an opportunity, too.
It's an opportunity to grow.
What doesn't kill us
makes us stronger, right ?
Hey, sheriff.
You're doing a terrific job.
Thank you, Roger.
How's the shop ?
Took a few lumps,
but we'll be back.
I know you will.
You see ?
He's a survivor
like all the folks that are gonna take us
to the next level.
In the aftermath of hurricane Eve, it seems
as if all of South Floridais taking stock.
But here in homestead,
taking stock means waiting...
waiting for loved ones
who are still missing.
And for many people, waiting in line
for the most basic necessities...
Ice, food, gas, water...
medicine.
All are in very short supply.
I'm here with Terrence Gale from
the Florida Department of Health.
Can you tell me, in situations like this,
should we expect things to get
worse before they get better ?
Well, with so much displacement,
we're always concerned about disease.
But that's why these relief
centers are so important.
Because they can
provide a ration of hope
for families who have been
forced out of their homes
and allow them to get food or medicine
or whatever they would require.
How do you keep up with demand ?
Access is the greatest challenge.
- I've visited most of these places...
- You're one of them.
You're one of them !
Help ! Help !
I'm pregnant. Stop ! I'm pregnant.
She's one of them !
Mona, I'm coming in with another load.
I have no idea where
we're gonna put'em all.
Here, take this little guy.
Be careful. He's a little scrappy.
Come on.
It's okay. It's okay.
How come you're playing Noah's ark ?
'Cause I can't use my truck. The
sheriff's got all the roads closed
Weren't closed for him.
He had no problem getting
Larkin to Key Largo.
What are they doing down there ?
She was following upon a story.
We have an E.T.A. On
when we're getting water ?
I've heard six weeks.
Six weeks ?
That's what they tell me.
The sheriff has water now.
How do you know ?
Because when I dropped the kids off at
his house, your ex was taking a bath.
That's how I know.
That son of a bitch !
No one has water.
Well, I guess it pays
to be the man, huh ?
Hey, Russ !
Where earlier today, Wnkw's Larkin
Groves was attacked on camera
by a deranged woman at the E.O.C.
But now the question remains...
Why did this woman attack her ?
Oh, no.
Do you know how they get in ?
They're in.
I saw her. I saw her
She was there.
I'm not crazy.
They get in. That's all
That's what they do. They're in
She was one of them.
She was.
She was one of what ?
One of them.
One of the...
television...
people.
They're everywhere.
5 milligrams of haldol.
You want a latte with that, Janie ?
Dr. Bates.
Looks like somebody
forgot to take their meds.
How long have you been treating her ?
Six years
She's schizophrenic.
When she's on her thorazine,
we don't have a problem.
Why did she stop taking it ?
It was not available
at the relief center.
- Should it have been ?
- Yes.
But the distributor
couldn't get into town.
He was turned away at
one of the roadblocks.
- When did you hear about this ?
- I just heard about it.
I was seeing a patient who's normally very
responsible, and she didn't take her meds
and it's because she couldn'T.
She couldn't get them. I see.
Was this medicine specifically
marked for paloma middle school ?
Yes.
And has this been an ongoing problem ?
Earlier today, I spoke with Terrence
Gale of the Department of Health
and he told me that he's been
to all of the relief centers,
and none of them have
the proper supplies.
I'm gonna get right
on this. Just hold on.
Okay, folks,
I'd like...
Hold it up !
Hold up ! Hold up !
I just need to know when
the grid's gonna be back up.
I can't give you a definitive answer.
Our crews are working. Listen up !
Our crews are working 24/7,
but we're talking about a very large
area here with very limited access.
Okay. A week, two weeks ?
Maybe six to eight.
Mayor ?
Power means nothing if
you don't have a roof.
But what we're hearing is that construction
materials are being doled out very selectively,
and some people are being
shut out all together.
That's not true.
If you go to a supply center
and get in line...
You may live to see another day.
My wife was just attacked at a center.
A mentally ill woman hadn't gotten her
medication because the truck carrying it
was turned away at a roadblock.
Now I thought this lockdown, or
"safety circle," as you called it, Mayor,
was supposed to protect our community,
not make it more dangerous.
Good morning, Russell.
I'm sorry about your wife.
I hope Larkin's all right.
The system isn't perfect, and I realize that
our checkpoints may becausing an inconvenience.
But we are safer for them.
They're helping us to enforce a curfew
- marginalize looting.
- They're choking us, tom.
And I don't really see who they're serving.
Half the checkpoints are in the town itself.
On roads that have already been cleared.
Nobody wants to be cut off. But we are.
And the business community can't
repair itself without supplies.
If you...
Mayor, if you just open up the roads that
are secure, it'll speed things up for us.
Then we need to lose the
perimeter. It's not helping anybody.
You're all missing the point.
We're still in the
containment stage here,
with so many people from
our town unaccounted for.
Chemical and fertilizer plants
that are damaged...
Those are all C.D.C. Issues.
- Our main water supply may be contaminated.
- Then why are you using it ?
Excuse me ?
You have water at your
house, right, Tom ?
- How'd you manage that ?
- We have a well.
Your development has a well ?
No,
I have a well.
Tom,
we all understand your concerns
but maybe we've gone too far here.
If people can't get to
us, we can't rebuild.
That'll be bad for everyone.
All right.
Let's open the doors.
And see what comes through.
You sure you're gonna be
able to carry all that stuff ?
I'm not carrying anything. She is.
I'm just working in
a management capacity.
I'm working in a management capacity.
- You're hammering.
- Oh, no, she's hammering.
Oh, oh, you want hammering ?
No, no,
no, no.
Aah, not the bag. Not the bag.
Underlay.
Are you fondling your brother again ?
- What do you want, Derek ?
- You.
When do I get my ration of you ?
Go away.
Going to Biscayne tonight,
to a little bonfire.
You should come.
I think I'll have other plans.
He can come, too.
So today was the big showdown, huh ?
Big public mano a mano ?
It wasn't that big.
You kicked his ass, right ?
Guess I kind of did.
That's awesome.
That guy needed a good ass kicking.
So no roadblocks, right ?
No.
Cool. Okay, first thing tomorrow. I
want Larkin to take us down to Key Largo.
Why ?
'Cause I want to see what she saw.
- I'm sure it's all gone by now, Dave.
- No, we don't know that.
Larkin said Underlay told her that they
were looking for some downed helicopter.
He told her that the Air Force was
looking for some missing weather airplane.
When they got there, they both saw soldiers
loading some mystery box into the back of a truck.
Wouldn't you like to know
what was in that mystery box ?
- I'd rather know why Underlay was showing it to her.
- You know why.
Control.
Guys like Underlay thrive on control.
He definitely knows there's aliens here.
Oh, Dave...
Air Force knows it, too.
He just has to control the information
or risk blowing his entire alliance.
What alliance ?
With the aliens.
Why are we stopping here ?
Because
we're returning to Earth.
What is this place ?
It's one of our research facilities.
They've been out of
radio contact all day.
What do they do here ?
They study animals, tropical diseases.
Shawn, you here ?
All the researchers left
before the hurricane,
but I know the care taker's been back.
It's Russell !
Oh, no.
the primates are gone.
What ?
How did they get out ?
Hurricane, I bet.
No, the care taker
said they were all here.
Yeah, well
they're not now.
Dave...
Dave ?
Dave, you home ?
I'm sorry.
I waited outside, but the
mosquitoes were killing me.
How did you...
I didn't see your car.
I parked in the back.
I didn't mean to startle you.
Russell's not here.
I know. How you doing ?
I heard about what happened.
I'm all right.
Just a little unnerving.
I'll bet.
Everything all right with the baby ?
Yeah.
Everybody's
okay.
Good.
I was curious if you'd learned
anything more about that box.
Oh.
No.
Haven't had the chance
to follow up on it yet.
You ?
Well, I called my
contact at the Air Force.
He's former C.I.A., So...
you never really know when
you're getting a straight story.
- I thought you said you trusted him.
- I do.
But sometimes he with holds.
- You really want to push this thing ?
- Yes.
If the military is working
on something secret down here
I want to know about it.
Okay.
But if you end up with a story,
you just can't tell anyone
that I helped you get it,
not even your husband.
Russell already knows you helped me.
Larkin.
What I showed you was
highly confidential.
Yeah, from the news.
- I didn't think you were talking about my family.
- From everyone.
I went out on a limb for you.
You wanna be a good wife ?
Talk to your husband.
But if you wanna be a
good reporter, talk to me.
Just don't tell anyone you're doing it.
It was feeding time.
The guy either opened every
cage at once because he's stupid,
or he opened one, maybe
two, apes got spooked,
broke out their buddies
and ripped the guy apart.
They weren't apes.
They were gray baboons.
And they didn't kill him,
at least not intentionally.
How do you know ?
Because his wounds were superficial.
He was bleeding from the nose and mouth.
You think he was poisoned ?
I think he contracted
an infectious disease.
These are all the test
regimens of the baboons inside.
Any or all of'em could
have been carriers.
Of what ?
I'm hoping he can tell us.
Any of you touch anything in there ?
No.
Good.
They're testing his blood now.
His blood's on my foot. I'd wash it.
What about the baboons ?
They'll have to be found.
Even if the disease isn't airborne
if they're carriers, anything
they touch will be contaminated.
Those the regimens ?
Can I see these ?
Start putting a team together.
All right, Dave, as soon
as you get the all clear,
I want you to go home and make sure
Larkin and the kids stay inside.
Don't let them out
until you hear from me.
Yeah, okay.
If the baboons are found quickly,
we may be able to contain this.
But if not...
Dispatch, this is Ranger Varon.
We're gonna need six
teams out here A.S.A.P.
To start tracking downthese primates.
Put wild life in charge of
three. I'll oversee the others.
Let's just start working the grid
and then we'll head east
towards homestead, roger ?
Roger that.
You owe me so big. I never
work this hard at my house.
Well, then this is
invaluable training, Kira.
- Jess ?
- What ?
Have you heard from your Dad lately ?
I don't have a radio.
Yeah, I tried radioing
him. He's not answering.
Well, he might be out of range.
You guys want dinner ?
Rose might, but Jesse
and I are going out.
We are ?
Out where ?
Bonfire.
What about the curfew ?
Oh, well, we'll be back before then.
I don't know, I think you guys
oughta wait and ask your father.
Well, can't we ask you ? I mean...
you do have some authority
around here, don't you ?
All right, but... don't be too late.
Nice play on the stepparent guilt.
Yeah, it's pretty effective.
You could try it with my dad...
if he actually felt guilt.
When did this come in ?
Five minutes ago.
Did you let everyone know ?
Absolutely.
Everything's opened up.
Route 1, krome
avenue--just let it bleed.
I'll be back in 20.
Roger that.
- Hello, mrs. Underlay.
- Hello.
Brought you lunch.
How you doing ?
I'm keeping my head above water.
Is that a joke ?
Yeah.
The woman who attacked
Larkin this morning...
she's schizophrenic.
Her doctor told me thats
he was abused as a child,
and as a result of that
abuse, she disassociated.
She still can't come to terms
with what happened to her.
You're not schizophrenic, mariel.
I know.
But I am different since the hurricane.
You're different because you survived.
Not everyone can say that.
But why did I survive ?
What's that ?
It's a...
warning from the health department.
Some baboons escaped from a
research facility in the glades.
They may be carrying
an infectious disease.
Dispatch ?
Dispatch, you there ? Over.
Tom, what the hell ? I almost hit you.
I understand there are primates out here
with some kind of killer disease.
Why wasn't I called ?
- We're in the glades.
- Oh, and what makes you think
this thing is gonna stayin the glades ?
There's a town just
north of here with people.
A notice went out from
the health department.
Yeah, I read the notice. You
tracking these things alone ?
No, our team just split up.
If I still had my lockdown, I might
have been able to contain this.
- You wanna help ?
- I don't have a choice.
Larkin ? hey, it's me. It's Dave.
- Dave.
- Hey, where are the kids ?
They're in bed.
No, no, no, Rose is here. She's
sleeping, but where's Jesse ?
Is he out with Kira somewhere ?
- It's past 11.
- Yeah, I know.
- Where are they ?
- They went to a park, but they said
that they would be
back here before curfew.
A park ? Where ? What park ?
What's wrong ?
We found a guy today who was
exposed to some kind of virus
that they think might have
killed him in less than 48 hours.
- What ?
- Yeah, it may be passed onby baboons.
- Baboons ? What are you talking...
- Russell's been out there hunting them all day.
But if Jesse and Kira
are still out there...
- Oh, my god !
- Larkin, where are you going ?
Hold on. Do you know where they are ?
- No, but I have to find them !
- Well, how ?
They said they went to a park !
Larkin, the entire everglades is a park.
I don't care ! Russell is gonna kill me.
- Mariel is gonna kill me.
- They're not gonna kill you. Listen !
Stay here with Rose, okay, and have
them radio me when they get back.
Larkin, I...
Stay !
Like I was sayin'before, if you want
it, you gotta go and get it, you know ?
Okay. Yeah.
- All right, man.
- Yeah, right.
Hello, girls. How are you ?
Dude, you want the worm ?
- I'm cool.
- You sure ?
Yeah. All right.
I was just wondering if maybe
I could steal this young lady ?
You know, my dad's a
ranger, too, you know ?
- I know.
- I think we even, like,
used to play together as kids and stuff.
Back when your dad was
married to that other babe.
That other babe's my mom.
Oh.
Cool.
So what's with the arm ?
Oh, I, uh...
- I got in an accident.
- Yeah, I guess you kinda did.
She's so hot. Man.
You're not related to her, are you ?
You know what time it is, man ?
No, man, sorry.
All right.
Later.
Hey, Kira.
Hey, I think we should get going.
Yeah, yeah, me, too.
Wait for me.
How many are we looking for, sheriff ?
I don't know. Ask him.
Seven, one male, six females.
Do you know how they got out ?
The care taker was probably
exposed during the hurricane,
got disoriented, let
them out by accident.
Shouldn't we be checking the trees ?
Hamadryas baboons spend most
of their time on the ground.
What's that ?
It's hearts of palm... baboon food.
Want a bite ?
No. Knock yourself out.
You talk to the kids ?
Not today.
Can I borrow your radio ? Mine's dead.
Channel 4 is your house.
You keep our frequency ?
Only as long as we share children.
Honey.
Honey, you there ?
- Yeah. Hey, baby.
- Hey.
Did Dave tell you what was going on ?
Yeah, yeah, he did. Are you all right ?
Yeah, still out here
looking. Tom's with me now.
The kids okay ?
Larkin ?
Yeah.
Everybody's gonna be all right.
Good. I'm gonna be out here pretty late.
I just wanted you to know. I love you.
Okay, I love you, too.
You guys are really cute.
Like a couple of newlyweds.
We are newlyweds.
Yeah, well, so are Mariel and
I, but we're not... as cute.
it could be an allergic
reaction, maybe an infection.
Her fever shot up pretty
quick. She's coughed up some blood.
I need to take a listen
to your lungs, honey.
Just take a deep breath.
And again.
Call the C.D.C.
This is torture.
It's merely a test.
A test of what ?
See if you're worthy.
- Close your eyes.
- No way.
Close your eyes...
and open your mouth.
You open your mouth.
Okay.
Now you.
****- What art ...****
- Shut, they're close.
Kill the flashlights.
Lewis.
Lewis ?
They're close.
Yeah.
Based on the first victim's blood test,
the C.D.C. thinks it may
be a strain of asian flu
that hasn't been seen since 1957.
I've ordered up the vaccine, but
they don't have any stored,
so it has to be synthesized.
They won't have it down
here for at least two days.
What does that mean for our girl ?
Not good.
Where did she come from ?
She's local.
Her father's the minister
at the first baptist church.
Did her family say anything
about encountering a baboon ?
No, but she's been
around a lot of people.
Her church has been
acting as a relief center.
That's the male.
So...
tell me why you took
Larkin down to Key Largo.
Now ?
Good a time as any.
I think you ought to shock the monkey.
If we wait, we'll have'em all.
If we capture the dominant male, the
females won't try to escape.
So why'd you do it ?
'Cause she was badgering
the hell out of me.
So that's the only reason ?
You know, Russell, if
you trusted me more,
it really would make
life easier for everyone,
and we'd both probably be home
right now, in bed with our wives.
What the hell ?
Kira.
I've been lookingfor you guys all night.
- I...
- Where's Jesse ?
Did I wait long enough ?
Jesse, you promised
me you would be home.
What was I supposed
to do, just leave her ?
Look, it's my fault,
Larkin. I'm really sorry.
Come on, let's just go.
Way to go, Derek !
Dude.
How many cases now ?
Three. Two more came in this morning.
- Good news or bad ?
- Both.
We've examined all the
baboons, none are carriers.
- What ?
- That's the good.
Your care taker, the little
girl, the two new patients ?
If you don't find a common thread
between all of them very quickly,
you'll have a hundred cases
before the end of the week.
You have to stop this, now.
- Quarantine ?
- Absolutely.
Lewis.
Yes, sir.
Safety circle's back on.
I want full quarantine protocol now.
Increase perimeter to 10 miles.
Two officers at every checkpoint.
Lock it down.
Yes, sir.
The care taker, the little
girl, the two new victims,
it's the same flu. There's
no common carrier.
No, but you know what ? There
is a pattern developing.
With the exception of your care taker,
all of the cases have
broken out at relief centers.
One of the new victims is from here.
That's bright water park.
And that little girl practically
lived at the first baptist church.
And the other
one's from here...
paloma middle school.
That's where Larkin was attacked.
I don't know if it's a coincidence
or by virtue of the fact
that so many people are
passing through these places.
We should talk to Terrence Gale.
Who's that ?
Department of health. He's the one that's
been running point at all these centers.
I mean, that's the person that
Larkin interviewed this morning.
He was first on the scene when
I put in the call about the care taker.
Thanks, Russ. We'll take it from here.
I'll talk to him.
Why don't you both talk to him ?
Mr. Gale ?
Yes ?
I'm Russell Varon. We met yesterday.
Stay there. Don't touch anything.
Why not ?
What do you want ?
To talk to you.
The disease seems to be connected
to all the relief centers.
You're here to arrest me ?
You're the carrier, aren't you ?
Mr. Gale ?
But I'm not sick.
God, you know, I was
exposed over a week ago.
I should be dead by now.
I'm not even sick.
Why am I not sick ?
How were you infected ?
I went to the research
facility the day after eve hit.
I asked the care taker
to show me what vaccines
that they had in case
that we needed more, and...
I'd had kind of a rough night.
I was shaky.
Did you contaminate yourself on purpose ?
No. What... why
would I do that ?
It was an accident.
I dropped one of the samples.
It spilled on my hands.
It was this flu.
I immediately called
to order up the vaccine.
But when I didn't get sick, I...
I thought it, the tube
was just mislabeled.
But when you saw the
care taker had died ?
I began to...
wonder if it might be me.
I'd shaken hands with
the man when I left.
Somehow my body has
resisted the infection.
And I've spread it to
all these other people.
It's miraculous.
Miraculous ?
Lewis, we're gonna need an
ambulance and a hazmat team.
Roger that.
You knew you were exposed, but
you still went out anyway ?
I didn't show any symptoms.
Did you touch my wife ?
Did you ?
Russ.
No. No.
Thank you, Mr. Gale.
The ambulance will be here in a minute.
Thank you.
Come on, Russ.
Good call.
We're gonna contain this thing.
Why isn't he sick, Tom ?
I don't know, but we
won't have to quarantine.
The vaccine's are coming tomorrow.
We'll get them to everyone
this guy's been in contact with.
Just keep the safety circle.
No quarantine ?
Maybe next time you give me
the benefit of the doubt, huh ?
Why isn't he sick ?
You take care. Drive safe.
Lewis.
Mr. Gale.
I think something happened
to you during the hurricane...
something maybe you don't understand.
We should talk.
What are you doing ?
Hey, I'm contagious.
Not to me.