Previously...
- where is the orb?
- What the orb?
You just want to take over
the world with some alien nation.
I am trying to save the world.
My cousin lois vanished for three
weeks and then suddenly appeared,
claiming that she was being
chased by a ninja-clad assassin.
I think i know
where she was. The future.
Could these vivid dreams you've
been having have something to do
with your three weeks
of blocked memory?
Why don't we have the powers
we should have under yellow sun?
I will find the answers
we are looking for,
or i will die in the quest!
I give you
the world's first solar tower.
- Why are you risking your own life?
- Because it's the only chance i have
- before you destroy our world.
- Clark would never in a million years
risk what needed to be done.
And i told you lois
doesn't have that kind of time.
You get dr. Weiss on a helicopter
and get him to met gen now.
I got three of the country's
best neuro mds on their way.
- It's too late. She is already missing.
- What do you mean she's missing?
You took her to the hospital.
You've been with her all night.
I was. I stepped out
to see if you called,
and when i got back, she was gone.
There's nothing in her chart.
There's no releases,
and there are no witnesses.
Hospital said someone called and
requested a copy of lois' test results.
Why would emil care about lois?
He wouldn't.
Maybe the person
he's working for would.
Spying on lois' computers
and hacking into her therapist files.
Did you really need to escalate into
kidnapping her from a coma ward?
There's a mystery
surrounding miss lane.
And this is my chance to solve it.
So, what, all this
because she told a shrink
she has headaches and sees
weird futuristic flashes?
What? I can't hack into
these files and not read them.
They're called boundaries,
stuart. Find some.
And these futuristic flashes
may not be imaginary.
Besides, lois was investigating zod's
orb when she vanished for three weeks.
you think these are repressed memories
that she's already been through?
This technology will tell us.
Can't you get more
than just fragments?
I'm sorry but her mind is like
a mental mosh pit right now, okay?
- Only a human,
- pause it.
That's zod's solar tower...
exactly as it's designed
to be built.
But the plans haven't even
gone public yet.
Lois did go to the future.
Okay, you better pop some popcorn.
She's remembering something.
Where's the orb?
What orb?!
Where are you? Don't start
what you can't finish.
What the hell?
Hello?!
Why are you out of uniform?
Maybe because i dropped out
of girl scouts years ago.
You're bleeding.
You're nothing but a filthy human.
This zone is off limits
to your kind.
But this dream is all mine,
so what's with the attitude?
It is not your place
to ask questions.
I'm a reporter.
Asking questions is in my blood.
Well, then...
it would be a shame to spill it.
The red-blue blur.
He'll stop you.
Not under a red sun.
Look around you.
The blur is dead.
Smallville - 9x09 - Pandora
Synchro: Flolo
For Seriessub.com
tuning the tv
to channel lois is one thing but
syncing your brainwaves to hers?
All we're seeing on the screen
are jumbled images.
To get the answers
i'm looking for, i need to plug in.
I didn't build
this technology, okay?
Don't you think we should have
someone from summerholt here?
Zod said that his tower's
going to change the world.
Lois' memories of the future
should show me how.
How hard can this be?
Time for food.
Come on. Let's go.
Stealing will not go unpunished.
Easy. I was just hoping
for some food here.
And i'm pretty sure this is a bad dream,
but right now, i could eat
- about 30 maple doughnuts.
- You want food?
And what do you have to trade?
Take this.
It's all i have.
It's yours if you let her go.
This will do...
for now.
I thought i'd lost you forever.
Thank god.
I can't believe you're alive.
- This dream just got 10 times brighter.
- What do you mean "dream"?
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you
this but you're not dreaming.
If this isn't a dream then it's the
worst nightmare i could ever imagine.
Since when did the kent
family farm become a prison?
Why would you give away the one thing
of your dad's that meant so much to you?
I did it for you.
Okay, hold on.
Explain about the wicked witch
and the flying freaks.
Have we been invaded
by "the wizard of oz"?
More like another planet.
Aliens?
Before i fought tess,
she went on and on about some orb,
called it alien technology, said
there was life inside of it.
This invasion, tess knew about it.
Yeah, tess may have helped.
These aliens have
their own leader. His name is zod.
I tried to fight him, but...
i made all the wrong choices.
A lot of people died.
Please tell me
chloe wasn't one of them.
I don't know.
After i thought i lost you,
i went off on my own.
I haven't talked to her in months.
Months?
You vanished a year ago.
No, i was just throwing down
with tess a few hours ago.
And then i grabbed that gold ring.
The legion ring?
It must have brought you here when
you put it on. Do you still have it?
Yeah.
You. Zod likes to see you.
Protect the ring.
Where's lois?
Last i heard, you dropped her
at the hospital.
Someone moved her and i know
that you had emil look into her records.
She's my cousin.
You've been hiding things
from me for months.
Now i think you're hiding lois.
Right accusation, wrong girl.
I may not have been sharing my deep,
dark secrets with you lately,
but someone else has been
playing hide-and-seek
a lot longer than i have.
Yeah. We can work
on your apology later.
Tess has been keeping more
than just an editorial eye on lois
for the past few months.
Lois can't answer any of
her questions. She's in a coma.
She doesn't have to talk to tess
for her to run tests on her.
And we both know how obsessed
she's been with the fact
that lois vanished for three weeks.
You think this has something to
do with her trip to the future.
I think it's possible.
Emil gave me
the hospital workups on her.
She suffers from
post-traumatic stress disorder.
So every time she has a memory,
her body relives the trauma.
Her heart can only take so much.
I have to find her.
Tess is never gonna admit that
she took lois. Let me try something.
I have a guy on the inside.
Okay, ladies, we're a little
touch-and-go here right now but
we are stable again.
And you should have a front-row
seat to the lois matinee.
No, no.
No.
I guess membership has
its privileges.
Try the truffle.
It's my favorite.
To think...
a few of these
could mean the difference
between life and death
for your kind.
I'm general zod.
And all of this
is mine to give...
if you give me the names
of whoever snuck you
into the restricted zone.
My dad's a general, too.
And he still
couldn't get me to spill
how i got an m1 abrams tank
to take me to prom.
So i'm definitely not
telling you anything.
Then you hear this.
No matter how many times
you resistance fighters
break into the zone, you'll never...
never take down my tower.
What is this?
You?
You redheaded rat!
Do you know her?
She used to work for me.
But then she disappeared.
Traitor!
I am this planet's savior!
I helped general zod take power
to ensure this earth's survival.
Tess mercer,
the ultimate ecoterrorist.
And what are you?
I understand you were seen
talking to clark kent.
It was only a matter of time
before the resistance got to him.
The only thing i'm resisting is
the urge to kick both your asses.
And if clark were here
right now, he would back me up.
The only reason clark is still alive
is because i'd hoped he'd join us
to bridge the gap
between our people.
Trust me, zod.
No one has worked as hard as i have
to get clark to see
the good that we're doing.
But i think we've fooled
ourselves long enough.
He won't come around.
Which is why...
Neither of you
is any good to me alive.
Excuse me?
A double execution
will send out a strong message
to anyone who would dare defy me.
Take heart, lois.
At least you can enjoy
a glorious last meal.
Today, two lives end...
but another begins.
Rise, soldier.
You betrayed the entire human
race for some crappy dog tags.
Way to go!
Let her go.
Take my life!
Let her live!
Your bravery is commendable.
But by defying me,
you have forced my hand.
I wanted you to join me
on this new earth.
But now i must bury you beneath it.
No!
There's too much kryptonite.
Heya, legs. Long time, no see.
And am i glad to see you
and your band of merrymen.
It's not my band.
- What?
- It's hers.
I didn't think i was ever
gonna see you again.
You almost didn't. Those crazy
space invaders almost killed us.
I guess we owe you guys our lives.
You always were a good shot.
I didn't do this to you.
I didn't.
I know.
I did this to myself.
It was a risk choosing zod
over my own people...
but someone had to save the earth.
I couldn't give up on that.
I had the shot.
I had to take it.
Chloe kills me.
I'm not sure
what you saw in there but out here,
you were still alive.
So, i guess i did okay, right?
You did your job, mensa boy.
Now finish it.
I don't want lois waking up with
the memories that i just saw.
That would be too dangerous.
Use the device to wipe them out.
If i make a mistake,
she could come out of this catatonic.
Don't argue with me, stuart.
No.
Okay? I won't do it.
I won't.
- Excuse me?
- I'm gonna pull her out.
I'm sorry,
but we are literally messing
with someone's mind here.
I'm sorry, too.
Stuart went rogue.
He took her.
- I had to stop him.
- What'd you do to her?
We may have won the battle,
but zod will come back harder now.
Then it's time we take a stand.
Lois vanished a year ago after
she put on the legion ring.
You time-traveled here?
I'm pretty sure i didn't walk a whole
year into the future. Not in these heels
The thing is, i lost the ring.
That one-named wonder, zod, took it.
We need to get the ring back.
Then lois can return to the past
and prevent zod's tower from
being built in the first place.
That's not a bad plan, clark,
but why should i trust you now?
You already left us once
to fight on your own.
You abandoned us, big guy.
Plain and simple.
I thought i could stop zod myself.
I tried to take him on
as my enemy, and i was wrong.
But i'm here now.
Okay, then, look.
Why clark decided to take on
our enemy e. t.s by himself
is beyond me, and maybe you think
he abandoned the cause or something.
But come on,
aren't we all in this together?
You guys shut down that tower
and bring back the yellow sun,
you know i'm your best chance
of getting back that ring.
Maybe.
I still don't trust you.
I guess that's a start.
So, about the tower?
The towers are the key
to the kandorians' power.
They collect all the sun's
radiation, turn it red,
and then beam it back up
to the luthorcorp satellites.
Those satellites take the radiation and
they beam it back down to earth,
giving those alien s. o.b. s
all their superhuman strength.
Now, we take the tower down,
we take them down.
Guys, i've seen zod's troops.
We are seriously outnumbered.
We'd never reach it.
We don't have to.
We have a secret weapon.
Watchtower.
I powered down watchtower
so the kandorians couldn't find it
but i can use the computers to
hack into zod's big red flashlight
and unleash a virus that should
shut it off remotely.
You guys bring back the yellow sun,
and i'll take the others
to find the legion ring.
I just have one more question.
How does turning the sun yellow
make clark our number-one draft pick
for taking on this zod guy?
Zod and i have history.
You okay?
Define "okay."
So far today,
i've traveled through time,
fought a flying alien,
and almost got my head chopped off.
But despite all those things...
one thing i can't believe...
i can't believe you and chloe
aren't friends anymore.
It's not her fault.
I turned my back on her.
After you disappeared, i couldn't...
i couldn't be around.
Oliver or chloe, it reminded me of you,
and that hurt too much.
So...
i left...
and trained myself to fight zod.
What did you mean about
having a history with him?
Let's just say
that i made some mistakes.
Stop beating yourself up.
You are not alone in this.
The truth is...
we could all die tomorrow.
I died when you left.
I'm here now.
I wish we had more time.
Clark, can you hear me?
Can you hear me, clark?
The ambulance will be here soon.
Stuart's lost a lot of blood,
but luckily he's still alive.
And i'm sure that mercer
"the merciless" will be fine.
How's clark?
Somehow this machine
synced their brainwaves.
Clark's literally
locked into lois' memories.
But i believe there's a way
that i can pull them out.
Don't close the curtain yet.
I took a peek into lois' therapy
files that tess hacked into.
I think that every time
that she saw her therapist,
it actually unlocked more of
her memories from the future.
These memories
are physically damaging.
You really want
to put their lives in danger?
If you pull clark out now,
it will put a lot of
other people's lives at stake.
When that assassin
from the future came back,
she told clark that
he would destroy the world.
Now, he has to know how to stop it.
Honey, i'm home.
Okay, remember when we were 10
and i kicked you out of
my clubhouse for spilling soda
and you said
you'd just build a cooler one?
You win.
So, this is what happens
when there's no blur.
That's why we need
every hero we can get.
For the woman who has everything.
It's a meteor-rock knife.
I've encased it in lead
so the enemy won't know you're
packing till it's too late.
Even in the future, you still
know how to charm a girl.
The last firewall's down.
I'm in the zod tower's command center.
The virus is almost ready.
Take that, master control.
There. Just a few minutes,
we should see our yellow sun
rise and shine again.
Kandorians are coming.
We should go.
I'll scout ahead and make sure
the coast is clear.
Go. I'll be right behind you.
Come on!
You can make it!
No!
Get the hell away from her.
Look at me!
You're gonna be fine!
You're gonna be okay!
The best way to avenge her death
is to get that ring.
No.
No, i won't leave her.
She's still alive in the past, lois.
You can save her!
Make sure this future never
happens and you'll save all of us.
You better get going.
Clark's heading to the tower.
I'll cover you.
I should have guessed
you'd come after me.
All to save a doomed race.
When faced with a crumbling
world, these humans,
they'd rather die
than unite under a single leader
and do what's required
to build a glorious new world.
It's tragic. You thought you could
take me on like this.
Metropolis would not be destroyed
if you had all just
stopped fighting and joined me.
We'll never stop fighting, zod.
Humanity will never lose its spirit.
Goodbye, son of jor-el.
No.
Your reign of terror is over, zod.
I'm sending lois home to the past.
She can warn us about your tower
before it's ever built.
You chose to fight me.
You forced me to unleash my power!
We could have made this planet
a paradise!
It always was.
But you never gave humanity
a chance.
They've made you weak.
If she travels back in time,
then the lives we know
will cease to exist.
You have destroyed our world.
Take the ring, put it on.
- No.
- You have to. Now.
What if i never see you again?
You will.
- Welcome back.
- How's lois?
She'll be up in a few minutes
with a headache,
but it's nothing that a couple
of aspirin can't handle.
I was able to isolate
the area of her cortex
where her synapses were firing
at an accelerated rate.
By injecting her with a chemical inhibitor
i effectively reset those synapses.
So her memories from the future
are gone, right?
If she had them while under the influence
of the machine she won't remember.
From the look on your face,
i take it the future isn't so bright.
What did you see, clark?
Here.
This is for you.
You just got back from a trip
to the hospital, not hawaii.
You need to take it slow.
I have hypoglycemia.
Not arthritis.
Doc says as long as i eat
every three hours, i'm gold.
- Happy?
- Very.
I almost lost you once.
I don't want it to happen again.
What are we doing?
I'm eating a maple doughnut.
And you're kind of invading
my personal space.
I mean us.
Lois and clark,
clark and lois, as a couple.
Cowboy!
You just went from 10 to,
like, 110 in 2 seconds flat.
Let's just slow it down.
I still need
to get my feet back under me.
You can lean on me for strength.
I feel stronger
when you're around, anyway.
I have done this dating
thing wrong so many times.
Then let's do it right.
Let's take our time.
Really?
In that case...
let's go get a real cup of coffee.
And then we'll have lunch ...
the first of many.
There will be ice cream
and chalupas,
picnics in the park,
dancing in the rain.
And you will take me
to a monster-truck rally.
For a guy who just got a mondo case
of kryptonite, you sure seem happy.
The sun is shining,
lois is gonna be all right.
She should be fine. Dr. Emil ran
every possible test on her,
and she's healthy
and doesn't remember a thing.
Except, of course, the flowers
that clark sent to her hospital room,
but who could forget
five dozen roses?
Five dozen roses.
Wow. That's subtle.
I really don't get why
the two of you are grinning,
considering the fact that we're all
about to die terribly tragic deaths
in the not-so-distant future.
That's because if we do something in
the present, we can change all that.
I vote we take zod out right now.
That way, he doesn't have a chance
to take the sunshine
off our shoulders.
In the future that i saw,
i tried to fight zod.
All i did was turn him
into a more powerful enemy.
Just because you learned
a lesson in teamwork
doesn't mean
we have to stop fighting zod.
But going up against zod will only force
him to come back with everything he has.
what, you think you two
can just hug it out?
When my father said "save zod,"
what i think he meant
was save zod from himself.
Now if i can befriend him,
show him how good life can be here.
That would be a mistake.
If zod gets his solar towers online that
gives him all the power in the world
and us none, including you.
Zod will fly
psychopathic circles around you.
I've seen what happens
when i treat zod like the enemy.
This time, i'm gonna do things
the right way.
This tower must be built...
at all costs!
You...
you find your way into city hall.
Smooth over any laws
that might get in our way.
You, infiltrate the power plant
to divert the energy we need.
And you...
i understand
you've been looking for me.
My brother and sister kandorians...
he has come.
Kneel... before kal-el.