So, uh, we used to come to
places like this together?
I can't believe it's all blank.
It'll come back.
How about i rein you to your favorite bevvy?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hey.
The promoter needs some gum,
and i'm fresh out.
You got any?
Look around, einstein.
We're in a gum factory.
Right.
Let's hear some noise!
And here is one republic!
Hey, look out!
Hey, what happened?
Thanks.
Smallville 713 : "Hero"
Synchro : Flolo
Transcript : Yyets.net
www.SeriesSub.com
Well, at least kara didn't forget
how to use up all the hot water.
Yes, but i understand that,
She still hasn't managed
to recover her memory.
She still thinks she's from minnesota.
But i think the more
she looks into her past...
She'll realize it's all a lie.
Do you think, if she was, uh,
taken to the fortress...
It might speed up the, uh, process?
Last time i went to jor-El for advice,
he kept me prisoner in the fortress.
I think it's time to tell her the truth.
She won't believe you.
Clark, we have to protect her.
I agree, especially when she's been...
Visiting...
With lex.
As much as i hate to admit it, it makes sense.
He found her. She trusts him.
Her bracelet.
That connects her to krypton.
Yes, but, uh, i thought it had gone missing.
It has, but there's got
to be some way to find it.
Oh... in the meantime,
I suggest you keep a sharp eye on lex's,
Latest endeavor.
Pete ross. What a surprise.
- Oh, my god, pete.
- Hey.
Pete, it's good to see you.
What are you doing here?
More importantly, what's he doing here?
I guess more has changed
around here than i thought.
It's a long story.
Lex?
I take it the fresh farm air isn't as
invigorating as it's cracked up to be.
I spend every day wandering
around that place,
Trying to find something
that will jog my memory.
Well... did anything stand out?
Anything out of the ordinary?
Actually, yeah.
Everything.
I don't feel connected to it at all.
But thanks for finding what you did.
I know it matches with the girl
formerly known as kara kent, but...
The girl in that folder isn't me.
How well do you know clark?
Do you trust him?
I wish i could say yes.
I'm starting to wonder if he's
hiding something from me.
Doesn't it seem weird that i don't have
any medical or dental records?
Who doesn't get sick?
Clark can be evasive.
Why would he lie to me?
I mean, what in my past could be so horrible
he wouldn't want me to know about it?
I promise you...
I will do everything in my power
to help you get your memory back.
Now, i don't suppose clark has mentioned
anything about your missing bracelet?
No.
Then i guess i should tell you.
The design on your bracelet is a symbol...
A symbol that matches others
that have appeared around smallville.
These were first seen as paintings
in the kawatchee caves.
But they've appeared much more recently...
Burned into the kent barn.
Whatever clark's hiding from you...
I think it has something
to do with these symbols.
That bracelet could be the clue
to uncovering your true identity.
Well, i'll see you this afternoon.
Are you sure you don't
want me to go with you?
No, it's okay. Ben will
help me unload the posts.
So, the secret of the century
is not so secret anymore.
Lionel, chloe, and lana
All know the truth about your
extraterrestrial crash landing?
It all just kind of happened.
Well, the truth is, with all the danger
i put you in, knowing my secret,
I actually didn't want to tell anybody else, but...
But... let me guess.
You couldn't stop trying to save the world,
and you got caught.
Let's go.
Wonder what your dad would think about
a luthor hanging out in his kitchen.
2-1.
Since my dad's been gone...
Lionel's done a lot for me and my mom.
Oh, i'm sure he has. I mean,
He's done a lot for my family, too.
Took our factory, caused my parents' divorce.
The guy's a real saint.
That's the way it used to be.
I can't really expect you
to understand. I mean,
You have been gone for over three years.
What have you been doing?
We don't all land our dream career like chloe.
Kind of been doing the roadie gig.
Pays the bills.
Could of at least returned one of my calls.
You think it's easy saying goodbye
to your best friend?
I couldn't risk anyone using me
to get to the truth about your secret.
I figured it was better just leaving
it all in the past.
- I didn't ask you to do that, pete.
- I know,
But it doesn't change the fact that i've been
looking over my shoulder ever since.
I mean, i had to leave my life
behind because of you, clark.
And to be honest...
It was better than living in your shadow.
I didn't know.
Luckily, everything's changed.
I finally brought my game up
to your level, clark.
- What happened to you?
- Doesn't matter.
The other night, i saved this girl,
And i finally got a taste of what
it felt like to be you...
To be a hero.
Whatever it is, we need to
find a way to reverse it.
I should have known you
couldn't be happy for me.
- I want you to be careful.
- And what, hide like you?
This isn't you. It's the kryptonite.
You know what it does, it warps your reality.
The only thing warped is how many more
people's lives you're gonna ruin
By keeping your powers a secret.
I'm not gonna make anyone live
with that burden like you did.
Things change, clark.
Time to share the glory, and
if you try to stop me,
My secret isn't gonna be the only
one in danger of being exposed.
Well, who should i blame
for my server problems?
I've been locked out of my files.
Yes!
Thank you.
Open my e-Mail yet?
Sorry, jimmy, i've been in i.T.
Hell all morning.
Some network issue has got me
surfing the slow lane.
Okay. Here.
Pretty cool, huh?
Oh, my god.
I know, right?
This guy's elastic limbs
Are gonna slingshot his story straight
to the front page.
Jimmy, this guy is pete ross.
He was, like, my best friend in high school,
Like, back before clark.
You, uh, ditched him for clark?
No.
Uh, i mean, we were all friends.
We were all best friends.
Well, he is gonna be an overnight superstar.
I just got off the phone.
He's the first meteor freak.
Uh... biologically enhanced individual...
... who's willing to be
interviewed about his powers.
I just need to flesh this out a little.
- Interviewed? Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Imagine what a guy like pete could do for the
public perception of the meteor-Enhanced.
He's smart. He's funny.
The guy's story is beyond amazing, it's great.
Okay, so, he's a walking personal ad,
But, jimmy, as much as i appreciate
your socially conscious attitude adjustment,
The press would turn pete into a circus freak.
It's just an interview.
You know what? Maybe you're right.
Do you mind if i, um,
Add a little purple prose,
just to smooth out the rough edges?
Please sprinkle some of your hemingway dust.
Look, i'm off to the stride factory.
I'm gonna interview a few of elastic man's
comrades before they start the next gig.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Hey, clark, uh, we've got a problem,
And it appears to be growing.
Chloe.
Glad to see someone's taking advantage
of my open-Door policy.
The i.T. Department told me
you've been monitoring
Everything that happens on
the daily planet computers.
Unauthorized surveillance is totally unethical.
Pretty big words from a cub reporter.
Shouldn't you be using them to write stories?
Good idea.
I think "office espionage"
has a nice ring to it.
Look...
I'm new here, but i thought lois had first
stab at conspiracy theories.
You hacked into my computer
and copied my files, lex!
- I have rights!
- No. You don't have rights.
You have responsibilities.
Owning the daily planet means
everything within these walls,
And if you have a problem with the way
i run this paper, miss sullivan,
You're free to find out if the inquisitor
offers a more considerate environment!
You're excused.
- What time is the concert tonight?
- 8:00.
Thanks, bro. Keep livin'.
Hey, c.K.
Kara tell you about pete's
stretch save last night?
Snapped his arms out like silly
putty right in front of me.
Maybe you didn't see what you
thought you saw, jimmy.
What, you don't want to think that one of
your best friends could be a meteor freak?
Look, i just hate to think that you have
something against the meteor-Enhanced.
That's not it... i just don't want to see
anything happen to pete... that's all.
Like what, get the credit he deserves?
Pete ross is a hero. He saved kara's life.
And having the courage
To reveal that to the rest of the world...
that's a big deal.
I'm not sure the rest of the world
is gonna see it that way.
Why? The world needs a hero
now more than ever, clark.
Maybe meteor freaks can walk among
us without being afraid.
Wouldn't you want that if one was your friend?
I always knew the torch would light
the way to the big leagues.
Pete, hey! It's so good to see you!
Don't be too impressed, though. I just went
from being a big fish in a small pond
To a minnow in the atlantic.
Well, i, for one, have read all your stories.
And as much as some things change,
some things always remain the same.
I couldn't agree more.
I'm actually in the process of mopping up
lex luthor's daily carnage as we speak.
Now, there's a name i don't miss.
He's playing big brother on all of
the computers at the daily planet.
All my work is under his cyber lock and key.
Well, can't you just work some of your
virtual voodoo and get them back?
Short of a direct hit from a massive virus,
All of these files will forever be in
the clutches of citizen lex.
Maybe i can give him something
else to focus on.
Cool, huh?
A-Actually, yeah.
Uh, come here.
You don't want lex or anyone else
seeing that you can do that.
Come on, chloe, don't tell me that clark's
got you running scared
- Because of his secret, too?
- Okay, i know you don't mean that.
- Cause this isn't about clark.
- Isn't it?
I mean, i remember what it was
like, covering for him...
Always having to watch what
you had to say, lying...
To you.
Sometimes you don't have another choice.
Yes, you do.
And for once, i'm glad not to be
following in clark's footsteps.
No secrets, chloe. Put it on the front page.
Okay, pete, i get the whole "reach
for the stars" mentality,
And right now you actually could reach
a few of those stars. But
What all about all the meteor-Infected people
who still appreciate their privacy?
If they want to keep living a lie,
that's their problem.
Maybe it's time for everyone to realize
that a real hero doesn't hide in the shadows.
Excuse me.
Are you looking for something?
Lana.
Um... yeah, i was...
Kara, i don't think that clark would
appreciate you going through his things.
What do you know about these symbols?
As much as anyone in smallville, i guess.
They're from a local indian tribe.
Then why were they on the
bracelet i used to wear?
Well, maybe you bought it
while you were here visiting the kents,
Or maybe they sent it to you as a present.
Know what's amazing?
How you and clark can just lie
on autopilot like that.
I know about the symbol's
burned into the barn...
And the fields.
And i know about this.
A tattoo you somehow don't have anymore.
Where did you get these?
Lex.
Lex has a way of being the hero
At the exact moment that you need to be saved.
I know how enticing that can be.
One day, he'll turn the tables,
and you'll realize that everything was a lie.
If you really want to prove that
lex is the one lying...
Then just tell me the truth.
It's obvious you're covering something.
Please, lana.
You know, you can keep
shoveling dirt over my past...
But eventually...
I'll uncover the truth.
Please... don't let me disturb you.
Quite the hero these days,
aren't you, pete?
Saving kara.
And now i gather you're
trying to impress chloe
By erasing any record of her
extracurricular projects.
I guess things never change.
You're living proof of that.
You know, we may have more
in common than you think.
We both had a friend who let us down,
And something tells me you know
what it's like to love a woman
Who's still infatuated with clark kent.
Maybe i was wrong.
Things do change.
You're even more messed up than before.
I thought an olive branch was
a pretty civilized response
To breaking and entering. But...
However you want to see it, one truth remains...
I control chloe's fate.
And if you really want to be her hero,
You're gonna put that amazing
ability to work for me.
Now... there's a certain bracelet
That i believe is locked in my father's vault.
I want it.
I'm sure you do.
But chloe wouldn't want you
using her job to make me do anything.
I'm not talking about her job, pete.
I'm talking about the secret
she's been keeping.
Do you really want to be
the reason the world
Finds out that chloe's a meteor freak?
- Stride gum factory?
- It's been used as an underground venue
For bands until it was shut
down a few months ago.
It's already been closed?
Maybe next time they won't let
the flavor last quite so long.
I found the source of pete's powers.
Kryptonite-Enhanced gum.
I found a whole stockpile.
Chewing gum? Is nothing sacred anymore?
I destroyed it, but we have to find pete.
His attitude is changing.
Ah, so, you got a whiff of pete
"the boss" ross, too, huh?
If he ingests any more kryptonite...
we both know what happens to people.
Present company on standby.
And since the "go-Go gadget" arms
Has been going public with his
abilities, he's got to be...
What's going on?
It looks like some kind of virus.
My computer's totally fried.
And judging from the collective sighs,
so is everybody else's.
Clark, i think our new hero went vigilante
and wiped out the planet's server to protect me.
Hey, guys!
Major scoop.
Pete's headed over to lionel luthor's office.
He's stealing something for lex.
Guess your world's only big enough for one hero.
This isn't the way to be a hero, pete.
The kryptonite is affecting your judgment.
Just tell me what lex has on you.
I'll take care of it.
By doing what?
I've only been back in town one day, and already
lex is squeezing me to get to your secret.
My secret?
Look familiar?
It always comes back to you.
Guess you didn't know your new
best friend had that?
- There must be a reason.
- His last name, clark.
Lionel, lex... they're the same person.
And they're not gonna stop using people
until they get to the truth about you.
Sorry, clark...
... but i don't have a choice.
Now, if i turn that bracelet over to lex,
he's gonna get one step closer to your secret.
The only way to stop all this
is to take lex out of the equation.
It's my turn to save you...
And everybody else from lex once and for all.
Pete... you're late.
You're right.
I should have done this three years ago.
How many more people are you gonna hurt?!
When is it gonna end?
Where's the bracelet, pete?
I never found it!
- I don't have it.
- Where is it?
I don't have it.
You're starting to try my patience, pete.
Then bring it on...
cause the truth isn't gonna change.
Then maybe we can help.
What happened, clark?
You and i need to talk.
First, i need to stop pete from
making a huge mistake.
I don't like this any more
than you do, pete...
But i need that bracelet.
Now, this is the last time
i'm gonna ask you.
Where is it?
I don't have it! I already told
you i don't have it!
And i never did.
Okay.
You okay?
Yeah.
I guess the best part about
knowing your secret is...
Being able to say...
Thank you.
I got to admit...
One-On-One was a lot more
fun when i had powers.
Now i'm really at a disadvantage.
Come on, pete.
Even without powers, you were
always at a disadvantage.
Let's just hope for a quick recovery.
Look, clark, um, i didn't really mean
what i said yesterday.
You're not the reason my life's
ended up the way it has.
I know the kryptonite
Can get you a little amped,
but you weren't wrong.
Almost every day, i wonder what it would
be like not to have to live a lie,
But... you can't. I know.
I never really understood how
hard it was being you.
I was always a little jealous
of your life, and...
It was easier to blame you.
I'm sorry.
It's time for me to make a change.
I know there's a hero inside
me somewhere. I just...
I got to find another way to save the world.
Hey, chloe.
Hey.
Is this the "barry bonds" pete
or the "hank aaron" pete?
This is a "100% pete ross" pete.
I just came by to apologize before i left.
Clark told me what you did.
Thank you.
You risked your life to protect me. Now,
that's not only webster's definition of "hero,"
It's mine, too. There's no apology needed.
Chloe, um, lex told me you had a power.
Y-You don't have to tell me what it is.
This...
Is for ruining your computer.
Pete...
Just promise me you won't let another
light-Year pass by before i see you again.
- You can count on it.
- Come here.
Hey!
Jimmy.
No hard feelings, man.
I-I decided to live my life in anonymity.
I understand.
- Some secrets are better kept.
- Yeah.
- See you soon.
Pete!
Relax.
It's kryptonite-Free.
Bye.
So, you guys gonna be hanging out anytime soon?
I just mean, it looks like
gumby found his pokey.
- Unless you...
- You were right the first time.
- Pete and i are just friends.
- Cool.
Yeah, it's cool.
What about you?
How was date night with kara?
Uh, you know...
No, kara's great... but...
I think the spark kind of
fizzled for both of us.
Sorry.
No, you're not.
No, n-No, w-Wha... uh, what i meant
was that i... i hope that you're not.
I should have just said that i'm not, right?
Is there any...
Interest in seeing if we can breathe
some fire into this ember over a cup of coffee?
I'll bring the butane.
Mr. Luthor?
I checked with the metropolis observatory
About the constellation in your family crest.
The last time these stars were configured
in this exact arrangement
Was october 7, 1989.
The day of the first meteor shower.
And there's something else.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to disturb you.
I thought i made myself clear.
You're always welcome here.
I was hoping you'd say that.
I don't trust clark and lana anymore.
And the idea of living with them on the farm...
I hope you don't mind, lex, but i was
wondering if i could stay here...
With you.
Synchro : Flolo
Transcript : www.Yyets.Net