Quiet morning.
It's cold, still...
Bleak.
Almost reminds you of Krypton, doesn't it?
Who are you?
The answer to many
of your unanswered questions.
I seriously think you have
the wrong farmhouse.
I would have expected a girl raised by
such a stoic race to be a better liar.
But you're just as transparent as Kal-El.
- How do you know Kal-El?
- I've been watching.
I don't know what you want,
But that life is in my past.
Only because you have no option to
return, but you woul wouldn't you?
You have to miss the way
things used to be.
Getting memory back must have been...
A disappointment.
I like my life here.
And I think you should leave.
That's a valiant effort,
But it's not the truth.
What if I told you
That there was a way to go back...
To save everyone you loved?
I'd say you weren't the first Kryptonian
to use those memories against me.
And it won't work.
That's unfortunate...
Because I need you.
Sorry. At's not my problem.
Well, at least you can't say
I didn't ask nicely.
Just remember...
If we'd have done this my way,
No one would have gotten hurt.
Smallville 715
Synchro : Flolo
Transcript : www.1000fr.Com
For SeriesSub.com
Why didn't you tell me there was
another Kryptonian on Earth?
You were halfway across the country
with no memory. And he's not a guy.
He's a machine. He's a...
He's a computer.
Brainiac.
The last time I went up
against this thing,
He wanted me to release Zod.
But you destroyed Zod, right?
What is he after now?
Me.
Your father.
He made a lot of bad choices toward
the end. Is it possible that he and
- Zod were allies?
- Never.
If there's one thing
that our fathers agreed on,
It was their hatred for Zod.
Then why has he turned
his attention toward you?
I don't know.
But when we go up against him,
It would be helpful if we were all
on the same playing field.
Or should I say "sky"?
Aren't articles supposed to have words?
Well, I just start with the best
part and work backwards.
Well, my photo card has
an equally big blank spot
That's dying to be filled, and I was
just wondering if...
... well, If you needed some eye candy to
complement those pros, but it looks like...
Don't they put you guys on assignment?
Yeah, yeah. The, um, the little stuff.
But now that the news is brought
to you by Luthorcorp,
I need something really, really big
to stay off the gallows.
Don't worry. Lex couldn't hate you
more than he hates me.
So why not give him a double whammy?
Lois Lane and Jimmy Olsen
in their big debut.
What about Chloe?
Well, I know this will shock
you, but Clark called,
And Chloe ran off
on some big secret project.
Okay. Better make sure that camera
is loaded with ammo
Because I got tomorrow's headline.
"Daughter of nobel-Winning
astronomer murdered."
That Swann woman they fished out
of the lake last night?
Yeah.
I thought that she drowned.
More like sank.
Kind of hard to swim
after you've been shot.
All the tracks have been
covered, Mr. Luthor.
No one will ever be able to
trace the locket back to you.
- I don't need to remind you.
- Absolute secrecy.
After this many years, trust me,
I understand the magnitude of this moment.
It's funny.
All those global treasure hunts
and cave excavations,
And the secret of veritas was
so much closer than I thought.
I suppose it's poetic in a way.
Most things we spend our lives searching for
Usually are right in front of us.
There is one thing I don't quite understand.
You say you've been
searching your whole life.
But I thought you didn't learn
about veritas until recently.
I've always known my father
was covering a secret...
A secret of cryptic symbols
and mystic stones.
I just didn't know it had a name.
And what was it?
The final piece?
My own memory.
After the first meteor shower,
there were years I blocked out.
I keep having flashes of things
that I'd forgotten.
And that's how you remembered that.
Come on, Patty. It's your turn.
But I just went.
Patty!
Okay, okay. I'll go.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Ready or not, here I come.
Dr. Swann has been very
open about the traveler.
Has he? I feel like I'm trying to solve
a puzzle fill with a few pieces,
- He's keeping things from us.
- Lionel! He's being cautious.
And from the... you're
suggesting, he should be.
Swann only tells us
what we need to know.
- It's safer that way.
- I understand, but
Suppose it's all been a trick, a ruse?
If we don't open that envelope,
Dr. Swann's conclusions could be as
mythical as the gods of mount olympus.
Virgil's gonna be here any minute.
I suggest you don't
Refer to his life's work as mythology.
Veritas...
Is the greatest secret the world
will ever know.
We form this group to use our wealth and power
to protect that secret, not expose it.
Is that Robert Queen talking,
or is that Virgil Swann?
- You're sounding more like him every day.
- Yes.
Dr. Swann made the discovery alone,
But that does not give him
the right to keep it to p mself.
Give me the envelope, please.
We promised that we
would meet the traveler
Before we decided to pursue
a way to control him.
Don't talk to me about promises.
You've been working in secret
with dr. Swann, haven't you?
And you, Edward, you and genevieve
gallivanting around the world.
You've been searching
for those magical stones.
Lionel, this is bigger than the Queens
or the teagues or the Luthors!
Long before our families united,
Men died protecting the secret of veritas.
If Edward's ancestors are right,
They've been sacrificing themselves
to prote it for centuries.
If dr. Swan prediction is correct,
The traveler is coming now.
We can't wait.
That envelope and the secret inside it
Will give us ultimate power.
You're afraid.
You don't trust yourself
with that, do you?
There isn't one among us
Who could resist that temptation.
We agreed we would not open that envelope
Unless the traveler proved to be a threat.
That's why Swann and I
are flying to Zurich ...
To make sure that the secret
is kept locked safely away
And ultimate power is left
in the hands of the gods.
Robert...
Find the bank this key belongs to.
Sir, that could take months.
Try 24 hours.
It's in Zurich.
Mr. Luthor, do you have any comment
on the death of Patricia Swann?
Put the camera down. Put it down!
Very Resourceful.
I realize that an appointment
or a press conference would be too
"Conventional"
for you, miss lane, but...
Oh, come on. You wouldn't take an interview
with me if your life depended on it.
So what makes you think
i'll respond to an ambush?
- This is your chance to tell the truth.
- The truth?
Before you're hauled away for murder.
I can't decide. Is it boundless courage you have,
Or is it incorrigible stupidity?
Potato, "po-Tah-To."
You were the last person
to speak with Swann
Before the poor woman ended up
sucking pond water.
All right.
This, uh, clever conversation is now over.
Suit yourself, but i'm not gonna be
the only one asking questions.
According to phone records,
you had five calls in one day
From a woman who was previously
questered overseas.
Just happened to be the day
that she ended up dead.
Business calls evidence of a business
transaction, which it was.
- Oh, I dont doubt that.
- Look.
Every photo ever taken of Patricia Swann
shows her weing this family locket.
Now, not only was this locket missing
when they fished her out of the lake,
But there was a burn,
Right here on her neck,
Where the chain was forcibly removed.
Very sad.
- My heart goes out to her family.
- Mr. Luthor ...
And now if that is all
from the dynamic duo,
Security will be very happy
to help you find your way out.
Easy as pie.
Clark, I know you sent Lana off to Isis
So she wouldn't see your maiden voyage.
When are you gonna stop stalling?
Not helping.
I'm sorry. Yeah, I know. It...
But it's just really easy.
Just up, up, and away.
- I don't have time for this.
- You saw Brainiac fly away.
- How do you plan on catching him?
- It won't matter if we don't find him first.
Instead, we're wasting time
with abilities that I don't have yet.
Fine. You cover the land,
and i'll cover the sky.
I wish it were that easy.
Chloe's been working overtime
trying to help me locate Brainiac.
Then he just shows up
with no warning.
There's got to be some way to track him.
Power.
Everyone needs to be fueled by something.
He's not affected by the sun like we are.
So what does he run on?
Maybe energy.
He's a computer.
Hello, Lana.
Let me go.
Chloe,
Why didn't you tell me
they found her last night?
I... just walked through the door.
Another member of
the veritas clan silenced.
Chloe, do you think Lionel's behind this?
I know he was throwing suspicion onto
Lex when you were captured,
But nothing I dug up reveals any links
Between Lex and the veritas clan
other than his father.
Looks like all the roads lead to Lionel.
What if she died...
Protecting me, Chloe?
Protecting my secret.
Clark, we don't have time
for guilt right now.
Look, I spent the entire morning
Sweet-Talking the centurion
at the department of water and power,
And he finall agreed to
fast-Track my password approval
So that we could scan the power grids
for any unusual surges.
Brazil, Honduras...
Florida.
God, Brainiac really gets around.
Oh, my god.
What is it?
A massive power surge flared up in
Metropolis right near the isis foundation.
- Save it for the police.
- Please, I came to see Lana.
I'd hoped that she could talk
some sense into you,
But we're running out of time, son.
You must listen to me.
You've already destroyed the life of
one son. You don't get a second chance.
The only real son you have
hates you just as much as I do.
That... That doesn't matter, but you've...
You've got to listen to me. Please!
You're right, It doesn't, cause you're just
gonna wash your hands of it, aren't you?
Just like you did when you murdered
dr. Swann and the Queens?
You haven't changed. Patricia told me,
and you killed her for it.
No. Clark, no. I'd never ...
All right. But it's...
It's not important
What you think of me, but I...
There are some things
that you should know.
I have kept your secret hidden
longer than you imagine.
I should have listened to my father.
I was stupid to think you could care
about anyone other than yourself.
You're less human than I am.
Clark, there's... There's! Something I...
I mus... Give you. Here, take this.
- Please!
- There's nothing you have that I want.
- Now, where's Lana?
- I don't know.
The receptionist
Said she had a visitor, and then she left.
A visitor.
Thank god you weren't at isis!
I was afraid Brainiac
had gone there to find you.
Lana, your hand.
No.
So much for team work.
Why'd you disappear on me?
I thought you were gonna check in with me
when you and Chloe found Brainiac.
Clark, what's wrong?
What happened?
It's Brainiac.
He's done something.
It was supposed to be me.
"Deliver Kara.
Daily Planet."
Lana please.
Well, It kind of takes the intrigue
out of breaking and entering.
So, why do you think that Lionel search
his deep, dark, murderous on Lana
He left his office and came
straight here. Just look around.
I am sorry, but this is really
Creepy.
Sexy.
No way.
Who is that?
Patricia Swann's driver/suspected
killer who's vanished.
Right.
And that's significant because...?
"Lana, I'm innocent. You have to
believe me. I need your help. Lionel."
The guy who killed Patricia Swann
wasn't hired by lionel.
He was working for Lex.
They're preparing the jet.
I hope you found the bank.
Sir, we traced the key to the
national depository of Switzerland,
But we hit a roadblock.
When we're this close, Ink it's fair to say
That persuading a glorified teller
should be the least of our worries.
If someone's holding out,
pay them whatever they're asking.
Sir, this bank held off the Third Reich, The Sicilian
mafia, and Al-Qaeda. With all due respect,
- I'm fairly certain they won't bow to you.
- I don't understand.
If they're requiring authorization,
that's not an issue. We have the key.
We have one key. Each safety-Deposit box in the
high-Security vault requires two.
Two?
We've already started trying
to track down the other, but...
We don't have any leads.
Hold on a minute, will you?
The divers... Did they
find anyone who survive?
No, sir. The Queens have
been confirmed dead.
- And their son... Oliver?
- Away at boarding school.
Their key... Do you have the key?
Your helicopter's waiting, sir.
Thank you.
I've got it.
No, well, we ...
We just need dr. Swann's.
No, all right.
Listen to me one more time.
The traveler is useless to us
unless we can control him.
Well the answer to that
Is sitting in a safety-Deposit
box in zurich.
Look, we'll talk later, all right?
Are you ready for an adventure, son?
Where's your tie?
Ah, okay. Here we go.
We are gonna fly in a helicopter
To a friendly little town just...
Just outside the city
Called Smallville.
Okay. Let's go.
I'm not sure we need to look
that far for the key.
Sir?
Like you said...
Most things we're searching
for are closer than we realize.
I can't let you do this.
What happened to Lana...
It's my fault.
Brainiac wants me.
But we don't know what for.
- And I won't lose you and Lana.
- You won't have to.
What did you do to Lana?
A little adjustment
to her central nervous system.
Absolutely irreversible
by any human standards.
Completely reversible by me.
Whatever you want me to do.
Just don't let Lana suffer.
I'm afraid that she is suffering.
There's a part of Lana that is completely
aware of what's happening around her,
But she has no control over her body.
Her motor skills, her speech,
ery breath she takes Is controlled by me.
Leave her out of this.
Did I mention that Lana
is in excruciating pain?
She just can't express it.
But you can end this.
Just come with me.
Kara? Kara, no!
It's a trap!
You can't trust him!
It's the only way to save Lana.
Miss Sullivan. You must talk to Clark.
I need you to talk to Clark.
A little late to mend that fence.
Amazing how a couple of cold-Blooded
murders can come between people.
No, no. I have taken moral responsibility
for every atrocity I committed in the past.
Past?! Try last week! Maybe even today.
Who knows with you?
I did not... Did not kill
Patricia Swann.
After you knocked off her father and the
rest of the veritas coven of yours,
I'm supposed to believe you why?
Because I was given a gift.
I was chosen by Jor-El to serve him ...
To be his vessel, his emissary.
And that changed me.
That made me a different man.
We're not stupid.
You preyed on Clark's inherent need
to find good in all people
And his constant willingness for forgiveness.
But now you have cried wolf
one too many times.
Miss sullivan, please.
I'm begging you to listen.
Clark won't talk to me.
He's turned away from Jor-El,
And now he is vulnerable.
He is in terrible danger.
- If he's in any danger, it's only from you.
- No, I've repented!
That's right. You're
an intensely spiritual man.
You amassed all the power a human could
until you found out about Clark.
Be friending him is the closest thing
you'll ever get to seeing god.
Protecting him is the only way
I found to pay for my sins.
And isn't that what we all want?
To repent and be forgiven.
But none of that matters.
Because what's coming is so terrible.
- Another false warning.
- No!
- You seriously need to come up with a new line.
- No! It...
Hey. How is she?
- Clark, I'm so sorry.
- I really need to find Brainiac.
- Please tell me that you've got a lead.
- I wish I did,
But it's like kara and Brainiac
vanished off the map.
You can see her now.
I'll wait here for you.
It's me... Clark.
Kal-El.
You're too late, Kal-El.
For SeriesSub.com