Previously on smallville...
Chloe, i can't tell you how happy
i am the two of you found each other.
Your wedding day's gonna be
perfect. I'm gonna make sure of it.
I've always felt like there
was this darkness inside me.
Run!
- What's wrong?
- Lex is alive.
Jimmy!
I've forgotten almost everyone.
I'm being taken over by brainiac.
There is some sort of
connection between us,
And i know that you feel it, too.
Since you don't have
a plus-One tonight,
I'd like you to meet one of
my friends. Name's clark kent.
Trust me...  lois and clark
would be great together.
No way! I can't believe
it! Lana, you're back!
It was the hardest decision
i have ever had to make.
If we want to fight
for the greater good,
Maybe we all have to be
a little more like clark.
Chloe deserves a life free
from the burden of my secret.
When you restore her memory, i don't
want her to remember my abilities.
Doomsday is coming.
- It's too late. That thing took chloe.
- Jimmy's in bad shape.
I'm gonna go with him to star city.
Why do these terrible things
keep happening all around us?
Lana!
I don't know what more i can do.
I checked three time zones. No sign
of chloe or the creature that took her.
That thing that did this...
What was it?
Jor-El warned me about
an ultimate destroyer...
From krypton.
It should have gone after me, not chloe.
This was supposed to be the
happiest day of her life.
You should get some rest.
No, i'm...  i'm gonna go
to the isis foundation.
Chloe has files on just about
everything strange and unexplained.
Let me do it, lana.
Clark, i can help.
I know i've only been gone seven months,
But i'm a different person now.
Chloe needs us.
She needs both of us.
I'll call you as soon
as i find anything.
Hey, who are you? What
are you doing here?
I'll take that.
Let's see if he's ticklish.
Have a nice trip home, you hack.
Who are you? What's going on?
Kal-El, it is an absolute
honor and a privilege.
How do you know that name?
We are the legion.
We've come from the 31st century.
Hey, kal, where's your cape?
Cape?
Smallville 811
Synchro : Flolo
Transcript : Yyets.net
For Seriessub.com
That ax could split an atom. You'll
heal but not as fast as you'd expect.
He's gonna be fine, imra.
- We need to go.
- We shouldn't be attracting attention.
It's a little too late for that, isn't
it? You said you're from the 31st century.
- Why should i believe you?
- 'Cause we know everything about you.
You may be known as clark kent now,
but one day you'll be known as sup...
Garth!
It doesn't matter if
you believe us or not.
The less you know, the better.
There's one thing we can tell you.
We're your friends.
We're also leaving... now.
Garth!
No way!
I saw this in the levitz
museum behind visoglass.
- Put that back.
-  Get the magnet out of your ass, rokk.
I mean, this is... this is unreal.
You know the code...
don't touch anything.
Why are you here?
We're here to save you.
And now that you're okay,
we're heading straight back.
Not before you tell me who
that ax-Wielding psycho was.
- It's against legion code.
- I don't care about your code!
And i don't care about your legion!
That's the second attack
i've had in this barn tonight.
My best friend is missing,
and i need to find her.
You know anything, tell me.
The guy with the ax...
He goes by the name "persuader."
He's part of the human
supremacist movement.
A group of xenophobes who'd rather
die than live in peace with aliens.
And they all... pretty much hate you.
They stole one of our legion rings,
And they broke into the time
institute to come after you.
What does a 31st-Century
terrorist want with me?
Kal-El, your... your influence
will reach far beyond earth.
It's because of you that the world learns
to welcome alien immigrants with open arms.
What do you know about aliens?
Kal, i may have the smoldering
good looks of a human,
But i'm actually from a
hunk of mud called winath.
Rokk and imra are from
different planets, too.
We've come together,
Across the universe,
to form the legion...
To help others, as you do.
Without you, none of
that would have happened.
And now it's time for us to say goodbye.
Wait... we're not going anywhere.
This was the phantom zone crystal.
I know my history. This
was supposed to be used
To extract brainiac from
whoever he possessed.
The persuader didn't
come to kill kal-El.
He came to make sure brainiac survives.
Brainiac's gone. He's been destroyed.
No, he hasn't, kal... not yet.
Chloe?
Oh, my god. Are you okay?
I'm just about perfect.
- You appear undamaged.
- Chloe, what happened to you?
Chloe sullivan ceased to exist the
minute she entered this fortress.
I'm a brain interactive construct.
Look at me.
It's me. It's davis.
You're not davis bloome.
You're not even human.
Don't tell me the thought
never crossed your mind.
You were hatched by
kryptonian geneticists.
Your dna was designed to
adapt to any world you inhabit.
Now you no longer need
your camouflage abilities.
Those painful transformations
you've been experiencing...
They're the beginning
of your metamorphosis.
This is insane.
No.
It's... sad, from a human perspective...
Your naive romantic attraction
To the human i chose to inhabit.
Chloe, if you're in there anywhere,
You know that the feelings
that i have for you are real.
Feelings?
That was just a program i
was running to get you to me.
Your journey's just beginning.
Now it's time for you to incubate
In your kryptonian chrysalis.
Once you emerge, there
will be no more pain,
No doubt.
Only absolute rage
and unparalleled power.
Stay the hell away.
But you play a vital
part in my directive.
Once i get everything i need,
You will eradicate the other kryptonian
and then the rest of the planet.
I am not going to hurt anyone.
You have no free will.
12 days in the chrysalis,
And you're destined to
become what you really are.
Doomsday.
I think your timeline's a little off.
Brainiac did infect someone, but
it's already over. He's been defeated.
I'll admit a lot of
history might be inaccurate,
But today's date... it's been
known for over 1,000 years.
Kal, i flunked history,
And even i know that today's
the day you destroyed brainiac.
It's no coincidence the persuader
showed up right when he did.
This girl you're thinking about...
The one that was brutally taken away...
Why do you think she has
something to do with brainiac?
I don't know.
You think she's the host.
If brainiac is still out there, then
i'll find him, and i'll stop him.
The three of you can go home to
the future. Let me handle this.
If brainiac isn't stopped today,
We won't have a future to go home to.
Kal, the problem is,
You were supposed to defeat
brainiac using this shield.
Now that it's been smashed...
The crystal can't be
the only way to stop him.
It's the only way to destroy him
Without killing the
human host in the process.
Kal, i'm sorry, but if
you know who the host is,
You need to take their life.
There's no other choice.
Who's chloe sullivan?
Why did you leave?
I need to do this my own way... alone.
- No one's killing anybody.
- What's with the ground transpo?
We should be having this
conversation up in the sky.
I can't fly.
You can't fly?
Rokk, what's up with that?
He obviously hasn't learned yet, garth.
- Where were you running to, kal?
- North, to see jor-El.
Of course... the fortress.
I think he can help.
You're positive chloe
sullivan is brainiac's host?
No, but she was attacked
last year by brainiac.
Her i.Q. Skyrocketed. Her
memories were being erased.
But it stopped. She was cured.
Kal-El, i have to tell you...
We've heard of lois lane...
Lana lang... even jimmy olsen...
But we've never heard a thing
about any chloe sullivan.
Then you don't know me
as well as you think.
He name was probably just
lost in the annals of history.
What she's trying to say
is that chloe sullivan
Probably isn't in the
history books because...
She didn't survive.
Chloe sullivan doesn't die. You hear me?
Kal.
Lightning lad.
You might want to take your a.C. Foot
Out of your d.C. Mouth
before you short yourself out.
Grife, rokk. I thought kal-El was known
For doing whatever it
took to save the world.
- Are you sure we got the right guy?
- It's him.
I don't know... no glasses,
no tights, no flights?
So far, he's nothing
like the man of steel.
I'm sorry, lana.
I didn't mean to scare you.
But i desperately need your help.
How do you know who i am?
I'm from the future.
Look...
I understand that this
feels real for you.
But we can get you some help.
You're looking for chloe sullivan.
You're worried about her.
What do you know about chloe?
That she's changed.
She's been taken over by brainiac.
We'll find chloe, and we'll
figure out a way to stop him.
The only way to stop brainiac
now is to kill his host.
I need you to convince clark to do that.
That's why i came to you.
He won't listen to us.
I'd never ask clark to kill anyone.
Do you understand?
Ever since i was little,
i've read stories about you...
About the hardships you've overcome
And the incredible
things you'll go on to do.
You're part of the reason kal-El
becomes the hero we look up to.
Lana...
If brainiac survives...
Billions will die.
I came to you because you understand
sacrifice more than anyone.
You've sacrificed so much for clark.
Sacrificing my friend's
life isn't an option.
You still haven't told him
the reasons why you disappeared
And what you plan on doing next.
You're reading my thoughts.
If i know you...
You'll eventually realize
that taking chloe's life
Is the only way to stop brainiac.
Cos, we should be trying to
catch up to kal-El right now.
Right now, i want to find out
more about this chloe sullivan
So we can track her down.
She has a lot of information
about superhumans.
Something called the isis foundation.
- The isis foundation?
- Yeah.
Lana lang founded that organization
To help people embrace their powers.
If chloe sullivan was
involved with them,
Maybe she was helping kal-El
to embrace his abilities.
Or maybe kal-El wanted chloe
to go under a different name
When he started flying...
you know, to protect her.
Maybe chloe's death is what inspired
him to take flight in the first place.
Jor-El!!
Your father is gone.
And all the knowledge this fortress
ever held finally belongs to me.
Leave chloe alone.
You have what you want.
My hunger's never satisfied.
Knowledge is what fuels me.
And as savage as human beings are,
Their collective knowledge
is exceptionally rich.
Nothing about you is human.
And never will be.
After i've drained this planet
of all the human information,
Doomsday will annihilate what's left.
Doomsday.
It's a simple plan, actually.
Absorb and destroy.
You brought that thing here.
Go on.
Kill me.
I knew you'd never harm
me in this human's skin.
Why do you think i chose her?
Great. The air here's worse
than the sulfur pit on tharr.
And they won't be replacing
carbon fuels for another 20 years.
These people... we need to protect them.
Without the humans and
their incredible spirit,
Kal-El would have never
become the hero he was.
The world we know would never exist.
Rokk, think about it...
everything we know about kal-El...
It's all through data
files and holovids.
It's so far in the past.
Maybe the person we've
always been looking up to
Is more legend than legion.
Look, he might not be everything
we thought he would be,
But he is no fraud.
Rokk, we have to stop brainiac...
With or without kal-El.
We're gonna have to kill
chloe sullivan ourselves.
Lana. That creature's
the least of our worries.
Brainiac is behind everything.
I know. And now he's taken over chloe.
I had a visitor. She seemed
to know a lot about all of us.
Imra?
I'm searching the global power grid
for power surges anywhere in the world.
Hopefully, that will
lead us to brainiac.
Clark...
That girl said the only
way to stop brainiac
Is to kill his host.
What if she's right?
Lana, i have always put my
loved ones before everything.
But this time, i'm
putting chloe's well-Being
Before the lives of billions of people.
I may have been gone awhile,
But the clark i know
would never doubt himself.
Lana... he would never waver.
He would insist that he
could save chloe's life
And the rest of the world.
Hey, matt, what's
going on? Are you okay?
A power surge.
It's showing a voltage spike
somewhere in downtown metropolis.
Can you pinpoint the address?
Looks like it's coming
from the daily planet.
Makes sense... it is
the hub of information.
Lana.
Lana, can you hear me?
Nice try, telepath.
Your sadism's historic
where i come from.
But so is your defeat.
History's about to get a rewrite.
- Nice sync-Up.
- For once.
Electromagnetism. That
pulse can crash any computer.
Now we need to pull
the plug. You okay, im?
I'm fine, aside from
a splitting headache.
I'm picking up
low-Level brain activity.
We don't have much time.
- Neither does the rest of the world.
- What's brainiac doing?
Using human brain-Wave entrainment.
He's downloading every last byte of
their knowledge, one mind at a time.
- I'll do it.
- No.
When i joined the legion, i pledged
an oath to do whatever it took.
And i'm gonna honor that...
For once.
It's okay, garth.
Give me the knife.
What are you doing?
We powered him down with
an electromagnetic pulse,
But he will be back online within
minutes. So we need to don't touch her.
Kal, whoever your friend
was, she's not there anymore.
- Did you power them down, too?
- No, brainiac can take credit for that.
Kal-El, we need to shut brainiac down,
- And for that, the host has to die.
- Does your legion have any principles?
You speak of a code,
But if it had anything to do with me,
Rule number one would
be do not kill... ever!
- Kal-El...
- If you ever believed in me...
And even if you don't now... help me.
There's a human being inside there.
We need to help her.
And together, i think we can.
Rokk...
Kal's right.
Chloe's there.
I can hear her.
What are we doing here?
We're running out of time.
Listen, if brainiac reboots,
I don't want him near
any computer networks.
- What do you want us to do?
- Work together... all of us.
I want to try to connect with chloe.
Imra, can you do that?
I'll try.
Between the two of you, i think
we can neutralize brainiac.
An electromagnetic
blast only lasts so long.
But he's a computer.
Whatever microscopic parts he's made
out of, they're probably metal, right?
I've never focused my
powers like this before,
But i can try to magnetically
extract the nanites.
I could short-Circuit
him with a static attack.
Get ready for a techno-Exorcism.
I've got her. Kal?
She's asking for you.
Chloe?
Chloe, i'm here.
Chloe, we're gonna try to get rid
of brainiac, okay? Just hang on.
Brainiac's fighting.
He's coming back online.
Rokk, now!
Come on, chloe. Hang in there.
Chloe?
Imra, can you hear anything?
- Chloe.
- I'm getting something.
Chloe. Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I definitely feel a whole lot dumber.
It's nice to see the
kinder, gentler chloe.
nothing like having a binary bad
guy cleansed from your system
to put a spring back in your step.
But i'll feel even better once
i get to star city to see my husband.
I'm gonna relieve lois
of her nurse's duties.
It was nice of lois
to take care of jimmy.
Though, i think he'd rather have
his temperature taken by you.
Yeah. I'm just glad he's
okay. From what i hear,
He was lucky to make it
past that creature alive.
Whoever that destroyer was,
i haven't seen a sign of him since.
He was definitely linked
to brainiac, though.
Well, hopefully, he was powered
down along with brainiac.
So, how's your memory?
It's fine.
Up until "here comes the bride."
Then it's all a bit of a blur.
You don't remember
anything unusual about me?
Are we talking about your secret?
Clark, what in the world
would make me forget that?
Chloe, you've been through a lot lately.
It would take a lot more than brainiac
To wipe that from my memory.
Thanks for not giving up on me.
I'd never give up on
you, chloe. You know that.
I just hope that if it turned out
that there was no other choice,
You would choose to do the right thing.
What choice would that be?
To do what's best for the world...
And not for me.
Know that i'd understand.
Well, as long as i'm around,
that's never gonna happen.
Oh, hi.
I was looking for clark.
The boys are out fixing the barn.
Thanks.
Imra, i understand
that you were only doing
What you thought was best.
We were willing to
take the easy way out.
But kal-El... he never gave up.
You know, it's...
It's true what history says about him.
He really does bring
out the best in people.
You're very lucky.
I probably shouldn't
be asking this, but...
You're curious about you and clark.
I couldn't help but wonder about us,
About where we go from here.
Well, that's for you two
to discover yourselves.
But i will tell you this, lana...
You're remembered for a lot more
Than just your
relationship with kal-El.
You have a destiny all your own.
But don't worry.
Your secret's safe with me.
Holy sprock!
I've read about this.
You don't read. I told you about that.
It's one of the artifacts
they could never find...
The first baseball you ever hit.
It went clear across smallville.
You're right. My dad spent
hours walking the fields.
He finally found it on
the other side of town.
Hey, do you think i could
keep this? Like, as a souvenir?
- Sure.
- Could you sign it?
- Garth, you're acting like a sub.
- What? It's for my sister.
Thanks.
Hey, guys.
Looks brand-New.
I guess it's time to go home.
You sure you want to take that with you?
I'm sure we'll be able to reprogram
What's left of brainiac
into something useful.
Let's hope brainiac 5 is
a little more friendly.
I'm sorry i doubted you, kal.
You did stop brainiac,
and without taking a life.
There's always a way, rokk. If
it ever seems like there isn't,
Just remember what we
accomplished here today.
Preserve life at all costs.
That will be the number-One
rule in legion code from now on.
It truly was an honor.
And if you ever want to
meet the rest of the legion,
Just put this ring on.
I've reprogrammed it
for time travel only.
No flights. Not yet.
So, looks like you're gonna have to
learn to fly without training wheels.
Just focus on 3009. We'll
be there to greet you.
Thanks.
But i think i'll stick closer
to my time zone for a while.
We do hope we see you again.
Kal...
Be careful in the days ahead.
Long live the legion.
I didn't think you
were much for jewelry.
I'm not.
It's a going-Away gift.
It's strange to meet people who
know exactly where you're going,
Exactly when you're gonna get there.
Well, they don't know everything.
I mean, if they did, chloe
wouldn't be alive right now.
And, unfortunately, they
didn't have what i had...
Human parents who taught me more
than just how to use my abilities.
They have a different role model.
With everything i've learned,
Everything i've been through,
Apparently, i'm just getting started.
According to the legion,
I will accomplish things so legendary,
I'll be known throughout the galaxy.
And you're not sure that you'll
be able to live up to that.
Clark...
There is no doubt in
my mind that you will.
Just do it on your
schedule... not theirs.
Well, did they happen to mention
anything about your place in history?
A little.
But the way i see it,
it doesn't really matter.
Our destiny is not written
in some book in the future.
We write it ourselves... every day.
And the question is...
what do we write next?
For Seriessub.com