Previously on Smallville...
When you saw my fate, what did you see?
You will lead this generation,
a silver age of heroism.
I started the training
Jor-El always planned for me.
- Do you believe in fate?
- Only the kind you make happen.
Blue Kryptonite takes
away my abilities, too.
- No strings, no ribbons.
- It's just a gift.
- I've been talking to The Blur.
- The question is am i enough?
You can't protect us
if we know who you are.
Then you shall be the Savior of Kandor.
The last thing we remember is
our blood being taken in Kandor.
How did we get here?
- I'll be in touch.
- There are aliens here on our planet.
You get to write a
story with Perry White.
You lied about having
powers. How'd you get them?
From your blood.
The time has come to
share in your birthright.
Zod's been looking for something that wields
great power. Who knows what he will do?
The humans killed the
mother of my unborn child.
The last time that I saw
Faora, she was with Zod.
- Why should they believe you?
- The Book of Rau isn't here.
You say you're saving the planet
but you only care about yourself.
The Book of Rau can
transport the Kandorians
to another plane of
existence, including you.
- I need your help.
- Anything.
I finished tracing our
rogue Blur. It was Zod.
If anyone calls claiming to
be me, don't believe them.
Kneel before Zod.
Soon, the world will need
all the help it can get.
Now the season finale of "Smallville."
If you remember,
I'm the one who said 2012 would be
just another y2k scare and I was right.
Not to fear, White. If there's
a scandal in the Pentagon,
yours truly will be the one to find it.
Seven calls from the State Department
confirmation on your flight to Jordan,
fruit basket from the Dalai
Lama and Clark's at the deli.
He wants to know if you
want pastrami or roast beef.
Clark would forget his head if
it wasn't attached with a necktie.
There's something else.
Luthor is making a
play for the oval office
and White has me playing dodge ball
with armchair quarterbacks
at the Pentagon?!
I can't believe it!
News helicopter lost power!
It's heading straight
for The Daily Planet!
You had better be getting
every pixel of this.
Look, up in the sky!
Your fate is utterly binding.
You will lead this generation
as hawkman once led ours.
Smallville 9x21
- Salvation
Synchro : Flolo
For Seriessub.com/soustitre.eu
I thought you said
we'd never talk again.
I'm glad you broke radio
silence, but why now?
How can you be The Blur?
That alien snatcher, Chisholm, shot you.
I saw the wound.
My powers cured me.
Clark Kent's mild-mannered FBI friend
is the guy who's always saving my butt?
You were willing to risk
your life to save me.
You are my hero.
My hero told me not to trust
anyone that said he was The Blur.
I know I did.
But I had no one else to
turn to. Lois, please...
I need your help again.
Someone is becoming dangerously close
to discovering who I am, if they do,
they could destroy
everything I've worked for.
It's Clark Kent.
I'm sorry. I think all that
superspeeding has crisscrossed your wires,
because Clark would never harm anyone.
I know you don't want to
see it, Lois, but it's true.
It's why he told you
to stay away from me.
It's why he took away
the charm I gave you.
He knows what we mean to each other.
I will admit that Clark's played
the jealousy card once or twice.
But you're wrong about him.
You don't have to take my word for it.
You are the best
investigator I've known.
Now, you dig a little deeper...
but I guarantee you'll find that
Clark Kent is not who he says he is.
Even though Watchtower's
back in the game,
I'm still coming up empty-handed
on the Kandorian front.
It's like they vanished into thin air.
That might have something to do
with the fact that they can fly.
Sarcasm noted.
How do we know these people
aren't half a galaxy away already?
Zod doesn't want to play Thunderdome
on a planet that is desolate.
He needs people to rule over.
I have a feeling that is
coming soon to a planet near us.
I'm heading back to Watchtower.
If a war breaks out, i want
to be in the foxhole with you.
Because...
Right, because we need to
protect Watchtower's database.
Yeah, the database is, is important.
Over and out.
Everyone's mobilizing.
They're all out on the field...
Kryptonite weapons? That's
only gonna stall them.
We're no match for the Kandorians,
even when we work together.
It's only a matter of time
before Zod commands his soldiers
- to bring the world to its knees.
- Then let's move on to plan "A."
I assume you brought the
infamous secret weapon.
I still don't understand
how the Red Queen of the Kent
farm knew about the Book of Rau.
My mom inherited the Kryptonian
library when Lionel died.
It's no surprise that Zod would lie.
The Book of Rau is not a bible.
It was created by Jor-El to send
the Kandorians to another world.
A world they could call their own.
Let's fire up this
intergalactic subway token
and send our visitors on
a fast train to Nirvana.
I can't.
Once it's activated, it sends
all Kryptonians to the new world.
Including you.
I know my destiny, and it's here.
I've seen it. Dr. Fate has seen it, too.
And Jor-El has sent me
on trials to prove it.
I finally know who I am
and what I'm meant to do here
on earth. I'm not leaving.
No one wants to see you reach
your true potential more than I do.
I've been with you through every
bump along this insane ride.
But what if every trial
has just been a preparation for
you to make the ultimate sacrifice?
Then why would my father have
gone silent in the fortress?
If this was a trial, my father would never
skip on any chance to give me a lecture.
Because this isn't a trial.
And maybe your father disappeared on you
because he knew you needed to
make this last mile on your own.
Then it's up to me
and I think there's
another way to save Zod.
Jor-El did not tell you to
stay here and be our guardian.
Are you saying it's selfish
for me to try to save people?
You think I want you to go?
I can't imagine being in
this world without you.
You've inspired an entire team of
heroes who will be here to protect us.
And maybe your true purpose
is to lead your own people.
You've refused to speak to me, Jor-El.
Now I'll make sure you'll
never speak to your son again...
and share the secrets of Rau with him.
You're not welcome here.
I've been playing hide-and-seek with
this ice castle for over two years.
So the least you can do is just
give me a minute to take it all in.
- It's breathtaking.
- How did you get here?
I flew.
Icarus flew to where he didn't belong.
And he fell to his
death from the heavens.
Icarus was on an ego trip.
But I have a higher calling.
I was made to see the error of my ways.
I'm here...
to redeem myself.
It's too late.
My people discovered
you had the Book of Rau
and hid it from me.
I won't forgive that deception.
It's not your forgiveness
that I'm looking for.
I've seen the future.
And you enslave this planet...
and destroy anyone
that ever opposed you!
Including Clark.
And the Red Queen made me realize.
I won't let you kill him.
You touched the sun when
you freed me from the orb.
You're about to learn what
it feels like to get burned.
I know that you told me to save Zod...
but I won't.
Not if it means leaving
everyone I promised to protect.
Now, my destiny is here on Earth.
And if everything that
you've trained me for
was for another purpose,
then it was a waste,
because I'm staying.
There must be some
other way to stop Zod.
Your father can't help you anymore.
I made sure of that.
My people are overtaking this planet,
and you can't stop me.
You want war, but it
doesn't have to be like this.
Have you taken a look around
you? It's always like this!
Might makes right!
Only the strong survive!
Have you learned nothing from the
natural world in which you love so much?
What I've learned is that no matter how
much someone has hurt you or betrayed you
or how much it seems
that someone is evil,
at their core, everyone is worth saving.
What exactly do you think
you're saving me from?
From making another mistake like Faora.
Do you really think there's
redemption for what I did?
- It's never too late.
- How would you know?
Because I killed my own father.
My Earth father warned
me not to play God...
not to reach for power that's not mine.
But I tempted fate, and
because of that, he died.
You have to forgive yourself.
My entire team is equipped
with Kryptonite weapons.
Hardly a match for my battalion.
Too many people will die.
You need to end this now.
You can't win.
I know my destiny.
And I know mine.
You never give up, do you, Perry?
I'm so sorry...
I tracked... Corben to
locate your fortress.
And I did it only to save you from Zod.
I have the Book of Rau, Tess.
But even if I wanted to use it, I can't,
because Zod destroyed the
console in the fortress.
You don't need the fort-tress.
When the Kandorians...
were building the Rau Tower...
they put together these
crystals as an energy source
when they were trying
to turn the sun red.
And I think these crystals will also...
power the Book of Rau.
I aready destroyed the tower.
I pulled the console from the rubble...
and moved it...
to your crow's nest a-above the city.
This is my last chance
to atone for my sins.
You...
are the only one that can save us.
And you've run out of time.
The war has already begun.
I think we have a little bit more
time before the U.N. gets involved.
All our Queen Industry sources
say that our military friends
believe this is just some hoax.
Any new activity?
This is Stargirl online
from the nation's capital.
No sign of the Kandorians
after te attack.
Black Canary here.
Story's the same in Athens.
All I found in Giza are mummies.
We need to flush these aliens out.
I've been around long enough
to know the best way to win
a war is to strike first.
No, that's the best way to win
a bowling tournament, Tweety.
We're dealing with
superpowered soldiers here.
Just as expected, Mr.
Green jeans has gone yellow.
The Kandorians are Clark's people.
So we're not gonna
take any sort of action
- until he's with us.
- Watchtower's right.
I agree with Hawkman. We wait too
long, they'll have the advantage.
- We hold off until Kal- El has a chance
to. - how long we gonna wait, Martian.
- long enough from them to wipe us out?
- We wait, the Kandorians win.
Zod's symbols say one
thing, he wants a fight.
I say we move now and cause some pain.
At what cost?
Your abilities allow
you to come back, Carter.
After you die but what about
the others on both sides?
So you want us to play nice?
The Kandorians have
been led astray by Zod.
I don't want to see them die
any more than I want
to lose any one of you.
I will use the Book of Rau...
to send them all away.
I've made my decision.
Once I lead my people to another
world, I'll never be able to come back.
- You need to think about this.
- What about your life here?
- There's got to be another way.
- With us by your side,
you don't have to do this alone.
This is the only peaceful
way to eliminate the threat.
Without a war, a war
that no one will win...
once the Kandorians are gone there
will be other threats to mankind.
The world will need you.
You'll have to work together to become
the team that you were meant to be.
I once believed that my
destiny was here on earth,
but now you need to
accept that destiny for me.
Clark's right.
We'll protect the world... As one.
It has been my honor to serve
alongside each and everyone one of you.
The honor was ours, Kal-El.
I'm proud of you.
You got to let her go, Clark.
She's trying to be strong, you know?
When your oldest friend leaves forever,
there's really no way to say goodbye.
That said, I think we both know there're
someone else you need to see one last time.
Considering everything Lois
and I have been through,
I don't think that's such a good idea.
You owe her the truth.
I want to open up to
her more than anything.
But why tell Lois who I really
am, only to rip it away from her?
Wouldn't that hurt her more?
I wouldn't do that to her.
That doesn't mean you
can't at least say goodbye.
General.
Have you retrieved the Book of Rau?
Sir, if Kal-El still holds it,
- you said he'd use it to kill us all.
- Do not question my resolve.
I will not fail.
I will destroy the Book of Rau. Do
you not have a mission to complete?
Kal-El's comrades have been lured
to your crests, just as you ordered.
So they have to have been
dispersed around the world,
and Kal-El is alone in Metropolis.
Our soldiers have cut
off their communications.
All their satellites
have been destroyed.
Then by dawn, we'll
have the Book of Rau.
And this planet will be ours.
We lost all satellite
communication. I can't reach anybody.
It's like everyone I sent
out there is a sitting duck
and Zod's about to call
a start to hunting season.
Take a breath. You've stared
down the barrel of a gun before.
We're dealing with like 100 Clarks here. I
don't know if I can dodge this speeding bullet.
You're not in it alone. We're
a team, right? You got me?
Trust me.
Thank you.
But I don't think talking me off a ledge
is gonna help us solve
our technical difficulties.
Okay, then maybe this will.
When Tess broke into our
little clubhouse here,
I had Queen Industries launch an
orbiter dedicated to Watchtower.
Wait a minute.
We have our own satellite?
Yeah. Why didn't you
tell me this before?
It was sort of a gift.
I guess giving you a sweater for your
birthday Is sort of out of the question now.
The satellite's up and running,
but the transponders haven't
been initiated for downlink yet.
I'm gonna need to flip
a couple of switches
at the earth station in order
to be able to spy from the sky.
Then we should just stay in
touch the old-fashioned way.
I mean...
If Zod has been trying to
destroy satellites from space,
he's definitely not gonna be happy that
you're putting another satellite online.
Do me a favor, okay?
Just keep a low profile.
I'm wearing green leather,
so I'll do my best.
How could a guy who kept a journal
in High School ever hurt anyone?
I've been looking all over for you.
Funny. Me too.
I have something I need to tell
you. And if I don't tell you now...
I never will. I know that things
have been rocky between us, but...
I'm listening.
My whole life has been full of
relationships that have ended too soon.
And then when I went
away last fall, I...
Lois, I felt so lost.
When I came back to the bullpen...
you were there waiting for me.
You jumped out of your seat,
you threw your arms around me
and the way that your eyes
sparkled when you smiled, I just...
I knew.
I just knew that you were the
one that I've always needed.
And I needed you to know that.
What is it?
He's offered me a job at
the foreign desk in Kenya.
That's great. Congratulations.
I'm not sure I'm going.
Lois, your...
your career is so important to
you, what would make you stay?
For you.
I would stay for you.
Clark, as important as
my career is to me...
you are more important.
I would give up Africa...
to be with you.
But only if we stop keeping
secrets from each other.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, you do, Clark.
Come on.
I need you to be honest with me.
Lois, there's nothing to tell you.
I think you leaving
Metropolis is the best thing...
for you right now.
Just now that wherever you
are, I'll be watching over you.
I'll be thinking of you.
I'm sorry.
I should go.
Doctor!
- Her blood pressure's dropping.
- Oxygen.
Hurry up. We're losing her.
- 10 mil epi...
- charge to 200!
- Charging.
- Clear!
- No pulse.
- Charge to 250.
Clear!
No response.
Let's call it.
Time of death... 3:33 P.M.
Call the morgue. Have them send
somebody up to collect the body.
- Houston, we got a problem.
- Are you at the satellite station yet?
Yeah, I'm way ahead of
you, but I'm a little lost.
I need you to be my own personal
mapquest if you don't mind.
- All right, what's your 20?
- I'm inside the air ducts right now.
Access to the main grid is
through one of the routing panels.
Mole man, just think happy
thoughts and keep on tunneling.
Let me know when you've reached the "t."
I hate small spaces.
Completed the first
level. I'm at the "t."
Now, halfway through the second tunnel,
on your left-hand side, you're
gonna find three panels. The one with
JJ-910-60
is...
the one in the middle, yeah, I got it.
You got to admit, I know how
to treat a girl on date night.
Next week, do you think maybe we could
grab some thai food and catch a movie?
That sounds like a good plan,
but for tonight, you're gonna have
to settle for stream satellite video.
The link is up!
Why don't you make your way home? I'm
gonna see if I can access the building
schematics and find you a
less cramped return trip.
The station's motion
sensors have picked you up.
No. You've got visitors.
There's a whole swarm of them,
and they're closing in on you fast.
You need to get out of there now.
If they find the signal,
they'll trace me back to you!
- I got to go!
- No, Ollie, no!
I love you!
Chloe, they're not Kandorian!
I knew i could count on you.
I still can't believe you
were right about Clark.
Just when it seems that
you're out of my life for good,
you turn out to be the one
person I can believe in.
My only regret is I
can see your heartbreak.
It's not broken.
It's shattered.
I know how hard it is to
discover the person you love...
is not what you think they were.
I will never deceive you
like Clark did... ever.
Now I need the Book of Rau.
I can't.
I hid it.
I was worried that
Clark would follow me.
Where is it?
I hid it where I confessed to you
that you were the most
important person in my life.
This is not a game.
You're not really him.
I should've known better than to
deceive The Blur's most devoted follower.
- Just who the hell are you?
- Unlike The Blur,
I'm someone who doesn't
care whether you live or die.
Can you ever forgive me
for thinking he was you?
Please say something.
Anything.
You can't stop me. We're
leaving this planet.
I'm not going anywhere.
And neither are they.
Having others finish a
fight that you started
only proves what a coward you are.
My soldiers know I have never
wavered in the face of death.
All you've ever done
is hide in the shadows.
You've hidden, too...
the truth from them.
The Book of Rau will not destroy us!
It will lead us to a better place...
another planet where
we can live in peace,
where we an build a new home.
Krypton will live again.
This is just another one of his deceits.
We all know where his allegiance lies.
What about your deceptions?
If they knew the truth,
they'd never follow you.
My men willingly follow me.
And what about Faora? All
she wanted was to leave you.
- That is a lie!
- And she paid for it with her life.
Faora never should've trusted you.
But she wasn't the only one
who paid the price, was she?
Faora was a traitor.
Do you think I wanted
to kill my own child?
Your sister was a traitor.
She would've betrayed us al.
Wait!
We will deal with him
once we're on our own soil.
Kal-El, take us home.
Blue Kryptonite.
I told you. I'm not going anywhere.
You knew the blue Kryptonite would
prevent you from ascending like the others!
Better to rule in hell
than to serve in heaven.
Seeing as you love the humans so
much, let's see if you fight like one!
Unlike you, I will lead from
a throne, not from the shadows.
Every human, including the woman
you love, will kneel before Zod!
You already destroyed my first
home. I won't let you take this one.
Synchro: Flolo
Seriessub/soustitre. eu