- Please don't send me away, father.
- This is for the best.
Until this war is over,
you'll be safer on Earth.
The journey takes three years!
It's the only way. The council
destroyed all the remaining portals...
so general Zod and his men
couldn't escape.
What if I never see you again?
I'm your father, Kara.
Trust my wisdom.
Everything and everyone
that I love is here on Krypton.
This crystal is your way back to us.
As long as you have it, the world
you know and love will be safe.
Why can't you come with me?
I'm needed here to protect Kandor.
You must protect the crystal.
It contains instructions for what you must do
when you rescue your cousin Kal-El.
I don't want to go.
Remember, Kara, a true Kryptonian
embraces their destiny no matter what.
I love you.
You must go now.
Go.
I love you, Kara.
"Somebody save me"
"Let your warm hands
break right through me"
"Somebody save me"
"I don't care how you do it"
"Just save me, save me"
"Come on"
"I've been waiting for you"
"I've made this whole world shine for you"
"Just save me, save me"
"Come on"
SMALLVILLE 7x06 "LARA"
Subtitles subspace
Support for the meteor-infected.
This is what was so urgent.
Right now, my worries should be
the least of your worries, Clark.
The FAA halted all air traffic
over Washington late last night.
Some commercial airline pilot
reported a near miss...
with an object that shot
into the sky in a red-blue blur.
No.
Yeah, they think it may have
been a ground-to-air missile,
but if y ask me,
I think we just found -
Kara.
Chloe, this is all my fault.
Clark, you're not the one who
played chicken with an airplane.
Besides, she's not your responsibility.
You're her cousin, not her father.
I pushed her away, Chloe.
I didn't trust her.
And now she's alone and angry.
I have to find her and bring her back
before she hurts someone.
Or uncorks the Kent family secret.
I mean, clearly, Kara
does not fly below the radar.
Hey, Clark. Did you hear from Kara?
And is she okay?
You guys look worried.
What's going on?
Apparently, Kara decided
to go to Washington, D.C.,
alone, and not tell anyone.
Maybe she's doing the tourist thing.
Postcards are probably already in the mail.
You know something, don't you?
Jimmy she's my cousin.
She's my family. If you know
anything, you need to tell me.
Kara asked to see a video that Lois took of
some so-called spaceship out in Granville.
The recording was ruined, but I managed
to get a partial image of equipment that...
pointed to the government.
And you didn't tell us this because...?
Because Kara asked me to keep it a secret.
She trusted me.
I'm sorry, C. K.
She said it was a hobby.
I had no idea that she'd follow
the lead all the way to Capitol Hill.
Thanks, Jimmy.
Chloe, if he's right,
the government might have Kara's crystal.
That's her last tie to Krypton.
She'll do anything to get it back.
Lionel...
- Welcome back.
- Clark. Oh.
I'm glad you're okay.
Yes, well...
In the darkest hour,
the soul is replenished...
and given strength
to continue and endure.
Luthors are survivors, Clark.
I hear that a new member of the
Kent family has turned up in Smallville.
- My cousin Kara.
- Kara.
You haven't mentioned her
before, have you?
Which side of the family?
- My father's side.
- Oh.
Which father?
My adoptive father.
Look, the reason I'm here...
I came across an underground
government lab.
It's located beneath a silo in Granville.
You have a lot of contacts
in Washington.
I thought maybe you could
tell me something about it.
What were you doing
in a government lab, Clark?
Researching a story for a friend.
I believe that lab in Granville belongs
to the Department of Domestic Security.
Tell your friend that -
Tell her it's not a front-page story.
Domestic security?
I thought they dealt with terrorism.
Among other things.
You know, Washington has had a wary eye
on the heavens for decades, Clark,
watching for any threat
from beyond the stars.
I've heard they call
that program Starhawk.
They came to Smallville right
after the second meteor shower.
I've done everything I could to
divert their attention away from you.
Why didn't you say anything to me?
Your life is complicated enough.
I understood they were
about to leave Smallville.
They'd found no conclusive
evidence of an alien threat.
Do you think that something they discovered,
something in that lab, changed their minds?
Tell me everything you know
about Starhawk.
Initiating LIVS.
Microscopic analysis almost complete.
The LIVS shows crossed pieces...
Composition -
Beryllium...
aluminum silicate with fluorine...
7% material unknown.
Lock it down.
Give me a full report
as soon as possible.
Agent Carter, Mr. Luthor
has entered the building.
Quite the brain trust
you have here, agent carter.
This is a restricted facility.
You never told me you stole
something from that spacecraft.
Our work is classified -
For reasons of national
security, Mr. Luthor.
And you've obviously made
an effort to see it remains secure.
However, the term "classified"...
has never prevented me
from getting what I want.
That's right, you've got this...
angelic, blond saint watching over you.
In the halls of power,
you don't amount to much, agent.
It's only a matter of time before
I find out what it is you're hiding.
Reinitiating sequence.
Yes sir, unlocking containment field.
Reinitiating LIBS.
Laser and X-Ray photo-electro-
spectrographic analysis.
Starting external scan.
So, they put it to a vote.
You know, the redhead from Langley.
I'd rather be out in the field
chasing UFOS than stuck in a lab.
...buttons out of samples.
Half the stuff's hazardous.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I've been working so hard,
I haven't been able to get a...
date.
Nice choker.
You, uh, work for Domestic Security?
I know I've had a few,
but am I really that obvious?
You know what's sexy?
The thought of a government agent
keeping me safe.
I'm not really an agent.
Don't tell me you're just other pencil pusher
from the home office across the street.
No, I head up a team
of lab technicians outside the city.
But go out in the field a lot.
Good.
I was hoping you were hands-on.
Ever investigate anything -
I don't know - Extraterrestrial?
- Excuse me?
- You know,
UFOS, aliens, galaxies far, far away?
I - I can't really be talking
about what I do.
Life from other planets -
That's hot.
I would have loved
to have chatted about it.
Yeah.
Wait.
So, where did you find the ship?
Um, Kansas -
out in the boondocks somewhere.
I can't believe that you work
with real flying saucers.
It's such a turn-on.
What do you say...
we get out of here?
In these spaceships,
ever find anything in them?
We can talk more at my apartment.
It's not too far away.
Oh, come on,
secret-agent man,
tell me what was in that ship,
and I'll go wherever you want.
Oh, it's just some weird crystal.
We're studying it at the lab.
Seriously, do you really think that
I can wait till we get to your place?
Well...
Why don't we get
a bit more comfortable?
Hey, where did you...?
Can I help you?
- Yeah, I was hoping I could get a...
- Chloe!
Lana?
What are you doing here?
I stumbled across
the Isis foundation website...
and saw they were reaching out
to meteor victims.
I - I wanted to see
if I could get an interview.
Do you work here?
You could say that.
I actual kind of am the foundation.
When did you become such a champion
for the meteor challenged?
Lex ruined lives with 33.1-
Not just his victims,
but their families and friends.
I'm using the divorce settlement
to fight back.
Lana, this is a little more impressive
than just writing a check.
I mean, this is a major operation.
Right now, it's just me in an office. But
eventually, I'd like to open a free clinic,
start support groups,
set up a crisis hotline.
I'm so proud of you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't want anyone to know until I've had
the chance to build this into something real.
You're on the web.
You're already out there.
I launched the site so that people
that needed help could find me.
Grassroots is really
all I want right now.
Chloe...
do me a favor
and don't tell Clark, okay?
I thought you two were all about
full disclosure now.
Well, you know how he is. He's gonna
think that the work's too dangerous,
and he's gonna try
and talk me out of it.
Lana, I've interviewed enough people
to know when someone's bending the truth.
And as much as I love
what you're doing,
I'm sensing a right angle
in here somewhere.
That right angle is your imagination.
Please, Chloe,
don't tell Clark anything.
This conversation
is officially off the record.
Thank you.
- Hey!
- Give me back my wallet.
I will when you tell me the real
location of the crystal.
- Who are you?
- It wasn't in the lab.
- Where is it?!
- It's there! We never move it!
Let him go, Kara.
Give him his wallet back.
- I've been looking all over for you.
- Congratulations, you found me.
Is this the part where you
give me a stern talking to?
You're looking for the crystal,
aren't you?
That's my business, not yours.
You nearly took out an airplane, Kara.
Do you have any idea how many
people you could have killed?
My mind kind of wandered.
If you continue this way,
it's only a matter of time
before you get hurt or found out.
Why do you care?
You're my cousin, Kara.
I care about you.
Well, family believes in one another.
And you betrayed me.
You'd rather
talk to anyone else but me.
Kara, I'm really trying here,
but everything I've been told -
By who?
Your friend,
the Martian manhunter?
My father wasn't a traitor.
He didn't try to kill anyone.
He was a good man.
I'm gonna prove that to you.
Forget about the crystal.
It could be anywhere.
That crystal is the only thing
I have left from home,
- ...but you could care less.
- That's not true.
It's always about what you want.
You act like such a hero.
But really,
all you ever think about is yourself.
I'm not the one who took off and
didn't tell anybody where I went.
Was I supposed to give you
an itinerary?
We may be cousins,
but I don't have to like you.
Stay out of my life.
I'm not letting you leave.
You don't have a choice.
Kara!
You okay?
When did you get back from D.C.?
I just flew in.
You know, Clark was looking
for you. He was really worried.
You might want to think about diving into
the digital age and use your cell phone.
Don't worry about Clark.
Look, I hope you don't mind
me using your computer.
Just thought I'd check some stuff
against The Planet database.
No, no,
that's no problem at all.
Feel free to rev
your search engine here anytime.
Well, unless you're hacking
into national security networks.
Which is exactly
what you're doing.
Kara, this is top-secret information.
They can trace my I.P. address...
and arrest me for this.
No. Not after running it
through a torpark filter...
and rerouting it through
half a dozen servers.
You are a very mysterious girl.
I'm trying to find
who entered this one lab,
someone who could have stolen
something from it.
Have you ever heard
of LX Dynamics?
Yeah, they're a
LuthorCorp Defense contractor...
working assignment down
at one of their plants.
As in Lex Luthor.
Here, scoot over, and I will
pull up our file on them.
And here...
it is.
Kara?
ISIS FOUNDATION
I suspected that you a Luthor
were working together.
What are you doing?
I've been waiting for the chance
to use these restraints on you.
When I saw how that meteor rock
disabled your ship,
I figured it might do
the same thing to the passenger.
Tell your boss
I only want what's mine.
My boss is the United States of America.
We have some questions for you.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Step back, Mr. Luthor.
This is a matter of national security.
I said stand down.
You better have official
authorization to make an arrest.
- You're being recorded.
- I disabled the feed.
- My guards will be here in seconds.
- I disabled them, too.
- What have you done to her?
- I know that you stole something from me.
I don't know what you mean.
Is it a coincidence you were in my lab
the same day she broke in?
What makes you think
she would break into your lab?
I know you've got my property
hidden somewhere in here...
but it doesn't matter anymore.
She's the real prize now.
So blinded by devotion, he couldn't see
the danger that you pose our planet.
Clark, it's Lana.
I know where Kara is.
I don't need a frank assessment, senator,
just your assurance Agent Carter
will be fired by morning.
Where's Kara?
Take it easy, Clark.
Where is she?
She was just arrested by the
Department of Domestic Security.
I swear to God, Lex, if you're lying -
I tried to stop the agent,
but he got the upper hand.
- I only want to help her.
- I wish I could believe you.
I swear.
She's been taken to a lab in Virginia.
Clark, why would they arrest her?
Why are you doing this?
You' hurting me.
Well, if I wasn't hurting you,
you'd be hurting me.
We humans - we call it
"survival of the fittest."
I am human.
Then how did you smash
into an impenetrable vault?
See, I talked to that lab tech,
the one you tried to seduce.
I know it was you.
This machine will reveal the truth.
Summerholt's created this technology
to force people to relive their memories.
But it was unstable.
Now, I can control the process...
by delivering the meteor-rock solution
directly into your veins.
I want to know
about your home planet.
You're on it.
It's called Earth.
Now...
Let's start at the beginning.
Where are you from and when did
you first arrive on this planet?
Kara?
Hi, aunt Lara.
You followed me?
Well, with the speed we have
on this planet, it wasn't hard.
Visiting me at home is one thing, Kara,
but sneaking through
the last remaining portal...
to follow me here was far too dangerous.
I had to get out of Kandor.
The war's been getting worse, and I can hear
the mines being bombed day and night.
Does Zor-El know you're here?
You know my father never
lets me out of Kandor alone.
But he's been spending so much time in
the lab that it was easy to sneak away.
Why are you here?
I...
I wanted to see where
my son may grow up.
What? But you don't have...
Wait. You're pregnant?
I'm so happy for you! I know how much
you and Jor-El wanted this!
He's our miracle baby.
I don't understand. I mean,
why would he grow up here?
Kara...
Krypton may never
see the end of this war.
Jor-El's brain-interactive construct
may very well save us, but...
I won't risk my son's life
on that chance.
Well, I'll be there,
and I'll protect him.
As much as this pains me,
it may be my only choice.
I can't let the destiny of my child
be dictated by the fate of our planet.
Well, aren't you worried about
your son growing up with humans?
I mean, they're so primitive.
Jor-El visited Earth many years ago,
and he chose this family...
because he was impressed
by their capacity for love.
I hope it's more impressive
than the way that they live.
This place is a mess.
It's one of many structures,
Kara, it's not the residence.
- Come, let me show you.
- Okay, aunt Lara.
Amazing.
You were here
before the first meteor shower.
No. I'm hallucinating.
No, it wasn't a hallucination.
You came to Earth in 1986.
- It's not true! I never-
- Who did you visit?
- I didn't. I swear.
- That would be a lie.
So, I guess we could use
a little higher concentration.
I want you to go back to your first
journey here. Who did you contact?
What if we get caught, Lara?
Are these people here right now?
No, they're attending a spiritual
celebration called church.
It's one of their traditions.
Sure smells a lot better in here.
I believe they're cooking.
Sunday roast.
It is so peaceful here
compared to Krypton.
- It's a true home.
- I don't know.
It's kind of small and cluttered.
Careful, Kara.
We must leave no trace of our visit.
I don't want to influence them
in any way.
They're destined to raise my child.
It's important they feel secure.
Have you given your baby a name yet?
No.
With everything happening on Krypton
Jor-El and I have yet to discuss one.
He'll be so far from home.
Our sun will be nothing
but a distant star.
Maybe you could name him Kal-El.
And that way, when he looks at the sky,
he could think of us.
Kal-El.
Well, that's a beautiful name.
This must be her.
She'll make a good mother.
Kara.
Don't you want your son
to have a picture of you?
We better hide it somewhere.
Zor-El!
Father!
Get away from her!
Oh, my god.
You're one of them.
I figured there were more of you,
living among us, hiding in plain sight.
She's been exposed too long.
You' killing her.
Extreme measures for extreme times.
I had to push her to her limit to learn
about your dangerous species.
If you disconnect her, I'll tell you
everything you need to know.
Yeah, you will -
when I'm done with her.
Kara!
Kara,
wake up!
Father!
- Kara, I told you not to leave Kandor!
- It's my fault.
I thought Kara could learn something
about the world by coming here.
- It's not true.
- Kara, go wait outside.
There's no reason to be angry.
You know Kara is safe with me.
You always did watch out for her.
In fact, I'm relieved you're here.
We both know our planet
could be destroyed soon.
With the end so near,
there's no reason to return.
Stay with me here on Earth.
We could rule this planet
with strength as a family.
No! Jor-El -
He's my husband.
We're having a child...
a son.
Jor-El's blood runs too cold
to be a father.
You tried to kill him.
- What does that make you?
- Passionate!
My brother stole you from me.
He took away my life.
Jor-El didn't steal me.
He'll never feel the way I feel about you.
I know you love Kara.
I'll love your son as my own.
Zor-el, stop!
You're delusional.
We will be together, Lara.
If not here today,
then one day through my science.
Your science?
You -
You stole my DNA?
Your strands are safely
stored within a crystal...
that, like you, is full
of light and beauty.
I refuse to be your next
science experiment!
Oh, you're much more
than that, Lara.
Father!
How could you?
I told you to wait outside!
- What are you doing?! Stop!
- No!
You will forget everything about this day.
Kara?!
Kara, come back!
Kara!
Kara.
Sorry, Clark, I'd never told you about this
place if I'd known how dangerous it was.
Kal-El.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Everything's gonna be all right.
I don't believe it.
After all this time.
That means that I really was here,
and everything that I saw is true.
When I saw my mother in your memory,
she was so beautiful...
just as beautiful as she is
in this picture.
You really loved her, didn't you?
I did.
Just like I loved my father.
Until now, I thought he was such a god -
a real Kryptonian hero.
But you're right,
he was nothing like that.
Your father did some terrible things.
but in his own misguided way,
I'm sure he loved you.
I don't know what's worse -
finding out the truth or
losing who I thought he was.
We're not defined by our parents, Kara.
One of the most important things
that my adoptive parents taught me...
is that we shape our own destiny.
Maybe it's time I stopped holding on
so tightly to my past and...
started looking ahead
to my life on Earth -
Find the kind of friends that you have.
I'm sorry, Clark. I was so obsessed
with trying to find the crystal...
that it put us both in danger.
I don't blame you for wanting
to find the crystal so badly -
especially now that I know
how important it is.
I said some terrible things to you.
Things that weren't true.
I'm happy you're in my life, Clark.
Well, I'm happy to be in your life, Kara.
Lara loved you very much.
I'm glad you got to see
my memory of her.
Me, too.
I hope I can see her again someday.
Striving for complete isolation?
Dangerous choice.
No man is an island entire of itself.
Glad to know your son still ranks a spot
on your busy itinerary.
You know, I tried to use
the LuthorCorp jet the other night,
but you'd already taken it
to Washington.
I'm amazed you'd be traveling so soon
after your recent ordeal in the woods.
I' got some catching up to do.
Oh, I got a bit of news from my contacts
at the Department of Domestic Security.
There's a new girl in town...
and apparently,
you are fascinated with her.
If you're referring to Kara Kent,
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
She just works for me at the Talon.
First Lana, now Kara, don't you think
it's time to give up this...
fixation with Clark
and everyone connected with him?
So, that's it?
Your fatherly advice for the day?
Can't I take an interest
in my son's well-being?
Oh, and which son is that?
You spend as much time protecting
Clark as you do pushing me away.
Exactly whose father are you?
I wish I could say yours
and be proud.
Your treatment of Lana -
Come on, dad...
I learned from watching you with mom.
I was just... being a Luthor.
I don't know what you're being.
You have crossed a line.
Look...
I realize your first instinct
is to assume the worst, dad...
but believe me,
I'm not that person anymore.
You're right, you're not.
These illicit projects of yours-
you hide them like an expert.
I'm sure you can fool the people around you.
You can probably fool yourself.
But not me.
You can never fool me.
I think I owe you an apology
for running off last night.
I know what it's like
to chase a lead, Kara. I just...
hate to think that you only
want me for my computer.
I know, it just takes a lot to put a
frown on that face of yours James but...
I was so focused on tracking down spaceships
that I wasn't much of a friend.
You were there for me every time.
- So, you noticed?
- Noticed?
If it weren't for you I wouldn't
have had any lead to chase.
Well, I don't know, Kara,
I saw how fast you went...
from computers 101 to
hacking the Pentagon.
I think you can do just about anything
once you put your mind to it.
Well, right now, all I want to do
is treat you lunch.
How about some more Chinese?
I'm getting the hang
of that whole chopstick thing.
I'll go get my jacket.
Okay, great.
Whoa.
Hey, you're looking chipper.
Really, I do?
It's nothing, it's just a...
beautiful day.
You know, even though we're not each
other's automatic plus-one anymore...
doesn't mean we still can't be friends.
Are you doing anything for lunch?
Actually, I - I have plans.
With Kara.
It's just lunch, Chloe.
Look, I know how this is gonna sound,
coming from me, but...
you and Kara are from different worlds.
just be careful, okay?
Chloe, Kara is from Minnesota.
It's not like she's from another planet.
After you.
So, what's the big surprise?
I wouldn't have found Kara
if it wasn't for you.
I'm glad you still have
those contacts in the mansion.
I'm just glad she's okay.
Well, when I found her, Lana,
she gave me this.
It's my birth mother.
Her name is Lara.
She's stunning.
Clark, this was taken in your house.
When did you -
It's a long story, Lana,
but there is more.
I told you I wanted to share
everything with you.
What's in that?
Inside this crystal...
is my mother's DNA.
Transcript subway-sub
Synch and revised subXpacio y TusSeries