A kryptonian.
If anyone's gonna stop
this phantom, it's gonna be me.
I took a little piece
of your dna,
And now i'm gonna take
your life.
Do we have what we need?
It looks like
your fleet of fighters
Are about to get
their jet fuel.
I had a run-In
with the last phantom.
I have to leave
earth's atmosphere to heal.
I'm leaving lex.
Do you really think
i could just let you walk away?
Lana!
Lana -- She's dead, son.
I don't believe you.
Why did you kill her?
I'm some kind of meteor freak,
aren't i?
I'm not going anywhere
Until you tell me what's
really going on at this dam.
You can't die.
You're under arrest
for the murder of lana luthor.
Chloe?
What the hell are you?
I'm you,
only a little more bizarre.
and now the season premier
of "smallville."
Dad, how long
are we staying here?
Dad,
there's no fish here.
Son, this is the bes??
Hang on, chlo.
I'll get us out of here.
Those people.
I have to get back to the dam.
Hey, clark.
You ever wonder what would
happen to all these humans
If you weren't here
to play savior?
I know you do.
You just never admit it.
You don't know
anything about me.
No, clark.
I know everything about you.
I didn't just borrow
your dna.
I have all your memories,
all your thoughts,
Every last twisted one
of them.
When i'm living your life,
I won't make
those same mistakes.
Hey, bud. Dad?
Run!
Dad! Dad! Wake up!
Dad! Dad, wake up!
Run! Dad!
Are you all right,
buddy?
No!
Help me, please.
Hey.
It's okay.
Lionel?!
Help!
Can anybody hear us?!
Is she dead?
No, honey.
She's not dead.
She's just...
a litt hurt.
Help!
How did you do --
The ceiling's unstable.
We're lucky it caved in.
Oh, let's not wait
to get lucky again.
Chloe?
£¿£¿
Start an arterial line.
Inflate gases.
Prep for a chest tube now,
stat.
Lois.
You want to tell me
what happened out there?
It's gonna sound insane.
I don't know, clark.
Maybe i was unconscious
and dreaming.
Maybe you weren't.
The last thing i remember,
I was pulling an
eight-Inch knife out of my gut,
And there was
blood everywhere.
I dialed chloe,
and i had this chill,
And my hands
started to tingle,
And then
i must have passed out.
So someone stabbed you?
A guard -- Right here.
I know.
But there was this warm light
all around me.
And when i woke up,
the wound was healed
And chloe was lying
a few feet away, unconscious.
You said that lex
May have been doing
some experiments down there.
When i was out,
Maybe one of his men
did something to me...
And chloe.
That's it. I can't just
stand around here waiting.
I'm going to see
what lex did to her.
Lex?
Lex is dangerous.
I am not stupid,
smallville, okay?
I know that
he's not just gonna cough up
All his deep,
dark secrets.
But you heard the doctors.
None of chloe's vitals
were normal.
If someone at the mansion
knows what happened,
I will take my chances
with dr. Evil.
Maybe lana can help me
do some digging.
Lois, um...
...there's something
you should know.
If this is another
heart-To-Heart about lana,
I don't mean
to be insensitive,
But chloe is fighting
for her life,
And i am barely
keeping it together,
So one more ounce of emotion --
I might just lose it.
So make yourself useful
for once.
Just stay here and make sure
nothing happens to my coz, okay?
Wo mr. Luthor,
the helicopter's waiting.
We should have you out of
u.S. Jurisdiction in two hours.
I was dead.
And there
was this light.
And an angel.
Why would she save me...
After all i've done?
Lock down the perimeter.
Secure the stairwell.
The only thing gettingn
or out of here is that chopper.
Sir, you're wanted
for your wife's murder.
We need you to hurry.
Her soft skin...
And her hair...
That half-Awake smile
Wh she saw me come in
like...
She didn't know
if she was still in a dream.
She was the only thing
i was living for.
I'm sorry for your loss,
sir.
But right now
we need to get you airborne.
Police will be here
any minute.
I'm well aware of that.
I'm turning myself in.
Okay.
Whoa!
Smallville,
you scared me.
Where have you
been hiding?
Uh, maybe where
i told you i'd be.
Although i got zilch.
Lex's men must have
cleared everything out
Before the cops came.
Hey!
Hey.
Why aren't
you watching chloe?
Man, how can a guy miss
What's been right
in front of him l this time?
Slow down there, tiger.
A little
personal-Space breach.
Come on,
i know you're looking for a guy
Who doesn't
play by the rules.
And on what planet
is that you, smallville?
Whatever planet
you want me to take you to.
Whoa, hey!
Maybe next time.
Wo where's my 1 mil
of epinephrine?
I'm on it.
It's in.
She's not responding.
Check that monitor.
Those readings aren't possible.
We've got
atrial fibrillation.
Charge the defib. I need
200 joules. Come on, chloe.
Pump it up.
New charge.
Clear.
Come on, chloe.
Stay with me.
Clear.
Time of death 13:48.
Help!
Somebody help me!
No.
Where's miss lane?
She just left.
Chloe's gonna be okay,
isn't she?
I can't share
any information with you
Until we've notified
Miss sullivan's
immediate family.
No.
No
That's a restricted area.
Get him out.
You can't be in here.
Where's
chloe sullivan?
She didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
Clark!
Somebody help me!
Help!
It's okay.
Clark, what happened?
Am i in a morgue?
Come on,
let's get you out --
Why am i in a morgue?
You're alive.
That's what matters now.
But i wasn't alive,
was i?
Lois.
Lois is fine.
I'm guessing you know that
better than anyone.
Turn around.
She showed me
her stab wound,
The one that
didn't leave a scratch.
I thought i had the market
on resurrections today.
May have done something to you
when you were out.
You want to tell me
what really haened?
Clark, as much as
i would love to contribute
To lois'
divine-Intervention story,
I was a little busy
being unconscious.
Clark, i don't have time
for 20 questions right now.
You just died
and came back to life.
Don't you think you should
have your blood pressure taken?
And get turned
into some sort of lab rat?
From one guinea pig to another,
i think i'll pass.
clark means more to me
than you ever will.
that's the last time
you'll ever touch me.
do you really think
i could just let you walk away?
what are you going to do,
lex?
kill me?
With evidence like that,
I doubt we'd be able to
get you bail.
I'm not worried about me.
I want an update on
the recovery efforts of the dam,
And more specifically i need
to know the status of model 503.
Most of the compromised units
have been recovered,
But we're still looking
for 503.
My father?
Still unaccounted for.
Sir, we have to find you
an alibi.
I wasn't miraculously saved
To run away from my demons,
keating.
I was brought back
to face them.
Be careful
what you wish for.
That was easy.
I loed for you at the mansion.
¶àóàµä»°we need
a little privacy.
The phantom.
You took clark's body.
Just a few cells.
Clark's still alive.
He's out there.
And you will
help me kill him.
I need meteor rocks --A lot
I'd never
help you kill clark.
Lex, redemption
doesn't suit you.
Why protect a clark kent
who hates u
When you can help the one
who wants to be your ally?
It's what
you've always wanted.
Isn't it, lex?
Hey.
Oh, it's really hard
to concentrate
When lana was here one minute
and now she's just...
Ò²ëãã»óðóãµägone.
I'm so sorry, clark.
There's a lot more people
that could get hurt right now.
Yeah.
Denial should be our friend
right now.
Okay, so, this phantom-Clark
thing was inhabiting humans.
But when he touched you,
it just replicated. Why?
The phantom
needed a kryptonian body
In order to replicate
to become whole again.
Chloe, i don't know
how to stop him.
It's not like
i can just fly after him.
This guy can fly?
God, clark.
You got to get on that one.
Well, where's
our bizarro clark now?
I don't know.
But, chloe, before i hit him,
his face distorted,
Almost like he was hurt.
Which is
why he pushed pause
On his one-Man mission
to kill you.
But why would your doppelganger
weaken if you didn't?
It's like everything
affects him the opposite.
When lionel held
the meteor rock to him,
It almost
made him stronger.
Soaybe he went to find
more meteor rocks
So he could recharge
and finish the job he started.
Oliver's been tracking
all of lex's meteor shipments
For his 33.1 experiments.
Yeah, and it says here
in these records
That there were
several containers
Transferred to reeves dam
just a couple weeks ago.
Clark, if he gets there
before you do,
There's no way you can
go up against him alone.
I mean, how are you
gonna take this guy down?
I don't know, chloe.
But there is
someone who might.
When you left here,
you were hurt pretty badly.
How did you heal so fast?
I just had to leave
the earth's atmosphere.
But in my absence,
it appeared you did
Exactly what you were always
trying to prevent.
I unleashed
a carbon copy of myself...
Only without my --
Humanity.
What was
i supposed to do,
Let him kill
every host he inhabited?
That is one of the hardest
trials you will face, kal-El.
While your humanity
is your greatest strength,
It is also
your greatest vulnerability.
Well, it's part of who i am.
And it's who i want to be.
I'm prd that i was raised
to care about people,
And i am not gonna apologize
for it anymore.
I know.
But this creature
Was discarded at birth
as a poor imitation.
He was shown no compassion,
no conscience.
Therefore, he has none.
He knows only one thing --
Survival.
How do i stop someone
Who has all my powers
and none of my weaknesses?
By opening your eyes
To what you take for granted
every day.
Your faith in humans
Is not the only thing
that gives you strength.
Yellow sun.
That's why his face distorted
when he got into the light.
That may be the only way
to defeat him.
I can help,
but it's your battle.
The section of the dam
where the meteor rock is stored
Shouldn't have been compromised.
The meteor rocks are in there.
I may have tracked you
around the globe,
But clearly you're not a native.
Where are you from,
And why did you
only replicate clark?
Now you got
a decision to make, lex.
What's more important --
Destroying me
Or solving the mystery
of clark kent?
Wrong decision.
You had the existence
i could only dream of,
Every pleasure  at your disposal,
and you wasted it.
You don't deserve this life, clark.
But i do.
Come on.
Wo thfairy-Tale marriage
of lana lang to lex luthor
ended in tragedy.
sources say the billionaire
is being held for questioning
in the explosion
that cut short such a...
Clark?
police say
lang's vehicle exploded
in what was believed to be
a car bomb
behind a local coffeehouse.
according to wire services,
a funeral date
has yet to be set.
although no witnesses
have come forward,
lex luthor was apprehended
near reeves dam,
which was the source
of the recent...
I know you wanted to
be alone, but...
I thought i'd come byand see
If i could get more
than two words out of you.
Thanks, chloe.
I think i'll take a rain check.
Yeah, well, i guess you deserve
A little bit of peace and quiet
After sending
the evil bobbsey twin
To the sunny side of mars.
Who's to say
he's any more evil than i am?
Unless you have
a second secret identity
That i don't know about,
i...
Chloe, when i heard about lana,
I went to find lex.And i wasn't gonna
let him leave there alive.
The irony is
i think it was the first time
I ever really understood lex.
Loving someone is hard.
It's difficult.
But hate --
Hate is so...
Clean.
Maybe you need to feel this
right now.
I mean, anger is
a natural human emotion.
Well, that's just it.
'Cause when that phantom
was trying to kill me
And i was staring
into my own eyes,
I saw the monster that
i could become if i wanted to.
It was a reminder
that i am not human.
Tell that to every person
you've ever saved.
Clark, whether you want to e it or not,
You're one of us now.
And the fact that you're
from a galaxy far, far away .Just...
Adds character.
And you know i'm here,
No matter what side
of nature or nurture
Happens to be winning out.
It goes both ways,
chloe.
Whatever happened in that dam,
You ended up in a morgue.
Yeah, it was nothing.
I'm just saying
that when you're ready --
Thanks.
Clark, there you are.
I forgive you.
For what?
Oh,don't make me relive it.
It was traumatizing enough
the first time around.
And by the way, you've got
some explaining to do there.
Lois, i'm sorry.
I know you are.
And i know you didn't mean it.
You were just in shock.
I heard about lana on the news.
Clark, i'm so sorry.
Look, all i can say is...
At first you don't know how
you'll ever make it through,
But somehow you do.
Just trust me on this one.
But if you ever
grab my ass again,
I will be taking your head
with me when i go.
Okay?
Your father would be proud.
He did everything he could to
prepare you.
But bravery
is not something you can learn.
How much bravery does it take
when you're getting pummeled?
Kal-El...
You could have ignored
all the phantoms
That escaped the phantom zone,
But you chose to take
responsibility and stop them,
Even one more powerful than you.
In a weird way,
he may have been right.
Maybe i have allowed myself
to become weak,
Caring too much about everything,
everyone here.
You've learned a lot
from your time in smallville.
These people  have made you who you are.
They won't always be here.
Losing lana has made me realize
No matter how close i get,
someday they'll all be gone.
And all the time
that i've spent
Ignoring my destiny,
Trying to be something i'll never be...
Human.