activity
Take your squad.
Sweep the perimeter. Go.
What's our status?
Security breach --northeast sector.
What have the surveillance
cameras picked up?
Not a damn thing.
Anything comes down this tunnel, kill it.
-Got it.
Contact?
-Tunnel 7.
Wait.
Section "f" compromised.
Lock it down.
Section "D."compromised
That's only 30 meters from here.
Section "C"compromised
20 meters.
10.
Section "B."compromised
Maybe this wasn'tsuch a good idea.
-Section "A."compromised
Mission accomplished.
Standing by for further instructions.
Vitals are steady.
He didn't even break a sweat.
2 minutes, 18 seconds to
infiltrate a secured facility,
disable my best men,
and eliminate the target.
Not a bad test run.
Get some fresh guards.
I want to see him do it again.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-addychristen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Smallville
Season 06 Episode 21
We have about a dozen people
that could do that for you.
Next thing you know,
they'll be brushing my teeth for me.
There are some things
I'd rather do on my own.
Independent and not afraid
to get her hands dirty --
two of the billion or so reasons
I fell in love with you.
The shoulder's just still
a little bit sore.
Maybe we should have the doctor
look at it again.
No, it's okay.
Lana, you were shot.
Takes more than a bullet
to stop a luthor.
Sir, senator burke has arrived.
Show him in.
You've been seeing a lot
of the senator recently.
The price of doing business
with the government.
But this will just take a minute.
I'll be in the garden.
Mrs. Luthor.
-Senator
I hope I didn't interrupt a tender moment.
If you had, you'd still
be waiting outside.
I'm not gonna keep you
from your pretty lady.
I just, uh...swung by
for an update on ares.
The prototype is in the final
stages of testing.
Everything's on schedule.
Really?
I heard everything
was ahead of schedule --
way ahead.
I stuck my neck out
to get the armed services committee
to allow you access to military resources
and personnel to "r" and "d"
a single prototype,
but you've started gearing up
for mass production.
Just looking towards the future, senator.
I assumed a visionary like you
would understand that.
How long do you think
you're gonna be able
to keep what you've really
got going on here a secret?
See...
one of my own men believed he uncovered
a mole right in your backyard.
Who?
Well, I wish I could tell you,
but my boy doesn't talk too good
with a bullet through his heart.
Senator, if there are leaks in my security,
I assure you,
I will have them taken care of.
Well, doesn't that just fill me
with the warm fuzzies?
Do you know what'll happen to me
if the senate ever got wind
of what you're up to now?
I assume
they wouldn't care for it...
just like they wouldn't care
for all the money
I've transferred into your cayman
account over the last year.
Project ares is over.
I'm shutting it down.
That would be ill-advised.
No.
What's ill-advised is you ever opening
your mouth about our arrangement.
I so much as hear a peep out of you,
I'll make sure the committee
reviews every business deal
luthorcorp has made
in the last 20 years,
and u'll be lucky to keep
that fancy shirt on your back.
Do we understand each other...
luthor?
Perfectly.
LUTHORCORP
***
-Yes
Greetings from patagonia,
the most beautiful place on earth.
What is that?
We have to talk.
Clark, you should, uh,
try picking up the phone occasionally --
might be quicker.
Oh, but maybe not.
What do you know about lana?
Letting go --
never been one of your strong points, was it?
Telling the truth was never one of yours.
And you're accusing me of what,
exactly, this time?
Lana came to me the day of the wedding
to tell me she wasn't going through with it,
that she was leaving lex.
Apparently, she changed her mind.
Or someone changed it for her.
So, you think I had something
to do with her decision?
If lana was so unhappy with lex,
why go through with the marriage?
It's surprising, clark,
what people will do when they, uh,
feel they have no other options.
If I find out that you had anything to do
with lana marrying lex,
the gloves will come off.
How do you like that option?
Triple espresso mocha cappu latte --
my own invention,
guaranteed to put the zip-a-dee
back in your doo-dah.
Thanks.
Come on.It's not that bad.
Jimmy is coming back one day...
maybe.
You know, besides, distance
is good for the relationship.
That is what all the guys who've
moved away from me have said.
Lois, you should really stick
to investigative reporting
and out of the advice column.
That's the plan.
Hey, smallville.
Love to hear about the cows and the corn,
but I got a lead on a dirty senator
that needs to be hosed down.
See you on the front page.
She going after a senator?
I guess so.
She hasn't told me much about it.
Lot of that going around lately.
Was that jab directed at my chin?
I went to lionel to ask about lana.
What did he say?
Nothing, just like you.
Did you forget what he did to you,
what he did to your mother?
No, I haven't forgotten.
I don't want anything to happen to lana.
Neither do I.
But if she's staying in that marriage,
all I can say is, she must have
a damn good reason.
Are you sure about this?
Got the reservation.
Eats here every time he's in town.
Voil?
Thanks for the tip.
Senator burke.
How do you do?
Lois lane, reporter.
I was hoping to ask a few questions.
Sure. Schedule an interview with my office.
You know, I tried to,
but no one returned my calls.
Well, that ought to tell you
something, sweet cakes.
Senator, last year,
your salary was $150,000.
Can you tell me how you managed to deposit
over $5 million in a cayman account?
What paper did you say
you work for, uh, miss...
lane -- lois lane.
I'm a reporter for the inquisitor.
The inquisitor?
That's not a newspaper.That's a --
that's a cat-box liner.
Now get her out of here.
Hey, get your hands off me,you fascist!
I'm warning you!If you don't --
Oh, my god.
Wes?
Chloe, what's going on?
You haven't heard?
Senator burke was murdered.
What?
It looks like burke was in bed with la famiglia.
He crossed them.
They gave him the fredo treatment.
It's a mob hit.
Well, all evidence points to that,
but there is one witness
who doesn't think so.
Lois?
-Thanks.
What happened to you?
well, one minute, I was
harassing a public official,
and the next, he came
out of nowhere, like a ghost.
Burke and his men never had a chance.
Y-you saw who did this?
Yeah, I did more than see him,
clark -- I know him.
His name's wes keenan.
We were army brats together
when we were kids.
I'm running a check on his name.
Looks like he works for the mob now.
Wes? No way.
He's career military.
He's been decorated more than a christmas tree.
Even my dad loved him,
and the general hates everybody.
Lois, are you sure
the man you saw is wes keenan?
I haven't seen him for years,
but he has this little scar
above his right eye, and --
trust me.It was wes.
Not according to the U.S. Government.
He was in a helicopter crash
in afghanistan four months ago.
He was killed in action.
No, that is not possible.
I know what I saw.
What else does it say?
-Nothing.
I mean, his military records
have been classified.
What is that?
His alpha wave just spiked for a second.
It's probably just feedback
from the implants in his cortex.
Probably?
It's nothing to worry about.
Everything's still holding
within operational parameters.
Make sure it stays that way.
Sir.
Just received information
that burke's been eliminated.
Evidence trail?
Leads straight back to the mob,
per your instructions.
There's been a complication.
There was a witness.
Nothing can get in the way
of completing this project --
nothing.
Take care of it.
You heard the man.
Prep him.
Lois, quit being stubborn.
You're gonna stay here
until we get this cleared up.
Thanks, but I can take care of myself.
Nobody's doubting that,
but you'd be safer here at the farm.
It'll be like old times,
like when you first got to smallville.
Oh, you're just hoping
to catch me in the shower again.
I-I mean, um, thank you.
I-I really appreciate it.
You're always welcome here, lois.
You're practically family.
well,since I'm being a burden,
can I just ask one more favor?
What do you need?
Your mom's political influence.
Look, do you think that
you could use your connections to get a look
at wes' military jacket?
I thought you said
that file was classified.
It is.
I contacted the general,but, uh,
he went all cold war on me
and said that I should drop it.
He might have a point.
Three men are already dead.
Which is why I have to get
my hands on that file.
It might explain why wes is doing this.
Well, I've made a few friends in washington.
I don't know if they can help,
but I'll see what I can do.
Thanks, mrs. Kent.
I know that look,
and it's usually followed by you almost
getting yourself killed.
This isn't just another story, clark --
not this time.
Wes and I --
we were close.
I know it was him.
Stay here.
See?It was just the wind.
Clark, watch out!
Wes?
How could lois have been kidnapped
with you standing right there?
She just vanished, chloe,literally.
So, he could teleport, like alicia?
But something's different.
It's more like what graham garrett could do.
So, he can turn himself invisible?
Not just himself --
he took lois with him.
And it's not his only ability.
When he hit me --
chloe, I haven't felt anything like that
since I went up against titan.
Clark, we need to find lois before wes --
we will.
Were you able to uncover
anything about wes
that might be able to help us
figure out where he took her?
I haven't been able to retrieve any
information from the military files,
but I did run a cross-check on his name,
and I found one hit --
jodi keenan.
Jodi keenan?
Isn't that the woman who tried
to kill lex in the tunnels?
Guess who she's married to.
-Wes?
Looks like jodi found out that wes
wasn't killed in afghanistan.
She followed the trail
all the way back here to lex.
Okay, so, wes is exhibiting
multiple krypto-abilities.
And according to lois,
he's also on the receiving end
of some sort of mind control.
How much do you want to bet that all of
this plays into lex's 33.1 experiments?
Chloe, I need you to contact
oliver and his team.
They've been taking out 33.1 facilities
all around the world.
Don't you think that's
a hero-to-hero phone call?
I'm gonna talk to lex.
Clark, come on.
We both know that lex
isn't gonna tell you anything.
Then I'll find somebody who will.
Too much?
No, it'S...
I thought maybe if I set the mood...
or maybe not.
Lex...
Sorry to bother you, sir.
The asset failed to return.
I'll be right back.
Lana.
You shouldn't be here.
Lex is just outside.
I had to see you.
Clark...
it's not about you and me.
Lois is in trouble.
And what makes you think I can help?
'Cause it seems there's a connection to lex.
Lana, if you've seen
or heard anything --
maybe something about the military...
ares.
That's the god of war.
Lex has been talking to senator burke
about this military project called "ares."
Yesterday, he threatened to shut it down.
Maybe you should talk with him.
I can'T.
Senator burke is dead.
He was murdered by the same man
who has lois.
Lana, is there anything else --
maybe something that lex let slip?
One of his men was just saying something
about an asset that failed to return.
An asset?
That's what the military
calls its soldiers.
Lex is connected to this.
Lana, whatever reason you had
to go through with the wedding,
it was the wrong choice.
You have no idea what he's capable of.
You'd be surprised what I know.
Then why are you still here?
We all have our secrets,clark.
Sometimes,we have to keep them to protect
the people that we care about.
Lana...
I know.
Lana?
You okay?
Yeah, yeah.I'm just a little chilly.
Look,something's come up.
I need to go in to the office.
Don't wait up.
Wes.
Designation incorrect.
Call sign "ares,"prototype mark iv.
You don't remember me,do you?
It's lois -- lois lane.
My father is general sam lane.
When I was a kid,
he used to drag me around to all the bases
that he was stationed at.
One of them was fort addleson,
where I met you.
Do you remember how you got that scar?
You used to tell everybody that you got it
falling off your dirt bike.
But that's not how it happened.
We got into the general's whiskey.
Then we broke into the storage warehouse.
We were wrestling around, being stupid.
And I kissed you...
...the first timeI ever kissed anybody.
And you smiled your crooked smile.
And then you puked and passed out and
cracked your head open on the floor.
Never could handle your liquor, wes.
Mission incomplete.
-No.
Eliminate target.
Why did you bring me here?
Think.Wes.
This is fort addleson, okay?
This is the warehouse.
This is where I kissed you that night.
Remember me!
Mr. Luthor.
Three years and a billion
dollars spent on ares,
and you're telling me you lost him?
Well, we're in unchartered
territory here, mr. Luthor.
Synthesizing multiple meteor
abilities is difficult enough,
but stringing together the molecular chain
with peptides extracted from that creature
that bartlett recovered --
the only thing that allows all these
abilities to exist in one subject.
Titan's genetic material was the key
to making this project viable.
Yes, which makes the results
as unpredictable as the substances
I'm being asked to work with.
What you're being asked to do
is help protect the world, doctor.
Unstable criminals with dangerous
powers are becoming more and more common.
Humanity's only chance of surviving
the onslaught is this project.
So, kick that big brain of yours
into high gear
and figure out what the hell went wrong!
It's possible something might have
triggered a decay in his memory blocks --
a familiar place or person.
Can't you get a fix on him?
The field he generates makes it impossible
to track him electronically.
It's part of his design.
I want our dog back on his leash, doctor,
or you'll be my next experiment.
Maybe I could reposition
the luthorcorp satellites...
...generate a broad-spectrum
pulse that will, hopefully,
re-initiate his command directives,
but there's no guarantee.
I'm not asking for guarantees.
I'm asking for results.
I want ares back online
and his mission complete.
Start the pulse.
I killed a united states senator?
What happened?
How did you end up like this?
I was stationed in afghanistan.
Our convoy hit an I.E.D.
And then I woke up in the military hospital.
That's when luthor showed up.
Lex.
I should have known.
He forced you into this, didn't he?
He offered me a way
to keep serving my country.
By turning you into a brain-dead assassin?
You think this is what I signed on for?
He told me project ares was gonna
help soldiers protect themselves on the field,
so they wouldn't end up like I did.
We won't let him get away
with this, I promise you.
Okay, we will expose lex and project ares.
What? What?What is it? What?
Them --
they're trying
to get back into my head.
Well, fight it, wes.
Look at me. Look at me!
Run. Run!Run!
I think lex was experimenting on wes,
trying to make him into a supersoldier.
With pick-and-choose meteor powers --
oliver told me pretty much the same thing.
Oliver knew about wes?
No. He found an earlier model
in the utah desert.
It looks like this isn't the first time
one of lex's souped-up rambos has gone awol.
Was he able to stop him?
-Barely.
It took the equivalent of a mini-nuk
to break through his force field.
Clark, even if you find him,
I'm not sure --
maybe this will help --
wes' military jacket.
How did you get that?
Called in a few favors and had to promise
a couple dozen of my own.
Lois is right.Wes was a hero.
He took her instead of killing her.
you know If whatever programming
they're using to control wes is failing,
maybe he'll go back to a place he remembers.
Somewhere he lived or --or was stationed.
The military base that wes grew up on
was decommissioned a few years ago --
fort addleson,just outside of metropolis.
Sam lane was stationed there
when lois was in junior high.
Maybe that's where --
Do you ever get used to that?
-Not really.
Wes?
You have to fight this.
Don't let them do this to you again.
You are not a murderer.
Please.
Wes.
System...damaged.
Turn protocol 38529532...
wes.
...38.
Lois.
You're gonna be fine.
Do you understand me?
You're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna go get help,all right?
No.
Better this way.
They'll never...
stop trying...
to control me.
You have to stay with me.
Do you hear me?
Don'T...
let them do this...
to anyone else.
Okay?
-Okay.
I promise, but you just
stay with me, okay?
Don't leave me.
Wes?
wes?
No, no, no.No.
Wes?
Wes!
Come on!
Don't leave me!
kent farm
How does this happen?
All wes wanted to do
was serve his country,
and he wound up being used as a pawn.
It happens more than I'd like to think.
Well, now that senator burke is gone --
oh, burke isn't the only one
on the hill lining his pockets.
Wherever there's power,
there will be men like lex to exploit it.
Maybe you can do something,
maybe open an investigation.
Clark, I'm a little fish in a tiny pond.
My influence doesn't reach
nearly that far up.
Then perhaps it's time
to extend that influence.
I just got off the phone
with the governor.
We were talking about your
filling burke's senatorial seat
until the next election.
Me?
Kansas needs to be represented
by someone of unassailable character
who can restore the faith
that burke has tarnished.
The governor agreed.
You are the perfect choice
for the U.S. Senate.
Clark...
you agree?
You should do it, mom.
I think you should do it.
And I think dad would have wanted you to.
I-I can't move to washington.
We're barely keeping the farm
running as it is.
Clark can take care of that.
Can't you, clark?
I could lease out the back 40
to ben hubbard.
He's been wanting
to work that land for years.
Oh, clark.
You and dad always taught me
to put other people first,
to use my abilities
to help those in need.
You have the chance
to affect so many people,
to change so many lives
if you go to washington.
That's where you need to be if
you really want to make a difference, mom.
And it's where people like wes
need you to be.
I don't care what it takes.
I want the body transported
to the lab immediately.
Make it happen.
Hey, you're up.
For a while now.
You never came home last night.
There was an unforeseen
complication with project ares.
Ares?
The secret military project I was discussing
with senator burke yesterday...
when you were listening outside the door.
Lex, I'm sorry.
There is no excuse.
My curiosity got the best of me.
You're not a cat, lana.
Don't skulk around like one.
It won't happen again.
Every time I've opened my heart
to someone I care about,
I've ended up being very disappointed.
If --
if you ever betrayed me...
I don't know what I'd do.
I'd never hurt the man I love.
Of course not.
But if there's anything you ever want to know
about my business dealings...
just ask.
No secrets?
No secrets.
Mrs. Kent goes to washington.
Well, if anyone can give jimmy stewart
a run for his money...
I just wish lionel wasn't helping her.
What, you think the king of ulterior motives
may have something up his armani sleeve?
When doesn't he?
Just, right now,
his son's a bigger problem.
That's the understatement of the century.
I mean, we've always known
lex has a dark side,
but with what he's been doing recently,
we're headed towards pitch black.
I want to make sure that lana's nowhere
near him when the lights go out.
Hopefully, he'll be behind bars
long before that.
I mean, lois is meeting the feds
at the morgue.
And once they connect wes' body with lex
and then burke's murder.
Don't hold your breath.
Wes' body's gone.
What about the feds?
What did they say when you
told them what happened?
I work at the inquisitor --
you know, aliens,bigfoot, elvis.
What do you think they said?
As far as they're concerned,wes keenan
died in action four months ago.
Just like it said in his file.
He deserved better than this.
Lois, I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry for me.
Be sorry for lex.
He's gonna pay for what he did to wes,
and I'm gonna make damn sure that
he doesn't do this to anyone else.
You were almost perfect.
Take him apart.
I want to know exactly what went wrong
so we don't make the same mistake next time.
Quantitating the abnormality
won't do us any good,mr. Luthor.
We used up nearly everything
we harvested from titan.
There aren't enough alien peptide
sequences to continue the project.
I'm already working
on procuring a replacement.
I promise you, doctor,
this isn't the end of project ares.
This is just the beginning.
Smallville
Season 06 Episode 21
sync:YTET-addychristen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-