There's the hut.
Let's hope word of the evac order
made it out this far.
Let's go.
Good God.
Son of a bitch.
All right, let's get blood samples.
Ten cc's each.
Right.
Hey, this is a quarantined
hot zone. Get out! Now!
Did you hear me?
You're exposing yourself
to a deadly virus.
Clark, you're amazing.
Okay, so you're not gonna
win any dance contests...
...but you're definitely not the worst.
Lana, I almost started a 10-person
pileup doing the two-step.
We should skip the dancing
before someone gets hurt.
Well, maybe we should try
something else more often.
Like what?
Well, I'll give you a hint.
Chloe happens to be pulling
an all nighter at the Daily Planet.
So you have the dorm room
all to yourself.
All to ourselves.
That sounds great, it really does.
But I have to get back to the farm.
It's gonna rain tomorrow
and I have to put up some tarps.
Clark, whenever you're ready,
I'll be waiting.
As long as it takes.
No pressure.
Lana.
I gotta go, it's getting late.
But I'll talk to you tomorrow.
- Okay.
I thought she'd never leave.
Hi, I'm Simone.
I was just leaving.
What's the hurry?
You're not going anywhere
until I tell you to.
Okay.
You're gonna believe
everything I tell you...
...and you're gonna do
everything I say.
Starting now.
What do you have in mind?
Smallville?
What the hell are you doing?
Lois, I'd like you to meet Simone...
...my new girlfriend.
I got your text message.
Lana, I apologize for interrupting
your Saturday night...
...but I thought
you'd be interested.
It's okay. I was just
on my way back to Metropolis.
What's going on?
My father taught me
never to reveal my hand...
...but I consider you my partner.
If it wasn't for you, I would have
never known the spacecraft existed.
- Have you found the ship?
- No.
But I have managed
to track down Milton Fine.
- What does he got to do with this?
- He was seen several times around...
...the warehouse where
I stored the spacecraft.
And he happened
to disappear from Smallville...
...the same exact day
the ship vanished.
Something tells me
it's not a coincidence.
So either you're planning
an exotic vacation...
...or this professor is somewhere
in Central America?
He was last seen in Honduras.
My jet leaves in an hour.
Lex, let me come with you,
maybe I can help.
Lana, I appreciate your passion...
...but I have no idea
what I'm walking into.
I can't risk putting you in danger.
I promise, when I get back,
I'll tell you everything.
Here you go.
Apple pie. Well, what else?
- My mom just made it.
- Of course she did.
That's delicious.
All I need now is
a glass of champagne.
But I don't suppose you have that
hidden behind the marmalade.
Clark?
What did you...?
- Where did you get that?
- Hal's Liquor Store in Metropolis.
What?
Metropolis? How?
I can run really fast.
So if I were to say, "clark...
...I want some
chocolate-covered strawberries."
Here you go.
You are too good to be true.
Yeah.
I think it's time you told
your girlfriend about us.
Call her and ask her to come over.
Okay, I am the first person
to concede...
...that anything is possible
in this universe...
...but Clark Kent lip-Iocked
with another girl?
Chloe, I'm telling you,
it was the last tango at the Talon.
Unfortunately, I had front row seats.
Well, something must have
happened to him...
...because he wouldn't just do this.
I know you have this whole
hero-worship thing with the guy...
...but face it, Clark is no different
than any other red-blooded male.
His brain, it's not his
commanding officer.
No, you don't know him
like I do. He is different.
- He wouldn't do this to Lana.
- He already has.
- Lf Lana's our friend, we need to warn...
- No, hold your fire.
Now, before you utter one word
to Lana about this, I just wan...
One word about what?
What's going on?
Lois needs a place to stay.
She needs to stay at our dorm room...
...for a couple of nights.
- Right, the heater's on the fritz.
I just wanted to make sure
I brought it up to you...
...before she said anything.
Okay.
Lois, you are always welcome here.
- Great.
I thought you were
pulling an all nighter.
Well, as much as I enjoy
a good dose of sleep deprivation...
...my deadline was pushed.
Nice.
Hello. Hi.
Oh, is everything all right?
Yeah, I'll be there as soon as I can.
- Who was that?
- That was Clark.
He said he needs to talk to me.
Seems really urgent.
I'll see you guys later.
So, lightning legs...
...got any other special skills?
- Well, l...
- I wanna know...
...everything you're capable of.
An S for Simone.
Ever since I was little, I dreamed
about my knight in shining armor.
And now that dream
has actually come true.
Take off your shirt.
Your turn.
Now, take off
the rest of your clothes.
Simone...
...with my powers...
...I could hurt you.
That's a chance I'm willing to take.
Make love to me, Clark.
Oh, God.
You don't care
about her anymore, Clark.
Go tell her that it's over.
Lana, wait.
This is why you couldn't
spend the night with me?
Lana, I've fallen in love
with someone else.
Mr. Luthor?
Welcome, Simone.
Don 't you look
delectable this evening.
Do I ever get to meet the billionaire
boy wonder face to face?
Well, as much as I'd like
to admire you up close and personal...
...I prefer to hold on to my free will.
How is your progress?
Let's just say Lana Lang
won 't be sending Clark...
... any more Valentine's Day cards.
And what about Clark?
Have you discovered anything
unusual about him?
Absolutely.
What is it?
Clark Kent is the most extraordinary...
... kisser.
There must be more.
If he had some secret,
don 't you think I would know?
With Clark Kent, what you see
is what you get. A corn-fed farm boy.
I've done everything
you've asked me to.
Now you can get the hell out
of my life and leave me alone.
Patience, Simone.
There's someone else
I'd like you to meet...
...in Honduras.
- No way. This was a one-time deal.
- Remember?
- Do you remember that I just...
...unearthed evidence that could put you
in prison for the rest of your life?
Now, I think the least you could do
is one more little favor for me.
I'll be back tomorrow night.
We'll talk then.
Sir, I have Roberts on the secure line.
Turns out Milton Fine
isn't who we think he is.
Oh, thank God you're fully clothed.
I was afraid I'd be walking in
on some sort of dangerous liaison.
I take it you talked to Lana.
I could barely hear her
through the sobs, but yeah.
She called to tell me that she was
spending the night at Aunt Nell's.
So where's the hottie?
If you're talking about Simone,
she's in the house.
I don't get it.
I mean, if it was Red K,
you wouldn't be doing chores.
If it was Silver K, you'd be afraid that
that pitchfork...
...was gonna turn you
into a shish kebab.
What happened to you, Clark?
I fell in love.
I don't think you fell.
I think you were pushed...
...off a cliff.
Chloe, just because you know my secret,
doesn't mean you know how I feel.
Yeah, but I do know that you'd never
intentionally hurt Lana like this.
You said my relationship with Lana
would never go anywhere...
...as long as I have to lie about
who I am. And you were right.
So how are things gonna be
any different with Simone?
I told Simone about my powers.
Wait a minute, Clark. You may think
you're madly in love with this girl...
...but you need to stay away.
- You don't even know her.
No, but I know you well enough
to know when you're being manipulated.
You're crossing a line here.
I've always trusted you.
So how about this time,
you trust me? Let me live my life.
Back off.
- Clark, is that you?
- Hi, you must be Simone.
I'm... I'm chloe. I'm clark's friend.
It's really great to finally meet you.
Hello.
I'm so glad that clark
hooked up with you.
I mean, he was just
miserable with Lana...
...and now, I honestly have never
seen him more happy.
You two are really
perfect for each other.
That's nice to hear.
- Do you know where he is?
- Yeah, he's in the barn.
Clark, I need you.
Clark?
I would have had tea and petits fours
waiting, but I didn't expect you so soon.
You knew I was coming.
You leave a trail of breadcrumbs,
no surprise when the crow comes calling.
I think a simple phone call
would have sufficed.
I couldn't reveal the truth
about myself until I was sure...
...you were dedicated to your cause.
- Well, I hate to disappoint you...
...but I already know what you are.
And it's not
a professor of history, is it?
No, it's something
much more exciting.
Tell me, what's the benefits package
of a government operative...
...working for a covert branch
of the State Department?
Very good.
You found that breadcrumb
on your own.
I want to know
what you were doing...
...posing as a college professor
in a Kansas farm town.
I was investigating the possibility
of an extraterrestrial presence.
This investigation...
...did it bear any fruit?
Well, we believe a spacecraft
of unknown origin...
...touched down during
the recent meteor shower.
But an individual
with quick reflexes and vast resources...
...was able to get to it
before we could.
So that's why you were
investigating LuthorCorp.
Yeah.
And I admire the remarkable advances
you've made in the name of science.
Too bad you couldn't get into
that ship when you had a chance.
You know where it is.
The ancient Mayans believed they were
visited by great beings from the heavens.
You think the ship's in Honduras.
Well, I'm certainly
not here for the coffee.
So I think clark's bizarre behavior might
be some form of supercharged hypnosis.
I've heard of hypnotism being used
to stop smoking or lose weight...
...but to reduce Clark to some
goo-goo-eyed love slave?
This isn't over-the-counter hypnosis,
it's prescription strength.
And it never wears off.
Check this out.
Simone's dad was world-renowned
for curing his patients of all inflictions...
...everything from cravings to cancer.
Maybe I can talk to him
about my nail-biting.
I'm afraid it's a little late for that.
Last month he died
during a botched burglary.
Wait a second, I've seen that jewel.
So have I, around Simone's
scrawny little neck.
It's an ancient family heirloom
that dates back...
...to the alchemists
in medieval England.
It was also the only thing stolen.
Are you saying Simone's responsible
for her own father's death?
I don't know. If it meant getting
daddy's hyper-hypno powers, maybe.
I just think it's a tad bit cocky to be
wearing it around your neck like a medal.
Not if you can make any cop
believe that you're innocent.
What I don't understand is,
of all people, why go after Clark?
I don't know.
We need to snap him
out of it soon...
...before he does something
he can't ever come back from.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's move.
Yeah, you know, l...
I just need to grab something.
- I'll meet you there.
- Okay.
His father carved it.
After claiming to have seen
a carroza de los dioses land from the sky.
- Chariot of the gods.
- Yeah.
I wanna talk to him.
I know you can do many things...
...but I'm not sure
you can communicate with the dead.
Days after the sighting, his wife
came home to find his charred remains.
Despite urban myths...
...human beings
don't spontaneously combust.
No.
We believe whoever or whatever was
in that spaceship incinerated the man.
In fact, we suspect this alien race
poses a grave threat to the entire planet.
Well, how do you defend against
a threat of that magnitude?
It presents a great challenge.
We are working on
a potential weapon...
...a weapon that would greatly benefit
from Luthorcorp's assistance.
We're well aware of your tireless quest
for extraterrestrial life.
Your tenacity is impressive.
I'll help in any way I can...
...but I want unrestricted access
to all your data.
- That's a bold request.
- Well, without it, this discussion is over.
I'm not sure
you understand me, Mr. Luthor.
If we don't work together,
there may not be a LuthorCorp...
...or a government left.
Think about that on your flight home.
Where you off to, Romeo?
- A motel with vibrating beds?
- Simone and I are going to California.
That way I can get away
from your commentary.
My running commentary says
you're hypnotized.
You need to drop your suitcase
because you're not going.
I'm asking you nicely, step aside.
Look, I didn't wanna have to do this...
...but if necessary,
I'm gonna have to take you down.
I see we have a visitor.
I suggest you turn your boy toy
back to normal...
...before I reach over and rip out
those pearly white teeth.
- Clark, be a love and knock her out.
- Yeah, right.
Oh, my God. What happened?
Mrs. Kent, I want you to do whatever
it takes to stop her from following us.
Where are you off to?
We're leaving Smallville forever.
And you couldn't be more thrilled.
You won't miss clark one bit.
Well then, you two
have a wonderful time.
Thanks, Mom.
- We better go.
- Okay. Bye.
Oh, and we have to make one quick
pit stop at the Luthor mansion.
- I need you to do me a favor.
- Whatever you need.
Clark, you're gonna kill Lex Luthor.
He's a dead man.
Mrs. Kent, what are you doing?
Stay right where you are.
Look, you're not yourself...
...so why don't you quit
the Calamity Jane impersonation...
...and drop the weapon.
I don't like it
any more than you do, Lois...
...but it's the only way
to keep you here.
Oh, my God,
I just knocked out Martha Kent.
Hello? The woman was about
to wallpaper her living room...
...with my brain matter.
- Right. Where's clark?
Well, while I was seeing stars,
I think his girlfriend...
...said she wanted to go
to the Luthor mansion or something.
So why don't you stay here
and keep Mrs. Kent...
Mrs. Kent?
Well, it's always nice to be
welcomed home after a trip...
...but I didn't expect to find you here.
Clark, you've been hypnotized.
How else could you throw me
across a room?
- I'm done with you, Lex.
- You're under Simone's control now.
The girl's a cold-blooded
murderer, Clark.
Your lies can't help you now.
Clark, before she wore that jewel,
she was nothing but a petty shoplifter.
Her dad never trusted her with the gem,
so she murdered him.
I have the whole thing
on surveillance tape.
You don't believe
a word he said, Clark.
My security's on the way.
Oh, I've met your security team.
I hope you don't mind,
I gave them all the day off.
Finish him off, Clark...
...and make him suffer.
- I'm sorry, clark.
- No. Chloe, no.
Lex! Kill her...
...and then kill yourself.
Are you all right, Clark?
I think so.
I feel like I woke up
from a bad dream...
...except I remember all the details.
Yeah. Did you and Simone
ever actually...?
- No. Thank God.
- Okay.
The moral of the story is never gaze
into the eyes of a seductive woman...
...wearing a gemstone
around her neck...
...unless, of course,
her name is Lana Lang.
Have you talked to her yet?
You guys kiss and make up?
- You haven't talked to her, have you?
- No.
What are you waiting for?
I mean, she knows
that you were hypnotized.
Every single one of us
has gone through...
...some sort of an identity crisis
at one point.
It's like a rite of passage in Smallville.
She'll understand.
Maybe I don't want her to understand.
See, as horrible as all this was...
...it did accomplish one thing
that I didn't have the guts to do myself.
It broke me and Lana up.
What? Wait a minute.
Are you still hypno'd?
Chloe, how many times can I break
someone's heart before it crumbles?
Yeah, but it wasn't your fault.
- You were hypnotized.
- Lana wasn't.
Chloe, her feelings were real.
The look of pain in her eye
when she walked in on Simone and I...
...it made me realize that
my power to hurt Lana...
...is stronger than all my powers
put together.
Meeting a girl with hocus-pocus jewelry
isn't an everyday occurrence.
Yeah, but hurting Lana
has become one.
And as long as I have to lie to her about
who I am, I'm gonna cause her pain.
And as long as you don't set the record
straight, she's gonna hate you.
Maybe that's not such a bad thing.
Maybe it'll help her move on,
forget I ever existed...
...and find someone who can
give her what she deserves.
You just need to know
that if you do this...
...that's it, game over,
there's no more quarters left.
I mean, you're saying
goodbye forever.
It will crush her, Clark.
Please just think long and hard
before you end this for good.
I've climbed these stairs
so many times before...
...why do they seem steeper
than ever?
Thanks for coming,
I didn't wanna bother you at school.
Clark, you can spare me the speech
about how sorry you are.
I know you were hypnotized...
...and I know that you weren't in control
of your actions.
I need to be honest with you.
That would be refreshing.
I don't know any other way to say it...
...but the truth is...
...my feelings for you have changed.
Clark, I want you
to look me in the eye...
...and tell me that you don't love me.
I don't love you.
I have waited for you to grow up...
...to get over whatever
hang-ups you may have.
I never meant to hurt you.
I don't want another
Clark Kent apology.
It's over.
Forever.
We need more samples.
How did she take it?
I've never seen her so hurt...
...so angry.
Saying those words was
the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
You're an adult now, clark...
...in an adult relationship...
...and they rarely end
the way we want them to.
You know, I just didn't know
what else to do.
It was either make a clean break...
...or tell her my secret.
- Yeah.
I know you didn't tell Lana the truth
because you wanted to protect her...
...but maybe there was
actually more to it.
What do you mean?
Do you think you didn't tell her
because maybe deep down...
...you didn't think she was the one?
- Mom, I'll always love Lana.
- I know.
That's why you did this.
But you didn't just
break her heart, Clark...
...you gave her reason to hate you.
I just hope her anger doesn't drive her
to do something we'll all regret.
Oh, just the woman I wanted to see.
So it turns out everybody's
favorite academic, Milton Fine...
...isn't a professor at all.
Lex, I'm not here
to talk about Milton Fine.
I actually wanted you
to be the first to know.
Is everything okay?
Clark and I broke up.
For real.
- Lana, I'm... I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay. Don't be.
I actually do feel like
a hundred tons of secrets and lies...
...have been lifted off my shoulders.
You know what it's like
being friends with Clark.
No matter what he tells you,
you don't know if it's the truth.
You can never trust him.
Lana...
...I know clark's probably not the easiest
guy to be in a relationship with.
I don't think he... He means...
Please don't defend him, Lex.
How could I have been so stupid?
You're not stupid.
You just put your trust
in the wrong person.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
www.tvsubtitles.net