Vodka on the rocks.
Then, Lord ...
Is Kawakami?
If you do not mind me say,
I like you more with s mustache.
Yes, the old hated it.
Deca-to picaba.
Women.
Sorry.
This seems to milk.
In fact, the use
of a letter .
It is good for you.
Will give you strong bones
and an amazing buzz.
Now and again bela © ba
in six years.
Okay, please do not Echesa me.
I need to stay.
© Settlement an appointment for my mom
with my boxing coach.
It's perfect for her.
This event takes a year of production n.
Agreed. You have my attention n.
He lied. Utility brokers ©
y os deceptive.
He kept everything hidden.
My mom will kill me if I knew!
What I'm doing.
Sold.
I like your way of working,
Mr. Kawakami.
Let's see if we can find
a good seat.
√ â l are giving him
a bite of his dinner.
It'sa good sign to, cierto?
- A holder of whom n
- On √ © l.
- But you are fueling it.
- Ka-Ching!
Trevor!
Why should a teen
my office?
I imagine that you wont ©
sitting on the bar.
My mom! Is on a blind date.
The're spying.
I see.
N things are accelerating.
S I need you behind the bar.
Come on.  Can you cover me?
Marshall worked much
to find the perfect
for her mom!.
What is perfect for this guy?
She manages a station of n
n television public. √ â l trains boxing.
© rdame recover again why
this guy is perfect for your mom!?
She chose .
There was a catalog.
Is there a catalog of types?
Even Saturday it was an option n.
Catalog of the sperm bank.
My mom do not know it,
but that there -
that's my dad!.
Okay then.
. :: WWw.Subs-Team.Tv::.
P r e s e n t
A Translation of: Chuchi,
dulinnor and Iriel.
Sync : Chuchi and Iriel.
N Correction: Iriel.
Cupid - S01E03
The Great Right Hope
I am a hacker.
Get into the archives of the bank
sperm was cake.
Get the name of Clint,
© look at what Google,
Found © was owner or a gym.
Finger-to want-to learn to box
- ... Well pruned to meet my dad!.
-  And she has no idea?
Are you kidding?
My mom it's a total pacifist.
No. To find your dad!.
No. No way, dude.
It is really sensible for her ability
to criarme alone.
Bueno, ndo paneas four deca-rselo?
Does my deathbed?  Is your deathbed?
Still not decided.
I suppose that if it works, I can
mention the toast of the wedding.
Something is amiss.
Come on.
Hey. What happens ?
The guy said it was a Republican.
The woman began to rear  I feel
I was joking.
- Y √ © l told him no.
- Clint is a Republican?
It was put in all this GITMO.
Then she uses the expression ,
which I will not use
in front of the child,
but I'll say the same thing
Felix whenever you get
in my personal affairs.
If I'm thinking,
is not particularly friendly.
Well. N The passion is good.
No, you do not understand.
My mom it's a hard leftist.
Are you saying that your mother s leave
go to their type soa ± ado by the policy?
It is exactly what I'm saying.
The pair are convicted.
Trevor, Why have
a teenager with you?
Who n √ © l
This is my nia ± o internally.
© not only how they got .
I'm a little mad.
Trevor --
Can we dispense
premilinares games?
Marshall's mother is too  crater. They are in
a date with this great guy, ok?
They are doing awesome.
It turns out that he is √ © republicano.
Boom - She walks out the door.
I do not understand.  other crate,
Republican to whom No le importa?
Opinions policies are topics
essential for many people.
When you make a relationship n
is work hard, so
Why start with a
preclude a gigantic ass?
they may end up
with a wonderful thing.
- Sorry. I can cut?
- Of course. Please.
My parents were in extreme
opposites in the spectrum policy.
For 40 years,
nullified the votes of the other,
- But had a great marriage.
- How do you drive?
They found something that mattered
s most passionately
the Polish case. The Yankees.
What s more to love your mom! And Clint?
Seriously, Trevor, is bad enough
to get in adulthood
couples when your arms,
but involve a nia ± o?
A teenager who wants
his mother Be happy.
Look, this is not just about what more
armando my couples.
It's what your people
Call-a "Mitzvah".
I'm not-a darkness.
- Marshall is the one that began it all.
- So that according  l √ © quoted.
It's adorable, no?
I call him "Mini-Cupid."
Got it. His other great passion N
is the wine.
Mama, do not expect.
And your luggage.
It's nice to see you again, guys.
- Looks like it was yesterday.
- It ended with Hector.
The flamenco dance-n?
That was Ronaldo.
Hector is a playwright.
An undiscovered genius.
Are not always discovered,
and if you managed
to find them.
I do not think that can continue.
S√ © it feels as if your world
was to end now,
but we'll overcome.
I do not want it.
Love my bones.
© Bring your suitcases.
Hello.  Are you Hallie?
Yes.
I'm Trevor Pierce of WNYD.
Congratulations.
earn a pass for the American premiere
Beaujolais this year o.
Really?
I mean, I always go for moral --
But not a contest ©,
so that how to --
There was a competition will test.
were asked to participants
write about someone
to believe that you deserve it.
- Your child  wrote about you.
- Are Marshall's essay won ?
In additional to degustaci√
n also receive this.
Is that your son?
For the test, did not give the impression n
to be so full ... of life.
In fact, he lost a   amount of weight.
- I have to bring a better picture.
- Yes, I was a little thick nia ± o.
I mean, all that decline was an angelic,
but I did not speak to sab√an
my cheerful behavior.
- What causes the change
-  find a yoga class.
It's amazing.
It has been completely transformed.
I mean, it's safe now.
Sociable.
It is even better at school,
except chemical.
But we are talking
looking for a tutor.
- Sorry. I bored.
- No, I understand completely.
Nothing more than a happy father s
see what your child does well.
S√  I'm going to the Regency Hotel Chase
Thursday at 8:00?
In fact, the station n
will need a photo.
So that if it can be in this direction n
one hour before the event.
Not even you Quito
pajamas today?
I have to put the
to-day with "I Love Lucy."
Do you know why all
love Lucy?
Because everything you do for love.
No, all it does Lucy
is ego and insecurity.
No consideration has n  by
the life of Ricky
or hard work and talent
it took to get AHA.
Why are so tense s, Claire?
No s√ ©, Mom!, But I have
a slight suspicion
that may change
When you go home.
I have no home.
Without the bones of Hector,
yes, I understand.
No, leave it © Hector goes
my apartment forever.
Mama, do not give your adult
apartments to their ex-boyfriends.
∫ Perhaps you may speak with-as √ © l.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Only hopefully the other winners,
and photo  grafo.
- Be here in a minute.
- Great. I am so excited.
Well, in most e-con -
This will be much better
than I expected.
Oh, God, or more.
What's interesting?
Mom?
Are you sure it was s yoga
what we did lose weight?
So-Is that all this time I thought
you were taking classes
yoga, have you been here?
I thought not let me do that, you know,
so feel the violence.
Not that you were
Cambodia bombing.
Do I love boxing? No.
But it is a sport.
S but no more lies,
or arm pairs.
All I did was show Ginny
Biography and a picture of Clint
Web site gym,
then leap like a cat
and said that if no sal√as
√ © l with, she will.
And degustaci√   wine?
That was in large part to Trevor.
Does not work at a station of radio.
It is my tutor. Besides working in s
bar that you like, Tres Equis.
As I can see that
make things work between You and Clint.
Dear, Clint is a man
great, really.
But we have fundamental disagreements.
Is a Republican, and what have you?
It's like someone says,
"Aha, you are the best portions of pizza ,
© but sneezes on her. "
No matter what is so perfect
if you are covered by a sneeze.
Marshall, Do you let a minute?
What happened ?
Abama supon√a we are a
found at degustaci√ up of wines.
Novato.
Look, you are Rocky, I'm Mickey.
- I want to catch the hen.
- What?
Con-a-more, NIA ± o. S√ © exactly
what I'm doing.
I suppose that if I used the
entrance me Marshall
for wine degustaci√ ,
we hubi√ © ramos found.
Perde will by all this.
Apparently, my son is
Metiches a secret.
Sometimes it gets a bit ...
Too excited?
- It is one of his best qualities.
- True.
Marshall is a guy in-ble.
S√ © that whatever you do,
comes from a good place.
Wanted to say what
s the same for most people.
So, What are we going to do
n  degustaci√ with this wine?
So that, Clint, Marshall told me to
das classes Boxing Free
for children from poor areas.
I told you exactly that.
Think what will life
Clint without these guys:
Drogas, armas... pelea de perros?
Too.
Well, that was a good spectator! Ass.
- Although you do is admirable.
- No deal.
Sabes, producimos un pequeÒo segmento
de "HÈroes de la comunidad"
No station in the PSB for the job.
Your work in the gym would be
a very good piece.
I'm very flattered, but the
I really do not have the rite methods.
At least he'll think s?
Do not leave me n entrar.
Apparently, I am not enough
great wine to spit in a bucket.
Well, must go home-owners alike.
And to prove the missing Chateau 2005
de Chinon Les Coulaine Picasso?
I will never forgive you.
Go to mob and drink.
Wait here with the © ny ± o.
I come from a long, distinguished line -
de entusiastas de cerveza de una lata.
You know, even I was interested in wine
Pela-when I saw the film "Sideways"
and all that thinking was pruning
"God Mao, please! llense comfortable."
And then I had my first cup
the Russian River Valley Barbera
© and found myself using
the word "mellow."
CAA is a field-day.
Why the hell is still moving?
I will go on the other side.
Trevor, What you doing?
-  "Mirone is a word?
- No.
Well, then I'm not doing that.
Hello. I'm Liv.
I am the mother of Claire.
Is Claire's mother?
Really?
- You must have many stories.
- Trevor.
If you do not mind me say,
his daughter is beautiful increased substantially,
- But it really is a bother.
- I see you know very well.
As the palm of your smart
sexy and critical hand.
I think you found a good, Claire.
Not Found ©. Not me-o.
Never me
none of their boyfriends.
Not my boyfriend.
Estamos distanciados.
- Are not alienated.
- En serio? What you gonna do then?
Well, I can always get
a room, my dear.
It's fine with us, Mom!.
- I know Trevor's work.
- Oh, I see.
- Your secrets are safe with me.
- Thanks.
No, no n ∫ ning secret.
It FICCI .
Es tan lindo ver que finalmente
tienes quÌmica con alguien.
- No what-mica.
- See you down, Claire,
and if they end up in the apartment,
just leave it a socks-n at the door.
It is not my fault that we have what-mica.
I'm surprised you've agreed to
go out with me first.
Not the kind of person who
is a blind date.
Well, I have a bit of the
effect of wine,
© so that will be honest.
I made this computer dating thing
makes a lot simo-time
And when you saw full
questionnaire
ba naming physically
all qualities
the person s who are looking for?
Well, when you describe Ginny-a,
was like going ticking
all my answers.
Except for the part of Republican.
Surprisingly, the policy
I never pass through the mind.
That is surprising.
Insurance had ceased
to one of ours.
Definitely. A role,
all the right answers
was immediately terminated
with the word "Republican."
A√ ∫ n, here are s-,
and I am thinking of
all the right answers.
I can not believe that you
want to join, Trevor.
She chose a time
in a folder full of donors.
Wait, Are you telling me that you are s
coupled to Hallie
with the parent donor
sperm of her son?
Lo s√ ©. Is a breeze.
Sometimes I feel that I am the
ero dating companions of destiny.
Trevor, you gotta see this.
Hey, in case you wonder,
the sound beam going from one side
to the other by the last hours
- Is indeed disturbing.
- So, is as animal feed.
Can you try to sit
into a block of more rmol
- And put your hand in mind
- Marshal said that his mother and Clint
have been watching every night
for two weeks.
- Everything is great.
- So skilled is the problem?
The account has not moved.
It has been well for weeks.
- No account Hallie-Clint.
- Wait.
Only ... I think I can solve it for you.
How about just ...
The account will not move until the
gods decide that it is true love.
You know that I am not
answer for that?
Four l do not understand is the problem.
So, Marshall said that
the policy ever arose .
You have to know
friends and family of the other?
I think not.
That may-be.
A√ ∫ n remain in the cocoon.
To be a partner
have to live in the real world.
So if I were not in
the gym, d√ de shall?
Not  s√ ©. This gym
is a house for me.
Okay, you are right.
We got it.
- Thanks.
- Thanks, James.
- Something you need more s, Damelo.
- Okay.
- How do you feel loved?
- Por n whom, James?
I cut-throat
if you look at askance.
That is true, white.
He said that he let you stay
- When his father came out of imprisonment .
- S√  were a couple of weeks.
Are you ready to go! S something for dinner?
Yes, we have to Tres Equis passes.
Marshall sent me a message.
Leave  geometr√a Hence his book.
Is should be concerned if my son
passes the time in a bar?
Hello.
Hallie! Clint!
What can I serve you?
In fact we go to find the book
mathematical characteristics of my son at the bar,
but I guess it is pretty quiet
here to do homework, no?
They are pretty quiet tonight.
Fiesta private.
Are you sure you do not want to drink?
No.
s take something for your cumplea√ ± os?
Not until my cumplea√ ± os
within six weeks.
This is Inca way.
What is it?
Sorpresa!
God-or more.
These are all people I know,
and some people who do not.
So you do not know my neighbor Phil,
my companions ero bedroom
the university,
or my brothers?
So what you think?
Surprised?
Yes, I think our
brother tena no reason
You are extremely great
to be liberal.
And if you start to drink coffee soy s
and drive a car that works
C√ scara with eggs and garbage,
maybe have a problem.
- You seem a very intelligent.
- Thanks.
- How can you be a Republican?
- I think what he means is that
people who are educated
about certain topics,
others end up being  crater.
Tra tion history, the
truth. Was  other crater.
Then in a car accident,
I had a head injury.
Since then I've been thinking
in a small government
and strong military.
I was kidding, sign pray.
∫ lpenme Disc.
Can I ask you borrowed for a minute?
Of course.
- This is a disaster.
- Okay.
Seriously, that is, were you raised
in a different home
your siblings?
How are you so different?
- I am not so different.
- The downfall as a compliment.
Is Insulting my brothers is a compliment?
Mira, lo siento, s√-?
- I was nervous.
- Well, it's part of its charm.
- Prego ∫ ntal to their former wives.
- But honestly
Is Almost six years after s
de "No Mission Accomplished"?
How can we continue to believe that
Iraq war was good idea?
Not s√ ©.
Why was a good idea?
You know, yes, mistakes were made --
Really believe that?
I think there are bad people out
and have to handle that.
So we need to bombard all
those who do things we do not like?
Well, you can not reason with a madman.
- You have to take the fight.
- True, I forgot ©.
Diplomacy, the bulwark of
the Western civilization ,
nia ± as is.
Yes, I'm not sure
what is a good idea.
Tena-by that was done.
We need to remove them from the cocoon.
We're taking
the real world to them.
Yes, well, maybe it is
too real world.
Hallie  ? Marshall College
l√-nea in 2.
Hallie Butler.
What was what?
What possessed you to
hitting another kid?
I get tired of that goal ©
me all day.
- One guy can not get much.
- We went through this.
Try to speak to the teacher or flames.
Talking does not work, and I have to say
how Clint was
s much more rewarding.
Is Clint?
He said that if that kid
bothering to safety,
put your ass on the floor.
That's what I did.
Did you tell my son that
hit another kid?
Chico? The guy who got
Marshal to have beards.
Was willing to accept the boxing
but attacking another
kid is not acceptable.
It was getting into with Marshal.
Tena-to learn to defend themselves.
- It's not your decision n. I am the mother.
- Perhaps you are the mother
but never were a boy 15 years.
Sorry, but "calling the teacher" no
solves this particular problem.
So you know better than me what is
better for Marshall that his mother?
In this case, yes.
Violence as a solution n.
Qu√ © republican of you.
Perhaps we should act as  other crater
to kill will give milk and cookies,
talk about their feelings.
- We have finished.
-  You think?
Come on. Ended up here.
- Come on, Marshall.
- You have to consider another option n.
Do Tell Mom that Clint es mi papa?
T√ ∫ I want to be
clean breast of the pond!
- In the middle of the floor?
- Do not you understand?
That thing they care
s most passionately
that the Polish policy is not the wine, my friend.
Eres t√ ∫.
Marshall! Come on.
Hey.
Hi, Marshall.
How was your day-to?
A little recreation
task with popcorn?
The guy has it already?
Only a couple of hours to complete
Marat will the war
24 hours of silence.
Can you do it?
Ladies and gentlemen, is a record
the boy in the kitchen from hell!
Two cups?
Okay, I understand.
Are you mad at me because s
no te dejo box.
You know, maybe you should consider
be passive aggressive
instead of hitting a
that kid at school.
You are very good at it too n.
Marshall, go.
Let's talk about this,-s√?
Only you say something.
Anything?
I think Dick Cheney is a bad blow.
Mr. Roberts, we have already exceeded that.
You're broke. It is not invisible.
Now he feels s√ ©
that people ignore
being bare, but that's --
Dr. McCrae, his mother are here.
- You will have to wait.
- Really need it.
- Mam·, What happens?
- Steals © its umbrella.
Well, here are s-.
Apparently, owners of bars os
giving good advice, it is not true.
Felix told me to pull tena
Hallie to Clint and his cocoon.
A total disaster. I need your help.
Liv, What happens?
- What did Claire
- I went to the apartment of my lover.
Your apartment is, mamma!,
And it's your ex-love --
Do not hab√amos agreed
to use the term "boyfriend"?
- D√ © jala talk, Claire.
- Thank you, Trevor.
© AHA-I stayed outside his door,
ready to tell Hector,
but our love was not dark,
- We must move forward.
- Why? The guy sounds perfect.
- Trevor.
- It's a drug addict, Trevor.
- Well, OK, that's different.
- It's a drug addict,
I am drugs.
If this is a goal! Fora,
I am going back to "play."
- Mam·, the umbrella.
- S√ © what you say:
that may never finish his masterpiece
because you can not take
the hands of his muse.
That is not going to say,
Not at all.
I saw her leaning umbrella Hence,
next to the door,
even n h√ ∫ medo on his morning walk.
- Tena who possess it.
- I think that's beautiful.
Mr. Roberts, I can see it.
Please remedy espa ©
in my office.
© then come back,
I promise.
Is Mr. Robert-you are here?
D√ de?
Wherever it © s, friend
te or strange, as all
B Wing boys!
Okay, what do you know
all need here?
A good dose of reality.
Mr. Roberts, the reason for which n
Diane Sawyer never took the rose
-you hold on to
the barricade GMA
because she was not
could not "see it".
Cancer , with you or without you, Hector drgadicta s
finish his masterpiece.
And Trevor, your partners drgadicta s
n be affected if their
can not survive
in the real world.
n Is everyone clear now?
Excellent.
Mr. Roberts,
go back to work.
Trevor, come back to this s more
afternoon. Cancer , I will post ©
around the issue of Hector, as
both sab√amos that finally will.
Really mad at my daughter,
-as saba what?
Way home, I had another idea
that I have in mind.
© s√ far, in Canada,
There are no Republicans
or other crater.
What think
the reubicaci√ ?
Yes, of course, it will be.
Mom?
First the lies,
now challenged ndome completely?
You know very well that no
must be-as here.
- What not?
- Sorry, not a Saturday.
Marshall just said
that I had not been able to come.
- Come on, Clint, follow.
- Marshall. Hey, buddy, come on.
Marshall, stop.
Low immediately.
- We're going home.
- T√ ∫ do not want to go out with Clint
basa! ndote something as
∫ I ask is as policy,
This choice is t√ ∫ n, but can not
© prevent further via Ndolo.
Sure I can.
I am your mother.
Yes.
Well ...
√ â l es mi father.
What say, dad
boxeando Can I continue?
What you just said, Marshall?
© The tracking,  right?
© find the name of the agency
in your files,
and me in your database.
Defamation was not so easy.
Clint ...
Is this ... possible?
D√ de has ...
Have you ever ...
S suppose you are waiting for
a pension .
S√  Quero-to know what my dad!.
The first time I came,
tell me more like
if you were a great fool,
s√  seguir√a it my way
and forget that once-a
te investigu√ ©.
But you were.
Changed my life.
Marshall, your mother!.
Mama!
How is everything?
Are you reacting?
They are more quiet s,
but was defamation cyl.
©  Spend three hours last
trying to convince
© does not try to find my father
me because she has failed.
S√   discussed what to do.
Have you talked to her
about Clint?
This is not the time, Trevor.
Understand, speak morning.
Adia  s.
It sounds as if the truth came to light ?
Con-a-more.
It's the best.
Lo s√ ©, but so far
is not the desired effect.
© I think I will have to take the floor.
Hey, of course,
it was quite nice
receive your call today.
I mean, it is a beginning,
∫ t√ © ndome asked a favor.
Now just to clarify what, where
Hector this answer the door
- Do you want noquee
- No, just what I want to be sure.
© called him yesterday and he was sharp when
Suggest that it was time to move.
Only what the date next to me and tries to
s see more like God of War
that the God of Love
Mu√ © stralen your face cruel.
Y s√ © careful.
If my mother was creative as possible
Hector in your life this past
habr√a been a samurai without honor.
Apparently, even
talk to the wind.
Have your delirious patient
ndote helped with your crazy mother.
I think
it is a. ..
Not only © mature alga d√ ∫ n-a.
View the world as it is.
Sees the world full of love and beauty.
Sees the best in people.
What is wrong with that?
- Es-sta ego√.
- Ego√-sta? How can it be?
Put your heart on your sleeve N
y wounded.
So, Who think n then
to collect side?
He leaves his daughter, 16 years to ndose ©
by her younger sister,
As she goes behind a s
glass blower in Peru.
"It's a great teacher, Claire."
© The look, Trevor.
There is a great teacher
glass blower.
No response.
Maybe I took seriously
y  moves by SA alone.
Much better than advertised.
Hector, Who  plays the
...puerta?
You have ten minutes to
pick your stuff.
S After this, call the police-© a
and decide whom they n
entered without authorization n.
Hello.
So that in the last 19 hours,
I have been trying to order
my feelings,
and that is what insurance s√ ©.
Mostly what I feel
is happy-a.
I felt this connection n
with Marshall
from the day-to entered
gym.
So I am asking are s
if you can continue to see Marshall?
Yes.
But these are also n.
I think we must give-amos
another chance.
We will break the heart-amos n
a Marshall
if we tried and it does not work.
You know, I try to instill this
attitude in kids
who train with me.
Nothing worth having
been easy.
Marshall came to my gym
22 kilos overweight.
And there were day-as it was
soaked in sweat
and pressed so hard,
I thought that not volver√a
the next day.
But he kept coming.
We had a chance,
and throw in the towel.
We owe it to Marshall
a real effort.
Realmente No matter whom we vote for?
Hallie  ? It's school
Marshall again. L√-nea three.
Hallie Butler.
No, I understand. Of course.
© it-there will be more s soon as possible.
Marshall got into another fight.
Apparently, the other guy
involved need points
by the cut above his eye.
You know, this is not my son who was
before you know, Clint,
d√ © jame so that very clear.
There is no possibility of
our thing happens,
and when you see a
a Marshall again
I am not sure that your
influence has been good for √ © l.
This ends, Marshall.
It ends now.
I mean, What possessed you to
get into another fight?
I do not want to talk about it.
That is the fag that gave you a beating?
Now I see the day her son was nfrom
wonderful manners.
Mama, come on.
If you did this to you, maybe not
be the only who is gay.
You know, not that it matters,
but my son is not gay.
© rtelo not feel I had said before,
but come on, have you never
you cross through the mind?
Yes, I shall cross.
You know that I will love and support
- No matter what, huh
- My mom liberal?
I probably won some points.
I am a badge of honor.
I think I understand.
Boxing ... fighting,
No I do not even like it but I understand.
Clint said that they are just a couple of
fights, leaving n getting me.
I go 2 to 0.
Is Clint knows the reason for the n
that get you?
I know long ago.
It has been great with that.
s Are you angry?
Yes.
Me.
Comet-a grave error.
© How to stop a man like Clint?
Sabaa that Marshall was gay.
treats him like a son.
So, I do not mind whom to vote No. I ...
You know, this is the kind of man who
want on the life of Marshall.
- In my life. It is the only type -
- Stop, stop.
Do not spend all that strong passion in me-n.
Not that there's a small
Clint fly on the wall.
But not my address! Called.
That is all I want, and you lose.
Perhaps you've lost by
now, but ... Marshall no.
S shall not in mood to make a
perfectly ingenious plan, o s√?
Hello.
- D√ de are?
- D√ de whom are n?
- Marshall. -You said you want to see me.
- Surely only.
Called me and said,
"Marshall wants to see.
Can you come to the bar?"
Do you see what I did AHA-?
I'm so smart for.
Always something up his sleeve.
Makes you wonder what
I'm going to make a continuation .
Way #  by these streets ©
© before walking #
Quer-I think that Marshall is here-© s
to see the world premiere of the work
of your mother at your gym.
My son- sell drugs on the corner.
My son was in a gang.
Boxing gives my child a place
to release their anger.
Trinity Boxing Club gave me
a son d√ de to go.
Clint Wilson  is more that s
a simple coach.
is a mentor.
is a father figure.
Clint  is the white knight
our family.
I am a single mother,
and however much I like
I can think to do everything,
I can not.
So thank God that you
you have people
Clint Wilson  as to fill
the holes.
I can not imagine life
without my son √ © l.
I can not imagine my life without √ © l.
A√ ∫ n n are working on √ © l.
I think it hastened a little production,
but I think that is what you can
call a "Tribute to Love."
I will look for Hallie.
Your account are paid.
Sorry, but where I come from,
men do not let the
women buy them drinks.
Come the years 50?
You look good.
Thank you. All my Bible about
fighting and carrying weapons
keeps me young.
While at my age working long hours
I pay less than a man
who does the same job.
You're all I ever
wanted in a man,
and not a thing.
Prego four ntame ∫ nt me that thing.
Do you care Cu· nt -?
What I said?
They are the perfect match.
Yes. © Not only if you can provide
with Roy Rogers, but ...
©  Salut.
So seriously think
you're Cupid, no?
Yes.
What makes you so nervous
what is so good at this?
Well, the good side
you're so strict
which is exactly when s√ ©
'll get home.
- Hiciste dinner?
- Not acting is so very strange.
No, I'm just surprised and excited
that requires covered
and you do not
I sit on the floor and
eat lentils with my fingers.
You know, I was very close
to et√ope food.
Trevor reason to tena-n again.
Trevor?
Please tell me that it was
a cork out
a bottle of wine on their own.
- Vaya! It's like a machine.
- What you do here?
Is Coming to class?
After s that were very direct
me in your office,
Trevor and I started to speak,
y © invites to dinner.
I have been lifting the √ nimo.
Perhaps you do not know this,
but I am a ball of sunshine.
You do not have to be bad, mama!,
© Hector because he spoke with,
and it will move.
Well, not to worry-as tena.
He was about to go talk
√ © l with myself.
Lo s√ ©, but was in the neighborhood
and I thought that I look at it.
Well, How was I?
He feels things very deeply.
Was ... destroyed.
And it is obvious that n still loves you.
But I had not said anything that
I would like more t√ ∫ s that you are happy.
You see, Claire?
That is love.
Claire is slow, but
understands it.
Know what is love.
I have never been so sure of that
until this very moment.
Disc lpenme ∫.
Hola?
Hello.
s Are you kidding?
Of course.
© be there in 20 minutes.
Stop. You can wait that long.
Derek wants to be
me to drink.
No matter, verdad?
We know it today in Whole Foods.
It's like a young Julia Raa ∫ l.
In this darkness,
you have to feel those eyes
as if you had seen in another life.
It was an instant connection n nea.
Maybe come back with √ © l for dessert.
What's going to want
tu mama knows the truth?
I think it is time to accept the fact
this is the truth for her.
In other words, is as well.
Do you want wine with your meal or -?
You're not staying.
You're a horrible host.
Good evening, Trevor.
But you are a wonderful daughter.
Thank you.
So, Trevor,
How was your day-to?
Yes, was, you know, my kind of day-a.
You know, I'm thrilled by © ...
. :: WWw.Subs-Team.Tv::.
P resent √