Here's what you need to know.
You remember Kate Farrell,
Huey's widow?
How'd you get naked photos
of her?
She asked Tommy to have
his wake at The Firecracker.
A little awkward,
seeing as Tommy did kill Huey.
But Tommy had bigger problems.
Like Huey's brother, Dokey,
who thought Jimmy killed Huey.
Actually, Jimmy killed
Louie the bookie.
And since no bookie
means no money
for Louie's boss, Nicky,
Tommy has to make up
the difference every week.
Did I mention Sean was
still in the hospital?
He was getting a little TLC
from Kim,
or at least until
his mom showed up.
But that's not the point.
Back to Tommy.
See, there was nothing
Tommy wanted more than Jenny.
But after what Tommy
did to Huey,
Jenny decided to want
something else
and chose a delivery guy,
Samson,
and right in front of Tommy.
Now that had to hurt.
I'm not lying.
Joey, you're pathological.
Hey, that's not very nice.
You believe that what
you're telling me is true?
I need to understand this,
Joey,
in order to continue
your therapy.
If I'm pathological,
every guy in my neighborhood's
a clinical study.
Let's try starting
with one truth.
Little steps.
Sean Donnelly,
was he in the hospital?
Yes, he was.
Well, see?
That wasn't so hard,
was it?
Actually, he was leaving
the hospital.
Hey, Seanie.
Let's get going.
Quit rushing me.
I'm late for class,
and I already missed
three days.
Big deal.
Kind of a big deal, Sean.
Would you leave me alone?
I'm sick.
You're not sick.
I'm injured.
Let's go, come on!
Stop it!
Tommy, go and get
the paperwork
I need to sign.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
It's that girl, Kim.
I don't want to talk
to anybody.
What's the matter, Seanie?
Nothing.
Look at me, Sean.
I want you to go
back to school.
That's Tommy, Ma.
I was no good at school.
Because you didn't try.
This time
I'm gonna make you.
Because this is never gonna
happen to you again.
JOEY. Even someone as good
as Jenny Reilly
couldn't start the day
without lying.
Hey.
Hi.
I was just gonna
write you a note.
Really?
It looks like you were gonna
sneak out on me.
No. I didn't wanna wake you.
Well, Jenny, I was joking.
I mean,
unless you really were.
Were you?
JOEY. But then,
is it really a lie
if you're trying to spare
someone's feelings?
I just have to get to work.
It's okay,
I'll walk you out.
JENNY: No, no, don't get up.
I'm sorry, Samson.
This was wrong, and...
You are such a sweet guy
and last night I thought
I could do this,
but I'm still stuck.
There's someone else.
That's fine.
It is?
I mean, if you're not ready,
you're not ready,
so I could just
leave the ball in your court.
Yeah. Thanks.
Of course,
I'll be hoping you call.
Don't.
(TRAIN RUMBLING PAST)
JOEY: Hello?
Who's that?
Jimmy?
What are you doing?
This is a bar,
not a place to sleep.
I was just resting my eyes.
Want some wine?
Are you nuts?
There's an alien
inside my head.
You're a wuss.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
What is that?
Somebody's cell phone.
Where's it coming from?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Over there.
Hello? Damn it. Hung up.
What were you gonna say?
"Hi, I don't know
whose phone this is?"
I know whose phone it is,
it's Louie Downtown's.
You think he dropped it
when you had him tied up
down here?
When who had who
tied up down where?
No idea.
I'll get the bags
in the back, Mom.
What do we owe you?
Let's try this again, huh?
Go back out the door,
and make a right,
two buildings up.
Two buildings up.
Thank you. You're very nice.
At least I'm not lost.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Hey, Tommy.
Nice to see little Seanie
up and about.
What the hell
are you doing here?
It's payday.
You got my money?
I told you already,
you're not getting any money.
See, that's what
you don't know yet.
I am gonna get my money.
By midnight tonight.
And you're the one
that's gonna be
giving it to me.
Don't get near my mother
or anyone in my family again,
you understand me?
The way to avoid that
is to pay me my money.
You come here again,
I'll kill you.
You know where to find me,
kid.
Just bring
a handful of cash.
(GUNSHO TS)
HELEN: What took you?
Just giving that guy
directions.
To two doors down?
He was all confused.
Kevin, come here a minute.
I'm eating my cereal.
What, is it gonna get cold?
Soggy. I hate that.
Kevin...
Nicky wants the money.
And he's not taking no
for an answer.
So?
You already told him
you weren't gonna pay him
and nothing happened.
Because it wasn't due
until today.
He was talking to Ma
in the hall.
He touches Ma, he's dead.
We can't kill him.
Why not?
We kill Nicky,
this whole thing unravels.
Louie Downtown, Huey, Sal,
everything.
They'll find out about
all of it.
So you got a better idea?
I'm gonna get the money.
How you gonna do that?
I got a way.
JOEY. Tommy didn't have a way.
But that's the thing
about a lie.
Sometimes you gotta tell one
until you come up
with something better.
I'll see you soon.
Where you going?
TOMMY: School.
Stay with Mom.
Don't let her
out of your sight.
Can't Sean do that?
Can't Sean do what?
Sean just got out
of the hospital.
Well, he looks okay to me.
Hey, I'm right here.
What are you guys
talking about?
Huey, the Italians, what?
'Cause I know everything,
so what are we doing?
We're not doing anything.
Ma goes anywhere,
you go, too.
Twenty-three AR with missiles.
What do you think that means?
Don't know.
What about B32 Colts. Fifty X.
I don't know
about the numbers,
but Colts gotta be
football Colts, right?
Right. Some guy named B32
bet on the Colts.
There's a whole bunch of them
on here.
PA31, JR32,
and it goes on like that.
You think Louie's got
his whole book in there?
I do think that.
I think half the bets on here
gotta be losers.
Probably more.
Too bad Louie's not around
to collect.
Get Kevin down here.
Let's figure this thing out.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello? What?
No, I can't.
Because I can't.
Look, tell Jimmy
if he needs my help,
he's gotta come over here.
What?
Hey! Hey, Tommy,
how you doing?
I'm great.
How you doing?
Look, Tommy,
I've always liked you.
And I don't want to have
any problems with you,
I just...
I want to let you know
that Jenny and I got
together last night.
Look, I didn't want you
to hear about it
from anybody but me.
What does that mean,
you got together?
Tommy, it ain't right
to ask that.
Okay, I'm trying to do
the right thing here,
I hope you appreciate that.
Like I said,
I'm not looking
for any problems.
No problems.
All right.
Take care, all right?
Yeah.
Okay.
You outlasted me.
You won't come in,
I'll come to you.
Thanks, Father,
but I'm not here
for confession.
You've been on your knees
for 45 minutes.
I know a sin
when I see one.
(SIGHS) I feel terrible.
You look terrible.
Thanks.
Well, tell me about it.
I broke my vows this week.
Okay.
And I did it
again last night.
With someone else.
And you feel bad
about that?
Yes.
Good, you should.
What's worse,
I did it to hurt the person
I'm really in love with.
Who was the first guy.
Who isn't your husband?
No.
I don't know what to do,
Father.
I just make one mistake
after another.
It's been over a year now.
Marked a new anniversary
on my calendar.
The day my husband
never came home.
Well, thank God
for small favors.
Your husband was a louse.
You should never have
gotten involved with him
in the first place.
Want my advice?
Not if it comes
with penance.
Undo your problems,
one at a time.
Are you telling me
to get a divorce?
Well, the Church
still believes
that divorce is punishable
by the flames of hell.
I'd look into an annulment.
KEVIN:
Fifty X means times five,
so that's $250
on the Colts to win.
This is stupid.
No one's gonna pay you
Louie's money.
JIMMY: What's the B32?
The customers' code names.
The ones that aren't gonna be
giving you any money.
How do you know
it's a code name?
Because I had a code name.
And I wouldn't be giving you
any money, by the way.
What was your code name?
It's not important.
Kevin, I'm gonna beat you up
if you don't tell me.
L21.
What's the L for?
Lucky.
Lucky?
This is why
I don't tell you things.
Wait, 21, what's that?
This is stupid.
It's the number that
Louie would give you.
Try the speed dial.
Lucky 21. Here you are.
You want to know
how much you owe?
Don't! Don't!
All right!
Do not.
Now if you lost,
then what?
Louie or someone
from the office would
call you on payday
and tell you
how much you owe.
All right, this is good.
When's payday?
Today.
Or if you won,
then he'd give you the money
on Tuesday.
We won't be needing Tuesdays.
Give me the phone.
Hey, this is Jimmy.
From the office.
Your number
for the week is 250.
No, no, Louie's out of town.
I'll be making the pickups.
JOEY: See you later, Kev.
KIM: Hey, Tommy?
Tommy!
Tommy, I need to talk to you.
Oh, hey, Kim.
It's about Sean.
What about him?
He's ignoring me.
I'm sure he doesn't mean to.
Yeah, so did you say
anything to him?
About what?
About me being a slut.
What?
I mean, I'm not a slut,
but is that
what you told him?
Why would I do that?
'Cause when we met,
I thought you were gonna
ask me out,
and then I went out
with your little brother.
Kim, I don't care about that.
Then why won't he see me?
I have no clue.
But if I were you,
I'd go stand outside
our front door
and wait
until he gives you an answer.
You would?
Yeah, I'd go right now.
Tommy Donnelly.
I'm dropping out
next semester.
You don't sound so sure
about that.
I'm sure.
I just want my money back.
Well, sorry,
that we can't do.
No, no.
I checked. I got 10 days
to withdraw from classes,
and today's the tenth day.
Yes, but you don't have the...
No, no.
I'm within the deadline.
I need my money back.
Mr. Donnelly,
if you'll just listen
for a second.
Okay.
Your tuition wasn't paid
this semester.
What?
Actually,
it was paid
but then it was cancelled.
Cancelled?
Who cancelled it?
JOEY. Huey Farrell had been
paying Tommy's tuition
through the union.
Up until this moment,
Tommy somehow believed
that killing Huey
wasn't gonna change that.
The hardest lies are
the ones we believe ourselves.
Like Jimmy thinking
you could go out
and make a lot of money
and respect would follow.
Jimmy, we're up to six guys.
How many of these collections
are we gonna make?
What's the matter,
you don't like money?
MAN ON PHONE.
Hello?
Hey, it's Jimmy
from the office.
Yeah, what's up?
Your number for the week's
$440.
No, no, Louie's out of town.
I'll be making the pickups.
Joey.
Where do you guys
usually meet?
You seen Tommy?
No, I haven't seen him?
Want one?
No, thanks.
6:00, I'll be there.
Jenny!
Yeah, Jimmy?
Good times last night, huh?
Sure, Jimmy, if that's
what you call a good time.
Oh, I don't mean
the part about Dokey
holding us hostage
in the basement and almost
chopping off our toes.
That sucked.
I mean last time I saw you.
You know, it's funny.
I never would have known
you were married.
Does Samson know?
Just tell Tommy I was here,
okay?
I'll be sure to tell Tommy,
I mean Samson, I mean Tommy.
I'm sorry,
I made a mistake.
Anybody could make a mistake,
right?
Did I miss something?
Yeah. How a guy can waste
15 years of his life
on some backstabbing,
open-her-legs-for-any-dumbass
bread man whore.
You're talking about Tommy,
right?
Shut up.
Time to start collecting
the money.
Grab the phone, idiot!
Yeah. I had it.
You made me forget
with all that Jenny stuff.
I told you to shut up
about that.
Yeah. Okay, I'm done.
Shut up.
MAN:
Every month with this guy.
Then do what you feel is best.
It's your business.
Thanks for taking a minute,
Dokey, I appreciate it.
Absolutely.
After last night,
you and I are old friends.
What can I do for you?
I guess you know
I go to art school downtown.
Yeah, I heard.
But art school,
that's not like real school,
right? That's...
The tuition was taken care
of by the union.
Huey said it was covered
under my father's
death benefits.
Yeah, well, it wasn't.
It was a handout.
And you know that.
And that's why
I cancelled it.
Well, we got a problem, Dokey,
'cause I was counting on
that money.
The problem you and I have is
you think I'm stupid enough
to take food
out of the mouths of my men?
That money came from
union coffers, Tommy.
My brother, he was a jerk
with a soft heart.
And I'm not.
Last night, when I told you
about kidnapping an Italian
to get out
from under a debt...
Yeah?
Well, we're not quite out
from under.
I'm in the hole to Nicky
for 25 a week.
The first payment's
due tonight.
So?
If I can't get
that tuition money, Dokey,
I'm gonna need
to borrow $2,500.
Tommy, tell me one person
who would loan a kid like you
that kind of money?
I was hoping you would.
Well, then I'm afraid
you got your head up your ass.
But I'll tell you
what I will do.
I'll throw you a job.
What kind of a job?
I've noticed that
you've become pretty tight
with my sister-in-law.
Kate?
Not more than anyone else.
Well,
she's got something
inside the house,
and all I want you to do
is get it for me.
You want me to rob
from your sister-in-law?
Huey had an office
in the basement.
There's a large box
in the desk.
Now, I'm not gonna
confuse you by telling you
what's in the box.
All I want you to do,
grab it
and bring it back here.
Forget it.
Hey.
You bring me that box,
and your problem with Nicky
goes away.
I can't rob a widow.
I'll figure it out.
Kevin, you damn dummy.
What?
You didn't pull
the door shut.
Yes, I did.
Not all the way,
it didn't latch.
Ma, let me go ahead of you.
What the hell for?
I don't know.
What are you
all worried about,
Kevin?
You owe people money again?
No.
Then stop acting
like an idiot!
KEVIN: Seanie?
SEAN: Yeah, what?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
NICKY. Now you know you
closed that door, right?
But it makes you wonder.
Someone's been inside.
Maybe left something.
Nicky?
Tell your brother
clock's ticking.
Look, you go to hell...
(PHONE DISCONNECTS)
You find him?
No.
Where's he calling from?
I don't know, Tommy,
he scared the hell out of me.
Mom know anything?
No. Tommy, let's rob somebody
and give him his money,
but let's kill him.
Kevin, relax.
Where's Mom?
In the kitchen.
Hey, Ma.
Hi.
How we doing?
Good.
Your brother's acting
a little weird.
Yeah. What's that?
Casserole for Seanie.
What are you doing?
I'm taking the casserole.
You keep an eye on Ma?
Yeah.
Tommy.
Hey.
My mother made a casserole.
She asked me to drop it off.
That was nice.
Please thank her for me.
I will.
And you, too.
The wake was
just what I wanted.
And everything you said
was beautiful.
Huey had to be
smiling down.
I hope so.
Is that one of his sweaters?
Oh...
Yeah.
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to...
I should go.
It's ugly, isn't it?
He never wore it.
But it was made in Ireland,
so he'd never get rid of it.
And now I can't seem to,
either.
You cleaning out his closets?
I've been at it two hours,
this is as far as I've gotten.
I could help you.
No, it wouldn't
be a problem.
That would be wonderful.
Yeah.
MAN 1: The soup smells good.
MAN 2: Yeah.
Dad?
Yeah?
The hamburger patties,
they were in the oven.
What?
The patties that were
delivered this morning,
did you put them
in the oven?
You're asking me if I put
the hamburger patties
in the oven?
You think I'm an idiot?
Well, somebody did it.
I didn't.
Well, I didn't do it, either.
Well, one of us did.
I vote for you.
Order another box.
Damn waste of money, Jen.
Hi, Mrs. Donnelly.
Hello.
I was wondering
if Sean was here.
He is, but he's sleeping.
Mom? Who's that? Oh, hey.
What's the matter
with you today, huh?
Nothing, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to see
who it was.
Kevin,
is Sean really sleeping?
I just told you
he was sleeping.
Mrs. Donnelly,
I know Sean's in there,
and I don't think
he's sleeping.
And I'm not gonna leave
without talking to him.
Ma.
Damn!
What do you want
from my Seanie?
Why don't you like me?
If someone's told you
something, tell me.
Nobody has to say anything.
All I have to do
is look at you
and I can tell
you're wrong for my son.
Isn't it bad enough
that he already took
this terrible beating for you?
For me?
What'd you do, huh?
Did you give these fellows
a little smile, a little wave?
Playing the big shot beauty?
God knows what my other sons
had to do to avenge this.
So you just do me a favor
and stay the hell out
of our lives.
Sean'll do just fine
without you.
Hey, how we doing out here?
Shut the door, Kevin,
or I'm gonna hit you in
the head with something.
Okay, okay.
Did Sean say
I did any of that?
Sean's too much of a gentleman
to say anything.
Please don't come back.
Can you give Sean
a message for me?
(STUTTERING)
Not if my Mom
doesn't want me to.
What kind of people are you?
Worst part was going
to the morgue.
Identifying the body.
I can't imagine.
It wasn't the bullet hole.
It was seeing him in
this awful plastic bag.
I'm sorry.
Have you been to a morgue?
No.
Huey loved the cold.
He, he hated the heat.
Irish blood.
That's what I thought about,
looking at him.
That he would have liked
how cold it was.
MATTHEW: Mom?
Honey?
I'm ready for bed.
Oh. Did you brush your teeth?
Yeah.
Come here.
Open your mouth.
Breathe.
You still need to
brush your teeth.
Oh, jeez.
Moms will catch you
every time.
Go on.
I'll be in to kiss you
good night.
I hope he didn't
hear all that.
No, he didn't.
Can I help you guys
with something?
We're from the office.
What office is that?
Louie's office.
I'm Ryan.
That's Steve-O.
How's it going?
Where's Jimmy?
Jimmy? Jimmy who?
Jimmy.
The guy who called me
from the office,
said he was working
for Louie.
Jimmy couldn't come.
He sent me.
You know what?
This whole thing stinks.
You have Jimmy
or Louie call me
from the office.
I'll deal with them.
All right, wait a minute.
I am Jimmy.
He is. He really is Jimmy.
Get the hell out
of my office.
Just pay me the money.
I'm not paying.
Joey, shut the blinds.
Joey?
What happened to Steve-O?
So?
Perfect.
What?
Joey!
Get in here and hit this guy!
(MEN GRUNTING)
Come on, Steve-O, let's go.
Matthew's a good kid.
I always feel bad
he's an only child.
It must be great
having a lot of brothers.
I don't know about great.
I know it's a lot of headache.
I had three brothers
growing up.
They were always hitting
and biting and kicking.
It was ridiculous.
But now I think
it's good for boys.
They need
that physical thing.
Were you guys like that?
A little bit.
My brothers were
so vicious,
they would knee each other
in the balls, headlocks.
Except one thing,
they would never punch
in the face.
Is that how you guys were?
No, we punch in the face.
Really?
Yeah. That's the first place
we go.
Our mother taught us that.
I'll tell you what.
You really feel like
Matthew's missing out,
why don't you just send him
over to our house?
We can hold down
one of my brothers,
and we'll let Matthew
kick the crap out of him.
You okay?
I know how close
you were to Huey,
but you barely know me
and Matthew.
Sorry.
Okay.
Ma, turn it off, please.
Sorry, did I wake you?
No.
Hungry?
Can you bring it in?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Look at me.
Would you look at me,
please?
Is that what
you're worried about?
What your face looks like?
It's pretty bad.
What you look like,
your face...
I know that's
who you think you are,
but it's not.
It's what's
inside your heart,
that's what makes you
a Donnelly.
Your father would be
ashamed of you if you thought
anything else.
Now I'm gonna
put dinner on.
And I'm not
bringing it in here.
JOEY. See, the thing about
telling lies is
if you're good at it,
people don't know
they're being lied to.
So then the question is,
can you live with
the lies you tell?
KATE: Tommy?
Yeah.
You leaving?
Yeah, it's getting late.
What time is it?
It's 9:00.
Oh, okay.
Well...
Sorry about all the crying.
Don't be silly.
Good night.
Did you look in it?
No.
If I were you, I would've
at least taken a peek.
I didn't wanna be tempted.
And I figured
you knew exactly how much
was in there.
Smart.
JOEY. Being a thief made
Tommy feel pretty bad.
$2,500.
Getting robbed made him feel
a lot worse.
The deal was you were gonna
make my problem go away.
I will. This week.
That wasn't the deal.
Sure it was, Tommy.
No.
You said you were gonna
talk to Nicky
and make my problem go away.
I held up my end
and you...
Yeah, well,
let me just stop you
right there, okay?
I think maybe
what we have here
is a communication problem
between you and I.
Let's call it that.
Because calling it
anything else
could result in you
losing your toes.
You're right.
It was my mistake.
Next time we do business,
I'll make sure
we understand each other.
By the way,
I need to ask you a favor.
What's that?
I need an address.
Put a plate out
for your brother.
He's not coming out.
Put another plate out.
He doesn't want anybody
seeing him looking
like a Cyclops.
I heard that.
I'm just kidding.
You look like half a Cyclops.
What about me?
HELEN:
There's not enough for you.
Have another piece of bread.
That's not fair.
You should have thought
about that
when you let Tommy
steal my casserole.
Go out and eat, you haven't
been out of my hair all day.
I don't want to go out.
Have some squash.
I don't like squash.
I don't even like saying it.
This is great, Mom.
It's $2,500.
We're even.
Even?
That's right. I'm done.
I'll tell you why.
One of the last things
Huey Farrell said to me
was my brother Sean wasn't
supposed to get beat up.
I'm thinking you did that
on your own.
I'm thinking that's
a piece of information
that Sal's boss, Alo,
would like to hear.
That's why the $2,500
makes us even.
That pastry for your mother?
Why don't you say hi for me?
She lives upstairs, right?
You find something amusing
about what just happened?
If you had to bet on him
or Dokey,
who would you bet on?
Dokey.
Okay, I missed something,
right?
JOEY. For a moment
Tommy believed that
what he had done
might have been worth it.
(CHATTERING)
Hey.
Jenny.
I was in here earlier
looking for you.
Tommy! Nine ball!
Me and you, partners.
I can't lose again tonight.
Makes one of us, Jimmy.
Maybe want to go outside
and talk.
Didn't we do that last night?
I know I hurt you last night,
I'm sorry.
You wanted something else,
I get it.
JIMMY: Tommy!
Come on, we need a fourth.
Jimmy, shut the hell up,
we're trying to
have a conversation!
I give up, don't shoot.
What?
What I did last night
was mean.
And stupid.
Did you sleep with him?
Yeah.
You could have lied to me.
Tommy.
I don't want to be the person
that I was last night.
I need a fresh start.
I need to not be married,
I need to not be with you,
I need to not be
with another guy
in order to get at you.
Jenny,
I don't want to hear it.
I mean, whatever you gotta do,
you should just do it.
Okay?
Guess I'll go then.
Good.
JIMMY:
You made the balls go back.
KEVIN: That was nice!
Oh! I got it!
(MEN CHEERING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey, Firecracker.
Tommy, it's Kate.
I need you to come back.
I came down here
after you left.
I thought maybe
I'd put it someplace else.
I've been in
and out of it so much
with all the arrangements.
Is there anything else
missing?
No.
How much was it?
It's not the money.
See, he can get into my house
any time he wants.
Who?
That bastard brother-in-law
of mine, Dokey.
Oh.
He has Huey's keys.
Says he doesn't,
but he does.
The two of them worked
down here.
So what do you
want me to do?
Change the locks.
TOMMY: Okay.
Can you do it tonight?
Uh-huh.
Find a place open,
not in the neighborhood.
Dokey owns
all the locksmiths.
Sure.
(CREAKING)
You hear that?
No, what?
Matty's crying.
Hey, it's okay, baby.
It's my fault, I should have
left your light on.
Okay?
Can I have a juice?
Okay.
But then it's back to bed.
You want something, Tommy?
No, I'm fine. Thanks.
Okay. Here you go.
I left the lights on
in the basement.
I saw what you did.
What?
But I won't tell.
JOEY. Like I said,
it all comes down
to what you can live with.
Hey, I could keep going.