DETECTIVE:
So, where are the bodies?
Oh, man.
These guys are my friends.
Here's the deal, Joey.
You tell us
where the bodies are,
how they got there,
you stay in solitary,
nice and safe.
You lie, you go
to general population
where more people
than I can count
want to see you dead.
Where are the bodies?
There's two things
that happened
to Jimmy Donnelly
that made him turn out
the way he did.
The first thing,
do you know what
a half-moon ride is?
JOEY.
It came around every summer.
It was like
an instant block party,
and Jimmy had just stolen
enough for us to get on.
Now, the Donnelly brothers
were always together.
There was Kevin, Tommy, Jimmy
and little Sean.
And Jenny Reilly was, like,
sewn to the hip.
Even back then
she drove poor Tommy crazy.
Wait.
I got the wrong year.
It was the year
I got my nickname,
Joey Ice Cream.
'Cause under pressure,
I'm like ice.
Just give me some ice cream!
But there's
hardly any left.
There's five gallons.
(GRUNTS)
Hey!
(GRUNTING)
Hey, that's mine!
I stole that!
Come on!
Come back!
No one even heard it coming.
One of Jimmy's legs
just shattered.
He never grew much after that.
And they never found
the driver.
(KIDS SHOUTING)
Didn't seem to slow him
down much, though.
It's like he barely noticed.
(BOYS SHOUTING)
BOY: Lucky shot!
DETECTIVE.
You said it changed his life.
JOEY. It did.
Not in the way you'd think.
Awesome.
And not for a long time.
I always wanted
brothers like that.
(GUNSHO TS)
Okay, fast forward, here.
(WHISTLING)
It's 1999, I'm flush,
I'm feeling good.
Firecracker Lounge, please.
You were in juvie in '99.
It's 2002, I am flush,
I am feeling good.
You get one more chance.
It's 2005
and I just spent the night
with a woman
who wouldn't stop.
Here, take this.
Gram, I don't need
a raincoat.
Oh, it folds up.
Put it in your pocket.
Firecracker Lounge.
Go, go!
Have you got your rubbers?
See, all through history,
people have accused
the Black Irish
of every crime
that came along.
They were supposed to have
Gypsy blood, or Spanish
or something,
but my grandmother told me
that before the Celts even
showed up in Ireland,
there was a race
of dark-haired people
who the Celts then proceeded
to wipe out.
But they could never
get them all.
A few of them ended up
at the Firecracker Lounge.
There was always something
going on there.
That day, it was
a birthday party.
No, it was a wake.
JOEY: I'm going to miss you,
Paddy. Have a raincoat.
(IRISH MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Now, Jimmy won the bar
in a crap game with
Donny McCue a year before.
It came with rotting floors
and a gigantic tax lien.
McCue swore
he didn't lose on purpose.
Now, Kevin had always thought
of himself as a gambler.
He always believed
he was lucky.
The fact that he'd never
won a bet in his life
somehow never dissuaded him
of this notion.
Really, Kevin?
$2,000?
How could you lose
$2,000 on jai alai?
You don't even know
what jai alai is, do you?
Why don't you show me.
Show me how you play, Kevin.
Tommy had a knack
for two things.
Drawing and getting
his brothers out of trouble.
What he didn't seem
to understand
is that he'd never go
anywhere with the first
if he couldn't let go
of the second.
Hold on.
Which was the second?
The bodies.
Are you telling the story
or am I?
Sean was still the baby.
Everybody loved Sean,
especially women,
which is why his brothers
never let their girlfriends
anywhere near him.
Do you know how much
Kevin owes?
I don't know, 3,000?
Oh, 3,000. Kevin!
$3,000, Kevin?
Now, a couple years before,
Jenny, she married
a schoolteacher.
Now, Teach forgets to mention
that he robs drug dealers
to pay for his student loans.
He goes into hiding,
somebody stuffs him
in an oil drum.
Nobody had the heart
to tell Jenny.
I mean, even me,
and we were like an item.
Bug off, Joey.
Yeah, you got it.
She's a great girl,
isn't she?
Is Joey Ice Cream
bothering you?
No, no.
He's just a little concerned
that with my husband
out of town,
I might not be
getting enough.
And so he invited me
to the bathroom
for a couple minutes.
Hey! Hey, Joey!
Get back here!
You know Kevin
tried to borrow
$4,000 from me today?
Oh, 4,000.
Okay.
How's it going with Bonnie?
Bonnie?
The blond
you introduced me to?
What was she,
a business student
or something?
Oh, it didn't work out.
That's a real shame.
FRANKIE: Hey, Jenny.
Hey, Frankie.
I'd pass on the ham.
FRANKIE: Oh.
You finally making your move?
You and your friend
are afraid to come in here
without a badge?
How's Jimmy?
Jimmy's great.
Yeah?
Why? What's up?
Well, somebody stole
a truck this morning
in the garment district.
The detective
who caught the case,
he asked me about Jimmy.
How could Jimmy steal a truck,
Frankie? He can't even drive.
That's what I told the man.
You do with it
what you want.
I gotta get out of here.
Hey, you got any naked models
in that art school?
'Cause I want to visit.
(CHUCKLING) Get out of here.
Nice spread.
Jimmy!
Here you go.
How you doing?
How's Frankie?
You robbing trucks?
What are you talking about?
Don't lie to me, Jimmy.
Yeah, I'm going to lie to you.
What are you, a cop?
(BANGING)
Hey, no banging
on the machines!
What? It took my money!
JIMMY: It's supposed
to take your money!
You want to yell
in my other ear?
The Irish have
always been victims
of negative stereotyping.
I mean, people think
we're all drunks and brawlers,
and sometimes
it gets you so mad,
all you want to do
is get drunk
and punch somebody.
(MAN GROANING)
He's going my way!
What's this, the truck
you didn't steal, Jimmy?
Tommy, lighten up!
Get out of the truck.
The cop's here.
Come on,
you know Jimmy can't drive!
Neither can you!
Get out of the truck!
Son of a bitch!
Get back in the truck.
Now I should get in the truck.
Hey, Tommy,
do you like this shirt?
You're asking me
if I like that shirt?
Yeah.
'Cause I got
a couple thousand more
in the back.
Tommy could drive anything.
Before he became
Mother Teresa,
he had a big-time penchant
for joyriding.
Hey! Hey, do you wanna move?
Now, Jimmy knew a guy
who would take the shirts
for 50 cents apiece.
There was only
one complication.
Apparently,
while we were in the bar,
somebody stole
the stolen shirts.
TOMMY: So, anybody got
any idea how to get $4,000?
KEVIN: You hear
what Bobby O and
J.J. McGrane did?
They stole an Italian.
Held him for ransom.
Where's Bobby O
and J.J. Right now?
I don't know.
Attica, I think.
Right.
I'll see you later.
Now, the bookie
Kevin owed the money to
was named Louie Downtown.
Louie ran the book
for Sal Minnetta.
Sal and his right hand,
Nicky Cottero,
would drop by once a week
just to keep Louie honest,
but they weren't there
right now.
Since Kevin was short,
he had to tell Louie
that he needed more time.
So Sean borrowed
a friend's cab while
the friend wasn't looking,
and they took Jimmy along
in case Louie didn't
take the news too well.
Did I tell you
the second thing you had
to know to understand Jimmy?
Jimmy's father worked for
the Steelworkers' union
which was run by the Irish.
Now, some Italians were
trying to change that.
Hey, Jimmy.
Where's your father?
He's in the coffee shop.
Thanks.
It wasn't his fault.
He didn't know.
But while he was
listening to music,
they were beating his father
to death.
He never saw their faces
before or after,
but he knew one thing.
He knew they were Italian.
And that's what
Louie Downtown was.
Italian.
JOEY. For three months now,
Tommy had been working up
to asking out
this photography student.
Uh, Blow-Up.
Your favorite movie?
Yeah.
Oh, my God! Me, too.
You're kidding?
Yeah!
Well, I had a book...
He might've had a shot if
Huey Farrell hadn't shown up.
Will you give me a minute?
Yeah.
Huey took over
the neighborhood
from Old Man Mulligan.
The Irish had run it
since the 1890s.
Huey made sure
it stayed that way.
It's good.
Look, Tommy,
did you hear what happened
to Louie Downtown?
No.
Some guys snatched him
this morning.
No kidding?
Yeah. Three of them.
Stuffed him in the trunk
of a car and then drove off.
Tell me your brothers spent
the day at the tracks
so I can go home happy.
Huey, my brothers
aren't that stupid.
You know who Sal Minnetta is?
Yeah, of course.
Well, it turns out
Louie Downtown is his nephew.
Who knew, right?
Keep working on the art stuff.
Proud of you.
Do you have a car?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Where's Louie?
Louie who?
Stop lying!
And keep an eye on her.
Where's Kevin?
I didn't take anything.
How much did you steal?
Nothing. Not a nickel.
Yeah? Get out of here.
You got it, champ.
TOMMY: Hey!
Oh, man.
Hey, Kevin!
Tommy, me and Jimmy went
downtown with goodness in our
hearts to work out a deal.
But Louie starts
threatening me. I mean,
what was I supposed to do?
Kevin, everybody knows
who did this.
You kidnap somebody,
they're not supposed
to know who you are.
Tommy, you think we're stupid?
We wore masks.
You went own there
with goodness in your hearts,
but you wore masks.
Get out of the way.
(MUFFLED)
Hey, get me out of here!
Please, help me!
Help me please!
(LOUIE CONTINUES HOLLERING)
What are you doing?
I'm getting a knife.
We're cutting him loose.
Tommy, I love you,
but I'd rather fight you
than Jimmy.
He's banged out
of his head.
Where is he?
Hey!
Hey, Sean!
What the hell
are you doing?
You guys, like,
seeing each other?
'Cause I didn't know!
Go home!
You go back to school!
He's Sal Minnetta's nephew?
Yeah.
So he's worth a lot more.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Jimmy.
We've got to give him back.
What "we"?
You walked away.
He's not your Italian,
he's our Italian.
No, we got a thing,
here, Jimmy.
You've got to see that.
You know what I see, Tommy?
We got Louie Downtown.
If we give him back now,
are they going to thank us?
No, they're going to think
we're scared.
Which means they're going
to hunt us down and they're
going to beat us to death.
Is that what you want, Tommy?
Hey, Tommy,
you leave the door open?
Did I leave the door open?
Yeah, 'cause I went
to get a beer,
went right back down there.
He wasn't there.
Oh, hell!
We got his shoes
and his wallet.
He's not going to catch a cab.
Kevin, take a...
Hey, kid.
Where'd you get that shirt?
Bug off!
Jimmy! Louie.
Kevin, that way!
Split up!
(GROANING)
Hey, Jimmy!
Jimmy!
Jimmy, Jimmy, come on!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You, too, Tommy?
What are you thinking?
Listen to me.
I'll talk to my uncle.
You guys'll walk away
with broken legs.
And I'll throw in
the five grand Kevin owes.
Five grand? Five grand?
Sal Minnetta
did all his business
out of the same booth
every day and every night
for 46 years.
People say he had
a toilet under the table.
What kind of freakin' idiots
live in this world?
You don't kidnap
a Louie Downtown.
You ask, we give,
no problem.
(SIGHS) It's his nephew,
Nicky. Do not make me laugh.
You'll get me killed.
(PHONE RINGING)
Uh-huh?
No, you listen to me, fella.
He's my sister's son.
You treat him well.
How much?
Thirty thou.
Hey, it's family.
The Donnelly brothers?
You know them?
You know their father.
Bobby Donnelly.
The guy was
a Local 96 delegate.
He was the father?
What is this,
some kind of vendetta?
You know what
I think it is?
I think Huey Farrell
is losing his grip
on his neighborhood.
I don't understand why
we just don't go take it.
It had long annoyed Nicky
that the Irish had gotten away
with ignoring the rules
everyone else had to live by.
In fact, just an hour before,
he had a lively conversation
with Mickey Hogan
on the subject of using
union carpenters rather
than family and friends.
(GROANING)
We play this out
till we get my nephew back.
Nobody does anything
till then.
Sure, Sal.
I'll pass the word.
Stick.
Hit.
Busted. Damn.
You owe me $900.
Okay, once more
through the deck.
No, I'm not playing no more.
No, no, no.
I am down 900.
Damn right,
you're going to keep playing.
You're not going to pay me,
so why should I play?
Are you calling me a welcher?
So this is a real game
and you're going to pay me?
I'll pay you
out of the ransom money.
Fine, deal. Go ahead.
Stick.
Damn.
No, I'm good, good.
Thank you, yeah.
You okay?
Yeah.
If you want something to eat,
let me know.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
I talked to
my detective friend.
They got a witness
for this truck thing.
They're going to put Jimmy
in a lineup.
Now, the thing is
the witness said
that Jimmy had a gun.
This was armed robbery.
And I think Kevin and Sean
were with him.
Why do you think that?
There were three of them.
It doesn't take a genius.
Now, look, Tommy,
your father was a good man
and, because of that,
I'm doing all I can here.
But Jimmy's out of control.
I think you should
get him some help
before he takes
your other brothers
down with him.
All right, I appreciate it,
Frankie.
All right.
Thanks.
Take care, darling.
Bye.
(SIREN WAILING)
What?
Problems?
No.
Liar.
When are you going to show me
some of your drawings?
You can put some up
around here, you know,
try and sell them.
Yeah? You got a lot of
art patrons coming in here?
You'd be surprised.
Bet I would.
I might have to
buy one myself,
you know,
as an investment,
when you're famous.
Yeah.
Hey, be careful.
Why?
I don't know,
just worry about yourself
once in a while.
Thanks.
Hey.
Jimmy, hey.
We, uh, gotta talk.
What time is it?
It's 11:30.
We have to be
at the drop at 12:00.
Just give me two seconds.
We gotta talk first,
Jimmy.
Oh, give me a second,
will you?
Jimmy.
Get out of here, Tommy.
What are you doing?
Ahhh!
Hmm?
Are you crazy? I had
that needle in my arm!
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Get out!
Get out.
Get your money
and get out of here.
And you try to take
Kevin or Sean with you
and I'm gonna kill you.
(CHUCKLING)
You'll kill me?
If you have that much pain,
Jimmy, why don't you just
jump off the roof?
Hey, Sean.
You're Sean Donnelly, right?
It's all right. Go.
Go!
Where you going?
TOMMY: Seanie!
Sean! Seanie!
Seanie!
(TOMMY AND KEVIN SHOUTING)
Call an ambulance!
You saw what
they did to Sean.
You know what
that would have
done to Jimmy.
All I can do is talk to Sal
and try and make him see that.
But I need your word
Jimmy isn't planning
anything else.
You got my word.
Tell your mother
Sean's in my prayers.
Yeah, I will.
I got one dollar
and this thing's
got to take it.
Sal had no right.
I was giving Louie back.
Nah, he had no right.
You've got to get him, Tommy.
You know that.
You got him, Jimmy.
I sure as hell did.
What did you do
with his body?
You don't need to know.
Did you get rid
of the gun?
As soon as I'm
finished with it.
If you get caught with that,
you might as well confess.
How come there's never
anything you want?
You got three
or four more guns
in the bar alone.
Don't be stupid.
Let me get rid of it.
(SIREN WAILING)
You know I got
to do this, right?
You know that,
no matter what you say,
I gotta make this right.
You ask me to say I won't,
I'll just lie.
I did that to him,
Tommy.
I did it again.
Thanks, Nicky.
What about his brothers?
Is that a problem?
Jimmy's the only problem.
He's a punk and a doper.
He'd be more comfort
to his mother
dead than alive.
Tommy's a smart boy.
When Jimmy's gone,
he'll be able to say
he did what he could.
As long as it's only Jimmy,
because anything
other than that,
it'll be me with the problem.
HUEY: I got it.
You hear Mickey Hogan's
at Saint Margaret's?
No kidding?
Someone busted up his bar.
Beggars are our business.
Must be nice having
a right hand like Nicky.
You can retire anytime
and know your business
is in good hands.
I'll see you around, Sal.
Hey.
Thank you for coming.
Where's your mother?
She's in the waiting room
just waiting to hear
from the doctor.
I brought some food
from the restaurant,
so I'll go...
Good.
Maybe if we get some more,
we can open up a deli.
You know,
when I heard about it,
the person who told me
thought it was you.
I thought,
what if he dies
and he never knows
that I loved him?
Dumb, huh?
I mean, I'm a married woman.
Nothing's ever gonna happen.
I just...
I just couldn't stand the idea
of you dying and not knowing
that.
Hey, Tommy.
Hey, Huey.
How you doing, Jenny?
Hi.
Going in there?
Give that to Helen for me,
from my wife.
Sure. Okay.
I'll be with your mother.
Let's go get a coffee.
Well...
It's gonna be painful,
but it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay?
What, you talked to Sal?
When I walked in the room,
he wanted you all dead.
But I had something to trade.
You don't need to know what.
He wants his money back
and he wants Jimmy
to apologize to him
tonight, in person.
Can you get your brother
to do that?
To apologize?
Jimmy'll have to be
willing to take a beating.
I'm not going to lie to you.
Not as bad as Sean.
But you get your brother
to go down to Sal's tonight
by himself.
He walks in there
with you guys or a weapon,
he's going to get killed.
You get him
to take his beating,
everything will be okay.
Okay?
It was at that moment...
Hey, I can't
thank you enough, Huey.
It was at that moment
that Tommy knew
that Jimmy was dead.
You all right?
Yeah.
Jimmy was the price
they were gonna pay.
Huey had sold them out.
You like that shirt?
Yeah. You want one?
Nah, I'm good.
Don't worry about it.
Jimmy.
Hey, Francis.
How you doing tonight?
Good. How are you?
Oh, same old, same old.
Detective Calero,
I want you to take note
that the suspect is
turning himself in
voluntarily.
Yeah, I see that
very clearly.
Not for nothing,
but what am I turning
myself in for?
Jimmy, you boost
a truckload of shirts,
you get seen. That's unlucky.
You walk around all day
wearing the evidence,
I can't feel
too sorry for you.
So, this is
for the truck thing?
You got something else
you want to confess to?
No, I'm good.
All right.
How'd you know
where I was?
Jimmy, your little
brother's up there.
Where else you gonna be?
It's raining again.
Jimmy got pinched
for the truck thing.
But he just went down
to get some beers.
Yeah.
That sucks.
I talked to Frankie.
He said he'd get him
into rehab.
So you talked
to Frankie?
I talked to Frankie.
Huh.
So, it's not
a bad thing?
No, it's not.
I'm gonna step out
for a minute.
Sure.
Where you going?
Wherever you are.
Hey.
I'm making you
a sandwich.
Well, save it for me.
Tommy, listen to me.
You are not
your brother.
Stay and eat your sandwich.
Please.
I'll be back for it.
(SIGHING)
Yeah?
It's Tommy Donnelly.
Says he needs a word.
Tommy Donnelly wants
to talk to me.
Send him down.
Downstairs.
JOEY. You remember I told you
about the day that changed
Jimmy's life?
I was the only one
who saw him,
the only one who knew
that it was Tommy
driving the car.
To this day,
it's the one thing
I never told anybody.
I'm ashamed to be
telling you now.
Tommy never stole a car again,
never did nothing,
turned his whole life around.
I mean, he could have
made it out,
only he was never
going to let his brother
be hurt again.
And this was the day
that changed Jimmy's life
forever.
'Cause Jimmy went to rehab,
and Tommy...
Tommy became everything
he never wanted.
And whether he realized it
or not, with Huey dead,
Tommy had just taken over
the neighborhood.
And he was going to
have to defend it.
And that's where
we left the bodies,
right where they lay.
And what the Italians did
with them...
I mean, I can't say.
Those aren't the bodies
we were asking about.
Oh.