God, it's cold.
Gettin' too damn
old for this.
Make sure that blast cap's
on tight.
It's not the blast cap
I'm worried about;
it's my damn fingers.
Stop your complaining.
We fall behind schedule,
we violate our permit.
Just a minute.
Almost there.
Zone one clear.
Zone two clear.
Zone three
Zone four clear.
Got a squatter in zone five.
Getting him out.
After that,
we're clear here, too.
Zone six clear.
Okay, people.
Building's clean.
Wrap it up and get out.
We're go for demolition
in three minutes.
T-minus three minutes.
So what's up, man?
Stateside diner,
meatloaf sandwich?
Thinking steak and eggs
at Cora's.
Well, we could always head up
Route Nine to Parkview.
Sure.
What?
"What?"
The waitress.
The brunette. What's her name?
Oh, Marcie?
No, I wasn't even...
I was thinking about
the lean corned beef.
Yeah, right,
the lean corned beef named Marcie.
Hold up.
What's the matter?
You okay?
Dennis.
What's the problem?
Nothing.
I don't know.
- You swept it, right?
- Sure.
I just...
I don't know.
All of a sudden,
I got a weird feeling.
Yeah? Me too.
Mine's called,
"I don't wanna die looking at Dennis."
Come on, man.
Hey, radio Mike,
will ya?
Tell him I wanna do
another sweep.
Come on, man,
where you going?
Dennis, they're holding
the countdown for us.
- Damn it! Over here, let's go!
- Where we going?
I think we missed something.
The plans show
another room over here.
Ahh,
this doesn't make sense.
Phil, you got Dennis?
What's going on?
We don't have
a lot of time.
Just two more minutes.
We'll be right out.
- Do you hear that?
- What?
Sounds hollow.
Come on, man, this place
has been completely prepped.
There's nothing
underneath there.
Just solid foundation.
Does that sound
solid to you?
It's probably
just frost damage.
The... the
concrete's cracked, man.
Ohh!
Mike, I think you should
come down here.
This...
was definitely not in the blueprints.
God,
and what's that smell?
What do you think
this was?
I don't know,
but it's old.
Well, good,
that narrows it down.
What the hell?
Oh, my God!
Transcript:
SCG-Dream2008.cn
Final Edits By: VeRdiKT
[Subscene.com]
S01E15:
Inner Child
Ella?
Mommy gets grumpy
if I wake her too early.
She always did.
Mm, come on.
Oy, oy, oy.
Well,
do you want some...
Pancakes?
- Yes.
- Yeah? Mm-hmm.
Francis.
Hey, Jim.
How are you, buddy?
I saw that
your mayor got himself
into a
little bit of trouble.
That couldn't have been
fun for you guys.
When?
Has anyone taken anything
from that fax
- in the last five minutes?
- Yes, sir. It's here.
I'll call you back.
Ugh, Liv, I'm sorry.
I told her to
let you sleep late.
Oh, she did until 6:17.
Yup,
that sounds late for her.
Which one?
Uh, the yellow one.
Aunt Liv?
Definitely the yellow.
Did you tell her?
- Go get dressed.
- Okay.
What?
We went
apartment hunting yesterday.
Really?
You're thinking of moving to Boston?
Yeah, well,
Ella loves it here,
and so do I, so...
Well, you know
that you can stay here
for as long
as you want.
I know,
but you don't need
a little creature waking
you up at 6:17 every morning.
If that little creature
is Ella, I am fine with it.
Hello.
It's me.
The Artist is back.
How do you know?
Did we receive another fax?
Yeah.
Hartford office
got one too.
Well,
did we get a trace?
Said from a
copy store in Allston.
So I've got
Mason and Louis headed over
to question the employees,
see if someone can give us a
description of whoever sent it.
Okay, I'm gonna be there
in 15 minutes.
Some new horrifying event
you're not allowed
to tell me about?
Yeah.
Okay,
now it's gonna be 14.
Excuse me,
Agent Dunham?
- Oh, hey.
- Get the Bishops soon.
I need you to meet me
at Children's Hospital.
Actually, I just had an
old case reopened, and I...
It can wait.
After the
boy was found,
construction crews performed
a search of the tunnels.
It was determined
they'd been
sealed shut
for at least 70 years.
The place
was a sarcophagus.
The only living things down
there were rats, insects...
And him.
And we have no idea
how he got down there?
He's so pale.
He seems to be developing
some sort of pigmentation.
Well, he probably hasn't
seen sunlight in years.
Does he have a name?
He hasn't spoken a
word since he was found.
Dr. Bishop, any thoughts?
Perhaps.
But first I need a piece of
special equipment.
My turntable.
Is that some kind of
lab equipment?
No, a turntable.
Record player.
You enjoy music,
don't you, Mr. Broyles?
Well, imagine the
agony of having
an extensive record collection,
and having no means to play it.
The agony.
I'll have someone
get right on that.
It's Doctor Wenick.
Chief of Pediatrics.
Look, I understand your agency's
taken an interest
in this child, but he's
been through quite a trauma.
Is he sick?
Not as far as
we can tell, but...
he's having difficulty breathing.
We need to
administer oxygen.
No, no, no, no.
I wouldn't do that.
You said the tunnel was sealed,
is that correct?
Well, then it's obvious
that the child
was trapped in a low-oxygen
environment for so long
that his body
adapted to it.
And that is why he's
having trouble breathing.
I don't think so.
Unless you have an
IQ higher than mine,
I'm not interested in
what you think.
Administering additional
oxygen at the stage
would simply
cause his lungs
to fill with fluid and
drown him where he lies.
We need to
deprive him of oxygen.
Get him a nasal cannula
and a tank with
low oxygen content.
Perhaps 5% to start.
A griffin.
'Scuse me?
Your tattoo.
The body of a lion,
and the head of an eagle.
That's a griffin, right?
Just picked it
outta the sample book.
Thought it looked cool.
Oh, well.
A nice choice.
Did it hurt much?
I always imagined getting a
tattoo would hurt real bad.
It's a good pain.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to embarrass you or any--
You didn't.
Hey.
Do you need a hand?
Uh, thanks,
I got it.
Um, actually, you know,
a-a little help would be great.
Cool motorcycle.
What make?
'67 Harley Shovelhead.
She's a beauty.
Yeah, she is.
Any minute, now.
It worked.
You'll want to increase
the oxygen flow by 10%
every hour,
'til he acclimates.
So you said
that he hasn't talked.
How do we know
he can hear?
He responds to sound.
And we examined
his tympanic membrane,
there's no physical damage.
In fact...
Considering how he was found,
he seems fairly healthy.
His heart sounds fine,
his blood pressure's strong.
And how do we think
he survived down there?
- I mean, what did he eat?
- Rats.
I'd think.
Moss, insects.
High in protein.
Tastier than you may think,
especially millipedes.
Although they all lack
certain minerals
which may account for
his follicular dilemma.
His baldness.
Have you performed
a urinalysis?
We haven't been able to.
We've been feeding him,
intravenously.
He hasn't relieved himself
since he arrived.
Can't say I blame him for
not wanting to try this.
This looks worse than the dreadful food
they served at St. Clare's.
You were on staff
at St. Clare's Asylum?
No, no, no,
not a medical doctor.
I was a patient.
- Got such a sense of humor, huh?
- Hmm?
Walter,
what do ya say we keep
those old St. Clare's
stories to ourself, yeah?
Hello.
My name's Olivia.
What's yours?
It's my phone.
It's Charlie.
Hi. I'm, uh,
still in the hospital.
You won't remember this,
Peter,
but you didn't
talk much either, as a child.
- Could you get me the address?
- In fact, you were quite shy.
What's it say?
Sam Gilmore.
He can write?
Is that your name?
I'll see what we have on any
Sam Gilmores in Massachusetts.
The body was found just
after 6:00 pm.
This part of the park's usually
empty this time of the year.
Couple of kids were using it
as a shortcut when they found her.
Definitely the work
of the Artist.
He clearly made alterations
to the body post mortem,
and put her out here for
the whole world to see.
Here's what
we have so far.
She's a local girl.
A process server
from Weston.
Next of kin is being notified by
local agents as we speak.
Samantha Gilmore.
Wait,
did you say Sam Gilmore?
Yeah.
Samantha Gilmore.
You know her?
Our perp's name
is the Artist.
Now, some of you here
may recall
that we had our first encounter
with him three years ago.
He killed four women
in lower Jamaica plain
over a period of two days.
After the fourth murder,
he stopped.
Are you holding
for Dr. Winnik?
Uh, yes.
- One moment, please.
- Samantha Gilmore, age 24.
Now, the killing bears all
of the Artist's trademarks.
His MO is to kidnap, sedate,
and kill his victims.
Then after he kills them,
using surgical tools and chemicals,
he, in his mind,
enhances their appearance.
In this case,
he bleached her skin,
removed multiple piercings,
and dyed her hair,
I'll let Dr. Winnik
know that you called.
- like the others...
- Thanks.
It was preceded with a faxed
invitation to view new work
that was to be displayed
- somewhere in public.
- Anything yet?
No.
That was the hospital.
They're giving the boy an MRI.
When he's done, I'm gonna go in
and talk to him again.
In the meantime,
I've sent his picture
to Samantha Gilmore's
friends and family,
but, so far,
no one recognizes him.
You didn't really expect
that they would, did you?
No.
So let me ask you
the obvious.
What's the connection?
Amala and Kamala,
the wolf girls of India.
And... and, ah...
Marie-Angelique Memmie Leblanc,
the wild girl of Champagne.
They're all feral children who...
who grew up completely
isolated from human contact,
surviving, like our boy,
uh, for many years alone.
Yeah, but I'm guessing none of them
could write upside-down.
You're saying that the
boy grew up down there.
Well, based on the
blood work, yes.
I'm fairly certain that the
lack of Vitamin D, for one,
but also the complete
absence of lactobacillus...
Microorganisms
that help us digest.
- They're everywhere.
- Precisely.
If the boy had spent any
time above the ground,
then he certainly
would have absorbed those.
But that still doesn't explain
how he got there
in the first place.
You said that-that place had
been sealed off for decades.
The boy couldn't be
more than ten.
Well, he certainly
looks that.
You believe
he might be older.
Well, given the
environmental conditions...
the lack of
oxygen and light...
and their impact on his
biological development,
he could be
significantly older.
But none of that explains
how he knew Samantha Gilmore.
No.
That I can't explain.
But good news,
Mr. Broyles.
I have located my turntable.
So I-I don't need you to
purchase me one after all.
It was under
the sink in the john.
So obviously,
I was sitting
on the toilet, and I--
Walter, I think that's
probably enough information.
Agent Dunham.
We just got
another one.
The Artist is going
after another victim.
Easy, easy.
That's a beautiful dog.
- Thank you.
- Is he friendly?
Of course.
His name's Mack.
Hey, Mack.
Hey, Mackie.
Hi, Mack.
Hey.
They, uh...
They told me that you haven't
eaten anything solid yet.
So I, uh...
I thought that
you might like these
more than the mystery meat.
When I was a kid,
I used to live on these.
Except the yellow.
Something about the color.
Reminded me of medicine.
You wanna try one?
That's it. Good.
Thank you.
Ahem.
Yesterday, you wrote down
a name for me.
Remember?
I thought today,
you could give me your name.
You have a
real way with him.
Elliot Michaels.
Department of Social Services.
Uh, Olivia Dunham, FBI.
Um, do you mind if I borrow
Miss Dunham for a few minutes?
I-I promise I'll bring her
right back.
I'll be just outside.
Dr. Winnik brought me up
to speed
about your interest
in the boy's case.
The circumstances
by which he was found
attracted our interest.
It's bizarre, huh?
Have you been able to find out
anything more about him?
You know, first name,
where he's from...
Uh, no.
I'm afraid not yet.
Well, I'm not gonna get
in your way.
I just thought I'd stop by
and see him
before I get the
ball rolling.
How so?
How so? Uh, well,
you know... physically, it...
It doesn't seem as if there's
anything really wrong with him,
so I've arranged
to have him moved.
Moved?
To a facility that can provide
the treatment he needs.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
You know, I hope.
Assuming all the paperwork
is in order.
- What's wrong?
- Uh, I'm not sure.
His BP and his heart rate
are spiking.
It's okay, it's okay.
Hey.
It's okay.
Shh.
It's gonna be okay.
Oh...
Good...
Should I get the doctor?
- I-I think we're okay.
- Alright.
You okay, there?
Maybe if you just, uh,
gave us a moment.
- Of course. Just take your time.
- Thank you.
I'm at the hospital.
I think we may have
found another one.
I should let you get
some rest.
Anything so far?
I just got here
five seconds ago.
So what's the plan?
Start knocking on doors?
Unless you can think
of a better idea.
All right.
You go east,
I take west.
Okay.
Shh...
Shh, shh, shh...
Shh, shh, shh.
Good. You are very good.
Mind some company?
Of course not.
Did I miss you last night,
or did you not even come home?
Uh, no.
You didn't miss me.
Have you eaten anything?
Uh, M&Ms.
Liv...
Do you like it?
Your job?
Yeah.
Most days.
Today,
not so much.
I followed a lead
that didn't pan out.
What about you?
Why are you up?
Um...
I'm sorry.
Hello.
We found our second victim.
It's Kate Harper.
Where?
She's right outside
St. Catherine's.
Surrounded by candles.
Good news is we might have
finally caught a break.
E.R.T. said they found some
blood underneath her nails.
So they're running it.
Okay. I'll be right in.
Just one more thing, Liv.
The address the boy gave us.
Little while after we left,
a neighbor found a dog
tied to a fence.
It was whimpering.
It was the victim's dog.
We were there.
There's no way
we could've known, Liv.
But he was trying to tell us,
he was right and we were there.
Walter.
Olivia's here.
She needs to talk to ya.
Walter!
Could she come back later?
I'm about to step in the bath.
No, she can't come
back later.
It's the
middle of the night.
She needs to talk to you
right now.
Honestly, Peter,
can't a man get a...
Agent Dunham.
Peter, why didn't you tell me
Agent Dunham was here?
I'm pretty sure I did.
Well, what can I do
for you?
Walter, it turns out that
the boy was right.
He gave me a clue, but I didn't
know what I was looking for.
So do you have
any thoughts at all?
Any idea that how I can reach him
or how he's doing any of this?
I... I believe I know
how he's doing it.
Since he's been living
underground for so long,
his hypersensitivity
to light and sound...
It's just possible
he may also
be sensitive to
people's emotions.
A raw nerve.
Able to intuit the feelings
and intentions of others.
Your killer, for one.
So are you saying
that he's psychic?
No, no.
More a shark.
A shark?
Specifically,
their electromagnetic field,
which allows them to detect
their prey's bioelectric field
from a distance
of many miles.
We humans
have it too, of course.
Pheromones.
Undetectable chemicals
that nonetheless
affect our behavior,
our sex drive, our--
Hey, speaking of sex drive.
Oh, Peter,
don't be such a prude.
I'm sure Agent Dunham knows
what a penis looks like.
Don't you, Agent Dunham?
My father,
ladies and gentlemen.
But how would he know
things that I don't?
Know about the killer or
victims that he's never even met?
My dear,
there is much that is unexplained.
Until it is.
In short, he has no idea.
Even if you're right,
and he can sense the killer,
he can't tell me that.
Not in a way that I could
do anything about it.
Well, if that's the problem,
then there's no problem.
What does that mean?
Well, the boy is
obviously thinking, yes?
Having thoughts.
We just haven't been able
to hear them.
And I'm sure you
can do that, can't you?
Hear his thoughts.
Perhaps I can.
Did you make that?
Hey.
Listen, I wanna take you away
from here for a while.
Is that okay?
- Super-genius--
- Vintage Bugs Bunny.
Ee, what's up, doc?
Didn't get any better
than this, right?
- A genius certainly has his--
- Aha! I found it!
Neurostimulator.
Is there anything you can't do?
Walter, is that what
you're gonna use
to read the boy's thoughts?
Not to read them,
my dear.
To listen to them.
I wish you would have
told us
that that's what
you were gonna use.
Why?
'Cause you coulda saved us
the hassle.
You're not putting that medieval
torture device on that poor kid.
Walter, the last time
you used that thing,
you drilled it into
the guy's head.
If you think
he'll find it disagreeable...
- I suppose it could be modified.
- Really?
You didn't think to mention
that to the last guy?
It shouldn't be
too much trouble.
We merely need to intercept
the neural responses
from the speech centers
of the boy's brain,
which can be achieved by
placing electrodes in the halo ring.
After that,
it's simply
a matter of
synthesizing the impulses.
Think of it as creating
artificial vocal cords.
Simple.
Like makin' an omelet.
Actually, son, a good omelet
is far more complex. Eh?
We'll have him
talking in no time.
Where's the child
that was in this room?
He was discharged.
By whom?
Just remember
that you don't
have to do anything
that you don't wanna do.
If for a second
you're scared,
or you don't like
what's happening,
you just
squeeze my hand like that.
Okay?
Is he ready?
As ready as he'll ever be.
I guess.
I've seen
that look before.
Usually right before
somebody throws up.
Agent Farnsworth,
ready?
Walter,
what're you doing?
Watch and learn, son.
# Love and happiness #
# Wait a minute #
# Something's going wrong #
# Someone's on the phone #
# 3:00 in the morning #
# Yeah #
# Talkin' 'bout #
- Ooh!
- # She can make it right, yeah #
# Well #
# Happiness is when #
# You really feel
good about somebody #
# There's nothing wrong #
# being in love with someone #
# Yeah #
# Yeah, oh, baby #
Nicely done, Walter.
- Thank you.
- # Love and happiness #
You can turn the music off now,
Agent Farnsworth.
What's wrong?
What's going on in here?
Did you really think you
could just steal a child
out of protective custody
and that somehow
no one would notice?
Look, first of all,
I didn't steal him.
The child's assisting us in an
active criminal investigation.
Assisting you how?
No offense,
Mr. Michaels,
but that's
classified information.
The Department of Social Services
doesn't have clearance
to know that.
- What?
- Mr. Michaels isn't Social Services.
He's with the CIA's Directorate
of Science and Technology.
I'd have told you
earlier myself, but...
You don't have
clearance to know that.
This morning,
we were informed
the D.S.N.T. will be taking full
custody of the child.
So they can what?
Study him?
This child was apparently
able to survive for years,
underground,
in an oxygen-deprived environment
with no food or water.
Surely you could see
how someone who doesn't
have his best interests at heart
might want to exploit that.
Oh, so you wanna take him
to protect him, is that it?
Forgive me for
sounding harsh,
but I don't buy that
for a second.
Dunham.
It's all right.
To be honest, it really
doesn't make any difference
what you think.
The boy's coming with me.
I'm afraid this is
above both of us.
Agent Francis just called.
He said we got another invitation
from the Artist.
Mr. Michaels,
suppose you give us one day.
A day?
He could help us catch a
murderer and save a life.
The boy would be
under my protection.
I'll personally
guarantee his safety.
If I agree to this,
then you'll turn the boy
over to me without a fight?
Do we have an agreement?
We do.
My very educated mother
just served us
nine pies.
No.
That's the planets
of the solar system,
or at least was.
You wanna
take a look at this?
His name is Roadblock.
He's not really one of
your top-tier G.I. Joes,
but it is the best we had.
- Wait!
- Huh.
It's funny,
I always remember
the scar being on
the other side.
You want him?
Cannot build phallic puzzles
in the lab.
What is he doing?
Mnemonics.
You know, like a rhyme
or phrase to help memory.
Like, uh, "HOME" stands
for the Great Lakes.
That's Huron...
I'm familiar with it.
Why is he doing it?
Well, he is trying
to remember
which wires go into which
connections on the machine.
Yeah, thanks, Charlie.
I will.
Keep me posted.
More bad news?
We got the
forensics report.
We were hoping that
the blood we found under the
second victim's fingernails
was a match for the killer.
But no?
Not unless
Gene is the killer.
It wasn't human,
it was bovine.
You said cow blood?
Yeah,
and some plastic polymers.
How would someone
get cow's blood
on their fingers in Boston?
Astrid, could you contact
the Bureau of Animal Health?
We should start pulling
livestock licenses
around Boston.
Petting farms,
research facilities, anything.
- Yeah. Gotcha.
- She's a bad mamma jamma! Ha!
Alpha, beta,
beta and gamma...
She's a bad mamma jamma.
Signal amplification,
bifurcation,
modulation, juxtaposition.
You hanging in there, kiddo?
Vocal linguistic
impulses into magnets--
Yeah, me too.
Peter, get me the red wires.
Peter.
Here's a thought.
A couple years ago,
I was working down in Tennessee
as a floor sweeper
at a meat packing plant.
Sounds awesome.
You have no idea.
My point is:
We had these
big rolls of
industrial-grade plastic
that we used to wrap
their cuts of meat in
before we would send them
to the grocery stores.
Cow's blood in plastic.
Yeah.
Okay.
I believe we're ready.
- Peter?
- Yeah.
Yes.
Listen to that.
Listen to what, Walter?
That's just random noise.
No, that's
just the computer
calibrating the signal
to noise ratio.
Adjust the attenuation
setting to 70 decibels.
Okay, that sounds
a little more like a voice.
Yes, now,
the sound pressure level.
Eh, dial the
audio meter to 1,500 hertz.
Slower, damn it,
go slower.
Okay, if you wanna do this yourself,
feel free.
No, there.
Astrid, quickly,
get me a tape recorder.
Walter, turn the
machine off right now.
Turn it off now.
He's freezing.
Help me get this off of him.
Hey, Astrid,
can you grab us a blanket?
- All right, free in the front.
- Here.
All right, we're gonna
get you warmed up.
Doesn't make any sense.
If anything, brain activity
should generate heat.
We're trying to track down
a suspect in a
murder investigation.
What, you mean the
guy on the news...
who killed those girls?
We're not sure.
Maybe.
But any past or present
employees that stick out to you?
Like antisocial behavior
or a history of violent
incidences here at work?
No. They're good men.
Hard workers.
I'm gonna need a copy of your
employee records, regardless.
Okay.
And also a sample of
your shipping plastic.
Plastic? Why?
It could be an element
in our investigation.
- Will that be a problem?
- No, but...
Mr. Wu?
A man came in here
yesterday,
and I...
I sold him some plastic.
Allow me.
Oh, thank you.
Your mother
raised you well.
Hey, Peter, it's me.
I'm just leaving.
So, how's the boy?
Has Walter made any progress?
Hard to say;
we heard something,
but I don't know if it
was the kid trying to talk.
Look, I don't want you
to get upset about this
because he is fine,
but something kinda
weird did happen.
Weird how?
Well, he started shivering
all of the sudden.
Like, the temperature dropped
30 degrees, except it didn't.
Is he sick?
No, he seems fine.
We got him wrapped up in a blanket.
He's doing okay.
How 'bout you?
You find anything?
Yeah, looks like
the Artist bought some plastic
from a slaughterhouse
in Roxbury.
I got his sketch,
all thanks to you.
Hey, guys.
We got good news.
What's that?
Turns out the plastic did
come from a meat packing plant.
Olivia got a sketch of the guy.
What about you?
You gonna go back to the FBI,
or you coming here?
Ask her if it was refrigerated.
- Hold on a second.
- Peter!
Ask her if
the plant was refrigerated.
It's a meat-packing plant
full of raw meat.
So yeah, let's go out
on a limb here
and say that it's
probably refrigerated.
What does that
even matter?
Because that
explains everything.
Walter, slow down.
You're not making any sense.
Of course I am.
The boy...
Our strange, little friend...
is an empathy.
Yes.
He senses other people's emotions.
You already said that,
Walter.
Go on, Walter,
what are you saying?
That he's capable of
making connections...
Emotional connections.
Uh, to a construction worker
who found him, the killer,
but most importantly,
he is emotionally bonded to you,
Agent Dunham.
That's why he's telling
you about the crimes.
Because he knows
that the information
is important to you.
He's trying to help you.
Are you trying
to help me?
That man who's been
hurting people
is going to hurt someone else
unless I stop him.
Do you know
who he is?
Can you tell me
anything about him?
Maybe he doesn't know.
Or he can't control
the ability all the time.
Perhaps a small electric shock
to kick-start things.
No.
It's something different.
It's like
he's mad at me.
Because he doesn't
wanna leave.
What?
Well, you told Michaels
that once the boy
helped you stop the Artist,
you'd turn him over to him.
He heard you.
Or, more accurately,
felt you.
I'm sorry.
I've been so caught up in
what I needed that I forgot how...
strange
this must seem to you.
And I know how
scared you must be,
but I need your help again.
And I can't even stop
them from taking you.
Even though I wish I could.
And if you really can feel
what I'm thinking...
You know how much
I mean that.
Thank you.
Nice car, sir.
Where ya headed?
Uh, home.
I was out to dinner.
Open the trunk,
please.
It's clear.
Okay. Thank you.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
What's going on,
officer?
What are you doing
in the neighborhood, sir?
I... just, uh,
coming home from work.
Haven't had
anything to drink.
Would you mind
if I ask what you...
What you're looking for?
Uh, I'm sorry.
We're not allowed to say.
Sir, we need to check
the back of your vehicle.
Charlie!
Check the back of the van!
Liv, it's him.
We found the victim.
She's alive.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Oh, God!
This is Francis.
I need E.M.S. at the cemetery
behind the 1600 block of York.
- Broyles.
- It's Olivia.
I need you to help me
with something.
Here. Here.
And then we just do
the blood work, okay?
Excuse me,
Dr. Winnik?
Yes.
I was wondering if I could
talk to you for a moment.
Sure.
Hi.
I think you'll find
he's doing much better.
Hi.
Oh, thank you.
You remember
Dr. Winnik.
She's gonna take you now.
But not to a facility.
She's going to take you to a home.
With a very nice family
that are gonna take care of you.
And keep you safe.
We should go now.
Bye.
What do you mean
he's gone?
I'm sorry, Mr. Michaels.
Gone where?
Well, that's what
we can't figure out.
He disappeared from right under
the noses of protective detail.
How is that possible?
He's just a kid.
Yes.
A kid who,
as you said yourself,
lived his entire life
underground,
which still begs the question
how he got there
in the first place.
I'm beginning
to suspect there's
a lot about him
we don't understand.
And apparently,
we never will.
- You said it!
- No!
- I didn't! I didn't say it!
- Yes, yes, yes, you cheater!
Waah!
Hi, Liv.
Mommy is so bad at Simon Says
she won't even do what I say.
Four years old and
she's drunk with power.
I have created a monster!
Do you wanna
play with us?
Oh, don't do that.
Let Aunt Liv rest.
Sure.
- I'm Simon.
- Okay.
Simon says,
"Put your hands in the air."
- Okay.
- Touch your nose.
You lost!
- Okay. Again, again.
- Simon says--
Transcript:
SCG-Dream2008.cn
Final Edits By: VeRdiKT
[Subscene.com]
www.tvsubtitles.net