Hold on.
What floor?
16.
- Gonna be a nice one today.
- I think so.
Man, you don't look so good.
Are you okay?
Linda, I think something's wrong
with that guy.
Sir, you have to sign in.
Linda, call 911.
He's dead.
_.•´¯¯LIAISON¯¯`•._
¯`•.__Team__.•´¯
Retrouvez-nous chaque semaine...
pour découvrir les énigmes de
Saison 2 Épisode 13
- What Lies Below -
Bon épisode...
May I help you?
Yes, I'm looking for someone
who seems to have gotten lost.
Okay, what school is he from?
He's not from any school. He's a man.
His name is Dr. Walter Bishop.
I see. A special needs individual.
You have no idea.
When the Victoria,
the last surviving ship,
returned to its harbor of departure,
after the first circumnavigation
of the earth,
only 18 of the original 237 men
were on board.
- What happened to them?
- They all died, young lady.
Horrible and most likely
painful deaths.
You see, when you open new doors,
There is a price to pay.
Now imagine...
Tonight, you look under your bed,
And, lo and behold,
you find a monster!
And you're immediately eaten.
Now, if you hadn't looked
for the monster,
You wouldn't have found it.
And you'd still be happy in your beds,
Instead of being slowly digested
in the stomach sack of the creature.
But, with any luck,
your sisters or your brothers
might have heard your screams.
And your endeavor will serve
as a valuable lesson for them.
Excuse me, do you work here?
No, I'm a season pass holder.
But thank you. Dr. Walter Bishop.
They had no right
to revoke my membership.
- No right.
- Walter, you terrified those kids.
- These children should know the truth.
- Hello. Agent Dunham?
They're tragically
coddled and ill-advised.
Have you already told Peter?
We'll be there right away.
Come on.
Detective, I'm agent Dunham.
This is Peter Bishop.
Detective Kassel.
We've been taking witness statements,
trying to figure out what went down.
- Is the ME here yet?
- On his way.
It's a dutch license.
Radjan Vandenkemp.
I've never seen anything like this.
Lucky you.
I'm gonna talk
to some of the witnesses.
I'm agent Dunham with the FBI.
- I'll let you two talk.
- Thank you.
Did he have an appointment
here at Vitas?
No one knew him.
No one was expecting him.
I don't even think he knew
where he was going himself.
He got off the elevator,
- Seemed confused, and then collapsed.
- Okay, thanks.
It's broyles. He's downstairs.
He's gonna run Vandenkemp
and see what he can come up with.
He didn't know anybody here.
And this doesn't seem like the kind
of business that you just walk into.
Excuse me. Can I ask a question?
Sure, Mr...
Ames. Vincent Ames.
I'm the VP of geotechnical engineering.
- Will we be able to leave soon?
- Not yet, I'm afraid.
- Do we know what happened to him yet?
- That's what we're trying to figure out.
But we'll let you know
as soon as you can leave.
Mike, the courier rode up with him.
Which one's Mike?
He's sitting right over here.
Got a deceased male, age 50.
We believe he's from the Netherlands.
Walked into Vitas Petrol
at 7:30 this morning,
and his veins ruptured.
I see. Well, vasculitis
could be a cause.
Or, an arteriovenous fistula,
which is an abnormal channel
between the vessels.
Extremely high blood pressure results,
resulting in swelling of the veins.
- Until they rupture?
- No, not usually.
But then, that's why we're here,
I imagine.
Don't, no, don't!
This building must be
quarantined immediately.
No one goes in or out.
I believe we have a contagion
on our hands.
But Olivia and Peter...
They'll be trapped inside.
Quarantine the building,
agent Broyles.
I need to find out more
about the first victim, Peter.
The dutchman.
If I can find out where he came from,
where he was,
then I could begin to ascertain
what could have infected him.
We don't know yet.
Who was he coming to see?
Someone up there must know him.
Know something.
The CDC is here.
- You be careful up there, son.
- I will.
The CDC is here.
Walter, it's gonna be okay.
We should get to work.
Why is the police holding us here?
We think we're in the midst
of a virus contamination.
The centers for disease
control are here.
- Are you saying we're quarantined?
- For now, yes.
What happened to Mike?
He was infected.
Is he dead?
He was closest to him.
He was right over the guy.
You were there too, Carl.
You were next to the courier.
And Devon and Vincent.
You all got his blood on you.
Then why aren't they sick too?
How do you explain that?
I don't know, Elaine. But I'm sure
it's just a matter of time.
They shut down the airflow.
I asked detective Castle
to take care of it.
His protocol. We don't want it
to spread through the building.
So I'm gonna need to
separate you into groups.
Those who were near Vandenkemp,
if you could gather in one
of the boardrooms.
It's just a precaution
until we know what this is
and how it's being spread.
Come on, let's go!
Agent Broyles, Arnold McFadden,
Field director, CDC.
I understand
you've got two people up there.
Do we know yet whether this is
the result of a bioterrorism event?
We're looking into that possibility
as we speak, but nothing yet.
You wanted me?
Let's get a team into the lobby.
Get blood work on your way.
Cut a two-block radius
with barriers.
I will need at least half a dozen
of those samples, young man.
Excuse me, who are you?
Take me to your centrifuge.
Walter has been arrested.
Agent Broyles, thank god you're here.
Please tell these men to release me.
He breached the security line.
Claims he's FBI,
- but he's got no credentials.
- I said I was a consultant.
Dr. Bishop works with us.
His son Peter's inside the building.
I need to get back to the lab.
I'm trying to determine
what pathogen I'm dealing with.
I need a blood sample,
something to work with.
I can understand your wanting
to assist, doctor.
But I have a great deal
of experience with pathogens.
And I was chairman
of biochemistry at Harvard.
And have little patience
for small-minded bureaucrats.
That's not helping.
I'm sorry.
We need more information.
My son tells me that several people
got blood on them
from the infected man.
But only one of them died. Why him?
Why aren't the others
showing symptoms?
I must get back to my lab
and find out.
No matter what your impressions are of,
I assure you he's a valuable asset.
Hubert, you will escort
Dr. Bishop to his lab
with samples that you will
not let out of your sight.
Thank you. Thank you.
Quickly, get your pajamas off and...
Come on, let's go!
Come on, come on.
I can't find the name Vandenkemp
anywhere in this database.
But he must have been here
to see somebody.
- How far back did you go?
- Two months.
They're all calling their families.
Wanna call your sister?
Just to let her know
what's going on?
What do you make of this?
This guy, Ames,
he had two appointments this morning,
but he cleared his calendar
last minute yesterday.
But he's here.
That doesn't necessarily mean
anything.
And it doesn't necessarily
not mean anything, either.
Guys...
We have a problem.
What's happening to me?
Come on in here.
I want you to lay down and just try rest
and relax as best you can, okay?
I'm gonna get you some water.
Thank you.
Be right back.
So how much time
do you think she has?
I don't know, the courier died...
Maybe half hour
after giving Vandenkemp cpr.
She's sick?
I'm afraid so.
- But she didn't get blood on her.
- You can't be sure.
She was not near him when he died!
Which means we could all have it.
But we don't know that.
She was friends with the courier.
Maybe he touched her.
And infected her.
The fact is, we just don't know.
- But it's important to stay calm.
- Can I talk to you in private?
Okay, I know Mr. Vandenkemp
was here to see you.
Your schedule was rearranged yesterday
and your morning was cleared out.
Why was he here?
He came here to sell me information
from one of our competitors.
What kind of information?
All he said was it was
from a recent reserve find.
Maybe Vandenkemp came in contact
with the virus there,
so do you know which oil reserve?
- Which competitor was it?
- He wouldn't say.
All he said was,
"I have something to show you."
Something I would
find very valuable.
He was supposed to be gone
before the staff came in this morning.
Well, where is it,
- the information?
- I don't know.
He didn't have anything with him.
It's a very competitive business,
agent Dunham. I know what I did breaks
a dozen federal laws, but I'd rather go
to prison than die here.
Well, it may be too late
to trade one for the other now,
Mr. Ames.
Radjan Vandenkemp
was an oil consultant.
He arrived at Logan three days
ago on a flight from Dubai.
We've already contacted 174
of the 212 passengers on board.
No one's shown
any signs of infection.
- Were you able to track his movements?
- He was staying at a continental inn.
We have agents at the hotel.
No symptoms reported there either,
but also no indication of any
information he was selling.
Have you heard from Walter?
Has he been able to identify the virus?
No, not yet, but I'll
let you know when I do.
If we can isolate
the strain, we may be
able to understand
this virus's personality.
The personality?
- Walter, it's not a person.
- Centrifuge is over there.
No, viruses are not people, Astrid.
But they seem
to have minds of their own.
The rabies virus
can't survive in water.
So it inflicts its host
with a paralyzing fear of water.
Walter, that sounds...
Heh, trust me, I know how it sounds.
It's almost beyond belief.
The more we learn about viruses,
the more unbelievable they become.
They deny our definitions
of living and dead.
And their only function seems to be
to survive, to replicate.
And they use us
as a vehicle to do so.
It's the folly of humans to believe
we're at the top of the food chain.
In truth, viruses are.
The strain won't isolate.
- The sample was too fragile.
- Damn it.
I was afraid of that.
Well, this is one piece
of good news.
I believe the virus is not airborne.
No. If it were,
there'd be many more people
showing signs of infection
in that building.
We need a better sample.
Broyles have anything?
Whatever Vandenkemp was trying
to sell, they can't find it.
You able to get a hold of Rachel?
I didn't try.
She just went through all this stuff
with me in the hospital,
and she's still having nightmares
about me being dead.
What's the point
in scaring her again?
We are gonna get out of this.
That's just like you.
Even now, you're protecting her.
I thought that was
the point of having people
who care about you in your life...
to have someone to talk
to when you're scared.
She's out.
The receptionist.
What the hell's happening up there?
Peter, be careful.
Can't wait any longer.
Stop it!
Get away from him now!
I got his blood on me. If I wasn't
infected before, I probably am now.
- Peter, this is insane!
- They're down there and we're up here.
And they're not sending
anybody else up.
This is our last chance
to figure out whatever it was
that he came here to try and sell.
Rental car keys.
Never take anything into a negotiation
that can land you in jail.
Always leave it
in neutral territory.
The CDC is opening
the briefcase now.
You said his car was found
in a garage nearby.
- It's underground?
- That's right.
I believe I have a hypothesis
- as to how this virus behaves.
- Go on.
Well, the receptionist had
a very different reaction
to the virus
than the other two victims.
And I believe I know why.
This virus...
has to spread itself,
but in order to do so,
it needs other organisms to infect.
Vandenkemp arrived alone
at the building,
and it wasn't until he was in an
office full of people that he sprayed.
But...
having successfully
infected other people,
I believe that the virus
now senses that
it's contained within the building,
And... and it wants to get
outside to continue spreading.
The virus wants to get outside?
Doesn't that strike even
you as a bit far-fetched?
No...
the courier only spewed
As he approached the glass doors.
And from what you've said,
the receptionist
showed an irrational desire
to get outside,
and then she sprayed.
The virus compelled her
to leave the building.
It wanted to get outside.
You're saying
the virus made her jump.
Yes. Yes!
I believe so.
Among other things in the briefcase,
we found a drill core sample
from an exploratory oil dig.
This is our virus.
The sample was stolen
from solum oil corp.
By normal procedure,
it would have been stored
in an airtight, protective case.
Which suggests Vandenkemp
may have removed it
in order to smuggle it out.
Do those documents indicate
how far down it came from?
It came from ten miles down.
In that case,
I believe we're in the presence
of a 75,000 year-old terror.
One that might have been responsible
for wiping out the ice age mammals.
Some things are meant
to be left alone.
Dr. Bishop,
can you find a cure for it?
Maybe, in time.
But right now, we need
to keep the safe people safe.
Now that I have an isolated sample,
I can produce a tox screen.
At least we can identify
who's been infected.
Would diamonds or emeralds do?
- Bill Hubert, CDC.
- Hi.
So, how do you want to do this?
Two groups.
We divide alphabetically.
Okay, I can do that.
"A" through MS, if you come with me.
And the rest can go
with agent Hubert.
Call the state department.
Get approval
for a level six eradication.
Level six?
We don't know how to contain it.
If anybody on the outside
got infected...
- Thank you.
- No problem.
How we doing in here?
We're just getting started.
First up, Vincent Ames.
Hohow will I know?
If you're infected,
the solution will turn black.
Swab.
Please swab the inside
of your cheek.
Amber.
You're clear.
We'll be in touch.
All right, next is Peter,
and then Olivia.
Ladies first.
Swab your cheek.
You're not infected.
You're okay.
Okay, next.
Okay, let's get
this first group downstairs.
You guys, come with me.
Let's go.
This is the first batch of uninfected
from both testing groups.
Nona Norris.
Lauren Nossel.
Glen Paulsen.
Vincent Ames.
Wait, stop!
He's bleeding from the nose.
- He's infected.
- I just have to get outside.
Stop him!
Get him away from the door!
I just have to get outside!
I just have to get outside.
I'm infected?
I'm afraid so.
But I wasn't near anyone.
Steve,...
you need to come with me.
Olivia, please!
- Please, you've got to open this door.
- Peter, I can't. You know that.
Look at me.
Just look at me.
I'm fine.
Amber. You're clear.
Olivia,
we just finished the tox screens.
Peter is infected.
The test was wrong.
I don't know how, but...
but he's bleeding from his nose
and he's still in the building.
What was that about Peter?
The cambodian outbreak of '04...
killed 7,300 people, most of which
could have been avoided
if the Chinese authorities
had moved quicker.
That was level four.
This is classified as six.
Right now, it's the only option.
- They finished the tox screens.
- I heard.
11 civilians infected,
and your colleague.
I'm sorry.
So what do we do now?
Extract the rest
of the ones that tested negative,
and the state department
has authorized us
to have the army move
in and contain the rest.
The army?
It's the only definitive way to make
sure that the virus is eradicated.
There are still a dozen
people in that building.
You cannot tell me that killing
them is our only option.
Come with me.
Run it for her.
This model is based on just one
of those people getting out
and infecting someone
on the outside.
This is two weeks from now.
We have no symptom blocker, no cure.
What solution do you propose,
agent Dunham?
Walter, you can't take that off.
It doesn't matter.
The virus isn't airborne.
It's transmitted by bodily fluids,
blood, saliva.
Walter,
we are going to figure this out.
Peter's gonna be fine.
It's time to go.
We're taking all non-infected personnel
out of the building... now.
Walter, we'll have
to help Peter from outside.
Come on, Walter, let's go.
- Astrid, where are you?
- Walter won't leave.
He thinks he can
come up with a cure.
Does he have any idea
how to do that?
No, not yet.
Astrid, they're giving up.
The CDC doesn't want
to risk contamination,
so they're planning on killing
everyone inside.
You can't be in there.
Walter will figure something out.
We're gonna be fine.
What did agent Dunham want?
Nothing.
Help me drag this dutchman
into the kitchen.
There's a table in there,
and a sink.
Homo sapiens persevered...
100 millennia ago.
So something
must have killed this virus.
Slower metabolisms,
evolving blood types.
Unless the wretched virus
isn't organism-specific.
If I had an animal,
a cat or a mouse...
No, there's no time for that,
of course.
What can I do?
I can't let Peter die again.
And he's going to.
They all will.
And there's nothing
I can do about it.
Walter,
do you remember this morning?
What you said at the science museum.
That Magellan
set sail around the world
with a crew of 237 people.
237.
Nearly all of whom died.
Yeah, but 18 of them didn't.
That's what you said, Walter.
Despite the odds, 18 of them
came back to their families.
The rest died of scurvy.
A slow, horrific death.
Uncontrollable diarrhea,
pustulous bleeding.
They all died.
Except...
We're still here.
75,000 years ago,
our virus here
wiped the planet clean.
Then life resumed.
So something...
Must have killed...
The active virus.
- Ash.
- Astrid.
Ash.
Mount toba...
The biggest volcanic eruption
for the last 25 million years.
It blocked out the sun.
Sulfuric ash...
rained down.
All around the world.
Sulfur.
Sulfur!
- That could be it.
- Where do we get sulfur?
Open the fridge.
Now, tell me
what we've got to work with.
There's diet soda.
There's relish, there's...
There's yogurt, there's string cheese,
there's horseradish, there's milk...
Horseradish! Horseradish, good.
Grab that.
The glycoside in horseradish
is high in sulfur.
If I'm right,
this should attack the virus.
Thank you.
Sulfide
diluted to four parts per million.
Then apply heat
to catalyze the base.
1.5 ccs should be enough.
I got it.
After we've notified
the families of the deceased,
We'll release a statement.
The virus has been controlled.
And we don't have any fear
of a further outbreak.
- Walter found a cure.
- I'll call you back.
This is what he needs.
Sulfide base, neuraminidase blocker.
We'd need a chemical supply lab.
The closest one's in wellesley.
And several hours
to synthesize the antidote.
I'm sorry,
we just don't have that long.
That glass isn't gonna hold
much longer.
- What if we could buy you some time?
- What are you thinking?
Fentanyl gas.
Pump it inside the building.
Knock them out long enough
to synthesize a cure.
A gas truck could be
here in 10 minutes.
Even if we could, it wouldn't disperse.
The ventilation system is down,
and I can't risk sending
any more people inside.
Then I'll do it.
That's up to agent Broyles, not me.
You've got 15 minutes.
After that, I can't take the chance.
Yes, sir.
Let us out!
Dunham, the gas truck is here.
What's your 20?
I'm in the elevator,
Proceeding to the parking garage.
- Listen, I'm here to help you.
- Give me the gun.
They're gonna shoot you.
They're gonna kill us all anyway.
The cure is out there.
They're lying to us.
And you locked me in here.
You betrayed me!
Stay down.
Agent Dunham, can you hear me?
Agent Farnsworth.
- Sir.
- Is the ventilation system on yet?
No, sir. It's still off.
Olivia hasn't made it yet.
We have to move.
I gave you 15 minutes.
I understand you have
operational authority here.
But there are people in there
that are like family to me.
- Another ten minutes.
- I'm sorry.
Vents are on. You go.
Here, put this on.
Trust me.
You're going to be okay, Peter.
Just rest, son.
Son.
Thank you.
All of you.
You feeling better?
I'm sorry.
You weren't yourself.
It's lucky for me that you were.
Inside... Upstairs...
When you said,
"I can't let peter die again..."
What did you mean by that?
Some things
are meant to be left alone.