Previously on Fringe...
We have evidence that indicates
William Bell may be involved
with several biological attacks.
I will turn this world over
looking for him.
William Bell is not in this world.
I've been waiting for this.
- Who are you?
- I'm William Bell.
Where am I?
You were missing from your car
for at least an hour
- before you came crashing back.
- He told me something.
- Who?
- I can't remember.
But It was very important.
There's something that I have to do.
Walter thinks, he was a shape-changing
soldier from another universe.
Charlie, what if I don't
want to remember?
Mind if we speed things up, Kurt?
I'd hate for these popsicles to melt.
I don't think we have
to worry about that.
Cargo is secure.
Who is this guy?
Could I get some directions?
What are you doing here?
You're trespassing, pal.
Why don't you get in your car
and turn around?
Sure.
Oh, my God! Son of a bitch!
We got to call...
- Anyone else in the warehouse?
- That's it.
The keys are in his pocket.
Let me know if he's in there.
You know where to reach...
_.•´¯¯LIAISON¯¯`•._
¯`•.__Team__.•´¯
Retrouvez-nous chaque semaine...
pour découvrir les énigmes de
Saison 2 Épisode 04
-Momentum Deferred-
Bon épisode...
100, Walter.
Almost, 50 more chops.
So, you said you wanted to see me.
I had an idea.
I think I may be able
to help you retrieve your memories
From the accident, when you disappeared
from the automobile in New York.
- I remember that bit.
- Of course you do.
Walter, I thought that we agreed
that this was a stupid idea.
No, you decided. I still maintain
that the principle is perfectly sound.
He wants you to eat worms.
Not just worms, flatworms!
The thing is,
I recalled an experiment
that Belly and I did
where we trained a handful of flatworms
to respond to light.
We then crushed them up
and fed them to other worms.
It was Belly's idea.
Because who wouldn't
think to do that?
The point is
that these other worms,
without having been trained,
Began to respond to light.
It seems the first worms
transferred their memories
to the other worms
through ingestion.
Right, but that still has nothing to do
with stimulating Agent Dunham's memory.
How will we know unless we try?
That's why it's called an experiment.
- I know what an experiment is.
- If Archimedes
- never decided to take a bath...
- Guys?
Astrid, water.
I was going to mix it
with strawberries.
Bishop's deli.
This is what we know so far.
Facility manager arrived
to work this morning at 6:30,
saw the bodies and called it in
to the local PD.
So, the robbery took place
in the middle of the night.
That makes three cryogenic facilities
in a week,
same MO as Chicago and New York.
But Chicago was
a straight "B" and "E."
But in all three cases,
the target was the same.
Frozen heads.
Which does bring up
several obvious questions.
First of which, what the hell for?
Police recovered ten shell casings
from a nine millimeter.
Looks like a single perp rolled up
and dropped four men,
two of whom were armed.
Excuse me.
Can I see the body
that's bleeding silver now?
Fascinating.
Perfect, son.
It has the consistency of mercury.
These robberies
are obviously connected.
We should pull the files
on New York and Chicago.
I'll make some calls,
tell the local agents that we're taking
over the investigations.
Yes, sir.
- You okay?
- Yeah. So, what does Walter think?
Meet Mr. Silver-Blood.
Walter thinks it's actually mercury.
Mercury?
Agent Francis, hello.
You all right? You look pale.
I didn't get much sleep last night.
I may be able to help you with that.
A little cannabis before bedtime
does wonders?
I recognize this.
This is the device
the shape-shifter used.
You look like hell.
That was...
That was sloppy.
You killed four men last night,
including one of our own.
There's nothing to link him to us.
Maybe not,
but now the FBI...
They have him.
They understand...
what he is.
You've been in this body too long.
You're dying.
You need to get back home and get fitted
with a new conversion device.
I'd let you use mine...
but what would be the point?
It wouldn't do anything anyway.
You've asked for extraction.
They say not until the mission...
is done.
They're real sweethearts.
Damn.
That's the last one.
He's not here.
There's another facility
in North Carolina.
I have another idea.
Olivia Dunham...
is starting to remember her time
on the other side.
I'm thinking...
she may know where it's hidden.
His head?
What makes you think that?
If Bell knows that
we're looking for it,
it seemed like a likely reason
why he'd bring her
over to the other side.
Well, if you're right,
and you don't want that
body to be your last,
then I suggest you do whatever it takes
to make her remember.
Why?
Why...
Why are shape-shifting soldiers from
another universe stealing frozen heads?
The most likely explanation
that we can think of
is that they're looking
for a specific head,
but they don't know where it is.
- Then who?
- We don't know.
These facilities
pride themselves on secrecy.
So despite the thefts,
none of them have been willing
to give up their client lists.
What about the other device,
the one we found a few weeks ago?
Did it give any indication
who these people are?
Unfortunately,
the other device is broken.
We asked Massive Dynamic
what they could make of it,
but apparently they've been stumped.
Well, this one
doesn't appear to be damaged.
So maybe Peter
can figure something out.
I suppose he knows a guy?
He knew enough about engineering
to fake his way into MIT.
Let me know if you learn anything.
In the meantime,
I'm considering giving you
a protective detail.
A protective detail? Why?
The last time Peter showed me
one of these devices,
its owner had just tried
to kill you.
I'm not worried,
'cause that was six weeks ago.
So if a shape-shifting assassin
wanted me dead...
then I would be.
Let's see how this thing operates.
What are you saying,
this is not a person?
My dear, I'm not certain that you're not
simply a figment of my imagination.
No, this is certainly not human,
rather a highly advanced
technology...
A mechano/organic hybrid.
I suspect that they produce
or possibly ingest the mercury
and that it controls the tissue,
instructing it to take
and maintain shapes.
What?
We have to call Agent Dunham.
I need to talk to her right away.
You know what this reminds me of?
Did you ever see that movie
Invasion of the Body Snatchers?
Which version...
Don Siegel or Philip Kaufman?
The remake.
I remember when I saw that movie, I was
so scared, I didn't sleep for a week.
I was convinced that if I fell asleep,
I was gonna be replaced by a pod person.
Is this your way of trying
to ask me if I'm scared?
Of course not.
I figure if you were scared,
you'd tell me, right?
Besides,
I figure between the two of us,
you're the one that carries the gun.
What the hell?
What is it?
I'm not sure.
I was just trying to turn it on, but...
Looks like this thing
is streaming data...
and lots of it.
I've got good news and bad news.
The bad news is
that the shape-shifter's blood
47% mercury.
Which means?
Well, I'm not sure,
but I went back and re-examined
the autopsy reports
for the first shape-shifter.
- And?
- And...
her blood sample
is perfectly normal...
Just traces of mercury,
which would suggest that,
despite what we thought back then...
She wasn't a shape-shifter at all.
- I'm afraid so.
- So the shape-shifter is still alive,
which means by now,
- it could be disguised as anyone.
- And you could still be in danger.
Would you like to hear
the good news now?
I think I may know how to find him.
You showed us this.
The girl you experimented on.
Yes, to see things others could not.
Oh, yes, a soldier...
From somewhere else.
- There.
- He's glowing, man.
If she was able to identify
the shape-shifter once,
she may be able to do it again.
He's from a place that looks like this,
but it's not here.
He's from another universe, man.
Looks like we may have some leads
on how to identify the shape-shifters.
Walter has an idea, and I have
a thought about the device.
But in the meantime,
can you check in with Broyles,
see if there's something new
from the crime scenes?
Sure thing.
Starting your own pharmacy?
You found another one.
Peter says this device
is streaming loads of data,
and he also believes it's possible
that these devices store a pattern
of their last victim.
Our scientists have the same theory.
In fact, they thought they might
be able to extract an image.
They also theorize that each device
is tuned to a specific user,
which suggests that since
the shape-changer that tried to kill you
no longer has his device,
he's trapped in his current body.
Our scientists have been working on
revealing that shape-shifter's identity,
but what with all the damage
to the other unit...
Well, this one is intact.
Then let's take a look, shall we?
So can you fix it?
Do you understand you're asking me
if I can repair a piece of technology
that is entirely unlike anything
that has ever existed here on Earth?
Now that I have one that works,
I can do it in three hours... tops.
Good, then get started right away.
I'm gonna head back to Boston.
Will you call me if he gets it working?
I can do better than that.
I can set up a rendering program
and patch you in...
in real time.
If you want, you can see it
all for yourself
from a computer, from your cell phone,
I can log you into our server.
The public one.
The public server, of course...
if it's okay with you.
- Nice house.
- Yes, it's lovely.
Rebecca always had fine taste.
Do you think she'll remember me?
I think she might.
I'm gonna guess there's not too many
men in her life who have strapped her
to a table and pumped her full of
a massive amount of psychedelics.
Walter, you didn't...
What, son?
Nothing.
Peter, wait.
Could you do the talking?
Please, son.
Sure.
I'm Peter Bishop.
- Is it you?
- Hello, Rebecca.
At first, I assumed it was all
just a figment of my imagination
and the LSD, of course.
But after a while,
it wasn't just during the experiments.
I would see their faces
in front of me.
They seemed to have, I don't know,
a certain glow about them.
The shape-shifters?
It took me a year or two to...
really understand it.
But I realized that...
I was recognizing people that...
didn't belong.
You know,
like that children's song...
"One of These Things
is Not Like the Others."
is Not Like the Others.
One of These Things Just Doesn't
Belong." Sesame Street.
Yes, that's it.
Our experiment triggered an ability
to see beyond the limits of your vision.
You gave me a great gift, Walter.
You...
opened my mind for a time.
In fact, I even tried to look you up
about ten years ago,
tried to contact Harvard,
but no one knew where you were
or how to reach you.
- I was...
- Traveling.
My father was traveling.
You said "for a time." Does that mean
that the ability has faded?
Not entirely, no.
Comes and goes as it pleases.
I just have...
memories.
These people... The shape-shifters...
We have reason to believe
that some of them
are amongst us right now.
We were hoping that you might
be able to help us identify them.
I told you, it's mostly gone.
What if you could get it back?
Your ability?
You mean do the experiment again?
Which I must advise against.
Anytime one exposes one's brain
to that amount of hallucinogens...
Yeah, sure.
I'll help you.
Just a couple more.
Actually, that one goes
more on my temple.
You're an old pro at this, huh?
Drug-infused mystical awakenings,
guided by your father,
aren't exactly something
you can forget.
I'm Agent Olivia Dunham.
Thank you so much for doing this.
You said you wanted to start her
with salvia. We don't have any salvia.
You used to...
in that cabinet on the second shelf
over on the right.
Got it.
I don't suppose you recall
where I left my slippers.
Excuse me.
Could you do me a favor?
Do you think you could log onto
this site from your computer?
"Massive Dynamic."
This looks like their secure FTP.
Sure thing.
This is the first
of the psychedelics.
Ready to begin?
I think I've been ready
for the past ten years.
It's working.
The tech must be rebuilding
the image from the broken device.
It looks like
a department store mannequin.
Now let's just load it up
on my phone.
When Belly and I first did this,
we prepped her for 36 hours.
But I'm thinking...
for this type of spatial disorientation
we can reduce it to a few moments.
- Isn't that dangerous?
- More than injecting her with...
substantial amounts of untested,
homemade psychoactive drugs?
Get me three syringes
of phenothiazine.
It's on the top shelf,
under "A" for "Anti-Psychotics."
And two vials of Valium...
just to be safe.
- Ready?
- Yes, son.
I want you to tell me if this starts
to get uncomfortable, okay?
Thank you.
I met you once before.
You were just a baby, but...
I swore I saw...
Here we go!
I think we're ready.
Focus on my voice.
What?
Concentrate on the people
who don't belong.
You mean...
the ones that change their appearance?
There's no need to be afraid.
You can see them...
They can't see you.
Listen to my voice.
I'm going to take you
over the threshold.
We're walking through Johnston Gate
into Harvard Yard.
Can you see it?
It's autumn, and it's late.
The leaves crunch under our feet.
Past the statue of John Harvard.
Now we're passing University Hall,
Memorial Church is up ahead.
Ring.
After all these years...
it is so nice
to finally see you again.
You'll have to forgive me.
The method by which I brought you over
here was crude and I'm sorry for that,
but there were people who were
trying to prevent our meeting.
This is not at all the kind of reunion
I'd always envisioned.
The reunion that you had envisioned?
Dr. Bell, I have been trying
to meet with you for over a year.
Please, call me William...
or "Willam"...
if that feels warmer to you.
That's what you always called me
when you were a girl.
How do you like your tea?
I don't want any tea.
I want answers.
You're still a little disoriented
from the time slips, aren't you?
Happened to me
when I first came here.
You're out of sync with this side.
You're lucky. Most people
who cross dimensions
without your natural talent
are simply torn apart.
Well, "lucky" isn't the word
that I would choose.
I don't know how much
Walter's told you by now.
I don't know how much he remembers.
He told me what you two did to me
when I was just a girl...
How you conducted drug trials
on young children.
We weren't trying
to hurt you, Olivia.
We weren't trying to hurt anybody.
Guess what?
You did.
I've met some of the others.
To say that they are permanently damaged
would be an understatement.
In any search for knowledge,
there are always
unintended consequences...
Victims, you might say.
But not you.
I can see that...
just by looking at you.
In fact, you're just coming
into your ability.
I've seen history repeat
itself enough times to know
a war is coming,
just as we predicted,
Walter and I, years ago,
and we knew that we had
to prepare a guardian,
someone to watch the gate.
The gate?
Between this side and yours.
I would like to say "ours,"
because that's where I came from,
but I'm afraid
I would sound disingenuous.
Go on.
For reasons that will
become clear in time,
I cannot go back yet,
maybe not ever.
But now we know how difficult
it is to cross over.
I can count on my hand the number
of people who've done it safely.
But on this side,
they've become more insidious.
They have designed hybrids...
Part organic tissue, part machine...
that can do things
that humans can't.
They can change shapes,
taking the form of human beings.
Over here, they call them
"the first wave."
So you're saying that these hybrids
are already on our side.
I know it's difficult to grasp.
I can grasp it just fine.
I don't trust you, Dr. Bell...
or William or...
Willam...
or whatever cutesy name
you think might appeal
to my childhood instincts.
It won't.
Your company has been involved in,
if not directly responsible for,
some of the most horrific things
that I have ever seen,
to say nothing of the fact
that you just yanked me
into a parallel universe
to warn me about
an inter-dimensional war
that I believe you are
responsible for starting.
So what I want is not warmth or tea.
It's the truth.
The truth will come out.
It always does.
Livvy,...
you don't have to trust me.
You don't even have to like me,
but you can't deny
I have a unique perspective,
shaped by having lived
in two worlds.
I know the difference
a wrong choice can make...
or a right one.
For example, this building
is still standing
because different choices were made.
So, Livvy,...
if you can look past your anger,
you may find that I'm more
of an ally than you think.
A storm is coming,
perhaps the last
and worst storm of all.
And when it is over,
I fear there will be
little left of our world.
The shape-shifters on your side
are looking for someone,
someone to open the door
between universes,
and if they find him,
there will be no stopping them,
and that is why you
must find him first.
Me?
You are the one, Olivia.
Of all the children
that Walter and I prepared,
you were the strongest.
You were always the strongest.
Remember this symbol.
It's hidden on their leader.
That's how you'll know him.
Show this to Nina Sharp.
She can help you.
We're out of time.
Olivia!
Can you hear me?
Astrid, nitroglycerine, 30 CCs.
Please turn the head to the side,
make sure she can breathe.
What's happening?
She's receiving a flood of memories.
It could be too much, too fast.
You should stand.
I think it'll be
less painful that way.
What will?
And remember this...
Einai kalytero...
Anthropo apo ton patera toy.
Tell that to Peter.
You're going to need him by your side.
Tell it to him.
He'll know what it means.
We have to shock her heart.
There's a vial of adrenaline, Peter.
And I'm afraid there's no avoiding
what has to happen next.
I pulled you out of a moving car.
Momentum can be deferred,
but it must always
be paid back in full.
Into her heart, between the ribs.
Count three. One, two...
As I once said to Walter,
physics is a bitch.
- Three!
- Sorry, Olivia.
I need to speak to Nina Sharp.
- Nina Sharp.
- Nina, we need to talk.
I'm on my way there now.
I'm sorry. I'm just about
to leave for Hong Kong.
I have a message from William Bell.
Cancel the plane.
I wish I could have been
more of a help to you.
You did great.
- You sure you're all right to drive?
- She's fine.
The injections I gave her
would have counteracted
any hallucinogenics in her system.
I think I'd like
to drive home with her.
You just said that all the drugs
were out of her system.
How are you gonna get back home?
The bus.
Peter, I need some money.
He said okay.
Terrific.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
You too, Peter.
Say good-bye to Agent Dunham
for me, will you?
What?
Nothing. I...
I'm sorry.
It's probably just the drugs.
Where is everyone?
Peter and Dr. Bishop are out,
and Olivia went to New York
to see Nina Sharp.
- I can call her. She just left...
- No, that's okay.
I'll talk to her when she gets back.
What is this?
That's Massive Dynamic.
They're rebuilding the image
from the broken device.
Dr. Bell showed you this?
Have you ever seen
that before... that symbol?
Well, that's what he told me.
He said it would be hidden
somewhere on their leader's body.
Well, then I suspect
it would be on his head,
assuming that's what
the cryogenic hijackings are about.
And that's all Dr. Bell told you?
He said that the man
with that mark...
would try to open a door
between our two worlds...
that a storm was coming,
and that the only way to stop it
would be for me to find him
before the shape-shifters did.
A storm?
What?
It was a phrase he used.
When Dr. Bell realized
the existence of the other side,
the thing he dreaded most
was the inevitable collision...
if our two universes
ever came together.
Collision?
The Pauli exclusion principle
means that no two objects can occupy
the same space at the same time.
Dr. Bell was afraid
that if the doorway
between the two sides
was ever opened
that the unavoidable conclusion...
only one world would remain.
It's what he called
the last great storm.
Laston-Hennings Cryonics.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Whatever Massive Dynamic can do
to help find this man,
we're at your service.
- How'd you know?
- Listen to me carefully.
My car's around the corner,
we got a SWAT team inbound.
As soon as I verify
you're out of this building,
they're gonna shred this place.
Let's move.
Oh, God, Charlie,
I almost told her everything.
- I got to call Broyles.
- What do you mean "almost"?
Well, I just realized where it is,
the head that they're looking for.
Bell told me.
It's at Laston-Hennings Cryonics.
It's me.
Laston-Hennings Cryonics.
What are you doing?
Won't you come in?
I don't think I should.
The bus leaves
every half hour, and...
I only have 14 minutes
to walk to the stop.
Some day, huh?
Not at all what I expected
when I woke up this morning.
That's the way of things.
The best days and
the worst days rarely are.
Rebecca, what I did to you...
It was wrong.
Not, no. You were young,
and I took advantage,
and...
I've wanted to do that for so long.
What you did...
You made me...
special.
The truth is...
I believe you were always special.
I must go...
under 12 minutes.
You had no choice.
If you didn't kill him,
he would have killed you.
It's not your fault.
Whatever...
that thing was, it wasn't Charlie.
They killed him for what?
To open a door to the other side?
And who are these people,
and what do they want?
What did we do to them?
Laston-Hennings Cryonics
was hit 15 minutes
before our protective detail arrived.
They took everything.
All the cryo-capsules are gone.
So they found
who they were looking for.
I assume so.
William Bell pulled me
to another universe...
to give me a warning.
That's how important this is.
And I failed.
We'll find them.
À la semaine prochaine !