Color and sound check,
Milton/Staller wedding.
Linda, Neal.
Hi, Mr. Staller.
- Glad you could make it.
- Good to see you.
Take it easy, Nana.
There's no hurry.
You take it easy.
This my regular speed.
- Everyone decent in here?
- Come on in, Mrs. Staller.
Look who I brought, Shelley.
This is how David can see you
in your dress before the wedding
without the bad luck.
You look stunning.
Thank you so much for...
everything.
I'm so happy
you're joining the family.
David is lucky to have you.
I'm crying now.
Let's not film this part.
No, no. Turn it off, turn it off.
- It'll calm him down.
- I didn't think I'd be this nervous.
Happens to everyone, even me.
And look how I turned out.
Lynn...
Who is that man?
I don't know.
Must be from Shelley's side.
Just breathe, man.
No, where's your inhaler?
- Where is it?
- It's here.
Harry, just give us a few minutes?
Sorry.
You're all right.
Just a couple minutes.
He's okay. He's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
I can safely say David
is not going to run.
So just everybody hang tight.
He'll be fine. He's just had
a little bit of a reaction...
It can't be.
- It can't be true.
- What's wrong, Nana?
It can't be.
- It's him.
- Nana, what are you talking about?
It's him.
You! You!
Nana, what's wrong?
Nana, my God, what is it?
Oh, my God.
Someone call 911.
Josh!
Sweetheart!
My God!
What is happening?
_.•´¯¯LIAISON¯¯`•._
¯`•.__Team__.•´¯
Retrouvez-nous chaque semaine...
pour découvrir les énigmes de
Saison 2 Épisode 14
- The Bishop Revival -
Bon épisode...
Agent Dunham.
- Detective.
- Burt Manning. We spoke on the phone.
- So has anyone touched anything?
- ME is inside.
We put them in a holding
pattern until you got here.
It's pretty bad.
Do we have a final count
on the victims?
14... so far.
I quite like weddings.
Did I ever tell you
about when your mother and I,
- God rest her soul, got married?
- I think I missed that one.
And try to stop driving
with both feet.
She was so beautiful, Peter.
So beautiful in white.
I won't deny I was never happier.
I kept my tuxedo
in the hope that one day
I would have a son who would wear it.
You could wear it
on your wedding day.
Yeah, you know, Walter?
- Tuxedo styles change.
- Nonsense.
Purple never goes out of style.
And the day may come
sooner than you think.
Do you think she'll call me Dad?
Who?
Agent Dunham.
My guess would be no.
Don't look at me like that.
She's just what you need.
Someone who can see
right through you.
Agent Dunham,
don't you look lovely today?
- Doesn't she look lovely, Peter?
- You look lovely, Agent Dunham.
Dr. Walter Bishop.
How do you do?
Lose a bet?
It was either that
or flying lessons.
Swelling of the vitreous humor.
Petechial hemorrhaging.
Yeah, not to mention the blue skin.
It's definitely asphyxiation.
The airway's clear.
Yeah, same here.
No fluid in the lungs.
So all the victims that I've identified
so far are on the groom's side.
I mean, maybe they came in contact
with something before the wedding.
Anaphylactic shock.
Maybe they're all having an allergic
reaction to something they ate or drank.
That would be logical, if they were
all exposed at the same time.
I'll have the detectives reconstruct
where they all were.
We may find a connection.
She was a Holocaust survivor.
That's dreadful...
to survive a thing like that...
and finish up like this.
Walter, do you think this could be
a deliberate attack?
I don't know yet.
All I know for certain is that
these 14 people suffocated
in a room full of air.
There's gotta be something
they all ate or drank.
There, maybe that.
It's hard to believe that a few hour ago
this was actually a happy place.
Oh, my God!
We need a medic on the second floor!
All right.
He's dropped his inhaler.
Grab it.
It's curious. All 15 victims.
- So they're all blood relatives, then.
- Yes.
All of the victims are direct
descendants of Eva Staller.
Holocaust survivor.
And anyone not related
to her survived,
along with one grandchild
who I think might be illegitimate.
Therefore, not a blood relative,
or I suspect
he would have perished too.
Astrid, can you come here, dear?
What color is this?
The blood?
- It's blue.
- Good.
Then I'm not imagining it.
Something has bonded
with the hemoglobin in the blood,
changing its color
and robbing the body of oxygen.
I believe these people literally
suffocated from the inside out.
No, that might...
be what killed him.
No, that kept him alive
longer than the others.
I suspect it temporarily
weakened the toxin.
That still leaves the how.
How was the toxin delivered?
Mrs. Staller, I understand that you were
in charge of the guest list?
Did you notice anyone who shouldn't
have been at the wedding?
Someone who wasn't invited.
No. Of course, I don't know
the bride's entire family.
Although, my mother-in-law,
she was very upset
with someone before...
A man I had never seen before.
I thought she was just
having a moment.
If we showed you the video,
you would be able to point him out?
I could try.
It's jasmine.
Shelley picked out the scent.
Represents happiness and love.
Do you mind giving me a moment?
Of course.
I'll help you with the video.
Thank you.
She said all the rest of the candles
in this place are jasmine, right?
Smell that.
This one's cinnamon.
And?
Patience, son.
Like when you were a little boy,
your mother used to say
you had ants in your pants.
Put that in the spectrometer.
That's the man
that Mrs. Staller identified.
- Can you make it clearer?
- I can try.
- That's the best I can do.
- All right.
Upload it to the joint law
enforcement database
and maybe we'll get a hit.
- All right.
- Walter.
Come here.
Take a look at this.
That is interesting.
You were right.
This is our toxin.
Appears to be a variant of...
What is that?
Hydrogen cyanide?
The candle would suggest
that it was activated by heat,
and then dispersed into the air.
If it was in the air, how come it
only killed some of the guests?
Good question.
What?
Chemical weapons.
Death by asphyxiation.
The Nazis.
I knew this was familiar.
- The Nazis?
- The Nazis were scientific pioneers.
They attempted to advance
every branch of science...
Molecular bombs,
flying saucers, eternal youth.
Before DNA was even discovered,
Josef Mengele
wanted to create a weapon
capable of targeting
specific victims,
a weapon capable of...
of picking people out in a crowd,
just like what happened here.
It seems that science may have finally
caught up with Nazi ambition.
Mrs. Staller was a Holocaust survivor.
Do you think that's...
Relevant?
I don't know, Olivia.
Of course, I'm not saying
that this is the work of the Nazis.
Nor suddenly am I convinced
that this was just a murder.
A wedding...
is the perfect laboratory.
You have your target group,
the Stallers,
and you have your control group,
everyone else.
Are you saying that you think
this was a science experiment?
It's a theory.
And one that I think I can prove.
How?
A scientist always tries
to recreate his results.
If I'm right,
this will happen again.
One soy latte, one orange juice,
two yogurts.
Say thank you, Jordan.
Thank you.
I'd like a cup of tea, please.
And make sure the water is very hot.
Sure thing.
What kind of tea?
I don't know... You pick.
Whichever is your favorite.
And please...
Make sure the water is very hot.
So do you like her?
Mrs. Greenwalt?
Yeah, she's nice.
But she always makes us
take a nap after lunch.
Well, maybe you need time
to get your energy back.
I think Mrs. Greenwalt
is the one who's sleepy.
She's very smart, your daughter.
Yeah, she is.
Soon you'll be outsmarting
the teachers.
Well, we're already there. We're talking
about skipping her up a grade.
Don't be in too much of a hurry.
These days are precious.
Soon all you will have...
are pictures.
That smells good. Is that cinnamon?
Something like that.
Nine victims.
Suffocated just like
the wedding in Brookline.
Except unlike the Stallers, none of
these people were related to each other.
Might have to rework
that hypothesis, Walter.
Maybe this toxin isn't
transmitted genetically.
It's just a theory, Peter.
Any surveillance?
No cameras inside or on the street.
Could be why our suspect
chose this place.
No candles, I suppose.
Not a single one.
Is there any other way
that this toxin could be delivered?
Any number of ways, I would think.
Simply requires
a heat source to disperse it
into the air.
- What about a cup of tea?
- Yes, thank you.
Yes, that would work.
As long as the water was hot enough.
Cinnamon.
I want this cup dusted
for prints immediately.
Yes, sir.
Right away.
Peter, can you help me?
That man there,
what color are his eyes?
Brown.
I was right after all.
It is a targeted toxin.
They all have brown eyes.
That's the common genetic trait.
Check the survivors,
but I'm sure I'm right.
It's a good thing you weren't here
at the time, or you would be dead too.
So first it was a family.
Now it's people with brown eyes.
Why is he targeting these people?
You said you think
it's an experiment.
So what... He's just killing
these people to prove that he can?
Perhaps.
I'm going to drive us
back to the lab.
I think I have an idea.
Why don't I drive?
An idea about what?
I don't know yet.
Excuse me, officer.
That man over there.
He's named Bischoff.
You mean Dr. Bishop.
Dr. Bishop.
- Did you need something?
- No, I'm just trying to place him.
He looks just like his father.
Is that the teacup?
But they could only pull
a partial print,
so no good to run
through any databases.
That's unfortunate.
But you are just in time.
Just in time for what?
Show and tell, apparently.
This is a molecular model
of the toxin.
This blue portion,
that's the deadly part.
This red part...
that's the targeted group.
In the first instance,
the Staller family...
And in this instance,
people with brown eyes.
Because he can program the toxin
to target whatever group he wants.
Any group with common
physical characteristics
or genetic similarities, yes.
Tall people, short people,
fat people, skinny people,
black people, brown people,
or white people...
We get it.
Anyway,
whoever created this
was apparently proud of his work.
Although I don't know
why he should be,
apart from the genetic targeting,
the toxin itself
is quite rudimentary.
It's a blend of chromium trioxide
- and hydrogen cyanide.
- Chromium trioxide?
That's highly regulated. If this guy
was buying it in any quantity...
- Astrid, can you...
- Dig up any companies
that deal with chromium trioxide.
So, Walter, what were you saying
about him being proud of his work?
See this?
That's a carbon chain.
It's inert.
It's the signature of the creator.
Some chemists spell out
their initials in molecules.
Others create a symbol.
Are you saying that we may be able
to identify whoever made this?
Yes, but this could be anybody's.
Well, it looks like a stylized "S",
- or a snake.
- Actually...
looks more like a sea horse to me.
A sea horse. I suppose it could...
What is it?
Die seepferdchen.
The sea horse.
I know who created this toxin.
Wait, Walter...
What's going on?
They called him "the sea horse"
because he was a great swimmer.
Okay, good for him.
But who is he?
My father.
Dr. Robert Bishop.
Wait, wait, your father?
I told you these
were Nazi experiments.
My father was a scientific pioneer
at the University of Berlin.
Yes, I know, who came here in 1933,
which is long before
the Nazis ever took power.
It was 1943.
Given the nature of his work,
I fudged the date a little.
What are you telling me?
- That my grandfather was a Nazi?
- Technically, yes.
Actually...
he worked as a spy for the Allies,
sabotaging German research and...
and smuggling scientific
information to the Americans.
I...
I knew I recognized the experiment.
I must have seen the formula
in one of my father's books.
Put this there.
Are you saying your father helped
develop the formula for this toxin?
It would seem so.
But of course, at the time,
it was just theoretical.
DNA itself was theoretical.
That formula has to be here
somewhere.
These are all of
my father's favorite books,
first editions
of Goethe, Thomas Mann...
And you're sure that all those notes
were hidden inside of German novels?
It was the only way he could smuggle
them out of Germany when he left.
You're not gonna find
those books in there.
They will be here.
- These are all the books in my library.
- No, they won't.
They're not in there.
I sold those books.
All of them.
About ten years ago.
You sold them.
Why?
I needed money.
Money?
They were my books.
He left them to me.
He knew how dangerous they were.
The odds this has anything
to do with your father's work...
The very thing
that he was trying to stop,
- you put back into the world.
- We don't know that for sure.
Yes, we do!
Of course we do.
How else would whoever is doing this
have gotten hold of the formula?
And because I failed to protect it,
my father's work is killing people.
So the killer is using a toxin
based on a formula created
by Dr. Bishop's father?
Just another skeleton
in the Bishop family closet.
It's in a book I sold.
So the formula is very complex.
We believe that the killer must
have found it in one of the books.
If we can trace the books,
then hopefully we can find him.
Then do it.
Quickly.
We'll find those books.
Come on, Bishop!
You sold me those books,
like, ten years ago.
How am I supposed to know
where they are now?
Because, Markham, you're exactly
the kind of fastidious packrat
who keeps a handwritten log
of every book he's ever sold.
Such a way with words.
How is it that a beautiful lady like you
is stuck with this guy?
It's my job.
I got plenty of books
on how to rethink your career.
"What color is your parachute?"
- "Do what you are..."
- That's thoughtful of you.
I really need you to find out
who it was who bought those books.
Whoever did may be in the midst
of a killing spree.
Sounds serious.
Give me a minute,
I'll see what I can find.
What?
You didn't really sell Walter's books
for money, did you?
Walter's got heaps
of valuable stuff.
Why did you just sell his books?
It was a long time ago.
Walter was still in St. Claire,
so I wasn't exactly very fond
of him at the time.
Those books were amongst
his favorite possessions.
And no, to answer your question,
I'm not proud of it.
They were sold last year.
The name I got is Eric Franko.
Lives over in Kendall Square.
He struck me as a real weirdo.
Coming from you,
that's saying something.
I owe you one.
Doesn't look like he's here.
Well...
why don't we just
poke around for a bit?
Freeze! FBI!
Get down on your knees.
Don't shoot me.
Please don't shoot me.
I'm not a Nazi.
I'm an artist.
It's about the banality of evil,
like the Nuremberg trials
showing history's tyrants
as these...
regular schmucks.
That's deep.
Where are the books
you bought from Markham?
The German novels.
The ones with all
the creepy stuff inside.
The Alice in Wonderland
meets the,...
The evil Nazi experiment?
Well, you're looking at one of them.
So what do those books
have to do with the FBI?
It's a long story.
So none of these have
ever been displayed.
You're the only person
who's ever seen them.
Sadly, the contemporary
art scene has yet to...
fully recognize
my particular contributions.
I'd like to get these books back...
or what's left. I'll pay you
whatever you had to pay for them.
Sure...
It's gonna take me a while
to dig them all...
But...
you should also know
the...
collage is for sale.
Or I could donate it.
Your grandfather
was a fan of modern art.
But I don't think
he would have appreciated this.
I'm sorry, Walter.
Apology not accepted.
Of course, this means the perpetrator
didn't get the formula from the books.
We don't see how he could have.
Then how on Earth
did he recreate the formula
using my father's signature,
no less?
No match on
the killer's DNA, Walter.
Great.
More bad news.
Wait, I don't understand.
His DNA?
Where did you get his DNA?
Dr. Bishop was able to get some
from the partial fingerprints...
From the skin cells in the oil.
That's pretty amazing.
Not my best work, I'm afraid.
The telomere degradation
suggested that the man
was over a hundred years old,
which is fascinating,
but not a likely possibility.
You said this toxin could be programmed
to target any genetic trait, right?
Could it be programmed
to target more than one?
Say, green eyes and
brown hair at the same time?
- Yes, I suppose it could.
- What are you thinking?
Das herrenvolk.
The master race.
The Nazis' ultimate goal.
The purification of the German
people and the white race.
So Nazi science for a Nazi agenda.
All of Hitler's dreams
in one little toxin.
What are you doing there?
I'm conducting a test...
to monitor the dispersion rate
of my experiment.
Please...
you can watch.
- What are you doing to those rats?
- Killing them.
Well, hopefully only the white ones.
I thought you were
trying to block the toxin.
I am.
But I have to replicate it before
I can figure out how to stop it.
Astrid couldn't find any companies
that purchased chromium trioxide
within the past six months. But...
our EPA contact suggested
we search for sodium chromate?
Of course.
It's a sister compound.
You treat it with sulphuric acid,
you get chromium trioxide.
Okay, well, here are
three local buyers.
- Do you recognize any of them?
- Those two...
pharmaceutical companies.
This one I've never heard of.
Shipping address
is 3340 Eastham Road.
Newton, Mass?
That's a residential address.
Sir?
It's Dunham.
I think we have a location.
Are we clear, Agent Doble?
The air is safe.
We're good!
All clear!
Makes your lab look downright homey.
Schwarzes haut,
braunes haut,
grune augen...
Genetic traits.
Eye color,
hair color, skin tone...
It's the works.
Creating the master race
by process of elimination.
Guys?
I think I found something.
Looks like he was making
some kind of ID.
Walter, this is your sweater.
Get him out of here!
We need some help downstairs!
- We need that oxygen, now!
- Oxygen...
Breathe...
Just breathe, Walter.
Breathe. Breathe.
Walter, how are you feeling?
You got me out just in time.
I'd like my sweater back.
We'll work on that, Walter.
Why did he go after you?
I don't know.
Perhaps he knew my father
betrayed the Nazis.
Were you able to get
that photo to Broyles?
He's sending it out wide.
I also found this.
I know that logo.
I have to check
the contents of the box.
Of course.
All right, go ahead.
It's the annual World Tolerance
Conference at the Boston Center
for Performing Arts.
- Do you know who he's targeting?
- No, with that spectrum of genetic
markers, the target group
could be anybody.
- We need to evacuate the building.
- I'll call the head of security.
But there are any number of foreign
dignitaries, so we follow protocol.
- That'll take time.
- We may not have it.
There are many difficulties,
but we must continue
to confront discrimination
and uphold the rights
of the oppressed.
The theme of this year's conference,
"Individual and Cultural Rights,"
was not chosen lightly.
This organization
has a proud tradition
of upholding both human rights
and cultural diversity.
Yet these goals, at times,
may appear difficult.
Together, we are committed
to the promotion of tolerance.
Whenever you're ready, I'll...
take you home.
I want you to take me
to the Performing Arts center.
I can stop this.
We're looking for the man,
or the mechanism.
It's gonna be something hot.
A candle, a coffee urn...
So...
now, remember,
he could be anywhere...
on the floor,
on the balconies...
Anywhere.
Peter, there's a candle
on every table.
I know.
They've been burning for so long.
There's no victims. He must be using
something more potent.
Walter, the conference is this way.
No, Astrid.
We need to take the higher ground.
We are on the north west corner.
- I got nothing.
- Nothing here, either.
Keep circulating.
...a difference of values,
of religions,
and of lifestyles.
We must take great care,
lest our advocacy become
its own form of oppression,
One that unjustifiably
- takes sides.
- Olivia, I'm in the bar.
It could be anything back here.
Candles, coffee pots...
It's a disaster.
Hold on a second.
Let's hold off on those
for one second.
I think I got it.
We are united by a common...
Where's the victim?
FBI. Everybody, move!
Please. Make room! Make room.
I said move! Get outta my way!
I need a paramedic!
Bischoff!
Traitor!
Dr. Bishop.
Yes, Agent Broyles?
- What you did tonight...
- Was...
to use the killer's DNA
to target him
and only him using his own toxin.
If you plan to press charges,
then so be it.
But I don't regret what I did.
Good night, Dr. Bishop.
That man...
He corrupted my father's work.
- I understand.
- No, no, it was more than that.
You see,
family is very important to me.
There's nothing I wouldn't do.
- What's this?
- It's a present.
Your father's work.
I had Franko give me everything
that wasn't totally destroyed.
Oh, look, Peter.
It's your grandfather.
Robert Bischoff?
That was his name.
He changed it
when he came over here.
Your mother always said
that you shared his noble brow.
It's a pity you never
got to know him.
You two would have gotten
along very well, I think.
You know, there is still one thing
that doesn't make any sense.
If the formula for the toxin didn't
come from your father's notes,
how did this guy get it?
Perhaps there are some mysteries
that are destined to remain unsolved.
Thank you for bringing these back.