Previously on Fringe...
You nearly died when you were a boy.
I became consumed with saving you.
I don't remember any of that.
There is more
than one of everything.
I have said too much.
I am not supposed to get involved.
What did you people do to us?
Of the children that William Bell and I
experimented on,
you were the first to identify things
from the other side.
Was it me who described it
as a glimmer?
I've never met anyone who can
do the things that you do.
I'll go get my coat.
Please don't tell him.
Our success thus far
should serve as an example
of our ability to achieve
that which most can't even imagine.
What you must understand is that,
as scientists,
we must embrace every possibility.
No limitations.
No boundaries.
There is no reason for them.
Gentlemen...
I would like you to
take a look at this.
It's a mobile telephone.
It can be made much smaller,
I assure you.
Does this work?
Not here, not yet.
This phone is digital, not analog.
It'll take us 30 years
to get up to speed.
I didn't invent it. I wish I had.
We were under the impression
Dr. Bell would be here this evening.
I'm afraid that's not possible.
Dr. Bell is in Europe.
But I am here,
so I can answer any questions
you may have.
Dr. Bishop,
is this Russian technology?
It is not.
It is quite American. But...
It is technology
from another universe.
An alternate universe
just like ours...
But more advanced in some area.
Are you suggesting you somehow
visited this alternate universe
and acquired this
advanced technology?
It is theoratically impossible
to go there.
Then how did you come
to possess this?
I copied it.
For the last several years,
William and I have been
conducting various experiments
regarding this other universe.
So based on our findings,
we developed a window of sorts,
a way of looking into
this neighboring world.
And that is why we are
asking for funding.
This is my colleague,
Dr. Carla Warren.
Hello, sirs.
This window works
by capturing errant photons
from the universe beside ours.
The window essentially stretches
the membrane between our worlds
and allows us...
to see their image from our side.
You're gonna make some sort
of alternate Manhattan appear?
It's already there, General Hames.
Dr. Warren.
At all times,
right in front of our eyes.
We just can't see it.
I'm sure you know
that the original purpose
for the so-called observation deck
of The Empire State Building
was to be a docking station...
for zeppers of course.
Gentlemen,
you are looking through a window...
into another world.
Walter, what are you doing here?
You left me no choice.
You wouldn't answer your telephone,
return my messages.
I tried to communicate.
I need time, okay?
I don't even know...
how to begin to work this out.
I think I do.
Please, Olivia,
I need to explain.
And if you wouldn't mind,
I could use a sip of something,
myself.
Have you told Agent Broyles?
But to be honest,
that doesn't mean that I won't.
I always knew that one day I'd have
to pay the price for my deception.
Well, we're not really sure
what the cost is yet, are we?
No, I suppose not.
I invented this
after William and I learned
that we had doubles on the other side.
Or maybe it was before.
I can't remember.
It's a window to the other universe.
I was a different man then.
I was going to change the world.
But you see,
after Peter became sick,
none of that seemed
to matter anymore.
The illness was genetic.
Savage.
Wasting.
I tried everything.
There was simply no hope.
At least...
not on this side.
But over there...
They're more
technologically advanced.
If the alternate Peter
was also sick over there,
then wouldn't his father be equally
motivated to find a cure?
He was.
God help me...
Any progress?
He's synthesizing
a new compound now.
He's using cobalt and magnesium.
Any idea yet how he's selecting
the filtering compounds?
Random, I think.
Chance, fate, luck of the draw.
I've given him a name, Carla.
Walternate.
This is it.
This should be the reaction.
No cure.
Perhaps with a higher
iodine purification.
- Is he...
- No, he's fine.
He's all right right now.
But...
What?
I think you should come
home now, Walter.
I think it's time you came home.
He looks worse.
Keeps asking for you.
It's not like before.
What is it like?
It's different.
He keeps saying
he wants to talk to you.
He says he's worried
he won't be able to.
I just can't bear it
when you're not here.
You know what I'm doing.
You know where I am
24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
I won't give up, Elizabeth.
I can do this.
I need you not to doubt me.
You're supposed to get some rest,
my son.
Dad?
I've almost got it.
Let me show you.
Now...
Slowly...
Watch...
one finger at a time.
You show me.
Very good.
I want you to have it,
my lucky silver dollar,
if I die.
It's okay.
I'm not scared.
Nothing's going to happen to you.
I promise.
You're going to be just fine.
Now get some rest.
Will you wake me for dinner?
I don't wanna miss it.
You're not gonna miss anything.
You know how much William
wanted to be here.
But with the meetings in Berlin...
I don't need to tell you
how important they are.
For both of you.
He wanted me to make sure
that you know how terrible he feels.
I understand.
I'm glad you came.
We didn't give him a good life.
We didn't.
He practically never
got out of the house.
He was always too sick.
He didn't go to a proper school.
He didn't have any proper friends.
He had no family but us.
We kept him so well,
we never let anyone
else get to know him.
We did the best we could.
We dealt with what we were given.
He knew he was loved.
Didn't he?
Walter, what's wrong?
You're cold. Have you been outside?
Come with me.
Walter, what is this?
How's this possible?
How are you doing this?
What I've been working on,
Elizabeth,
it's a window to another universe.
Like ours, but different.
Please.
Please turn it back on again.
Please turn it on.
I want to see him again!
I am telling you this
because I want you to know
that somewhere Peter will grow up,
somewhere he will lead
a proper life,
somewhere he will be happy,
but just not here.
And we must take comfort in this.
And we must begin to move on.
The compounds
you're using for the cure...
not random at all.
You are very smart.
You did it!
By God, you did it!
You had it, the cure.
All you have to do is
stabilize the compound,
and you can save him.
You can save him.
Their theories are fascinating.
They are not theories.
They are entertainment.
I have made...
a mistake.
So I've heard.
What were you doing in the lab?
Dr. Bishop was on
the verge of developing
a cure for the boy.
It was an important moment
he discovered me.
There was no other way
to witness the moment.
You have changed the future.
You have created a new set
of probabilities.
But...
you must agree
the moment was significant.
The boy...
is significant.
You need to take action
to restore balance.
How?
You will...
have an opportunity...
to fix this.
Dr. Warren.
Have you been here all night?
I've been working.
- Working on what?
- This.
What is this?
Walternate found a cure.
He found a cure for Peter.
And... and it works, Carla.
It's not too late.
I can save him.
Peter is dead.
I know.
Of course I know that!
I'm not talking about my Peter.
I'm talking about the other Peter,
The one on the other side.
He missed it. The other Walter.
He... he missed it and, you know...
It was right there in front of him,
And... and he didn't see it.
- He was distracted by the man.
- What man?
The man in the lab.
He was distracted.
And... and when he returned,
the positive result had failed,
and so he moved on.
Maybe he'll realize what he missed,
and he'll go back.
Carla, he is just... like... me.
I wouldn't look back,
and neither will he.
He didn't see the compound...
But I did.
And I've reproduced it.
It just needed...
Minor modification.
And without this, Peter will die.
He'll die all over again.
Which is why I have
to go over there.
What?
The casimir effect should produce
a thinner,
more porous region of space-time.
I only need to affect
the area for long enough
to cross over to the other
side with a vial of the cure.
And... and then, of course,
recreate the effect
to cross back again.
Walter, you're trying to create
a wormhole into another universe?
I think I just said that.
Where's my map?
When I looked into his
room on the other side,
I saw that his mother
had already packed
his suitcase for our lake house,
just like we do
every year at this time.
That's where we need
to find a location to set up.
Walter, I'm sorry, but you can't.
Yes, I think I can.
No, Walter, I mean you can't.
Shattering the wall
between universes would
rupture the fundamental
constants of nature.
It's a theory.
We don't know that to be true.
It's a good theory. It is why we have
been lying to the military,
telling them it's impossible.
Walter,
there has to be a line somewhere.
There has to be
a line we can't cross.
I always considered you as a scientist,
Dr. Warren...
Despite your personal needs
for religious claptrap.
I see I was wrong.
"I am become death,
destroyer of worlds."
- Don't you quote Oppenheimer to me.
- Knowledge cannot be pursued
without morality.
I may go to church every sunday,
but I also have three degrees
in theoretical physics,
and I am telling you
you cannot do this.
We both know the amount
of energy required
to create a portal will
forever ruin both universes.
For the sake of one life,
you will destroy the world.
Some things are not
ours to tamper with.
Some things are god's.
My son is dying, Dr. Warren.
I will not allow
that to happen again.
There's only room for one god
in this lab, and it's not yours.
The lake.
It's perfect.
The water will absorb
the excess energy.
And I won't be needing your assistance
any further today, Dr. Warren.
That will be all.
Walter's always been like that.
He often goes off
on flights of fancy.
But even if he was serious,
The design itself is decades
beyond anything we could imagine.
No. You don't understand.
He already has the design.
He's building it.
Yes. Dr. Bell's room, please.
Here... Here we do.
See you've changed your mind, Carla.
Good.
I'm sorry, Walter.
You disappoint me, Dr. Warren.
Go home, Nina.
There's work to be done here.
Walter, don't do this.
I'll be there and back
before you know it.
That's not the point.
We know that there's
more to it than that.
Don't mean to say
that creating a doorway
between universes is trivial.
I'm simply suggesting...
- If William were here...
- William were here?
He'd be applauding.
- That's not true.
- No? Then why isn't he here?
I... the funding, his schedule.
He's in Europe chasing funding?
Too busy to come and stop me
from destroying the universe?
How many times have
you rang him today?
Once? 20?
How many times has
he returned your call?
You know how many times that William
has encouraged me to
take this very risk?
To expedite our espionage program?
"Why simply take a peek into
the other universe, Walter,
when you can go there?"
So till now,
he couldn't make me find a way
to try to get there
until I had to find a way.
No, I don't believe that.
No, you wouldn't,
because you don't understand him.
Like everyone else, you're blinded
by the charming mannerly,
the air of intelligence,
the whole damn show.
All William Bell ever cared about
was finding a way to
increase the power and the wealth
and the legend of William Bell.
Walter,
regardless of what William wants,
or who he is,
I know why you're doing this.
I understand.
You know how much Peter meant to me,
and how difficult it will be for me
to admit that he's gone.
But... this.
This isn't the answer.
I won't let him die again.
No! Walter! I won't let you do it!
Help me!
You're supposed to get some rest.
Look.
I've almost got it.
Okay, let's take a look.
Here, let's see, okay.
It's like this.
Okay, slowly.
One finger at a time.
Slowly.
Two...
Three.
Good job.
All right, love.
Now sleep, okay?
Good night, sweetheart.
Mom?
I want you to have it.
What, darling?
My lucky silver dollar.
I want you to have it
if I die.
Sweetheart, well...
It's okay.
I'm not scared.
Listen.
Nothing is going to happen to you.
I promise.
You're gonna be fine.
You just need to get
some rest now, okay?
All right.
Okay, my love.
Dad?
Hello, son.
Are you all right?
Baby, who you talking to?
What are you doing here? I thought
you were working late at Cambridge.
I...
Walter, what are you wearing?
Where did you get that coat?
I think I found a cure.
What?
I think I found it,
a cure for him.
Are you certain?
Yes, I believe so.
I'll need to take him back
to Cambridge to the lab.
- We'll need to leave now.
- Yes, of course.
Right, Peter, darling, get up.
I'm going to get you dressed.
Darling, let's get you out of this.
Okay. Good boy.
There's a good chap.
Darling, we have to go
to daddy's work.
May I have a word, please?
Yeah, of course.
Put the gloves on.
What is it?
I think you should stay here.
What?
The cure, there's still testing
to be done, and
it could take all night
to find the correct dosage.
Well, I can pack a bag.
You haven't slept in weeks.
If it works, there could be
many days and weeks of recuperation.
Peter will need you.
He'll need you to be strong.
- I'm fine.
- Please, Liz.
I need you not to doubt me.
God, he's burning up.
We should leave.
You take this for luck.
- I love you very much.
- I love you too, Mom.
I'm going to be waiting
for you right here.
Okay, go on.
Gloves.
Bring him back to me.
I promise.
Are you warm enough?
I'm cold.
Me too.
Just a little farther.
Where are we going?
Why aren't we taking the car?
We can't get where
we're going in a car.
You're not my father,
are you?
Of course I am.
Who else would I be?
And I'm going
to make you all better.
Hold on tight, son.
We did it.
Is he okay?
Who are you?
You're the man I saw...
in the lab...
on the other side.
Your friend and the one
who was injured,
they left to seek medical attention.
He won't live much longer.
You must fix him.
Your lab is six miles from here.
Can you drive?
Think so.
Why did you save us?
The boy is important.
He has to live.
I just got off with the hospital.
Dr. Bell called in
a team of specialists.
He has some thoughts on Nina's arm.
Thank you for coming in to help
with Peter, after all that happened.
Of course, Walter.
He looks better.
He's getting his color back.
Seems to be working.
You're going to return him.
Once he's stabilized.
Good.
- I'd like to go now.
- Of course.
Thank you.
Love, you didn't
come home last night.
I was worried about you.
I thought...
How?
He was dying, Elizabeth.
This is the boy I showed you,
the other Peter.
It was the only way
I could save him.
My baby.
Elizabeth, don't.
He's not ours.
I have to take him back.
And I realized
at that moment
that despite what I'd promised,
what I fully intended to do...
that I could never take Peter back.
The way she looked at him,
I saw in her
what I feared most in myself
when I saw him...
That I couldn't lose him again.
It was the first hole, Olivia.
The first breach.
The first crack in
a pattern of cracks,
spaces between the worlds.
And it's my fault.
You can't imagine what it's like
to lose a child.