You all right, soldier?
You need a doctor?
Easy, soldier.
It'll be all right. Just--
just put that gun down.
What about Jeremy,
the one from the bar?
- Married.
- Not happily.
- You're in a good mood tonight.
- I'm always in a good mood.
Honey, you have been walking
around miserable all week.
Seriously, what's going on with you?
It's like the weight of
the world's on you lately.
That's what margaritas are for.
What about my brother?
- Uh, no.
- Why not?
- Because honestly, Robin, he's gay.
- He is not!
Look, it's fine, just stop trying to
set him up with your girlfriends.
You guys are so cynical.
Besides, I don't need a
man in my life right now.
Yes, you do.
Honey, it's almost winter.
Every day is precious. Trust me,
I don't need a man to make me happy.
- That is really sad.
- Pathetic.
Yeah, ditto.
Oh, my god. Girls, look at this.
Names of the victims will be released
after the families have been notified.
This is a stunning and tragic event.
The soldier was a P.O.W.
held captive and feared dead for two months.
He was set to ship
home later this week.
- Hello.
- We have a situation.
What is it?
It's supposed to be a
treatment for depression.
I feel better already.
It has to be implanted
in your brain.
But this particular neural
implant has some side-effects.
Okay, three american soldiers,
all P.O.W.'S held by an Al-Qaeda cell,
all released.
All suddenly make very specific
attacks on their own men.
They're like human car bombs.
- They all had this neural implant?
- We don't know what it does, but...
we know where it comes from.
Professor Howard Samuels.
He runs the country's
most cutting-edge lab
developing these things
at Stanwick university.
How about we start by
arresting Samuels?
- We're not cops.
- Antonio's gonna go after the buyer,
and you're going after the implants.
- So what, I break into the lab?
- It's not that simple.
What's this?
Student I.D.
You're going to college.
You're transferring in from England.
How's your british accent?
Okay, these are the basic
classes you would've had taken
as a transfer student
in neurobiology.
Cellular neuroscience,
which is just about how
neurons process physiological
and electrochemical signals.
- Glad that's all it's about.
- Systems neuroscience,
which is just about how neurons,
you know, form circuits--
can you just stop saying
"which is just about?"
This is an insane amount of
information to process this quickly.
You just have to pull up that
Harvard part of your brain.
The part that never went
to Harvard is much bigger.
Besides, I was gonna
major in Irish literature.
Wow, then you dodged a bullet
when you didn't go, because
you would've ended up a hundred
grand in debt and still a bartender.
Science, Jaime.
That's what pays the bills.
I'm gonna look like a total idiot.
You can't fake math and science.
Okay, okay, okay, just calm down.
Going to college was
a fantasy for me.
But in my fantasy,
I'm hanging out with intellectual people,
tossing a frisbee around,
making a nice pot of Earl Grey,
and finishing my
dissertation on James Joyce.
Wow, we have very little in common.
And now I'm gonna look like a
total idiot faking my way through
- cellular neuron science physio--
- Yeah, neuroscience. Yeah.
You could wear glasses.
Then you would look smarter.
Thank you, Nathan,
for that completely unhelpful suggestion.
Just doing my job.
"Thank you, nathan." You're welcome!
Starting with the primary
somatosensory cortex,
we have areas one, two, and three defined
by the medial longitudinal fissure,
central and lateral sulcus.
This region receives the majority--
Young lady, you are new?
Sorry. Sorry.
Yes, I, um... I just transferred
in from Oxford. Clarissa Whyte.
I presume English is
your first language.
Yes.
Then perhaps you can tell
me what that sign says.
No cell phones.
Well, come on,
a little conviction in your voice.
Try again.
- No cell phones.
- That is so much better.
Now you're on a roll,
perhaps you can tell me when
my lecture's interrupted
by students who can't remember
to turn off their cell phones,
what area of my brain
is firing like crazy?
- Um, well, that would be--
- I'll give you a hint.
It's the region that processes
emotions like irritation.
If that doesn't help,
it's bordered by the inferior
and middle temporal area.
Um, that would be Brodmann area 38,
also known as the Polar Gyrus.
Yes, that is correct.
Keep your cell phone
off in my classroom.
How about this? Faraj Habib.
I'd say if he weren't in Guantanamo
right now he'd be our guy.
- Nadeem Samad?
- I like him for this.
Well, he has no known ties to
any terrorist organization.
He has no criminal record.
He graduated college with honors.
He started obsessively visiting
terrorist web sites 14 months ago.
I'm on web sites all the time.
You're doing research.
Maybe he was too,
doing a paper in college.
He took two classes
with professor Samuels
and became a practicing muslim
all in the same time period.
Ruth, this is racial profiling.
Hmm. Or brilliant detective work.
Check him out.
Hey.
Aoki!
Oy!
Every time you crumple that paper,
it makes me want to kill myself.
That's what my last roommate did.
Great.
It was great.
I got all "A"s for the semester.
You're kidding.
Yes. What are you working on?
- Neuroscience lab work.
- Really?
I love that class.
- Easy "A."
- Of course you did.
- What are you working on?
- I have a paper on James Joyce due.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
The dead.
I don't even understand
what it's about.
It's all, like,
irish and stupid and nothing happens--
No, it's a great book.
It's all from the husband's
point of view the whole time,
until the end of the book, when his wife
tells a story about her first love.
And the husband, who's been so
loving towards his wife all evening,
realizes she wasn't even
thinking about him.
She was thinking about her first love,
who's dead.
It's about how you can't escape.
Like somebody dies,
and you think you're free, but you're not.
The dead are always there.
Which is a different
ending to Ulysses,
which is all about love,
and life, and sex, and optimism--
Okay.
You want to--
you want to just do it for me?
- You want to do my lab work?
- Deal.
Deal, give me one of
these chocolate bars.
Sure.
There's a-- there's a party later,
if you want to go with me.
- So do you know lots of people here?
- Eh, a few.
- Ooh, there's food here.
- Yeah, okay.
Hey, the transfer
student from Oxford.
- The merciful T.A.
- Mm-hmm.
- Tom Gilchrist.
- Clarissa.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you so much for earlier.
- I totally blanked.
- Well, Samuels can be intimidating.
Yeah, he is a little--
he's a mean, mean cranky old man.
- Yes, he is.
- That's what he is.
But you're very nice
to take pity on me.
Um, can I interest you
in a tasty beverage?
A tasty beverage. Who--
Step off. Who is this guy?
You know what they say about the brits.
We love our drinks.
Go away!
He's trying to get you drunk.
Can't you see at?
- Vodka, wine?
- Uh, wine.
So you must be lonely being
so far away from home.
Actually, no,
it's quite exciting being in America and all.
I feel like Felicity.
Only she wasn't from England,
and she wasn't a scientist,
and she went to college to look for a guy,
which I didn't, so...
I don't feel like Felicity at all.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Can you talk now?
I kind of like listening
to you free associate.
I feel a little discombobulated.
Jet lag.
How about you?
How long have you been Samuels' T.A?
Oh, just this semester.
It's too bad he's such a bastard,
because he really is brilliant.
He's... doing work that's
going to make a difference.
It's his work in neural
imaging research
that made me want to become his T.A.
My... my dad...
died of Parkinson's last year.
- I'm so sorry.
- Aw, oh, yeah? Aww!
Oh, god, the oldest trick in the book,
Sommers. Answer the phone!
But after he was diagnosed,
it was a wake up call.
Before that,
I was a bit of a screw up,
almost dropped out of college.
- You'd never know it.
- Well, now...
I want to be a neurosurgeon.
Neurosurgeon? Oh, what?
Was astronaut taken? Am I right?
I want to help people.
I want to change their lives.
You know, I want to make--
I'm sorry. This is boring.
- No, no.
- Yes,
chatty Cathy, cut the cord.
God, what-- okay.
Hate to have to do this to you,
Jaime, but you leave me no choice.
Ahh!
- You all right?
- Ow, yeah, bionic ear's hurting.
Yeah, earache.
I left my drops at home.
Could you excuse me?
- You're an ass.
- Tick tock, okay?
The changeover for the
lab isn't till 11:00.
- Yeah, which is in five minutes.
- Yeah, I know what time is it.
I was doing--
what do you call it-- recon.
Recon? You can't just throw
around the word recon, okay?
That wasn't recon.
That guy wants to be on top of you.
Really? Do you think so?
Get your head in the game, Sommers.
You gotta get over to the museum.
- What are you eating?
- Chinese food.
- Kung pao cafe?
- Mm-hmm.
- You get the moo shu?
- Mmm, low mein chicken.
The moo shu's better.
You should see a ladder to the roof.
- There's no ladder.
- Okay, what's plan "b"?
Um...plan "b" is your bionic.
Figure it out.
Okay, hold on.
You okay?
Yeah, just hanging on to my cell phone.
It messed me up.
So typical of this place.
They spend $50 million on you,
and then won't spring for a bluetooth.
By the way,
I'll bet my paycheck that the story
about his dad dying of
Parkinson's was a load of... crap!
You're so cynical, Nathan.
It's not attractive.
- I'm telling you as a friend.
- I'm just saying that
you can't believe everything
everybody says to you.
And I'm just saying you have
to assume the best in people.
You have to assume that not everyone
is trying to screw you over.
Even if it's hard sometimes.
Okay, hang on a sec.
Okay, where was I? Yeah,
not everyone is gonna want to screw with you,
even if it's hard to believe.
Wow, that'd be a good attitude
to have if you weren't a spy.
- Why are you not in the lab already?
- I'm going as fast as I can, bossy.
Crap.
The glass is wired.
Don't worry, it's an analog circuit.
We can override that easy schmeezy.
Can you find the contacts?
By the way,
why are you using the accent with me?
I'm a method actor.
Fine by me.
It's literally the hottest thing ever.
- Found 'em.
- Okay.
You gotta put something metal
between the contact points
to keep the circuit from breaking.
Like a paperclip or a hairpin.
Or a steel bar.
- Okay, give me the code.
- 3QR4561.
I'm here, I'm in. What do I do?
Computer, let's start scanning.
We need to get the dirt on Samuels.
So I'm a glorified fax machine?
Come on, don't sell yourself short.
You can also open cans.
We need to find out who he may have
contacted about the neural implants.
Okay, old journal articles.
MPTP neurotoxicity.
Apparently the guy's a pioneer
in Parkinson's simulation.
There's some grant
applications. Wait.
Synthetic neurotransducers.
That's it, right, Nathan?
No, it looks good.
Now let's get out of there.
- What are you doing?
- I'm just curious about him.
- I want to know how old he is.
- Unbelievable.
- Professor Samuels.
- I know who you are.
Sean, go back to my office and
get started on the research
while I talk to Ms. Whyte.
I'm well aware of every pharmaceutical
company, competing university,
and everyone else trying to
steal information from us.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
- I just transferred in from Oxford.
- I don't care where you're from.
I just want to know what
you were doing in my lab.
Sir, I've wanted to be part
of this program for years.
You know,
you're a pioneer in Parkinson's simulation.
That's why I transferred here.
Your work is cutting edge.
And I made such an idiot of myself in class,
and someone said
if I wanted to get back in the good
books to clean out the monkey cages,
and now I realize it was a joke,
and I feel so stupid.
- How did you get past security?
- The door was unlocked.
Clarissa, what are you--
you didn't actually clean out
the monkey cages, did you?
Yeah, I did.
I told her to do that.
Sorry.
I'm also the one that
left the door unlocked.
I forgot some papers to grade.
I came back to get them.
The only reason I'm here now
is because I remembered
I left the door unlocked.
Never happen again.
So... you're dedicated.
I'll give you that.
Okay, Tom.
How about you escort Ms. Whyte out.
I'm watching you.
Thanks.
What were you actually
doing in there?
- The truth?
- Yeah.
I was trying to get a
copy of the lecture.
I, um, can't read my notes,
and I'm in way over my head.
Well, I can help you with that.
You can?
For a price.
Dinner, tomorrow night.
8:00 work for you?
I'm supposed to buy you dinner?
I'm buying.
I just want you to show up.
Sure.
...didn't turn out quite as well
as I would've hoped, but...
You know what? The next time you
have a crappy lame hunch like this,
- put Nathan on it, please.
- What's the latest?
They're getting
through the appetizers.
She had the caesar. He had the soup du jour.
Both were wonderful.
The tortilla soup was a little
spicier than he expected.
And I swear to god,
if I have to sit here
while they order dessert,
I'm gonna kill you.
What a minute, wait a minute.
Hold on.
Hello.
Yes, that's right.
Sunday won't be acceptable.
Friday. We said 5,000.
Get backup.
We're gonna need someone on this guy 24/7.
There are those who find DNA
mapping to be the key to our future.
Me, it's the map of the brain.
The way we think.
How, why, who we are is in here.
Yes?
Check this out.
Before the implant,
the subject's tremors were so severe
he couldn't hold a knife,
a fork, drive a car.
- That's amazing.
- You think that's good?
Watch this.
He can juggle. Great.
No, you're missing the point.
The neural implant not only
reroutes the pathways,
but it acts as a receiver.
You send a signal to juggle,
and he juggles.
What you're seeing there...
totally involuntary.
- It's sick.
- Wait.
- You can make him do that?
- Anything. Watch this.
When a computer takes over his body,
the subject can be more coordinated
and capable than he ever was before.
Stop it.
Stop it!
We can modify pain tolerance too.
Brave new world, isn't it?
- What do we got?
- Nothing.
The guy hasn't made any
modifications to the application.
He's just treating parkinson's.
There's no money
trail with him either.
Maybe he's not the guy.
Whoa, whoa. Who's that?
Oh, it's the T.A.
who's trying to get into Jaime's pants.
- Really.
- I know. It's like,
"keep your grubby hands off our
50 million dollar piece of--"
- Hey!
- Yeah, right, right, right.
- So what do we know about him?
- He went to undergrad at Stanford.
Majored in cognitive and
neurosystem sciences.
Oh, really.
I went to Stanford.
Okay.
I just think that technology
has become way too advanced.
Isn't it creepy?
I mean, it's mind control.
Well, the possibility for abuse exists,
but think of all the people who--
you know what,
I don't want to talk about the chip.
Let's talk about you.
You're just here for
a semester, right?
- Yeah.
- I guess I have to work fast then.
- Oh, wow.
- I know, bold.
Yeah.
Just tell me if I have to slow down.
This is-- this is cool.
I just realized this
is my college fantasy.
This is just what I
thought it would be like.
Mm-hmm.
What? What?! What?
You-- you have
something on your nose.
- Oh, god!
- No, it's okay.
- Here, wait.
- Embarrassing.
I think you need a
little more on there.
Hi!
Hi.
What, you're not gonna
introduce me, Clarissa?
- Uh, this is Tony, my--
- Uncle. How are you?
I know, it confuses a lot of people,
me being american and all.
- Sure. Hi, Tony. I'm Tom.
- Shouldn't you be at work?
Actually, I need a little word.
It's really important.
Oh! Well, I gotta get going anyway,
but it's great meeting you.
We're still on for 8:00, right?
Dinner, you and me? Okay.
- What the hell is that about?
- We think Samuels is clean.
But that guy Tom is
under some scrutiny.
He only has a paper trail
for the last six years.
- Before that, nothing.
- That doesn't mean he's involved.
He says he majored at cognitive
neurosystem sciences at Stanford.
There isn't a degree of
that name at Stanford.
So he lied on his application.
A lot of people do.
He's had a hard time.
His dad died of Parkinson's, you know.
We have to assume that
he's the enemy, Jaime.
I don't believe it. My gut tells
me he has nothing to do with this.
The last time you listened
to your gut about a guy,
you had your limbs replaced.
Your paper's done.
I emailed it to you.
- Mmm, these are delicious.
- I know, huh?
I have some butterfingers
hidden in the bathroom,
but they're better dipped
in butterscotch pudding.
- What's with all the hiding food?
- I just like secret food, okay?
Why is that such a big deal?
It's time to take my meds.
Hello.
I thought we should have a
little post-first kiss caucus.
I'm good with the kiss.
It was great.
Let's do it again some time.
Well, what are you doing right now?
Oh, not now. I'm cramming.
I have to go to the bookstore to
get this book on neuroscience.
Microchips for dummies,
I think it's called.
Supposed to be brilliant.
- All right. We still on for 8:00?
- Absolutely.
Great. Bye.
Bye.
Oh, my god. You totally like him.
Stop!
You have no idea what
I can do to you.
I can't stop myself. Help me.
Matches the one they pulled
out the soldier in Iraq.
- My god. Is he gonna be okay?
- They think so.
Who knew where you were going?
- Tom.
- What did I tell you?
- It wasn't him.
- Can I just--
What does a guy have to do to
get you to break up with him?
- He had you manchurian candidated.
- The drop is now up to 5,000 chips.
That's it. I'm pulling you off this.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, he is. It's too dangerous.
I can help. If he's the bad guy,
I want to know just as much as you do.
Come on. You're not gonna get
anybody closer to him than me.
- How's your sushi?
- Mmm, good.
- How's yours?
- Yeah, it's great. I love sushi.
I don't really like sushi. Sorry.
It's okay,
I don't really like sushi either.
Well, why did we come here?
I'm sorry, this is a little weird.
- You feel weird.
- You just seem kind of stressed.
- Do I?
- Just a little bit.
It feels like something's on your mind.
You look a little preoccupied.
I'm sorry, I just insulted you, didn't I?
That was terrible.
This is not going the
way I wanted it to go.
No.
I didn't mean that.
You look beautiful. You really do.
And I don't know why I'm still talking.
This is going kind of awfully.
You look amazing, and I'm--
all I'm doing is insulting you.
It's really terrible.
Do you want to--
Do you want to get out of here?
- I would love that.
- Shall we?
- I think that's a great idea.
- Best idea you've had all night.
- Uh, you know what would be good?
- Yeah, I'm one step ahead of you.
Do you, um--I know this may sound silly.
Do you have any champagne?
- Do-- You want champagne?
- Yeah.
All right, I'll get some champagne.
What kind do you like?
- The pink kind.
- Of course you do.
Be right back.
This guy's too good to be true.
Tarragon? He is the perfect guy.
Tarragon?
He's too perfect.
He lied. I'm an idiot.
We'll know if it's the
same chip by morning.
Nathan needs to run a few tests,
so we'll just keep him under observation.
He's gonna want to know
what happened to me.
And he's gonna want to know
what happened to his microchip.
No, just sit tight.
We've got your dorm room wired.
Subject spotted with a blue sweater.
Subject at the door.
Five...
four, three...
two, one.
Let's do this.
- Go, go, go!
- Show me your hands!
- Don't shoot, no!
Clear!
- What are you doing here?
- My brother lives here, man.
I was just dropping off his ipod.
I swear to you.
This is for transporting the chips.
Who supplies to you?
I don't know what
you're talking about--
What I am talking about
is the Everest project!
is american soldiers
that you are participating
in murdering.
Tell me who is
supplying to you... now.
Was that your family?
Is this why you did what you did?
Nadeem... you're
killing innocent men.
That's all you're accomplishing.
Tell me where the drop
is and when the drop is,
and no one else needs
to get hurt by this.
This is what I think.
Too many people have died already.
Your people...
our people.
So let's just end this here.
- Hello.
- Jaime, the chip's a match.
Antonio just found out the drop is now,
right now.
We're on our way, so you follow him.
Do not let him make the drop.
- Kill him if you have to.
- Okay.
- Hey, Lee.
- Here, man.
Got the answers to the final,
all right?
- You're a friggin' angel, man.
- I know.
Thank you.
- Excuse me. Can I have that?
- What?
- Can you give me your paper?
- No, that's mine.
- Just give it to me.
- No, it's mine.
- I need this, okay?
- No, you don't understand--
- Back away.
- I need that--
- Back away!
- Crazy bitch!
Whoa, let me guess.
You stand him up too?
Obviously you thought I was
handing him something covert.
- No, I--
- Who are you?
- I asked you first.
- Why were you following me?
- I wasn't following you.
- Are you FBI?
- No!
You're friggin' FBI, aren't you?
You're supposed to leave this to us.
- Who is us?
- Come on.
- God, are you like a CIA agent?
- Well, what the hell are you?
I'm with the Berkut group.
- The Berkut group.
- Yeah.
The insidious, arrogant,
always getting in our way--
Oh, did I mention arrogant--
Berkut group?
Look, it's really just a
temporary gig for me, okay?
- Uh-huh?
- Yeah.
- I thought it was you.
- Well, it's not.
- I thought maybe it was you.
- You're the good guy.
Well, CIA.
It's open to interpretation.
The Berkut group had
you investigating me?
First Samuels, then you. Sorry.
That's why you went out with me,
isn't it?
Yeah-- I mean,
not at first, but then yeah.
- Well, that really sucks.
- Why'd you want to go out with me?
Because I thought you
might be the buyer.
- Yeah, well, same thing.
- No, no, it's completely different.
I marked you off my list before--
What happened to your accent?
- I'm not really from england.
- Oh, that's disappointing.
I loved the way you said "brilliant."
It was really a selling point.
- It turned me on.
- Yeah, well,
you wanting to be neurosurgeon was a
big turn on and selling point for me,
- and that was crap, right?
- Yeah.
- Your name's not Clarissa, is it?
- You're not Tom?
Hello, Sean.
You got it?
Stay right here. We'll come to you.
- Wait, isn't that--
- Yeah, it is.
- They're making the drop.
- All right, I'll go down,
- you stay up here and cover me.
- Don't underestimate me.
Relax, I'm trying to be chivalrous.
Drop the bag, Sean.
- That wasn't a request.
- Don't do it.
Oh, I think you
should do what I say.
- I'm not afraid to die.
- I can arrange that.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Look out!
Get up or die.
Get up, get up, get up.
Get up, get up,
get up, get up, get up!
Don't move, man.
I swear to you, don't move.
Where's Sean?
- You got some cuffs on you?
- Yeah.
You want to cuff him?
How did you do that?
Top secret.
- You all right?
- I'm good.
Okay.
Had a nice chat with our boy Sean.
Why'd he do it?
Some deeply distorted political reason?
Money.
So why does the CIA
hate Berkut so much?
Well, you ask me, they're jealous.
We do what the military,
the CIA, and the FBI can't.
We don't have any red
tape or bureaucracy.
We get things done, Jaime.
Not a good idea.
- I can't believe you're leaving.
- Yeah, I have to go back to England.
- Family emergency.
- That's too bad.
- You were my favorite roommate.
- Oh.
Oh, check it out.
You got an "A" on your
James Joyce paper.
Now the prof wants me to
apply to her graduate program.
So I don't know how I'm
gonna get out of that.
Oh, uh, keep it. I'm late for class.
- See you around.
- See you.
Where are you going?
I was just, uh, casing the joint.
You know, gonna rob you later.
You were coming to see me,
weren't you?
Yeah, I was just-- you know,
I wanted to see how you were, and--
Come on, help me pack.
So I joined the army
right after high school.
They gave me some tests.
Sent me to college, trained me,
and put me right in the field.
I've got a nice face.
People trust me.
That's true.
So... what about you?
I mean, what's your story?
I mean, you've got quite an arm.
Were you a quarterback in
high school or something?
I don't want to talk about that.
It's my last night at college.
Can we just hang out?
Pretend we're normal?
Can we just have a night?
Yeah.
Wait, wait. Um...
I don't even know your name.
Jaime.
Jaime Sommers.
Hi, Jaime.
www.forom.com
Transcript: raceman - Synchro: Travis