www.Team-NCIS.com
What's an NCIS agent
doing so far from home?
I'm teaching a class
on the forensics of cold cases.
We're using the murder of a man named
Pedro Hernandez as a case study.
He was killed by a sniper
hiding on a ridge
- almost a thousand meters from here.
- How do you know that?
Because the killer left behind
a message on that ridge.
I need you to exhume
the body of Pedro Hernandez.
The body of a drug dealer
from 20 years ago?
- I don't think anyone would mind.
- I think I have it.
I matched the bullet
in Pedro Hernandez head
to your sniper rifle.
I didn't find this out by accident.
Rule 40.
If it seems like someone's out
to get you, they are.
Welcome to Mexico, Agent Gibbs.
Don't even think about it.
NCIS Season 7 Episode 23
Patriot Down 1.0 LOL
Synchro: Gaillots.
Rereading: Bruno & Magic Turtle.
www.Team-NCIS.com
Following this year's inspirational
commencement speech,
the 2010 U.S. Naval Academy
graduating class began
- their weeklong celebration.
- Good times.
And, never to be outdone,
the city of Annapolis hopes
to make it a graduation to remember.
Ah, graduation.
For many,
an alcohol-induced purple haze.
Easy there, Hendrix, it'll pass.
Back when I was on Baltimore P.D.,
every graduation,
you'd go down to the drunk tank and
100 seniors throwing up on themselves.
Good times.
Need I remind you that I, too,
will become a graduate soon?
With a degree in what?
English as a tenth language.
My naturalization interview
is this week,
both the written and oral exams.
It is how an alien
becomes a citizen.
Oh, I know what it means, E.T.
You ready?
I think so.
Ask me anything.
Fifth Amendment to the Constitution
of the United States.
Due process.
No person shall be held
to answer for any capital crime,
- unless indicted by a grand jury.
- Nice.
Not bad, David, not bad at all.
DiNozzo,
eighth letter of the alphabet.
- "G."
- No, "H" for homicide.
Got one on the beach in Annapolis.
Could be academy-related.
Let's go.
One minute, Gibbs.
Every TV station in D.C.'ll be covering
the Annapolis graduation this week,
so until we know something,
let's keep this on the down-low.
Keep what on the down-low, Director?
Hell of a way to go.
It smells like mesquite.
Who are you... Bobby Flay?
I'm just saying, certain woods
burn differently than others.
There's still green.
That's why it's smoldering.
Hmm, it is perfect for s'mores.
- Never liked s'mores.
- What are you talking about?
What's not to like?
You got your chocolate,
Graham crackers, Gooey marshmallows.
What kind of Boy Scout are you?
I'm a Webelos, actually.
Well, zip up, Webelos.
Your inner geek is showing.
Are you sure you didn't see
something last night, Ensign Bosch?
No, sir.
The fire was ready to go
when we got here.
I set it up the night before
so we could just drop a match and party.
And you think
someone came during the night and
deliberately hid the body underneath?
Had to have, ma'am.
You feeling all right?
Tired, sir.
I've been up all night, celebrating.
Go get some sleep.
We'll be in touch.
"Whenever a good nor'wester blows,
Christopher is certain
to have sand between the toes."
And who exactly is Christopher?
He's a creation of A.A. Milne,
who, reputedly,
also liked a good romp on the beach.
Well, well, well, well...
This one put up quite a fight.
Fingernails are broken
at the cuticle.
Heat has cooked off
most of the flesh,
but not all.
Killers often assume
that a good fire will
act like a crematorium.
They are unaware
that it is impossible to generate
the necessary temperature.
See that?
- Wood wasn't hot enough.
- Thank you, Wee Willy Webelos.
Do you have your portable fingerprint
scanner with you, Timothy?
Yeah, I believe I do.
By rehydrating the heat-dried digit
with saline,
the swirls
and ridges regain definition,
possibly allowing us
to get an identification.
It's like watering a mummy.
Anything?
Words, McGee.
Boss,
this is Special Agent Lara Macy.
According to Special Agent
Macy's personnel file,
she left the L.A. office
last year under special circumstances.
Was transferred to the Force
Protection Detachment in Marseille.
You're supposed to feel safer
on American soil.
That could have happened anywhere.
To any of us.
That is the risk we take.
The agency's on alert.
The director has ordered
a threat assessment.
So now what?
We assess.
Figure out who killed
another female federal agent.
And uphold justice
to the full extent of the law.
Or whatever it takes.
Okay, she's a Marine,
an agent, a daughter.
All right, daughter first.
Macy's mom lives on a farm
in Cumberland, Maryland.
- Call her. Tell her we're coming.
- On it.
Right away.
A member
of Special Agent Macy's team
from Marseille is calling into MTAC.
Threat assessment's been put out.
Think they know?
Special Agent Macy left
four days ago, sir.
A flight from De Gaulle to Dulles,
aboard a C-130 transport.
Do you know why?
Said she needed some personal time.
Special Agent Macy is dead.
We found her here in Annapolis
early this morning.
How...? What happened?
She was murdered.
On my watch, Agent Mineoux.
So if you think
this is case-related,
I'm gonna need every document, file
that you can get your hands on.
Of course.
We'll send everything.
But it doesn't make sense.
Who would want her dead?
You check her apartment,
her phone records and her mail.
Any idea where she was staying
while she was here?
She said I could reach her
at a hotel in Norfolk...
the Freemont Inn.
This is a great loss for us,
Director.
The whole agency.
You have no idea.
It's just us. So tell me...
who did this wretched thing to you?
Did it merely coincide
with your line of work,
or was it caused by it?
Your silence speaks volumes.
It's amazing how someone so demure
can say so much with so little.
- You're talking to yourself again.
- On the contrary.
Agent Macy is enlightening me.
Take a look at this.
There's a bone chip
on the anterior side
of the C-4 vertebra.
I believe a serrated knife
was pulled violently up
and across her neck,
practically severing it
from the spinal column.
Macy could hold her own.
- Professional hit?
- Well, certainly looks like it.
If someone wanted her dead,
why wait until she got home?
And why set her remains ablaze
in NCIS jurisdiction?
- Hey, Abs, what do you got?
- Questions. For you.
Case first.
People only travel for two reasons,
business or pleasure.
If Agent Macy
was traveling for pleasure
then why didn't she stay
at her mom's house in Maryland?
Instead, she checked into a motel
and everything we collected
from her room is work-related, so...
Work-related items,
work-related visit.
That's her NCIS laptop.
And that's her work cell phone.
Last call?
It was incoming,
from early last evening.
From a store-bought disposable.
I'm trying to track it now.
What's really interesting are
the five calls that Agent Macy made
in the last three days.
All to a Petty Officer
Kaylen Burrows.
Pull the file.
I already did.
Burrows is currently stationed
on the USS Majestic.
It's been docked outside Marseille
until a few weeks ago, and then
made port in Norfolk
at the same time that Agent Macy did.
Agent Macy followed
Burrows back to the States.
- Business...
- Not pleasure.
Speaking of business,
we need to talk.
About...
stuff... and things.
Not now, Abs.
Hello, Mr. Gibbs.
Miss Hart,
still not used to you wandering around.
I got a pass now, remember?
Limited access.
Your client... Colonel Bell...
he'll be disappointed.
This isn't about the Colonel.
Actually,
I'm on my way to see Ms. Sciuto.
The Mexican government
wants their body back.
It's just a drug dealer.
Maybe, but if you had an unsolved case,
you'd want your evidence back, too.
You better get to work.
Do you want to grab
some dinner later?
No, I can't.
Beer?
No. Can't do that, either.
If I didn't know any better, Mr. Gibbs,
I'd think you were avoiding me.
Something smells good.
Oh, yeah.
- You like mashed potatoes?
- We are not here to eat, Tony.
Well, I mourn, I eat.
I'm Italian.
Jews and Italians
are similar that way.
That's her.
Petty Officer Burrows?
Yes.
NCIS. This is Agent David,
I'm Agent DiNozzo.
- Can we talk?
- I'm running a little late.
I have a quarterdeck watch to start.
How's the flan?
The what?
Custard-like dessert
on your plate there.
It's tough to master the flan.
Texture needs to be smooth.
Just the right ratio
of milk to vanilla to caramel.
- Can we stop talking about the flan?
- What are you, anti-flan?
Will you tell us
what happened between you and
Special Agent Macy in Marseille?
- I don't know who that is.
- Sure, you do.
You guys spoke this week...
five times.
Petty Officer, we need to go.
We're gonna be late for muster.
That's kind of cute how you guys
all look out for each other.
And you ate all your flan.
Well done, big boy.
This is a private conversation.
Well, this is a U.S. Naval vessel,
ma'am, and we have responsibilities.
And so do we.
She'll meet you up on deck.
Gentlemen.
I did it!
Did what?
I busted through the back door
of Agent Macy's encrypted laptop.
Agent Macy had started a case file,
but she never turned it in
because it was incomplete.
Why?
The victim in the crime
refused to testify.
As a matter of fact, the victim
refused to cooperate at all.
And who was the victim, exactly?
Petty Officer Second Class
Kaylen Burrows.
What was the crime?
Rape.
Tell us what happened in France,
Kaylen.
Nothing you say will leave
this room.
You can't promise that, ma'am.
No disrespect, but,
I've been in this Navy too long.
I know better.
According to the ship's log,
you had a 24-hour liberty
in Marseille.
It's a fun town.
I guess.
A little Bordeaux, little Cognac.
Things went too far?
I met someone, we partied.
I'm as responsible as anyone.
Can anybody verify that?
It seems your shipmates,
Capetanos and Wachter,
were on liberty, as well.
Why did they not want you
to talk to us?
What I did is my business.
Look...
you were attacked.
I'm not pressing any charges.
Yeah, I told Agent Macy
the same thing.
I just...
want to go back to the Majestic now.
Well...
No can do.
Why?
Because you're also a witness
in a murder investigation.
That's impossible.
Who?
Special Agent Lara Macy.
I've already approved the return of
Pedro Hernandez's body back to Mexico.
Your liaison, Ms. Hart,
has agreed to make
the transportation arrangements.
The evidence should be on its way
in a few days, Mr. Rivera.
My government and I very much appreciate
your assistance, Director Vance,
especially loaning us Ms. Sciuto.
Her visit was illuminating,
to say the least.
I think Ms. Sciuto enjoyed her time
in your country, too, for the most part.
Let me videoconference her in.
Buenas noches, everyone.
Abby, I am still amazed
that you've managed
to make progress in such an old case.
I am very much looking forward
to reading your report.
So am I.
See,
that's what I wanted to mention.
'Cause I really need
a little more time with it.
You know, just to make sure
I did a thorough job.
I mean, it's...
I need to double-check
and triple-check everything.
Señor Rivera, you'll have
that report as soon as possible.
We did just lose an agent, Director,
and that does take priority.
It's certainly a priority of mine.
I'm sorry, Director Vance.
I know what it's like to lose
people fighting for a cause.
- We face it every day.
- Thank you.
Alejandro, I swear I'll get it
to you as soon as I can.
Of course, Abby.
I hate to see so much
on that brilliant mind of yours.
The case has been
dormant for 20 years.
A few more days cannot hurt.
Thank you, Ms. Sciuto.
Did you know my daughter well?
Well, unfortunately,
I only got to meet her one time.
She was an outstanding agent.
Good person.
It's excellent tea, ma'am.
It was her favorite.
Lara and I used to sit
with a pot and talk for hours.
Funny how a cup of tea
can mean so much.
We're gonna need to go
through her belongings.
Well, everything in Lara's room's
exactly as she left it.
Clothes in the closet date
all the way back to high school.
But I already showed
your people everything.
Not our people, ma'am.
Yes. There was a man here earlier.
He couldn't have been nicer.
Can you describe him?
Handsome. Military.
After he went through her room,
I showed him
the mud room off the kitchen.
That's
where she kept her papers and...
whatnot.
Oh, dear,
he left quite a mess.
- All of this is Lara's?
- Most of it.
Amazing what we collect
over the years.
I really need to get in here
and go through these things.
So many memories.
Agent Macy's personal notes.
There's years of them here.
All dating back to when she was an M.P.
at Pendleton.
Box it. All of it, McGee.
Check the dates.
See if anything's missing.
Try to figure out
what this guy's looking for.
Anything in particular?
Just check it.
Get a sketch artist out there.
Let's I.D. this guy.
I already made the call,
but I can make it again...
- Making it again, Boss.
- Come on, chew.
What do you got from overseas?
Agents spoke to the owner
of the bar that
- Burrows was in the night of the rape.
- Swallow.
Remembers an American
civilian hanging with her.
Young guy, big mouth, big drinker.
Does he got a name?
I used a credit card
to run his bank statements,
and came up with a Tyler Hammond,
22, out of Chevy Chase.
His dad...
Randall,
is a big muckety-muck builder
in D.C.
He founded Derby Winner Construction.
They've got sites all over the city.
Junior finished Georgetown last year.
Kicked around for a little bit,
Mom and Dad got tired of his face,
sent him to Europe for 3 months.
- He still in Europe?
- Negatory.
Flew back a week ago.
Tyler's home now.
- Maybe Agent Macy went to see him.
- Maybe she got too close.
Take Ziva.
Bring him in.
This community relies
on its police department,
and this is the kind
of support we get?
I know you're chief of police,
but I pay a lot of taxes
to keep this neighborhood safe.
I want you to find those men.
Do you hear me?
- What is going on here?
- It's a nice fountain.
It's very Caesar Palace.
Hey, guys.
You Tyler Hammond?
Who the hell are you?
Damn Navy.
Where were you a few minutes ago?
Can you tell us what's going on?
A couple of guys in ski masks pulled up
and beat the daylights out of my son.
Well, that's not good.
Can you describe these guys, Tyler?
Big.
I never saw them coming.
So you did not see their faces?
Didn't need to.
They took off in an SUV
with Navy base permits on the glass.
Couple of respectable military guys
beating up an innocent kid.
I have friends at the Pentagon.
I'm going to call my lawyer.
And I'm going to sue you people.
Okay. All right.
Why don't you call Gibbs,
give him a heads-up?
Tell him
our attacker's been attacked.
Special Agent Gibbs.
How you feeling, Tyler?
We've been waiting for you
for over an hour.
It's nice of you to finally show.
Busy day, Mr. Hammond.
Maybe you need to get your priorities
straight, Special Agent Gibbs.
Look what they did to my son.
Who, exactly?
Navy guys.
Your Navy.
I was walking to my car.
They grabbed me and...
You don't need to say any more.
Sound advice. Who are you?
Marshall Tomko,
Mr. Hammond's attorney.
Well, you're right, Mr. Tomko.
Tyler, you don't have
to say anything else.
It makes you look guilty.
My son didn't do anything wrong.
That's not
what Petty Officer Burrows says.
I know all about her,
her little story.
She's lying.
If your son's so clean,
why'd two Navy sailors
drive all the way out here
to kick his ass?
Because Tyler Hammond
witnessed them rape
one of their own
that evening in Marseille.
He tried to stop it, but couldn't.
That's not the Petty
Officer's story.
She's afraid, intimidated.
They're on that ship together, 24/7.
They know that Tyler can I.D. them.
They're scared he'll talk,
and they're desperate.
It's a theory.
How about you, Tyler?
You got an opinion?
My son just wanted to help.
And this is the thanks he gets.
What if the lawyer's right?
What if her shipmates did do it?
Then I understand why Petty Officer
Burrows has kept her mouth shut.
I don't.
Why would you let someone
get away with rape?
Perception.
Burrows is in the military.
If a woman cries rape,
no man on that ship would ever
totally trust her again.
Well, you're a woman.
What would you do?
I'm different.
After torturing them
until they cried like babies,
I would castrate them.
Give them what they deserve.
- Spoken like a true almost-American.
- Background check.
I'm listening.
Wachter and Capetanos both
show some teenage offenses.
Both were on 24-hour liberty from
the Majestic the night Macy was killed.
And Seaman Wachter did sign out
a motor pool van earlier today.
It's possible Burrows
is being strong-armed.
And when Macy started snooping,
they killed her, too?
Agent Macy's investigation shows
a hospital rape kit
was administered the morning
after Burrows was attacked.
Swabs, blood work, everything.
Were the results determined?
You can't tell from here.
When Burrows backed off the case,
the results were never posted.
Have Abby check with
the infirmary on the ship.
See if that rape kit's still there.
You talk to those enlisted guys.
- Already did it, Boss.
- Do it again!
Doing it again, Boss.
Everybody out except you two,
Wachter,
Capetanos.
George,
is this your con-locker?
You don't mind?
We have a witness that puts you and,
Big Karl at Tyler Hammond's house.
You guys make a habit
of beating up civilians?
What are you looking for, sir?
- Evidence.
- Of what?
The assault
on Petty Officer Burrows.
- That's crazy.
- Is it?
'Cause every time I look at her,
you guys are...
all over her.
You afraid
she's gonna say something?
You got it wrong.
What about the murder
of Special Agent Lara Macy?
- This is outta hand.
- Shut up!
- We don't know...
You shut up!
Look, we jumped that rich punk,
Hammond.
We were at the bar
that night in Marseille.
We saw them leave together.
He raped Petty Officer Burrows.
She's one of us.
And we take care of our own.
So you're confessing
to the fistfight,
but not the rape or the murder.
And why should we believe you?
Because it's the truth.
Relax.
Exhale.
- I'm trying, sir.
- Try harder, and don't call me sir.
Not forcing you to do anything here.
I know.
I get the kind of pressure, the kind
of scrutiny you're under, Kaylen.
Don't let whoever did this
get away with it.
It's not just about you.
It's about the truth.
It's about a dead NCIS agent.
It's about somebody
getting away with murder...
until now.
Special Agent Lara Macy.
She died trying...
to arrest whoever did this to you.
That was her job.
Now this is my job.
So, who did it?
Those two sailors on the Majestic?
No!
It was the College kid...
Tyler Hammond.
But he wasn't alone.
It's contaminated, Gibbs.
Burrows' rape kit?
Also known as a Vitullo kit. Yeah.
When Petty Officer Burrows
refused to allow its use,
the hospital filed it away
in some storage closet.
I mean, legally,
they have to run the test anyway,
but by the time they processed it,
something happened.
Abs, you can't pull
anything from it?
I'm really sorry, Gibbs,
but scientifically,
you're no closer to knowing who did this
than you're when you started.
- Give me the results, anyway.
- I just told you they're useless.
I know that.
Well, I know that you know, but I...
I'm confused.
I know.
You're doing your Gibbs thing,
to get a confession.
Get Tyler Hammond back in here.
I'm on it.
I know that Special
Agent Macy's murder
is super important,
and I know that you guys have
a long history together
going back to
when you were a Marine.
And not a lot of people know that,
but Gibbs,
we really need
to talk about Mexico...
What'd you just say?
I said we need
to talk about Mexico...
Agent Macy's notebooks chronologically,
I have figured out what we're missing.
January '91 through February '92.
Those are all dates
when Macy was an MP at Pendleton.
Now that's the same time
that you were at Pendleton.
- Boss, what's going on?
- Drawing of the guy from Macy's house.
I need an I.D., McGee, now.
Bueno?
Habla usted inglés?
Sí. This is Camila.
Who is this?
Camila, this is Jethro Gibbs,
Mike Franks' friend.
Señor Gibbs! Como estas?
Bien. I need you to get
a message to Mike for me.
I have not seen him. But when he comes
in, I will make sure he...
You need to get the message to him now.
Right now.
Sí, señor. I will try.
The message is "Rule number 44".
Repeat it back to me.
Rule 44.
He will know what this means?
Just give him the message.
Make sure he has Leyla
and Amira with him.
Just do that, okay?
Señor Gibbs, are you all right?
Kaylen Burrows had a rape kit done
the night of the attack.
It's positive.
Your son's DNA's all over it.
- There has to be some kind of mistake.
- There's no mistake.
I know what's going on here, Gibbs.
- This is the Navy covering for its own.
- It's positive for you, too!
You flew to France
to meet Tyler for a few days,
spend some quality time with your son.
He didn't rape that girl alone.
You both raped her together!
Who the hell do you think you are?
- We're done here.
- Sit your asses down!
I'd like to speak to my son.
I'd like to speak to Lara Macy,
but she's dead!
Did you kill her?
Who the hell is Lara freakin' Macy?
Did you kill her?!
Did you?!
That Navy girl...
She was drunk, but she wanted it.
But I swear
we didn't kill anybody!
We didn't kill that agent.
I'm sorry.
Duck, the knife used to kill
Lara Macy...
who made the knife?
For the most part,
linking a specific weapon
to a nick in a human bone
is virtually impossible.
Okay, but?
But... in this case,
I can go out on the proverbial limb.
The pattern is indicative
of a KA-BAR 12-77.
12-77.
That's an Army knife.
Yes. Our assailant knew
that the first cut had to be sufficient.
He ended her life deliberately,
brutally and without hesitation.
She was executed.
Yeah, and then left
to be discovered,
to taunt whoever would be hurt
the most by her untimely death.
Not unlike leaving a single bullet
to be found in the Mexican sun.
You're familiar with the kind
of killer to which I speak.
I am.
Now, Jethro... Wait.
This is as much about you
as it is about Special Agent Macy.
Listen to me.
I autopsied Pedro Hernandez.
The name seemed familiar
at the time.
Now I know why.
I know what you've been carrying
around for nearly 20 years.
You may not have wanted this to come
to the surface, but someone else did.
And now they are forcing your hand.
Who is it?
I mean, tell me Jethro!
Señor, I am glad you answered.
Camila, did Franks get my message?
Sí, señor, but there are men here.
Soldados. Soldiers with guns.
Your amigo is in bad trouble.
Where is he?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
The hell you don't.
Colonel Bell.
Where is he?
- I haven't spoken to him.
- Sure, you have.
What are you doing to me, Allison?
- I'm here to help with the task force.
- This isn't about that.
This is about Colonel Merton Bell
using you to get to me.
I haven't told him
anything about you.
You must have,
'cause people around me are dying.
People I care about.
Bell is after me.
Because you threw him
in a Mexican jail.
- He's a criminal.
- Is he?
Is that for you to decide?
I am his attorney, Mr. Gibbs.
He's a patriot.
It's my job to defend him.
He's a murderer!
How's it feel to be
in the murder business, Ms. Hart?
- I don't like what you're suggesting.
- Be honest with me!
Just one time, be honest with me.
Where is he?
Last I heard,
he was headed back down to Mexico.
To Baja.
What are you going to do?
You're making a dangerous mistake.
Bell's corporate jet
registered a flight plan out
of Virginia two days ago.
Final destination was Mexico.
They're after Mike Franks.
Pulled the passenger manifest:
Flight crew, Bell himself and a couple
of his current employees.
Names, backgrounds.
We've got one ex-con, a few dishonorable
discharges, all low-ranking,
except for this guy.
Former Army Ranger Jason Paul Dean.
Army Ranger.
Highly decorated, until he killed
Afghan civilians and got discharged.
After which, he was hired
by none other than Merton Bell.
Two peas in a bullet-proof pod.
I think we've got a match
on who stole Agent Macy's notebooks.
Last call Macy got was
from a disposable cell.
- Abby find out where that came from?
- Still working on it.
Info on Bell
after he landed in Mexico.
- Anything specific you want me...
- Everything. I want everything.
Gibbs, come and look at this.
Talk to me, Abs.
The disposable cell phone
that was used to call Agent Macy...
finally tracked it to a convenience
store in Norfolk.
I'm processing the security camera
footage to find out who bought it.
But it's... it's gonna take a while.
You know, if you want to just relax.
Relax?
This is a lockdown.
A what?
We're going to talk, Gibbs.
- Like hell. Not now.
- Yes!
Now!
Since when did I become the kid
in class that the teacher won't call on?
The evidence in my report says
that you killed
Pedro Hernandez.
And you're not even willing
to talk to me about it.
I didn't think I needed to.
I owe you everything.
You're Gibbs.
No one needs to know the truth
about the Hernandez investigation.
I am willing to do anything for you.
I just need you
to tell me what to do.
No, you don't, Abs.
I've only ever needed you
to do one thing.
My job.
But it's different this time.
I mean, it has to be, right?
No, it doesn't.
Former Army Ranger Jason Dean.
Hell...
He's one of Bell's men.
I bet his knife matches
Agent Macy's wound.
You know too much, Abby.
What do I do?
You send in the report
to the task force.
All of it.
I know.
You shouldn't have to tell me,
right?
Where's Gibbs?
Security said he ran out
of this place like it was on fire.
Excuse me, Sir,
but why am I here exactly?
'Cause based on what I'm hearing,
Special Agent Macy's killer
worked for Colonel Bell... your client.
This is Lieutenant Jason Paul Dean.
That was Bell's right-hand man.
I don't represent Mr. Dean.
But you represent Bell's firm...
First Defense PMC.
Dean is employed by First Defense.
Which means you're in the hot seat,
M. Allison Hart.
I'll find Gibbs.
- Before you say anything...
- Before you try to explain to me
why I don't have
the legal right to question you,
let me assure you, I looked into it.
I do.
This is a possible matter
of National Security,
thanks to Bell crossing federal borders
and working with narco-terrorists.
Which gives me a whole lot
of wiggle room.
Do I need a lawyer?
You need to listen.
I got a lot of pieces
to a puzzle here.
And the only thing
these pieces have in common
are Colonel Bell and First Defense.
So let's cut to the chase.
What the hell's going on?
Do you care about Gibbs?
What kind of a question is that?
Stop being a lawyer,
start being a friend.
Do you care about what happens
to Special Agent Gibbs?
Yes.
Then tell me what your patriot,
Bell, is up to.
Ever since Colonel Bell
got out of prison,
he's been accumulating information
on Special Agent Gibbs.
To what end?
Revenge?
Blackmail? Leverage?
Mike.
Don't even think about it.
You're Dean?
Welcome to Mexico, Agent Gibbs.
First Macy, then you kill Franks?
That ain't Franks.
Who is it?
Colonel Merton Bell.
Who do you really work for?
www.Team-NCIS.com