And it's another beautiful morning here
in the southland.
Clear and sunny skies with a high
for the day of 78 degrees.
Current temperature outside
is a crisp 60.
Still no traffic problems
at this early hour.
Clear cruising
on most of the major freeways, but...
watch out for construction
at the entrance
of the 101 off Vine and Hollywood.
Commuters headed
in that direction of Vine...
Fourth and Spring?
No problem.
You see that sunrise?
Yeah.
Another day in paradise, right?
Not a morning person?
Who is?
If you want my money, take it!
It's not your money I want.
Help! Help!
Help me!
.: Team UnderCovers :.
NCIS LA 1x12
[ Past Lives ]
I got it.
Cowboy Bar on Sunset.
- With the mechanical bull?
- Yeah.
No, Hetty, plus mechanical bull,
plus tequila equals bar fight.
Trust me, I've been there. Dom?
Is that a doll?
No.
This is one of only 500 Alpha Centauri
Imperial Class Guardian
Bobbleheads in the entire world.
- It's... not a doll.
- You're playing with an alien doll?
At work?
There is a difference
between dolls and bobbleheads.
And Imperial Class Alpha
Centauris are only part alien.
The other part is cyborg,
I mean, everyone...
- How about Disneyland?
- I hate Disneyland.
- Kensi hates Disneyland.
- The happiest place on Earth?
I have issues with...
- grown men in furry costumes.
- Unless it's Thursday night.
- What are we talking about?
- Quality time with the team.
Apparently,
it's been too long since we hung out,
unless there's a corpse involved.
- We're brainstorming ideas.
- Bowling.
It's great competition,
builds camaraderie,
and you wear those funny shoes.
No bowling.
What about the Cowboy Bar on Sunset?
Oh, that sounds like fun.
They have a mechanical bull, Hetty.
No, never mind.
Mr. Callen,
you've received
an email this morning.
More specifically, Jason Tedrow
received an email.
Who's Jason Tedrow?
Alias... from an old case.
I don't remember it.
You were on assignment
in Afghanistan.
A case that now involves all of us.
Why is that?
Because the man who sent you
the email was killed two hours ago.
The cabbie's name was Joey Gale.
- Former navy systems technician.
- How'd he end up driving a cab?
Four years ago,
we took Gale and his accomplices down
for pulling an electronic heist
of five million dollars from
the Naval Advanced
Defense Research Fund.
Gale was the inside guy.
Montrell Perez.
- He was the crew's leader.
- Sociopath with gang ties.
- Fourth Street Flats.
- Flats, rough boys.
Tight knit.
- Jon Donnelly.
- No prior record.
Bunked with Perez,
who dragged him into it.
- How'd you catch them?
- Deep cover op.
I went in as Jason Tedrow,
a dirty MP.
Spent months getting close to them.
Told them I knew they had the money
and that I could use my connections
to sabotage the investigation.
They believed me.
I asked for a cut.
And on the day of the payoff,
NCIS arrested all of us.
Now,
Gale and Donnelly
struck up a deal
to testify against Perez.
They each did four years
and got released.
But Perez wasn't so lucky.
He's doing a ten-year stretch
at the Naval Consolidated Brig
at Miramar
So, where does this crew think
their buddy Tedrow ended up?
Shipped off to a brig
in South Carolina.
- And the 5 million?
- Gone.
Gale used his access to transfer
the money from the fund
to an outside account.
But the money was gone from the account
when the investigators got access.
Gale and the rest of them
passed lie detector tests.
They had no idea
where that money went.
NCIS got the convictions
that they wanted,
but the 5 million dollars
was never found.
Which leads us back to the email
Gale sent to Jason Tedrow.
Right. Now, Gale's been tracking down
the money
since he was paroled
three weeks ago.
He found an account number.
Now he wants
Jason Tedrow's help getting it.
Why get in touch with someone
he hasn't seen for so long?
I'm just a naturally likeable guy.
- Or he was desperate.
- Could be a little bit of both.
Given their history,
Gale must've thought Tedrow was
- of the only people he could trust.
- Honor among thieves.
Gale connected the money
to a shell corporation,
but the account was closed
approximately two hours ago,
right around the time
that this happened.
This is a traffic cam on the corner.
He tossed the murder weapon
so he wouldn't be caught with it.
It wasn't a mugging,
it was an execution.
Someone knew he was getting close
to the money.
Kensi, head down to the brig in Miramar.
Find out what Perez knows.
And if Perez has ties to the Flats,
then he's a suspect.
- Could've ordered the hit from prison.
- All right, on my way.
Where's Jon Donnelly?
Paroled three weeks ago, like Gale.
But no driver's license,
no utility bills, no credit cards.
Off the grid.
I'll find him.
How is our old friend Jason Tedrow?
- It's just another alias, Hetty.
- An alias that reminds me
of something
Theodore Roethke once wrote:
"My soul, like some
"heat-maddened summer fly,
keeps buzzing at the sill.
Which I
is I?"
- Well, I've been a lot of people.
- Yes,
but you enjoyed being
Jason Tedrow best.
It bothers me, too, Mr. Hanna.
He's going lone wolf on us.
Keep an eye on him.
He's good at spotting tails.
And you're good at running them.
Stay close.
Lone wolf or not,
Mr. Callen is one of our own.
Oh, my God.
Been a while.
Mom!
Jason, this is Michael.
My son.
What is this?
You think you can just waltz back
into my life?
- Thought you'd be glad to see me.
- You disappeared.
I was in prison.
That's not an excuse.
You didn't even say good-bye.
That would've made it harder. I didn't
want you to have to deal with this, too.
The only person who decides
what I am fit to deal with is me.
I've dealt with plenty.
And I'm doing just fine.
- I'm looking for your brother.
- Jon?
He's still a lost cause.
Figures you'd be looking for him.
Kristin?
In the kitchen.
Hey, big guy!
- Come here!
- How are you, kid?
Jason Tedrow, this is Tommy Boyd.
My fiancé.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Jason's an old friend of Jon's.
He was just leaving.
- You're getting married?
- Met him right after you vanished.
You thought
I was just gonna wait for you?
No, I...
I get it.
Last I heard,
Jon was hanging out in front
of the Supply Depot in East L.A.
Just looking to pick up odd jobs.
Trying to make ends meet.
Thanks.
I've moved on.
Please,
don't come back.
I spotted your tail
a half mile into my drive.
If you spotted me,
you would have tried to shake me.
It was that, leapfrog maneuver
on Olympic that gave you away.
You wish.
What?
You got involved with Donnelly's sister
during the case?
She was never a suspect or a witness,
okay? It was deep cover.
I just used her to gain
the trust of her brother's crew.
So I got close to her.
She doesn't know my real name. The man
she fell in love with never exist.
What about the kid?
He was never a suspect, either,
but he did seem a little shifty.
Who's the kid's father?
I don't know.
- User log in, please.
- Thanks.
Agent Blye, NCIS?
- That's me.
- Lieutenant Commander Neil Corby, JAG.
- Montrell Perez is my client.
- And?
You're assuming I have conditions?
We arrested him.
You defended him.
And our relationship
is adversarial by nature.
I need something.
You have it.
Namely,
the cooperation of my client.
Quid pro quo.
I scratch your back,
you scratch mine.
Easy now, Agent Blye. We just met.
What do you want?
I'm petitioning the Court of Appeals
for a reduction in his sentence.
I'd appreciate the support
of NCIS at the hearing.
I will see what I can do.
Much obliged.
So now...
let's scratch your itch.
Keep it down,
gentlemen.
Here comes our boy.
- You smell her?
- Counselor, put a leash on your client,
or I'll do it myself.
Agent Blye is prepared to help us get
you out of here earlier than planned.
All you have to do
is answer some questions.
For this piece, I'll do it for free.
Joey Gale is dead.
And not from natural causes?
- Gunned in the street this morning.
- Well, I hope it hurt.
I didn't do it.
But you're tight
with people who could.
Prison records show
you made a dozen calls to
the Fourth Street Flats members
over the last month.
Ain't no crime to phone home.
- What about Jon Donnelly?
- I hope he's next.
Gale and Donnelly turned on me.
Karma's a bitch.
Montrell.
Please stop making yourself
a suspect in this case.
Knock it off.
I haven't had a visitor in a long time.
Let me try to work this out.
We're done.
Call me, huh?
I ain't going anywhere.
Maybe we could go out on a date.
Package for you...
from a JAG lawyer.
- Corby?
- You read the card.
For security purposes.
You know, national security,
classified document protocol...
He doesn't have clearance
to know about this location.
He sent them through central
NCIS mail dispatch in San Diego.
In record time.
I hate flowers.
Give him points for trying.
- Here we go.
- I'll handle it.
This crowd can smell
a cop a mile away.
- I smell like a cop?
- Actually, you smell like baby powder
- but that's a different conversation.
- What?
You're scaring me.
Jon?
I just want to talk.
- God!
- Geez!
You trying to get killed?
I'm trying to stop myself
from getting killed!
You all right?
I heard about Gale.
Thought maybe I was next.
Haven't seen anyone run so fast
since you got caught with that
Marine's girlfriend in San Diego.
That guy was a knuckle dragger.
The only reason I ran is
because you broke the land speed record
getting out of that bar after
you realized he had buddies with him.
It's good to see you.
Isn't this where you tell me I look good
for a guy who did 48 months in the brig?
I'm a thief, I'm not a liar.
How'd you find me?
Kristin.
Bet she was glad to see you.
Well, not as much as I'd hoped.
I saw the report
on Gale this morning...
And you heard
it was a botched mugging,
- you thought I killed him.
- I didn't say that.
Don't feel bad.
I thought the same thing about you.
So the 5 million's still missing,
isn't it?
I don't know anything
about the money.
I don't want to be looking
over my shoulder the rest of my life.
You think Perez
could have done this?
He's a sick bastard.
When I was locked up,
every time I talked to my sister,
she made a point of asking
if I'd heard from you.
Broke her heart pretty bad.
I made a mistake.
You're damn right.
And to make up for it,
you're gonna call
my little sister and apologize
for all the things and...
This is the security cam
from Jet Plastics.
No plates, guy in a mask.
No way to ID the driver.
Gale and Donnelly are both dead.
That leaves Montrell Perez.
Guy in the SUV didn't take a shot
at Jason Tedrow.
Why not?
You okay?
Jason Tedrow didn't show up
as a player until the end.
Gale and Donnelly more than me.
Or he tried to shot you too
and he missed.
Gale and Donnelly both testified
against Perez in court.
He hated them for that.
He could buy himself
a Fourth Street Flats hit squad
for a whole lot less
than 5 million dollars.
Right.
I'll take another shot at him.
Thought you hated flowers.
Pulled up everything on Kristin
Donnelly's fiancé, Tommy Boyd.
- And?
- Skeletons in the closet.
Five years at Folsom State Prison
for armed robbery.
Served his full sentence.
Released in 2002.
Anyone else think Kristin's got
a thing for bad boys?
Moving on.
Boyd's records show an incident
where he was a minor.
Underage drinking and a DUI.
He was acquitted, but the details
of the case were sealed by the court.
Work with Eric, get it unsealed.
Kristin has no idea
she's marrying an ex-con.
- You don't know that.
- I know her.
She'd never go down that path again.
It's not your place to look out for her.
She's a part of this case.
And Boyd just drops into her life
after I leave?
It could be a coincidence.
Somebody dropped a hammer
on Gale and Donnelly.
Perez making hits from prison.
It's a good theory.
It's not the only theory.
Do you think it's Boyd?
Or do you want it to be Boyd?
Just as you said, I'll be okay.
- What is this?
- I was thinking Ping-Pong.
Ping-Pong.
More specifically,
a Ping-Pong night.
Yeah, for the team outing.
And not to brag or anything, but...
I'm really good.
Fortunately for you,
it's easy to pick up.
Serve it up.
There you go.
- How's the case?
- Callen wants to work alone.
Behavior that conflicts with one
of the fundamental tenets
of a Navy SEAL's psychology:
teamwork.
One of the fundamental tenets
of G. Callen is to tackle things solo.
It's the way he makes sense
of the world.
He's been doing it his whole life.
You debrief him after every case.
You know what's not in the files.
- And that's all you're gonna say?
- That's all I can say.
If it affects NCIS,
it's my job to speak up.
But as far as the innermost thoughts
of the field agents are concerned,
it's my job to make sure
that they stay confidential.
He trusts you
more than anyone else, Sam.
What if he doesn't need
my help this time?
You'll be ready to offer it anyway.
What about the girl?
Kristin Donnelly?
Nothing he can't handle.
Did I mention I have one of the sickest
topspin serves you've ever seen?
- Ready?
- Sure.
Free lesson?
Yeah, I just got...
I got to warm up next time.
'Cause I got... I have this...
this rotator cuff thing.
You ever get that? Like...
When you're in the gym?
Probably not.
Beat your ass at Pictionary.
Thank you, sir.
Right this way, ma'am.
This isn't a social call.
How did you guess?
The flowers weren't nice enough
to warrant a same day visit.
I hate flowers,
but the gesture didn't go unnoticed.
What branch of NCIS
are you with, anyway?
I made an inquiry...
and got hit with the kind of clearance
requests you'd expect from Langley.
There's been another shooting.
Jon Donnelly.
We think Montrell Perez may have had
something to do with it.
May I ask why?
I can think of
about five million reasons.
A less tactful attorney
might suggest
your efforts are better spent trying
to locate this alleged hit man
rather than assigning blame
to a prisoner already serving his time.
Perez is a legitimate suspect.
And if you still want us
to support his appeal,
he needs to tell us
everything he knows.
He told me he'd talk to you anytime.
So long as it's face-to-face.
And they say chivalry is dead.
- Just run it through my office first.
- Of course.
Thank you for the flowers.
You said you didn't like flowers.
I kind of like that you sent them.
- What are you doing here?
- Kristin doesn't know, does she?
Know what?
That you got sent
to Folsom State Prison
for a liquor store robbery
that left the owner paralyzed.
Look, I was 18. I'm not the guy
who pulled the trigger.
And it takes a hell of a lot more
than talking like a cop to rattle me.
She'll leave me if she finds out.
She's had it with people
who disappoint her.
How'd you meet?
At a bar.
- What do you want from me?
- I want you to convince me
that you had nothing to do
with Jon Donnelly's murder.
That liquor store thing,
I was a kid caught up
with the wrong crowd, all right?
It's not an excuse,
it's what happened.
But I served every day
of my sentence.
We all make mistakes.
We do.
But one mistake I'll never make
is walking out on Kristin.
That's more
than I can say for you...
whoever you are.
- At least he didn't shoot you.
- There is that.
You mind explaining how this visit
is connected to our case?
Is my partner interrogating me?
Your partner is watching your back.
Something's wrong with this guy.
It's just...
he's got some demons.
Don't we all?
He said he met Kristin in a bar, but
it just feels like there's more to it.
Then there probably is.
But he does seem to care
about Kristin and the boy.
I don't know.
Four years ago, walking away seemed
like the right thing to do, but...
I told her so many lies.
The deeper you get,
the easier it is to leave the lies
in place and just disappear.
The best thing you can do
is find the man who killed her brother.
I got a call
from Miramar Naval Brigg.
Perez just got a visit
from Andres Rodriguo.
AKA Icy Andres.
He's a Fourth Street Flats enforcer
who's a prime suspect in,
I don't know, eight homicides.
Now, unfortunately,
police can't make anything stick
due to the fact
that witnesses against Senior Icy
tend to suffer from such maladies
as unnatural strangulation,
untimely dismemberment,
and unfortunate spills down
empty elevator shafts.
Am I the only one who thinks
he delivers that information
- a little too cheerfully?
- Hey, don't hate.
I love my job.
Question Perez again,
but don't tell his lawyer.
Let's see how he does
without coaching.
Go behind Corby's back?
Intrigue. Betrayal.
This is getting good.
Sometimes he's so cheerful,
I just want to punch him.
Repeatedly.
Since Corby said
Perez will see you anytime, then...
he doesn't need to know.
Have another sit-down, smile a lot,
look like you're interested.
Be still my beating heart.
Another chance to hear
the latest penitentiary pickup lines.
We dress you in something tight.
He will be so bewitched and bothered,
he won't even notice
when you plant
this little bug on him.
Nice.
- You put that on just for me?
- Sure, I did.
Jon Donnelly was killed
in a drive-by shooting this afternoon.
It's tragic.
You're the only one
in that crew that isn't dead.
And you don't seem to be too scared
about being next.
Scared?
Right.
I'm a big dog in here.
Untouchable.
To most.
Do you like having me here?
Then give me something I can use
or I'm gone.
What do you want to know?
What happened
to the money you stole?
Off the record?
Sure.
We stole five mil.
Four-point-five of
which I never saw again.
- What happened to the difference?
- In a bank.
Got my name on it.
I'm gonna tell you something
I haven't told anybody before.
Not even that JAG lawyer of mine,
Corby.
Four years ago, the night
before the trial, I got a phone call.
Guy on the line was wearing
one of those voice distorter things.
He told me I was going down,
but I could walk away with some cash
if I did my time,
kept my mouth shut.
Do you have any idea
who it might have been?
Could have been
any of a dozen guys who knew.
Bunch of my old Flats boys.
Maybe even this bent MP
named Tedrow.
Gale and Donnelly
said they got calls, too.
They told the guy no. Thought they'd do
their time, get out, find the money.
Guess they were wrong.
Is that all?
For today.
You think I'm coming back?
I sure do.
It'll be like Silence of the Lambs,
only you're hotter
than the FBI chick...
and I'm a lot smarter
than the creepy old killer guy.
Call me.
Our killer started working on his plan
four years ago.
He spoke to Perez and the others
before the trial.
"Call me", you see that?
Sounds like he had inside information
on the case.
They all like the bad boys,
you know that.
You promised you'd run all visits
with Perez through me first.
I'm sorry.
Someone must have screwed up
at the office.
Munro, what is it with you, man?
You jealous?
I'm trying to kick it
to this hot agent, man.
In your dreams.
No, you saw the way
she touched my shoulder, man.
Perez?
Perez!
Get a medic, now!
Get back in there.
- His pulse is fading fast.
- What happened?
He started choking and collapsed!
Who was the man on the phone?
Perez!
Who took the money?
It's too late.
He's dead.
Initial toxicology results
indicate that Perez was poisoned.
Sodium cyanide.
It's a colorless salt
that induces cardiac arrest.
Slip it
into someone's food or drink,
and it can take hours to kill them.
I got something
on Kristin Donnelly's fiancé.
Remember that sealed case
on Tommy Boyd's record?
The DUI he got as a minor.
I finally managed to access
the court records and get it unsealed.
Tommy was acquitted
due to a technicality.
His court-assigned lawyer
discovered an error
in the arrest paperwork and got
the prosecutor to seal the case.
That's pretty good
for a public defender.
It was Neil Corby.
Corby's a former Navy Petty Officer.
After graduating law school, he went
the public defender route for four years
and then decided
he was a military man at heart.
Next stop was JAG.
Perez said he didn't tell
anyone about the phone call.
But Corby knew about it.
So either Perez was lying to me,
trying to make me feel special...
or Corby knows more about this case
than he's letting on.
I hate flowers.
- You and Neil Corby...
- And don't hold back.
What, you bring him along to lay
a beating on me? Is that what this is?
He saved my ass on a DUI charge
when I was 17. I owed him.
I kept in touch.
I mean, the way my life was headed,
I figured I could use a lawyer
who was a buddy and
four years ago, he...
he called in the favor.
He wanted me to get close to a girl.
- Kristin Donnelly.
- The woman you supposedly met in a bar.
No, I did. He told me
where she would be, and he sent me in.
- Why?
- To keep tabs on her brother, Jon.
Apparently,
he just got sent to prison, and
Corby seemed to think that he might
have known about missing money,
but as far as I could tell, Jon didn't
know anything and neither did Kristin.
And you fell for her.
When she told me she was pregnant,
I figured it was meant to be.
Her and that boy, they're my family.
I mean,
it doesn't matter how it started...
they're all I care about now.
Is she in some kind
of danger from Corby?
Why should I believe you?
'Cause you're not the only one
that cares about her.
Corby represented Perez in the trial.
He had inside information about.
Got to the money,
switched it to another account.
Got nervous that Donnelly might find out
so he hired Boyd to keep an eye on him.
But in the end, it was Joey Gale
who put it all together.
- We'd better talk to Kensi.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Thank you for meeting me.
I have to apologize.
I'm very sorry about Perez.
Well, this isn't exactly the way
I envisioned our first date, but...
The case has hit a dead end.
There was another guy
who got arrested four years ago.
A crooked MP, Jason Tedrow.
- I read his name in the case file.
- He just got released from Charleston.
- All right, I'll check him out.
- I already did.
Several times.
Every time I went to Charleston
to visit one of my clients
over the past 4 years,
I made it a point to try to meet him.
One time, the warden told me
Tedrow was in the infirmary.
Another time,
Tedrow was on work duty.
He was even in solitary once.
With Jason Tedrow,
it was always something.
Man's like a ghost.
So, now that he's out,
you can see why I've taken an interest.
Yes, certainly does
sound suspicious.
It does.
I started considering
all the possibilities with Tedrow,
and I landed on this one.
There's this story,
it's passed around the JAG guys.
NCIS has an undercover operator
who can turn himself into anyone
at any time for any reason.
Gets his man, then he's gone.
Like some urban legend.
Doesn't even have a real name.
Just... "Callen".
Yeah, I'm not a huge fan
of urban legends.
I know there was
an undercover NCIS element
involved in the case 4 years ago.
I think...
Jason Tedrow and Callen
are the same guy.
Which means you...
are wearing a wire...
and he is listening
to every word of this.
So, either he shows
his face right now
or I pull the trigger and leave you
bleeding out all over that seat.
Why is Boyd here?
- What are you doing?
- I followed you from your house.
I'm making sure
you don't hurt Kristin.
She doesn't know where the money is.
Turn around, walk away.
Look, whatever favor
I owed you is paid.
- It's not that easy.
- Yeah? I figured you'd say that.
He's got a gun!
You want to shoot a federal agent,
you go right ahead.
Let her go!
Get down!
Okay, hang in there.
I gotcha. Hang in there.
You're okay, you're all right.
It's not that bad. You'll be okay.
Come on. Ambulance is on the way.
That's him, isn't it?
I never heard of him.
Hang in there.
I had to protect her.
You did.
I win,
right?
I don't know this Jason Tedrow guy,
but he's becoming a pain in my ass.
Is he retired now?
Almost.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
Congratulations are in order.
Jason Tedrow has
officially ridden off
into the sunset.
What about Kristin?
She has her son, Michael.
Is there anything you don't know?
Plenty.
But whether such things
are worth knowing, however,
is debatable.
What do I do?
Ask yourself a question.
"Which
I is I?"
Then tell her the truth.
I'm certain she'll return the favor.
Which truth?
The one that sets you free.
What are you drawing?
Looks good.
- Hi.
- I'm sorry for showing up.
I just...
I probably should've called.
Why start now?
How's Tommy?
Doctors say
he can come home tomorrow.
He's a good man.
Yes, he is.
Michael's not your son.
I should've told you the moment
you came back, but I was so angry.
I wanted you to wonder.
I wanted you to suffer
like I had after you left.
That was wrong.
One last thing, I...
My real name...
Good-bye...
What?
We were waiting on you.
Why?
The team outing, remember?
Dom made reservations.
Do I even want to know
what he chose?
I chose.
I hope you all enjoy karaoke
as much as I do.
But if not,
deal with it.
Come on.
You don't have to.
And miss the opportunity to show up
your pathetic Mick Jagger impersonation
with my Springsteen?
Not a chance.
You, Springsteen?
This I gotta hear.
Where's Dom?
I don't know,
meeting us there, I guess.
I bet he doesn't show.
Bet he's got himself a hot date instead.
Guess he'll just have to hear you
some other time, Hetty.
What are you going to sing?
I thought a little Ella Fitzgerald.
I've been told
I sound just like her.
.: Team UnderCovers :.