www.Team-NCIS.com
- My corps.
- Your corps.
- Our corps.
- Marine Corps.
Four miles to go, Marines.
Back in formation, Fricker.
Platoon, halt.
At ease.
Marine,
what part of "fall in"
don't you understand?
- Sergeant, we got a problem.
- Shut yourself, Fricker.
Don't answer me.
Don't even look at me.
What do you think you're doing?
Over there, Sergeant.
NCIS Season 7 Episode 18
Jurisdiction 1.0 LOL
Synchro: Gaillots.
Rereading: Bruno & Magic Turtle.
www.Team-NCIS.com
Come on.
I got gum.
I got...
spare change,
old lip balm.
They're not in here.
Found candy left over
from Valentine's Day.
- Candy from who?
- Why does it matter?
It matters
because you didn't eat it.
And so that person must not mean
very much to you.
- It means something.
- It means nothing.
I'm glad I wasn't your Valentine.
So am I.
Here you go, McGee.
I found this.
One of my motivational CDs.
I've been looking for this.
Yeah, you should've looked harder.
Gee, I'm sorry I didn't think
to look in your desk.
You know what?
Whoever drove the van last
probably has the keys.
Yeah!
I went and got pizza yesterday
'cause I was hungry.
Then what did you do with the keys?
Well, I drove back.
I ate the pizza.
I threw out the box, and...
You know what?
Today is garbage day.
- You'd better... you'd better hurry.
- Where is the dumpster?
- In the basement.
- Did you lose something, David?
Not I.
Tony did.
What'd you lose? Your watch?
Driver's license?
- Neither.
- Got a dead body.
Navy diver.
Who's driving?
There's a little problem.
No, the problem
is that I found these
on the elevator floor.
That's my bad.
Won't happen.
I doubt that.
Meet you all downstairs.
"I do like to be beside the seaside"
"I do like to be beside the sea..."
You know, strolling on a beach
like this at this time of year
reminds me of weekends
we used to spend with Mother
and some friends in Brighton.
They made us eat winkles.
To this day,
I shudder at the thought
of eating any kind of snail.
I've always preferred
oysters myself.
Of course you do, Jimbo.
Oysters, nature's aphrodisiac.
Surprised Blondie doesn't have you
shucking night and day.
That's pretty cute.
Shucks.
- So how is Bryn anyway?
- Excellent.
She just became a union rep
for her embalmer's local.
- She must have quite a pair of hands.
- Her talents never cease to amaze me.
Navy diver.
What are you thinking?
Well, he didn't run out of air.
However,
I can't rule out nitrox poisoning.
The fishes sure did a number on him.
As did a propeller. See?
The blade sliced through and
removed his entire left forearm, but
almost certainly after he was dead.
"This was no boating accident!"
Richard Dreyfuss in Jaws,
you know, when he finds the arm?
- The medical ex...
- I love that part.
Jaws is classic.
I estimate the time of death
to be between three and five days ago,
based on the degree
of decomposition.
A Navy diver doesn't go out alone.
A long time not to be reported missing.
Unless he wasn't supposed
to be found.
McGee, details.
Lieutenant Michael Jensen, age 36.
Prior enlisted.
U.S. Navy master diver
based out of the...
Experimental Diving Unit in Panama City,
then detailed to Little Creek.
Also says here he was on leave.
C.O. wouldn't have reported him U.A.
Diving on his day off.
Yeah, or moonlighting.
Hello, hello.
What have we here?
There's a puncture wound
through his wet suit.
Swordfish?
Doubtful.
Speargun?
It's difficult to tell
till I get him back.
Blood loss from this would
accelerate the feeding frenzy.
You were right, Jethro.
Lieutenant Jensen was not diving alone.
Whoever was with him stabbed him
and then left him
in the water to die.
- Any family?
- Owned a home in Portsmith.
No wife, no kids.
No accident.
Could have sent McGee.
Yeah, could have.
I wanted to see how Jensen lived.
It says a lot about a man.
Take your house, for instance.
Clean, no nonsense, stoic.
Stoic?
My house is stoic?
Understated, then?
I planted some roses last weekend.
Red ones.
Red roses are stoic?
- Yeah, prickly and thorny like...
- Door.
Clear, boss.
Maybe not totally clear.
Toss the gun.
Do it now.
Take it easy, sweetheart.
Who are you?
I'm not the one
breaking and entering.
No, the door was open.
Ladies first.
It's turning into a party
around here.
Looks a little like Reservoir Dogs.
Except you're cuter
than Harvey Keitel.
We're federal agents.
Get his I.D.
Look. Don't touch.
Come on, really?
Who are you guys?
DEA? FBI?
CGIS.
Coast Guard, Boss.
- You got a problem with that?
- No.
Put the weapon away, Kyle.
Yes, ma'am.
That's a nice head slap.
What is CGIS?
Coast Guard Investigative Service.
The Coast Guard has
an investigative branch?
Well, they're smaller than us,
but with a wider law enforcement reach.
But it is the Coast Guard.
No need to get all uppity.
Yes, Virginia, there is a CGIS.
They may not have our track record,
or our je ne sais quoi,
but they are a legitimate sibling.
Like Corky in Life Goes On.
Who?
We ran into Borin
and her probie at Jensen's house.
She remind you of anyone?
Like who, exactly?
Come on in.
Get you a cup of coffee?
That'd be fine, Agent Gibbs.
So this is NCIS.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Of course, I'm going to need
to talk to your director right away.
Well, my case, my questions.
Jensen's Navy.
- The case belongs to NCIS.
- That depends on his involvement.
How's him being dead?
He still could be my killer.
Whose murder are you investigating?
About a week ago,
one of our recon flights
spotted a salvage boat adrift
about 8 miles off the coast of Virginia.
Only one on board was the Captain...
a guy named Martin Lime.
Found him bludgeoned to death.
Case fell in my lap.
How's Jensen fit?
I found some security video
of Jensen
and Captain Lime talking
at the marina.
My gut said
he might be worth questioning.
Your gut?
I like to conduct
my own investigation.
Right there with you.
Any death on a U.S. registered
vessel is FBI or
- Coast Guard jurisdiction.
- So where's the FBI?
They told us to call
if we get close on anything.
I got your number.
No, you don't.
So, what's your beef, Gibbs?
That I'm Coast Guard?
That I'm a woman?
Or that I managed to get
the drop on you in that house?
I don't know you.
That's it?
It was a maxim of Captain Swosser...
speaking
in his naval figurative manner,
that "If you only have
a plank to swab,
"you should swab it
as if Davy Jones were after you."
He was certainly
after this poor fellow.
You quoting Jack Sparrow?
No, no, no, Mr. Palmer.
Charles Dickens...
Bleak House.
I prefer Treasure Island.
Robert Louis Stevenson.
One of my favorites, too.
I used to jump up on my bed,
pretend I was Jim Hawkins
- sailing with Long John Silver.
- Magnificent.
How old were you, ten, nine?
23.
"For the boy's story is the best
that is ever told."
Dickens.
And what's his story, Duck?
But, unfortunately,
much of this poor lad's demise...
It must remain a mystery.
Dead men do tell tales,
and some better than others.
I mean, he's the same height
and build as Lieutenant Jensen,
but the only way
to confirm his identity is by DNA
- and dental records.
- Cause of death?
Being shanked
by a screwdriver didn't help.
I'm sorry.
Sea lice in his esophagus,
the cyanosis and nasal hemorrhage,
all point to death by drowning.
Master diver drowns
swimming to shore?
May I remind you, uh...
an injured diver.
Even the best of us meet our match.
Abby is processing
his diving equipment.
Thank you.
Tread softly, Jethro.
Ms. Sciuto, for some unexplained reason,
is not herself today.
I was just cleaning Jensen's laptop.
- Everything all right?
- No, it's not. What are you doing here?
I work here.
I know what you're doing "here",
but I always know
when you're coming here, and I didn't.
- You don't have anything?
- I've got nothing.
Okay, Jensen drowned,
but he still had plenty
of nitrox in his tanks.
I'm still processing
these little rubber things in his teeth.
I think they're from the regulator.
And I have no idea
how to get into Jensen's laptop.
He's got a code built in here
that would make the NSA proud.
I'm just... I'm off my game.
- Maybe this will help.
- You think I didn't try this already?
I had 2 this morning.
That's kind of
when things started going south.
I just... I don't know what's wrong.
- Abs, I need what's in that laptop.
- I know you do.
Maybe a hug would help.
Didn't help.
I guess I'm just going
to keep banging my head.
Don't do that.
I need what's in that head.
Special Agent Abigail Borin.
She's 34.
Served a tour of duty
in Iraq as a sergeant.
No spouse. No little Borins.
It's uncanny, isn't it?
What?
A former Marine turned
surly investigative agent who...
- flies by the seat of her gut.
- How do you know that?
He was eavesdropping
outside the conference room.
It's called research, McTattle.
Anyway, I think
a law of nature's being violated here.
Like matter and antimatter
colliding or something.
That would be bad.
You read comic books.
Are you obsessed with this woman
because she reminds you of Gibbs
or because she is quite attractive?
- Gosh, I hadn't even noticed.
- Noticed what?
We're just talking
about the case, and
the complexities
and the deeply layered... Where's Gibbs?
He's avoiding me,
but I am not going anywhere.
So, what do you got?
"What do you got?" She says.
What we have is
Lieutenant Michael Jensen.
He was in the service 12 years,
last eight as a master diver.
His record was spotless:
several commendations,
two Purple Hearts.
Video shows him
at the marina with Lime.
So any other connections?
Nothing in Jensen's finances.
There was an odd charge, though.
Payment to a storage facility
in Alexandria...
three years, paid in full.
That's a long time to keep
something in a locker, huh?
Unless you want people
to forget about it.
So when can we have access?
We?
Well, first thing tomorrow morning.
Great.
Is there a problem?
No, it's just...
Do you have any siblings?
None. Only child.
Small town in Ohio.
Tell Gibbs I'll wait for him
outside MTAC.
Nice comm.
Must have set
the Navy back a few bucks.
The Coast Guard does not have
capabilities like this?
We're still capable of plenty.
Just because CGIS is small,
it doesn't mean we're impotent.
- Jensen and the boat connected?
- Quantico, please.
Yes, ma'am.
- Hi.
- That one of yours?
Outsourced.
Down sizing's rough.
We make it work.
Ms. Choi,
could you tell Special Agent Gibbs
your findings, please?
We dusted Martin Lime's boat,
and Lieutenant Jensen's prints
were all over it.
- Blood?
- Some.
The type matched
the Lieutenant as well.
Still waiting for DNA.
We think you have
a double homicide on your hands:
Captain Lime and Lieutenant Jensen.
One civilian,
- one Navy.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Do we keep chasing
each other in circles,
or do we work together
to find a killer?
- We have everything we need right here.
- I'm willing to try.
Welcome aboard.
Our recon flight spotted
Captain Lime's vessel the Delilah here.
Did the boat have a GPS on it?
Yeah, which indicated
it'd been trolling back and
- forth in a grid pattern for a week.
- He was looking for something.
It stopped in this location, and
presumably the murders took place there.
So once the killer found
what he was looking for,
he kills Captain Lime,
tosses Lieutenant Jensen overboard
and abandons ship.
It's miles to shore.
No way he could swim it.
Maybe.
You have satellite photos
of other ships in the area?
- My people are already working on it.
- What about my people?
Yes, we...
tracked several large deposits recently
made to the Captain's bank account.
And we've got a recurring phone number
on Jensen's cell
to a Missy Dawkins out of Reston.
She's coming in.
I'll take it.
And?
And I have...
the warrant for the storage unit
Jensen rented.
- Get Ziva to check out the storage...
- Gibbs and I take....
Sorry. It's your house.
Get Ziva, check out the storage unit.
On it, Boss.
Agent Borin, you want to walk me
through your evidence log?
Yeah, no problem.
You can call me Abby.
No, no, that's not going to happen.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe he's dead.
What was your relationship
with the deceased?
You mean he's deceased, too?
How did you know Lieutenant Jensen?
We dated on and off
for the last six months.
He was a fun guy.
He just didn't have much...
Money.
I was runner-up Miss Biloxi.
I'm accustomed
to a certain lifestyle.
I bet you are.
When was the last time you saw him?
About two weeks ago.
Michael said he was going off
on some hush-hush Navy thing.
Told me when he came back,
he'd have a lot of money to burn.
Did he say exactly how much?
Enough to make
all my dreams come true.
According to the log, the last time
Jensen accessed his unit was
two weeks ago.
Was he alone?
I couldn't say.
What do the cameras say?
Not much.
They haven't worked for years.
Security's pretty tight
around here, huh?
Do I tell you how to do your job?
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
- Act like a jerk?
I can walk, you know,
and kick your Navy ass.
All right,
this is Jensen's unit.
I have a bigger unit
if you'd prefer to see that.
Keys.
I'll be in my office if you need me.
Smells musty.
What do we have here?
Look at all this stuff.
These are ocean charts.
This is
where the Delilah was abandoned.
Calafuego.
Treasure hunters.
Is that what this is all about,
treasure?
Pirate treasure.
This looks like David Jones' locker.
Davy Jones.
He used to sing with The Monkees.
Real monkeys?
I envy your brain sometimes.
Gold reales
and a sunken treasure, Gibbs.
All taken
from Jensen's storage locker.
Pretty cool.
Almost makes up for the way I feel.
Although I hear you're having
your own personal problems...
Special Agent Abigail Borin.
So, Abby, what do you got?
What do you got, Abs?
Other than
like a five-alarm migraine...
I was finally able
to decrypt Jensen's laptop.
The most interesting thing on here
is a nested folder containing e-mails
between Jensen
and a Dr. Joseph Mavrey.
He's a big surgeon in DC.
What were they about?
It seems
like they're talking about sports,
'cause they keep using
the term "a cage foul".
But that is an anagram for...
- Calafuego.
- It's the ship Jensen was researching.
- Maybe it's a coincidence.
- Don't believe in them.
Of course not.
Okay, so according to the history books,
the Calafuego went down off the East
Coast. Maybe Jensen was looking for it.
- Or found it.
- Maybe he had a partner.
It costs a lot to recover a ship.
They'd have to be rich.
Very.
Thanks, Abs.
Are you sure
I can't get you anything?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Mrs. Mavrey, we actually need
to speak with your husband.
I'm afraid that's impossible.
He's out of the country.
Another International Doctor's Group
crisis in South America.
He won't be back for weeks.
Is there any way to reach him?
No. Joe turns everything off
when he travels.
He says it distracts him
from the work.
Does the name
Michael Jensen ring a bell?
Is he a patient of my husband's?
He's a Navy diver.
He's dead.
I'm so sorry.
Apparently, you husband,
Dr. Mavrey, contacted him
multiple times.
Look, because
of the success of Joe's work,
he is constantly meeting new people.
There's no way I could possibly keep
track of them all.
When he checks in,
I'll be happy to mention it.
- But then it might be too late.
- When you do hear from him,
if you could let us know,
- we'd appreciate it.
- I will, absolutely.
- She's covering for her husband.
- Maybe.
We should bring her in
for questioning.
- Push her harder.
- Based on what?
Based on... my gut.
Right, right, yeah,
I've heard that before.
We're just supposed
to sit around and wait?
Yeah, for now.
Is that the Navy way?
It's the smart way.
SECNAV has pull
with the Attorney General.
Doctors' charity...
A.G.'s on the board.
So we'll get him.
I know that.
Look at all
of these swashbuckling movies.
And Errol Flynn.
Captain Blood!
And Douglas Fairbanks.
The Black Pirate.
Imagine Gibbs as a pirate?
A little eye patch and the peg leg?
A parrot on his shoulder?
We're not talking about pirate movies.
Look at this.
Mel Fisher found the Atochain 1985.
Made almost 450 million bucks.
The Real Calafuego went down
in 1647 loaded
with gifts
for the Spanish government.
If this really turns out
to be the Calafuego,
no telling how much money's
at stake here.
- Give me a ballpark, McGee.
- $250 million easy, Boss.
Jensen must have isolated
the wreck site
and went looking for a backer
to fund the recovery mission.
- Why Mavrey?
- He was more than just a good surgeon.
He had 16 patents pending.
So he could afford
to play treasure hunter.
So Mavrey killed him
to avoid splitting the loot.
It's very
Treasure of the Sierra Madre.
So Mavrey doesn't need the money,
though.
No, actually he does.
Apparently,
one of the stents is flawed.
Thousands of lawsuits
flying around now,
so he needs as many high-priced
lawyers as he can afford.
Just got a call from
the Attorney General's office.
Mavrey's doctor group
never left the country.
He's been here all along.
- BOLO, McGee. Find him.
- Already on it.
Okay, Dr. Mavrey just logged in
to his own Web site
to perform a bypass surgery.
Look, you can watch it live
if you click here and pay $19.99.
- Where is he?
- His own facility...
Northwest D.C.
That's 1200 Meadowlark Ave, Boss.
Click there.
Click it.
Hell of a place to hide.
His own clinic...
not real bright.
Dr. Mavrey...
where is he?
I'm sorry.
I'm not at liberty to say.
- Dr. Mavrey's gone.
- He just signed in online surgery.
- We need to see him, federal agents.
- He isn't here.
He hasn't been for days.
They're getting ready for surgery.
You can't go in there.
Dr. Mavrey, we need to talk.
What is this?
Who are you?
Victor Kalsa.
I'm Dr. Mavrey's associate.
I fill in for him
when he isn't available.
We start a surgery here.
I know that.
Where's Mavrey?
Well, to be honest, we haven't heard
from him in over a week.
This is what I'm talking about.
It's like one down...
- Was he there?
- No,
not exactly.
Dr. Mavrey has his partners do
his online surgeries for him.
Well, a flag just went up on one
of Mavrey's credit cards here.
Hired a private jet earlier today
to fly him to the Mariana Islands.
- The Marianas?
- Where is that exactly?
Guam. U.S. Commonwealth.
Now it's my turn.
Muggy.
Talk to me, Boss.
If this plane hasn't landed yet,
why don't we have
a Coast Guard aircraft intercept it
and suggest to his pilots
they may be abetting a fugitive.
On it.
Nice. You can do that?
Just scratching the surface.
- Yeah. Gibbs.
- Can I see you?
Yeah, Duck, on my way.
You're alone.
Who were you expecting?
Her, of course.
The whole building is talking
about your Coast Guard friend.
I'm feeling particularly alone
and depressed tonight.
First, Mother moves into the next world,
and then last night...
You broke up with Sophie?
You noticed.
She was so anxious
to change yours truly.
I was beginning
to question my own identity.
Yeah, I know
how protective you are of that.
She also
put some of Mother's silver
in the dishwasher.
Really?
Did you call me down here
to tell me something?
Jensen's medical records
are on the way over.
But in preparing this mold,
I made an interesting discovery.
Well, the guy had an overbite.
Yes, but he also has several
sub-fractures on three incisors.
Broken teeth from struggling?
No, I don't think so.
I think they were self-inflicted
from some kind of seizure.
I mean, take a look.
The jaw was clamped.
So tightly shut
that he quite literally
detached the masseter muscle
from the mandible bone.
Bit right through the mouthpiece.
Which explains the pieces of rubber
we found in his mouth.
I mean, in a dazed panic
and unable to breathe,
he rips off his mask and drowns.
Duck, why would a guy who's been diving
his whole life react like that?
I also...
found a history of hemochromatosis:
in his case, congenital.
It's a retention of iron,
to be precise.
I believe that this condition
would have precluded diver training,
unless, of course,
someone expunged his records.
Unbelievable. How they think
they can get away with this.
Who's they?
They, you know, the ubiquitous them.
You found something
in Jensen's blood?
No.
That's not Jensen's blood.
That's the spectrographic
analysis of Caf-POW.
Or so they'd like you to think.
They changed the formula, Gibbs.
And not to improve the flavor,
but to save money.
I mean,
no wonder I've been a total freak.
This is like New Coke
all over again.
I'm going to start a letter-writing
campaign. You help me?
You've got nothing on Jensen?
Actually, when Ducky said
that Jensen had a seizure...
I reran his blood and I found exactly
what I found before, which was nothing.
Jensen was using nitrox because
on deep dives, it's beneficial.
But he was headed into shallow water,
so why didn't he adjust?
A master diver would know that.
That's why I think
there's something rotten in Denmark.
Hang on a sec, Gibbs.
I might have something
sooner than later.
Fishermen just found
a punctured Zodiac
floating not too far
from where Jensen's body washed up.
- It's how they got back.
- Had to be.
And get this:
the Coast Guard
intercepted Mavrey's plane.
He wasn't on it.
Pilots were paid cash to fly
an empty plane to the Marianas.
- Empty?
- No, decoy.
We're being played.
Where's DiNozzo?
We need to bring in
that doctor's wife.
Nice pad.
Early American colossal.
Hello.
You must be Agent DiNozzo.
Mrs. Mavrey?
Impressive.
I got your message.
What's this about Joe
chartering a plane?
I don't understand.
Yeah, one-way.
Usually not a good indication.
- We have a few questions.
- Of course.
So do I.
We need your help in finding him.
If I knew anything,
I would tell you.
Please,
I will help you in any way I can.
That's not good.
Doc's having
some legal trouble, huh?
We've had a rough time lately.
Joe's been upset,
distracted.
But I never expected him to...
If you lie to us,
- you're aiding a fugitive.
- I keep telling you,
I don't know where he is.
Look,
I got this e-mail over a week ago.
Joe said that he was leaving
the country...
for work,
and that the lawsuits would be dealt
with when he got back,
that things would be better for us.
Joe's a good husband,
and a dedicated doctor.
And I love him.
Even if he murdered two people?
That's not possible.
Joe could never do that.
Let's look at a few pictures.
Lieutenant Michael Jensen,
U.S. Navy diver.
Dead.
Martin Lime.
Captain of a salvage ship.
Civilian. He's also dead.
As you can see, Andrea...
he's not only capable,
he's actually quite good at killing.
Now, we need you
to help us find him,
or we're going to have to charge you
as an accessory.
I didn't do
anything wrong.
Why is this happening?
Lieutenant Jensen's
medical records arrived.
As expected,
the Navy has no indication
of any liver condition.
Records could have been falsified.
Yes, sometimes the desire to serve
can override better judgment.
Right. But you don't think
that happened.
No, I spoke to the staff physician
at the Experimental Diving Unit.
He examined Jensen dozens
of times over the years.
And he saw absolutely
no indicators whatsoever
of hemochromatosis, whereas...
this gentleman...
shows absolutely every sign.
So this isn't Jensen.
I'm afraid not.
If this isn't Lieutenant Jensen,
who's in autopsy?
- First question.
- And the second?
Where is Lieutenant Jensen?
Got a BOLO out.
He's got a pretty good head start
on us, though.
Abby finished running
the John Doe's DNA.
- Any hits?
No, and without a name
to compare it to,
- Ducky's dental mold is useless.
- Find Jensen.
We got to I.D. that body.
Talk to Metro.
Get a list of missing persons.
- Getting a list of missing persons.
- Time to call the FBI.
Ziva, security footage
at the marina.
I.D. everybody there.
Mavrey's personal
medical records, pull them all.
- Got it, Boss.
- Medical records?
All right, nothing too exciting.
Elevated blood sugar level.
Got good cholesterol.
Look at this.
Something interesting here.
He had epileptic seizures as a boy
and has a congenital liver disorder.
You found my husband.
Where is he at?
I need to see him.
Well, he's...
he's here, Andrea.
He's...
He's been here all along.
I don't understand.
The dead body
in the wet suit wasn't Jensen.
I'm very sorry.
No, that's not possible.
The e-mail that he sent me.
Anyone could have accessed
his e-mail.
Who?
We're working on that.
The diving,
the treasure hunting,
that's supposed to be
a hobby, and now you're telling me
he's dead because of it?
Let us help you.
Is there anything
you haven't told us?
Because of the...
the lawsuits,
Joe started...
taking money out
of his corporate accounts.
Cash.
A lot of it.
I think that...
I think that he was putting it all
into some ridiculous treasure hunt.
Hoping that whatever
he found would pay for it all.
Well, that's risky.
Yeah, well, Joe was desperate.
So Mavrey finances the recovery
of the Calafuego, hires a boat
and pays Jensen to recover the gold.
It's a big payday: $200 million.
While Jensen fakes his own death,
kills them, and keeps all the treasure.
- It is like The Sierra Madre.
- Yeah, but who's Bogie?
Miss Biloxi, Missy Dawkins...
She just bought
two one-way tickets to Mexico.
The first is in her name:
the second is Michael Jensen.
Am I in trouble?
Depends.
On?
On whether you cooperate.
Why don't you tell us where you were
supposed to meet Michael Jensen.
I can't do that.
I mean,
I wasn't supposed to meet him.
He said he'd come to me.
You spoke to him?
We texted.
He said his ship had come in,
and I was supposed to buy
two tickets to Mexico, get packed, and
be ready to go, but...
He never showed.
I knew it was too good to be true.
He was using me, huh?
You're another decoy.
You buy the ticket, we chase you,
buys Jensen time.
I should have known
this was never going to work.
It's not like we really had
anything in common.
I mean, besides, he spent all his time
with that rich doctor
and his wife.
Yeah. Gibbs.
- Gibbs, I've got something.
- Abs, Abs, can't hear you.
- What? What?
- What's all the noise?
The noise!
- What do you got, Abs?
- Good news.
They decided to stick
with the original formula.
So everything in my Caf-POW
universe is okay again.
Congratulations.
Anything else?
Okay, so I got to thinking.
Why keep a bunch
of museum-quality Spanish coins
in a storage unit that has
no security? Stupid, right?
- Unless they're not museum-quality.
- Is that what you're tumbling?
Okay, in theory,
we have $250,000 worth of gold reales.
But look at this.
I added simple boric acid.
It ate away the gold plating.
Not real.
All of this stuff
from Jensen's storage unit,
it's worthless.
Jensen's been scamming everybody.
There's no Calafuego treasure.
He has been conning Dr. Mavrey
for months, bilking him dry.
He took advantage
of a desperate man.
So, then what was still
worth killing for?
A different kind of treasure.
Thanks, Abs.
- Mrs Mavrey said she never met Jensen.
- She was lying.
Jensen got into it to con the doctor,
but it turned into something else...
something with Mrs. Mavrey.
The real treasure's the millions
Mavrey took out of the bank.
Wait a minute.
You're saying the widow
and the stud diver...
did it together?
Did you hear that?
- Yes, what?
- Yes, I heard the wife did it.
Yes, you are a genius.
Okay, question.
Where would you hide a lot of money
if you were afraid
your house could be seized?
Not in my house.
Get over to the clinic, sweep it.
- Meet you at Mavrey's.
- On it, Boss.
Look, Michael, the money's not
in the safe or any of the cabinets.
Andrea, it is not
that easy to hide $10 million.
We've gone through the whole house.
- Think.
- I am.
- Well, we're running out of time.
- You guys looking for something?
- Who the hell are you?
- Came to see the grieving widow.
Guess she's not grieving anymore,
huh?
Well, Jensen, I knew
a Navy diver was too smart to drown.
You almost had us.
Body Heat.
William Hurt, Kathleen Turner.
Hire the stud to kill the husband.
Didn't really work out so well, did it?
So, guys, where's the money?
I don't know.
We do.
It is amazing the things
people keep in their work lockers.
Me, it's just dirty socks
and a Live Aid T-shirt.
Geldof signed it.
Mavrey's locker.
Did you really think that Jensen
there was going...
to take you with him?
He planned the whole thing.
He forced me.
He said he'd kill me if...
- if I didn't go along.
- She's lying.
You are under arrest for the murders
of Joseph Mavrey and Martin Lime.
It's time to walk the plank, matey.
Agent Borin,
I want to thank you personally
for working
so proficiently with NCIS.
Thank you, Director.
Agent Gibbs?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I just got off
the phone with SECNAV.
Now I know turf wars
are unavoidable,
but I find that cooperating
with our sister agencies
provides excellent results.
Don't you agree, Agent Gibbs?
Yeah, sure.
Well, hopefully,
we can do it again soon.
Anytime.
You know where to find me.
Likewise.
Are you ready
for the adventure of a lifetime?
It is just a movie, Tony.
How dare you.
Is Mickey just a mouse?
Ringling Brothers just a circus?
Yes.
Well, you see,
that's why you don't have any friends.
I do have friends.
Really, then,
what are you doing with me,
watching a movie
on a Friday night at work, huh?
You are my friend.
Really?
No.
My date cancelled.
Mine, too.
www.Team-NCIS.com