www.Team-NCIS.com
We can get arrested for this.
Oh, come on.
It's one little Christmas tree.
Why pay
when we can just cut it down?
Because this is a park.
- It's Christmas.
- It's illegal.
It's what
our grandparents used to do.
Hey, Lara.
- What?
- I like this whole...
criminal sexy thing.
- Stop it!
- So what's it gonna be this Christmas?
A little naughty or nice?
Dean, wait! Wait!
- Wait.
- What?
Oh, my gosh.
What's he doing?
Hey, mister.
You all right?
Must be freezing.
Sir?
Call the police.
NCIS Season 7 Episode 10
Faith 1.0 FQM
Synchro: Gaillots & Anne.
Rereading: Bruno & Magic Turtle.
www.Team-NCIS.com
Merry Christmas, everybody!
Loretta, thanks for the ride.
- Bye-bye.
- You drive careful now.
Hey, Dad.
I didn't expect you till tonight.
Well, I like my pilots
caffeinated and fresh.
I caught an earlier flight.
Yeah, but you should have called.
I would have picked you up.
No matter. I made it.
Yeah, you did.
Too many years
since I was here last.
Yeah. Whose fault is that, huh?
We gonna do this again, son?
Come on in.
Old place looks pretty good.
Yeah, well,
it could use a coat of paint.
Couldn't we all?
Well, look at this.
Hope you didn't get
all decked out on my account.
Plenty of comfortable hotels nearby.
I'll be fine just as long
as I have a working clicker.
There's the clicker.
No cable.
Color?
I'll manage.
That's your bed.
- What happened to the guest room?
- It's not a guest room anymore.
The...
the cupboard's not totally empty.
Maybe I'll cook us something.
As long as it's not your Stroganoff,
knock yourself out.
What's wrong with my Stroganoff?
I'm still surprised you came, Dad.
It's good to be
with family at Christmas.
You gonna be okay here alone?
I'll be fine, yeah.
You go to work.
Death doesn't take a holiday.
I'll be fine.
Leave my number right here
by the phone.
You need anything, Ericson family
two doors down same side of the street,
they're always home.
Leroy...
I'm glad to be here.
- It's freezing this morning.
- Man up, Chilly Willy.
Feel that warm blood
coursing through your veins.
Get in touch
with your inner McGrizzly Adams.
I got hand warmers.
Give me one.
- No.
- I'm not cold at all.
That's because you're cold-blooded,
David, like a lady Komodo dragon.
Ice queen, frigid and deadly.
And I remembered to wear
my thermal underwear.
I'll give you 50 bucks
for it right now.
- It wouldn't fit. You're too big.
- They'll stretch.
- Hand them over.
- Crime scene gloves.
Triple bag for insulation.
God, there's got to be
a better way to avoid frostbite.
- There is. Get to work.
- Right. On it, Boss.
Marine First Lieutenant
Thomas Ellis.
Married, decorated,
third generation Marine.
Father's a retired Marine Colonel,
George Ellis,
- who is now an ordained minister.
- Second career.
Second calling.
Well, his son experienced
the call of the wild.
Going barefoot and without gloves
in this weather
is ill-conceived, to say the least.
Was not a robbery.
Money and credit cards are still here.
Not much in the backpack
except for a towel
and what I think is
some soapy water.
Frozen soap residue
under his fingernails
confirms your discovery.
It's an odd place to take a bath.
Could have at least turned around,
enjoy the view.
Yeah, if he had,
it might have saved his life.
Recent footprints here
indicate the attacker came
from this direction.
Used a compass.
It's facing east.
Why would a Marine not even attempt
to fight back?
Lift him up, Duck.
Look under his knees.
Agent McGee,
if you would be so kind.
It is called a sajada.
An Islamic prayer rug.
Well, son of a preacher man was...
- Muslim.
- He was praying when he was killed.
As a Marine, Ellis officially changed
his religious status eight months ago
from Christian to Muslim.
- That was not just a passing interest.
- Fruit of the Month might be good.
Maybe a foot massager.
Gee, Tony,
never pegged you as a catalog shopper.
That's 'cause I'm not, Tiny Tim,
but desperate times call
for desperate measures.
I took these
from my neighbor's doorstep.
You stole them?
Doorstep's considered a common area.
I would never steal mail.
That's a federal offense.
Hold the phone, Malone.
Little bit of lingerie.
Nice. What do you get
for the shrew who has everything?
Is this for the Secret Santa?
How did I end up with Delores Bromstead
in Human Resources?
- She's a Grinch of a woman.
- Can't argue with you there.
Once wished her a happy Valentine's Day,
she claimed sexual harassment.
- You ever seen her smile?
- No.
Stop it, both of you. She is a single,
middle-aged, lonely woman.
- Have some compassion.
- Must be tough
living up there on Mount Crumpit.
Scheming to take Christmas
away from poor Cindy Lou Who.
Why do I bother?
Careful,
or I'll take your present back.
We have a rule, remember?
No presents.
But if I had gotten you one,
you'd be sorry.
DiNozzo desk.
- Hey, boss.
- You know where the Ellis live?
- Find out.
- No. Yes.
I'll meet you there.
- Now.
- Right away.
Yeah, he wants me to meet him
over at Colonel Ellis' house.
Don't touch my catalogs.
Was it a hate crime?
Don't know yet.
It's a possibility.
How long were you
and the lieutenant married, Mrs. Ellis?
Two years.
Thom had just gotten back
from his second tour, so we...
hadn't really spent
any real time together.
Nothing tests
a marriage like the Corps.
Nature of the beast.
I forgot you were a Marine,
Agent Gibbs.
I remember you, Colonel.
It's Reverend now.
- Why the change?
- When my wife died,
I wanted to be closer to God.
Now he's taken my son, as well.
If you don't mind my asking,
Mrs. Ellis,
when did you and Thom meet?
In College.
Here in Maryland.
He swam, and I played softball.
After he joined the Corps,
things changed.
He...
He started studying the Koran,
and he said it would make him
a better Marine.
Within the first year, though, he was...
he was reciting prayers, and
he was thinking about converting.
I blame myself for this.
Did I push my beliefs on Thomas?
Was all this Islamic study
just to spite me?
I asked a friend of mine,
a Muslim Navy Chaplain,
to reach out to him.
Maybe he can make
some sense of all this.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
This is my younger son, Patrick.
What happened?
What's wrong?
Thomas is dead, Pat.
Your brother's gone.
Come here.
Lieutenant, when you knelt
to commune with your maker,
did you have any idea
you'd be seeing him so soon?
I think not.
Is it true that Muslims
pray five times a day?
To be called Muslim, yes.
It is one of the Five Pillars
of Islam.
I don't do anything
five times a day.
Salaat, as it is called,
certainly takes dedication.
Yeah, perhaps if humanity focused
less on what separates us
from one another,
and more on what we could learn
from our differences,
we would stop killing one another.
That is what I pray for.
You're not the only one, Duck.
What do you got?
Well, I'm waiting for the Cleric
until I begin the autopsy proper,
but cursory examination
indicates blunt force trauma
to the parietal lobe,
and multiple lacerations
to his shoulders and neck.
- It's deep.
- Yeah, and oddly angled.
The blow was delivered
in a downward slicing motion.
- Delivered with what?
- Ah, good question.
Whatever it was, was cylindrical.
We found paint residue
and some kind of thread in the wound.
Yeah, well, we'll have to wait
until Abby is done with her analysis.
However,
there is still much to surmise.
The Lieutenant has minor scratches
on the soles of his feet.
And due to soap traces
on his lower appendages,
it appears that Lieutenant Ellis
cleansed his feet again
before returning to prayer.
Which means
he most likely knew his attacker.
Trusted 'em enough to turn
his back on them.
And paid for that misplaced trust
with his life.
These chocolates are delicious!
- Hey, Dad.
- Love chocolate.
- Stop making my team fat.
- I'd like another one.
Why didn't you tell us
your father was coming?
I didn't think he'd actually show.
Go ahead.
Have another one, Bubble Butt.
My metabolism is slowing with age.
It's nothing
a post-holiday cleanse won't cure.
Come on,
it's just candy for the holidays.
Homemade.
Best in Stillwater.
Ms. Hannigan, huh?
She's been after you
ever since mom died.
She means well.
Been cooking for me lately.
She does put together
a hell of a care package...
when people are hurting.
Our instincts were right, Boss.
The widow did have a fling
while the Lieutenant was overseas
with a banker named James Hanlin,
from Chevy Chase, Maryland.
- Any recent contact?
- Not that I can tell.
Called it off
when the husband found out.
- Assalamu alikum.
- Wa alikum assalam.
I'm Chaplain El-Sayed.
I'm looking for Special Agent Gibbs.
Thank you.
Most people don't know
that the Marine code
is not unlike the code of Islam,
as written in the Holy Koran.
Honor, courage, commitment.
Same three philosophies
that Islam teaches.
Yet, ignorance and bigotry remain
a problem in the military.
Well, ignorance isn't unique
to any one group, Agent David.
All we can do is try our best to educate
and pray for acceptance as a whole.
Lieutenant Ellis...
he find acceptance?
Like many of the Islamic Marines
I counsel, Thomas tried, but
opposition can be overwhelming.
Yet, he stuck with it,
determined to become a Muslim.
Because, I think, he found something
that was missing in his life.
Thomas referred to his awakening
as a devout Epiphany.
That's when he became Tareef Bashir.
Yes.
And how did the rest of his unit
react to his conversion?
Well, some were open to it.
Others not so much.
They found his need to pray multiple
times a day inopportune and dangerous.
Was any one Marine more vocal
about it than any other?
Thomas did ask me to personally speak
to a First Sergeant Louis Tibbens.
Successful?
Well, let's just say
that some battles can never be won.
Spoke to Ellis' C.O.
He was on vacation with his family, but
he did confirm that Tibbens
and Ellis did not get along.
Louis Tibbens, home on leave.
Athens, West Virginia.
Population: 900.
Bigger than Stillwater.
But does it have the charm?
Or the perpetual smell of coal.
I always liked that smell.
Keep going.
Yes...
no criminal priors, Boss,
but Tibbens does have two NJPs for being
disrespectful to a superior officer.
Tony, you and Ziva find Tibbens.
McGee,
look into Ellis' Muslim life.
As Tareef Bashir?
Let's see if two names means
he's leading two lives.
How the hell can you sit
like this all day?
No, I'm serious.
You'd think, after all these years,
they'd give you a couple of walls,
- some privacy.
- Come on.
- Got a job for you.
- Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
Here.
You're building toys.
We're building toys.
So, when did you get
into the spirit?
I don't know.
For me, it's more about the wood,
though having that deadline
of the 24th has been good.
You don't believe in Santa,
but you believe in hobbies.
As long as you believe in something,
I guess.
It settles my mind, Dad.
Keeps my hands busy.
So, you want me to finish all this,
paint it and put it together, huh?
If you want.
It's up to you.
If it settles my mind.
You want to let those kids down at
the children's hospital, go right ahead.
You're trying to Tom Sawyer me
into whitewashing a fence for you.
No, not for me.
With me.
If you feel up to it.
Go to work.
There's a steak in the fridge.
We'll talk when I get back.
Hey, Dad.
I mean that.
If Santa's looking for Rudolph,
I think I know what happened.
Tibbens' sister described
this place perfectly.
So, this is where
a "red throat" would hang out
after being overseas for months.
It's not red throat, it's redneck.
And I think we found
the entire cast of Hee Haw.
Over there.
That's him.
With his brother, Darryl,
and his other brother, Darryl?
First Sergeant Tibbens.
Call me Tibbs.
They call you Mr. Tibbs?
- Who the hell are you?
- NCIS.
I'm Special Agent Anthony DiNozzo.
This is my probationary sidekick,
Agent Ziva David.
- What's the problem?
- Thomas Ellis. He's dead.
Allah didn't save his ass, huh?
Guess he should have gone back
to Iraq where he belonged.
Where were you at dawn this morning?
- Why, do I need an alibi?
- Couldn't hurt.
I was in a hunting blind.
With these two.
Can you prove it?
Got a six-point buck
in the bed of my pickup.
How is that for proof?
But I bet a pretty little thing like
you never killed nothing before, huh?
- I'll never tell.
- Oh, boy.
You're going to have to come down
to NCIS with us. Come on.
I got a better idea.
How about this one comes
back to my place and...
decorates my tree.
Happy Hanukkah.
Now, let's go.
Easy, easy. Heel.
Sit down.
My turn.
Red throats.
Rednecks.
Whatever.
What people believe in
is their own business,
but the brass knows having
a devout Muslim
riding patrols
could blow up in our faces.
Really? Why?
Hajis think when a white Marine starts
reciting the Fatiha, he's mocking them,
and they hate him for it.
And they hate us even more,
so we get concerned.
You get concerned...
enough to kill?
Wasn't me.
So, if it wasn't you,
who was it, then?
He knows something.
Could be anyone.
Who?
Look, somebody out there felt
strong enough to offer us money...
good money...
to get Ellis to quit
the Corps for good.
So, someone paid
you guys to be bigots?
It was for the safety of the unit.
So, somebody offered you money.
Who?
Don't know.
Traveled word of mouth.
We answered to a PO box,
got wired the money.
No questions asked.
Oh, my God.
Remember freshman year...
Ms. Santa?
McGee, you're here.
Hey, got any, uh, specifics on
the metal we pulled from Ellis' wound?
Mass Spec's working on it as we speak.
But there's someone you have to meet.
This is one of my very bestest friends
in the whole world.
We went to College together, and she's
the lab tech over at the VA now.
Carol Wilson, Special Agent McGee.
- How goes it, McGee?
- Goes great.
Much better than this guy.
Santa... I don't know why he did
the lap band. I told him not to.
Well, you know, Santa...
can't have a lap band, you know.
He's got to be...
Doesn't work.
What are you drinking?
Caf-nog.
It's an old family recipe.
Speaking of families...
tell him.
This is my nephew, Fisher.
How cute is he?
His mother, my sister, is stationed on
a naval destroyer in the Indian Ocean.
Fisher has been staying
with Carol until she gets back.
I took Fisher to the mall today.
Watched as kid after kid sat
on some lame-ass Santa's lap
and asked for toys, video games.
But not Fisher.
All Fisher asked for was
to see his mom on Christmas Eve.
On a destroyer?
So...
we thought you could help.
Look, I sympathize, okay,
but satellite feeds
to the Indian Ocean are restricted
to all but the highest
priority communications.
What's a higher priority
than a little boy that wants
to see his mom on Christmas?
He's like...
a miracle worker.
If anyone can do this,
he can.
Right, McGee?
Boss, I've been running bank records
on each Marine in Ellis' unit.
So far, only two Marines, including
First Sergeant Tibbens,
accepted a bribe four grand apiece.
Merry Christmas.
All the money was drawn
from the same overseas account
and deposited around the same time.
- It's a dummy corp.
- Interpol is checking into it.
Tell them to check faster.
You do it.
Not you, Boss. You.
How many languages
do you speak, anyway?
Including the language of love, ten.
- Yeah. Gibbs.
- Leroy, you have to come home.
- Dad, I can't.
- I need you here.
- I almost burned your house down.
- You did what?!
Sir, everything's okay.
- Hey, guys. Thanks.
- No problem.
Dad... you okay?
When was the last time you...
you cleaned that flue?
The damn fireplace was all clogged.
- What is all this?
- Boxes.
- Decorations?
- They're your mom's stuff.
No use leaving 'em at home, I...
had 'em shipped...
for the tree.
It's a beauty, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, it's good,
- it's fine.
- Will you please stop patronizing me?
If you don't like what I'm doing,
speak up.
I am trying to make this work.
And I'm not?
Will you please put
that box in another room?
I don't like being
around what's in it.
- It's secure.
- It's dangerous.
Why won't you do what I ask?
How come everything with you
ends up in an argument?
For just once,
will you listen
to what I'm asking you?!
All right,
all right, I'll move it.
I'm going for a walk.
You want some company?
I'm all right. I'm fine.
Spoke to Interpol, Boss.
Got the account that was paying
those guys to pressure Ellis.
- You got a name?
- Colonel George Ellis.
His father?
How dare you guys come in here
and accuse a decorated Marine...
a reverend, no less...
- of hurting his own son.
- It's a fact.
- It's a lie.
- Not according to the bank.
People do things
for such misguided reasons.
Well, Marines aren't
just people, Sir.
You're right, Pat, they're not,
but they abide by the same laws.
Your father didn't.
We need to get in touch with Mr. Hanlin.
You have his number, right?
I understand. You need a shoulder
to cry on and he was happy to talk,
among other things.
- Where were you when Thom was killed?
- With friends
and Patrick was at school.
Why are you doing this?
Because you're not being
straight with us.
It's okay, Tina.
They have a right
to know everything.
You're correct, Agent DiNozzo,
but I didn't want him discharged.
I just wanted
this Muslim nonsense to end.
You paid off the men
he trusted with his life.
Because I thought if Thom knew
he was putting them in danger,
he would stop being selfish.
What I did was wrong
but well-intentioned.
And if it led to my son's death,
then God forgive me,
and Thom's God, too.
One and the same, Colonel.
Do you really think the Colonel
was involved in his son's death?
Well, he has a congregation.
Humiliation can do
irrational things to people.
- This is Delores Bromstead.
- It's her.
Hi, Delores.
- Is something wrong?
- I just... I have a cold.
Delores.
Human resources, the Grinch.
Watch, watch, watch.
This is going to be really good.
- You crack me up.
- Not funny. My office...
No, it's not... That's not funny.
Of course I'll be there.
With bells on.
Big silver bells.
Someone broke my cover.
She knows I'm her Secret Santa.
McGee, you wouldn't do that.
She wants me to meet her
at 6:00 on Christmas Eve.
- To exchange gifts?
- To wrap me in a coon of ivy
and suck the Christmas joy
out of me.
I'm going to say this again.
She is probably someone who just
lacks social skills, so be nice,
get her something special,
kill her with kindness.
Or with a stake of holly
through the heart.
What should I get her?
Ziva, meet me in Abby's lab.
All right.
Any of these things could kill,
but none of them did.
Any luck ID'ing the murder weapon?
This job is not about luck.
It's about the keen eye of science.
Would I have called you down here
if I didn't have something?
Hold that thought.
Go ahead,
taste one.
I'm sorry, Abby,
I could never eat you.
I'll take one to go...
for my dad.
Abs, I hope you have something
more than a gingerbread cookie.
Yeah, I have aluminum and titanium.
I found minute particles
in Lieutenant Ellis' head wound.
- How about a baseball bat?
- That's a very good guess.
So I used the angle of impact,
the depth of the wound,
and the density of bone to work
my way backwards to simulate the kill.
- What's that?
- On Dasher...
You weren't supposed...
to see that.
Okay, here, so,
check out the death blow.
It's the speed at which it impacts
Ellis' skull that's what's impressive.
Watch this.
Whoever killed Lieutenant Ellis
was definitely athletic
and knew how to generate
some serious momentum.
Mrs. Ellis,
your father-in-law said you were here.
I wanted to see where it happened.
I am Agent David from NCIS.
I hope you don't mind. Can we talk?
What could you possibly ask me
that your friends don't already know?
Look, I know we have brought up
some personal issues.
The affair you had
while your husband was overseas...
did he know about it?
Eventually.
He knew that James
and I were good friends.
You are in excellent shape, yes?
Agent David,
what is the purpose of this?
Do you still play softball?
- I'm sorry?
- Your husband...
he was killed by a blow to the head,
possibly by a bat.
The angle of the blow was unique.
And you think that I did it?
Well, you returned
to the crime scene.
Look...
I have a funeral to plan,
a military funeral for a hero
and a husband
that I loved very deeply.
If you'll excuse me.
And by... by the time I got there,
Leroy had fallen asleep,
he left the gate unlocked.
I don't remember what happened next.
Well, I spent the next 25 hours
trying to round up 26 missing sheep.
- That's right.
- Hello, Jethro.
Your father has been regaling me
with stories of his youth.
We have a lot in common.
Naive heartbreak,
tales of adolescent...
chivalry.
And fond memories
of skinny-dipping as children.
Come on, getting late.
Time to go.
Yes, there is Christmas shopping
to be done and a roose to be goasted.
A goose to be roasted.
A pleasure to finally meet you.
Pleasure is all mine.
Where's my coat?
What a sweet, lovely man, Jethro,
and certainly much warmer
than you depicted him,
and in many ways
more accessible than you are.
Please.
My dad?
You understand I cannot make
a firm diagnosis
on the basis
of such a short meeting,
but there is most
definitely something wrong.
Well, how bad?
That's an interesting question.
I doubt what you experienced
was any kind of dementia.
I mean, despite his disorientation,
your father shows
no signs of impaired recognition,
has no trouble solving problems.
He certainly doesn't have
any symptoms of motor aphasia.
What the hell is wrong with him?
Something far more old-fashioned,
I believe.
Your father...
is under
significant emotional distress,
the kind one sees
when one loses a loved one or...
I mean, has he experienced
any kind of trauma recently?
Well, it's nothing personal, Jethro,
but I don't think he came here
for your uplifting holiday cheer.
Martha Stewart, you are not.
Why'd he come?
Well, the answer to that question
is not in my purview.
You are, when all is said and done,
the investigator.
I prescribe some phone calls
back home, on your father's behalf.
They just might prove enlightening.
Okay, so you're telling me that
Ensign Blake cannot be reached on board?
You know what?
This is an emergency.
I have direct orders from Admiral...
Nicholas Whitebeard.
Yes, yes, that is his name.
He's the Admiral that oversees
the northern polar regions.
Great.
Get back to me as soon as possible,
please. Thank you.
Misplaced tidings of joy, McScrooge?
I'm donating my time to a very,
very worthy charity this year.
How worthy?
- Very.
- Who are you doing this favor for?
Abby, her friend, and the big man.
- Gibbs?
- Nope.
- Director Vance?
- Bigger... and rounder.
DiNozzo.
Yes, Sir.
Got it, yeah.
That was Director Vance,
he just spoke with SECNAV.
Colonel Ellis was visiting
his Chesapeake Bay home
at the time
the lieutenant was killed.
SECNAV's house?
- And the daughter-in-law?
- She drove him.
Thom stayed home.
Well, that is an airtight alibi.
So we have nothing.
In a manner of speaking. All I want
for Christmas is a clue trail.
I must see Special Agent Gibbs.
- Chaplain El-Sayed.
- We have a problem.
I just got this in the mail.
The letter came
through the military postal service.
So it could've been dropped
in a box on any base.
By someone who has
easy access to you.
So you think the threat is real?
Or a distraction,
if we're getting too close.
NCIS will provide protection.
- That won't be necessary.
- You have a wife and a daughter.
Whom I love very much,
but I am also a Navy Chaplain.
A man of honor and pride.
Bullheaded stubbornness.
Look, as much as I am here to pray
for the injured and the dying,
I am also here
to open the minds of people.
To help them to understand
the beauty and strength of Islam.
- You talk to teenagers, Chaplain?
- Yes.
Before society dictates for them
what is and isn't moral.
You see, in the Muslim religion,
the most immoral thing
a person can do is to not accept someone
who lives by the Pillars
of Islamic Belief.
A while back, Thomas asked me to speak
to his brother's prep school class.
So you spoke with Patrick Ellis?
I did.
And let me just say, it is amazing
how two siblings can be
so very different.
How fun would it be to have
a totally impromptu Christmas party,
like, right now?
We could decorate my test-tube tree,
we could warm up
dumplings in the incubator.
I know. Typing.
I feel like Scrooge being visited
by three grumpy ghosts.
- You want to see the attack again?
- The point of impact.
Like I said, whoever did this
had agility, speed
and power on their side.
Well, if I don't mind saying so,
I have many of those qualities myself.
Where's that generous holiday spirit,
probette?
- Bah Hum-Bog.
- Bah what?
- Here's another angle, Gibbs.
- Freeze it right there.
Patrick Ellis played lacrosse?
Yeah, Team Captain.
Abby, try lacrosse.
Checking.
Today's lacrosse sticks are
a composite of aluminum and titanium,
and the head is made out
of nylon and leather mesh.
The exact same breakdown
found in the wound.
Abel and Cain.
He killed his own brother.
What's going on?
We know that you were at the park
the other morning with Thomas.
I was at school.
What are you talking about?
You went there to confront him
about being Muslim.
You argued, you lost your temper.
Most lacrosse players like to run
with their sticks. Where's yours?
Dad, I just went on a run.
Is it broken,
or did you destroy the evidence?
I like the letter to the Chaplain.
The cut-and-paste letters...
very Zodiac.
Dad, you got to believe me.
Thom was embarrassing us.
People were laughing at him.
I did this for you.
Thomas just wanted
to find the good in people.
He found his God, that humiliated me,
but he was still my son.
But I'm your son, too.
You taught us to be proud, you know.
Proud of this family.
And when Thom changed,
everything changed,
because the one thing
this family always had
was honor,
and he ruined that.
I loved him so much,
and he turned his back on us.
I don't know.
Maybe we turned our back on him.
Not very traditional.
Yeah, it is.
Let's talk.
- You called Betty Hannigan?
- She told me to call the sheriff.
Ed sent you the report?
How about you fill in
some of the details?
He rumbled up in an old fastback.
Whole town could hear him.
- Dirt-kicker looking for trouble.
- I guess.
The Dobson girl was in the store.
She had a friend visiting.
I never got her name.
He said he come there to rob me.
He had a gun, Leroy.
I told him to take anything
he wanted from the register,
but...
the girls were in the corner,
crouching, terrified.
He turned after them and...
Well, that's not the first time
you've fired that Winchester.
It's not the first time
I killed somebody, either.
But it's the first time
I saw the face.
Twenty-three.
Had a kid, somebody told me.
Looks different from up there
in the cockpit, huh?
From up there,
it doesn't look like much of anything.
You pull the trigger,
feel the release, nothing.
I never even thought about it much.
Now, that's all I think about.
How did you do it
all these years, son?
I need to know.
This why you came?
That and because it's Christmas.
It's not supposed to be easy.
Nobody said it would be, huh?
Attention on deck!
- I can't. I can't.
- Of course you can. Go back. Go back.
I don't want to. I don't want to.
Come on, Tony. Go back.
I can't.
Special Agent DiNozzo?
Merry Christmas, Delores.
I got this for you.
I looked in your personnel file.
Which is legal, 'cause I have
that security clearance, but I saw that
that when you were...
eight years old,
all the little girls
in your neighborhood,
they all got this incredible...
doll, the Knee-High Cherry Pie doll.
And you didn't get one.
I guess Santa didn't make
enough that year, so...
I got this for you.
All right, Fisher.
Right this way, my friend.
What is this place?
This is a very special room
that only a few people know about.
It's a magic room called MTAC.
- Aunt...?
- Don't look at me.
See, Santa told me
very specifically to bring you here.
Why? What's gonna happen?
Well...
Let's make a Christmas wish
and see if it comes true.
How about that?
Want you to shut
your eyes good and tight.
Got 'em closed?
All right.
Now.
I want you to think of the one thing
you want for Christmas
more than anything else
in the entire world.
You ready?
Fisher, baby, is that you?
Mom!
I love you, sweetheart.
Merry Christmas.
Look at you.
You are getting so big.
I got all the mail you sent,
all your artwork.
- Your pictures.
- I'll make you more.
I can't wait.
I have told everybody here
all about you
about how proud I am of you.
We're going to have
a big Christmas dinner here tonight.
But I'd rather be there instead.
I wish you were, too.
Well, not bad, huh?
Pulled it off.
You would make a great Santa.
I guess you just got to believe.
I do believe.
I'll go warm up the sleigh.
www.Team-NCIS.com