www.Team-NCIS.com
Los Angeles, OSP.
They have the lead.
NCIS's Office of Special Projects.
They specialize
in undercover and surveillance.
Macy still agent in charge there?
- How are you, Callen?
- Did you see Mace?
- Yeah, I saw her.
- Let me do my job.
Like you did the first time we met?
Kickoff's in 30.
Guy on the right, Michael Rivkin.
When he called the other day,
I thought he must have been here.
No. Sadly, Michael is not here.
Go tight on Liam.
What do you see?
He's carrying...
Liam Coyle, former IRA arms dealer.
Motel.
Four blank passports.
Four suitcases filled with weapons.
That means whoever Liam's supplying is
probably coming back to collect this.
Looks like you're going
undercover as Liam.
- Been expecting you.
- It's a pleasure to finally meet you.
You have everything I want?
Times four.
Passports?
Everything.
And it's all here?
It's all here.
First the face, next the name.
You know, I met a man in Damascus
who said you were dead.
Well, let me know when he passes.
I'll come to his funeral.
Too late.
- Who are you?
- Abort, abort.
Target center of the room,
weapon drawn.
Federal agents! Don't move!
Put down your weapon.
Put it down!
Come on, Mace,
he wasn't gonna shoot me!
Tell her you weren't gonna shoot me?
I wasn't going to shoot him.
No tension in the upper body,
and the voice is all wrong.
Probably wasn't gonna shoot him.
- Be embarrassing if he had.
- There's no room for probably, Nate.
Do we have a name?
Well, we just started.
It's gonna take at least a...
- We got a match here.
- Put it on the screen.
Millions of possibilities,
we get a hit in six seconds?
Michael Rivkin.
His name's Michael Rivkin.
FBI?
CIA?
NCIS.
He's way too confident.
Think we're about to go pear-shaped.
Who are you?
Mossad.
You can prove that?
No, but I know someone who can.
Her name is Ziva David.
NCIS Season 6 Episode 23
Legend Part 2 V1.0 LOL
Synchro: Gaillots.
Rereading: Bruno.
www.Team-NCIS.com
Morning.
- Something up?
- Gibbs.
- He's back?
- MTAC.
Nice, three one-word answers.
Wanna go for a fourth?
No!
Now I'm gonna ask you a question
that's gonna demand
more than a one-word answer.
- Are you ready for that?
- No.
All right, here comes the question.
Ready?
No beverage is allowed in MTAC.
Hey. Soy vanilla latte, no sugar added.
Didn't blow back.
It's all yours.
God, question was right on the tip of
my tongue, and now I can't remember it.
How could I forget the question?
Questions are of course,
well, they're relative.
- And I don't mean that in a sense of...
- OSP's on-line.
McGee, put it up.
You recognize him?
Yes, I know him.
His name is Michael Rivkin.
He says he's Mossad.
Yes, he's with the Mossad.
Anything else you can tell us about him,
Officer David?
No.
I have not worked
with him in some time.
We will talk more about this later.
Of course.
You did not think
I would identify him.
That was not a question.
Anything you want to tell me?
No.
One-word answer.
I win.
His cover is an Israeli banker.
Flew in three days ago.
That's all we got, still looking.
What the hell is he doing here?
Same thing we are.
Tracking down a terrorist cell.
We're hunting the same cell.
Your search started here,
mine in Yemen.
Okay, well, if I'm Liam Coyle,
arms supplier, who does that make you?
Nick Quaderi, jihadist.
The real Liam's in the morgue.
Where exactly is the real Nick Quaderi?
In bed.
221 Pacific Avenue,
Apartment 27, Venice Beach.
No need to be quiet.
You won't wake him.
You should've called us. Would've
spared you a long ride from Yemen.
Need to be sure.
What did Quaderi tell you?
Weapons pickup here,
a man named Liam.
- Target?
- No.
Rest of the cell?
Fell asleep before he told me.
I can tell you
that one of the others is named Haziq.
Address.
That's all I have.
Give him your cell, Sam.
Be polite.
Good morning.
As I'm sure you're aware,
foreign intelligence agencies
are not authorized to act
within U.S. territorial borders.
I would hate for your actions
to cause an incident
by staying here any longer,
Mr. Rivkin.
We each have a job to do.
Yours is done.
Go home.
GPS tracker on his rental.
Sam, let him go.
Yeah.
Four passports, four suitcases.
Yeah, Rivkin's already put
one of them to sleep.
One down, three to go.
Eric, give me outside surveillance.
On screen.
Agent Renko, you got him?
I got him, Mace.
Callen, Sam, Venice Beach,
Quaderi's apartment.
Kensi,
shut it down.
- You thinking what I'm thinking?
- Mumbai.
They attack soft targets.
Hotels, a railway station.
We need a breathing suspect,
not a dead one.
That's not Rivkin's plan.
We have to stay ahead of him
until I get approval to lock him up
or send him home.
Officer David was sent back
to Israel
- last year.
- Are you asking me: do I trust her?
Because my answer is:
yes, with my life.
You don't think
I'm very good at this, do you?
The director must
or you wouldn't be doing this job.
You shouldn't judge me
on past performance.
It was 18 years ago.
What'd you find?
Okay, so...
Mossad gets a lead in Yemen
about a terrorist cell operating out
of Los Angeles, right?
Sends Rivkin to eliminate them.
Rivkin finds one of the terrorists,
Nick Quaderi, kills him,
but not before Quaderi mentions
that he's meeting
with an arms dealer named Liam.
And the only problem is,
we're hunting the same terrorist cell.
Terrorist cells are like families.
I mean, close-knit,
always checking on each other.
Now, if they lost contact
with one of their own,
it may trigger them
to step up the attack.
Next move is to find
the cell member Rivkin mentioned.
Haziq.
Before he panics.
You think that Rivkin knows
the identities of the rest of the cell?
It was right there
in his smug smile, McGee.
He knows.
You okay, Mace?
I already told you
not to go there, Nate.
Well...
you know me too well.
No one knows you, Nate.
You, on the other hand, being
the psychologist you are, know everyone.
Not Gibbs.
So you go back 18 years, huh?
I wasn't listening.
Odd word, occasional phrase.
Gibbs was a gunnery sergeant.
I was a green,
young lieutenant in the Military Police
determined to prove myself.
You worked a case together?
You could say that.
It was a JAGMAN investigation,
a murder.
I was the lead investigator.
And... Gibbs?
Gibbs was the suspect.
Nick Quaderi.
- Guy's a ghost.
- Definitely is now.
We got his name and his address.
Paid his rent in cash, utilities paid
by his landlord, so no photo
I.D. there, and no credit cards.
You have any idea how many times
your average law-abiding citizen
is recorded every week, McGee?
Yeah, probably north of 3,000 times.
Way north.
Like northern Alaska north.
Every phone call, credit card
transaction, Internet search,
all swallowed up
and stored on hard drives
so people can troll them
for personal information.
You mean,
like we're doing right now.
Yeah, that's okay 'cause
we work for the government.
We've got a national
security letter to prove it.
This guy really did not want
to be found.
Well, Rivkin found him, McGee.
- Are you still tracking Rivkin?
- Yeah, boss, we got him right there.
Marina Del Rey.
We're pulling up the pictometry now.
His car's parked at a hotel.
Special Agent Renko?
He's out of his car
and he's got a visual.
- Let him know I'm coming.
- I'm on it.
You got something else?
No, that about covers it.
I lived in a place like this
when I was a kid.
I probably lived down the hall.
This is it.
Apartment 27.
Nick Quaderi,
if you're inclined to believe Rivkin.
What is it between Mace and Gibbs?
They've never told me.
Think they'll work it out?
Not without some help.
One-inch tear.
Looks like a stab wound.
Clean and quick under the sternum,
up into the heart.
There's a secret department
in the Mossad
called the Kidon. I had dealings
with them when I was a Seal.
Highly trained, fearless.
They were formed
after the war to track down Nazis.
Now they come after all enemies
who would harm Israel.
I think Rivkin could be one of them.
Kidon?
Hebrew for "bayonet".
Morning, Mike.
Help yourself.
Where is he?
Hotel gazebo,
having coffee at the middle table.
Went inside, came back out
a couple minutes later.
He's been there ever since.
- He's waiting for somebody.
- That's my guess.
Whose boat is this?
I have no idea.
Sand with the grain
of the wood, Renko.
You done this before?
Yeah.
Download complete.
Rest in peace.
If that's what you want, sure.
Next week, then.
Yeah, ciao.
Hi.
Who are you?
My name's Liam.
I'm a friend of Nick's.
Sort of. And you are?
Shakira, his girlfriend...
sort of.
- Nick, I'm here!
- But Nick's not.
Then how did you get in?
He's supposed to meet me here,
but he's late.
I was just gonna leave him a note.
Liam.
- You got a plan?
- Hey, Nick.
Clever.
I'm in your apartment waiting.
Where the hell are you?
- I'm in the next room.
- Calm down, take it easy, all right?
Hey, Shakira just walked in.
Do you want to talk with her?
Not particularly.
Okay, no problem.
- What do you have in mind?
- Haziq's place?
Sure, if that's what you want,
we'll come right over.
He didn't want to talk on the phone.
He wants us to come
to his friend's place...
Haziq?
- Do you know him?
- You don't?
No.
Lucky you.
- I'll call a cab.
- My car's out front.
Great.
Is the bathroom through here?
Rivkin gives us Haziq's name.
She leads us to him.
Stay close.
How you gonna play this?
I gotta believe Haziq still wants
what Liam's got.
And if he doesn't?
You come rescue me.
You think she's involved?
They're sleeping together.
She's involved
whether she knows it or not.
Yeah.
- What kind of car do you drive?
- A convertible.
Convertible?
Red?
- Yellow.
- I like yellow.
- Mace?
- What's happening, Sam?
Callen's back in the game.
We're stopping at an auto shop
downtown... 13th and Bakers Lane.
This place creeps me out,
or maybe it's just Haziq.
Nick bring you here often?
Couple times.
Haziq was trying to recruit him.
- For what?
- Hey,
who's this?
Nick's friend.
He called.
Told us to meet him out here.
He didn't call me.
Nick's friend, huh?
Liam.
What can Nick's friend do for us?
I can give you
what you've been waiting for.
Come in, Nick's friend.
He's just met a guy, probably Haziq.
I'm downloading photos.
I need some more eyes down here.
Kensi's on her way.
Eric, live feeds?
No coverage.
Kensi, you're gonna have
to get a camera in there.
I'll come up with something.
You want to bang on something,
baby, you found your man.
Hey, relax.
We're cool, eh?
Not today, boys.
Have a nice day.
Shakira,
bring our guest a cold drink.
Are you armed?
Back.
Cell phone?
- She doesn't know?
- Why should she? She's just a woman.
Nick is not the one
who's supposed to contact you.
He called me,
told me to come to his apartment.
- Then he changed the meeting here.
- Why?
You're just gonna have
to ask him when he gets here.
- Thank you.
- Come and sit down.
The cell phone you are trying to reach
is switched off or out of range.
Please try again later.
Where is Rafi?
How would I know?
He's your brother.
You should be more respectful.
Sweet.
Eric, activate Callen's cell phone.
Microphone and camera coming online.
Phone cam's up at Haziq's auto shop.
Cell phone.
Trace it, and feed it through
to Sam to translate.
"I need you here, Nasim."
"Is Rafi with you?"
"What about Nick?
Have you heard from him?"
"I'm not sure
if there's something wrong.
Just get down here
as soon as you can."
He's anxious.
Feeling pressured.
- Wants his men around him.
- He's not the only one.
Director Vance
on the line for you, Mace.
Where's Kensi?
Director?
Hey. A guy just backed into me.
- Do you think you could possibly...
- We're closed.
Come on, man, I just need
to know if it's safe to drive.
You have a bathroom?
No, we don't.
This is not so bad.
You are safe.
It's cosmetic damage.
Just bring it back next week.
Okay.
- Is Wednesday okay?
- Wednesday's fine.
Thank you.
Camera's inside the door.
Pulling up the new camera angle.
I understand, Director. I will.
Good-bye.
Traced the call Haziq just received.
Caller's name is Nasim Boutros.
Home address is a long-stay hotel,
room 1122,
at 73 Promenade Way, Marina Del Rey.
Mace, that's the hotel
Rivkin is staking out.
Where was Nasim
when he made that call?
- Less than a half mile from the hotel.
- On his way home.
And Rivkin is waiting for him.
Get Gibbs.
- Yeah.
- Vance has cleared it
with the Attorney General.
We have a FISA warrant. Get Rivkin.
Go around back!
- Gibbs!
- Yeah. Clear.
Any idea what they're arguing about?
Cell phone coverage.
Haziq can't reach anyone
on his phone. And...
Jumah's telling him
it's a piece of American junk.
How did Nick sound on the phone?
He sounded okay.
They're planning something,
aren't they?
If they use
what they're buying from me...
yeah.
Do you have any idea what it is?
No.
Change of plans.
You are going to make
the weapons delivery today.
- Here?
- Yes, here.
Call whoever you need to call.
You have an hour,
and then our business is done.
- He's calling Sam.
- Hey, it's Liam.
Bring the suitcases to the auto shop
at 13th and Baker's Lane in one hour.
Okay, let's make it happen.
One hour.
McGee, anything on Rivkin?
No. GPS marker says he didn't leave
the hotel parking lot.
He must have found
the GPS tracker and dumped it.
Got a BOLO out on his rental.
Nothing yet.
- Keep on it.
- Yes, ma'am.
It's him. It's Tim.
He knows I'm sitting at his desk.
Tell him you're in your lab.
He won't know.
- He'll know. He knows everything.
- Gibbs knows everything.
McGenius is smart,
but he doesn't know everything.
Hi, Tim.
I'm not upstairs in the squad room.
I'm in my lab. I'm working.
Are you sitting at my desk?
No.
Abby, listen, last night,
you did a facial recognition search
on Michael Rivkin. Why?
What makes you think that?
You logged the search.
I did?
I did.
Did Tony ask you to do it?
I'm not at liberty to say.
- You are at my desk, aren't you?
- Yeah.
- And Tony is watching you?
Can I talk to Tony, please?
Okay. It's for you.
It's McGoo...
McGee... Tim.
Sorry, McGee.
Ignore her, Probie.
She's suffering Gibbs withdrawal.
Transferring it onto you because
of a deep-seated fear
that Gibbs may withhold love
and give her first-time head slap
if he came back and saw
his desk festooned in balloons
and decorated like
some tacky tiki bar
with messages of affection
written possibly in blood.
She ain't missing you at all.
In fact, I can't think
of a single person that's missing you.
Well, I'll tell you who we're
all missing and that's Michael Rivkin.
Define "missing".
Two members of the terrorist cell
are dead after Rivkin paid them a visit,
and now he's dropped out of sight.
Do you think
that there is any chance Ziva...
Don't ask that question.
Well, Tony, someone has to ask it.
I know, McGee.
I know.
Leave it to me.
Here you go.
Here's what we know.
Nick Quaderi, dead.
Almost certainly killed
by Michael Rivkin.
Nationality, unknown.
Date of birth, unknown.
Quaderi has a girlfriend, Shakira.
Who has a brother, Rafi Zayd.
No confirmed photo.
Moved back to Yemen when he was seven.
No record of him returning to the U.S.
Probably here illegally.
Nasim Boutros,
stabbed by Rivkin at his hotel.
American citizen, born in Syria.
Immigrated here when he was 14.
Has a degree in engineering.
No criminal record.
First name... Jumah.
Last name... unknown.
Looks like he works at the auto shop,
but he's not listed
as an employee with the IRS.
Possibly here illegally.
And finally, Haziq Khaleel.
Born in Syria. Immigrated 12 years ago.
Owns the auto shop.
Pays his taxes,
and has no criminal record.
Five men,
all born outside the United States.
Very few personal details,
no criminal activity.
Not on anyone's watch list.
It's a classic sleeper cell.
Rivkin's making sure
none of them wake up.
Five people.
Four passports, four suitcases.
Something's missing.
Then number five is the handler.
Maybe Haziq?
No, Haziq's an alpha male.
A physical, take-charge kind of guy.
Aggressive, angry.
Handlers are more refined.
Methodical planners, smooth talkers.
They know how to get
under people's skin.
You know, make 'em feel
things and do things, and...
You get the idea.
If it's not Haziq?
Well, Shakira's brother
Rafi's too young.
Wouldn't have the respect of the others
who all seem to be older.
- Then that leaves Nick Quaderi.
- Yeah, but according to Rafi's sister,
Nick Quaderi didn't know any of them
till her brother
introduced him to Haziq.
Then we're missing something.
Yep.
Or someone.
What did I miss?
Abby playing with crayons,
possibly blood.
McGee calling.
And I made a paper airplane
that was so fantastic
it broke the office gliding record.
But really all the fun's happening
in another area code.
Are we... fighting?
If we were,
you would be on the floor bleeding.
Okay, I accept that as a likely outcome.
So you're just annoyed with me?
Angry?
- You should not be surprised.
- Because of this morning?
You thought I would not identify
Michael Rivkin as a Mossad operative.
- I didn't say a word.
- You did not have to.
So you think you did
the right thing?
You think I didn't?
Maybe
you should have told them more.
Like how well you know him.
How well do I know him, Tony?
You know him better
than they think you do.
And you know that how?
You saw him when he was in D.C.
three days ago.
You didn't tell when you had the chance.
And I'm just wondering why, that's all.
Are you, by any chance,
questioning my loyalty?
I'm questioning why you didn't tell them
you saw him three days ago.
Are you jealous?
No.
I'm worried.
Because you don't seem to understand
that your secret friend is interfering
with this agency's ability
to shut down a terrorist cell.
Interfering? How is he interfering?
He's already killed two suspects.
Well, in my country
that would be cause for celebration.
You're not in your country,
and neither is he!
Have you finished?
Yes.
Good.
No.
Another question.
- You know where we can find him?
- No, I don't.
And if you did, would you tell me?
No.
But I would tell Gibbs.
I tried to stop my brother Rafi
from getting involved with them.
Now he's dragged Nick into it.
How long have you known him?
Three months.
He travels a lot. I don't get to see him
as much as I wanted.
At first Rafi didn't want me
to see him at all, but...
Nick was patient.
Now, they're like brothers.
I've never met Rafi.
You don't have any photos, do you?
Of course.
Nick took it.
And you've probably got tons
of photos of Nick in there, huh?
Nick's so camera shy, it's crazy.
Hard to believe, but...
this is the only photo I have.
Eric, talk to me.
- Have we lost audio?
- They're whispering, Mace.
- Who's whispering?
- Everybody.
Why the hell are they whispering?
- You ready?
- On your command, Mace.
Stand by. If you were Rivkin,
where would you be?
I wouldn't be far.
I'd want to finish the job.
At our expense. If we're gonna find
their target and their support team,
we need at least one of them alive.
No, he doesn't think that way.
- Where the hell are you going?
- Let you know when I get there.
Come on, G, speak up!
I need to contact Nick.
You heard Haziq...
he's not answering.
Well, I'm guessing he gave you
another number,
in case something bad happened.
Something bad is going to happen.
You can't keep running away
from this,
who they are,
what they're planning to do.
Something bad's going
to happen to Nick?
To your brother.
Who are you?
I'm someone you need
to trust right now.
Okay, they've stopped whispering.
I'm tired. I'm going home.
You can't keep me here.
No one leaves.
You can't stop me.
Your friend better be on time.
Promise me
nothing will happen to Rafi.
Promise me.
I promise you.
Three-one-0...
five-five-five...
zero-one-three-zero.
Nick Quaderi's real
name is Michael Rivkin.
He can be contacted at 310-555-0130.
I already have his number,
and I don't care what his real name is.
Okay?
- Searching for the number.
- Rivkin's been playing us all along.
It's a cell phone.
I need a GPS location now.
Nick Quaderi's the name
Michael Rivkin used.
He befriended Shakira so he could get
to know her brother Rafi.
Won over the brother
to get invited into the cell.
That means that the body Rivkin
told us was Quaderi is actually...
Rafi Zayd,
her brother.
All right, we got Rivkin's location.
He's almost on top of him.
Pass it on to the nearest team.
I can't wait. Sam?
- Game's yours.
- Okay, Mace. Moving in.
Go, go, go!
- Federal agents! Freeze!
- NCIS!
Sam, I want him alive.
- Clear!
All clear!
You'll live.
Secured.
Rivkin?
I got him, McGee.
You're Gibbs.
Time for you to go home.
Now.
I don't like leaving
things unfinished.
You're done.
I'm finishing it for you.
I leave, Washington
and Tel Aviv look the other way.
That's not what I'd do.
We fight the same war.
Only ours began in Auschwitz.
I have six million uniforms.
- Every one is different.
- I got one.
She works for me.
Shalom.
Guess
that drink's gonna have to wait.
Well, my basement's always open.
- It's good to see you, Jethro.
- Yeah.
Stay low.
- Red-eye, huh?
- Yeah.
Always worked for me.
Sorry.
Thanks.
No problem.
Long day, huh?
Yeah, yeah, long... day.
Just getting some, uh, some air.
Right.
Agent Gibbs?
Good to meet you, Nate.
Likewise.
I...
I took an oath not to betray
confidences,
but...
I can't see any harm
in telling you a story.
18 years ago, there was this young
lieutenant in the Military Police
who investigated a murder.
A Marine gunnery sergeant had taken out
this Mexican drug dealer
who killed his family.
The young lieutenant interrogated
the suspect, didn't hold back.
He just wanted closure, and...
she wouldn't leave his wife
and daughter to rest in peace.
Kind of thing that stays with you.
Anyway,
she got all the evidence
together, and...
then she buried it.
Decided it was a...
just killing.
My guess is that the guy
never even knew
that she'd been protecting him
all these years.
Well...
I think I had enough fresh air.
Are you gonna get out?
I think it's time to move.
Again?
That's 3 times
in the last 18 months.
It's 4.
I don't know, I...
I just feel like
someone's watching me.
It's probably that Russian girl
you told me about.
You ever gonna settle down, G?
One day.
Crazy son of a...
G!
Come on, G.
Come on, G. Stay with me.
Stay with me, G.
Don't do this to me, come on!
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
Ocean Front Road, Venice.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Come on, buddy.
I missed McGee.
I would never have guessed that.
Hey, you and Ziva want
to go get a drink?
She is already gone.
Did you do that secret thingy
I asked you to do?
Yep.
Rivkin flew out of Los Angeles today,
unescorted.
Destination?
Tel Aviv.
With a stopover...
in DC.
www.Team-NCIS.com