www.Team-NCIS.com
Okay, I came to a bar with you.
Now let's go.
No. No way.
I've been listening to you complain
the entire year
you don't have a girlfriend, okay?
All right, well, here they all are.
Yeah, I'm not very good
at picking up girls.
Look, even the worst pickup lines
are better than not trying.
Now, come on.
Give me something.
So, is it hot in here,
or is it just you?
Give me something else.
So, you Jamaican?
'cause you Jamaican me crazy.
I stand corrected.
That's absolutely worse
than not trying.
Maybe
you should just try being yourself.
Just be cool.
Yeah, well, if I was being myself,
I wouldn't be here.
Yeah, I know how you feel.
- My name's Lynne.
- Alfonso.
If you don't want to be here,
how come...
Don't have a TV at home?
Not being cool?
That's...
That's my brother's car.
Roman, what the hell's going on?!
Alfonso, listen carefully.
It's happening.
Wherever you are, you've got to run!
Now!
NCIS Season 7 Episode 14
Masquerade 1.0 LOL
Synchro: Gaillots.
Rereading: Bruno & Magic Turtle.
www.Team-NCIS.com
Dancing lessons?
You cannot be serious.
May 25, national tap dance day.
I want to be prepared.
- What if you're unprepared?
- Well, the unprepared do not get
invited to the national tap
dance parties,
and I want to go.
I got a tweet to go to this blog
that linked me to this holiday site.
Do you know how many holidays there are
that fly underneath the radar?
It's astonishing.
Lot of ladies at those parties.
I went to an international talk
like a pirate day party last year.
You did not. Excellent.
- Let me hear some pirate speak.
- Why is McGee wearing a tuxedo jacket?
Yes.
Tuxedo.
It's a bold fashion choice
for a young investigator.
Watch someone get married
at work day?
It's an online wedding.
Of course it is.
Look, it's a gamer buddy from Spain.
He set this up for people
that couldn't make it, okay?
I would be laughing if...
I weren't on the edge of tears.
This is sad.
Grab your gear. We got a...
- He's at a wedding.
- In Spain.
Boss, it's almost done.
Take your time.
I think McGee is taking
this technology thing a little too far.
And this is coming from the man
who follows tweets
to blogs to web sites.
- All done, boss. Thanks.
- Let's go.
Grab your gear.
Got an exploding car.
Got a dead Marine.
Could I just have a minute to...
Nope. You've had your minute, McGee.
Lucky the blast was isolated.
Considering the debris radius,
this could have been much worse.
- Not for this guy.
- Boss, the car was registered to a...
Lance Corporal Roman Vega,
stationed at Quantico,
just back
from his second tour in Iraq.
The chase started at Olive and 29th
when Vega ran a stop sign.
About a half mile later,
the car hit a pothole and kaboom.
Acetone hydroxide.
Bless you.
It is an explosive, Tony.
It was in the trunk.
It has a very distinctive odor,
highly volatile.
Given the lack
of any discernible trigger
and timing of detonation,
the explosion
was likely an accident.
Why would a Marine be driving
around with explosives In his trunk?
We found the torso.
Yes, it's resting in peace
around the corner there by...
that dumpster.
It matches
Corporal Vega's general build, but,
the burns are extensive.
We will probably need DNA
for a positive identification.
In the meantime,
he's ready for his close-up.
We're still missing
several major body parts.
Yeah, sorry.
I forgot about this.
It's the head.
- What's left of it.
- DNA.
Yeah, landed,
back behind an old bowling alley,
of all places.
I do hope,
if the time comes,
when your head finds itself
removed from your body,
it is treated with more respect.
- Ducky, I...
- Mr. Palmer!
Yes, sir?
We are still missing two patellas
and a shin bone.
- I didn't mean to be disrespectful.
- Get a tow truck.
Right.
That's weird.
Weirder than you carrying a head
around in a bag and forgetting about it?
What?
See, I get a signal over here.
Closer to the car,
drops off in inches.
Yeah, I got a dead spot like that
in my therapist's office.
Dead zones are common inside,
but out...
Therapist?
Physical therapist.
You seeing a physical therapist?
- I hurt my knee.
- How did you do that?
Kneeling.
I don't believe you.
Come on.
- What's that, a lie detector?
- No. It's a Geiger counter.
I just thought of something that could
cause localized RF interference.
Radiation.
First plague,
now radiation poisoning.
I'm starting to think
someone really has it in for me.
- I was there, too, near the car.
- We all were.
But don't let that stop you
from thinking about yourself.
This isn't about me.
It's about my little DiNozzo makers.
They've been nuked.
- I know.
- Do you?
I mean, sure,
your kids are gonna be smart,
But mine had a shot
at being really beautiful.
Well, hopefully,
Gibbs will bring us some good news.
That doesn't look like good news.
I was so worried!
I hitched a ride with the emergency team
when I heard.
- You guys okay?
- You tell us.
Yeah, you're okay.
They only found minute traces
of radiation on the car.
You guys could even get
your clothes back.
Nice work, McPanic.
What was the source
of the radiation?
Good news is
that it wasn't from the explosion.
But the vehicle... it had been used
to transport something called cobalt-60.
It's a byproduct
of nuclear reactors.
It's used for, like,
industrial mining and X-ray machines.
Dirty bombs.
And why was Lance Corporal Vega
transporting radioactive material?
If it can be used to make a dirty bomb,
the more pressing question is,
where is it now?
All the information regarding
international travel...
And nobody talks to the press.
And do not talk to the press!
This just in.
I think
it's a little too late for that.
... that a radiological dispersal
device commonly known as...
Dirty bomb loose in DC? We don't even
know there is a dirty bomb.
Nope, but it's good for ratings.
Corporal Vega...
Gibbs is gonna want a full briefing
when he gets done talking to Vance.
What do we got?
Well, we did a preliminary workup while
you were showering for the third time.
Lance Corporal Roman Vega.
- Born in Lima, Peru, 1981.
- He and his younger brother, Alfonso,
went to live with their aunt in Maryland
after their parents were killed.
Cell records show that Roman called
to his brother During the police chase.
- Let's bring him in.
- No one knows where he is.
Well, then find him!
- Kind of busy, Leon.
- You're gonna want to hear this.
Special Agent Gibbs,
meet Walter Kane.
I'm glad to finally meet you, Gunny.
Been following you for some time.
Yeah? Really?
What, on my blog?
Not exactly,
but I do my own research.
I knew
we'd be meeting up eventually.
How's that?
Lance Corporal Roman Vega.
Mr. Kane runs
a private intelligence firm.
- They do work for the Pentagon.
- Between Iraq and Afghanistan,
our country's own intel services
are stretched thin, so...
We outsource firms like Mr. Kane's
for countries
that we're not at war with.
- Like Peru.
- Good guess.
We handle it exclusively.
Currently, we're tracking
a group out of Lima
called Libertad Nueva. Means...
New liberty?
They claim to be
a grassroots organization,
formed to protest
US anti-drug policies in Peru.
Which they say have caused
civilian casualties.
It's a lie.
They're not freedom fighters.
They're drug dealers
who just want the US out of their hair.
We think they're planning an attack,
hoping to weaken our resolve.
What do you got on Vega?
Well, he's been seen
with suspected LN members in Lima.
And for a man with no family in Peru,
he travels there quite a bit.
That's it?
That and the fact
that his car glows in the dark.
I don't deny our intelligence linking
Vega to these terrorists is slim.
We're victims of budget cuts
like everyone else, but we're sure
there's a cell here.
And Vega was our only link to them.
Thank you.
We'll take it from here.
Thank you, sir.
I have to testify before the Senate.
An upcoming defense contractor bill.
Reason we don't have money
for real intelligence is
the boys on the Hill love to spend money
on toys that we don't really need.
Yeah. Gibbs.
Vega just checked his e-mail.
Belmont hotel.
I'll be right down.
Got a lead on Roman's brother.
He just logged on
to his e-mail account.
Belmont hotel.
Hotel manager said Vega came
into the lobby two hours ago,
- Used the guest computer...
- Then checked into room 102.
People have been coming
and going ever since.
What kind?
He said the kind of people
he wouldn't want to mess with.
- We knocking?
- No!
Would you like the honors?
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
NCIS! Federal agents!
- What the...?
- Put them down!
- You put them down! Federal agents.
- Don't see any I.D.
That won't be necessary.
Put your weapons down.
Hello, Mr. Gibbs.
You know each other?
He's my client.
Your "client"?
That's right.
Since when, Alfonso?
Don't answer that.
This is going to get ugly.
- I hope so.
- Go on. Get out of here.
- Will you turn that thing off?
- Give us a minute.
Don't worry, it'll be okay. Come on.
- Have you seen the news lately?
- I have.
- We don't have time for this.
- For what? The rule of law?
I don't have a problem with the law.
Roman Vega was a new client of mine.
He contacted me a few weeks ago.
About?
Sorry, attorney-client privilege.
After Mr. Vega was killed,
his brother called me.
He was scared.
He wanted to talk.
Don't bother asking me about...
What?
As a precaution,
I told him to meet me here,
and I arranged for private security.
Colonel Bell's men?
Colonel Bell owed me a favor
after I rescued him from that Mexican
hellhole you sent him to.
Not me, the rule of law.
Which also says I have
the right to talk to Alfonso.
Yes, it does.
And you're more than welcome,
as long as I'm in the room.
- Did I miss it?
- Nope, just starting.
Where's Ziva?
Bringing the popcorn.
Mr. Gibbs
is trying to make you nervous.
Don't let him.
Special Agent.
Excuse me?
Special Agent Gibbs.
And I'm not trying to make you nervous.
I just need answers.
And I think you want answers, too,
considering your brother is dead.
Now he's trying to piss you off.
Just ask the questions.
You talked to your brother, right,
before the explosion?
Yeah.
What did he say?
He told me to run.
- Why?
- Don't answer that.
Did he tell you why he was
transporting radioactive material?
Don't answer that.
Did you know that he was
a member of Libertad Nueva?
Looks like you didn't.
Nicely done.
Ziva better hurry,
or she is going to miss it.
Would you like to confer
with your client? Because
I think he knows something
you don't know.
- Roman didn't do anything wrong.
- We need a moment alone.
Yes! He's fishing,
And that's dangerous.
Mr. Gibbs has put plenty
of guilty men behind bars, but
- he's also put some innocent ones away.
- What's Libertad Nueva?
They're drug dealers, terrorists.
Roman would never be involved in.
- But he was involved with something.
- Don't answer that.
I want answers, too.
Don't know what he was messed up in,
but whatever it was...
had him really freaked out.
He wouldn't give me
any details, but...
He wanted you to do something.
I work for a cell phone company.
He asked me to...
back-trace some calls to a warehouse
in Virginia.
He wouldn't tell me why.
He just told me not to trust anybody.
I hope I'm not making
a mistake trusting you.
- Think he's telling the truth?
- He's telling a story, not sure whose.
The popcorn!
I burnt the first batch, but...
DiNozzo,
take Ziva and check out
that warehouse.
Taking Ziva.
Checking out the warehouse.
Well, I'm sure
you're feeling pretty satisfied.
I am going to go
get a haircut.
I'm feeling pretty satisfied.
Good.
Then you can release my client.
I can.
You have no right to hold him.
You haven't charged him with anything.
Terrorism. Don't need to.
Spoken like a third world dictator.
I don't make the rules. He's telling
the truth, he's better off here.
How noble of you.
Fine!
Then if he's staying,
I'm staying.
Fine.
Just past the door
to the vending machines.
Gun battle?
Hand-to-hand?
Knife fight?
Right?
Something about our friendly
neighborhood counselor
makes you think
she might be good with a blade.
Well, she is tenacious.
And training is important in a knife
fight, but not as important as spirit.
What is that?
It's a Geiger counter.
Can't be too careful.
What do you think Corporal Vega
was doing at an empty warehouse?
I don't know. Why don't you pick
the lock and find out?
We do not have a warrant.
This building is foreclosed,
which means it's owned by the banks,
and since the people own the banks,
I think technically we own the building.
Lock picked.
I do not think our friendly neighborhood
counselor would approve.
Let her spend
a night working a homicide.
Tell ya...
Things aren't so black and white
when the walls are all splattered
with red, are they?
Or when your way
of life is threatened.
Exactly.
Wait a second. Are you mocking me?
No, Tony. I was not mocking you.
It's just that...
when I was held hostage in Somalia,
Saleem used
similar justifications
for his actions.
Saleem...
Caf-Pow!-Swilling sociopath
was a terrorist, Ziva.
I'm sure he would say
he was just protecting his way of life.
You're not seriously defending him,
are you?
No, Tony.
His actions were indefensible,
Regardless of his reasons.
And that is my point.
This country holds itself
to a higher standard.
It is a nation of laws,
which are to be followed
not only
when it is convenient or easy.
I have seen firsthand what happens
when convenience
wins out.
You never talk about it.
What is there to talk about?
Come on, Ziva.
What Saleem did was bad enough.
Becoming like him
would be worse.
The food is fresh.
Whoever was here left in a hurry.
They had a little bonfire
before they split.
Acetone hydroxide.
Lots of wires.
A couple of timers.
They were building a bomb.
It's definitely the dirty kind.
I found traces of cobalt-60
on all of the evidence
that Tony and Ziva brought in.
Is it safe?
Yeah, totally.
This was just way too cool to take off.
I like the sound it makes when I move.
So did Tony and Ziva get any prints?
Hundreds.
But judging
by the decomposition of skin oil,
I'm thinking that they belong
to the building's old occupants.
- I'm running them now.
- Any idea how big a bomb could be out?
It looks like they mixed
enough acetone hydroxide
to blow up Roman Vega's car,
like, five times over.
So most of it is still out there.
Tony and Ziva
also found an old laptop.
It's burnt to a crisp,
but I still think
I can get something off the hard drive.
All right, let me know.
I've got to report back to Gibbs.
Wait, wait, wait!
- What?
- I can't believe this.
I had my whole presentation
timed out perfectly.
So when I said, "I can still pull
something off the hard drive",
my decryption algorithm
was supposed to...
Better late than never.
Okay, so, there's only
two things on the laptop:
An encrypted video file
and solitaire.
I guess terrorists get bored, too.
Here's the file.
Hola, Mis hermanos.
Get the package in position.
Wait for my order to detonate.
I repeat:
Do not detonate
until you hear from me.
Buena suerte.
I'm guessing by "package",
he means "bomb".
Look at the bright side.
If there's a bomb out there,
with Corporal Vega dead,
we've bought some time.
I'm afraid not as much
as you might think.
Here.
I need to talk to Gibbs.
The cause of death
was as we expected.
Multiple traumas caused by the...
Sorry...
Agent DiNozzo
actually invited me to...
It's not important.
Won't happen again.
Yes, well...
Dismemberment was
the cause of death.
I found a wound that,
predates the blast.
- It's a cigarette lighter?
- Yeah.
It's the one from the car
and the angle suggests
that it was not self-inflicted.
He wasn't in the car alone, then?
Well, whoever was there with him
apparently got out of the car
at some point during the police chase.
But that's not
why I called you down here.
Mr. Palmer,
I just sent some DNA up to Abby
for positive identification,
but before that,
we made a dental impression of the most
perfect set of teeth I've ever seen.
Not a single cavity.
No rotations.
Had all of his wisdom teeth.
Something Corporal Vega
did not have.
This isn't Vega.
Yeah, the Corporal is alive
to give whatever orders
he wishes, whenever he wishes.
This isn't Corporal Vega?
Then who is it?
His name's John Cook.
Former Sergeant.
Served briefly in the second Gulf War
before being dishonorably
discharged for looting.
Ducky finally found intact DNA.
- Victim or involved?
- Involved.
Abby lifted his prints off of one
of the bomb timers
Tony and Ziva found
in the warehouse.
So Cook makes the bombs,
and Vega gives the when and where.
So, when and where?
We're working on it.
Unfortunately,
Cook was our best link to Vega.
We've been doing deep background,
going through credit card statements.
So far, nothing unusual shows up.
Back it up.
Dr. Mallard's report said
Cook had perfect teeth, right?
- That's right.
- These right here.
Then why was he going
to a new dentist every two days?
That does qualify as unusual.
I'm gonna go find out.
I have to brief the Joint Chiefs.
You have any idea how Vega plans
to relay the detonation orders?
- Take your choice.
- Then we prepare for the worst.
I've been told that the risk
of radiation exposure
from a dirty bomb
is fairly negligible.
Most of the injuries will be
from the explosion itself.
But the real threat to the city
is panic.
That's why they call the dirty
bombs weapons of mass disruption.
When people get scared,
it gets deadly.
- Well, they are scared, Leon.
- I've been having second thoughts
about my testimony
against the defense contractor bill.
Seemed like overkill.
Yesterday.
Oh, yes, I remember him.
A walk-in.
Showed up, wanted his teeth cleaned.
Then he left.
Did you notice anything unusual?
Only that he had about the most
perfect teeth I'd ever seen.
We heard from the last
two dentists we visited.
Yeah. Well, working on him was...
almost orgasmic.
Didn't really need to hear that.
His retromolar pad was shaped just
like a renaissance bosom.
We're gonna go. Thank you.
You think he had something
to do with the robbery?
Robbery?
Isn't that why you're here?
Couple days later,
someone broke in.
Thieves cleaned out
all our X-ray machines.
How many exactly?
Well, in the entire practice...
15.
And these weren't those cheap
tube machines. These were
top-of-the-line cobalt-based units.
Excuse me, Dr. Shore,
you're needed in room 1.
Yes, I'm on my way.
Thank you.
I have a patient waiting.
Is that all?
- No, that's all for now. Thanks.
- Thank you.
Well, that explains
the credit card charges.
Cook was casing dentists' offices,
looking for radioactive material.
At the dentist?
It's the dirty secret
about dirty bombs.
Sources are everywhere.
Oil platforms, medical equipment.
There's too many to keep track of.
Is the cobalt of 15 machines
enough to make a dirty bomb?
Once the material's powderized,
it's enough to make five.
Five.
Fantastic.
You tell Gibbs.
Okay, well, get back here.
There's computery stuff for you to do.
Tell Gibbs about what?
Still here, how nice.
I told you I'm not leaving
until my client is released.
We could always have
security escort you out.
I was just
playing with words,
putting them together in random order.
Now that is Gibbs' desk.
Where is
Mr. Gibbs?
He hasn't left MTAC all day.
- I hope it's not because of me.
- It's probably more to do
with the impending terrorist attack
your client is planning.
Allegedly planning.
And I was as surprised
as you were that he was still alive.
Tell me something.
Who cuts Mr. Gibbs' hair?
Excuse me?
I think you can tell
a lot about a man by
who cuts his hair.
Who cuts your hair?
My sister.
She has for years.
I imagine
you spend more on your hair
than it'd cost to feed
a third world family for a year.
How much does that cost?
And Mr. Gibbs...
well, I see him getting his hair cut
at the same mom-and-pop shop
he's been going to for years.
Get out of my chair.
You talk to McGee?
Five.
What's the plan?
I would be... happy to leave...
as soon as you release my client.
Like I said before,
he's better off here.
Is that how you justify denying him
his right of habeas corpus?
- Is that what I'm doing?
- You know what I can justify?
Filing suit against NCIS
and you personally
for violating
over ten Federal and State
constitutional protections.
Calling security, yeah.
Let him go.
Let him go?
You heard him.
Release my client.
Releasing the client.
I have a visual on the target.
He's being cautious.
This is the third place he stopped after
his lawyer dropped him off at home.
But the first time
he has sent his taxi away.
Why do I get
a funny feeling Gibbs planned
on using this guy
as bait from the beginning?
Because he is Gibbs.
I sure hope I'm not around
when Miss Hart finds out
he used her client as bait.
Or maybe I do.
This is all assuming the brothers
had a prearranged meeting place.
He's here.
Yes, we should think positive.
No. I mean, he's here.
Right in front of me,
coming out the door.
All right, let's take him.
I screwed up, it's my fault.
All right...
NCIS. Freeze!
He said freeze!
You're making a mistake.
Really? Good.
I know someplace quaint we can talk.
I told your agents
I want to talk to my lawyer.
She's on her way.
So, you can't ask me any questions.
That is right.
You know you got the wrong guy.
I am not a terrorist.
Hola, Mis Hermanos.
Get the package in position.
Wait for my order to detonate.
- I can explain that.
- I can't wait.
All right, screw the lawyer. I...
What is that?
An attorney waiver.
What is the matter with you,
Marine?!
- I'm being set up.
- By who?
I don't know his name.
He said he worked
for the Department of Defense.
Said they needed
native Spanish speakers to perform
- in a top secret training video.
- That him?
- That's him.
- Well, he does not work for the DOD.
He had all the credentials.
He took me to this building.
It was set up to look like
a terrorist hideout.
I recorded...
all kinds of messages for the video.
BioTerror, dirty bomb attacks.
Hell, I even did
a militia insurrection.
- It was all fake.
- Not all.
- It was supposed to be.
- It wasn't!
A few days later,
I noticed I was followed.
So, I got suspicious,
and I started asking around
about the training program.
No one had heard about it.
I knew I was in trouble.
And you go hire a lawyer
instead of going to your superior?
Look, I didn't know who to trust.
I read an article about this woman.
Heard that she helps people like me.
We played phone tag for a while,
and before we could talk,
my recruiter shows up,
and he sticks a gun in my back,
and he says, "drive".
Luckily, I saw a cop.
I blew a stop sign to get attention.
I bailed in an alley
during the chase.
My recruiter had no choice
but to keep on going.
I called my brother, And then,
I heard the explosion right after.
And then what, you just play dead
until you figure out what else to do?
Do you believe me?
Well, you'd better,
because whatever terrorist attack
they're planning,
I don't know a thing about it.
Yeah, well, the cell records do confirm
the game of phone tag with the lawyer,
and,
we found traces of blood on the street
where Vega said he leapt from the car.
His blood?
Down to the last chromosome.
What about the trips to Peru?
Looks like pleasure, not business.
Her name is...
Gloria Garcia Ramirez
De Arroyo Fuentes.
She's a nurse in Lima.
There's no way he's our guy.
Not a suicide bomber in the world
who'd have a girlfriend looks like that.
Unless, you know,
your gut says otherwise.
He said he was set up.
Libertad Nueva needed a fall guy.
And Corporal Vega fit the profile.
Well, I guess we can assume
the upcoming attack's real.
It's too bad we lost
our number one suspect.
But we do have a number two:
the dentist.
I sent a forensic team to his place.
Assistant said he left for lunch
after our visit, never returned.
- Get a Bolo.
- Already out.
That's not why I came down here.
You have to see this.
Received verification
from several sources,
and now ZNN can confirm
the message was e-mailed
to our Washington bureau chief.
It warns that, unless the US agrees
to halt its anti-drug
operations in Peru,
Libertad Nueva is going to blow
one dirty bomb per day
in the DC metro area,
starting in one hour.
Homeland security is
advising people to stay home.
Panic is
the greater threat at this time.
I need a copy of that e-mail now.
- On it.
- DiNozzo...
- You need to talk to metro PD Chief.
- McGee, find the dentist.
- Already on it.
- Gibbs, tell me you got something.
The Joint Chiefs want a sit-rep now.
What can I give 'em?
Not Vega.
I heard. What can I give you?
- Lawyer.
- Already banned her from the building,
but she's the least of our concerns.
We've already had two traffic fatalities
in the rush to get out of the city.
- Do you have any leads on the target?
- Boss, I think I got something here.
Our dentist may be MIA,
But there's activity on a site
he belongs to called "oralhappiness.com"
a social networking site
for oral care providers.
Anyway, uploaded photos
of a bus station off G street.
Either this guy has
a serious greyhound fetish...
Anybody else looking at these?
Well, the photos
were recently viewed.
From behind a firewall,
but the IP address is out of Peru.
It must be how they're relaying
information on the target.
Let's go. We're moving.
- Bomb squad's on their way.
- They're not going to make it.
DiNozzo, Ziva,
coordinate with local LEOs.
Evacuate the building,
but nobody leaves!
All right, Gibbs.
Radiation sensors. They'll only work
if the bomb
is unshielded,
but it's better than nothing.
Come on, you're with me!
- Where are we going?
- To find the bomb!
Don't make me say it, McGee.
We'll be careful, Tony.
Hey, how much time?
- Less than five.
- What are we looking for?
In a inside setting like this,
something small.
How small?
Briefcase, maybe smaller.
It's somewhere over here,
but something is blocking the sensor.
Evacuate mission is complete.
You want us to hold our position?
Yeah, you stay outside.
Gives a whole new spin
to "dirty bomb".
Lead-lined.
- That's why it was blocking our sensor.
- You recognize the design?
Not really, I mean,
I know the good old black
and red wires probably
supplies the power.
We're going to have to do
better than a probably.
- We definitely have time to run.
- Then run.
The building's been evacuated.
We just let it blow.
Go. Leave.
Boss, the, the threat
of contamination is minimal.
Go! That's an order. Now, leave.
It's an order I'm disobeying.
OK, if it's a tamper-resistant circuit,
we're dead,
but I'd say cut the black...
I was going to say black, but...
I guess red works.
Actually, no, it didn't.
McGee was right.
There's a tamper-resistant circuit.
As soon as you cut any of the wires,
the bomb should have detonated.
I'm still here, Abs.
The explosive was mixed incorrectly.
The first batch was made too unstable,
so it blew up Roman Vega's trunk.
I don't know,
I guess they overcompensated
for the second batch,
made it too lean.
These terrorists, they get
an "A" for terrorizing,
but, gratefully,
an "F" in chemistry.
Been over the security tapes, Boss.
Whoever planted the bomb
knew to avoid the cameras.
I vote for the dentist.
Ever since Marathon Man,
I always vote for the dentist.
If it was him, that'll be the last bomb
he was planting.
Look at this, Boss.
Bolo came back.
Metro PD found his body
under the McGregor Bridge.
They're calling it a suicide.
Yep, left a note.
Took credit for everything.
Did he now?
Guy disappears suspiciously.
Then plants a bomb for a terrorist group
he has no connection to.
Yeah, and then kills himself.
I usually like things
all nice and tidy.
It does not add up.
Libertad Nueva has been
very careful up until now.
Vega was their original fall guy.
Maybe they're improvising now.
Despite calls for calm
from several government agencies,
panic has engulfed the city.
What about the other four bombs?
If you're wrong, we're putting
a lot of lives in jeopardy.
I'm not.
I got here as quick as I could.
Thank you.
As our resident
Libertad Nueva expert,
I wanted to get your take on something
before I went to the Joint Chiefs.
The next bomb is set
to go off in 12 hours.
To prepare, Agent Gibbs thinks
that we should do nothing.
Nothing?
Not gonna be another bomb.
Yeah, he says it's all for show.
LN isn't given to making idle threats.
What's the endgame?
The Senate is set to vote
on a new defense bill tonight.
It's a terrible bill,
it was never going to pass.
Gave away billions in pork
to defense contractors.
But now, after the attacks,
looks like it might go through.
What, you think Libertad Nueva
is trying to influence the Senate vote?
No, you are.
Did some checking. Your company stands
to make 10 of millions of dollars
if that bill should pass.
The funny thing
about all the intel we got
on Libertad Nueva,
it comes from your company.
All we could
verify independently of the group
was a kid with a web site.
13-year-old kid.
You know, it's not unheard of
for somebody in your position to...
amplify things
for their own personal gain.
People get scared,
they make bad decisions.
You were counting on it.
You cooked the intelligence,
you created a fake sleeper cell.
No senator would ever vote against
any defense bill at threat level red.
This is ridiculous.
Sit down.
Our people traced the IP address
that uploaded the bus station photos.
Came from a computer in your office.
You did your best to camouflage it.
Well, I guess we just have
better nerds than you do.
You cop to it now,
right now,
you let me get this city off alert,
I'll ask the Attorney General
to waive the death penalty.
You got ten seconds.
After that, you can start thinking
about which vein
you want us to shut you off with.
Five seconds.
I'll need to talk
to my lawyers first.
Yeah, I bet you do.
We finally traced the photos
from the bus station.
They came from a computer
in Kane's office.
You were bluffing.
Cuff him.
Am I the only one
who needs a warrant?
Door was unlocked.
Well, that's going to end soon.
How dare you use my client as bait!
Your client was lying to me.
He knew how to find his brother.
He was protecting his brother.
Roman was innocent,
in case you didn't notice.
Then he didn't need protection.
Is that how it works?
You never put the wrong guy away?
And you've never helped
the wrong guy get away?
That's a very nice suit
you're wearing.
Roman Vega isn't going
to pay for that.
It's scum like Colonel Bell that do.
Everyone is entitled to a defense.
Yeah, but you don't have
to be the one to do it.
I guess with rates like yours,
you don't ask too many questions.
I do plenty of pro bono work.
Yeah, you know what?
I checked into that. You get...
I don't know
maybe five requests a week,
but the only ones you seem to do
are the ones
that take you across my path.
Are you really that conceited?
You're standing in my house!
You didn't know anything
about Vega's case,
but you took him on
as a client anyway.
He needed help.
You knew that it was going
to land you...
in front of me.
Don't flatter yourself.
Yet here you are...
again.
I have my reasons.
And I have a job to do.
And you keep getting in the way.
www.Team-NCIS.com