www.Team-NCIS.com
- Can't keep up?
- Ten bucks says I beat you to the car.
Make it 20.
Guess you owe me 20 bucks.
Oh, my God! David!
NCIS Season 6 Episode 03
Capitol Offense Version 0tv 1.0
Synchro: ¤AkaZab¤
Thanks to Bruno and Magic Turtle.
www.Team-NCIS.com
Looks scrumptious!
They call it Chocoholic's Choice.
Claim it is the ultimate cupcake.
- That smells great.
- Don't you dare!
Isn't this the week
you're going gluten-free?
Thank you, Ziva.
You shouldn't have.
I owe you for letting me sleep
at your place.
Slumber party.
You two spent the night together?
- What's going on here, McGee?
- Don't know, don't care.
None of my business, DiNosey.
You are such a control geek.
Freak.
Yes. That, too.
Why do you always need to know
everything that everybody does, Tony?
What he needs to know
is that a Lieutenant Commander's body
was found in Rock Creek Park.
Identified as a female United
States Navy Lieutenant Commander.
Gear up.
Her name is being withheld,
pending notification of her next of kin.
Lieutenant Commander
Carrie McClellan, 35.
Stationed at the Pentagon.
She worked as a congressional
liaison officer for the Navy Office
of Legislative Affairs.
Lives alone
in the Cleveland Park area.
Help DiNozzo.
Single small-caliber gunshot
to the back.
No exit wound.
However, her death
took place elsewhere.
This bloodstain to her back
indicates she bled out
on a solid surface.
Time of death?
Movement of the body and immersion
in water complicates matters,
but at least 12 hours,
no more than 24.
I'll be able to be more accurate
when I get her back on the table.
They were predicting precipitation.
Just what we need.
Got a partial shoe print here, boss.
Boss?
Work fast. It rains, we lose evidence.
Yeah, Gibbs.
Stayed at Abby's last night?
Guess you sleep in the same room?
- It is a one-bedroom apartment.
- One bedroom, one bed.
- One coffin.
- You want the truth?
Yeah.
I think I can handle the truth.
My building was being fumigated,
and Abby was kind enough
to let me stay over.
On the couch. In my pajamas.
Come on, work with me.
- Couldn't you lie just a little bit?
- DiNozzo, after you're through here,
the victim's apartment.
Right.
We're fighting the weather and he wants
us to hurry up, and then he leaves.
What is this all about?
Senator?
Gunny.
Hello, Patrick.
- Thanks for coming, Jethro.
- Yeah, sure.
Why here?
Well, it's best we not be seen
together right now.
I saw on the news,
a Lieutenant Commander was found shot
in Rock Creek Park.
NCIS involved?
I just left them.
Was it Carrie McClellan?
Did you know her?
We were having an affair.
Why'd you think
it was Carrie McClellan?
News report said the victim
was a female Lieutenant Commander.
Carrie lived near the park.
We were supposed to meet last night.
She didn't show, didn't call.
Try to reach her?
Carrie always made the contact.
Nothing unusual about a congressional
liaison calling a senator's office.
Her parents have been told?
Not yet.
They'll be devastated.
She was an only child.
I'm an idiot, Gunny.
I've thrown my career away.
Lynn and the kids don't deserve this.
Once the affair is made public,
everyone is gonna think I killed her.
Pat, I can't cover this up.
Don't expect you to, Jethro.
Tell me about
the Lieutenant Commander.
She was an incredible young woman.
Smart.
- Well-liked.
- Ex-boyfriends?
- Not that she mentioned.
- Problems?
She had a run-in with
her commanding officer.
- Yeah? She say what it was about?
- Not really.
He took exception to a report
she wrote.
Media's gonna have
a field day with this.
Couldn't have happened at a worse time.
My energy bill
is up for vote next week.
It shouldn't be defeated
because of my indiscretions.
Legislation is far too important.
The economy is a mess,
and fuel costs are leading the way.
This bill is a way of
turning things around.
Could you please keep my name
out of this until after the vote?
I'll see what I can do.
It is sad.
It was her birthday last week.
Her grandmother sent her this card.
Am I the only one that's starving?
Haven't eaten since lunch.
Well, there's half a veggie pizza
in the fridge.
- What are you doing?
- I'm building a profile of the victim.
- Not exactly Navy issue.
- She was not just a Navy officer.
She was also a woman.
Officer and a gentlewoman.
Richard Gere. Debra Winger.
It's a rare commodity.
Military chick flick.
It appears she had a lover.
"To the woman I love.
You mean everything to me".
And it is signed, "You know who".
Why would he not sign his name?
Maybe it's not a he. Maybe it's a she.
We are dealing with the military.
Don't ask, don't tell.
- Looks like a man's handwriting.
- Definitely a man.
How do you know?
Medicine cabinet.
Low-estrogen birth control pills.
- She's on the ninth day of her cycle.
- You just
love snooping around
into other people's lives, don't you?
Yeah. That's why I became a cop.
Hey, boss. Everything all right?
- Yeah.
- No signs of a struggle.
Didn't find any traces of blood.
The commander wasn't shot here.
The neighbors described
the victim as a loner.
No one knew her particularly well.
Still looking her personal effects.
Keys, wallet, cell phone.
Her car's parked
in her space downstairs.
She's got a lover
who won't sign his name.
There's no pictures or evidence
of him in the apartment.
Boss, my gut tells me she was having
an affair with a married man.
Lieutenant Commander McClellan
spent more time on the Hill
than she did at the Pentagon, but
- that goes with her job.
- When's the last time you saw her?
Monday's staff meeting.
She had Top Secret clearance.
- Do I have a security problem here?
- I don't know.
What were her responsibilities?
Developing and coordinating
relationships between
representatives of the D.O.N. and
members of Congress.
She made a lot of powerful friends.
Carrie was on the fast track.
Ever meet her boyfriend?
Didn't know she had one.
Don't really know anything
about her personal life.
Understand you took exception
to a report
Lieutenant Commander McClellan filed.
Technical specs were supposedly
leaked to a defense contractor a couple
days before their official release.
It was no big deal.
Never traced to my command.
McClellan wrote it up.
I told her not to.
She could be stubborn.
- That it?
- Yeah, for now.
Gonna need to take a look
at her office.
Had it secured. I'll make
arrangements for you to get in.
- That's odd.
- What?
I'm looking at Commander McClellan's
cell phone calls for the past month.
Restaurants, family, nothing unusual.
But there is one number
she called 36 times.
- Trace it.
- I don't have to.
It's the Capitol switchboard.
Well, that makes sense.
I am sure she has to call senators' and
representatives' offices all the time.
- It's part of her job.
- That's exactly my point.
Wouldn't she have
their direct dial numbers?
- How'd it go?
- Admiral made an impression on DiNozzo.
I'm gonna check him out.
He was more interested in covering
his ass than the victim.
- You got anything?
- I ran a locator search
on McClellan's cell. Either her phone
is turned off or the battery's dead,
so I pulled her phone records.
She made numerous calls
to the Capitol,
but always to the switchboard.
- She didn't want her calls traced.
- Accessed to ESR.
She was fourth in her class
at the academy.
Been nothing but uphill since then.
Awards and rapid promotions.
The family has not returned
my call yet.
Got a minute?
So, what's up with el jefe?
Yesterday, he leaves the crime scene
with no explanation.
Today, he knew the admiral
had a problem with the victim.
- Where'd he get that?
- Maybe he's bluffing.
- It was on the nose.
- Whose nose?
On the money.
Bulls-eye. Right as rain.
You were doing better before you went
back to Israel. You've reverted.
I found this message
on my private line.
You have one saved message.
The gun that killed
Lieutenant Commander McClellan
can be found in the drainage ditch,
alongside the two-mile marker,
near the Grant Road entrance
to Rock Creek Park.
It's so filthy.
I can't see anything.
It is filthy.
Must be some kind of
sewage thing or something.
It's not here.
Someone's messing with us.
I see something.
Over here. Look.
Look, look, look.
There. See that?
Looks like a sort of shadowy thing.
Here. Your turn.
I am the Jedi Master.
You are the Padawan learner.
No, it's... farther.
Farther out!
- I can't go farther.
- Farther out!
- I can't.
- All right, here.
I gotcha. I gotcha.
- You got me?
- I'm holding you.
- Farther out.
- Here, hold on.
A little further.
What's that? What do you got there?
See, I told you I saw something.
I had nothing to do with that one.
It's a Smith & Wesson 32 kit.
Just like the gat Bogie
was packing in Maltese Falcon.
It's the stuff dreams are made of.
Out of my way.
Any prints on the weapon?
Gibbs, it was underwater
and covered in mud.
- McGee found it with his butt.
- The serial number remained intact.
I gave it to Ziva.
She's running it down.
So, the test-fired slug
is on the left.
And the one that Ducky removed
from our victim is on the right.
- You've got your murder weapon, Gibbs.
- Yeah.
Handed to us on a silver platter.
Near the Grant Road entrance
to Rock Creek Park.
Secure line, restricted number.
Find out who made the call.
Director Vance, I'll need the password
to your voice mail account.
- For your eyes only.
- Yes, sir.
And the messages from my wife,
not for your ears.
I understand.
Go home. Change.
You think this is
a catch-me-if-you-can?
The killer's taunting us?
Possibility.
The Lieutenant Commander
had Top Secret clearance.
Worked on the Hill.
Had a lot of high-profile contacts.
I'm going to need to be kept in
the loop on this.
I've been on the case
less than 24 hours.
When I get something concrete,
I will let you know.
- What're you doing?
- A boundary's been crossed, Gibbs.
I've been violated.
Nothing is sacred anymore.
Yeah. Tell me.
Someone stole my cupcake.
- Cupcake?
- Yes.
And it wasn't just any cupcake.
It was a Chocoholic's Choice cupcake.
There is a thief amongst us.
I'm gonna find out who,
and they're going to be sorry.
Do you think you could pull
yourself away
from this long enough
to focus on the murder?
I've been working, Gibbs.
Commander McClellan.
She buys a lot of clothes online.
She downloads classical music, and she
reads her horoscope every day, as do I.
Today it said I was gonna have
a positive encounter with a coworker.
- Not gonna happen.
- That all you got?
No. I also found fibers
on the victim's clothing.
They're consistent
with automobile carpet.
So, I'm running the fibers through
the FBI fiber database
to try to find out
the make and... model.
What?
What?!
Is that a cupcake crumb?
No.
We'll see.
Thanks, Jer.
You are indeed the man.
If Carrie McClellan had a married lover,
I've got a pretty good candidate.
Her CO, Admiral Graves.
What'd you find out?
He and the wife separated a
year ago. Now they're back together,
trying to make it work.
But my source at the Pentagon
says he's still a player.
Who's your source?
- Jerry the barber.
- A barber?
Yeah, works in the Pentagon
Athletic Center.
Overhears more gossip than
anyone else in the building.
Barbers, manicurists,
shoe-shine guys, they're invisible.
People talk in front of them
like they're not even there.
Graves is involved.
- You accusing an admiral, DiNozzo?
- Following my instincts.
Boss, the anonymous call made to
Director Vance came from a burn phone.
Was purchased in cash from
a convenience store in Arlington.
- When?
- More than a year ago.
Surveillance video
is only kept for a month.
Call originated from a cell tower
near Lafayette Park,
across from the White House.
And I identified the voice.
- Who?
- Not exactly a "who".
The sly brown fox quickly
jumped over the lazy dog.
It's a text reader from
Write Draft 2007.
The most sophisticated
voice-generating software around.
Are we ever gonna catch
a break on this one?
I got lucky with the gun.
Serial number indicates
it was manufactured in 1949.
Was never registered.
But the firing pin looked new,
so I checked around.
Turns out ten years ago,
it was taken to a master gunsmith
for restoration and cleaning.
The owner's name was...
Otis Tripp.
He died in 1999.
No one leaves here till I get back.
Okay. Now I'm officially curious.
We found the murder weapon.
- That's a good thing, right?
- Yeah.
Owned by a Marine who's been dead
nine years.
Otis Tripp, your father-in-law.
Smith & Wesson, 32 kit.
Have you ever seen it?
Yeah.
Otis left it to me.
I don't understand.
It was in my den, locked in the gun
cabinet with the rest of my collection.
Where did you find it?
All right, I see where this is going.
I did not kill that woman.
I could never get anything by you.
You could always see
right through my bull.
I'm telling you the truth.
I did not kill Carrie McClellan.
Somebody's framing me.
It sure looks that way.
Did Carrie get killed because of me?
Yeah, Gibbs.
I need you back at my office, now.
What?
I gotta go. I love you, too.
Yeah?
- When'd the call come in?
- About an hour ago.
You have reached the voice mail of...
What's taking so long?
I led you to the gun.
When is an arrest going to be made?
Is Special Agent Gibbs
covering up for an old friend?
If there's something
you've been holding back, now
would be a very good time
for you to tell me.
- Where the hell are you going?
- Director Vance.
Senator Patrick Kiley.
I met Carrie about
a year and a half ago.
She was helping me with
two high school students from my state
who I was sponsoring
for admission to the academy.
I became fascinated.
Her intelligence, wit,
beauty.
I kept finding excuses to see her.
Obviously, that was a mistake.
And when you heard she was dead,
you called Special Agent Gibbs.
I knew the investigation
would lead to me. In Jethro's defense,
the first thing he said was
he wouldn't cover anything up.
Senator's being framed.
By whom?
Any enemies?
I'm a politician, Director Vance.
Enemies come with the territory.
Anyone in particular?
Yeah. Big oil money.
I hate to accuse anyone.
- We're talking about murder.
- No, Pat.
No, we're talking about you.
We're talking about your life,
murder of a naval officer
who might have been killed because
of her association with you.
My energy bill is going to pass.
If I'm a suspect of a murder,
the legislation is dead.
There's a lobbyist...
... Reed Talbot, who's been trying
to dig up dirt on me.
Would he have killed somebody
over a bill not passing?
It could cost the oil companies
tens of billions of dollars.
- And the vote's next week.
- Tuesday.
Your status as a senator aside,
this investigation will take us
where it takes us.
But it's the agency's policy
never to divulge details
of an ongoing case.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
I identified the fibers I found on
the Lieutenant Commander's clothing.
Charcoal gray from the cargo
compartment of a 2003
to 2006 Jeep Grand Cherokee.
Must be hundreds of
those in the metro area.
1,267. Open your mouth.
- What? Why?
- I need a DNA swab.
- What's this about?
- Someone stole her cupcake.
No. It's an invasion of privacy.
McGee, I will get your DNA
one way or the another.
Do what the woman says.
She sleeps in a coffin.
Thanks. You're next.
Can I do that myself? I don't like
people putting things in my mouth.
Thanks.
Abby, you're making too much of this.
I'll buy you another cupcake.
Feeling guilty, Ziva?
I got you the cupcake.
No one is above suspicion.
Is that?
- Yes, it is.
- Ziva, background on Reed Talbot.
Lobbyist for oil interest.
McGee, Director got
another anonymous phone call.
On it, boss.
- Come on, DiNozzo. You're with me.
- Need your DNA, Gibbs.
- I'll show you to the study.
- Senator?
Is everything all right? You haven't
been answering your phone.
I turned if off, Cole.
Everything's fine.
You know you missed
the Press Club Dinner.
I know.
Special Agents Gibbs and DiNozzo,
this is Cole Erickson,
my chief of staff.
FBI?
NCIS.
We're here investigating
a stolen weapon.
I'll explain it later.
Leroy
Jethro
Gibbs.
I thought I heard a familiar voice.
I was going to give Patrick
grief for disappearing tonight,
but since he was with you,
I'll forgive him.
Hello, Lynn.
Hi. I'm Lynn.
Anthony DiNozzo.
Lynn, I wish it were,
but this isn't a social visit.
No?
- Honey, we have to talk.
- What's wrong?
Cole, would you take Agents Gibbs and
DiNozzo into the study?
They're here to look at
my gun cabinet.
Yes, sir.
Right this way.
Let's go in here.
Look at that. Armed to the teeth.
Desert Storm?
Yeah, our base camp in Doha.
You're that gunnery sergeant
the senator always talks about.
- We served together.
- Well, the way he tells it,
you made a young,
raw Lieutenant look good.
It's locked.
Know where the key is?
I believe he keeps it
in his top drawer.
I got it.
Thanks very much. We'll let you know
if we need anything.
Well, some things never change.
Door's unlocked, and you're down
here working on that damn boat.
How you doing, Lynn?
I've had better days.
It is a six to five game,
top of the seventh inning.
And the series is tied at
two games apiece.
Is the bar open?
Tonight. Digs in. There's the windup.
Sure.
And a strike on the inside corner,
just got it!
Thank God the boys are away at school.
I had to get out of the house.
Been driving around for hours.
Realized I needed someone to talk to.
'Cause I promised
the bastard I wouldn't tell
anyone about his sleazy affair
with the dead girl, but
but since you already know.
Go. Talk.
You were there for me.
If you can get through Shannon
and Kelly's deaths,
I can get through this.
Gonna be tough.
A circus when the media
gets ahold of it.
I'll tell you one thing.
I am not going to be the dutiful wife,
standing by his side
at the press conference.
He got himself into this.
He can deal with it.
You knew about the affair?
Not at first.
I mean, you suspect,
but you don't want to believe it.
I didn't even know who the woman was.
I knew where they were meeting.
At his chief of staff's apartment.
Cole Erickson?
I didn't like that weasel
from day one.
Seems very loyal.
Loyal?
He'd do anything Patrick asked.
I think he's in love with my husband.
I've never seen him with a woman.
Patrick.
It's the fifth time he's called.
You can't keep avoiding him.
I'm not feeling very forgiving
at the moment.
That'll come.
You need to go home.
Thanks for listening, Jethro.
You know, as much as I hate
Patrick at this moment, you and
I both know he's a Marine to the core,
and he would never shoot anyone,
let alone a woman, in the back.
- Okay, talk to me, Abs.
- Thanks.
Okay, I analyzed all the prints
from the gun cabinet,
and I matched them all to
the elimination prints that Tony took
from Senator Kiley, his wife
and the chief of staff, Cole Erickson.
There's was one right index finger
that didn't belong to anybody.
I ran it through AFIS. Nothing.
- Did the senator have a housekeeper?
- Well, I think so.
What's that? That the shoe print
McGee lifted from the crime scene?
No.
The print that he lifted was from
a metro policeman.
Well then, what's that?
I'm so close to a bust, Gibbs.
You cannot have my cupcake and
eat it, too.
- You're not serious.
- Dead.
Thurman Atteberry?
- The night janitor?
- Seems like he's...
recently put on a little weight.
Reed Talbot.
Look at the crooked grin on his face.
Well, he's a lobbyist.
Arm-twisting sleaze bag.
To quote a Congressional aide
I interviewed this morning,
"Reed Talbot will do anything
in his power to defeat
Senator Kiley's energy bill".
I have a feeling about this guy.
Yeah, I had a feeling
about Admiral Graves.
- Even I can be wrong.
- Abs got a fingerprint she can't match.
Talbot's on file?
No. Checked. He has never been
in the military or arrested.
Hey, are Cole Erickson's
prints on the gun cabinet?
- Yeah.
- He's moving up my list.
He drives a 2006 Jeep Cherokee.
Don't know what color the interior is,
but I'm gonna find out.
That second anonymous to the director
was made from the same burn phone.
- The same location?
- No.
I need this.
What for?
- Hey!
- The call lasted 26 seconds.
Started on this cell tower. Halfway
through, transferred to this one.
The caller was in a vehicle,
traveling west bound on Independence.
Probably used a laptop
to generate the voice.
Excuse me, sir.
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
I am collecting signatures
for a national referendum.
- What's it about?
- There is a movement
trying to reintroduce
the 55-mile-per-hour speed limit
to reduce fuel consumption.
We are against it.
Do you know who I am?
A very handsome man who looks like
he keeps himself in shape.
Where do I sign?
Phone number and e-mail?
That's optional...
Reed.
Well, I'll be happy to give them...
To you.
- Thank you very much.
- My pleasure.
Here's the number of Erickson's PDA.
Trace it.
- I'm in the middle of something.
- Now!
Cole Erickson's Jeep
has a charcoal gray interior.
Matches the fiber
Abby found on the victim.
- Get a look at the vehicle.
- Can't find Erickson.
Not answering his phones.
Called the Senator's office, Erickson
never showed for work this morning,
they're looking for him, too.
- PDA's on.
- Where is it?
- Watergate Complex.
- Erickson has an apartment there.
Yeah, we're here. Is it still on?
- Yeah.
- Location?
McGee says the PDA's still on
at this location.
Give me a key.
Keep the hallway clear.
Mr. Erickson, NCIS!
Clear.
Boss?
It's a suicide note.
The suicide note was written and
printed on his computer.
Erickson's Grand Cherokee is
still on his parking space,
having it towed
to the evidence garage
Looks like you were wrong about
Reed Talbot.
He's still a crumb bag.
- You got something?
- Yes.
This area of the carpet
was recently cleaned.
I will get the ALS.
I can give you
a preliminary cause of death.
Asphyxia.
Yes, well,
it is rather obvious, isn't it?
Would you care to venture
the time of death?
Little after 10:00 this morning.
I'm not feeling very needed.
On what do you base your reasoning?
Suicide note was written at 10:02.
Boss. Found this in the desk.
It's the burn phone Erickson used
to make the anonymous calls
to the Director.
The laptop has
Write Draft Text Reader.
- Listen to this.
- What's taking so long?
I led you to the gun.
Gibbs?
Visitor.
Cole's body is still in there?
Can I see him?
It's a secure crime scene, Pat.
I just can't believe Cole
would do this.
When did he learn about your affair?
He knew from the beginning.
He let us use his apartment.
What was his relationship with her?
Didn't really have one that I know of.
He met her a few times.
I had my own key, so he was...
usually gone before we got here.
If what you're asking is:
did Cole disapprove?
Yes.
He left a note.
Full confession.
Admitted making the calls to NCIS.
Addressed to you.
Blood.
Asphyxia confirmed.
And I found a large quantity of diazepam
in his stomach and bloodstream.
- A depressant?
- Well, it's not unusual.
Suicides often take drugs to relax
so they won't change their mind,
and in his case,
pull the bag off his head.
- You got an opinion?
- It doesn't feel right.
We were handed the gun and
a suicide confession. It's too easy.
Senator Kiley is holding
a press conference in two hours.
I've been asked to attend.
I would like to be able to confirm
that this case is solved,
but I'm getting the feeling
that you don't think so.
Hell, you can get a lot done
in two hours, Leon.
You looking for me, Tony?
No.
I am.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
No.
- You thought I wouldn't figure it out?
- What is she talking about?
The cupcake.
You stole it from my refrigerator!
I have forensic evidence.
Your big fat fingerprint.
Come on, you think I'm that stupid?
Look, if I was going to steal
your precious cupcake,
I would not leave a fingerprint
on your refrigerator.
You didn't.
You used latex gloves.
Brand-new box, McGee.
Only prints... mine and yours.
- You said you were going gluten-free.
- Where is it, McGee?
I was saving you from yourself, Abby.
Where did you "save it", McGee?
Okay, I ate it.
Look, it was late.
I hadn't eaten since lunch.
The machine in the break room
was empty,
and it looked so good.
What were you thinking, McGee?
She's a world-class forensic scientist.
- Thank you, Tony.
- I bought the cupcake for Abby.
So...
how was it?
It was life-changing.
- Book him, Danno.
- Break it up, we've got work to do.
Gibbs, we have a confession.
The blood on the carpet
was Carrie McClellan's.
She was killed at
Erickson's apartment.
More of her blood was in the back of
his truck. That's how he moved the body
to the park.
Pull Erickson's phone company records
for his PDA.
Find out if his device was used
during these dates and times.
Got you, boss.
- Your two hours are up.
- Jethro.
Appreciate you showing up.
It's good to have the support of
an old friend.
I'm not here to support you.
Let's...
I'm here to arrest you, Pat.
It's a joke?
I don't think so.
Cole Erickson's confession
didn't pan out.
He wasn't the anonymous caller.
At the time you got the second tip
from the burn phone,
Erickson... he was 50 miles away
talking to his mother on his PDA.
You placed those calls, Pat.
When you were coming to meet me
at the Tidal Basin.
- Jethro, I...
- No, you traded on our friendship.
You did know
that the investigation
of Commander McClellan's murder
would lead to you.
So you came to me,
and you volunteered the information.
I should have known
I'd never get it by you.
- I shot Carrie.
- No, you didn't.
You said that I'd always know
when you were lying.
Well, you're lying right now.
- No. Why would I...?
- Don't say any more, Patrick.
Your mistake, Lynn, coming to me,
saying to me that Pat
would never shoot anybody in the back.
That detail was never released.
You never should have gone to him.
What the hell happened to you two?
I didn't go to Cole's apartment
to kill her.
I took my father's gun
to scare her off.
She got defensive
and said terrible things.
I lost it.
I don't even remember
pulling the trigger.
I got there right after it happened.
I wasn't going to let Lynn
go to prison for something
that was ultimately my fault.
So when Cole got home,
I persuaded him
- to help me dispose of the body.
- Jethro...
- it was an accident.
- Maybe...
but the murder of Cole Erickson
was cold and was premeditated.
Framed him.
Made it look like suicide
to save yourselves.
You murdered him.
- Do we need to leave with handcuffs?
- You are all out of favors, Pat.
Earlier today, NCIS agents arrested
Senator Patrick Kiley and his wife,
Lynn Tripp Kiley, for the murders of
Lieutenant Commander Carrie McClellan
and Cole Erickson,
the senator's chief of staff.
Welcome to Washington.
Would have appreciated a heads-up
before the arrest.
You covered good.
Trust.
Loyalty.
They're important.
Guess you know all about that
after today.
How do you think we're gonna do
in that department?
www.Team-NCIS.com