-good morning ?
-?
ur one and only source
into the scandalous lives
of manhattan's elite.
top story on my home page--
serena van der woodsen,
everybody's favorite "it" girl,
has just returned
from a mysterious absence.
you'll never believe
what's on "gossip girl."
someone saw serena getting off
-everyone knows serena
and everyone is talking.
(eleanor)
blair, it's serena.
serena?
and b.'s boyfriend nate--
rumor has it--
he's always had a thing
for serena.
but you're back now.
i didn't come back for you.
look, blair's my best friend,
and you're her boyfriend,
and she loves you.
why did she leave?
why did she return?
must be a lot of rumors
why you're back.
yeah, but none of them
mention you.
he tries to take his own life,
and you're worried
it's gonna cost you, mom?
you have no idea
what it's been like.
the best friend
and the boyfriend--
that's pretty classy, s.
and nate's friend chuck
won't let serena
forget about her past.
i'm trying to change.
i liked you better before.
and then there's dan,
the outsider.
looks like his childhood crush
has returned.
she doesn't know me.
nobody knows me. it's cool.
no. no, no, no, no, no.
uh, serena, um,
do you know this young man?
oh, from last night.
you remember me?
you'd really go out
with some guy you don't know?
well, he can't be worse
than the guys i do know.
guess whose dad is cool.
it's a trick question.
(dan) yeah,
'cause it can't be ours.
"top ten forgotten bands
of the '90s."
yeah, check out
he's very proud.
hey! hey,
way to be forgotten.
(lily) why is my daughter
going to one of your concerts?
well, our kids were bound
to meet. it's a small island.
are you sure it's not some ploy,
-using my daughter to get to me
now that your wife left you?
serena and her mystery man
made a surprise appearance
at blair's
kiss on the lips party.
(both) serena's here?
what is she doing here?
she wasn't invited.
but serena wasn't the only one
who made an impression...
who's the newbie?
jenny made an impression
on chuck.
let's go and talk
somewhere quieter.
get off! stop!
hey! that is my little sister!
don't you
ever touch her again!
hey, your life is over, slut!
she better
not show her face again.
i'm actually hoping
she will.
you think i got a shot
at a second date?
we'll talk about it
and now that s. is back,
will the upper east side
ever be the same?
we're all just dying
to see what happens next.
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
æ¬ãû gossip.gir µúò»¼¾µú¶þ¼¯
-=ææàãðü×öä»×é=-
·­òë: ð£¶ô:
ê±¼äöá:ð¡d
i bet you're wondering
what gossip girl
is doing up so early.
truth is, i never went to bed.
why waste precious time
dreaming
when waking life
is so much better?
(gia farrell)
* i did cause a commotion
* i can't help
but make a scene *
* ooh
* i ain't looking
is there really anything better
than a lazy sunday?
reading the paper in bed,
sipping coffee,
scrambling an egg or two.
yeah, right.
we upper east siders
don't do lazy.
breakfast is brunch,
and it comes with champagne,
a dress code and a hundred
of our closest friends...
and enemies.
* say, hey,
is it gonna be tonight? *
* come hit me up,
come hit me up *
chuck's dad, bart bass,
is hosting the annual brunch
for his foundation.
everyone is invited.
well, not everyone.
* held me right
oh. hey, you're up.
and you're
checking up on me.
i'm okay.
really, i'm okay.
you know, i was okay
when you asked me at the party
and in the cab,
when we got home,
before and after
i brushed my teeth.
look, i just feel
really stupid.
i mean, how could
i have actually thought
that chuck bass
just wanted to talk to me?
because you trust people,
which is normally
a good thing.
yeah, except
when it involves chuck.
yeah, pretty much.
so the real question is,
uh, how are you?
me?
why wouldn't i be okay?
you know, at the end
of the night, with serena
and the--the--the...
was it really that bad?
this is me.
so... good night.
yeah. (chuckles)
yeah.
um, yeah, good night.
(scoffs) go! walk her
to the door. something. go!
okay.
oh! oh, god.
that hurt a lot.
whoa, whoa, stop, stop.
oh, i think
i have brain damage.
you know what, dan?
you wouldn't even know
if you had brain damage.
no, let's go, please.
(jenny) no!
h-hi.
so he waved?
£¿
no, he was just trying
to be funny.
maybe he's shy.
or he hates me.
no guy in the history
of the world has ever hated you.
she probably thinks
i hate her now.
i've waited my entire adolescent
life for a date with this girl,
you know,
serena van ddsen...
and i decide to close
the evening with a wave.
it was a nice wave.
at the end of a date?
come on, there's no such thing.
and you only get one shot
with a girl like serena.
i got mine, and i blew it.
which means
you have nothing to lose.
(sighs) no, nothing except
my last shred of dignity.
oh, no. i think that's gone.
you're right.
you know what? i'm just--
i'm gonna go talk to her.
i'm gonna apologize
for the wave.
i'm gonna tell her
how much i like her,
and i'm gonna ask
for a second shot.
no, i'm gonna get
a second shot.
yeah, you are.
yeah.
wait, wait, wait.
i love the plan,
but, uh, you need
a better outfit.
and maybe a shower.
whatever.
it's probably for the best.
the last thing i need
in my life is a new guy.
he was just so smart,
th
and--and funny...
it sounds like
you like him.
and really nice.
god, blair was
so mean to me last night.
i don't even know why.
whatever.
i'm sure if we talk about it,
we can work it out.
hey, maybe i should
go over there.
(blair) serena had better
just stay away.
thank you, dorota.
(isabel) yeah, thanks.
we love sleeping at blair's.
i don't want
to see serena at school,
and she better not show
at brunch today.
you're really mad at serena.
yeah, i hope you never
get that mad at us.
well, you would never do
no, never.
of course not.
i wonder if nate
remembered brunch.
it would be so wrong
for me to show up
without my boyfriend
whom i love, and who loves me.
(cell phone beeps)
mm.
hello?
hi, sweetie.
did i wake you?
no, i'm up.
well,
get some strong coffee
and jump in the shower,
sleepyhead.
chuck's dad's brunch
for his foundation
is today at the palace.
oh, right. of course.
nathaniel, keep it down.
some of us are trying
to regain our strength.
your dad's brunch is today.
alarm's set for 9:00.
it's 10:00.
ladies, double-time.
hmm?
oh, unless... nathaniel...
i'm good.
actually, could you two
bring some coffee
when you get a chance?
and some water... lots of water.
you want ice with that?
looks like
you could use some.
that's enough, ladies.
and i'll be sure
to tell my father
just how committed you are
to the hospitality industry.
that kid popped
you pretty good, huh?
never mess
with a guy's sister.
and if i knew his name,
why, 'cause you
kill people now?
you gonna strangle him
with your scarf?
don't mock the scarf, nathaniel.
it's my signature.
i'm just saying,
death by scarf--
not that intimidating.
he sucker punched me.
i told you.
besides,
better a broken nose
than a broken heart.
what? i didn't even talk
to serena last night.
who said anything
about serena?
do i look okay?
definitely
second-shot material.
all right,
then i'm gonna go.
oh, um,
and about what happened,
you know, with, uh, chuck?
if you wanna,
like, talk to someone...
n-not your brother--
just let me know.
okay.
yeah, i'll...
all right.
hey, uh, wait.
actually, there is someone
i wanna talk to.
hey, hey,
where you guys going?
i was gonna make waffles.
ooh. sorry, dad.
yeah, can't.
but i wanna hear
about your date.
(dan) later.
and your party.
when we get back.
you guys missed
a really great show,
and i make
really good waffles.
(rihanna) * my engine's ready
to explode, explode, explode *
(man) palace hotel lobby.
hi. this is,
uh, nate archibald
calling from the bass suite.
i know you don't normally
give out this information,
but can you tell me what room
the van der woodsens
are in, please?
hey, blair. it's me.
uh, i guess
you're still sleeping,
but i'm gonna come over.
i think we need to talk.
okay. uh, see you soon. bye.
* so if you feel me,
let me know, know, know *
* come on now
it looks like
the table's all set.
as soon as the guests arrive,
we can start dishing.
here's what's on the menu...
* watch me go, go, go, go
* get you where you wanna go,
if you know what i mean *
* baby, you got the keys
(tires screech, loud crash)
?  my michel perrys?
(groans)
i can't find anything in here!
well, it might help
if you unpacked.
look, you're home now.
it's your life.
you should start living it.
this is not life,
this is a hotel--
which we're living in because
you decided you didn't like
the color of the walls
in our real home.
mom, i said
i'd go to this brunch.
what more do you want from me?
sweetie, why are you
being like this?
you love parties.
this is just not like you.
maybe it is like me. maybe you
don't know what i'm really like.
oh, okay, tell me.
so did you and dan have fun
at the concert last night?
we, um, never made it.
we actually ended up
at the kiss on the lips party.
ah. well,
that must have pleased blair.
blair? actually,
no, not that pleased,
which is why i'm going
to talk to her.
well just be back
in time for brunch, okay?
mom.
look, honey, i know how hard
it is for you to be back,
but the more
you hide yourself away,
the more people are gonna think
you have something to hide.
coming from someone
who's keeping my brother
in an institution.
that's different.
i mean it. don't be late.
hey. how you doing?
uh, i-i was in yesterday
with serena.
how could i forget?
yeah, well, um,
is she in?
just missed her, actually,
but you're welcome to wait.
okay, maybe i will.
she--she probably
won't be that long, right?
once she went out and didn't
come back for six months,
but feel free to sit.
over there.
over there
is where i'll be.
hi, nate.
it's great to see you.
hi, mrs. van der woodsen.
good to see you.
oh, i'm just heading out.
oh, is serena in?
oh, you just missed her,
but i'll tell her you came by.
i'm sure she'll
be happy to hear it.
uh, i don't know aut that.
oh, what?
come on, serena loves you.
i mean, i think she's always
had a little crush on you.
of course, you and blair
are the perfect couple.
mm. is serena gonna be long?
i could just wait.oh, well,
dexter here can take care of you.
i'm just gonna step out
for a while.
nate's gonna wait
for serena.
great. he can get in line
behind that guy.
i had a feeling
you'd be back.
dan, is it?
humphrey. yes.
it's nice to see you again,
mrs. van der woodsen.
i hope you've had
a pleasant, uh...
uh, 21 hours
since i last saw you.
yes, it has
been very pleasant...
until now.
gentlemen.
hey.
blair?
serena.
hey, i got two bone-dry caps
and audrey.
(laughs) i must
have totally blanked
on the part
where i invited you over.
i-i called you.
blair, it's sunday morning.
coffee, croissants,
"breakfast at tiffany's."
it's our tradition.
i have new traditions now.
well, they're not traditions
if they're new.
look, blair, i'm really trying
to make an effort here.
i thought everything
was good between us.
it was...
before i found out
you had sex with my boyfriend.
how'd you find out?
nate told me.
at least he felt he owed it
to me to tell the truth.
i don't know what to say.
don't bother saying anything.
i wouldn't believe you anyway.
blair, it was...
you know...
i always knew
you were a whore.
i never took you
for a liar, too.
blair, how can i fix this?
you don't, serena.
you just stay away
from me,
my boyfriend
and my friends.
you're done here.
serena's visit was short
and apparently not very sweet.
but you know what is?
revenge.
we hear it's best served cold.
who's hungry?
dorota, i told you
i didn't want to see anyone.
hi, jenny.
hi.
what do you want?
uh...
i realized that i still have
your calligraphy pens
from the party invitations,
and thought you might
need them for something.
that is the lamest excuse
i've ever heard.
you wanna know what chuck bass
is saying about you.
no.
is he... saying things?
is anyone?
mm... no.
not yet, anyway.
chuck likes to brag about
his conquests, not his victims.
come on. you can help me
get ready for brunch.
okay. sure.
nice flowers.
they're hydrangeas.
just coffee.
i'm not staying long.
i'd like to get out of here
before someone throws me down
and tattoos me.
this is brooklyn, lil,
not the warped tour.
and don't tell me you had
all your tattoos removed.
i mean, even that one,
that little heart-shaped one
between your, uh...
uh, don't try to be cute, okay?
those days are well behind you.
and here i thought i was getting
better-looking every day.
so what's the big emergency?
dan went out
with serena last night.
and us humphreys sure
are proud of him.well, currently,
he's sitting in the lobby
of the hotel
where we're living.
(woman) hi. can i help you?
two americanos...
one with an extra shot?
mm-hmm.
you don't actually think
i'm gonna tell my kid
who he can and can't date.
i mean, is that really
the reason you came down here?
oh, well, i know what you're implying.
admit it. you're falling for me again.
you're right, you're right.
it's the low-income tax bracket,
the bad v-neck t-shirts,
the awful jokes.
i don't know
why your wife lied  you.
well, she's got better
taste than you.
here you are. thanks.
i mean, come on.
why else have i seen you
more in the last 2 days
than in the last 15 years?
an unfortunate twist of fate.
but fate nonetheless.
unless you, uh...
are you seeing someone?
no, not really.
uh-huh, not serious...
or he's married.
that is your type.
that's enough, rufus.
what's his name?
i've read about him
in "forbes" or "rolling stone"?
well, whoever he is, i'm sure
he can't keep up with you.
well, i'm gonna take that
as a compliment,
but i'm serious.
i'm worried about serena.
i don't need some new boy
influencing her,
distracting her
from her needs.
well, no offense, lil,
but i'm guessing a kid like dan
is exactly what serena needs.
so, uh...
what do you need
to talk to serena about?
nothing,
just in the neighborhood.
you?
i...
am nowhere near
the neighborhood,
but i'm working
on a better excuse.
you guys, like...
oh, uh...
i... i don't know.
yeah, well,
that's serena.
with her,
you'll never know.
nathaniel.
there you are.
what are you doing?
nothing, waiting for you.
him?
hey, what are you doing here?
why, what is this--
uh, your hotel?
actually, it is.
yeah, so unless you have
a reason to be here,
i'll have to ask you
to wait on the curb
with the rest of the trash.
trash? look, man,
i live in brooklyn, all right?
not the ozarks...
no offense to the ozarks.
but don't you think we're
taking this class warfare thing
a little too far?
i haven't even started, man.
okay, man, let's just go.
don't tell me you're sticking up
for serena's new bitch.
if anyone's got a reason
to kick his ass, it's you.
he's not worth it.
not here.
this isn't over.
hey, anytime, man.
that one black eye
looks a little lonely.
(nate) come on, chill out.
wow. blair, it's...
it's beautiful.
i mean, you look...
beautiful.
it's average.
the color is last season,
and besides,
stella mccartney has
a much better version
at bergdorf's.
right. i... i've been meaning
to go by bergdorf's.
wow,
these dolls are great.
oh, my god.
you have a cabbage patch.
my brother used to have one
of these. his name was cedric.
your brother's name is cedric?
uh, no that was
his cabbage patch kid.
my brother's name is dan.
actually, you might know him.
he, um, he went out
with serena last night.
that's your brother?
so does that mean
you're friends with serena now?
i mean, i don't have
a problem with her,
but if someone did have
i wouldn't have a problem
with that either.
you know...
if you like that dress,
you can have it.
what? no, no.
i'm sure you'll
find some way to repay me.
oh, blair, thank you.
i mean,
for the dress and...
for the other thing
about, uh, about chuck.
if you want to be
part of this world, jenny,
people will talk...
eventually,
and you need to decide
if all this is worth it.
dan. (laughs) hey.
i-i-i was
in the neighborhood...
uh, give or take 70 blocks.
um, i just wanted
to tell you in person
that, uh,
the end of last night
may have not been
my finest hour.
there was a, uh, a wave.
i-i-i saw that, yeah.
yeah, yeah, and since then,
i've just
been wondering, uh...
are you hungry?
yes.
actually, i've had
g.worsmornin
well, you--you wanna--
you wanna talk?
and eat? not necessarily
in that order.
yes, i would love to do both,
but food first,because i'm starving.
great.just in time for brunch.
mom.
ms. van der woodsen.
dan... still here.
look, mom,
i really don't think
it's a good idea
for me to go to that brunch.
you promised.
yeah, but that was bef--
before i knew dan
was hungry, too.
i can't let the boy starve.
it would be inhumane.
he's not invited.
yeah, that's why
i'm going with him.
because i can't go
with her.
and we have plans
to go to brunch togeth today
we had those plans.
serena, you're home,
living under my roof,
my rules.
what is it gonna take
to get you dressed
and through that door?
uh, you know what? may--
maybe this was a-a bad idea.
(laughs)
you've got to be kidding.
yeah, this was--this was
definitely a bad idea.
this should be fun.
looks like chuck and blair
showed up
with quite an appetite...
for destruction, that is.
hey, dad,
how's the new song going?
oh, i think
i need more coffee.
whatever works.
where'd you get the dress?
oh, it was a thank you-gift
from blair
for doing
the party invitations.
oh, and it looks like a very expensive thanks gift
dad, she has a closet
the size of this apartment
just full of them.
see, her mom designed it.
and her mom
but the dress you made
for yourself is much nicer.
which is why ?
uh, one of a couple
of reasons.
hey, you think
the farmers market's still open?
yeah. why, you wanna go?
yeah.
i thought you were getting too
old to go places with your dad.
well, you used to be cool,
and the '90s
are having a comeback.
you have no idea
how much that hurts.
well, i can't say much
for his child-rearing skills,
but bart bass
knows brunch.
* well, who the hell am i to
tell her how to live her life? *
* and if you could put dumb
in a shot glass *
* i'm just another lush
who's had one too many in me *
um, i, uh, i-i need to use
the ladies room.
uh, you think you'll be okay
by yourself for a while?
yeah. come on.
me and, uh, some beluga caviar?
can't get enough
of the stuff.
okay.
great.
hey, how's it going?
* and she's made me fiend
no, you're--you're okay.
yeah, just, uh, go ahead
and do your thing.
* oh, no
* hey
* she's at the bottom
of that bottle *
* yeah
* she's only one more swallow
* hey
* from being oh, so hollow
charles.
would you excuse me?
father.
the, uh,
the invitation said
"black tie,"
not "black eye."
are you okay?
i mean, if you're
in some kind of trouble...
only of my own making.
why do you think
i do all this, huh?
this party is for you,
okay?
so you can meet people,
you know,
become a part of something,
make some kind of change.
really?
i thought it was
another excuse for an open bar
and, uh, rehiring
of the nearly nude statues.
* 'cause baby girl's a queen
do me a favor, will you?
lose the scotch.
it's barely noon.
* she's at the bottom
of that bottle *
* hey
* she's only one more swallow
serena, i really need
to talk to you.
actually, i need to talk to you,
which means you can listen.
nate, you told blair.
what were you thinking?
look, i want to explain.
excuse me.
sorry.
we can't talk here.
what,
where blair might see us?
meet me in chuck's suite.
i'm not sneaking around
with you.
please. just to talk.
ten minutes.
i'll meet you up there.
(elevator bell dings)
you look beautiful,
as always.
where's your lovely mother
today?
paris. must be some drama
at the atelier.
oh, nothing too dramatic,
i hope.
her line is doing very well.
i was just telling my firm what
a great investment she'd make.
she's really going places.
hopefully places
far, far away. (laughs)
just kidding.
hey. let me get you a refill.
i'll be right back.
i'll go with you.
excuse us.
* oh, no
blair seems happy.
it looks like, uh,
you're taking care
of business, as discussed.
dad, not everything in life's
a business deal.
come talk to me
in thirty years.
i want to introduce you
to timothy good.
hi.
his firm has got some really
interesting summer internships.
nice to meet you.
* she's only one more swallow
* hey
* from being oh, so hollow
* hey, hey
i can't believe serena
came to this brunch.
i told her to stay away.
you worried about nate?
* and bow out gracefully
just a shot in the dark.
i think you know what you need
to do to get his attention.
and what's that?
the key to my suite,
nate's heart
and your future happiness.
* and bow out gracefully
i'm honored to be playing
even a small role
in your deflowering.
you're disgusting.
yes, i am, so why be shy?
just grab nate
and finish this.
report back with details.
* oh, no
* hey
* she's at the bottom
nice to meet you. dad.
(the captain)
hey, can i get you a drink?
what are you doing
right now?
uh, well, i was just gonna--
how about me?
um...
(chuckles) what, you have
a better offer or...
no, of course not.
yeah?
uh, now?
now. now. (laughs)
* swallow
* hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
mmm.
where are we going?
i got us the best room
in the whole place.
wait,
this is chuck's suite.
nate.
serena?
blair.
spotted--n. and b.
hot and heavy in the halls
of the palace hotel,
only to find s.
already waiting.
sparks were flying for sure,
but will it be a 3-way
or d-day?
what is she doing here?
i was meeting nate.
just to talk, i swear.
you said you'd never
speak to her again.
you said that?
why would you say that?
because you can't be trusted.
it's not serena's fault.
do not defend her.
i asked her to come.
oh. oh, so you do want
to talk to her.
yes, to explain
why i'm not talking to her.
maybe i'll leave you two
to finish that fascinating
conversation.
oh, no, no. i'll go. let you
guys get back to your quickie.
it wasn't a quickie.
sex is actually kind of
a big deal to some of us.
oh, yeah, i can see that.
chuck's bed? very romantic.
classy, too.
oh, like you?
i'll bet your new friend dan
would love to hear
all about how classy you are.
dan? what...
what, you really think
she would tell him?
it's blair.
i can't believe you told her.
you just expected me
to keep it a secret?
yes, nate. there's nothing wrong
with keeping a secret
if the truth
is gonna hurt someone.
that's a hell of a way
oh, i'm sorry. i didn't
realize all of a sudden
you're the most honest guy
on the planet.
well, it just seems to me
that you're the one
that doesn't want to be seen
together in public.
no, i do want
i just don't want to see you
with anyone else.
tell your harem
of shopgirls and models
that you're seeing someone.
i am, but those conversations
take a little time.
well, they've got nothing
but time, bart. they're 25.
excuse me.
dan, wait
look, i really don't appreciate
your lurking in the shadows,
eavesdropping
on my private conversation.
what? no. no, no, i wasn't.
i was looking for serena.
well, i don't see her.
do you?
no, which is why ?
i don't know
what you're doing here
or what you think
you heard...
nothing. i heard nothing.
but serena doesn't know.
and neither do i, okay?
so now if you'll excuse me,
i'm gonna go back inside,
not tell anyone a thing
and mind my own business.
* so if you feel me,
let me know,w, kw *
* come on now, what you
waiting for, for, for? *
* my engine's ready
to explode, explode, explode *
* so start me up
and watch me go, go, go *
dan.
hi. i'm blair waldorf,
serena's friend.
oh, hey. yeah, uh, do you
happen to know where she is?
as a matter of fact, i do.
(serena) blair.
serena, there you are.
uh, where were you?
she was waiting in a hotel room
to talk.
about why
we weren't talking.
that doesn't sound
any smarter the second time.
why weren't you talking?
does this have
anything to do with
why you were waiting
for serena this morning?
(blair) you were what?
(chuck) and here i thought
you were waiting for me.
oh, exactly what ?
now what is going on here?
we were just getting into that.
blair, please, don't do this.
sorry. oh,
do you wanna tell him?
i'll tell him.
(nate and blair) you know?
i know everything.
and apparently,
i know nothing.
look, dan, it--it was a long
time ago, and i regret it.
(chuck) look, serena,
stop trying to pretend
you're a good girl.
so you slept with
your best friend's boyfriend.
i kind of admire you
for it.
is that true?
well, then she ran away
and lied about it.
i just thought you should know
before you fall head over heels
for your perfect girl
and her perfect world,
and then get left all alone
with no one
but your cabbage patch kid.
cabbage patch?
did you talk to my sister?
ah, yes, little jenny.
i do believe she and i
have some unfinished business.
you stay away from her.
poor daniel. so little time,
so many sluts to defend.
it's fine. it's fine.
everyone can stop looking.
he's a jerk...
but it's my fault,
and--and i'm leaving.
i--i'll go with you.
actually,
i'd prefer if you didn't.
hope you're happy.
not even close.
looks like
it's just you and me.
apparently,
my room is available.
* shut up and drive,
drive, drive *
some might call this
a "fustercluck,"
but on the upper east side,
we call it sunday afternoon.
dan, wait. i'm so sorry.
there's no--
there's no need to be.
really, i shouldn't have come
here today. i made a mistake.
no, you didn't. look, i'm sorry
about blair and chuck--
it's not about
blair or chuck.
i mean, it is,
but it's--it's not just them.
no, i know. trust me, i know.
this world--it--it's crazy.
yeah, it--it is...
(sighs)
and you're a part of it.
what, and you didn't
know that?
i don't know.
i-i thought you were different.
well, i'm sorry
i'm not who you thought i was,
but what's happened
is in the past,
you know, and all i can do
is try to change.
but if you
can't accept that,
then, you know, you're
not who i thought you were.
well, i guess
we both made mistakes.
(jenny) hi.
hey, jen said
you went looking for serena.
did you find her?
mm. yeah, yeah, i found her,
and, uh, and then i lost her.
oh, uh, that's, uh...
it's fine. it's fine.
really, it's all for the best.
serena and her friends
and her family...
her whole world...
turns out it wasn't for me.
wait, dan. what happened?
did you tell blair waldorf
about cedric?
i...
it may have come up.
you can't trust
these people, jen.
don't tell 'em anything.
they're nice flowers.
they're hydrangeas.
look, blair,
either you try
to forgive me and move on...
or we end it.
* the faces all around me
* they don't smile,
they just crack *
* waiting for our ship to come
* but our ship's
not coming back *
well, serena's mystery man
is a mystery no longer.
his name is... oh, who cares?
now that he and s. are over,
so are his 15 minutes.
but his sister jenny
was spotted with a new dress...
gifted from blair herself.
everyone knows
an eleanor original
is the uniform
of b.'s private army.
but will j. be a loyal soldier
or will she side
with s.'s rebel forces?
and as for s. herself,
we hear that she left
today's brunch with nofriends,
no boy
and nowhere left to run.
* so give me something
to believe *
* 'cause i am living
just to breathe *
* and i need something more
* to keep on breathing for
* so give me something
to believe *
it looks like
the ultimate insider
has become a total outsider.
it's your move, serena,
and you know
who will be watching--
gossip girl.
ææàãðü×öä»×é
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë