Gossip girl here...
your one and only source into the
scandalous lives of manhattan's elite.
Blair, ever since you walked
into the gallery last week,
i haven't been able to
stop thinking about you.
Is it too weird to think that maybe
fate brought us back together again?
I was up all night finishing
the story for noah shapiro.
- The guy from "the paris review"? Which story?
- The one about chuck bass.
- You said you couldn't write that story.
- No, i could always write it. I chose not to.
You should do your own clothing line.
I can model them. Max
will do some photos.
If you think you're getting away
with this, you are dead wrong.
It's too late. It's done.
Gossip Girl 210
Synchro : Flolo
French Gossip girl Team
x.o.x.o., gossip girl.
You're in for a real treat, son.
I even amazed myself
with this bolognese.
I'm amazed at how calm you're acting.
Your 15-year-old daughter's moved in
granted, agnes' mother's more
courtney love than june cleaver, but
she's a committed parent,
and she's gone through
similar phases with agnes.
She promises to call
every day, so jenny's safe.
You're gonna act like
you're cool with it
so she chooses to come home
instead of being forced.
That's risky, but i like it.
- i hope it works.
- yeah.
- so you ready for the best sauce ever?
- you know, actually,
i can't stay. I'm gonna meet
shapiro, and i know you don't agree
with me writing a story
about chuck and his mother...
i don't believe in using other
people to get what you want.
Shapiro loved the story.
He's writing me the
recommendation for yale.
Congratulations. I'm happy for ya.
I'm happy for you and your sister both.
I'm glad you're a musician
and not an actor, dad, 'cause
our family would have starved.
Save me some cold pasta?
- i'll leave it on the stove for you.
- all right.
Though it seems like just yesterday
serena and i were 8 and playing
dress-up in my mother's vintage manolos,
my 18th birthday has finally arrived.
The party needs to be perfect,
so blood orange martinis
or beluga and belvedere? Why don't we make
different drinks tonight and do a taste test?
I can't. I'm meeting my
mother's new boyfriend.
Even moms have boyfriends, and i don't.
Cyrus has been one of my mom's
attorneys since the divorce.
He asked her out when they first met but
she didn't wanna mix business with pleasure.
Finally, his amorous
overtures wore her down,
and she agreed to dinner.
She's been smitten ever since.
Oh, that's so romantic.
One thing my mom has
is good taste in men.
Maybe a dashing stepdad
is just what i need.
Speaking of good taste in men,
how's the sexy artist, serena?
Aaron's amazing.
He's been sending me these maps
to the most beautiful places.
The other day i ended up in a
private room in the cloisters
- overlooking the gardens.
- spare them the details.
Hazel will kill herself from envy.
This is him again. I gotta go.
- what? What about my party?
- blood orange martinis all the way.
You girls have been
getting a lot of press.
- you got talent. Who's the designer?
- it's me.
And i'm the face of the line and
the brains behind the operation.
- who do you imagine your client will be?
- girls like us.
Sophisticated girls with a
bit of edge who can afford
high-end product, and i know these girls
and their style because i'm their peer,
so that's what makes
me unique as a designer.
What's the name of the label?
We haven't fully decided yet,
clearly, but, it really doesn't matter,
'cause we're just here to take
the work to the next level.
Definitely, which means finding
a clear vision for the brand.
Which since fashion is a
designer-based industry,
and i'm a designer,
that brand would be me.
No, the brand is the concept,
which we both came up with.
Can we just talk about this
later when we're alone, please?
No, we're gonna talk about this now.
If mr. Smith here wants to represent us,
- then he should know who he's dealing with.
- except mr. Smith
might get the wrong idea
about our professionalism.
Then cut the crap and start acting professional
instead of putting on the jenny show.
Me? Agnes, look at who's
acting out yet again
- in another business meeting.
- you wanna see acting out?
And yet another one
bites the dust, agnes.
What is the matter with you?
This guy was our last chance.
Okay, he totally overreacted.
I mean, we're artists.
We need to work with somebody
who's not gonna be freaked out
- by a little bit of passion.
- passion? You know the heat
from the fashion show's
not gonna last that long.
I will find us another
business manager tomorrow.
Good, because until we get one,
we can't meet with any buyers.
Yes. Okay? Now it's all gonna
work out, all right? And i'm on it.
- dorota.
- dorota!
Hurry up. Cyrus will be here any minute.
He is the most attractive,
brilliant man i have ever met.
- darling, you're gonna love him.
- i kind of already do.
I'm so excited to meet him.
I told you to put the roses on
the table next to cyrus' seat.
Cary grant always looked
his best with white roses.
Dorota, are you insane?
- i don't know.
- you used the everyday china.
Cyrus will think we're just
common upper middle class.
- go get the objet, and hurry up.
- yes, miss blair.
Eleanor, you look like a goddess.
- that must be his driver.
- and you're more handsome than ever.
Not enough!
Darling, come meet cyrus rose.
The lovely blair. Come here!
Not enough!
Happy 20th anniversary
for bass industries.
- surprised you remembered.
- not only did i remember i got you something.
You once told me that you snuck
into hockey games as a
kid, sat in the back row.
You bought a box for the season?
I thought you could revisit
your childhood passion in style.
We can go to rangers
games together, hang out.
Nice gesture, but, misguided as usual.
I don't have time for
hockey games. You know that.
I always knew you had chops, humphrey.
- here's your letter. Have a seat.
- thank you, sir. Thank you so much.
Don't thank me yet.
There's more to come.
Meet james wolf, senior
editor at "new york magazine."
It's nice to meet you.
Shapiro took
the liberty of showing me your piece.
I'm very interested.
I'm, i'm flattered. "New york magazine"
doesn't normally publish fiction.
- it's not really fiction, though, is it?
- i told james the trout character
is based on chuck bass,
son of bartholomew.
It's the 20th anniversary
of bass industries.
We want an exposé on the
man behind the company.
You dated the stepdaughter.
You know the son.
Yeah, look, the last thing i
need is bart bass as an enemy.
Yeah, and i'm really
not the undercover type.
If you're afraid of the man's wrath,
we won't print your name,
but if your reporting's
as good as your fiction,
i'll assign you another piece.
Look, i'm sorry, sir,
but he's not an idiot.
He's gonna know it came from me.
We'll only print something if
it's true and can be verified.
If the man's clean, the story goes away.
If he's not, that's on him, isn't it?
You just grew a pair,
humphrey. Don't lose them now.
This opportunity could
open real doors for you.
What? How did you do that? I
mean, it's amazing, but why?
You know, i've shown you the
most beautiful places i know,
and now i'm showing the
beautiful places you.
This is nothing, though.
I want you to pose for me.
- will you?
- sure, i guess.
Yes! Yes.
I can't believe this.
Spotted... s. And a. Bringing
sexy back to times square.
Move over, disney. 42nd
street is steaming up.
I called you, like,
ten times last night.
Where have you been? I went
to the dentist at lunch and
,yesterday i met aaron in times square.
- it was the most romantic thing.
- who cares about plaque or
pretentious artists when your
best friend's having a meltdown?
- he's totally unsuitable.
- who is?
Cyrus. He's 5 feet tall.
He has a catchphrase, and he's a hugger.
I was expecting cary grant,
and i got danny devito.
That sounds...
awful. Sorry. I gotta run. Oh, aaron?
Yeah. He asked me to pose for
him in his studio, to be his muse.
- and you said yes?
- why not? It's romantic.
No, it's a death trap. Being
the muse never works out.
Plenty of women have been both lover
and muse to famous artists, like picasso.
Serena, a guy starts
out in his blue period,
and everything's great, but it's only a
matter of time before he's all into cubism,
and it's some other girl's eye coming
out of her forehead.
I'm gonna go.
Wait! No, what about the
gnome? I have to take him down.
B., enough already. You
always said you wanted to be
an elegant woman at 18 like grace kelly.
You're right.
I'm going to be an adult.
I'll try and tolerate him.
Good girl.
This has been great.
Mr. Bass, thank you for
answering my questions.
- anything for a friend of serena's.
- as i mentioned, i'm just...
i'm kinda over the writing thing, and
i wanna see what else is out there.
You're easily the most
successful person i know,
so i figured why not at the top, right?
Yeah, i was hoping that i might
be able to shadow you for just
a few days a week after school.
I'm a busy man, daniel.
I don't think that's gonna be possible.
Yeah, of course. I don't want to impose.
It's just... you know...
my dad... his
world is pretty narrow.
He may have had a hit song in the '90s but
he didn't build half the manhattan skyline.
Your father's a fine man, but,
i can see how you'd want something more.
Why don't we start with two days a week?
That's, that's more
than enough. Thank you.
Agnes, it's 3:00. I have
been waiting up for you
at the apartment since
8:00 this morning.
Will you lower your voice?
Your high-pitched shrill is
not helping my pounding head.
Excuse me? Waitress, can
i get, a revive? Thank you.
Where the hell were you? I
went out with max last night,
and then we ran into some friends,
and it was really good.
You should have come.
Then you should have answered
your phone or at least turned it on
so that you could hear
the 50 messages i left you.
What are you, my mother?
No, agnes, i am your
partner! And you promised
that you'd find us a new
business manager today.
And i will do it on monday or
today, if my hangover ever wears off.
Do you understand how much
i've given up for this?
- yes.
- no, agnes, you don't.
I left home.
I quit my job,
- and my dad... he basically hates me.
- you need to chill.
Take a xanax or a
tequila shot or something.
Hi. This is jenny humphrey.
I'm calling for scott smith.
Yeah, i know. I met with him yesterday.
Well, again, thank you for your time.
It's been a pleasure, dan.
Listen, do you like hockey?
Sure, yeah. I was thinking maybe
i could give you a business primer
over a ranger game tuesday night.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry, sir. I told
him you were in a meeting.
I came by to have robert clear
your schedule for the game.
- apparently you already have a date.
- what are you doing here?
I'm newly interested in the
construction business. I thought...
i thought your dad
could show me the ropes.
I was just leaving. Thank you, mr. Bass.
$18 a flower? That's absurd.
Yeah, yeah, it, it is a bit steep.
Yeah. I'm an attorney,
and i'm telling you,
you're not paying for that peony.
You're paying for the
florist's madison avenue rent.
I am grace kelly. Grace kelly is me.
Blair, i would love
to fill this whole penthouse
with peonies for you
for your birthday, but would you
allow me to buy them someplace else?
I mean, it's the principle of the thing.
I prefer to get my own
peonies from my own florist,
but thank you so much.
Eleanor, over dinner,
you mentioned your
fondness for cyndi lauper.
Mom and i love cyndi lauper.
We used to re-enact "girls
just want to have fun."
Our first dvd was "vibes."
I got tickets to see
cyndi lauper at joe's pub
tomorrow night, and that
way, your mother and i
- will be out of your hair for the party.
- my mother's coming to my party.
- what? You never want me at your parties.
- this year is different.
I'm 18, and it's a grown-up party.
I e-mailed dorota a new guest list.
- parents are invited.
- we'll return the tickets.
No, nonsense, nonsense.
Blair and i will celebrate
her birthday on her
real birthday next week.
We are going to see cyndi lauper!
Thank you so much for
giving me another chance.
My, ex-partner had some issues,
so i've completely severed all
ties with her. I'm glad to hear it.
I'd be delighted to work
with you alone.
Really? That's amazing. I'm sure we can get
started on the incorporation right away.
- you are 18, aren't you?
- actually, no, i'm 15.
- that's not a problem, though, is it?
- no, not at all.
We just have to get the
papers signed by a parent,
but that's simple, and
then we're good to go.
Awesome. Yeah, no problem.
You can stand right here.
- thank you.
- you're welcome.
So... tell me, when you're ready.
I've been practicing my poses.
Okay, zoolander. Just give me a second.
So what is it that you want? You
want, like, a little bit of this?
Or, like, you know, some
of this? I don't know.
How about, how about a little less?
You know, try being
still. Try... nothing.
You can try that.
You can't hide your
face. That's no good.
I don't know what to do.
Can you say something?
Okay, okay. Put your head up here.
Put your feet up. Really enjoy yourself.
Okay. There you go. Look over here.
- that's too close. Get outta here.
- it's not too close.
I never thought i'd hear from you again.
Frankly, neither did i.
Are you still an intern
- at "new york magazine"?
- yeah. Why?
What do you know about
a guy named dan humphrey?
Nothing, except he's about to
walk into a meeting with my boss.
I have to go. I'll call you back.
Did brooklyn boy really think
he could bury the bone in the
backyard and no one would find it?
Every bass will have his day.
Now how many muses come over in
the morning bearing breakfast?
Oh, my gosh. You must have
stayed up all night making that.
Pretty much.
What do you think?
It's beautiful.
It's also kind of weird, maybe.
Not that it's weird,
but it makes me feel that way,
you know, seeing myself...
like this.
I should probably be more cool
and mysterious and stop talking.
I kinda like being your inspiration.
Good. Get used to it.
- am i early?
- no, actually, you're right on time.
Serena, this is danielle.
She models for me.
I thought modeling was our thing.
I'm doing a series.
I should go.
- no, you don't have to.
- yeah. No, i do.
I have this thing that i forgot about
- that i, i'm gonna do.
- oh, can i have this coffee?
Yes, yes. Have... have the coffee.
Noah, it's dan.
You know how i told you it might take a
while to get anything good on bass?
Turns out the story's not gonna take
as long to crack as we thought.
You have glow, miss eleanor,
like chinese lantern.
It's love, dorota.
How can you possibly love cyrus?
He does all the things you hate.
He uses the wrong fork.
He slurps his soup.
He wears sports socks.
He's short and pushy.
- he's nothing like daddy.
- which is precisely why i like him.
Harold was lovely in a million ways,
but he... he had his secrets.
Cyrus is someone i can trust.
Before i go see cyndi lauper,
i have to go pick up
my dress at barneys.
I have to get my hair done.
Would you like to come with?
No, thanks. But have fun.
- screw grace kelly. I need to scheme.
- oh, no.
That tiny man must have some
big secret i can exploit,
and with his trusting nature,
finding it out shouldn't be too hard.
You're humphrey?
I wasn't expecting a kid.
I'm sorry to disappoint,
but no one else is showing up.
So if you got information,
i'm right here.
All right, in '87, your friend bass
bought a building in
midtown to convert to condos.
The market crashed, and he couldn't
raise the funds to complete it.
So wouldn't you know?
That building burned down.
- are you saying it wasn't an accident?
- kinberg building.
Bass collects the insurance.
He goes on to build an empire.
It was just like in "all
the president's men."
Yeah, and i'm thinking there's
no way this could be legit,
but all of the facts check
out... the date, the building,
the fire, the insurance, even.
- and you're happy about this?
- it's huge.
An arsonist? This
article could change my life.
It could also change serena's life,
lily's life, their whole family's.
I know, all right? And
i feel badly about that, but
if this is true, then
people have the right to know.
Noah says all i need now is for
me to get a statement from bart.
By tricking him into telling you
information so you can exploit it.
Dad, i'm writing an important
story for a quality publication.
Why can't you just admit
this is a good thing for me?
Hello, alison.
Jenny asked you to sign what papers?
All right, thanks for having my
back on this. Talk to you later.
You and i are gonna talk more.
Now i have to go find jenny.
My mom is so happy. I've
never seen her like this.
Your mother is a diamond
in an ocean of coal.
From the moment we met,
i knew she was the one.
Have you always been so romantic?
Like, with your ex-wife?
Certainly not.
Actually, i've only felt like
this once before in my life.
Tell me about it.
You know, alice and i were
very young when we got married.
We were very fond of each
other but never passionate.
And then i got drafted.
I was sent to vietnam.
And i fell deeply in love with a
vietnamese girl named kim-ly.
It means "golden lion."
How feline.
Go on.
I knew i could never
stay married to alice
if i could feel a passion
like that for somebody else.
And i planned to bring
kim-ly back to america.
But first, i had to go
back by myself and...
end my marriage.
While i was breaking the news to alice,
kim-ly was killed
in a surprise attack on her village.
- she died?
- yeah.
So i was devastated.
But i always knew in my heart
that what i'd felt for
kim-ly was true love.
And i think i was too much of a romantic
to stay forever in a loveless marriage.
So ultimately, alice and
i parted as good friends.
I'd always hoped i could feel
something like that again,
and now i have with your mother.
Yeah. My prayers have been answered.
Aaron. Hey, it's me.
- what's up?
- it's such a beautiful day,
i was thinking i could take you to
one of my favorite spots for a change.
Have you ever been to the old
puppet theatre in central park?
That sounds great, but i'm still
in the studio with danielle.
- i'm sorry. Are you still working?
- no, no. We're just hangin'.
Can, we do the puppet thing tomorrow?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Looks like b.'s prophecy came true.
One day you're a muse.
The next, you're old news.
The caterers done setting up downstairs?
Yes.
And what about you, my sneaky daughter?
Are you done yet?
What do you mean?
Cyrus told me that you had lunch
together, and he was very touched.
Of course, he doesn't know yet that you
have an agenda for absolutely everything.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're not a child anymore.
But you can't help it, can you?
You can't stop meddling and
scheming. Let me guess...
you played nice
so that you could dig
up some dirt on cyrus.
But it didn't work, did it?
Because he is the most
upstanding man i have ever met.
Sorry, mom.
It turns out that cyrus
is just like daddy.
He cheated on his
ex-wife. He had an affair.
He fell in love with her.
I'm sorry.
It's true. You can ask him yourself.
Yeah?
This is scott smith's office
calling for jenny humphrey.
This is agnes andrews.
Oh, i'm sorry. I must have
mixed up your phone numbers.
I'm about to see jenny right now. Is
there something you want me to tell her?
Yes, please let her know the contracts
are ready for j. Humphrey designs.
- i'll give her that message.
- Thank you.
There's a totally cute
guy over there. The busboy?
Beggars can't be choosers.
How's your totally
cute boyfriend, serena?
- he's not exactly my boyfriend.
- you mean he's free?
Hazel, i can hear your
desperation from the other room.
Serena, what's wrong?
I think you were right. The whole
muse thing kinda backfired.
I would say i told you so, but
since i'm now 18, i'll refrain.
- what happened?
- we had this amazing night.
I modeled for him, and he did
this incredible installation.
He totally loves you.
But then another girl
showed up at the studio,
and she modeled for him, and
they've been hanging out all day.
So pablo's already moved on?
That was faster than i thought.
It's okay, s. It's
actually a good thing.
This way, you can get out
before you're in too far.
You just missed your dad.
- he was ringing the buzzer for an hour.
- my dad?
Wait, what are you
doing with my dresses?
When i let you in, i had no
idea you'd be such a little thief...
stealing my contact list
and our whole business.
- i wasn't stealing, agnes...
- you know, you think you're so
- talented and unique, don't you?
- no, i don't.
Three weeks ago, you were absolutely nothing.
You were a little intern pinning my hem.
It was my idea to do the fashion line.
I found the photographer and the models
for the fashion shoot.
It was also my idea
for the guerilla fashion show,
and i have all the contacts!
I know. You're right,
okay? You're right.
Just give me my dresses, please.
Do you know how many "talented" artists there
are living in brooklyn designing dresses?
Agnes, give me my dresses!
What are you doing?!
These dresses are as much
mine as they are yours.
- now they belong to nobody.
- are you totally insane?
Yes, i'm insane, jenny!
What are you doing? Agnes? Don't!
Agnes, please!
These dresses are everything!
They're my entire future!
You are out of your mind!
What the hell did you do, agnes?!
You did this! Now by
the time i get back,
i want you and your
crap out of my apartment.
It was good to see you.
The mythical serena.
You must be cyrus,
eleanor's boyfriend. How
did you know who i was?
Well, i recognized you
from aaron's studio.
You know aaron?
- he's my son!
- wh...
oh, my goodness.
You didn't catch the family resemblance?
No, it's okay.
You know, i think he's
quite smitten with you.
Really? I'm not so sure.
He told me that he
took you to the cloisters.
He definitely doesn't
do that with just anyone.
I'm actually
gonna go stop by his studio
to see him now, but it was
really nice meeting you.
Likewise.
- oh, eleanor.
- did yo cheat on your ex-wife?
- well, did you? Is it true?
- yes, it is.
Get out.
I thought he was...
different.
I have to go lie down.
- there are so many hot guys here.
- my god. Look at that guy.
Cyndi lauper?
What are you doing here?
My pal cyrus called me yesterday.
He bought out my gig and asked me to
play this girl's birthday party insad.
I guess he's madly in
love with her mother.
I'm looking for a blair waldorf.
How do you do?
Make yourself at home.
Dorota!
This is dorota. She's your biggest fan.
Oh, my. Miss lauper!
Wait! Miss blair, where are you going?
I wanted a harry winston choker for my
birthday. Instead, i got a conscience.
I gotta go.
Sorry to bother you at home, sir.
What was it you wanted
to speak to me about?
Something kind of strange happened
while i was at your office.
I overheard this guy talking
about you to an employee.
He said that you
were responsible for a fire
in one of your own buildings.
He had a lot of details.
I figured there must be
some kind of explanation,
if it even happened,
which, i'm sure it didn't.
And look, i know it's none
of my business. I'm sorry. But
he was so insistent, i figured if
he was telling people at work, he...
he could be telling other people, too.
So it's out.
I've had that man's death on
my conscience for 20 years.
Wait. Someone died?
Dad, don't say anything else.
He's writing a story for a magazine.
So what's it gonna cost
to make this go away?
I don't want your money.
If you use this against my
father, i will destroy you.
Chuck, what happened is
bigger than you hating me
or me trying to make it as a writer.
I couldn't ignore this if i wanted to.
It will ruin our family.
Don't do it.
Please.
You're still here.
I sent my driver to
dinner because i thought
i'd be at the party
ringing in your birthday.
You threw in the towel rather easily.
I expected a harder fight.
I'm smart enough to know
that getting into a war
with eleanor's daughter
is never gonna result in a victory.
So you retreated with dignity.
Who says i gave up?
Oh, my god. You outmaneuvered me.
You deliberately let me
win, counting on the fact
that cyndi lauper would
prey on my emotions.
I'm a lawyer. I do
think a few moves ahead.
Some of us can't rely entirely
on our looks, you know.
Well done.
- not enough.
- fine. You're a genius.
You better be good to my mother,
or i'll be coming for you.
Those are fair terms.
Now come upstairs and stand next to me
while i tell my mom the whole
truth about the golden lion.
She'll be furious with me,
so i may need an attorney.
You're not what i had in mind.
Well, you're not what i had in mind.
Sir?
This was left for you with
the concierge downstairs.
I'm sorry i'm interrupting your "work."
Serena, i thought i was
seeing you tomorrow. Excuse me.
Right, because you're
seeing danielle tonight.
I'm seeing a lot of people. You and
i just started hanging out, okay?
Did i miss a talk where
we decided to be exclusive?
Look, i don't know how
it works in high school, but
i like to date more than one person at
once. You're free to see other people, too.
Thank you for the condescending
lecture, but that's not really my thing.
Hey, dad. Can i come in?
Of course you can,
jenny. This is your home.
- i'm happy to have you back.
- i'm not back yet,
but i will be if you sign these papers.
The papers your
mother already refused to sign?
She only refused because she
didn't want to get in the middle.
And here i thought you'd
come to your senses.
You don't even have your coat off,
and you're already using
- emotional blackmail to get your way.
- spin it however you like.
- if i sign this paper, it means that
- everything you've done up to now...
this lying, cheating, manipulation...
it's all okay.
And if you don't sign it,
then everything i've done...
everything... is all for nothing.
I won't put my name on a piece of
paper condoning who you've become.
Fine. Then i'll just
have to find another way.
What other way? You gonna sleep
on agnes' couch till you turn 18?
If that's what it takes.
Poor little orphan jenny.
Looks like she needs a daddy warbucks.
But daddy warbucks
don't grow on trees...
at least not on a tree
that grows in brooklyn.
Mr. Smith? Hi.
Yeah, sorry to bother you on a sunday.
Is there any way that we can
meet at your office today?
Can i come in?
I can't stop you.
I want to apologize, son.
Apologize?
I never blamed you for
your mother's death.
I read that short story that,
dan humphrey wrote about
you and your mother.
I had no idea you felt that way.
It's my fault.
I know i've had trouble
being close to you.
But it's not for the reasons you think.
It's just hard because...
every time i look at you,
i see her.
- you miss her.
- you have no idea.
I've made some terrible mistakes in my
life but i don't want to make another.
I want to know my son.
So any, interest in
going to that hockey game?
I'll... clear my calendar.
I spoke to your sister.
My, plan didn't exactly pan out.
I heard. She called me.
You've been thinking about
that story on bart bass?
Yeah.
- i took your advice and killed it.
- you saved that family.
I think it's time you saved ours, dad.
It's so important to you to be right.
That's a trait i inherited.
I'd be the first to say it.
But you... you need to get jenny back,
even if it means letting her win.
So... what's the urgent question?
Neither of my parents
will sign the papers.
What else can i do?
You have one other
option, but it's extreme.
You could file a suit to
become emancipated.
What's that mean?
You'd be empowered to
be your own guardian.
Your legal ties with your
family would be severed.
You mean divorce my parents?
Okay. What do i need to do?
I can't believe aaron is cyrus' son.
Of course, you get the prince,
and i get stuck with the toad.
It doesn't look like i'm gonna
have the fairy tale ending.
I went to have a talk
with aaron yesterday.
- and?
- instead, he had a talk with me.
I really tried to deal with
the casual dating thing...
but i guess it's just not for me.
Of course not, because beneath
that free spirit facade,
you're totally
conventional, just like i am.
It's not a facade. I believe in
freedom, people following their hearts,
doing what they want. You know i
always wish i'd lived in the '60s.
You believe in long hair,
peasant skirts and sandals,
but you in an open
relationship? I don't think so.
Speaking of relationships, how are
you faring with cyrus and eleanor?
He's not exactly my cup of tea,
but he makes my mother happy, and...
- he's not that bad.
- i'm proud of you.
It's not like i have
to see him that often.
He'll come to pick her up
for dinner once, twice a week.
- have to go.
- bye.
Darling, we have some wonderful news.
Thanks to you, blair, we've been
up all night talking about love
and death and the brevity of life.
And we have decided that
he should move in today.
Some surprises hit you over
the head like a squash racket.
And others sneak up on you
when you're least expecting it.
What are you doing here?
I'm picking you up for an afternoon
of puppet theater in the park.
But we broke up last night, remember?
Wait, how did... how did we
break up if we're not going out?
Thanks for reminding
me. That feels good.
Serena, i really like you.
Even though i grew up
on the upper east side,
i don't want the same
life that my parents had...
social obligations and
forced conversations,
saying no to all the things
that i wanted to say yes to.
I thought you felt the same way.
And if i was wrong, i apologize.
No.
No, you were right.
Wait. What are you doing?
Don't you want to get dressed?
Nope.
And sometimes the biggest surprises
are the ones you spring on yourself.
Come on.
Scampering about in a slip
is one way to shed old skin.
But will embracing free love be as easy
as flinging off a pair of fendi flats?
Looks like someone's
going barefoot in the park.
X.o.x.o., gossip girl.