(Gossip girl) gossip girl
here--Your one and only source
Into the scandalous lives  of manhattan's
elite. I've decided to take over bass industries.
There is one stipulation-- That should
you in any way act inappropriately,
The board has the option to
replace you with your lel guardian,
Which--Wouldn't
you know it? Is me.
I had enough trouble with the
idea of mom and rufus dating,
But now i share a
sibling with my boyfriend?
Maybe we weren't meant to be a family.
Serena,dean berube.
I'd like to issue a press release that
you came up to visit our glorious campus.
Princeton is a trade
school. There is only yale.
He said that yale could really
use a girl like blair waldorf.
(Laughs) oh,b.,i'm so happy for you.
And who am i?
That's a secret  i'll never tell.
You know you love me.
X.O.X.O.,gossip girl.
-=זאדנצה»י=-
·­עכ:ן·¹cake נ°
נ£¶פ:נ°
ך±¼הצב:southwing
True love and betrayal,
revenge and more revenge,
A heroine  with an
impossible goal--
If only mozart had lived
on the upper east side.
(Harold) blair bear,you'll be late!
But you can keep  your
magic flute,amadeus.
All this queen wants is
a golden ticket to yale.
You look like a firing squad.
More like a welcoming
committee. It's the big day.
It's all the color of yale. You see?
That's just what i need to perk
me up. I couldn't sleep a wink.
We know. We heard you
watching "gilmore girls"
All night,again. (Chuckles)
Oh. I am so a better fit
for yale than that rory.
Dorota.
Don't be sad. I'm not going
anywhere for six months.
That wasn't dorota,dear.
That was handsome dan.
Look at him. Yeah,he's
a gift from all of us.
He's the yale
mascot,bulldog--
Just like you after today.
I don't know about the name,though.
We should just call him "handsome."
(Baby voice) you're adorable.
Yes,just don't look behind sofa.
No,you're a shoo-In,darling. (Laughs)
Mademoiselle.  Merci.
A shoo-In.
The personal letter that i wrote to
dean berube should simply cinch it.
We will celebrate your acceptance tonight at
the opera with champagne at all intermissions.
We will be so drunk. By the time
someone dies,we'll just laugh.
Is chuck joining us?
You know how he loves a good
tragedy. Yes. Where is mr. Chuck?
I wouldn't know,and i don't care.
He's as dead to me as his
father is to him. More bluerries.
Whew! Yale day.
Good morning. Mm.
I thought we could walk to
school together for support.
I keep telling myself that
everything happens for a reason.
You know,i'll--I'll end
up in the right place,
But what if i don't get in?
Pfft. Forget you. What
if i do and blair doesn't?
Fire and--And brimstone
and a lot of bitchy asides,
Death by dorota. Thanks. You
don't have to worry either.
Blair's a lock. The dean
told her as much,right?
Yeah. Yeah,yale is good.
We're good.
Everything will be fine.
You're referring to the
recent not fun event,
Uh,also known as the
"you two share a brother,
Oh,wait. No,you don't" roller coaster.
(Chuckles) not to be
outdone by the tilt-A-Whirl
Called "discovering
this fact has only served
To bringing rufus and
lily closer than ever."
(Chuckles) look,getting into
yale will change our lives.
It'll give us a chance
to reinvent ourselves.
Yeah. Yeah,and in the meantime,
At least our pents are
keeping it on the down low.
Yeah. Rufus,stop it.
Oh,hello.
I was planning on sneaking
out before anyone got up,
But lily and i got to bed so late. Oh,you
don't--You-- That's--Just stop there.
Right.
Well,now that this is
all out in the open,
Maybe we can stop sneaking around.
I mean,we've had the awkward
run-In,and it isn't so bad.
I don't know why we thought
this would be so weird.
Let's leave now. Nice try,mom.
Ah,seriously good effort.
So i was
thinking,tonight--
More than four hours of sleep?
That,and there is a
charity gala at the opera.
A full 12 hours then.
Oh,everyone will be there.
It's the--It's the
event of the season,
And i'm really feeling ready
to get back to the world.
Aren't you worried about people
seeing us together so soon?
The kids know. Why shouldn't the world?
And,uh,we might as well make
our society debut in style.
I was just trying to get out of
the opera part. I'm not a fan.
Well,you can become one tonight.
I would say,"get a room,"
but yours is right above mine.
Please try to remember that.
(Whispers) oh,my god.
No,i told you,under
18,and i want verification.
I don't care where you
have to import them from.
I want them young and unstable.
(Mouth full) you can cancel that order.
I already ate.
I'll get right back to you.
Your bush league
attempts to take me down--
They're getting boring.
Although,i must admit,
Having the freshman class of brearley hold
their annual sleepover in my hotel room--
That was a nictouch. By
the way,don't be alarmed,
But,uh,our stock might
take a little dip today.
I'm still adjusting to a learning curve.
No,what you're doing is trying too hard.
You're obviously not
cut out for the job,
Which is why bart never
let you out of the outback.
You should be more careful.
Or what? It's my company
now,kid. You saw to that.
Will the,uh,board and i be
seeing you at the opera tonight?
Even though you're no longer in charge,
You are still the public
face of the company.
I think it's important you display it,
Show there's no hard feelings.
Oh,wait. You're already doing
that for me,aren't you? No matter.
We probably won't be seeing
much of each other anyway.
I'll be in your father's seats,
And you'll be,well,somewhere else.
There's a new ki that "kid" is
my shakespeare teacher,miss carr.
That-That's miss carr? Does she
have benjamin button syndrome?
(Chuckles) here. Let us help you.
It's all right. Oh,thank you,serena. It's
like holding a door never occurred to anybody.
No,not on the upper east
side. These kids have probably
Never touched a door in their life. They
just magically open for them,don't they?
Oh,uh,this is my
boyfriend,dan humphrey. Hi.
Dan,this is miss ca. She's my favorite new
teacher. Well,i've heard a lot about you,
Although i-I wasn't expecting
you to look so... out of place?
No,i was gonna say "young." You could pass
for a student. Well,i was,until recently.
I've been doing teach for america
the past two years in alabama.
This is my first salaried job.
I've never even been to new york before.
It's a lot different than des moines.
My family is in the hotel business,
And the palace lobby is a wonderful
place to get away from the noise.
Yeah,and,you know,if
you're ever in brooklyn,
Uh,my dad has a gallery. There's a pretty cool cafe.
Brooklyn--That's,uh,the place across the bridge,right?
Ha ha. Yeah. You'll fit in just fine
here. Oh,hey,don't let the city get to you.
See you third period. Mm-Hmm.
Nice meeting you,daniel.
Nice meeting you,miss carr.
So good luck today.
You,too. May the best get in.
Refresh. Refresh. Refresh.
That's not my eli account. No,it's
mine. I applied to yale,too,remember?
Yes,but your application was merely a
formality to appease your overbearing parents.
You know very well there's no way
yale is going to accept someone
Who got a 2360 on her s.A.T.S,
So give up and go for
the gold,my gold. Refresh.
Hey,are you going to
the opera thing tonight?
Um,yeah. Serena's taking me.
Yeah? I might go,too.
You know,for a while,i couldn't
take vanessa anywhere really nice,
'Cause of the whole no money thing,
But i saw a dvd of the
"ring" cycle at her house,
And i figured she might like
some champagne in my family's box.
Yeah,that's good. That's good.
Don't tell her you saw that dvd,
Though,'cause i-I pointed it out once,
And she made me watch the whole
thing with no subtitles. Wow.
If you've ever seen
"a clockwork orange,"
You know how that ended up.
Wait. What's "a clockwork orange"?
Charles,i didn't
expect to see you today.
Or ever,if i had it my way.
Yes,well,i missed you,too.
I'm trying to do something.
I really wanted to do it on my own,
But that's not working.
I'm thinking you're the only
person left who can help.
What do you say?
What are you guys doing? Shh.
Don't talk to them. They're working.
Refresh.
My... god.
What? What is it?
I'm sorry. I...
i simply can't read it.
The font's too small. I have
to check it on a real computer.
It says "wait-Listed" in bold.
I got in. I did it.
I got in. Oh,my gosh!
I can't believe it. Oh,did you?
No. No,no. Um,i'm
wait-Listed,just like blair.
Well,don't worry. You'll get in.
We'll be together next fall.
Even if you have to wait
Another couple of months
to find out for sure,
It's all good,or it will be.
Yeah,i know it will.
(Blair) i need to see the headmistress.
Right now!
They say that it's not over  till the fat lady sings.
But who's that i hear
tuning up in the wings?
Sorry,b.  I think it's curtains.
??
?
You're living alone. Why
don't you move back in here?
It'll make it a lot easier to work together.
I'm not interested in a family reunion
Nor in assuaging your guilt
over my father's death.
Do you believe in my cause or not?
I do,
But your shenanigans--
Planting coke in his gym bag,
Ambushing him with a
transsexual hooker...
Two. They owed me a favor.
Will only cast a negative light
on you in the board's eyes.
I don't care about the board anymore.
You should. You need them.
So let me help you by
handling this like a grownup.
My 20% stake in bass industries
must count for something,
And when i'm done,
Perhaps you'll reconsider
your living situation.
Don't hold your breath.
Meet me here at 2:00?
How did this happen?
Dean berube said i was a perfect fit.
His exact words were,
"Yale could use a girl
like blair waldorf."
Well,apparently,they
found one somewhere else.
Calm yourself.
When i spoke to dean
berube this morning,
He assured me that if the student
they've accepted turns them down,
You are next in line.
Dan humphrey?
He's like a cafeteria
lady who won the lottery.
You couldn't pry that acceptance
from his hands with the jaws of life.
I wasn't speaking about mr. Humphrey.
Someone from constance got in?
Blair,in our school's
history,most wait-Listed students
Ultimately get into the
college of their choice.
Your transcript is a
series of unblemished a's.
All you have to do is keep up
your g.P.A.,and you'll get in.
I know that patience and trust
aren't necessarily your strong suits,
But you'll just have to
rise to the occasion,hmm?
Thank you. I'm sure i can do that.
Just tell me who got in.
You got in? Congratulations.
Oh,shh. Don't say it too loud.
I haven't told anyone yet,
Not even dan,especially not blair.
Well,why not? Oh,i-I couldn't.
She was wait-Listed. It
would have been a disaster.
A word of
unsolicited advice--
It sounds like you're
worrying about other people
When this is a decision about you.
Do you want yale?
Do you know you're the first
person that's ever asked me that?
The truth is,i
don't--I don't know.
The wholreason i went there in the
first place was because of blair,
And then i applied because of dan.
Honestly,i think yale might be
accepting me for the wrong reasons.
I would never advise anyone to
turn down a great opportunity,
But going to the right school for
you is the most important thing.
Serena,did you hear someone
from constance got in?
I bet it's that little nelly.
When i find her,she's
not gonna know--Hello.
Blair,i missed you first period.
I had a meeting.
You also missed getting this back.
I'll talk to you later,serena.Bye.
Well,if you're on a witch hunt,
That means you can't be too upset,right?
Witch hunts are my valium,serena.
I'm just trying to stay calm.
What about you?
I have to say,i'm totally
surprised yale passed up
The p.R. Of accepting "it"
girl serena van der woodsen.
They have more class than i thought.
Well,like you pointed
out,they didn't want me for me.
Dan must be pissed.
His hope of arriving on campus
with cachet has been shot to hell.
Now he'll just be lumped in with the
rest of the financial aid-Iots and poets.
Oh,my god.
What?
I have to go.
Hello? (Woman) miss van der woodsen,
This is shirley from
dean berube's office.
The dean would love to
issue a press release
That you'll be joining yale's
freshman class in the fall,
Assuming you're accepting.
Would you mind? Miss van der woodsen?
Um,i-I-I'm gonna have to call
you back. (Snaps phone shut)
Charles has left us no choice.
We wish you had been left
in charge of the company,
Of course,but that's
not how it laid out.
Well,surely there must be
something. Jack is charles' guardian,
And the contract clearly states
that his guardian has control.
Short of being able to prove
he's completely negligent,
All we can do is our best
to temper his actions.
Minority shareholders' meeting.
We were just finishing up.
See you soon,i hope,lilian?
Yes,peter,i'd like that.
Had i known my own personal
mata hari was going to be here,
I would have come sooner. Yes,well,i
was just being brought up to date
On your progress or lack thereof.
I'll right myself eventually.
I just have to get my
legs under me. (Sniffles)
Maybe the two of us could
come together in some way,
Help me find my strength...
or use it all up.
What's that for? Your nose.
You don't seem so worried about the same
morality clause that cost charles this company.
They won't touch me.
Although i may not be
doing a bang-Up job yet,
It beats having a won of
your reputation at the helm.
This is a "b."
Yes,it is.
You're new here,so you
don't know how it works.
I have a feeling you're about to explain.
Second semester seniors get a free pass,
Like pregnant ladies or
14-Year-Old chinese gymnasts.
Constance wants their students
to get into the best colleges.
That's why this free pass exists.
The headmistress-- If she
knew about this grade--
She'd rap you on the wrist.
Maybe in time,i'll get in trouble
For not inflating grades like
everyone else,miss waldorf,
But until then,i'll
give them based on merit.
I need to keep my g.P.A.
Perfect to get into yale.
You should have thought of that before.
What's wrong? I think i
might have just lost yale.
What am i gonna do?
I didn't apply anywhere else.
Just hold on a second.
There's a phone call i have to return.
??
???
Look,i understand why you're
trying to do these things,
But we have got to do
something that is not illegal.
I've put calls in to jack's
business associates in australia.
He's not the most upstanding citizen.
I'm sure we will find something.
You know,i,um,i thought i lost
you the day of the funeral,
And,um,i'm sorry
That jack's the one to
bring us back together,
But i'm glad that we're doing this.
If your people don't
come up with anything,
Maybe we could try number 26.
"Crash jack in plane."
The bass jet is kind
of expensive,charles.
There's insurance. (Cell phone rings)
Hello?
Yes. Yeah,that would be fine.
I can't really talk right now.
Yes,the,uh,the opera
has an early curtain.
Rufus,stop it.
Okay,okay. I'll see you then.
Bye.
I can't believe you.
You're actually going
To take your half-Price
hustler out on the town tonight.
I thought we were putting
this behind us,charles.
I'm here to help you.
And what part of you dating someone else
A month after my father's
death is helping me?
You say you want to be
family,but if you really meant it,
You wouldn't parade
your mistress in public.
You'd have some tact,
Some respect.
This isn't about your father,charles.
I should have known from your
history i couldn't count on you.
You think of yourself.
Your kids and my dead
father are proof of that.
Hey.
Hey,i was thinking maybe we
could go to yale this weekend,
Get some hope into you.
(Whispers) she's going down.
(Blair) yes,she's gonna go.
Would you excuse me for a
second? (Scoffs) not really.
I know that look. You're up to no
good. (Scoffs) good is subjective,
And if you don't believe me,you can look it up. You
want to get rachel back for the grade she gave you.
A new teacher's like a child.
It has to be taught. And spanked.
And i can't risk not getting into yale,
So it's open season on miss iowa.
(Blair) time to shuck the corn.
I wasn't supposed to say anything,but
you--You are going to yale.
You got in,an early admission. What?
How do you know that?
Because i declined my
acceptance. You're next in line.
They're gonna call you in a couple
hours. Whoa. You--You got in?
You're the constance student?
Cancel the nelly yuki project now!
S.,why would you turn down yale?
And don't say for me,because
even i wouldn't believe you.
Yeah,why--Why
would you do that?
I'm--I'm sorry. I-I
wanted to tell you.
You don't want to go?
No. No,i don't.
No,please. I'll--I'll
see you later.
So--So you're not gonna
go after rachel now,right?
What would be the point?
Okay,okay. Hey,so the reason i
asked you to come down is because--
No,wait,wait,wait. Me first.
Okay. Okay,ever since
you got your money back,
You've been taking me to do
all these archibald-Y things,
Which i love. I just can't keep up.
So i decided to do something for us.
We're going to the opera tonight.
Wow. That is fantastic.
They're nosebleed seats,but
at least they're something,
And i got them. So what did
you bring me up here for anyway?
Well,there's no reason.
I just wanted to see you.
And then the--The
queen of the night
Sings this kick-Ass aria,
"Der holle rache kocht
in meinem herzen,"
"The vengeance of hell
boils in my heart."
Lovely. It is.
It reaches a high "f"--That--
That never happens in operas.
You know,that's a good fact.
You should talk about
it at intermission.
You're gonna love "the magic flute."
It's,uh,well,it's... it's okay. You can say it.
Opera for amateurs.
(Chuckles) if anybody asks you
what you thought,just tell 'em,
"Ist war wunderschien.  Danke. Und sie?"
That's what klaus always used to say.
Well,that and--And
"geh zum teufel,"
But,um,whatever you do,don't--Don't
say that. Okay,this is ridiculous.
Dad,lily loves you 'cause you're not that
guy. Eh. This feels a little different.
Only 'cause you're letting it. No,he's
right. In our world,people say one thing,
But they expect something
else. If you can hd your own,
It'll go a long way with
my mom and her friends.
Everyone can geh zum teufel.
I just want to do right by her.
Let's talk "singspiel,"
shall we? "Singspiel."
The devil would say,
"You're already in
yale. You ha security.
Now more than ever,you
can do what you want."
And an angel would say,
"All the more reasonnotto.
Youhavewhat you want."
You don't have a perfect transcript.
But you don't need one. You're in.
Ugh! I hate having to play the angel.
I know. The devil is so much better.
So,b.,who won?
Gimme.
Hello. Miss carr? It's blair waldorf.
How did you get my number? I wanted
to apologize for my behavior earlier.
I was hoping you'd afford me the chance
to move past it. I'd like that,too,
But couldn't this have waited
till we saw each other again?
That's precisely why i'm calling.
Did you know the school
has a block of tickets
To the opera tonight? To the
opera? No,i didn't know that.
Oh,yes. It's a gala event,and my famil
Who's heard all about you,asked
if you could come to dinner
And then join us in our
grand tier seats afterwards.
I don't think that's such a
good idea in light of today
Or at all. Nonsense.
We have an extra ticket.
You're not gonna let
our little disagreement
Stand in the way of the opera?
I-I have always wanted to go.
Do you have a pen handy?
Yeah.
Spotted--B.
Hot for teacher.
Too bad miss carr
Doesn't remember  the
devil is in the details.
What do you say the
boathouse in central park?
We meet at 6:30 and walk
over for curtain at 8:00.
Thank you. Sounds wonderful.
Yes. Yes,it does.
That sounds great. I can't wait.
Box two. Uh,row two. Two for you.
Thanks.
You know what? Uh,if you'll excuse me?
(Speaks indistinctly) uh,no,thank you.
Uh... am i glad to see you.
Serena and i had to meet up with
our parents before we got here,
And it went from "family
ties" to faulkner...
Ooh. In one cocktail flat.
Uh,hey,you excited about your box?
My what? Oh,hey,we're on the
third tier,actually. Yeah.
It's,um,a better view and straight on.
Oh. Oh,yeah. Well,third tier's awesome.
Yep.
What's going on here?
Nothing. Nothing's going on.
Okay,so there might be some
other seats \available to us.
Lily. Didn't know you'd be here.
O's your lky escort this evening?
Someone you picked up at the funeral?
Mm,this is rufus
humphrey,the man i'm seeing.
Mm. You remember pauletta cho?
She's head of publicity for
my company.  Our company.
Yes,hi. It's nice to see you,pauletta.
But your choice of
companion? Not so nice.
I'm here to keep an eye on
him more than anything else.
Hope you both enjoy the show.
And if not,you can ponder why
You thought coming here
together was a good idea.
Enjoy "tristan und isolde."
Okay.
This isn't "e magic flute"? Oh,no.
That opera ended weeks
ago,and it's mainly for kids.
Ah,kids. You gotta love
'em. (Sighs deeply) yeah.
They do such great things,like
misread the opera calendar.
Bruce,hello.
Hey,my condolences about bart.
I-I haven't wanted to call.
I-I didn't want to be a bother
in your--Your time of grief.
Uh,well,now that you're here,what
do you want me to do about those,
Uh,documen i'd been working on?
Um... could you wait
here for just a moment?
What's going on? I just
need to talk to charles.
Um,you two can just talk
about opera while i'm gone.
The answer is so simple. How
could i have forgotten it?
Any chance you could try and forget me?
Just meet me back here in 15 minutes.
And if you don't like what i suggest,
I won't bother you
again. You have my word.
You don't have any binoculars,do you?
(Whispers) oh,or how about
those cool little spy glasses?
Or a telescope.
All right,i get it. You
want to go to the stupid box.
Not if you don't want to.
Once the show starts,i'm sure
it'll be great from up here. Yeah.
Candy,dear?
You know,it's not that you don't
want to go to the same college as me.
It's not? No. A lot of couples
go to different schools.
But,you know,for months,
You acted like going to yale
together was what you wanted.
Well,i didn't figure it out until today.
And brown is just a
better fit for me,dan.
Well,and what about us?
I mean,do we still "fit"?
Well,it's--It's not like we
have to decide anything now.
We can just-- What? We can
go on having you make choices
That affect both of our lives
without you talking to me?
Look,i'm sorry. (Sighs
deeply) i'm sorry.
I was just-- I was
so happy about yale.
If we went together,you know,
We'd get four years away
from--From everything and from...
everyone.
But   are gonna follow us
to college,wherever we go.
And what if our parents stay together?
What happens then? More
uncomfortable dinners?
Adjoining rooms on family vacations?
Pretending not to hear what we hear
in the middle of the night? (Chuckles)
I mean,who knows how long
that's gonna last for?
Well,you know,i think we'll just
have to compartmentalize everything.
The--The two of them
will be its own thing
That we'll put in a box and
just keep away somewhere.
Things don't just go in
boxes. They go all together.
No,they don't.
No,they--They go in boxes
with really tight lids
That you bury deep in holes
at the bottom of the ocean.
Okay. (Laughs)
Providence is just a
train ride from new haven.
I think we're just gonna have to try and
push through the next couple of months.
Yes.
And knowing them,it--It
won't last,right?
I mean,it can't.
It could never.
I,uh,studied the wrong opera.
I wanted to impress
you and your friends,
And prove that i could exist
in both your world and mine.
Oh,rufus. I don't care
what anyone thinks.
You exist in our world,and it's
the only world that matters.
Thanks for trying.
Oh. Oh,god. Where are
the boxes with the lids?
Why don't you guys
head,um,up to our seats?
I have to handle first.
Okay. Yeah.
(Dan) right behind you.
Here we go.
And,uh...
(cell phone rings)
darling,turn off your phone.
Remember the kevi
Hello,headmistress queller.
(Queller) blair,i'm sorry
to call you after hours,
But ms. Carr told me how upset
you were about your grade.
She did? I confirmed with her
That so long as the rest of your grades
Were up to your usual high standard,
That you would still end
the course with an "a."
It was sweet of ms.
Carr to be so concerned.
She's a good asset to the school.
I think she cares about her students.
She cares about their futures.
Have a good weekend. Thank you.
I'm sorry,but i have to go.
The opera's about to begin.
It can wait. I have to fix something.
Who's this? Bruce caplan. I'm
your father's family lawyer.
Before he died,
Your dad was going to
legally adopt serena and eric.
And i was going to legally adopt you.
We were serious about
becoming a real family,
And we'd had the papers drawn,and
your father had signed them.
I just didn't get to it in time.
Your stepmother asked me to have
these faxed over to the box office.
So if you adopt me...
then i'm your guardian.
Give me a pen.
Just to be clear,this doesn't
make us family,just even.
What do you think you're doing?
You can't sign anything
without my consent.
Not anymore.
I'm sending you back where you belong.
You just lost the company.
Sticks and stones  may break bones,
But a poison pen  is the best revenge.
Now if you'll excuse me,i'm going home.
I was on my way to find you and
apologize. "On your way" an hour later?
I feel terrible. I do.
And...
as much as i wish i
wasn't,i'm still learning.
It's like you not inflating your grades.
I can't not act out against people.
But i'm trying.
So... (sighs) please forgive me.
I accept your apology.
Come. Let's see if we can
find you another ticket.
I'm actually quite tired.
I'll just see you monday?
Yes,of course.
Thank you again.
Headmistress? (Queller) rachel?
I'm sorry to bother you.
I just need to talk
to you about something.
I hate losing.
You didn't lose. Mm-Hmm.
You just admitted defeat.
You know what's great about a box? Hmm?
(Whispers) when the opera gets boring...
* i don't care what
you did so long ago *
* it don't move... *
What do you think you're
doing? (Locks door)
I should ask you the same thing.
It's what bart wanted. I'm sorry.
So you say. I'm not so sure.
I'm not scared of
you,jack. You should be.
You're high and you're
not thinking clearly.
You need to think about the
repercussions of what you're doing.
I don't think i do.
I just had a full conversation with
this opera-Goer about "the magic flute."
And he pretended like that was
exactly what he just watched.
I'm beginning to get
these society people.
It's all a big game of pretending like
you know what you're talking about. Mm.
Where's lily? I don't know. I
haven't seen her all intermission.
Keep an eye out for her,huh? All right.
Chuck.
As much as i hate to ask you
anything,have you seen lily?
My dad's looking for her.
She said she was going
to the powder room.
But that was a while ago.
What's going on here?
What are you doing?
Why is this door locked?
* you only look at what
you see in the mirror *
* you never look at what
you see around here *
You think you can squeeze
me out,take away my power?!
I worked for this! I earned it!
* you only look... *
Jack,it's over.
Stop it! You can't do this! Get off me!
I can't? Who in this town
wouldn't believe that the whore
Didn't ask for it?! Stop! Please!
Hey! Get off her!
(Pts) you stup kid.
* suicide *
Oh,rufus! Oh,my god. Lily!
Come on.
Get off of me!
Oh,my god. Thank you.
??
I heard from the board that jack
is on his way back to sydney.
You didn't press charges.
No,i just wanted him gone.
But now i'm the,uh,interim
head of bass industries,
Believe it or not. Is that
why you called me here?
What you did for me
last night-- Lily...
It's okay. You don't
have to feel the same way.
But i do have faith
that when you're ready,
You will do wonders
with bass industries.
What are you talking about?
On your 18th birthday,i
want you to have everything.
I don't want this job
or the corporate jet
Or anything related to this business.
Just you,
As a part of my family.
Look...
i know what happened to
my father was an accident.
It was a terrible accident.
And,um...
if the offer still stands...
i'd like to move back in.
I would love that.
The thing about new beginnings
Is that they require
something else to end.
Hey! I'm just on my way out.
Miss blair,we must go or
we be late. (Mouths words)
The headmistress asked if i
could come meet her at school.
I figured she wants to have tea like
we did when i first applied to yale.
What are you doing? I'm just
reading the brown catalogue.
Oh,and i ordered a
home dreadlocking kit.
Wanna meet up later?
Definitely. Maybe we can get
a jump start on your veganism.
Have some celebratory
seitan at angelica kitchen?
Mm,i can't think of anything better...
Or grosser. (Laughs)
I'll call you after.
Okay.
Some endings take a long
time  to reveal themselves.
But when they do,they're
almost too easy to ignore.
Hey,ms. Carr. What are you doing here?
Rachel.
And i'm taking your advice to
come out to brooklyn sometime.
Can i--Can i get you anything?
I make a mean cappuccino.
Well,all i have to do is press "start," but
i like to pretend. That sounds great. Yeah.
Here,sit.
Some beginnings  start so quietly,
You don't even notice  they so
you've been on the subway now.
You've made it out to a borough.
How's the city working out for ya?
I think i'm getting the hang of it.
Like anything else,you just
have to make it work for you.
But most endings come
when you least expect them,
And what they portend
Is darker  than you've ever imagined.
I called you here this morning
Because ms. Carr told me what you did.
You leave me no choice
but to give you detention.
Yale has been notified.
Your acceptance has been placed on hold.
If you complete detention
to my satisfaction,
Yale will still be possible.
But if you do not...
(cold war kids) * lock all exit doors *
* "now i wanna be your dog" *
Put that puppy down,dorota.
What happened,miss blair?
* high tide rattling off *
It's what's going to happen
that you should be worried about.
Not all beginnings  are
cause for celebration.
A lot of bad things
begin--  Fight,flu season,
And the worst thing of all...
Uh-Oh. Is it war?
Yes.
But this one will be different.
I need to wait for my moment,and
then i'm going black ops--
Off the radar,no accountability.
This war,i'm gonna win.
Wanna be starting somethin'.
X.O.X.O.,gossip girl.זזאדנצה»י
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
»¶ף­¼ףטכ