Gossip Girl here,
your one and only source
into the scandalous lives
of Manhattan's elite.
I raided Lily's medicine cabinet.
- She gets headaches.
- That's a hell of a headache.
We need a second opinion.
Even if you do go with another doctor,
I'm gonna stick around.
Are you Blair Waldorf? We haven't read
about you on "Gossip Girl" in forever.
- You read "Gossip Girl"?
- Of course. Everyone at Columbia does.
I called your cell
to explain everything.
I even left her a message.
- She's lying. I never talked to her.
- Just get out.
There's only one spot,
and I didn't get it.
I got the spot.
- Why weren't you honest?
- Like you,
going behind my back to apply
for the one thing I wanted the most?
IfI couldn't talk to you earlier,
it's not about my dad.
It was about my mom.
She's sick, and I don't know
what'llhappen.
It's not working
exactly as I'd hoped.
I need you to write Lily
another prescription.
I doubt the authorities would be pleased
to know what you've been doing.
Subber East Siders
.: Arcadya Global Team :.
Season 03 Episode 20
It's a Dad, Dad, Dad World
www.arcadya.net
www.sous-titres.eu
It's said that we're all strapped
to fortune's wheel...
Nowhere is this truer
than the ever-changing landscape
of love.
As one couple enjoys an upswing.
Another is plunged downwards.
But top or bottom,
don't get too comfortable,
because the one thing
you can rely on
is that the wheel
will keep on turning.
I'm heading to my mom's
for breakfast.
You're coming in late and leaving early
all week. I'm starting to feel cheap.
I'm sorry I haven't been
around much lately.
Just with everything going
so well with my dad.
No worries.
I love being your crash pad,
but maybe you'd feel better
if you moved back in with your mom
while she's treated.
And have to see Jenny's lying face
first thing in the morning?
No, thank you.
That is not the same girl
Chuck came home with last night.
Has he come to talk to Lily yet?
- Do you want me to talk to him?
- I already tried,
but thank you. I'llcome
to your lacrosse game after brunch.
Judge away.
Shame turns me on.
She's going to Lily's for brunch.
Maybe waffles will help your hangover?
I find the cause is the best cure.
I gotta go. So I will see you later
at the library,
And I'm sorry about before
with the Tisch catalog.
It's fine.
Dan, I don't know how to do this.
We've been tiptoeing
around each other for days.
We're two artists in a relationship,
and sometimes
we're gonna be competing,
So, all right, we're smart people.
Let's come up with...
Some rules, a list of topics
that are off-limits.
Isn't that what got us in trouble?
No. This will be different,
because we'll know...
what we don't know.
Listen to me.
I'm quoting Donald Rumsfeld.
Until the sting of Tisch has worn off,
we shouldn't talk about classes.
Like, if you're taking
playwriting
with Sam Shepard, it may hurt my heart,
but if you take intro to mime,
I need to know everything. I want to be
here when you buy your leotard.
Playwriting competitions, I think
we can go out for the same ones,
but we can't read
each other's submissions.
Looking forward, it's the same thing
with internships and jobs.
The only things
we can talk about openly
are politics, "jersey shore",
and where we want to eat...
Which reminds me,
I need to get ready.
I'm gonna be late for breakfast.
Are you sure you don't want to come?
- No, I'm sorry. I have something.
- Is it something related to our list?
Actually, yeah.
Thank you for not sharing.
I can't believe
how much easier that is.
Ooh! Another sext session
with your new B.F.?
I'd hardly call Elliot a boyfriend.
Between me spending
all my time with my mom
and him being in every club in school,
We haven't even been on a first date.
Still using cooking as therapy?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Good morning.
Look at all of this food.
It's obscene.
- You okay?
- Please, everyone, relax.
What I need is
for the people who love me
to treat me like they always do.
Has anybody heard from Chuck?
Yeah, he's sorry
he couldn't make it.
Charles has the right idea.
If he were here,
then I'd really worry.
One thing
I'll say about the treatment
is that I have not lost my appetite.
I want waffles.
Music to my ears.
Dad.
- What's he doing here?
- I invited him.
Looks great, Lil.
Really great.
I hope you'll all cometo this doctors
without borders gala at Columbia.
I must admit, I feel a bit silly
about the whole thing.
Clearly, Columbia's run out
of alumni to honor,
if the best they could
come up with is... me.
False humility-check.
I'll be there. I invited Nate and Blair.
I really want them to get to know you.
Terrific. I'd be honored.
Rufus and I would love to come.
Why don't you grab a plate?
Help yourself.
What?
He left when I was 2.
- He's a total stranger to me.
- You have to give him a chance.
- No, I don't.
- Okay, everyone.
Let's sit down
and enjoy this wonderful food.
Dad, here. Sit here.
Rufus, scoot over, please.
Please.
Thank you.
What's up?
I thought I'd come
and watch your lacrosse game.
So if you could make sure
that there's a seat for me in V.I.P.,
preferably next to an injured
cute player, but not one on scholarship.
- Since when do you care about lacrosse?
- Since I needed to get away from N.Y.U.
Everyone's planning
their living arrangements for next year.
It's so depressing.
Your friends didn't ask you
to live with them?
In a postwar building on a street
that's not even numbered. It's lettered.
And its big selling point is
that it's above a falafel stand.
I gotta go.
There's no V.I.P. Area,
but there's a nice set of bleachers.
You probably don't remember us,
but we met at your mom's fashion show.
Yeah, of course.
Hair band girl.
I never forget a good accessory.
We're celebrating.
We just got
the most amazing apartment ever.
You would totally approve, prewar,
doorman, and the best part, Fauchon
is opening up next door.
Can I ask you something?
What do you think about falafel?
That's the food paralegals eat.
I never thought I'd see Blair Waldorf
on the Upper West Side.
Unless... Oh, my God.
Are you transferring to Columbia?
I hope so.
N.Y.U. is so beneath you.
It's true!
I'm a Columbia girl now.
As you should be.
The last time I was at a ceremony
in my honor, I slaughtered a chicken.
At least you've been honored.
I've never been honored,
I did win a contest once
at boarding school,
and I think there was a plaque,
but I'm not sure that really counts.
What kind of contest?
- Drinking hot chocolate at the fair.
- I had a buddy
that went to Exeter, and his stories
would make Keith Richards blush.
I wasn't really
into the party scene.
I was there more for the academics.
Sounds like
you've made great choices.
I'm glad.
The bad ones have a way of...
following you.
I've never heard
that hot chocolate story.
There're a lot you haven't heard.
True, but I did hear this one.
My ex-boyfriend went
to boarding school with Serena,
and he tells a great one about
her and this teacher one night
at a bed-and-breakfast.
Although I'm sure
they were studying.
Like she says,
she was all about the academics.
I have an announcement.
I'm moving back in.
That way,
I can be here with you, mom.
And it'll just be really great
to be back in my old room again.
Don't worry, Jenny.
We'll find a place for you.
That's great, because
I'm moving in, too.
Downstairs.
I was waiting to tell you until
the board approved my sublet tomorrow.
But I'm very excited.
All my family
together under one roof again.
Better watch out, Humphreys.
They say love makes a family,
but on the Upper East Side,
everyone knows
it's real estate.
Dad, I'm sorry I'm running so late.
- Can you save me a waffle?
- Always.
I'll put one in the oven for you.
How's Lily?
- She's great.
- And you?
How you holding up?
It must be weird.
Lily's ex-husband is now her doctor.
It was at first. But the fact is, he's
her doctor now. I'm her husband.
By the way, Vanessa can't make it.
Said she had to be somewhere.
Oh, right. The internship at CNN.
They called me as one of
the references she listed.
Yeah, I wouldn't know.
We are keeping our creative lives
separate right now.
You might wanna discuss this one,
Since it involves her going
to Haiti for three months.
You know what, dad? I think I'm gonna
have to cancel that waffle.
- Okay.
- All right. See you.
I know this gala tomorrow night
seems boring, but I thought,
if there's a girl you like,
perhaps you'd like to invite her.
Actually, I'm gay.
So if I was going, which I'm not,
then my date would be
a guy named Elliot.
That's cool.
Bring Elliot.
- I'd love to meet him.
- Please stop...
acting like you and I have
any kind of relationship.
You're right.
- I have a lot to make up for.
- I'm sorry.
The window for that closed somewhere
between my 12th birthday
and, my suicide attempt.
Don't worry. I'm fine now.
Going through without a father
made me realize that I don't need one.
I understand that I've lost the right
To be a father to you, but...
If there's any way that
we can get to know each other...
On your terms...
Serena may want
a relationship with you,
But I don't.
Serena, stop it! You can't do that.
The room was on loan I'm taking it back.
I don't care if I leave it in the closet
- Borrowing without asking is stealing.
- Dad, tell her to stop!
I think it's great you're moving back in
but tha's Jenny's room now.
You can stay in Chuck's old room.
No way. That room is haunted
by Chuck's depravity.
Jenny can take it. I'm sure
it wouldn't bother you.
Okay, what's going on with you two?
Nothing.
Fine. Whatever.
Serena can have her old room back.
That's ridiculous. I'll have Laryssa
make up Chuck's bed for you.
I'm confident
that there's no depravity
that brand-new E.Braun sheets
can't erase.
How many problems does J. have to cause
before you realize she's the problem?
Thanks for meeting me here.
The library started...
Did you apply for a documentary
internship in Haiti?
Yeah.
The producer just called.
I got the job.
When were you planning
on telling me about this?
This morning, then you put it on the
"do not discuss" list and I panicked.
Why? This is not about
competing for something.
This is about our relationship.
But both of those have been
so tied up in each other,
and this job is a huge deal for me.
But you can't pretend like you going
away for 3 months isn't gonna affect us.
I think I didn't wanna face that.
It was so much easier when we're friends
and we could talk about things.
All right,
is that what you want, then?
You wanna go back to just friends?
I don't know.
Anyway, Serena might be
a little upset.
Well, you were right.
She can stay in Charles' room.
- It's getting crowded around here.
- No kidding.
Throw in your ex-husband,
and now we're a Nancy Meyers movie.
I hope you don't mind.
I know it's awkward.
Well, I mean, it is a little
unusual, don't you think,
for a doctor to move in
to his patient's building?
Well, not if he's the father
of the patient's children.
What are you getting at?
Is it possible that...
Will's also trying
to get close to you?
Absolutely not.
I'm the one that told William
to stay away if he couldn't make good
on the promises he made
to the children.
And I'm sorry if this is
uncomfortable for you.
But if William wants to move in
to be closer to the kids,
I'm not gonna stand in his way.
Holland? Hi, it's Rufus.
I have a favor to ask.
And the social scene
at N.Y.U. Was criminal.
Ten freshmen, a keg and a tub of hummus
on a card table isn't a party.
It's a tragedy.
Blair Waldorf just got a text.
It's like watching lady gaga
set fire to a piano!
- Who's it from?
- Serena.
Apparently, Jenny
is claiming squatter's rights
on her old room.
It's disgusting.
Oh, my God. Jenny can't do that
to Serena van Der Woodsen.
So what's the plan of attack?
It's between Serena and Jenny.
Anyway, I've had some recent bad luck
getting involved in real estate disputes
So I was thinking
Warren-Tricomi mani/pedis?
I told you. It doesn't matter
if she transfers.
Blair Waldorf was over the minute
she became a student at N.Y.U.
Are you third personing me?
- I third person people, not you!
- Exactly.
You're Blair Waldorf,
fashion icon, Queen B.
And probably the future
President of the United States.
Or Chanel.
Jenny Humphrey just kicked
Serena van Der Woodsen
out of her room, and you're
not gonna do anything?
I would. I just don't have
any dirt on Jenny right now.
Ahem. I do.
Jenny and her boyfriend sold Adderall
to my boyfriend a couple of months ago.
Lose the judge-face, Zoe.
He took a very heavy course load
this semester.
Jenny Humphrey, drug dealer.
I can work with that.
We hear Blair Waldorf's
headed for a comeback.
But if she wants
to keep her fans happy...
Send.
She better keep serving up the hits.
- Sleep well?
- Don't even.
I can't believe you posted
on "Gossip Girl" that I'm a drug dealer.
I didn't post anything.
Fine. Maybe you didn't send the e-mail,
but I know Blair do your dirty work.
I can't help what Blair does.
And you are the one
who played Pablo Escobar
to underage preppy pill poppers.
My dad and I were finally in a good
place after a really, really bad patch.
And if he finds this out,
it'll destroy everything.
Maybe Rufus should know
that his daughter is dealing drugs.
You thought my father should know
all my adventures at boarding school.
Fine. Maybe I shouldn't
have said anything,
But you shouldn't
be lying to your dad.
Are you really lecturing me
about lying to a parent?
My dad knows who I am,
but you're building a relationship
with yours that's a complete lie.
I can't believe that you are
willing to destroy
My relationship with my father
because you're too scared that yours
won't love you for who you really are.
You were right. We need to make
these decisions together.
But the truth is, consulting with
someone else doesn't come easily to me.
I get it, Vanessa.
- I totally support you going.
- Thank you,
but I'm not taking the internship.
I'd rather lose the job
than lose you.
You're not gonna lose me
if you go to Haiti.
We're gonna find
a way to make this work.
But you gotta go.
I don't want to, and we both know it's
better for our relationship if I stayed.
I mean, three months
is too long, and...
I just wanna be with you.
Are you sure?
You're making this decision for you?
Not me?
Not even us?
All right. Okay.
Let's find a way to celebrate tonight,
then-a fun way. We could...
Let's see. You want to sneak 40s
into the midnight showing
of the lost weekend at film forum?
I'm supposed to have drinks
with the woman from CNN,
and I owe it to her to tell her
my decision face to face.
Okay. All right.
Well, tomorrow night, then.
Absolutely.
You never made it
to my lacrosse game yesterday.
What are you doing?
I could ask you the same. Does Serena
know you're trying to pull off plaid?
Seriously, I expected Chuck to go back
to his old habits after your breakup,
But I'd actually thought
you'd grown up a little.
Whatever do you mean?
Blair Waldorf on the upper West Side
two days in a row?
It looks like you're pretending
to be a Columbia student,
and not that I care much about what
Jenny Humphrey does these days,
But I saw that smackdown
on "Gossip Girl".
She was dealing drugs.
It's called an intervention.
It's called you going back
to plotting and conniving,
Okay, and that's
the Waldorf equivalent of Chuck
going around, sleeping
with every call girl in the city
and avoiding any kind
of emotional contact.
Okay. So I'm pretending
to be a student here.
But it's because
I'm living a nightmare.
I'm trapped at N.Y.U.,
and it's too late to transfer.
So what's wrong with cheering
myself up with a little denial
- and a "Gossip Girl" blast or two?
- Nothing, I guess,
but you can always make it right
with whoever you take down online.
And who knows if Chuck's even gonna
have time to do that with Lily or not?
Morning, sunshine.
I've got the Dom 95, your favorite.
No, thank you.
And I much prefer Roederer nowadays.
Oh, I apologize. Nadine left
behind some of her intimates.
She must have wanted
an excuse to come back.
Or maybe she just left in a hurry.
If you're here to mock me,
I'm not in the mood...
Unless you have
some punishment in mind.
We've broken up, Chuck,
and frankly, I don't care what you do.
But I can't sit by
and just watch you avoid Lily.
I'm actually quite busy with work.
Well, you had time for Nadine.
Trust me, she was work.
And I promise you,
Lily is not sitting around,
wondering when she's going
to hear from Chuck bass.
Justify not seeing Lily
all you want.
You and I both know what this is.
You've lost Bart,
Elizabeth betrayed you, and the thought
of losing Lily terrifies you.
Please.
Spare me your N.Y.U.
freshman psych analysis.
Perhaps if you were at an Ivy,
You'd have better insight.
Spotted: B claiming
to be a co-ed at Columbia,
When everyone knows
she's a zero at N.Y.U.
Poor B.
First she lost Chuck
and now her dignity.
- "Gossip Girl" blast?
- No, it's nothing.
Look, Chuck, sleep with every
Nadine in town for all I care,
but don't close your heart to Lily.
You and I both know that in the end,
The person you'll end up
hurting the most is you.
Amalia, it's Blair.
Are you still waiting on me
to sign the lease?
Well, tell the girls it's a yes.
I'll take the apartment.
You make your bed, you lie in it, B.
Too bad yours is in
the East village.
Were you able to convince
your brother to come tonight?
No. And please
don't act like you care.
I'm sorry? I just got
off the phone with my dad.
Someone didn't want him in the building,
so they gave him a bad recommendation,
and it worked.
The board didn't approve him.
You're behind this, right?
- I am.
- How could you do that?
I don't expect you to understand, but
I felt it was the right thing to do.
I know you and my father used to hate
each other but that was a long time ago.
You are the only one
still having this fight.
- He has moved on.
- Is everything okay?
Rufus went to the board and blocked
dad for the apartment.
That's absurd. Rufus would never
do something like that.
I would, to protect my marriage.
I don't trust William's intention, and
I don't want him living under my roof.
Rufus, you're being
completely paranoid.
At first he tried he tried to
isolate you from your family,
and now he's moving to the building
closer to you.
I told you, he's moving in
to be close to the children.
All I see here is jealousy run amok.
Mom, come on. We should go.
It's probably best
if you don't come tonight.
- What are you two doing here?
- This is an alumni event.
Columbia puts aside a bunch
of tickets for students.
We'd invite you to join,
but they were very explicit.
No fake students allowed.
If you'll excuse me a moment, I should
go say hello to a few old colleagues.
- I'll be right back.
- Don't rush.
Do I want to know what you had
to promise him to get him to come?
No, it wasn't me.
It's not he even listens to me, and he
probably ran out of girls to have sex.
I... want to apologize.
My absence has been inexcusable.
Well, I know my situation brings
up a lot of issues for you.
You've had to deal
with so much loss.
But I'm not gonna lose you.
I'm here for you,
Every step of the way.
You look good, Lily. In fact, you look
better than good. You look great.
Thank you. I feel great.
So you had better be prepared
for a lifetime of family brunches,
because I'm not going anywhere.
Okay.
I bailed on the Columbia gala.
I was kind of in the mood
for watching a pretentious movie
I don't understand with you and Vanessa.
No Vanessa, but pretentious movie?
Check.
Not that I'm not thrilled to expose you
to the joys of Russian cinema,
but does this visit have anything
to do with the "Gossip Girl" blast?
Is it true?
Are you dealing?
I was,
When I was dating Damien, yeah.
- But, no, not anymore.
- This could so easily get back to dad.
I think it'd be better if
he heard it from you.
Are you insane?
I mean, you and I both know
that's a suicide mission.
Look...
If you want him to have
faith in you, Jenny,
maybe you need to have
a little faith in him.
Yeah, all right.
I'll go see if I can
dig out a dress from my old closet.
Maybe I can catch him at the gala.
You know, big crowd,
lots of witnesses.
Is everything okay
with you and Vanessa?
Yeah, well, at least I think it is.
It's been hard to say lately.
Maybe you need to have
a little faith, too.
- It's great to see you again.
- You, too.
- What a pleasure. Good to see you.
- Good to see you, Bob.
Dad, do you have a second?
I want to talk to you
about something.
Sure. Please sit.
You know, the contest that I won
at boarding school...
It was for drinking...
Absinthe.
And that was probably
one of my tamer nights.
The truth is I've had
a pretty wild past,
and I've been a part
of more than one scandal.
Serena, I don't care
about any of that.
I know.
I guess I was just...
Scared that...
Once mom gets better,
You may not wanna stick around
if you knew the real me.
Honey, I want nothing more
than to be a part
of all of your lives again.
I'm trying to figure out
how big a role I can play
without stepping on anybody's toes.
You know, I love Rufus...
But you're my dad.
He's not.
Aw, Serena finally
has the perfect
relationship with her daddy.
But will her dream come true
be Rufus' worst nightmare?
Oh, of course. The theme
of this evening seems to be torture.
You're not a fan of
university galas?
Quite the opposite.
I'm in my natural habitat.
It's torture
because it's at Columbia.
And by some cruel Twist of fate,
I go to N.Y.U.
It's like being locked out of Lanvin
on the day they get fall in.
Sorry, I don't mean to ramble on.
I'm Blair Waldorf.
Wait. I know that name.
- You read "Gossip Girl"?
- No, I read college applications.
I work in the admissions office
at Columbia.
I was just looking
at your application today.
I'm sorry?
It's not our policy to do this,
but e-mails go out tomorrow,
and you're standing right here,
welcome to Columbia.
Champagne, please.
Are you okay?
You got crazy eyes.
I think I just became
a Columbia student... for real.
It doesn't make any sense.
I never applied.
Oh, my God.
I cannot believe he actually did it.
Months ago, Chuck joked
about applying for you.
He said you had too much pride
to admit N.Y.U. was a mistake.
Looks like he actually did
something right for once.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
You're not at the gala?
I thought it'd be best
for everybody if I didn't go.
I see my father
is still working his magic.
- It's not all him.
- Yes, it is.
It's just that no one else sees it.
You make my mom happier than
all of her ex-husbands combined.
It should be you with her tonight,
not some guy who disappeared.
I am already in the tux.
- Elliot, what are you doing here?
- Your father invited me?
He said he didn't think
you had plans tonight.
Not me.
I hope it's okay.
It's okay to be mad at him,
but it's okay to let him try
to make it right, too.
All right. I'm heading out.
Wish me luck.
You don't need it.
You're the only one for her.
After Dr. Van Der Woodsen organized
the response
to the polio outbreak in India,
he moved on to Somalia,
where he served
as a field coordinator in Huddur.
While there, he oversaw everything
from shrapnel wounds
- to cancer to chronic illness.
- Rufus.
- I'm surprised to see you here.
- Holland, if you'll excuse me,
I'll catch up with you later.
I need to talk to Lily.
- What're you doing here?
- I'm sorry about today.
I don't want Will
to come between us.
I don't give a damn who lives where.
I just want to be with you.
He has done all of this while
continuing to build his reputation
as a leader in the progressive
treatments of cancer.
Lily looks amazing, doesn't she?
Being sick hasn't
slowed her down at all.
She is the picture of health.
Invaluable member of our team.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Dr. William Van Der Woodsen.
Thank you, Dean. Thank you.
I had another speech prepared
for you this evening,
but my beautiful daughter Serena
came to me,
and she was so
honest and brave,
that it made me realize that...
I need to be honest, too.
I made many personal sacrifices
to be a doctor,
but I never quite realized
until now that...
the greatest sacrifice of all
was my family.
So the most important thing
that I can say here tonight
is not to all of you,
but to them.
I made the biggest mistake
of my life walking out on you,
and I promise to do everything
in my power
to make it up to you,
to make it right again,
because I love you.
My, oh, my.
Did Dr. Van Der Woodsen
just make a public pass
at Rufus' wife?
Looks like this Doctor Without
Borders needs a few boundaries.
I guess you
were right about William,
but it doesn't matter
how he feels about me,
because I don't love him.
I love you, Rufus.
I know you're comfortable
with him, Lil, but I'm not.
I need you to find another doctor.
I understand why you don't trust him,
but surely, you trust me.
I don't want to fight
with you, Rufus.
We'll put it aside till tomorrow.
Let's get you home.
You know what?
Right now, more than anything,
I just need a quiet night, alone.
Please, just for tonight,
I need you to sleep at the loft.
Jenny Humphrey.
You bitch. You told me
you were selling me oxy,
but those pills were antibiotics.
Yeah, I didn't get high.
I got a yeast infection.
I can explain.
I came here to tell you.
Please save your breath.
Like I'm gonna believe you.
Get your things and come with me.
We're going home... to Brooklyn.
What did you want to talk about?
The producer from CNN
just flew into town,
- and I'm gonna meet her in 20 minutes.
- Take the internship.
I don't want us to be making decisions
based on fear.
All right?
So whatever happens,
we'll figure it out.
Thank you.
I got you some stationery
so we can write letters to each other
- while you're away.
- That is so romantic.
Maybe if we become
famous writers one day,
they'll publish 'em after we die.
Maybe, but don't let that stop you
from writing some of the dirty stuff.
Just a little bit.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
Not if you don't go.
You don't want to be late to meet
your new boss. Get out of here.
Thank you.
- Hey, Holland.
- Hey. Have you seen your mother?
No. I think she left.
Is everything okay?
If Dr. Van Der Woodsen loves your mother
as much as he said he did in the speech,
then there's something
she should know about Rufus.
Listen carefully, S.
Holland has a tale to tell.
Apparently, her upstairs neighbor
has been coming downstairs.
Serena, I thought you left.
Is everything okay?
Not really, no.
I heard
what you said in your speech,
if you want to fight
for mom, then do it.
I think you girls
got some misinformation.
I will be attending Columbia
in the fall.
That's awesome.
We have an extra room
in the apartment.
- Maybe you wanna move in with us?
- No. I don't live with the help.
And you wanted to see
a Blair Waldorf takedown?
Cross me again,
and you'll experience one firsthand.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's Jenny.
I want to talk to you about Lily.
Obviously, I'm not a doctor,
and it's kind of a long story
how I know this,
but there's something weird
about her medicine.
Elliot's the perfect mix
of smart and fun.
He speaks three languages, but he has
a subscription to "People" magazine.
I invited dad over
for some hot chocolate.
I hope that's okay.
- If it's a bad idea, I can...
- No, it's okay.
William, join us.
Rufus. It's Serena.
Is your mom there?
Yeah, she's here.
She's just really tired right now.
I'll let her know you called.
They say that family are the people
who will always take you in.
But what if instead,
they shut the door?
I was just telling mom
about my date with Elliot.
We had a great time.
Thank you.
- Who was that?
- It was just Blair.
Or even worse,
let someone else take your place?
What do you say, Serena?
Who's your daddy?
X.O.X.O., Gossip Girl.