I loved you.
You loved me  ?
I hope i'm not interrupting.
We are so hard on you
Because we want you to challenge
yourself, to be your own person.
(Blair) how exactly did you get
graham to ditch jenny for kira?
I told graham that
what happens at camp suisse
Doesn't stay at camp suisse.
It's about who you've become.
I liked you because you were
different from everyone else.
I'm sorry, eric, but it's over.
(Olivia) you were looking at vanessa
Like you've never looked at me.
You were the one that needed
To kiss her again,
to realize for yourself
That your feelings for her are real.
My wife isn't who i thought she was
And neither is my marriage.
I don't know anything anymore.
I just know i don't want
to be alone.
(Blair) you went looking
for your father?
Yeah, and i-I found him, too,
but he didn't want to see me.
And who am i?
That's a secret
i'll never tell.
You know you love me.
X.O.X.O., gossip girl.
Thanksgiving began
when the pilgrims and indians
Came together to share
the bountiful harvest.
Okay, i've got the stuffing.
And, jenny, you have
the sweet potatoes, as usual.
Eric, what's your tradition?
I, um, don't think we van der woodsens
Have any thanksgiving traditions.
Serena apologizes, but she won't be able to
make it tomorrow.
I stand corrected.
She has to work on thanksgiving?
Well, tripp has his staff
Volunteering
at a soup kitchen,
And with scott and his parents
at the cape,
And my mother
still unable to travel,
It looks like it's just
going to be us and daniel.
Would you mind if i
just walked down to grace's
And ordered
one of their turkey dinners
So we don't have to cook?
Um, actually, lily, dad was just--
Thinking the same thing.
Keep it small, hassle-Free.
(Whispers) thank you.
Sorry, rufus, but you can't
really blame her.
Our thanksgivings tend to end
with french fries at a diner
And someone having been in a
mental institution.
Yeah, but why don't we show her
that this thanksgiving's gonna be different?
Well, there's nothing
we can do about serena,
But i can set up a video chat
on my netbook
And give grandma a place at the table.
A cece you can unplug. That's perfect.
Let's go give it a test run.
Hey, why don't you invite jonathan?
Jonathan and i aren't really happening anymore.
What? Since when?
A while now.
Well, what happened?
Let's not talk about it.
On the upper east side,
that tradition is upheld
With a bountiful harvest
of secrets, lies and scandal.
(Man) ?Ooh ?
(Chimes)
?Ooh ?
Good afternoon, congressman.
I have the press schedule
you asked for.
(Lowers voice) so did
you talk to maureen yet?
Last night.
She wasn't too happy about it,
But she agreed to the divorce.
Maureen's coming into town
so our people
Can write a joint statement
explaining the split.
Of course the public
won't get the real reason.
And the real reason is?
I'm sorry.
I just need to hear
That you're not leaving her
because of me.
Maureen orchestrated a fraud
to win the election.
If you walked away right now,
my decision wouldn't change.
But...
I hope you won't.
I have to.
You're married, and as long
as you are, we can't do this.
Serena.
Could our self-Imposed exile
start after tomorrow?
I can't bear the thought
of spending thanksgiving alone.
Well, i had a feeling
you might say that,
So i already told my mom
That you're making me work
at the soup kitchen all day.
But this means
pay-Per-View movies
And room service at my hotel,
And that's it.
I'll be good.
15 hours It's a record.
You haven't mentioned serena once.
Well, for much of that time,
i was asleep,
But since you're asking,
I've decided i'm putting her
out of my mind.
Besides, i have a far more cunning and
deceptive adversary To deal with.
When does your mother land again?
20 minutes. Flying in from paris
to escort me back?
How dumb does she think i am?
She has some bomb
She wants to drop on me
in a controlled environment,
Surrounded by air marshals
and french people.
Amazing. Your holiday paranoia
truly knows no bounds.
Precedence is not paranoia.
When i called daddy last night
And started asking him
questions,
He clammed up faster
than rihanna.
I need to find out
my mother's secret
Before boarding that plane.
Oh, i didn't know the empire
Had hourly rates.
One van der bilt isn't enough?
I'm not having an affair
with tripp,
And since you're gonna
find out anyway,
He's leaving his wife,
and it's not for me.
Then what are you, exactly,
An 18-Year-Old,
blonde coincidence?
Call me in six months, when he
meets his next "coincidence,"
That is, if he even leaves
his wife, which i highly doubt.
(Nate) i told you
it would end badly.
Threesomes, man--
Don't believe the hype.
Yeah, but here's the thing--
Olivia said she was leaving
Because she thought that
i-I had feelings for vanessa.
Do you?
H-How--How would i even know?
How'd olivia know?
Well, she--She said
she saw a look on my face.
Wait. You mean...
you mean during?
(Laughs) oh, if this is not your
next story for "the new yorker,"
I'm sending it out to
an entirely different magazine.
Oh, thank you. That really helps.
Oh, relax.
Chances are you're right.
It's just the threesome talking.
Exactly. Yes. Say--
Say more things like that.
Because i mean, this is--
This is just a phase.
Okay. All right. This is good.
So you around for thanksgiving?
Uh, no, actually.
I, um...
I've been going through
some--Some mixed feelings
For someone as well,
so i called my grandfather,
And i think i'm gonna head out
to the estate
And try and patch things up.
All right, well, tell him i said hello,
And that thanks to last
year's the longest yard,
My knee can now predict the weather.
(Elevator bell dings)
Will do, man. Peace.
Hey. Wanna go for a walk?
Hi. Sorry. I got
in a huge fight with my mom,
And i didn't sign the form
to stay in the dorm over break.
So could i crash with you
for a while?
What's with the face?
Oh. No. (Laughs) what?
No, this is my, um,
my surprised, happy face.
Uh, make yourself at home.
Lily told us you still weren't
well enough to travel,
So we thought video chat
would, uh, be a great way
To have you at thanksgiving tomorrow.
I'm fine.
Lily told me you weren't doing
anything for thanksgiving.
Well, i-I mean we're not
doing anything major,
But, uh, i'm sure after
everything you've been through,
She--She didn't want
to make you feel obligated.
(Gasps) oh.
Oh, how, um,
how thoughtful.
I'd love to be there
in person.
But let's keep it as
a surprise, shall we?
(Singsong voice)
see you soon.
(Beep)
(Cell phone ringing)
(Elevator bell dings)
(Ring)
"Hello" is the word
you're looking for.
I am sorry, miss blair.
(Beep)
i not talking with vanya,
And now he not stop calling
and texting
And tweeting
and writing on wall.
Lionel tribbey? That's
my mother's estate attorney.
"Please approve all changes
and return immediately."
She's changing her will.
I knew there was a secret.
(Elevator bell ding, doors open)
Darling, i'm home!
Mother!
(Clicks teeth)
Is that for me?
Yes.
Mm.
Why don't we open it now?
No, tea first.
I have the most amazing
lapsang souchong
From mariage frères.
(Nate) come on, serena.
You go off with tripp
after leaving me in a bar,
And then i hear through
the van der bilt grapevine
That... tripp's asking maureen
for a divorce.
You expect me to believe
that nothing happened?
It was one kiss,
And it was a huge mistake that
i don't intend on repeating.
I promise.
Fine.
(Cell phone rings)
(Ring)
Can i call you back?
I have to cancel on tomorrow.
Maureen was a mess
when she got here.
She kept asking if
something else was going on.
She wants to have
thanksgiving together.
I have to go.
(Snaps cell phone shut)
Sorry.
Hey, do you have plans
for thanksgiving?
I know it's last minute.
No, i don't, actually.
Well, how about 3:00
at my mom's?
And please bring something
stronger than rufus' cider.
(Laughs)
Oh.
Oh, nice coat.
Oh, you, too. Oh, my god.
Maureen.
Lily.
Oh, i am so glad to see you.
How is d.C.?
So much to get ready,
But tripp insisted we spend
the holidays here.
Speaking of, i'd love to know
why he has my daughter
Working on thanksgiving.
She said she's volunteering
at a soup kitchen with him.
I've never seen her work
these kinds of hours.
Is it always like this with him?
No. His schedule's been
Especially busy
these past few weeks.
This is probably
an overstep,
But do you think
you could convince him
To spend part of
your thanksgiving with us,
You know, force my daughter
to have a little family time?
Uh-Oh. Looks like
someone's "small" thanksgiving
Might just have a big problem.
Yes. Yes,
we'd--We'd love to come.
Great.
May the lord make us
truly thankful
For what we are about
to receive.
Then she starts lecturing
the poor cashier
That thanksgiving is
nothing more
Than a corporate agenda
of the food industry
Masquerading
as family sentiment.
Oh, you know what? That reminds
me. Um, if my dad asks,
We followed the homemade recipe
for his pie crust to the letter.
Sorry for unloading. I just
haven't had anyone to vent to
Since olivia left.
Have you talked to her
Since she went to do
"bitches of eastwick"?
Uh, no.
Hey, everything happens
for a reason, right?
Yeah. Yeah, apparently.
There it is again.
That face.
What? Oh, come on. There's, uh,
there's no--There's no face.
What is going on? You've been
quiet ever since i got here.
(Knock on door)
Who's that?
Don't--Don't hate me for this.
I'm here. I won't hate
you, 'cause you'll be dead.
Don't be mad at dan.
He was just trying to help.
Look, i know
i don't do holidays well,
But if you give me
another chance,
I promise i can
make it up to you.
I called rufus
on the way over here,
And he said we're more than
welcome to join him.
What?
We can have the thanksgiving
that you want. What do you say?
Fine
Great. Thank you.
Make yourself at home.
I'll give her one last shot.
If it doesn't work, consider me
moved in for the holidays.
(Elevator bell dings)
Tripp,
what are you doing here?
You wouldn't return
my calls.
So you're stalking me now?
Yes, serena,
i'm stalking you.
I thought our relationship
wasn't complicated enough,
So...
And get this--
Lily ran into maureen
And invited us
for thanksgiving,
So it looks like
We'll be spending tomorrow
together after all.
What?
Tripp, won't that be weird?
It doesn't have to be.
And besides, now we get
to spend some time together.
(The raveonettes' "last dance"
playing)
That's all i care about--
Even with everyone else around--
To be near you one last time.
?I rush to intensive care ?
Why does this have
to be so hard?
(Elevator bell dings)
We're almost to your floor.
You want me to come in?
Yes, which is why you can't.
?If this is the last dance,
i wanna know ?
?I wanna know ?
But then again, these elevators
can take forever.
?
?Baby ?
(Laughs) cyrus, enough.
Yes, enough.
I will. I will tell her.
I will. All right.
Good-Bye.
Cyrus says that he misses you
and loves you.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
(Elevator bell dings)
Sorry. I had to run out
before store closes.
I bring babka and make decaf.
You have to be up early
for flight.
No babka, dorota.
I have to turn in now.
It's 3:00 in the morning for
me. I should sleep early, too.
I agreed to work
at miss lily's tomorrow.
Big thanksgiving for them,
all the sudden,
But she offer me
time and a half, so...
Good night, dear.
Wait!
I have a wonderful idea.
Why don't we spend thanksgiving
with lily and serena?
What are you talking about?
You know how much
i love thanksgiving,
The parade on tv.
I'm 19. Childhood memories
are slipping away already.
Well,
let me at least call lily,
See if it's all right.
I am not getting on that plane
until i know my mother's secret,
And her secret is
in that envelope.
What are you clutching?
Uh, miss eleanor asked me to
pick up some things for paris.
It's private.
You know what isn't?
The i.N.S. Tip line.
Oh, my god.
That's why she's
changing her will?
My mother's pregnant.
Gratulacje.
Hey.
Yo.
I just came from a meeting
with hotel security.
Elevator cameras caught
a hotel guest
Pulling the emergency stop
To have a make-Out session
with her boyfriend.
(Chuckles) you just love
your job, don't you?
It was serena and tripp.
Well...
I guess he's not leaving maureen
over "hudson hero."
Though i bet that's
what he's telling serena.
It's less messy that way,
when he bolts in six months.
Come on.
How often does the other woman
get a "happily ever after"?
Someone needs to get through
to her before it's too late.
You know serena. Whoever tries
better bring a sledgehammer.
?Cool yourself,
you are flush red ?
Oh, dorota.
Happy thanksgiving.
When did you sneak in?
I took service elevator.
Oh, you don't have
to do that.
Vanya's on duty. I'm sure
he'd love to see you.
Mother.
Surprise.
(Eric) surprise!
Hello, lily.
This is the mystery guest?
Well, when rufus called
And found out that i was
feeling well enough to travel,
We thought we'd surprise you.
How wonderful.
Opening the door is his job, mom.
That's why he's called
the doorman.
It's not derogatory.
Rufus, thank you again so much for inviting us.
Uh, cece,
this is gabriela abrams
And her daughter vanessa. This is cece, lily's mom.
Lovely to see you. Hello, daniel.
You're looking well, cece.
I am, aren't i?
This table is exquisite.
Well, lily, it looks like we,
um, have a lot to talk about,
As do you and rufus.
What's the matter, mother?
Is the smoked salmon
making you nauseous?
No. No, i'm just a little
jet-Lagged. That's all.
Oh, charles, brut ros?
It's my favorite.
That's what blair said
when she suggested i pick it up.
Yes, mother, you simply
must have some tonight.
I'm not in the champagne mood.
But you love champagne.
I didn't say i didn't love it.
I said i'm not in the mood.
(Elevator bell dings)
Happy thanksgiving.
You, too.
I was just telling tripp
What a pleasant surprise it was
when i ran into lily.
We're really appreciate
the invitation.
Yes, especially since
you and tripp
Have been working
all those long hours.
Serena's been a great help.
You must be so proud. He has
such a strong work ethic.
Yes. That's him.
So where should i put my coat?
Here. Let me take that.
Thank you.
Um...
There's nate.
I should say hello.
The hardest part's over.
We'll get through this. Okay?
(Elevator bell dings,
doors open)
Serena, my dear,
happy thanksgiving.
Thank you. I didn't know you
guys were coming, either of you.
Surprise. Isn't this
just the best holiday?
Hello, congressman.
Where's your lovely wife?
Is it me or is my daughter just
getting crazier and crazier?
Hmm.
A little thanksgiving
proclamation--
You two ever play grab ass
in my elevator again,
And serena will be staying
at an airport marriott.
Happy holidays.
Hi.
Are tripp and serena
having an affair?
Nate, please.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
I just want him back.
I'm sorry, maureen.
But i think i have a way we can
end it quickly and quietly.
I don't know
if you want to see this.
If it will end it... i do.
(Sighs)
Where are you dragging me?
Haven't you ever heard of a whispered aside?
What did eric do at cotillion?
What do you mean?
I mean i invited jonathan for thanksgiving,
And he texted me back,
saying he was surprised
That eric and i were still
even friends after that night.
Please. You, of all people, respect
a well-Thought-Out sabotage.
Although you came
through unscathed,
Eric's plan was solid.
Eric's plan?
Stealing your escort,
leaving you stranded
At the top of the stairs--
It was all his idea.
By the way, how do
you find having a sibling,
Someone whose sole purpose
on earth is
To compete for your parents'
love and attention?
(Rufus) uh, if everyone could
please find their seats...
(Jason derulo and imogen heap)
?Mm, whatcha say? ?
?Mm,
that you only meant well? ?
?Well, of course you did ?
?Mm, whatcha say? ?
I am so happy we are sitting
next to each other, rufus.
Excuse me.
Cece, tell me everything about
rufus and lily's wedding.
I was boycotting
the floral industry,
Or i would have been there myself.
Tragically, i wasn't invited.
Apparently my son-In-Law felt
it better if i didn't attend.
Mom, it's none of your business.
You--You didn't want lily's own mother at your wedding?
Fifth wedding. But still.
Lily told me you were still too sick to travel.
Thank you, but, i mean,
I've been in remission since the middle of august.
But lily didn't come home till october.
?When the roof caved in
and the truth came out ?
Oh. Perhaps i'm--I'm--I'm wrong.
It's hard to keep track.
(Laughs) wine?
?We'll be living so large ?
?I'll do anything for you ?
?So tell me, girl ?
?Mm, whatcha say? ?
(Lowered voice) why does my mom
have to stick her nose
Into everyone's business?
Oh, come on. Cece's heart pumps secrets and gin.
It's not--It's not your mom's fault.
You've been defending her
all day and ignoring me.
What's going on with you?
And you're making that face again.
No. All right, look, this is getting ridiculous.
(Vanessa) jenny, have you
ever heard of someone
Starting to make a brand-New face at 19?
I don't know. Ask eric. He's mastered 2.
Excuse me?
Blair told me you were responsible
For sabotaging me
at cotillion.
What, you don't have
anything to say to me?
Your sweet potatoes
are bland.
?Mm, whatcha say? ?
?Mm, that you only meant well?
Well, of course you did ?
?Mm, whatcha say? ?
?Whatcha say? Whatcha say? ?
?Mm,
that it's all for the best ?
?Because it is ?
?Mm, what you say? ?
?Mm, that you
only meant well? ?
Mother, here's some camembert
from artisanal.
It's unpasteurized. Don't you want some?
That's enough. What has gotten into you?
Into me?
Try you. You're the one
who's pregnant.
?Knowing that i let
our love go ?
(Glass clinks)
Lily and i would like
to thank you all
For coming to our first
thanksgiving as a family.
Now before she gets back,
i'd like to tell you a joke
That i tell every year, which
lily has expressly forbidden.
A group of pilgrims
decide to start a band...
How can you two sit there,
smiling?
After several of the prominent elders...
don't you have any sense of decency?
Maureen--
No, not one second more.
(Rufus) the young pilgrim
says, "can i try?"
Tripp and i are going to
grow old together,
Without you.
Or i make my own statement.
Where did you get that?
(Sighs)
(rufus) ...blow them all away,
in a--In a style...
He'll be a political joke,
and you'll be a punch line.
Your affair ends now.
When he's done, one
of the older pilgrims says...
serena.
And he says, "that's what
i call plymouth rock!"
?'Cause things ain't right ?
?'Cause when the roof caved in
and the truth came out ?
?I just didn't know what to do ?
?But when i become a star,
we'll be living so large ?
You know what?
Why don't we just eat?
I lost my appetite.
?Baby, whatcha say? ?
?Mm, whatcha say? ?
And i want pie.
?Mm,
that you only meant well? ?
?Well, of course you did,
mm, whatcha say? ?
Kids.
Oh, and what makes you
an expert?
?Mm, whatcha say? ?
?Mm, that you only meant well?
Well, of course you did ?
I'm so glad you invited me,
rufus.
Cheers.
?What--What--What--
What did you say? ?
Mom, i can explain.
It's not what it looks like.
So you're not having an affair
with a married man?
No, i'm--I'm--I'm not having an affair.
I saw you kissing him, serena.
A kiss that
we didn't even have
Until after he decided
to leave his wife.
Do you know what it feels like
to be left? Because i do.
Well, it isn't like it was
with you.
Tripp actually cares
about me.
Oh, you think so?
Well, why don't you take a look
at what he's doing?
Leaving someone who,
up until today,
Thought the exact same thing.
Walk away, serena.
Until you do, you're not
welcome in this home.
So i don't get it.
You hate me,
But you've been pretending to be
my friend this entire time?
That's pretty much it, yeah.
Why wouldn't you just tell me
you were mad?
At least then
we could fight about it.
No, you lost
any rights to honesty
When you chose being queen
over our friendship.
That's not what happened.
Every time
you did something bad,
I defended you to jonathan.
He got sick of me
Making excuses for you
all the time,
So i decided to try to beat you
at your own game.
That was a mistake.
I figured if i could
take you down just once,
So you could know how it feels
to be the one getting egged,
Then maybe you'd realize
what you'd become,
And everything could go back
to the way it was.
And you lost jonathan
because of it.
I lost everything.
Not me.
Not if you apologize.
You say that now,
But you've bec  ome
a totally different person,
And as a result, so have i.
Apparently i became someone
That jonathan no longer wanted
to be with,
And for that, i blame you.
You told kira
she had to watch her back.
Well, now you have
to watch yours.
There you are.
Mother, how could you?
No offense to cyrus,
But do you think the world
really needs another aaron rose?
Blair, you are completely off base.
Thanksgiving always has secrets.
And in your case,
it's a miracle.
I am not pregnant.
I did come back to change my
will to reflect my new property.
Cyrus and i are moving
to paris full time.
But you love new york.
You always said anyone
who lives anywhere else
Is fooling themselves.
Perhaps it's time for me
to step back
And let you make manhattan
your own.
Besides, cyrus and i did find
a lovely penthouse flat
On the ile st.-Louis,
Right across from
your favorite restaurant.
Rôtisserie du beaujolais?
Mm.
Oh, that poulet rôti is
reason enough to move.
(Laughs)
Mother...
I'm sorry
For being so crazy.
You pregnant?
I mean, come on.
We both know you closed
for business a long time ago.
But then whose test was it?
Test?
Miss waldorfs...
I know dorota's upstairs.
She won't return my calls.
Please, tell her
whatever i did, i am sorry.
Oh, my god.
I'll be honest.
This isn't the thanksgiving
i had hoped for.
Look, i don't--I don't mean
to be presumptuous,
But don't you think
it's a little odd
That lily didn't
tell you the truth
About when her mother
went into remission?
I trust lily. When she's ready
to explain, she will.
Yes. Yes, but--
You know, i think i need
more whipped cream.
What is wrong with you?
I care about rufus.
I was being honest.
Just like you being honest when
i laid out my entire paycheck
To get us tickets to see "hair,"
and you told me
You'd rather spend the whole
show talking to a homeless man?
He was a vet.
This is who i am.
I care about people.
You know, um,
it's thanksgiving.
Yeah. I'm starting to think
this was a mistake.
Maybe i should go.
For once, mom, i agree.
Gabriela--Mm.
I'm sorry.
I could only imagine
what you're feeling.
What we did--
What i did was wrong.
I never meant to hurt anyone,
And--And i hurt you.
I promise
i'll never see tripp again.
What are you doing in here?
I wanted to go to my room,
But then i forgot
it's not my room anymore.
What do you want?
Chuck told me what happened.
You did the right thing.
Then why do i feel so bad?
Doing the right thing takes
courage and strength.
At least,
that's what i've heard.
(Chuckles)
And anything that hard is
only made more difficult
By not having your best friend
by your side.
I'm sorry you had
to go through it alone.
I'm sorry, too,
For everything.
What are you doing
this weekend?
Eating leftovers and feeling horrible.
No, you're coming to paris.
What? I am?
My mom and i are catching the red-Eye tonight.
If you're gonna be sad, you
might as well be sad in paris.
Chuck can shop for sweaters
with harold and roman,
And we can wander notre dame,
and spend time,
Just the two of us,
like we haven't for so long.
Is your passport here?
In the safe upstairs.
(Laughs) then you're ready
to go!
Come on. Allons-Y.
(Laughs)
Oh. I'm sorry.
I missed thanksgiving.
There's still dessert.
You're wonderful.
Why did you stay with cece
after she got better
Instead of coming home to me?
Well, um, my mother and i
were finally connecting.
I think,
faced with her illness,
She--She became a different
person. She was loving and kind.
And i wanted to stay
and enjoy this person
For as long as i could.
You could have told me that.
I know,
and i should have, but i...
I knew it wa
Leaving you here, in charge
of the kids and everything,
And, um, so i lied.
And then i just continued to lie
to cover it up.
So that's it then?
You love me so much
you couldn't let me go?
Well, you weren't supposed to
hear that, mother.
I'm glad i did.
I now have a witness
If she ever tries to tell me
how insufferable i am.
I'm gonna go clear the table.
(Sighs)
Thank you, mother.
So i take it
you didn't tell him
About your little trip
this summer?
No, and i'd like
to keep it that way.
When will you learn, my love,
That some secrets
can't stay hidden?
Well, this one will.
Let's hope so.
(Gasps) no, no, no.
I-I eat later.
This isn't for you.
It's for vanya.
Tom colicchio live in building.
I'm sure he sent plate already.
Mr. Rufus good cook,
but not top chef.
Hmm.
This plate is
the plate he wants.
Oh. You are going to have
to talk to him eventually.
Not for two or three months at least.
Dorota--
You not understand.
We not married.
My parents start
next polish-Soviet war.
Russia once again not victor,
believe me.
Good luck.
I-I don't want to do this!
Well, i guess it's a good thing
you travel light.
Look, i-I appreciate
your concern, dan.
I do, but it's a waste of time.
We're--We're too far apart.
Well, y-You're not as different
as you think.
Did you know she petitioned
to keep a historic bar
From closing in brooklyn
last year?
And she spent
the end of the summer
Rebuilding community gardens
in alphabet city.
She loves you. She does.
I think she just wishes
You'd spend half the time
on her
That you do on these people
you don't even know.
And when you do, trust me,
i-I really think you'll see
How, uh, how amazing she is.
I-I-I-I can't believe
i didn't see this till now.
Mm, what?
Oh, you're in love with her.
It's all over your face.
No. (Laughs)
No. That's, um...
Yeah.
I'll, uh, i'll let you guys
be alone.
I can't believe what you did.
You had a choice, tripp.
Seems like you made it.
What do you mean?
Now thanks to you, maureen
can cause a huge scandal.
I lose everything.
No, you lose your career. Tripp,
you've already lost serena.
The fact that this is
just now occurring to you
Makes me pretty sure
i did the right thing.
Why didn't you tell him the truth?
That is the truth. Okay, serena deserves
Someone who would sacrifice
anything to be with her.
Even if that means
stealing a security tape
From his best friend's
business?
Tell her how you feel.
Give her a chance
To be with a guy
who does deserve her.
(Strums note)
Gibson guitar,
Vinyl collection...
I guess this really isn't
bart's office anymore.
(Beep)
yeah, except i'm sure my mom
Hasn't given rufus
the combo to the safe yet.
(Beep)
Well, now that bart's not around
to keep files on everybody,
Maybe you guys don't
need one.
What are you still doing here?
I couldn't leave.
I could help you out with that.
The elevator comes,
You get on it, and we never see you again.
I don't care if maureen outs our affair.
I don't care if they run
me out of congress for it.
All i care about... is you.
If i'm gonna leave maureen,
Which...
i just told her i am...
I want to do it
with you by my side.
I'm gonna be downstairs,
waiting in my car, to go.
I hope you'll join me.
Wow. I didn't think
he had it in him.
What do i do?
Go.
I love you.
I love you, too.
What is that?
It's from my father.
It's postmarked from weeks ago,
and it's been opened.
(Eleanor) blair, we have to go.
(Whispers) go. It's okay.
I need to be alone.
Where are you going?
Tripp and his wife have left,
And you, um, you did the right thing.
Actually, tripp is divorcing maureen.
He's waiting for me downstairs.
We're going away together.
I thought we understood
each other, serena.
We do. I'm not welcome
in your home, so...
You're still responsible
for breaking up his marriage.
Don't go through with this.
It is a huge mistake,
One that you will regret
for the rest of your life.
You want to talk to me
about mistakes?
You don't get to judge me...
Ever again.
After the yelling died down,
i thought i'd take a chance
You might be ready
for some pie and coffee.
Well, my daughter and i had
Our first hear-To-Heart talk
in--In ever.
(Laughs) and thank you.
Of course.
It's all because of you.
But don't worry.
We're gonna move to a hotel
for the rest of the weekend.
Oh, you--You don't have
to leave.
I mean, you're welcome to stay,
uh, as long as you like.
Okay.
About what i said before--
You gave me some great advice.
I'm going to return the favor.
When vanessa told you her
feelings all those years ago,
You broke her heart,
And your friendship
almost didn't recover.
So unless you're sure
That my daughter is
who you want to be with,
I suggest you keep your feelings
to yourself.
Because if you break her heart
this time,
Your friendship won't survive.
And that would be a tragedy,
Because you are
a great friend for her.
Thank you.
Hey, mom. Paul hoffman,
that guy that i told you about--
He just texted me,
and his parents are in town.
He wants to meet for a drink.
Do you want to go?
I don't know. Dan, do i?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I--She likes him a lot.
I think you should meet him.
Great.
All right. Let's do it.
Yay!
(Horn honks)
Serena!
Excuse me if i didn't say good-Bye,
But after what you did--
Don't go.
What?
Don't go with tripp.
Nate.
Okay, i know what i did was wrong,
And i'm sorry.
I just--I did it because...
'Cause ever since last week,
Ever since three years ago
when you left...
Please don't get in the car.
Just stay here with me.
Just give me a chance.
Serena.
You coming?
(Paramore's "the only exception"
playing)
You'll come visit us in vermont?
I will.
Thanks for everything.
Another thanksgiving
has come and gone...
You know what?
I like your new face.
(Chuckles)
(Chuckles) it's cute.
And what am im most thankful for?
The truth.
Sometimes it's the truth
you've been trying not to face
Or the truth that will change
your life...
?And we've got to find
other ways ?
?To make it alone ?
?Keep a straight face ?
?And i've always lived
like this ?
?Keeping a comfortable... ?
Sometimes it's the truth
that's a long time coming...
?And up until now
i had sworn to myself ?
?That i'm content ?
Or the truth you prayed would
never see the light of day.
Lil?
Lily, have you seen
the other wedding album?
I want to show cece
the pictures
Of me jamming with kim and thurston.
Oh. Um...
You okay?
Oh, yes, everything's fine.
Um, i'll grab it.
?You are the only exception ?
Hey, do you mind if i stay?
Yes.
But that's why i love you.
(Sighs)
Come on.
Let's go get drunk.
Some truths may not be heard
the way we hoped they would.
(Speaks indistinctly)
But they linger long
after they've been said.
?Leave me with some kind
of proof it's not a dream ?
?Oh ?
?You are the only exception ?
Oh, i didn't see you,
miss van der bilt.
Sorry, dorota.
I forgot my coat.
It's been kind of
a crazy night.
Please tell lily and rufus
everything was wonderful.
?And i'm on my way
to believing ?
But the kind of truth
i'm most thankful for--
The one you never see coming
that falls right into your lap.
X.O.X.O., gossip girl.
Sync by ReHelen
www.addic7ed.com