Gossip Girl
Here--
Your One And Only Source Into The Scandalous Lives
Of Manhattan's Elite.
At What Point Do We Admit
That No Matter How Much
We Want It Or How Hard We Try...
It's Just Not Working.
You're Going Back To Hudson,
Aren't You?
Yeah.
Rufus, Why Are You Calling?
I Miss You.
Mom,
You Cannot Date Bart Bass.
You Said A Moment Ago
You Didn't Care Who It Was.
He Raised Chuck.
Would You Do Me The Honor
Of Being My Wife?
I Think You Like Dan ???
Just Thought I Should
Let You Know Someone's Watching.
Chuck, You Are
Not Answering My Calls.
Please, For The Love Of God,
Do Not Tell Anybody About Us.
Don't Worry. B.Who Would I Tell?(From Chuck)
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
And Who Am I?
That's A Secret
I'll Never Tell.
You Know You Love Me.
X.O.X.O., Gossip Girl.
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译:稀饭cake 小白
校对:小白
时间轴:小白家属 小白弟弟 小白苦力
On The Upper East Side,
It's Easy To Think  That The World
Is Exactly As It Appears--
Refined, Elegant, Imposing.
But Sometimes,
All It Takes Is A Little Key
To Open The Door
To The Wild Side.
Nate.
Why Have You
Been Avoiding Me?
Avoiding You? What?
Ever Since
I Got Back From Monaco,
You've Been--You're Not
Returning My Calls Or My Texts.
I've Barely Seen You.
Really? I Don't Recall.
Oh? Well, Do You Recall That
Night After The Debutante Ball
Yes, I Do.
Blair?
What Are You Doing?
This.
Good Catching Up.
Enough With The Blackmail.
Aren't You Bored Already?
I Can't Avoid Nate Forever.
Excuse Me.
I Didn't Say Forever.
Just Until The Sight
Of The Two Of You Together
Doesn't Turn My Stomach.
And When Will That Be?
Only Time Will Tell,
I'm Afraid.
So Unless You Want
Dear Nathaniel To Know How
You Lost Your Virginity To Me
In The Back Of A Moving Vehicle,
I Encourage Patience
And Restraint.
Isn't There Someone Else
You Can Torture?
Probably,
But I Choose You.
Why Don't I Turn That, Uh,
One-Piece Into A No-Piece?
Find A Floatie
To Talk To, Chuck.
You Know,
If My Dad And Your Mom
Come Back From South Africa
Tomorrow Engaged,
We'll Be Brother And Sister.
And You Know What They Say--
The Family That Plays Together
Stays Together.
Ah, Incest--
The Universal Taboo.
One Of The, Um, Only Ones
You Haven't Violated.
Well, I'm Game If You Are.
Dan Humphrey, Age 17,
Enjoying An Exotic Meal
Of Cheerios
On An Exciting
Saturday Night In.
Come On. Be Interesting.
You Don't Want Me
To Move Back To Vermont, Do You?
No,
But If Your Whole Future
Depends Getting This Grant
For Your Documentary,
I-I Really, Really Think
You Should Find A New Subject.
Absolutely Not.
The Outsider Goes Inside--
A Likable Everyman's Pursuit
Of His Dream Girl
Begins His Descent
Into The Bowels Of Hell.
This Is Mythic Stuff.
Okay,
Not Big On The Soundtrack.
Whatever Movie He's Scoring
Sounds Depressing.
Yeah, I Think It's A Biopic.
Try Listening To That
For Three Weeks Straight.
But Before Christmas, My Dad
Hadn't Finished A Song In Years,
So I Really Don't Have The Heart
To Ask Him To Stop.
Well, I Do.
Hey, Serena.
Yes! Finally Some Action.
Hey. What Are You Up To...
Besides Missing Me?
Oh, Uh, Just Wondering
If You're Missing Me.
Aw!
Well, Of Course I Am,
At This Party That Would Be
A Lot More Fun If You Were Here.
Party? I Thought It Was
A Quiet Night With Blair,
Your Last Night At Her Place
Before Your Mom Comes Home?
Yeah, We Were, And Then Kati And Is Showed Up,
And We All Went Out,
And We Ran Into Some People
And Then Ended Up Here.
Where--Where's Here?
719 E. 82nd Stre.
Wait A Second. That's, Um...
That's School, Is It Not?
Bring Your Bathing Suit!
You're Swimming?
No, You Hung Up.
So What Will It Be, Dan--
Cheerios And Chaucer
Or An Illegal Party
At Your Prep School Pool With
Your High Society Girlfriend
And Her Nasty Cohorts?
Dad?
Vanessa And I
Are--Are Going Out.
All Right.
Well, Uh,
If You Wanted To Get The Perfect Shot Of Me
Feeling Like An Outsider,
Then I'm Ready
For My Close-Up.
Dan! Oh!
Hey.
Hey!
Hehe Vanessa.
Hey.
Come On, Guys.
Help!
Call The Ambulance!
Call An Ambulance.
Someone Call 9-1-1.
Hi. Hi. We--We Need--
We Need An Ambulance.
Yeah, A-A Kid--
He--He Hit His Head,
And--And He Fell In The Pool.
It--It's 719, Uh,
East 82nd Street.
Thanks To The Cell Phone
That Somebody Left Behind,
We've Got Plenty Of Evidence
Of Who Was At The Party.
Lucky For You, Andrew Collins
Is Going To Be Fine.
Unlucky For You, We Need
To Hold Someone Responsible.
Ms. Queller?
Hello.
I'm Ms. Queller,
The New Headmistress
At Constance.
It's Unfortunate That We Meet
Under These Circumstances.
But I Look Forward
To Getting To Know Each And Every One Of You.
I've Already
Talked To Your Parents...
At Least, Those I Could Reach,
And Look Forward To Reading
Your Personal Essays--
10,000 Words
Describing How You Came To Be
On School Property After Hours,
Using Alcohol And Drugs,
Where A Fellow Student
Almost Died.
In Other Words,
What The Hell Is Wrong With You?
I'll Also Be Conducting
One-On-One Interviews
Until I Discover Ho Broke Into The Pool
And Initiated The Party.
That Person Will Be Expelled.
If That Person
Is Not Identified,
Then You'll All Face Expulsion.
So We All Know
How This Works.
Look, No One Talks,
No One Gets Into Trouble.
Who Did Break In, Anyway?
I Guess We Don't He To Worry About Nate
Cracking Under Pressure.
So Are We All Agreed?
Agreed.
Look, Blair, I-I Know You Have
Your Sights Set On Yale,
But This--This Skull And Bones
Stuff Is A Bit Much,
Don't You Think?
Maybe, But It Works...
Every Time.
You Know, When Someone
Says "Every Time,"
It Sounds Like--Like--Like
More Than A Few Times.
Erything's Gonna Be Fine.
Were You Just
In The Same Assembly As Me?
Do You Really Think
She's Gonna Expel Two-Thirds
Of The Junior Class?
Look, I Got You Into This.
I'm Gonna Get You Out Of It,
Okay?
Trust Me.
There's A Weak Link
In Every Chain,
And It's Just A Matter Of Time
Before This One Snaps.
I'm Innocent.
Well... Except For
A Crime Of Passion.
I Did Something Stupid
With Someone.
And Even Worse
Than Doing That Stupid Thing,
I Did The Same Stupid Thing
With Someone Else
And Pretended I Had Never Done
That Stupid Thing Before.
You Look Confused.
Should I Walk You Through It?
Let's Stay On Point.
I Reviewed Your Record.
It's Pristine.
If Constance Has A Shining Star,
It's Blair Waldorf.
I Would Never
Have Expected This From You.
I Know. I'm The Perfect One.
Ms. Waldorf,
Who Broke Into The Pool?
Like You Said, My Unfortunate
Participation In Said Party
Was Entirely
Out Of Character.
I Don't Know Anything
About It.
You're Taking That Paper
Seriously.
This Isn't A Paper. It's...
It's A Heartfelt Letter
To Blair.
A Heartfelt Letter?
Who Spayed You, Man?
Blair Doesn't Even Want You.
She's Been Crystal About That
Since We Got Back.
Didn't Seem That Way
En She Kissed Me At The Pool.
She Kissed You?
Well, I Kissed Her, But...
Yep.
What Was She Like? Into It? Or Was She More Like--
Of Course She Was Into It, Man.
What Do You Think?
Yeah, I Know, But, Uh...
You Know Blair...
Yes, I Do.
I Think She Wants Me
To Suffer A Little More.
You Know,
Even The Playing Field?
It's Worth It,
Believe Me.
Hey, Dad. Listen, Uh,
I-I Got Your 1,001 Messages.
I Just Haven't Had A Chance
To Get Back To Ya.
Yeah, That's Not Gonna Work.
I Guess You Heard From
The New Headmistress.
Look, I Know How Upset
And Apparently, Some Of The Kids
Who Were At The Party
Didn't Even Tell
Their Parents.
Look, You Don't Have To Say
I-I Regret Even
Leaving The House Saturday.
Yeah, But If You Know
Keep You Out Of Trouble,
Then You Need To Cooperate.
I Don't.
Dan, Don't Think For A Second
These Other Kids Aren't Gonna
Be Looking Out For Themselves.
You Need To Do The Same.
All Right?
I Hope I'm Not
Interrupting Anything.
I Just Got A Message
That Our Kids Are In
Some Kind Of Trouble At School.
And You Came All The Way
To Brooklyn To Talk About It?
No, No, Not About That.
Um, Bart And I
Just Landed At The Airport
Back From Our Trip,
And He Proposed,
And I'm Going To Say Yes.
I Wanted You
To Hear It From Me First,
Not From My Daughter
Or Your Son.
Right, The People
Who Actually Talk To Me.
Oh, If You're Referring
You Left Me
On Christmas Day,
I Didn't Get It Until
We Were Already On The Plane.
It Was Very Endearing,
Though.
But Not Enough
To Turn The G5 Around?
You Miss Me. That's Great.
I Miss You, Too.
What? You Kissed Me
At Eleanor's Party,
And Then You Say
You Can't See Me Anymore
Because Your Wife Came Home,
And Then You Call And Say
You Should've Never Let Me Go,
And Then You're
Back With Alison Again.
I Didn't Plan Any Of That.
That Is Just It With You, Rufus.
You Don't Even Plan Anything.
Well, I'm Sure
That Your Current Plan
Will Be Full Of Private Jets
And 5-Star Hotels.
Take Care, Rufus.
Do You Really Have
To Show This To Me Now?
Trust Me When I Say
You're Gonna Wanna See This
Before You Enter
Blair Waldorf's Evil Lair.
It's A Homework Group, Vanessa.
We're Just Gonna Be
Writing Papers, You Know?
Here.
I Wasn't Sure What It Was
Till I Got It Home And Saw It
On The Computer, But--
Okay, That's Chuck. Wh--Wh...
What Are You Holding Here?
It's A Key.
Spotted--Lonely Boy Learning
That When The Punishment
Fits The Crime,
There's No Reason You Can't
Serve Your Sentence In Style.
Yay! You're Here.
I Thought We Were Gonna
Work On Our Papers.
We Are.
One Night At Bilboquet,
Kati And Is Made Out With A Guy
In Cornell's Ethics Program.
They're Getting Tips Now.
I Thought I Told You
You Couldn't Film Me.
Come Here.
You Are So Naive.
Michael Moore Over There
Is Obviously Just Using
This Film To Get Close To Dan.
No, She Needs That Grant Money.
So Did You Bring
Your Legal Pad?
You Wait Here. I'll Find Us
A Quiet Place To Work.
Okay.
I Can't Believe
You Brought That Here.
It's Evidence.
Give It To Me.
Chuck.
You Need To Tell The Truth.
Whatever Happened To
"Don't Speak Until Spoken To"?
I Just Saw You With That Key.
I Know You Had It At The Party.
Poor Little Humphrey Dumpty.
Look, Let Me Clarify Something
For You.
Regardless Of Who You're
Currently Sleeping With,
You And I Come
From Different Worlds.
In My World,
If I'm Suspended Or Expelled,
A Wing Is Donated
In The Bass Name.
That Sounds Like
Quite A World.
Well, It's Not Perfect,
I'll Admit.
But One Thing It Does Offer
In Spades Is Security.
My Family Can Take Care
Of Me.
What Do The Humphreys Have
To Offer?
Used Metrocards?
Your Dad's Cassingle?
And In Case
You Were Wondering, You Narc,
I Only Took The Key
From The Party To Hide It
So We Didn't All Get Blamed...
Including You.
Blair.
Nate.
What Are You Doing Here?
I, Uh, Wanted To Talk To You.
I Brought You This.
It's A Love Letter.
A Hostess Can't Hide
In Her Room. It's Unladylike.
Hey. Hey,
Where Are You Going?
I Made Us A Study Area
In The Other Room.
You Know What? I'm Just Gonna
I-I Think--I Think
Chuck Is Right.
Wait. Chuck?
No, The Guy Has A Point,
Actually.
Maybe The Reason None Of
You Guys Take This Seriously
Is Because For You
It's Not.
No, It Is.
Vanessa, Please, Some Space.
I'm Sorry.
Sorry.
Look, I'm All For Loyalty
And I'm All
For Sticking Together,
But We Are Not
In The Same Boat Here.
I'm On A Partial Scholarship.
My Parents Have No Way
Of Buying My Way Back
Into This School, Or Any Other.
And I Know This Isn't Going
To Be A Popular Opinion
With--With Your
Band Of Brothers,
But If The Person Who Brought
That Key Refuses To Step Up,
Then Anybody Who Knows Anything
Has The Right To Say Something.
Do--Do You Know Who It Is?
You Do, Don't You, And You're
Not Gonna Say Anything?
Dan, Please.
You Don't Understand.
You're Right.
I-I Mean, I Don't Understand.
Hey, Let Go Of Me, Bass.
Drop Your Archibald Habit
First.
You Know I Already Have.
Really? A Kiss Does Sort Of
Send The Wrong Signal.
Let's Not Waste Time Denying.
You Know What? I'm Tired
Of This. Go Ahead And Tell Him.
Really?
You Want Me To Tell Him
How You Slept With Me
And Then Faked Your Virginity
For Him?
I'll Just Tell Him
And Who Do You Think
He'll Believe?
You, Who Bangs Anything
In His Field Of Vision,
Or Me, His Pure And Honest
Girlfriend Of Many Years?
Well, Now He'll Believe Me.
Why?
I Have Proof.
Good Eye, Docu-Girl.
I'll Take The Tape Now.
You Knew She Was Watching?
This Is My House.
That Tape Belongs To Me.
Actually, This Is My Footage,
And Thanks To Both Of You,
I Think I Got A New Angle
On My Subject.
Hey, Vanessa,
If You Think I'm Gonna...
Let Go Of Me.
Let You Walk Out Of Here
With That Tape, You're Crazy.
Hey!
Last Time I Checked,
I Still Owe You A Black Eye.
So Unless This Is You Coming
To Claim It, Stay Away From Her.
Now That Sex And Lies
Have Been Caught On Videotape,
V.'S Documentary Just Became
The Most Anticipated
New Release Of The Year.
Rufus.
What Are You Doing Here?
I'm Not Leaving A Message
From The Courtyard This Time.
Well, I Can See That.
But Five Minutes Ago,
My Kids Would've--
Why Did You Really Come
I Told You.
Out Of Respect For--
Respect Or Regret?
You Wanted Me
To Give You A Reason
Not To Spend The Rest
Of Your Life With Bart Bass.
Rufus...
I'm Still In Love With You.
So What Exactly
Are You Offering, Rufus?
Some Retrospective
Of The Way We Were
Over A Decade Ago?
Look, We're Not 20
And On The Road.
Thank God We're Not,
Because Your Mother
Made This Decision For You
Back Then, Remember?
Yes. Mm.
Look...
I Don't Know Exactly
What It Would Even Mean
For Us To Be Together.
But Can You Look At Me
And Tell Me You're Not
The Least Bit Curious?
You're At The Same Crossroads
You Were Years Ago.
Claim Your Life This Time.
Live It The Way
You Want To Live It.
I Did It.
I Broke Into The School.
After All Your Family
Has Been Through This Year,
I'm Surprised To Learn
That You're Behind
Something Like This.
I Know, I Know.
And I Apologize.
From What I Can See,
You Always Seem To Be
Toeing The Line Of Mediocrity,
Nathaniel.
Your Grades Are Average At Best,
Almost As Though
You're Not Committed To School
Or Your Future.
Can We Just Move On
To The Punishment Part
Of This Meeting, Please?
Certainly.
But I'm Curious.
Can You Please Describe
How You Broke Into The School?
I Can Do Betr.
I Can Show You.
And How Did You Get Access
To This Key?
You're Not On The Swim Team.
Not A Janitor, Right?
No.
Where's The Key Chain?
The Key Chain?
Do You Remember Its Color?
Size?
What It's Made Of?
Anything At All?
Who Are You Trying
To Protect?
May I Have A Word?
Off Camera.
Uh, Sure. But I Think I Know
What You're Gonna Say.
And I Can Save You
The Indignity Of Groveling
By Telling You Right Now--No Way
Are You Gonna Get That Tape.
I Wasn't Going To Grovel,
And The Fact That You Even
Went There Makes It Clear
You Have No Idea
Who You're Dealing With.
What Are You Gonna Do To Me,
Blackball Me From Eating Yogurt
On The Met Steps?
You Have Nothing I Need.
You Put That Footage
In Your Film,
You Won't Be Able To Show It.
I Won't Sign A Release.
I'm Not Looking For
A Distribution Deal,
Just A Local Arts Grant
So I Can Pay My Rent.
Now If You'll Excuse Me...
You're In My Shot.
What's That,
Your Stripper Money?
$10,000 For The Tape.
You Think I'd Take
Your Money?
Yes, I Do.
I Know Girlsilike You.
You Act Like
Money's Not Important.
The Truth Is,
Money's Important To Everyone.
And I Thought Blair
Was Manipulative.
Blair's An Amateur.
She Thinks You're Just Like Her.
To Blair,
This Money Is A Couple Pairs
Of Manolos And A Chanel Bag.
But I Know
That This Much Cash
Can Make A Real Difference
In Your Life.
You're Sick.
You're Welcome.
Who Knew B. And C.
Were Such Patrons Of The Arts?
Call It Philanthropy
Or Bribery.
It Looks Like
Everyone Has Their Price.
Something On Your Mind,
Lily?
Uh...
Yeah?
What Are You Saying?
I'm Sorry. It's Sheldon.
He Has Those Numbers
I Was Asking For.
Do You Mind?
No.
Yeah.
Just Make Sure He Gets It
At The Current Rate.
The Dollar's
Been All Over The Place.
Hello?
I Was Thinking
About What You Said.
Let's Do It.
Let's See What We Are.
Let's See What We Could Be.
Who Is This?
Rufus...
Lily, This Is Great.
Do You Know How Great This Is?
Well, Yes. I Mean, I-I Do.
I Mean, I Think So.
Let's Go Away Tonight.
Let's Get Away
From Everyone, Everything,
Just Figure It Out.
Wh-Where Would We Go?
Who Cares?
Okay, Sounds Like A Plan.
Um... 90th And 5th. 6:00?
Okay.
I'm Scared, Rufus...
In A Good Way.
Me, Too.
Settle Down, Please.
Yesterday, I Talked About
The Serious Consequences...
Proof. Worth Every Penny.
For Your Dishonorable Actions,
And Obviously,
You Didn't Believe Me.
But Someone Came Forward Today
And Claimed Responsibility...
Do You Know Who?
For A Crime He Did Not Commit.
And Although I Appreciate
His Self-Sacrifice,
I Don't Abide Dishonesty.
And I Think It's Time
You All Know How Serious I Am.
Nathaniel Archibald
Is Suspended From St. Jude's.
And, Yes, This Will Go On
His Transcript.
Effective Immediately.
Mr. Archibald,
You Know Where
To Find The Exit.
This Just In--Nate Archibald,
Dead Man Walking.
We Hear St. Jude's
Has A New Policy--
An Eye For A Lie.
Watch Him Go, Students.
Who Wants To Be Next?
Until One Of You Comes Forward,
We'll Keep Going
Until Every Last One Of You
Has Walked Out That Door.
I Don't Believe This.
Dan, It's Okay.
Serena, I-I Can't--
I Can't Get Expelled.
I Cannot Get Suspended.
My Whole Future
Is Riding On This.
If You Know Who Broke In,
Then Why Won't You Give Them Up?
Because It Was Me.
So Why--Why Didn't You
Tell Me Right Away?
'Cause I Didn't Want You
To Judge Me.
Aren't We Already Beyond That?
And I Didn't Want You To Know
Because I Didn't Want You
To Have To Be In
The Position You're In Now
Of Having To Choose Between
Protecting Me
And Helping Yourself.
So How'd You Even Get In?
I Have A Key.
You Had A Key To The Pool?
All Right, What Happened
To Being Beyond This?
Sorry.
The End Of Freshman Year,
I Kind Of Dated
The Swim Team Captain,
And He Gave Me A Key
So That We Could...
You Know, Meet Up, And...
That's--Enough Said.
And Saturday Night--
What Happened Then?
Well, Blair And I
Ran Out Of Places To Go,
And She Knew
I Still Had A Key,
And... Before I Knew It,
It's Like We Were All There.
And I Thought It Was
Just Gonna Be Us Girls.
And Then Everybody
Got On Their Phone,
And More People Started
Showing Up, And...
I Just Never Thought
Anybody Was Gonna Get Hurt.
Yeah. Well, You Can Still
Tell Queller The Truth.
I Think She'll Respect
Your Honesty.
Yeah, Like She Respected Nate's?
No, Nate Lied.
And Besides,
You're Serena Van Der Woodsen.
You Didn't Know Me
Before I Went Away.
Barely Got Back
Into Constance.
If I Got Expelled,
I Don't Think Any School
In Town Would Take Me.
I'm Sure That's Not True.
I Can't Risk Going Back
To Boarding School,
Being Away From You And Eric.
But I Don't Want You
To Lose Your Future.
Wow. Oh, Wow.
You Really Can Be
Damned If You Do
And Screwed If You Don't.
Dan Humphrey,
Headmistress Queller
Is Requesting
To See Y U Iher Office
After Class.
Nate.
Hey. Are You Okay?
Yeah,I'll Be Fine. It's,Uh...
My Parents Have So Much Other Stuff Going On Right Now...
They'll Get Over It. Either Way,It Was Worth It.
Worth It? Yes. Blair,I Know How Much Your Future Means To You.
And You've Worked So Hard For Yale And Everything--
What Are You Talking About?
You Don't Have To Lie. I Saw The Key In Your Bedroom.
That Key Isn't Mine.
I Was St Hiding It For Someone Else.
Wait...
That's Why You Were Suspended?
You Told The Headmistress It Was Yours
Because You Thought It Was Mine?
That's The Most Romantic Thing Anyone Has Ever Done For Me.
I Love You.
Please. You And I Just Can't Happen Right Now.
Why Not?
I Don't Want To Be With You.
Good Catching Up.
You're Home Early.
Please Don't Tell Me You're Expelled. Not Yet.
Your Position At That School Is Already Too Precarious.
One False Move, And You Know What?
I Can't Do Anything To Help You. I Know. I Know.
I Just Wanna Hide Under The Covers
And Make It All Go Away. And Apparently,You Do,Too.
You And Bart Just Got Back. Why Are You Packing Again?
Well,I Was Just Gonna Go For A,You Know,
A Little Spa Trip For The Weekend.
'Cause You're So Stressed Out From Your Vacation?
Aren't You Gonna Answer That? No,I Don't Think So.
Mom, Is Dan's Dad The Reason
You Haven't Answered Bart's Proposal?
You Can't.
Please,Mom,Not This One.
Look,I Will Not Base My Personal Life
On Your Preferences.
Dan Is My Boyfriend.
And I Know We're Too Young To Talk About Forever,
But Right Now That's What It Feels Like.
I Know It Does,Sweetie, But-- But What?
Tell Me That Rufus Is That Important To You.
Tell Me That Whatever The Two Of You Have
Is The Most Important Thing In Your Life,
Because That's What Dan Is To Me,Mom.
The Most Important.
I Would Rather Be Chuck's Stepsister Than Dan's.
Please Don't Do This To Me.
Dan Means That Much To You?
Yeah,He Does.
In Fact,I Have To Go. Wait. Where?
School. There's Something I Have To Do.
And I Hope There's Something You Have To Do,Too.
What Are You Doing Here?
I Brought This For You.
What's The Catch?
I Know This Might Come As A Shock,
But Not Everyone Operates From An Agenda.
In Fact, Some People Do Things
Simply Because It's The Decent Thing To Do.
Smash It,Burn It,Whatever. There Are No Copies.
What About The One You Gave To Chuck?
It's Blank,Which I'm Sure He'll Be Thrilled To Discover.
And About What's On That Tape-- Having Observed You
In Your Natural Habitat These Past Few Days...
Nate Seems Like One Of The Good Guys,
And You Seem To Really Care About Him.
Mr. Humphrey,You Have A Partial Scholarship At St. Jude's.
You Are Number Two In Your Class,
Have A Stellar Recommendation For Dartmouth From J.L. Hall.
It Looks As If Your Dreams Are Well Within Grasp.
Thank You,Thank You. Yeah,I Guess They Are.
But It Seems You're In With A N Crowd This Year,
Dating Serena Van Der Woodsen...
Is That On My File?
Who Had The Key To The School?
I Don't Know.
Let Me Remind You One Last Time
That You Are In A Different Position Than The Others.
You Need This School.
Headmistress Queller, I Have Something To Tell You.
I Must Say,Your File Reads More Like A Rap Sheet.
You Cut More Sophomore Classes Than You Attended,
Cheated On Tests, Talked Back To Teachers. Look,I Understand That This Is A Serious Matter.
That's Why It's Important To Me
That You Know-- You Being New Here--
That The Person That You Just Described
Is Not W I Am Anymore.
Oh,No? Who Are You Now?
Well,My Grades Are Up,
My Attendance Is Nearly Perfect,
And I've Stayed Out Of Trouble.
Until Now.
Please Understand
That I Never Intended For Anything Bad To Happen.
And It May Have Taken Some Time, But I Am Here Now,
Accepting Responsibility For My Actions.
Whatever You Think Is Fair.
Yes,Let's Discuss The...
Consequences.
Ahem.
I'll Be Brief.
And...
I'll Be Not Interested. Is That How You Speak To The Person
Who Just Paid Your Rent For A Year? What Did You Just Say?
Congratulations,Vanessa.
You Just Won 365 More Days In Your Ikea-Furnished Closet.
You Went To My Building? You Talked To My Landlord?
No,I Don't Speak Ukrainian,
But I Do Speak Envelope Of Cash.
And He Understood Me Perfectly.
I Can't Believe You. Blair Waldorf Is Not Indebted To Anyone,
No Matter How Much I Appreciate What You Did.
You're Welcome,I Guess?
Good. Now This Transaction Is Finished,
And I'm Free To Return To Disliking You.
I Wouldn't Have It Any Other Way.
Oh,And One More Thing.
If You Didn't Pay Your Rent With It,
What Did You Do With Chuck's Money?
I May Have Created
A Medical Grant For Teens With Genital Herpes...
In His Name.
I Can't Believe She Didn't Expel Me.
Yeah,I Know. It's Shocking.
I--You--25 Hours Of Community Outreach.
That's Not Bad At All.
I Mean,I Probably Would've Done It Anyway
Being As I'm On The Committee. That Had Occurred To Me. Yeah.
Wait. What Are You Saying?
No,No,I'm Not Saying Anything. Believe Me.
So You Don't Buy What She Said
About Me Being The Poster Child For The New Honor Code?
Look,I Know For A Fact
My Mom Didn't Plead My Case Or Donate Anything,Okay? I Didn't Say A Thing.
Are You Really Turning This
Into An "Upstairs,Downstairs" Thing?
No. No,You Are. I'm Being Completely Silent.
I'm Just Happy That You're Not Being Expelled
Or Leaving Town Anytime Soon. Are You Hungry? We Should... Always.
But You Still Believe That There's A Double Standard,
That People Like Me Get Specl Trtrtment.
Ms. Van Der Woodsen. Your Mother Sent Me To Pick You Up.
Oh. Great.
That Was... Thoughtful.
I Think You Get No Special Treatment At All.
Your Life Is Completely Uncharmed And... Average.
It's Okay. I'll Walk.
No,Come On. I'm--I Was Kidding. I Was Kidding.
You Going To Brooklyn?
It's A Rare Occasion
To Celebrate The Merging Of Two Families.
And I Couldn't Be Happier To Be Here Tonight
To Celebrate Lily's Acceptance Of My Proposal.
So To My Lovely Bride
And Our Growing Family.
You Packed Light.
Please Try To Understand.
I Think I Do.
I'm Just Sorry.
So Am I.
Mom Looks About As Happy As Grandma At Last Call. I Know.
It Seems Bart's Personality-- Or Lack Thereof--Is Contagious.
I Don't Even Know
How She Breathes With Her Blouse Buttoned That High.
How Glad Are You To See Our Families Merge,Sis?
So Glad That If You Ever Call Me That Again,
It'll Be The Last Thing You Ever Say,Chuck.
I Love It--Our First Brother/Sister Squabble.
I Hope You're Going To Make Yourself Available
For More Missed Childhood Memories--
Bathing Together, For Example.
You're Probably Wondering Why I Asked You Here.
After Our Last Conversation, Yeah.
Do You Think It's Possible
For Two People Who Have Been Through As Much As We Have
To Really Forgive And Forget?
If We Really Want To, I Think We Can.
A Lot Of Mistakes Have Been Made.
If You're Ready To Forgive Me...
Then Nothing Can Tear Us Apart.
I Promise.
What You Said Before...
I Love You,Too.
Always Have,Always Will.
So...
Your New Stepbrother Told Me About Your Problem At School.
Frankly,I Wasn't Surprised,
Given Your Propensity For Recklessness And Adventure.
I'm Sorry?
Don't Tell Your Mother, But I Made A Call.
You Did What? It Was Harder Than Usual.
That New Headmistress Of Yours Is A Real Piece Of Work.
I Had To Go Over Her Head.
Sorry I Couldn't Get The Charges Completely Dropped,But,Um...
At Least I Got You A Minimal Sentence.
One Thing About Being On The Inside--
Once You Get There,
You Don't Always Get To Choose Where You Stand... Or Sit.
I Was Just Looking Out For My Family.
The New Van Der Woodsen/Bass Library
Should Be Completed For Eric's Graduation.
I Can See That Lily And I
Are Gonna Have Our Hands Full With The Two Of You.
Will You Excuse Me? I Need Some Air.
Sometimes You Need To Step Outside,
Clear Your Head
And Remind Yourself Of Who You Are...
And Where You Want To Be.
Hey. Aren't You Supposed To Be At Your Mom's Engagement Thing?
Yeah,Well, I Had To Get Out Of There.
It Was Getting A Little Hard To Breathe,You Know?
Those Parties Can Be That Way.
So Are You,Um, Packing Up Your Music?
Nah. I Just...
Need To Find Something New To Write About.
And I Will.
Hey. You're A Little Overdressed
For The Study Date I Didn't Know We Had.
You Were Right About Everything.
You Wanna Talk About It?
Can I Just Sit Here With You For A While?
Yeah.
Chaucer? Yeah,I Got A Test On Friday.
Mine's Thursday.
And Sometimes You Have To Venture Outside Your World
In Order To Find Yourself.
As For Me, I'm Happy Right Where I Am.
I Only Wanna Be With You.
X.O.X.O.,Gossip Girl.
破烂熊字幕组
-==Http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
欢迎加入