Previously on Angel:
- For God's sake, help us.
- People are going to die.
I just can't seem to care.
Holland Manners is dead,
Angel....
- What you did is wrong.
- You went too far.
The three of us are all that's standing
between you and real darkness.
You're all fired.
- You think I don't have what it takes.
- I know you don't.
I guess we'll just have to find out.
Go on, English, make your move,
because it'll be your last.
Now I rule Europe, Australia
and South America!
I still got Kamchatka.
Three-fifths of the world is water,
the rest is me.
Who's your ruler, baby?
What's my name? Say it.
Fun as it is having you guys over day
and night, it's getting kind of late.
- It's only 7:30.
- Really? Oh, in that case...get out!
- What if you have a vision?
- I'll call.
- What if Angel--?
- We're not saying the "A" word.
Don't say the "A" word,
but wait for him to call.
We're not waiting for him to call.
He fired us.
We're a separate unit,
fighting the good fight.
Right. With no plan or office
or business cards.
He's never gonna call, is he?
The first thing we're scrapping:
these stupid calling cards.
They are not stupid. I designed them.
- That's an angel.
- The symbol of what we don't have.
That's an angel? Looks like
a lobster with a growth or....
- We'll make our own logo.
- Yes. Something sleek, but edgy.
- That says: "You need us, we're here."
- Exactly. "Danger is our business.
- We'll catch you when you fall."
- I like it.
Guys.
- Easy. Breathe. Breathe.
- What is it? What'd you get?
It has two heads and it breathes fire.
It's gigantic...
...and it's rising up in the sewers
beneath Kenyard School for Girls.
Don't go alone!
- Sorry.
- It's me. I didn't hurt you, did I?
- I'm fine.
- I couldn't see over the box.
I was rushing. I'm late for work.
You do clown work?
No. Just some old clothes
that got donated.
East Hills Teen Center.
It's on the box.
Oh. Right.
You missed one.
Hold on. Sorry.
Okay, I think I'm good.
I'm really sorry.
- No problem.
- They're for the kids.
There's always a feeding frenzy
when a new batch comes in.
- You work with runaways?
- Some of them.
Some are from around here
with nowhere to go.
We give them food, clothes,
somewhere to stay.
That's good that someone's--
Well, it's good to do.
- Well, I'm late.
- Right.
See you around.
- So it's big.
- Big.
- Fire-breathing.
- Breathing.
- Big, two-headed, fire-breathing--
- We have the picture.
He shouldn't be attending
the Kenyard School for Girls.
- I wouldn't mind having--
- Don't say it.
We don't.
It's no good wishing we had him.
- I was gonna say, some dynamite.
- Oh.
Dynamite.
Maybe it's not too late
to go back--
Oh, God.
The tunnel's 20 feet tall.
He was crouching.
We'll take another look,
and then we'll--
Die.
Wait, wait!
Wait till his back is turned.
Now!
I thought she said he breathed fire.
Evening, Merl.
What do you want, man?
I ain't inviting you in.
Demon lairs. No invite needed.
- But it's polite--
- You avoiding me, Merl?
I ask you for a favor, and you're
avoiding me. That's impolite.
Nearly drowning me and leaving me
in a sewer ain't exactly Emily Post.
So we're both rude.
Do you have the information...
...or must I see what the inside
of that head looks like?
Fine!
I checked out the girl. She's clean.
Changed her name twice, but no record.
- Her connection to Wolfram & Hart?
- She runs a shelter on Crenshaw.
Recently, they almost
lost their lease.
Wolfram & Hart step in,
clear it all up pro bono.
- But she's still working for them.
- You know so much, why ask?
Why do you need me?
What happened to that
hot chick working for you?
- Pro bono. It's gotta be an angle.
- Always is.
But as far as I could tell,
the shelter itself is strictly legit.
- Hey, what about my hundred bucks?
- Know what? I'll owe you.
Just make sure you use it
for some new furniture.
Beanbag chairs?
Merl....
What am I supposed to do?
Say no. Benny knows the rules.
He's not coming in here drunk.
Turn him out. Don't listen to him.
- Hey. Guy I ran over.
- Hey. Girl who ran over me.
- You can call me Anne. It's shorter.
- Angel.
- I don't know if they're good--
- That's great.
We can take them over here.
Well, let's see. What do you got?
Well, that's not what I expected.
- Doesn't fit anymore?
- Cuts me across the bust.
A friend left her clothes at my place.
I won't see her anytime soon....
- Ex-girlfriend?
- God, no.
I mean, just "no."
We really appreciate this.
Every little bit helps, you know.
- I just wish I could do more.
- Well, if you're not in a hurry....
You up for a tour?
Here's the vibrant nerve center
of our huge corporation.
Well....
- It's....
- Small.
I know. But I'm hardly ever in here.
You just come in for naps?
Oh, the bed.
Sometimes I'm here so late,
it's just easier than going home.
So, what do you think?
Amazing.
- You say it runs on donations?
- Every last penny.
Gotta be tough.
I mean, trying to stay ahead.
- Thankfully, we have a guardian angel.
- Guardian angel?
Wolfram & Hart, a law firm.
They've been a godsend.
Bailed us out of an eviction.
Defended some of our kids.
- They sound like saints.
- As far as I'm concerned.
- They came up with the Big Holdup.
- Holdup?
It's a fundraiser for the center.
Big TV celebrities pretend to rob
the guests of their donations.
- Wild West theme. It's gonna be big.
- Wolfram & Hart's picking up the tab?
They're donating everything.
Music, food....
- And they know all the TV stars.
- That's not surprising.
It's good for their image, I guess.
And it's a pretty dorky theme.
- But, hey, whatever it takes, right?
- Right.
- Does anybody knock?
- You Merl?
Merl? Merl who?
No, the name's Ed...Silverman.
- You're Angel's lackey.
- No. No, I'm not.
- Independent contractor.
- And what do you do for him?
- Pictures. Ow! I take--
- Pictures.
Surveillance, you know. Dig up dirt,
check people out for him.
Not that he appreciates it.
Who the hell are you, anyway? IRS?
Angel and I have a history.
An unfinished history.
That's nice. What, did you guys
go to college together?
These people you check out,
who are they?
Friends? Enemies?
What does Angel care about?
Last thing he had me do was follow
some chick who did charity work.
Why?
Well, between you and me,
it ain't about the girl.
- It's Wolfram & Hart.
- What's a Wolfram & Hart?
A law firm, technically.
More like Evil, Incorporated.
Lately, he's been gunning for them.
Especially these two lawyers.
Tell me about the lawyers.
Lilah. I just had to drop by and
congratulate you on your promotion.
Co-vice president of Special Projects.
That's super.
You deserve it.
Yeah. That, and so much more.
- Angel--
- You know what the special part is?
To think that maybe, in my small way,
I helped make it happen for you.
Makes me feel all good inside.
Angel, I can assure you...
...now that Lindsey and I are in
a position to affect policy...
...things will change.
Change? Well, yeah,
because I get it now.
"It"?
The game. It's actually fun
when you know the rules.
I mean, when you know
that there aren't any.
You screw with me
and you screw with me...
...and you screw with me.
Now I get to screw with you.
- That's gonna be great.
- Please--
No, no.
The begging, that comes later.
- He was in my car.
- Yet here you are, still alive.
- He was trying to spook you.
- It worked.
Relax. He doesn't kill
humans personally.
- He's not playing by the old rules.
- Mr, McDonald, your 10 is here,
- I don't have a 10:00.
- I'm not gonna tell him that,
- Sorry, but I'm afraid I'm--
- Shut the door.
- Won't you come in, Mr...?
- Call me Boone.
- Are you the better half of this team?
- I like to think so.
We run Special Projects.
Do you have a special project?
More like a grudge.
With a fella named Angel.
I haven't seen Angel
since Juarez in the '20s.
We had a little disagreement
over a señorita,
I called him out.
We fought for 3½ hours.
Obviously, both of you survived.
I'd been working on a three-day drunk
at the time. I wasn't at my peak.
- How did it end?
- The sun came up. I let him go.
- You let him go? Why?
- The sun came up.
It would have been too easy.
You people know anything about honor?
Anyway, life is long
when you're eternal.
Always knew I'd cross his path again.
And behold,
I'm in a karaoke bar downtown...
...when I get wind
of this lizard demon, Merl...
...who sometimes does favors
for the vampire with a soul.
I find Merl, and he tells me...
...that Angel's planning
on bringing you two down.
- Did he mention how?
- Don't know, don't care.
All I do know is,
when Angel comes for you...
...he's gonna find me instead.
I like the "finding you instead" part.
How much do you charge?
This isn't about money.
It's about knowing.
- Knowing what?
- Who's better. Him or me.
If you're talking about murder,
we can't help you.
Would you excuse us
for a moment, please?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Bring him onboard.
Don't forget the senior partners
want him alive.
So?
What if this guy's as good
as he says and actually kills Angel?
Boo-hoo. Let me wipe away the tears
with my plastic hand.
Napoleon, we're partners.
Your plan explodes...
- ...we both end up in tiny pieces.
- Want Angel in your back seat again?
If he won't play by the
old rules, why should we?
- It's huge.
- We were getting stomped.
I'm thrown into the sewer--
You come back stinking, cursing.
The mouth on this boy.
Gunn hits from behind, yelling,
"Look at us when we kill you!"
- Both its heads turn!
- Wes sinks his ax into head number one.
Gunn stabs him, pulls out
intestines the size of your leg!
- We turned him inside out.
- You weren't scared?
Mother in heaven.
Pants-wetting, ask-God-to-save-you
kind of scared.
- But you did it.
- No. We did it. All of us.
- All of us together.
- To us.
I did something.
I hope you guys don't mind.
I started looking for an office
for our new agency.
- Our new agency?
- Our new agency.
There's this little place nearby.
It's not much, but--
- Why are we still here?
- Let's go.
- Our new agency.
- "The Wyndam-Pryce Agency."
- The what?
- You don't like it? It's classy.
It's stuffy. "The Chase Agency."
That has the right ring.
- Why?
- Because it's my name.
There's only one player here
with the name...
...that strikes dread
in the demon heart.
Gunn? Oh, yeah, that's so original.
I've got a gun, and my name is Gunn!
- "Wyndam-Pryce" says it all.
- Shut up!
You gotta be kidding me.
I swear I didn't rat on you, Angel.
- I didn't say nothing to the guy.
- Shut up, Merl.
Jeez, does everybody know
where I live?
- Gotta get myself a new lair.
- Merl, Lilah.
Now that we're past the pleasantries...
You do favors for Angel?
- What are those favors?
- I don't go selling out my pals.
- How much you gonna pay?
- I think you'll find our offer...
- ...competitive.
- I would have taken a credit card.
Down, Fluffy. Jeez!
- Lately, I've been following a girl.
- What girl?
Hello?
Is anybody out here?
Anne.
You startled me.
What are you doing here?
I have to talk to you.
Oh, boy. You're not
stalking me, are you?
Actually, I am.
Excuse me?
These are pictures I've taken of you.
Surveillance photos.
I took your wallet when we
accidentally ran into each other.
- It wasn't an accident.
- I'm calling the police.
I won't hurt you.
I couldn't lie to you anymore.
- About being a psycho?
- I've been following you...
- ...but it's not why you think.
- You have a reason?
Wolfram & Hart aren't saints.
They don't care about your shelter.
- You're following me--
- I've checked.
They'll use you for good PR,
offer to host a fundraiser.
Money starts rolling in,
but you're not the one counting it...
...so who knows how much
they're keeping?
Next, they'll give you
a list of necessary expenses.
But what do you know,
after a number of untraceable fees...
...you're left with 5 percent, tops.
You follow me, take my picture,
steal my wallet....
- Why should I believe you?
- Wolfram & Hart aren't what they seem.
They show the world one face,
but it's not the truth.
I can prove it.
Everything they say is a lie.
I guess you have something in common.
- Lindsey.
- Are you all right?
- Fine. I--
- He didn't hurt you, did he?
Had I known he was contacting you,
I'd have come sooner.
I'm just thankful
that I got here in time.
A little over the top.
Work on that look of concern.
- He's dangerous.
- You haven't seen anything yet.
Neither have you.
- It's been a long time.
- I brought some protection.
Boone. Working for Wolfram & Hart.
- I thought you had integrity.
- I do.
Here's fair warning.
- Wait.
- He's getting away.
As long as he's not threatening
my client. Soon, but not here.
Go to the car. I'll meet you there.
He won't be back tonight.
It's okay. Angel's gone.
You're safe.
That guy who beat up Angel,
he wasn't human.
See, there's a different world that--
- I'm not naive.
- Angel's not human. He's a vampire.
He's a sick, deranged--
He says you're gonna steal
most of the funds.
Well, he's lying.
I mean, there are expenses.
You know how it works
with any charity event.
- But we don't steal.
- He says he has proof.
He's lying about that too.
Who are you gonna trust?
A mentally unstable vampire...
...or the people that put the
fundraiser together for your kids?
I'd hate to see them lose out
because you made the wrong choice.
So he doesn't have proof?
He can't have proof.
- He's got proof?
- Maybe.
- She said he had proof.
- It'll be okay.
Sure, we only schemed to steal
$2 million from a teen shelter.
- How did this happen?
- If he's got proof, it's from you.
- Me?
- You talked and it's on tape, probably.
You have the professional death wish.
How do I know you're not
on a kamikaze mission?
I only talk to you in my office,
which is swept for bugs.
- I never discussed stealing in public.
- Until now.
The bastard got us on tape.
What'll he do with it?
He's gonna use it to humiliate us.
He's gonna send it to the news.
National coverage--
- It's not personal enough.
- What, then?
- He's gotta be there.
- What? Why?
To see us swing, that's why.
With the bosses there, watching.
It's me. I want security
at the charity ball doubled...
...and put a vampire detector there.
- I thought you'd show up again.
- You all right?
A monster didn't pound my face,
so I figure I'm better than you.
- What did Lindsey say about me?
- That you were a bad man.
A bad man?
A psychotic vampire who cut off
his hand, harassed his firm...
...and is schizophrenic.
I gave you the short version.
Do you believe that?
You're a vampire for sure.
A human would be in the hospital.
And that doesn't frighten you?
Before, it'd have been a turn-on.
- I thought vampires were the coolest.
- What happened?
- I met one.
- You're not afraid of me.
I've seen worse things since.
Saw a 14-year-old sit in blood after
a rough trick, people just walking by.
Vampires, demons, even lawyers
don't impress me.
Maybe you had good reason
to cut off Lindsey's hand.
I care about the shelter. If an evil
law firm will raise $2 million--
- You'll see only 5 percent.
- I did the math.
Five percent is $100,000. That's more
than we could raise in two years.
And the other 95%? You don't care
where it goes or who it hurts?
- I can't.
- There's blood on that money.
Are you a person who can ignore that?
Have you become that yet?
I don't think you have.
- You don't know what it takes--
- Help me.
Get me into the party. This'll show
a whole new side of Wolfram & Hart.
- Why should I?
- Because in the long run, it's right.
Most of my kids don't have a long run.
No.
I'm saying no.
The world can be dangerous, Especially
for our most vulnerable citizens;
Our children,
Far from home,
with little money or hope...
... too many runaways
find themselves on the streets...
...over their heads
and under society's radar,
But there's a place in L.A.
that can help these troubled kids;
The East Hills Teen Center,
It's a terrific refuge that
we at Wolfram & Hart support 100%,
- Lilah.
- Good evening, sir.
- Things progressing nicely?
- Well, it's a pretty simple formula.
The rich pay to touch the famous.
We film the not-quite-prostitutional act.
It goes into public consciousness as
a good deed, courtesy Wolfram & Hart.
It's really true. Charity gives
you this warm glow, you know?
Anne?
Meet one of my bosses, Nathan Reed.
Mr. Reed, this is Anne.
So this is the young woman whose
dedication brings us together tonight.
I try to help where I can.
Thank you for everything.
I think my job underlines
the "heart" in Wolfram & Hart.
Save some time for interviews.
- You're the public face of the charity.
- What a face it is.
Never underestimate
the power of positive publicity.
- He stays here. We forget anything?
- No, sir.
Every entry point's covered.
We're in radio contact.
If this vampire gets within 100 feet,
Zorn will let us know.
If he senses anything, alert Boone.
Can we really change the world?
At Wolfram & Hart,
we're counting on it,
Holland Manners is gone,
but he's looking down on us tonight.
Don't you feel it?
Holland had a vision of the future
most of us can't imagine.
Let's make it come true together.
Let's get started.
But not with a plea for money.
We're not gonna ask you for money.
We're gonna take it at gunpoint.
Welcome our celebrity bandits
from the show life lessons;
Serena Tate, Holden Raynes,
C.J. McCard and Jordan Johns!
Those are some nice duds there, fella.
Let's see that cash you got stowed.
Hey, cowboy, don't hurt me now.
My daughter from my first marriage
is a huge fan.
All posts report in, Over,
West gate clear,
Serena, I have to know.
Your character being gay...
...is that like all about ratings?
Because I don't get it.
No sign of your friend yet.
Angel.
I feared you wouldn't show.
Ready to finish this?
Thank you, wonderful stars
from life lessons...
...for giving so generously
of your time.
- I'm gonna kill my agent.
- And to all of you, our benefactors...
...let me just say that
we can change the world.
With your support, we can make it
a safer place for all our children.
Stunts? This will take forever.
The makeup's fake.
You think we wouldn't
be ready for you?
Where's the tape?
- Where is it? Where's the tape?
- He doesn't have it.
- You okay? I tried to break the fall.
- I'll be fine.
- What the hell?
- Thanks for getting me in.
This place is like a fortress.
- What's going on?
- They're in it together.
- Me, I'm just here for the show.
- She's got the tape.
Watch it!
Be careful!
Excuse me!
- How do you turn it on?
- Give me!
It's not a toy,
It's for gathering evidence,
- Let go,
- You'll just play with it,
I give you two children, Bill,
and you leave me for a man?
No, don't speak, Don't say anything,
What is there to say?
- Interesting choice.
- I believe the coat rack more.
Mmm, Milk,
Mmm! Milk!
I don't get it, How am I not working?
What's happening?
Looks to me like you two
were acting like crazy people.
On camera too.
Ouch.
Pryce, Wesley Wyndam-Pryce,
Isn't he dating Virginia Bryce?
- You don't have us on tape, do you?
- I got nothing.
You know how hard it is to record
someone as paranoid as you two?
- This whole thing was a setup.
- You hired Boone.
No, you did.
For a whole lot of money too.
The money!
Look out! Move!
- Look out!
- Move!
Come on!
- Damn!
- What happened?
- He stole the money.
- Who?
The cowboy.
How dare you? I risked everything.
I risked my kids.
- There was no exposé.
- They'd have covered it up.
I wanted to shake them up.
It's a start.
- And the money?
- The money was tainted.
- I don't care about--
- Yes, you do.
That's the difference between us.
You still care.
You embarrassed us all. You lost
$2 million earmarked for this firm.
Worst of all, you violated
company policy by hiring an assassin.
One who was, in fact,
in league with Angel.
- I'm very sorry, sir.
- Sorry isn't acceptable.
Holland Manners
was a brilliant lawyer.
Had a tremendous mind.
But he had a soft spot
for the two of you...
...which I believe
clouded his judgment.
- I won't make that mistake.
- Understood.
My advice to you:
- Start piling up wins. Fast.
- Yes, sir.
How do you expect us to succeed...
...when you handcuff us with these
idiotic rules protecting Angel?
I'm sorry, did you say something?
He's an obstacle to all that we do.
Give me a good reason why
we can't kill him.
Because Angel is a major player.
- In business?
- In the Apocalypse.
Oh, that.
The prophesies say
when the final battle is waged...
- ...he is key.
- Good for him.
Which side he's on is the gray area.
We'll continue making it gray.
Works for me.
Until then, his growing obsession
with the two of you...
...the increasing possibility that,
to scratch that itch...
...he'll go as far as to kill you...
...that could play
in the firm's favor.
It would be a sign that Angel
is on the path to joining our team.
As hard as it is
to lose good attorneys...
...well, the truth is,
you're both expendable.
Angel isn't.
I thought you'd be halfway
to Brazil by now.
No, you didn't.
No, I didn't.
How much it come to?
With jewelry, north of
2.5 million, I'd say.
- That's a lot to lay on the line.
- Yeah.
But I gotta know.
All of it. A little bit more
than 5 percent.
- If Wolfram & Hart find out--
- I can hide it.
What's this?
Blood.
It'll wash.
Thank you, thank you very much,