Previously on Angel:
These people were threatened
at their offices...
...by an intruder who was released
right before they were murdered.
- We're not judging you.
- You're firing me.
How do you feel?
- Stronger.
- You're getting stronger every day.
Do you love her?
Is that it?
Wesley doesn't need you.
We don't need you.
- We hoped you'd be in the office.
- Mrs. Sharp.
One of them is on their way here.
- The ring?
- The Band of Blacknil.
The Kleynach use it to move
between dimensions.
Will it get me to the Home Office?
You realize this Home Office
is probably Hell.
Why do you wanna go to Hell?
Welcome to the Home Office.
The world doesn't work in spite
of evil. It works with us.
It works because of us.
What do you want, Darla? This?
Oh, God.
Don't fight it, my love.
Just let it happen.
It'll only hurt for a minute.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Yes, I know. It was
the same for me.
The soul is gone, but
it leaves a bitterness.
It'll pass.
You need a fresh kill. Hot human blood
will wash away the foul memory of it.
I promise.
What?
What is it?
You saved me.
Yes. But I was going
to kill you tonight.
Take you out of this world
the way I brought you in.
But I didn't have to.
You gave yourself over
so completely, Angelus.
I felt you surrender.
I gave you everything I had left.
Yes.
I'm so sorry.
You don't have to be.
But I am.
I am sorry.
- What?
- I'm sorry, Darla.
- No.
- You saved me.
- Sorry I couldn't do the same.
- Let go of me.
You still have a soul.
- But we....
- Yeah.
And you....
I know.
- Then I....
- Three times.
You're not evil.
I don't understand.
Was I...?
Was it not good?
I don't accept that. You cannot
tell me that wasn't perfect.
I've been around 400 years. I've done
this professionally. That was perfect.
- We'll go again.
- No, no.
We can't.
You know we can't.
- We're finished.
- Finished? Why?
Because you suddenly decide?
An hour ago you wanted this!
You weren't tricked!
- I didn't seduce you! You wanted this!
- Yeah, and it was perfect.
It was perfect despair.
And you were the reason.
You've always been the reason.
You were the thing
that made me what I am.
I thought that
if I could save you...
...I'd somehow save myself,
but I was wrong.
- When I failed--
- Stop it!
When I failed, you saved me.
I have to thank you for that.
There's nothing I can do for you now.
I can't even hate you.
You knew this would happen.
You made me trust you!
You made me believe!
We're done. Let yourself out.
Where are you going?
You did me a favor tonight.
Now I'll do one for you.
Get dressed and get out...
...because next time I see you,
I'll have to kill you.
Kate! Kate!
Kate, open the door! Kate!
Kate.
Thanks.
Now get out.
Darla...
...I've been calling all night.
Why haven't you answered?
Get away from the window.
It's not safe.
They called an emergency meeting
tonight after what happened.
The official order on you
is to stake on sight.
You should've told me your plan.
I would've talked you out of it.
Helped you. I don't know.
Things are getting complicated for us.
Yes. Yes, I believe they are.
We should clear your stuff out.
Move it in my bedroom.
I just think it'd be best for us....
Darla, what's wrong? What is this?
Where'd you get this?
What's the difference?
It doesn't work.
Of course not. After Angel stole it,
there was a disenchanting ceremony.
How did you get this?
It was my payment.
Your payment?
What are you talking about?
- What do you think?
- I don't know!
What happened?
Nothing. Nothing happened.
- My God, nothing at all.
- Tell me. I have to know.
You want details?
Is that what you want?
Yes, I want details.
I need to know everything. All of it.
What did he do to you?
All right! All right, already.
I'm not deaf, you know.
Jeez, keep your pants on!
I see we're a little late
with that advice.
Probably should've killed her.
Kill her, give her cab fare. Whatever.
The point is, you've turned a corner.
Yeah, you. Zuzu's petals.
It's about time.
If it had taken you much longer to
hit your bottom, I was gonna kick it.
- I don't understand what happened.
- What?
You're not the first guy who saw
what was lying next to him and went--
You're not, believe me.
It's called a moment of clarity,
my lamb, and you've just had one.
Sort of appalling to see
where you've gotten yourself.
- How do I get back?
- That's the thing.
You don't. You go on to
the new place, whatever that is.
I don't know if I can.
I've done things.
Questionable things.
Yes, you have. But you
didn't kill those lawyers.
That was slated to happen.
The Powers tried to work it
so it'd be without you.
You weren't much help.
If they wanted me to stay away,
why not tell me?
Would you listen? And what
makes you think they didn't?
Over and over and,
as for example, over?
They could've been more specific.
Isn't this the 'tude
that got you here?
If you're gonna switch back to
brood mode, we'd rather have you evil.
Then, at least, leather pants.
What now?
- What do you mean?
- What do the Powers want me to do?
Am I hearing voices? No, I'm not.
I was never your link with the Powers.
You lost that when
you fired your crew.
That's gonna be the
hardest part of this.
- Yeah.
- And there's a good chance...
...you can't put this back together.
It just....
- It depends, really.
- Whether they'll even talk to me.
No, it depends on whether
they live through the night.
And I gotta tell you, at the
moment, the odds? Not good.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Good night.
Hello?
Mrs. Sharp?
Anybody home?
Cordelia Chase here.
If you haven't gone to bed already....
Took me a little longer to
get here than I expected.
Hope you're still paying your bill.
Which I just happened to
bring with me.
Hello?
Well, that was helpful!
Human!
Destroyer of our spawn.
Destroyer of your...?
- Have we met?
- The others. Make them come to us.
- What others?
- Three are responsible. Three must pay.
I think you have me
confused with someone else.
I haven't destroyed
anyone's spawn. Promise.
Hey, you have a third eye
in the back of your head...
...just like that
little girl did before...
- ...we destroyed your spawn.
- We've located the wheeled one.
Where's the other?
The wheeled one?
- Angel!
- Invite me in. I haven't been here.
- Invite me in.
- If you'd shown interest....
Wesley.
Absolutely. I invite you in.
In, I invite you!
- What are they?
- The third eye indicates Skilosh.
It's the first time
I've had occasion to--
- How do I kill them?
- There are many ways.
- Wesley!
- Right, yes.
Hack it to pieces!
I think I got it.
I only pray Mrs. Starns isn't at home.
What are you doing here?
- She's not picking up.
- She wasn't at home before, either.
I stopped by before
I went to your place.
Did you? Just keep going straight.
So I guess you're probably
wondering why I'm back.
Hadn't occurred to me.
Take a right turn.
- I know how to get to your offices.
- Yes, you did pop by.
Stole a book.
- I'll avoid the bumps.
- I'd appreciate that.
Actually, it's kind of funny.
I recently got a gut wound myself.
Not a gunshot like you got there...
...but it was kind of...
...an antique sword, is what it was.
It went deep.
Yes, it did.
- Hey, guess who stabbed me?
- Darla.
Yeah.
Actually, kind of a funny story.
The reason I had this epiphany.
- Tell me about these Skilosh demons.
- Very well.
A family contracted us at Angel
Investigations to investigate...
...a third eye on the back
of their daughter's head.
Oh, really?
You kept the name?
Pardon?
You kept the name,
"Angel Investigations."
We're gonna change it.
- Go on.
- I diagnosed the girl's condition...
...as "infection by a Skilosh."
- With your books.
- Yes.
You were always so good with
your books. Made it look so easy.
You know, it isn't.
Skilosh: a violent, asexual,
self-replicating species of demon.
Has the habit of injecting its demon
spawn into the skull of a human host.
A key diagnostic symptom is the third
eye in the back of the host's head.
If this condition is not arrested...
...a newborn Skilosh will erupt
from the skull of its human host.
- But you guys saved the little girl?
- Yes, we did.
You did a good thing.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
"Hey, look behind you!" is
really not gonna work, is it?
Two more have been destroyed.
What?
Oh, no!
Wesley, Gunn! You killed them?
You horrible, ugly, three-eyed--
Three must pay.
Oh, two of you have
been destroyed. Okay.
Oh, that's bad.
- I'm sorry?
- More must rise.
No. Hey, hey, wait a sec! Guys!
- No! No more must rise, honest!
I've been impregnated by demon spawn
before. Didn't really work out.
Oh, God. Please don't
do this. Please, no!
Let go! Don't! Please!
No! Let go!
She's not here.
That doesn't bode well.
That truck's passed three times.
- Maybe she's out on a date.
- That's unlikely.
- It's Friday night.
- So?
We are talking about the same
Cordelia Chase, right?
Correct.
- Knowing her--
- But you don't.
You don't know her at all.
For months now, you haven't cared to.
Otherwise, you'd have realized
Cordelia has become very solitary.
She's not the vain, carefree
creature she once was.
Well, certainly not carefree.
It's the visions. The visions
that were meant to guide you.
You could turn away from them.
She doesn't have that luxury.
She experiences this city's pain,
and because of who she is...
...she's compelled to do
something about it.
It's left her little time
for anything else.
You'd have known that,
if your head wasn't up your...
...place that isn't
on top of your neck.
We have to find her.
We agree on that.
She could be in grave danger.
And even if she's not....
- Something's coming.
- Turn off the lights.
The Skilosh may have followed us.
Gunn!
- What are you doing here?
- Passing by. Saw the lights on.
- Besides, I work here.
- I thought you'd gone.
Yeah, but that don't mean
I wasn't coming back.
Did you think I'd
abandon you like this guy?
- No, certainly not.
- English, you know you my man.
I see you guys have bonded.
- We fight together.
- Hip to shoulder.
- He took a bullet for me.
- It was nothing.
- What's he doing here?
- Saw the host at Caritas.
He said my friends were in danger.
- What's he doing here?
- He had an epiphany.
- Why are you hiding?
- There was a demon attack at my home.
- I saved him.
- We were followed.
- Demon attack?
- Skilosh.
- I thought we got rid of that.
- We did.
That's why we're targeted
for retribution.
- Where's Cordy?
- We don't know.
- You checked her pad?
- I stopped by.
You enjoying your visit to 1973?
I meant her message pad.
Oh, right, yeah. That's a good idea.
Use this to rub the impression
of the last thing she wrote.
- Or we could just read the carbon.
- Or that.
- Directions.
- Let me see.
That's the Sharps' address, the
family whose daughter we treated.
She wrote that tonight.
You think she went there?
- She took the original.
- What'll they do?
I hate to imagine. We must prepare.
Get the de-oculation powder.
Guys. Guys?
Would she go there in the middle of
the night without calling you?
- They owe us money.
- Let's go.
Oh, God, you're still here.
You're not leaving, are you?
And no one's coming for me.
No one's expecting me anyplace.
No one's gonna miss me.
And how come I can see you?
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
- What is it?
- I don't know.
Nothing, I guess.
So you had an epiphany, did you?
Yeah.
What, you just wake up and bang?
It was sort of the other way around.
That's good you can have those.
Right, Wes?
Epiphanies, they're handy.
When will you have another?
- Gunn--
- No, I'm interested.
They can strike any time.
Next time you see a lawyer...
...you'll get epiphanied off at them.
- No.
- No? You don't think so?
Hope you don't have one
before we find Cordelia...
...because if something happens to
her, I might just have an epiphany.
- You okay?
- Yes.
Angel?
We should probably go.
Yo, Angel.
- You guys go ahead.
- What?
If I don't stop them,
they'll flank us at the house.
Then I'll meet you there.
I'll be there. Just get to Cordelia.
- Thank you. What do you see?
- She's in there.
- Is she--?
- She's alive.
- You sure?
- Yeah, her eyes are open.
- All three of them.
- Oh, dear.
- Wait. Three more.
- Eyes?
Demons.
The tribe's gathering. Gestation is
almost done. We have little time.
Where is he?
That's gotta hurt.
It'll hurt more when the thing
gestating inside her hatches.
Stop saying "gestating."
How long we gonna wait for Angel?
- We're not.
- Good.
- Why wait?
- We shouldn't.
- We've done fine without him.
- Yes.
- He orders us to wait and we do it?
- Hell, no.
- He may have changed his mind.
- True.
We're not going to sit idly by.
We're going in there...
...and we're saving our friend.
I say, let's do this.
- One thing.
- What?
I'm toppling over.
You're gonna tell me everything.
Everything you did with her.
All of it.
You're gonna tell me.
- Why?
- Because I wanna hear it from you.
Tell me!
No.
I'm sorry, Lindsey.
I really am.
I'm sorry she'll never love you.
I'm sorry you have to live with that.
That I didn't try harder to help you.
That you made the wrong choice.
Could've been the other one.
Be glad I had an epiphany.
Mind if I borrow your truck?
Gunn!
Wesley!
- We came to rescue you.
- I knew you would.
But they caught us
coming in the back door.
Thank you.
More must rise.
- This gonna hurt?
- A lot.
Angel, hi.
Hi.
You okay?
No.
- You're not?
- No.
You really hurt my feelings.
Darla?
I feel like such an idiot.
A lot of that going around.
I just couldn't....
My whole life has been
about being a cop.
If I'm not part of the force,
nothing I do means anything.
- It doesn't.
- Doesn't what?
Mean anything. In the greater
scheme, in the big picture...
...nothing we do matters.
There's no grand plan, no big win.
- You seem chipper about that.
- I guess I kind of worked it out.
If there's no great glorious end to
all this, if nothing we do matters...
...then all that matters
is what we do.
Because that's all there is.
What we do. Now, today.
I fought for so long for
redemption, for a reward...
...and finally just to beat the
other guy. But I never got it.
- Now you do?
- Not all of it.
All I wanna do is help.
I wanna help...
...because people shouldn't
suffer as they do.
Because if there's
no bigger meaning...
...then the smallest act of kindness
is the greatest thing in the world.
- You've had an epiphany.
- I say that, but nobody's listening.
I'm pretty much convinced,
since I'm alive to be convinced.
- You don't have to be a cop to--
- I'm okay.
I'm not headed for
another pill-a-thon.
I'm very grateful.
I never thought you'd
come for me, but...
...I got cut a huge break,
and I believe....
I don't know what I believe, but...
...I have faith.
I think maybe we're not alone in this.
Why?
Because I never invited you in.
Angel Investigations. We help
the helpless. How can we...
...help you?
The check is in the mail.
I'm sorry.
Before you say any more...
...we've discussed it,
and we're not ready--
It's okay, Wesley. I don't want
you to come back and work for me.
Oh. I see.
I wanna work for you.
You wanna work for us?
Yeah, I do.
Why?
Because I think I can help.
How do we know we can trust you?
I guess I'll just have to earn that.
No.
No!
The usual big scary, rising up in
a housing project in Topanga.
Why am I not on the floor this time?
I've got you.
Maybe he should drive?
Let's go.
Thank you,