Previously on Angel:
- Charles Gunn.
- Anne, meet Rondell and George.
- Somebody could have told me.
- You ain't been around.
You've been playing
demon-detective with your new family.
Hands on the wall, spread your feet.
Wait! Officer, wait!
- He took a bullet for me.
- It was nothing.
I see you guys have bonded.
None of us are ready just yet--
I don't want you to work for me.
I wanna work for you.
Cordy!
What did you see?
Are these vision
hangovers getting longer?
I wish it would stop hurting.
- Want to try my sashimi?
- Raw fish?
Maybe when hell freezes over.
What are you looking for?
Celebrities. They won't put them out
here. They put them back in the dark.
Not like here, where
it's bright and open...
...and everyone can
stare at you and....
It's a little exposed. Kind of public.
That public thing. It happens
when you go where people are.
No, I like people.
Normal people.
I wanna be one,
celebrate Cordy's good news.
- It's just a commercial.
- A national commercial. Here's to you.
I can't drink. I have to be up
at 4:30 a.m. for the shoot.
But continue toasting and praising.
- You'll knock them dead.
- Don't leave us when you get famous.
Don't worry.
I can't leave you guys while I'm still
the owner of debilitating visions.
I feel a little guilty.
Don't.
A $19 sashimi couscous appetizer
is money well spent.
How is it? Good? It ought to be good.
Delicious, but that's
not why I feel guilty.
I'm not cheap, I'm old.
I remember when a few bob got you a
meal, a bottle and a tavern wench.
- You were saying?
- I was saying...
...I feel guilty leaving you guys
mid-case to do a commercial.
Angel will contact his
informant in the morning.
- Is it a he or an it?
- Actually, both.
Then it/he points us to the thing
you saw in your vision.
The Haklar demon. The
informant will lead us to its grounds...
...where we manly men will
gather around and kill it to death.
Sounds like fun.
If you guys want more wine....
Not for me. That imported
stuff goes to your head.
- Should we get a flame thrower?
- For the Haklar?
If you want another bottle--
If we're in a tight space,
we could burn each other.
Right, right.
You're the boss. You'll decide.
A flame thrower is big and loud.
It might call unwanted attention.
Stealth being a larger part of--
- Isn't this interesting?
- What? My shawl?
- Shroud woven of a child's skin.
- What's he doing?
I know a Voctar witch when I see one!
I can read the markings--
- Looks different up close.
- It's beautiful, ma'am.
It's a beautiful, thousand-dollar
Laura Mina original.
My friend loves beautiful things
so much, he can't control himself.
Because he's from France.
We're so sorry. So sorry.
We could set the table on fire with a
flame thrower, draw more attention.
- Those markings, from afar, looked--
- Let's just eat and go without--
Oh, God.
- What is it? What do you see?
- Moo--
- Moo? Some sort of cow-monster?
- Move! The sashimi's coming up.
They'll take that off the bill.
Yes, Mum.
Yes, well, put him on.
Right. You too.
Hello, Father. Happy birthday.
How are you?
Good.
No, it's going quite well, actually.
Yes.
I have news. I've been put
in charge of our group.
Yes, as their leader.
No, it's a permanent position.
As permanent as these things--
No, I certainly won't be fired.
Well, yes, I was that one time. Yes.
Again. No, you're right.
I see how you--
Yes, I'd forgotten. Thank you.
Yes.
Just recently. It's going
quite well so far.
No, I think this time--
I hope it will be different.
No. No, you're right.
I see how you--
I just thought you'd be--
I thought you'd want to know.
Right. Well, again, happy birthday.
Okay.
Talking to someone?
- My father.
- English, Sr.? How is he?
- Well. It's his birthday.
- Nice.
He sends his greetings
to all in Tinseltown.
Sorry.
What are you doing here?
Getting a tan.
Not bursting into flames.
So, what are you doing here?
In your vision, did the Haklar--?
Shut up! Seth,
the director, is coming.
- Hi. Thanks for casting me.
- You're welcome. Lose the bathrobe.
- Excuse me?
- You don't speak English?
The wardrobe, I need to see it.
Lose the robe, princess.
Sure, sure.
Turn around.
Well, nothing wrong there.
Okay, turn.
- When does she go to makeup?
- I've been to makeup.
Take her back and tell David to get
rid of the circles under her eyes.
She looks like an abused woman.
- I had food poisoning.
- Yeah, right. You eat. Good one.
I should want to sleep with her.
I don't.
- Do you? Of course you don't.
- You're out of line.
Apologize to her.
Let me guess. Wannabe rocker
or part-time male model.
- Could be either.
- Apologize.
- Billy, get security.
- Angel--
- Who the hell you think you are?
- I'm the director.
You're smart bringing your
unemployed boyfriend onto my set...
...to tell me how to film.
Really helps your career.
- Sorry. He won't bother you anymore.
- I know.
Security's gonna toss his ass.
Now get into makeup and
hope they can work miracles.
Want me to rip his head off?
I can rip his head right off his body.
Are you trying to ruin my career?
Is this a conscious effort on your part?
- No, I just--
- You need to go now.
- Why are you still here? Go!
- I have to ask you a question.
What?
In your vision, did the Haklar eat
his victim whole or rip out the liver?
According to my informant...
...liver-eaters feed differently
than people-eaters.
I have to know which it was
so I can kill it.
I hate my whole life.
This Heckler demon
we're supposed to kill--
- Haklar. Two A's.
- This Haklar we're supposed to kill.
Give me the specs.
What should I know?
The Haklar, descended from the Klenzen
demons, can weigh up to three tons.
It awakes from hibernation during
full moons only to feed and mate.
Often simultaneously. Incapable of
speech, they learned to communicate...
...via a complex pattern
of timed facial tics...
...similar to our own Morse code.
It prefers a warm, moist climate--
- Wesley.
- Yes?
I meant how do we kill it?
Your standard slice-and-dice.
Hey!
- What are y'all doing?
- Got a situation.
You remember Rondell and George.
Certainly. I never
thanked you properly.
- I owe you men my life.
- It's cool.
You got shot because
you had our backs.
- How you feeling?
- Better, thank you.
- What's the situation?
- Vamps.
Making Mackenzie Park
their new restaurant.
- Many homeless there.
- They're the meals.
- Sounds like we need to set a trap.
- Trap's already set.
It is?
We know the drill.
Everything's in motion.
- You just need me to--
- Lend us your truck.
- My ride?
- It's still tricked out for dusting?
- Yeah, but--
- We wanna go in with all we got.
- Count me in.
- And the Haklar?
Angel finds it, page me.
It lives by Lake Hollywood.
Let's hurry. A 5K race starts there soon.
Consider yourself paged.
I gotta take this. Wait for me.
We'll hook up at base camp
and go out together.
Whatever, G. Let's roll, Ron.
Angel, is everything all right?
- It's Cordy.
- What about her?
- More headaches?
- What happened?
Nothing happened.
It's just....
Acting's her dream?
She wants to live that?
- With those people? I don't get it.
- Who?
Mr. I'm-a-Commercial-Director-
So-I'm-the-Center-of-the-Universe?
If you're not in showbiz,
you're a step down.
We only save the world.
The way he talks to her!
It's like she's his commodity
or his slave.
The worst part? She took it.
When has she taken crap from us?
- Never. And the day after never.
- Exactly.
He's also got her wearing this
flimsy swimsuit that covers, like...
...nothing.
- Appalling.
- Disgusting.
- Shouldn't we be killing something?
- Absolutely.
Good. Let's get this show on the road.
Very superstitious
The devil's on his way
A broken looking-glass
Seven years of bad luck
Good things in your past
Oh, if you believe in things
that you don't understand
Then you suffer
Superst--
It's okay. Everything's fine.
Nothing to worry about.
It's all part of the show.
It goes on smooth like a lover's kiss.
It's the only suntan lotion
good enough for our man.
Cut! Cut!
- You're in his light.
- Still?
I told you, you have
to bend over more.
If I bend over more,
I'll fall out of my top.
Then you'll be out of his light.
Everyone wins.
- Isn't there something we--?
- You aren't here to play Ophelia.
Show cleavage, say the line.
Or do you wanna waste more time?
Got it.
- Has it--?
- Stopped bleeding? Yeah.
Cordelia.
Hi.
Look, if I was out of line today--
If you were out of line? If?
You're comfortable with your use
of the word "if" here, are you?
Sorry I embarrassed you.
Who am I kidding?
I embarrassed myself.
I just wanted to act, that's all.
For them to appreciate my talent.
I never wanted to feel like this.
- Wasn't Gunn with you?
- He had to take care of some vampires.
How was the big fight?
We killed it just before
it devoured some power walkers.
- Horrible.
- I know.
I saw it in my vision.
Not the Haklar, the walkers.
Walking I get, but power walking?
Why not run for a shorter time?
Weird.
- One of them hit him.
- A walker?
She felt I disrespected
the Haklar's culture.
This town sucks.
Am I happy to see you!
You're still a knight for hire, yeah?
I'm hiring. I need you
to kill something.
Here are the particulars:
It's a Drokken.
- Drokken?
- It's not in the books.
- It's from another world.
- How so?
Portal. Right in the middle
of my tune. Threw me off.
I hate to disappoint an audience.
What's important is you kill it.
I can't stress enough.
Kill it. You must.
- Where is it?
- No idea.
But I imagine it's getting
pretty hungry by now.
- That's it?
- Why is it here?
What's it want?
What's it capable of?
Who cares? It trashed
my club, my clientele.
Isn't violence was impossible there?
Isn't it a sanctuary?
I didn't say it killed anyone.
It knocked over a few of my regulars.
There were angry glances.
I sensed some bad intentions.
Not a nice fella. Bad beast.
Did I mention the teeth?
- You mentioned them.
- Are you gonna help me?
We can start at Caritas,
do a circular search.
Hope we get lucky.
Angel....
I didn't mean
to step on your toes, Wesley.
Quite all right.
- He's our leader.
- It's been a long time coming.
Kudos. Nice choice of conductor.
- So what do we do now?
- Well, um....
Angel's right. A circular search
for the beast seems best.
I like it.
Hey, what's with her?
Food poisoning.
Very expensive appetizers.
Or possibly a vision.
- Okay?
- Why does everyone ask me that?
Do I look okay?
- What'd you see?
- A woman at the public library.
She works there.
She was reading a book.
As scary as that sounds,
crazed Drokken on the loose.
I was here first.
There was an opening behind her.
Something magical. A portal.
- A portal?
- Like the one the Drokken used?
- We don't know that.
Let's get the library.
They close soon.
Great, The Powers That Be
have an interest in--
I mean--The problem I brought you.
What a break.
You coming?
I...thought you'd never ask.
Junior, where is everybody?
What's wrong?
What--?
- Did they make him drink?
- We don't know.
I have the weirdest sense of déjà vu.
How come you and me always end up
in a library? Let's do something fun.
- Like what?
- Elton's in town. Back row seats?
I don't do crowded.
Elton starts "Yellow Brick Road"...
...you feel like the only person there.
Hi. How are you?
You...you're...
...here for the children's program.
- Yes. Yes, I am.
- It's tomorrow.
- Yes.
I don't perform without
checking the space.
Oh! Well, the kids will flip
over your costume.
- It looks so real.
- Thanks.
- Not the horns. They're hard to fake.
- If you only knew.
The reading area's down that way.
Toodles. See you
and the munchkins tomorrow.
We close in five minutes.
We're looking for
a woman who works here.
- Who's that?
- Okay. She's tall.
She has brown hair.
Wears glasses. Pretty.
Sorry.
She wears a locket, shaped like a
ball or an apple, I think.
An apple? Fred wore one of those.
- Fred?
- Winifred. We called her Fred.
Do you know where she is?
She disappeared five years ago.
They never found her.
Police said if she didn't show up, well....
- We stopped hoping long ago.
- This is her.
Tell us about her?
She worked with me.
She wanted to be a physicist.
- The day she disappeared--
- Oh.... It was creepy.
She was cataloging in Foreign Language
and then she was gone.
Angel, why don't you look there?
I'll look over here and....
- Why are we here?
- I saw the portal here in my vision.
The reading room? To die for!
Stage, chair, fabulous colors.
I'm tempted to come tomorrow.
We're doing what you wanted us to do.
I liked that search pattern you pitched.
Are we going to do that?
Here it is. This is the book that
Fred had in my vision.
"Scrsqwrn." What language is that?
Last checked out May 6, 1996...
...and returned May 7, 1996.
The day she disappeared.
"Pat, I'll buy a vowel."
Landok? Is that you?
- You know him?
- That doesn't mean you should stop.
- Please continue.
- Can it be you?
Krevlornswath of the Deathwok Clan?
- Do it, Angel.
- Krevlornswath?
Of the Deathwok Clan?
- I prefer Lorne.
- Lorne?
Yes, Lorne. Though I
generally don't go by that....
- Green?
- Huh?
Right! Lorne Greene.
Bonanza?
15 years on the air
means nothing to you?
Okay, now I feel old.
- What is this place?
- Los Angeles.
- This isn't a hot spot.
- Is it a prison?
Whoa, big fella. Put it down.
They're friends.
Angel, Cordelia, Wesley...
- ...this is Landok.
- Landokmar of the Deathwok Clan.
Deathwok Clan again.
- The two of you are--
- Cousins.
- Your cousin?
- Your vanishing was a great mystery.
Long story, boring ending.
It wouldn't interest you.
We hoped you died atoning
in the Sacrificial Canyons of Trelinsk.
It's been fun. But we have to go.
You'll be fine.
New people come to L.A. each day.
Were you abducted here?
- I came by portal.
- We will find a path back to our home.
- We'll go together.
- My ticket was one-way.
You won't return to remove shame
from your Life-Giver?
Is anyone else hungry?
How about Italian?
- Your mother's burden is terrible.
- Misses me, does she?
She rips your images...
...and feeds them to swine.
Butchers them...
- ...and feeds them to dogs.
- That's Ma. You pick.
I'm game for anything.
- You coward.
- These people...
- ...don't care about our family.
- Sure we do.
Yes! Let's hear about it.
Okay, for your information,
not a coward.
We were just on a Drokken hunt.
We must return to it.
- Excuse us--
- A Drokken's near?
- I will assist.
- Find your own.
- How do we kill it?
- Pierce it with thromite.
Sorry, cuz. Thromite: not exactly
existing in this world. Thanks.
Killing it will be most difficult.
- Decapitation?
- Stabbing?
- Electrocution?
- We've had luck with that before.
You must use thromite. The Drokken's
strong and fast, hard to hit.
- We gotta find it first.
- I can track it.
- You can?
- It leaves waves of hostility.
And you can read these waves?
All your people do this?
- Those who submit to training.
- Everybody on board.
- Guilt trip leaving.
- Show me where it appeared.
- I will help you.
- We welcome your help.
- You should've waited for me.
- We've been waiting for months.
Our path is true, our arrival late.
The Drokken has consumed.
It'll be at maximum power.
What's he doing?
He's channeling to identify its aura.
I use that to find destiny, and I'm a freak.
He uses it to hunt,
he's the golden spawn. Go figure.
So he's a hero back home?
Talk about weird values.
A world of only good and evil.
Black and white.
No music, no art.
Just champions roaming the country
fighting for justice. Boring.
Problems solved with a sword.
No one admits to having feelings
and emotions or talks about them.
- Can you imagine living like that?
- Not really.
Why isn't Gunn answering?
What if he's in trouble?
Maybe he's in the middle
of his stake-o-rama.
Last time we went chasing
after him, you got shot.
Point taken.
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
- We're missing something.
- When we get back...
- ...I'll decipher it.
- I mean something bigger.
- Like what?
- I don't know.
I feel like we're chasing after
the monster, which is good...
...but we're missing something.
It's this way. The aura's strong.
It's not far.
- What do you want, a medal?
- Krevlornswath mocks me?
Just the L.A. in me.
The Krevlornswath who refused
the traditional hunting and gathering?
I'll tell you a secret.
While you were hunting...
...I was with the señoritas,
gathering a little love.
- You brought cowardice to the joust.
- For the last time...
...not a coward.
I saw both sides of the joust.
How can you joust someone
when you agree with them?
It has taken food to consume later.
More food?
Oh, you mean people?
Oh! You mean people!
You sure this is where it came?
I am sure.
What do we do, Wesley?
We don't have Gunn.
- If it's as strong as Landok says--
- Yeah?
I have flares.
The light will distract him...
- ...long enough for us to--
- Enough words!
Patience: not a virtue with my people.
Angel, what are you-- What are you....
But we don't have a plan.
- Where is my sword?
- You're hurt.
- Fetch it.
- You're poisoned.
- There's time to die later.
- Poisoned?
The Drokken's bite is deadly
to my people.
- Is there an antidote?
- Back in our world.
It's going after the woman.
Find her, get her out.
I'll find the Drokken.
Krevlornswath of the Deathwok Clan,
my sword!
Hello? Martyr complex?
You can't even lift your arm.
Hey, you want food?
I can be food.
Pretty tasty here.
Come on, where are you?
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty!
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
It's all right.
I'll get you out of here.
Don't be scared.
That was fun.
- If I perish tonight--
- Stop. No perishables allowed.
- You'll perform the rituals.
- I certainly will not.
I won't receive glory if you don't.
Glory you won't have.
You're the only one here
who can officiate.
We must get him home or he'll die.
- I think I understand.
- What?
- This book. It's how we do it.
- What do you mean?
If he reads from it,
it'll send him back.
My vision showed what happened
to that girl Fred.
The portal works both ways.
- And if it sends something here?
- It won't.
- How can you be sure?
- I can't. I just am.
Don't ask me how I know, I just know.
Let's go.
Krevlornswath of the Deathwok Clan,
give me your pledge.
Will you perform the rituals?
I won't have to. No one's dying.
- Where'd it appear?
- There. Talk about upstaging me.
Cordy.
Just read aloud from it.
Well, that's the theory.
To defeat the Drokken,
you must be a noble warrior.
Well, you know.... I try.
I am happy to know you.
- Landok, be safe.
- Bye, Krevlornswath of Deathwok Clan.
Tell my mother I--
Tell her I threw myself into the
Canyons of Trelinsk.
- I feel we will meet again someday.
- Oh, God, I hope not.
"Klmprkthr pwlznth wrv...
...blrpnkntr vrbqwptl spgr drpvln--"
What say we all forget
this ever happened?
I'm down with that. Wesley?
Fine with me.
Cordy?
Cordy!
Oh, crap!
Thank you,