- Previously on Angel:
- That's her.
So you're what they
brought back in that box as human.
- We want him dark, not dead.
- Forces can change Angel to Angelus.
He knows happiness, he goes evil.
We were together 150 years.
- The middle one.
- She has the sight.
She is innocence.
We'll turn her into one of us.
The gypsies gave you a soul.
A filthy soul! No!
- I remember everything.
- You have a soul now.
Soon those memories start
eating away at you.
Believe me, I know.
- What is it, Wesley?
- "It"?
There's no it.
It's nothing, really.
Just popping around,
see if everything's all right.
- Fine.
- Oh, good. Good.
You're certain?
Uh-huh.
Good night.
You're still here.
Apparently. So you're sure there's
nothing on your mind?
That is to say, nothing you'd
like to perhaps share?
Nope.
Really?
Hello, Lindsey.
- You're bleeding.
- I guess I am.
- Something happened?
- Oh, God, yes.
So many things, I remember them all.
Which one were you thinking of?
It was too soon.
We shouldn't have sent you to him.
Lindsey. You never talk
about yourself, Lindsey.
Got a girlfriend? Boyfriend?
Someone special?
There's no one.
No. No, there really isn't, is there?
You can be with someone for 150 years,
think you know them.
Still, doesn't work out.
Angelus.
Oh, you should've seen us together.
He was different then.
And so was I.
Do you know what we've become?
Enemies.
Oh, no. Much worse.
Now we're soul mates.
Someone close the shutters.
Seems wrong that I should die
while the sun is still so bright.
You'll not see it again.
Before it sets,
you will have left this life.
I didn't ask for a priest.
Who invited him here?
You did. You cried out for me
in your delirium.
I don't remember.
Do you even know what I am?
A woman of some property.
No husband, no inheritance.
Yes, I know what you are.
- I'm a whore.
- Well, yes. That too.
You should've asked for a priest long
ago. Your life may have been better.
And you should've visited me
before today, Father.
Your life may have been more
interesting for it.
Are you prepared now to renounce
Satan and beg God his forgiveness?
God never did anything for me.
Leave us.
You can't save her life.
Perhaps I can still save her soul.
My soul is well past saving.
Let the Devil take me if he wants.
Either way, I die.
No, you will not die.
You will be reborn.
I know you.
I came to you last night.
I sang to you from that window.
I remember now.
You're Death?
No.
What then?
I'm your savior.
God never did anything for you.
But I will.
I think this is a really bad idea.
We can't wait for Wolfram & Hart
to make a move. Let's get ahead.
- Will it involve kidnapping?
- All we do is find her.
This is the woman you didn't know
was in your bedroom for three weeks?
- That was different.
- Different, yeah.
- Cordelia has a point.
- Finally!
Before, Darla wanted to be found.
Now she's out among 6 million people.
She could be anywhere.
We're detectives, we investigate.
That's what we're good at.
It's what we suck at.
Unless there's a website:
"www.Darla-is-stashed-here.com,"
we're out of luck.
It's not gonna be easy.
Before, he said he could smell her.
How about we cruise around
with the top down...
...and you take big whiffs?
We'll wait until after the sun sets.
Big firm, they gotta have housing.
It's not as if they
flew her in from Miami.
She was raised from the depths
of hell by an ancient ritual.
They got to put her up.
That's an expense.
You think these lawyers have
no way to write that off?
- I'll examine their real estate.
- Subsidiary holdings as well.
She'd want something with a view.
Darla always loved a view.
Angelus.
The Latinate for "Angel."
It's marvelous!
His name would be legend
had he left anyone alive to tell it.
You had a nice trip.
I'm so glad.
We cut a bloody swath
through Wales and England.
He was magnificent.
Yorkshiremen. Tough as leather.
Darla tells me you're a master.
The Master. He commands our order.
The Order of Aurelius.
We are the select, the elite.
And you live in the sewers?
We lurk below, giving tribute
to the Old Ones...
...awaiting that promised day
when we will arise.
Arise and lay waste
to the world above!
- Why'd you want to do that?
- Huh?
Well, I mean, have you
been above lately?
It's quite nice.
Me, I could never live in a
rat-infested stinkhole like this.
Pardon me, but I gotta have
me a proper bed or I'm a terror.
Isn't that right, love?
He's young.
And this one,
down and goose feathers...
...and the finest linens.
And the view.
She's always gotta have the view,
don't you, my lamb?
We fed recently.
The blood is still hot in his veins.
You noticed that?
We stalk the surface to feed
and grow our ranks.
We do not live amongst
the human pestilence.
I'll be honest. You couldn't
with that face, could you?
Angelus!
It's not stuck like that, is it?
The Master has outgrown
human features.
Will I get
a bat nose like that?
Few vampires are cunning enough
to have lived this long.
Which you now demonstrate.
Naples. You and me, Darla.
What do you say?
Angelus.
This is no place for you,
bound to the likes of him.
You should show respect.
You belong by my side.
Out in the world...
...feeding as we like,
taking what we need.
I'll give you that view you crave.
I'll give you everything.
Tell the truth.
Whose face do you wanna
look at forever?
His or mine?
Idiot. I made her.
You're leaving with
the stallion, aren't you?
No, let them go.
It won't last.
I give it a century, tops.
"Darla."
"Anglo-Saxon derivation,
meaning 'Dear one."'
Didn't come into common usage
until 100 years after her birth.
He must've given it to her.
I didn't even know her real name.
Any luck?
Not yet. Working on it.
- Something will come up.
- Yes, that's my fear.
Angel, your record pertaining
to Darla has been...
...spotty at best.
I killed her, Wesley, and she
came back. They brought her back.
I need to know why. Why human?
Perhaps that was the
only way they could hope...
...to control her
with any degree of success.
Angel, this might be why
they've brought her back.
You have all your attention focused
on finding this one woman.
They went through all this trouble
just to keep me distracted?
It is possible.
And if that's the case....
It's working.
Are you hungry?
I could grab some sandwiches
from the vending machine.
It's not exactly
gourmet cuisine, but--
Lindsey.
Holland.
Darla, how are you?
I'm fine, Holland. Good to see you.
Always a pleasure.
Lindsey, a word. You'll excuse us.
I'll be right outside.
I thought we were very clear on this,
She's made contact.
It's not prudent to have her here.
I know. I just didn't feel
I could leave her alone.
There's a problem.
She shows post-traumatic--
- She's cracking up.
- I wouldn't say that.
She's ahead of schedule.
- What?
- We'll have to accelerate matters.
But we're ready.
You did the right thing. Good work.
Don't let her leave here.
Oh, letter openers, staple guns,
even pens...
...you should remove
sharp items from your office.
So beautiful.
Not a blemish, not a freckle.
We should've preserved that beauty.
Still, he won't now age.
No, but he'll rot. Seems a pity.
When I bit into him,
I could hear the ocean.
Of course you could.
I'm full and warm, yet all alone.
- That's not true. You've got us.
- Not in the least.
You won't even hurt me just a bit.
- All you have to do is ask.
- No.
- He's too full of you, Grandmother.
- Stop calling me that.
Don't be cross. I could be your mommy.
Make yourself a playmate.
I could. I could pick the wisest and
bravest knight in all the land...
...and make him mine forever
with a kiss.
Watch where you're going!
Or you could take
the first idiot that comes along.
- Think she'll find a good one?
- I found you.
We think that the search is over.
- Property's owned by Wolfram & Hart.
- Annapolis.
- A Wolfram & Hart client.
- That's slim.
- It has a view.
- Not enough.
- And Berber carpets.
- Narrow it down further.
And my sister lives in unit 319.
- You don't have one.
- I do.
My older, way older, like 400 years...
...older, blond sister, Darla.
No last name.
I've been trying to find her...
...because Mom and Dad
are in the coma.
Sue, the property manager,
was very helpful.
She even cried.
Let's go.
Perhaps I should contact Gunn.
He and I could check this out.
We do the reconnaissance.
Then we can all decide
how to proceed, as a team.
Probably a good idea.
It's 1 p.m. and that's
a Sun Valley address.
Right.
- Sun.
- I was thinking Valley.
Why go there if you don't have to?
Darla.
Say that again?
I just....
I said your name, Darla.
Sounds so odd, doesn't it?
What do you mean?
It wasn't my name when I was human.
First time I was human, I mean.
What was your name?
I don't remember.
I'm not her, whoever she was.
I was Darla for so long.
Then I wasn't.
I wasn't anything. I just stopped.
He killed me, I was done.
Then you brought me back.
Yes.
What did you bring back?
What am I?
That girl whose name
I can't remember...
...or did you bring back
something else?
The other thing?
Both.
Neither. You're just you...
- ...whatever that is.
- Why haven't you kissed me?
You've been dying for it.
- I didn't know if you wanted me to.
- Should that matter?
Do you think I ever hesitate
when I want something?
Life's too short.
Believe me, I know.
Four hundred years,
and still too short.
That's how humans get what they want.
I remember that much.
Do you like it?
It's nice.
It's not me you wanna screw.
What?
It's him.
You all think you can use me
to get to Angel.
Maybe.
What am I?
I don't know, and I don't care.
- Now do you care?
- No.
That's how vampires get things.
What am I?
- Darla.
- Is that it? Am I Darla?
Yes.
Careful, Darla would snap you in half.
Is that who I am?
- I know what you're going through.
- No, nobody understands.
Nobody can understand.
I can feel this body dying, Lindsey.
I can feel it decaying every moment.
It's being eaten away
by this thing inside.
It's a cancer, this soul.
You took him from me. You stole him.
- You gave him a soul.
- He must suffer...
- ...as all his victims have.
- That is no justice.
Whatever pain he caused was momentary.
Over in an instant...
...or an hour.
But what you've done will make
him suffer for eternity.
Remove the filthy soul
so my boy might return to me.
Angelus has gone away. Where is he?
Drusilla, the camp.
Go on! Kill things.
He'll be very cross...
...if he finds we had a lovely
slaughter without him.
He'll join us soon.
Now do as you're told.
Okay.
In that wagon is your family.
Your family will die tonight
without my protection.
But if you do as I say,
your family can live.
What?
Pretty music. Pretty, pretty music.
They cry out for mercy.
- They cry out for mercy.
- Show none.
Did someone break in?
Well, us.
You guys did this? Real mature.
This is the way we found it.
No forced entry evident.
- Not till we got there.
- It seems she did this.
She smashed all the mirrors.
- Why?
- It's obvious.
- It's not.
- She feels the weight of her soul.
We don't know that.
- She was a vampire who now has a soul.
- So why don't you smash mirrors?
I don't have to look
at myself in them.
We have to find her.
- Angel--
- She needs help.
It might be what somebody
would like you to think.
- Angel.
- Cordy, just take a message.
So this is a setup?
- Don't rule it out.
- Angel!
Cordy, please, I'm talking.
Hi, Darla. He can't talk now.
He'll call you back
once he's found you.
- Darla?
- My boy. My darling boy.
Where are you?
Better question: Where was I?
I don't remember anything.
It's a great big nothing,
Could it be there's no hell?
There's a hell, I've been to one,
I told him no one could understand,
But I was wrong, wasn't I?
My boy knows.
- I know.
- You said you'd give me everything,
Do you remember that?
I believed it then.
I still do,
I'll do whatever I can.
It's been centuries since
I've had to be afraid.
- And now I'm sick with it.
- I know.
Angel.
Darla, what are you doing?
Help me.
- Just put down the phone,
- Darla?
Hang up the phone.
It's okay.
Darla?
It's okay. All right?
Just put it down.
- Everything okay?
- Yes, we're fine.
- Mr. Manners told me to--
- No, leave.
I have to go to him, Lindsey.
Don't say that.
- He's the only one. He can help me.
- No. I can help you too.
No. No, you can't.
You don't have it in you. I'm sorry.
- Let's go to Mr. Manners' office.
- I'll handle this. Go.
- She's not leaving here.
- I said go!
Darla?
- She's not leaving here,
- I said go!
Come on, let's go,
You gotta come with me,
You not only allowed her to escape,
you facilitated it.
Things were confusing.
Things are often confusing for you.
Especially when it comes to her.
You allowed yourself
to be ruled by emotions.
What about the guard?
Family's been notified.
Police have a suspect in custody.
You're off this project.
- I can find her.
- We picked her up two blocks away.
She's safe?
- We won't discuss it further.
- If you think--
This situation has gone
out of control.
I'm terminating the project.
Terminating?
Go home, Lindsey. Get some rest.
We'll start fresh tomorrow.
- Want me to come?
- I have to do this alone.
- Thanks.
- Angel.
I know, I could walk into a trap.
- I get that.
- You don't.
I can't turn my back.
No, you shouldn't.
You know what she was.
What we were.
I know what she's going through.
Maybe she won't have to go
through it alone.
You're not alone.
You may be right.
She may experience this as you did.
You wandered for 100 years,
never seeking redemption.
That's right. I sought her.
You're so warm. You've just fed.
- You found me.
- You can't resist war.
You always talked about China.
I just followed the bodies.
You never used to be so careless.
Maybe I wanted to be found.
- Spike and Dru?
- They're here.
Probably out in the riots.
Maybe starting a new one.
I should kill you.
- Go ahead.
- Is that why you've come?
Too much of a coward
to end your own existence?
Release that filthy soul?
If you like.
I can still smell it, you know.
That's not all.
You reek of vermin. Is that
what you've been living off of?
This should be nothing.
Go ahead, Darla.
Make sure you cut clean to the bone.
What do you want?
- A second chance.
- What?
I want things to be like they were.
You and me together.
Darla, I miss the view.
- It's impossible.
- It's not impossible.
- You have a soul.
- I'm still a vampire.
You're not.
I don't know what you are anymore.
You know what I am.
You made me, Darla.
- I'm Angelus.
- Not anymore.
I can be again.
Give me a chance to prove it to you.
You almost made me believe you.
Believe it.
We can have the whirlwind back.
- We can do this.
- Yes, we can.
- We can do anything.
- Anything we like.
Where is she?
- I was--
- No.
Just enough breath
to tell me where she is.
We help the helpless,
How can we help you? Hello?
I was trying to call you.
They'll kill her. Stop it.
She needs you, please.
- You're a liar.
- It's true!
Where?
In an abandoned bank.
Wolfram & Hart's property.
- I'm pretty sure that's where--
- Pretty sure?
I'm not in the loop on this.
It's where they do that stuff.
Where the vaults used to be.
If this is a trick,
I'll come back for you.
I might be back for you anyway.
Darla?
Darla.
Angelus?
The whirlwind, Angelus.
- What's over here?
- Nothing.
Bodies. Let's find something warm.
Yes, some missionaries.
We'll drain the piety
right out of them.
Where have you been?
- May I tell?
- No need to be humble.
My little Spike just killed
himself a slayer.
Did you hear that?
Congratulations.
That makes you one of us.
Don't be so glum, mate.
One slayer snuffs it,
another one rises.
There's a new Chosen One
getting chosen now.
When this new bird shows up,
I'll give you first crack at her.
I smell fear.
This whole place reeks of it.
It's intoxicating.
Let's go. This rebellion's boring me.
Are you with me, Angel?
Why aren't you with me?
Sorry, lady. It's just us.
Where have you been?
Darla.
Answer me.
Just out. Why?
- Feeding?
- Yeah.
On vermin?
No.
- Don't lie to me.
- I've killed men. You've seen it.
Rapists and murderers.
Thieves and scoundrels.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
Only evildoers,
that's all you hunt now.
You swore. You said if I took
you back, you'd prove yourself.
- And I will.
- Good.
Now's your chance.
I went back before dawn.
They were still cowering there...
...praying to their God for salvation.
But their only savior
was at the waterfront...
...dining on rats.
I won't be made a fool, Angelus.
Not by you.
Not by anyone.
- I didn't mean--
- While Spike killed a slayer...
...you were saving missionaries.
From me.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
No more words.
Act.
Darla?
Everything okay?
Family's been notified,
- Did you re-notify his family?
- Lindsey.
You played me, and her.
- You had to believe it.
- Why?
Because she had to believe it.
Angel has to.
The crisis needed to be real.
You think she'll give him
that happiness?
He'll come on our side? Won't happen.
He'll never take advantage of her.
You don't understand him.
There's no prospect for intimacy.
Don't torture yourself.
- What do you expect him to do?
- What he will do.
What he must do.
Save her soul.
She'll be okay.
Maybe we should get her a doctor.
No doctors.
Angelus.
Sorry, I know you're Concussion Gal,
but around here it's Angel.
Just Angel, okay?
Guys, you mind?
Just give us a minute.
- Yeah, of course.
- No problem.
Thought I was dead.
You're not dead.
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
I know what you mean.
I'm so lucky to have
someone who understands.
Who knows.
That's something you never had.
- Wasn't your fault.
- No, no.
But there's so much that is.
It's gonna be okay.
I knew you'd help me.
I knew if I could only get to you....
Funny, that's why
they brought me back.
To get to you.
Now I find I need you
just as I've always needed you.
You'll make the pain stop, won't you?
Takes time.
It takes moments.
Do it.
Now.
What?
Make me what I was.
- Darla--
- You said you'd help me.
I will.
I want to. But not like this.
Turn me back. My God!
I can't bear this pounding chest
for another instant!
It's a gift.
To feel that heart beat...
...to know really and for once
that you're alive.
You're human again, Darla.
You know what that means?
Of course I do.
It means pain and suffering
and disease and death.
I released you from this world once.
I gave you eternal life.
It's time to return the favor.
Favor?
Is that what you think?
You think you did me a favor?
You damned me.
If it's such a punishment,
take out your revenge. Pay me back.
Please.
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
You won't.
I can't seem to be what I'm not.
I'm sorry.
You disgust me.
- Darla, wait.
- No!
Don't look for me again.
Thank you,