Previously on ghost whisperer...
No!
I want you to remember
me this way, please.
No. not you.
- I will always love you, melinda.
- Oh, please not you.
I am so empty without you.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- No, you have to cross over.
I don't want to.
Jim, no!
- You're back.
- Do I know you?
Look, I see the same guy that you see.
Different hair, nose,
eyes. It's not jim.
I just know what I see
when I look in those eyes,
And jim is in there
somewhere. He just has to be.
Do you believe in the afterlife?
Wait, you're not gonna tell me you
think I'm your husband reincarnated,
Because you're the only sane
person I've met since I woke up.
It's not much, but maybe you
could help me finish my garage.
And you could live there
while you do the work,
Just until you figure
out your next move.
Will you tell me what
is going on between us?
Do you know how lucky you are?
You are gonna get a second
shot at your one true love.
Oh! Oh. Hey. You're up early.
Hey, Sam. Yeah, just... you know.
Trying to be good.
Yeah, me, too. Get a workout in.
You want to, uh...
- Together?
- Ooh, I don't know.
- No, that's stupid of me.
- I'm sorry. what?
This is probably a time when,
you know, you want to be alone.
- After what you've been through...
- No, it's not that.
- Get your stuff together.
- Right.
Something you probably did with
your husband, huh? in the morning?
- I don't want to get in your way.
- No. not at all. um...
He worked a lot of weird hours,
and liked to sleep in a lot.
You're really not in my way at all.
I should... well...
Ah, nice work, Sam. um...
Have a good morning. I'll run that way.
I'll go this way.
- See ya.
Why couldn't I just say "your
legs are longer than mine,
"and I might not be able to keep up. "
What is so hard with saying that?
Well, it's probably
better than saying, "hey,
You're the love of my life in a
new body, "and every time I see you,
My knees go weak. "
Ugh. my knees, my legs.
I fumble with words, it's
like my voice gets shaky.
I'm a total dork... whoa!
Hey, Sam.
- Hey. How you doin', Sam?
- Hey, Delia. Hey look...
I've had this stuff in my truck
for a couple of days... unh!
And I've been meaning to give it to
you, but every time I see you, I just.
Forget.
It's not like I don't forget
everything else I've done in my life, I
mean. How to read a blueprint I made,
- the name of my dog.
- You have a dog?
No. but, I mean, that's what I
think about when I wake up, you know?
Anyhow, this is all yours
to keep, or sell, or toss.
Wow, you've got some nice things
in here. Where did you get them?
Well, I got a job doing some demo
on a big house off of route 18.
They're getting rid of all the hardware
- Do you have a first aid kit I can...
- It's ok. it's just a cut.
Here. here you go.
You look a little pale.
You have got to stop skipping breakfast.
It's, you know, low blood sugar.
Yeah. yeah. um, you said
that there was more stuff?
Yeah, in my truck, but... There's
also tons more back at the site.
- Can I go look at it? Yeah,
- I was going there right now.
Yeah, we started the job
from the back of the house.
I don't know if the owner wants to
gut it or tear it down, but uh...
I don't think you're gonna find
too much high-end stuff here.
- Is there water around here anywhere?
- Water? why?
Well, the tiles. I just was...
I don't know. is there
a fountain or a pool?
There's a well right there. Is
that what you were looking for?
Why not, huh? It is a wishing well.
Careful what you wish for.
Are you sure this little girl is...
- What do you call it?
- Attached to him? No.
But as soon as Sam made his wish,
she was right out of the well,
- Standing next to him, warning.
- Warning you or him?
Who knows? maybe anybody who
comes by the well. But she was
- definitely focused on him.
- Well, do you know what he wished?
You got me.
It had to be to get his memory
back. And if so, what's the
problem? We all know it's jim's
spirit. You know it. even I know.
What? what's that look for?
- Believing me.
- So, what are you going to do?
Stop worrying about myself and
the things I can't control...
Help a dead little girl whose
spirit is stuck down a well.
- Do you know if she ever lived in the house?
- The last owner was a widow.
She had children, but no daughters.
The place is, like, 100 years old.
So, you're searching for what?
A missing or dead child
over the last century?
Basically. Or I wait until she
appears again and then try to
Figure out if her warning
was a threat or a promise.
It's still good. why
are they tossing it?
Contractor wants all new, you know?
Man, I think I just lost
an eardrum. You heard that?
Yeah, it was Bob's truck.
- But twice?
- I don't think so.
- Help me with this.
- Yeah.
Sam, you ok? yeah.
It's Melinda.
Hang on a second.
- You just got in. How did you get...
- Uh, naked? um, sorry.
Let me turn down the radio.
Sorry. I had the radio on a little loud.
- Didn't you hear me?
- no. um...
Hang on a second.
So, uh, hey. what's up?
What happened? did you hurt yourself?
Well, not that I know of.
And nothing that my doctor here or
the one back home knows about, either.
What do you mean?
I thought it had something
to do with the car accident.
But that turns out to be
a straight up head injury.
I mean, sure. It could cause muscle
trauma. Why am I feeling it now?
- When did it start?
- Well, it's weird.
The first time I felt it, I heard a
car backfire. It was like a rifle shot.
I heard it twice, but
it only happened once.
I'm sure I just imagined it, but...
Well, don't brush it off. I
mean, it could be a memory.
You know? one that you want to
forget, But it could lead to others.
Well, I hope so. I mean, I'm
going through all these boxes,
All my old stuff. Just
trying to jog something loose.
And? I don't know. I listen to cds,
I see pictures of people I'm
supposed to have known, you know?
I have a cell phone here. what do I do?
I call these people and say, "hey.
do you remember me?" 'cause I don't.
You said that it happened at
work. Were you near the well?
Nah, I was in and out of the house, you
know. Coming and going past the well.
And has anything weird happened
there? To you or anyone?
- No. not that I can think of. why?
- What about the owners? I mean,
Have you talked to anyone
who lived in the house?
I'm just working for the contractor.
What are you getting at? why are
you so curious about the well?
I... it's my business.
In a way. you know? Antiques, wells...
I mean, there's actually a market for
that kind of thing, Believe it or not.
I should go.
All right.
Sorry about being naked.
Who are you? what do you want?
Look, talk to me, but
just leave him alone.
I made your, uh, chicken with the
tahini sauce. And a good salad.
good, you're eating.
Yeah.
That's me. I am eating.
Ugh. something that looks
inedible And totally raw.
Well, what'd you cook the chicken on?
- On? a pan.
- I mean what temperature?
I told you for an hour at...
Yeah, I did an hour.
In the oven?
In the oven? you...
you said on for an hour.
No. no, no, no.
That was the pan searing. I
said inside the oven at 425.
Well, I didn't hear that part.
Delia, I miss him so much.
He's keeping his distance
Because he thinks I'm
grieving. And the truth is...
I am.
I just miss him.
You know, and today...
Today he remembered
something from his life...
I mean Jim's. or at least I think
he did. Well, that's great, honey.
No, it's not. because...
He remembered being shot.
You know? and I-I think...
I think the ghost is responsible for
that If that's what he wished for.
I'm... I'm so sorry. It just scares me.
You know, what he
might have to go through
To come back to me. and...
What if he doesn't want to?
He already came back to you.
I want you to remember that.
Jim did all of this for you.
Could you just...
Stay on the phone with me
for, like, 5 more minutes?
Then I promise we'll both go to sleep.
Yeah, sure.
We can talk all night if you want to.
I warned you.
Stay away from the well.
My arms and legs. Did
someone do that to you?
Terrible things will happen
if you don't stay away.
So what is it about explicitly
being told to stay away
That inspires you to come
running to this house?
I can't exactly search for clues With
everyone working here, especially Sam.
How was she when you saw her
before? One piece or chopped liver?
She was all in one piece. Must
have happened after she died.
Yeah, for transport. For
some killers, dismemberment's
a fetish, But for most it's
a matter of convenience.
I mean, how else are you gonna
stuff the body in the trunk?
Your encyclopedic knowledge of
the depraved Is awe-inspiring.
And if you've got a crowbar
in that snazzy little tote,
I'll be impressed.
They didn't even lock it. Come in.
Look at all these
newspapers. Oh, my god.
Welcome to the nest
of the giant pack rat.
Who lived here?
A widow in her sixties. Heart attack.
You know they linked
hoarding to perfectionism?
It's ironic, isn't it? because people
who have it End up living like this.
Yeah. not the most inviting
place For a kid to visit.
Do you think that she was drawn to
the property Because of the well?
Maybe it's just where she wound up.
Nearest dispose-all where the
killer could dump her body.
Wait.
Swing that back over there.
What is that?
Forget transport. I'm thinking fetish.
How long has this house been empty?
I don't know. The widow
died a few months ago.
And has it always been empty, or
could someone else be living here.
I no longer care if the
neighbors call the cops.
What is this?
They're wishes.
A wish for new toys, A million dollars.
A teacup terrier who won't bite.
It's like they were
all written by children.
Santa would have been a better bet.
Wait, look at this one. This
looks like adult handwriting.
"I wish he could know she was here. "
I gotta say, It's awfully nice of
someone who chops up a little girl
To leave a note. for who?
The girl's father? wishing
he'd learn the truth?
So nice of that old lady pack rat
to save it. Um, she saved everything.
Meaning she had no idea there
was a little girl down the well?
Meaning we don't know if there's
a little girl in the well.
I'm not going down that well.
I don't care if you have
flippers and a mask in that bag,
- I'm not going.
- Ok, fine.
I just think she's haunting it 'cause
it has something to do with her death.
Good morning.
- Eli, right?
- Yeah. Sam, hey.
- We were just...
- We went to this, um...
It's early, right? Yeah. it's morning.
I'm... I'm just gonna read the sports.
Maybe I'll remember what team I like.
Oh, hey. Melinda?
Remember you were asking me
about the history of that well?
You had a buyer or
something? Yeah, right.
Yeah. well, I asked around. it
turns out That the contractors
were hired by the old lady's
son. He pretty much owns it now.
He's staying at a
place called the, um...
Grandview Court. his
last name's Ackerman.
- Travis Ackerman.
- Great. thanks.
- Sure.
- Can I ask you a...
A strange question?
What did you wish for? At the well?
I can't tell you that.
Might not come true.
I cannot wait for this ghost to
cross over as soon as possible.
Let's go see that pack
rat's son. Travis Ackerman.
- Let me do it.
- Are you sure?
Yeah no problem.
You said you called because you have a
buyer For some of the items at the house?
I thought that we got
anything of value out of there.
I was visiting a friend up
there, And I saw these dolls.
Dolls? Doll pieces.
That's weird.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
There was a... a pile of them.
You know? arms and legs.
They were next to a box of notes,
Or, um... wishes. Actually. I think.
You know what? I... I do know
what you're talking about.
I found a bunch of broken
dolls. They were yanked apart.
Um, somebody left them with a note
- At the foot of the well.
- The well?
Yeah, there's this old
well on our property.
It's a wishing well, actually.
Neighborhood kids knew about it.
I was already 15 when we
moved into that old place,
But, uh, every once in a
while,I would see them out there.
Of course,they would run the minute
anyone from the house came out.
- Why's that?
- You know, uh,
Old, creaky place near
the new subdivision.
We were instantly the spooky house.
I was going through a bit
of a rough patch at the time.
And I kinda figured if I could help
Grant some little girl's wish, why not?
So I, uh, I took the broken parts...
Which, big surprise, it
sounds like my mother saved,
And I, uh, I left a new doll.
And the next day, it was gone.
Did you have any idea who the girl was?
No. I only ever saw her from
a distance. She was alone.
No more than 10, long dark hair.
You know, the truth is I learned
to keep my distance from that well.
I kinda wish everyone would.
Why is that?
You'll think I'm nuts.
It's unlikely. I can usually tell.
All right. um...
When I was 18, i... I got a full
scholarship to an out-of-state school.
And then I found out that
my girlfriend was pregnant.
I didn't say it was all your fault...
You know, I saw my future slipping away.
I would be one more thing
that my mom could hang onto.
You know, me, Allison, and a
baby all stuck in that house.
- And...
- We will be happy.
I wished.
With Allison right there, I
wished... That she weren't pregnant.
I said I'd give anything.
Allison's car was parked out front,
Right along the side of the road.
And these, uh, these racers... these
cyclists Came flying down the hill.
And she got hit.
She lost the baby, and I went away to
school And she never spoke to me again.
So...
Wish granted.
But I'm sure that you don't
believe in All of that stuff anyway.
You'd be surprised what I believe.
Let me tell you what a friend
of mine saw down your well.
So just like that the son
agrees to drain the well?
It was an easy sell. The
ghost got the guy halfway
believing She was real
just by granting his wish.
He feels if she's down there,
the family deserves to know.
Well, that's cooperative. Not what
you'd expect from a brutal killer.
I didn't get that from this guy.
What about his mother?
She seemed like a nice lady
With an anxiety disorder.
What? what am I missing?
Well, I'm just thinking about
the wish That Travis had granted.
I mean, it certainly
proves the ghost's point.
Be careful what you wish for. Yeah,
but what caused the little girl's death?
Because she keeps
warning us against wishes
So it obviously has to be
something that she wished for.
That ought to be easy to figure out.
A little girl who wished for something.
Yeah, but maybe we have more than that.
I mean, now we know when
she lived, right? So what if
she's the girl that Travis
Ackerman saw leaving doll parts?
The severed doll parts.
It's got to be her.
Yeah, but when did she go missing?
Well, Travis said he
was 15 when he moved in.
Yeah, and he left for
school when he was 18.
And he's late 20s now.
I mean, how many girls
Could go deceased or missing
in Grandview in a 3-year span?
Gretchen Dennis. that's her.
Missing since 1996.
You were right. and,
uh... It's pretty awful.
I'm sorry. Thanks for doing this.
Yeah. yeah, um...
Is the girl here? I mean,
the spirit that you saw?
- No.
- Well, maybe, now that they've found her body,
she's at peace?
It's a step. What did
you tell the police?
Just that I was having it
drained before I sold the place.
You know, it's an insurance hazard
And I didn't want anyone getting hurt.
Um, Allison? could... Could
a ghost have done that to her?
I mean, caused an accident like that?
I don't know. maybe. I'm sorry.
Help me!
What? what is it?
The little girl.
She might not be the only one that died.
That was fast. Neighbors
have built a shrine already.
Yeah, it's all over the local news.
Gretchen's been missing for 12 years.
Are we gonna go talk to the
family? It seems a little soon.
No, the ghost.
Look at me, Clay! I
hate you! look at me!
Look at what you did to
me, clay. I hate you, clay.
What is it? what's
wrong? He did this to me.
He killed me. Who is that?
My brother.
I just can't believe that a little boy
would slice his sister into bits.
Oh, he could.
You're the search queen.
type in "sororicide".
That's sister-killing.
you'll get 100 hits.
Clay may have killed her,
but he didn't chop her.
- How do you know that?
- I just got an e-mail
From my friend down at the morgue.
Even after 12 years, her
skeleton was still intact.
There were some minor fractures, But
nothing that indicated dismemberment.
What about the boy? I mean, were
there any other bones down in the well?
Nope. one set of bones.
But you said he was a
vision, not a spirit, right?
So that means what happened to him Was
something the little girl experienced.
Ok.
What if the armless boy that
you saw Was clay's first kill?
And she witnessed it.
So if those were her dolls
that were chopped into pieces...
That could have been a warning.
She could have seen what her brother
had done And she was gonna narc on him.
And to shut her up, he
threw her down a well?
It's hard to believe.
But I guess either way, we
have to talk to the parents.
Melinda, they just learned that their
daughter Is never coming home alive.
Yeah, but they also don't know that
she still needs their help. and yours.
Look, Eli, I'm serious. You're a
very experienced grief counselor.
You saw the news you're here to help,
And you couldn't stop wondering about...
Gretchen's relationship
with her brother?
Are you asking us how
he handled the news?
Oh. well, he can't even talk
about it. But that's nothing new.
Clay...
Clay is so smart. He's
such a good athlete.
He was a great ball player.
But when Gretchen went
missing, he was devastated.
He lost interest in
everything. it was...
It was like we lost him, too.
How do you mean?
"survivor's guilt". That's what
the family therapist called it.
I understand. But is it
possible for Clay, Would
he have anything specific
to feel guilty about?
In terms of Gretchen?
did they get along?
Well, they fought like any siblings.
- He was older.
- Typical boy.
And Gretchen was such a little girl.
It's gonna seem odd, but did
she like to play with dolls?
Don't most girls? What's odd about that?
Did Clay ever do anything to her dolls?
Not really.
Well, they... no, wait, Aaron, they did.
When, uh, when he was trying to get back at her
For who knows what, he hid them. all of them.
And Gretchen just about lost her mind.
And that was all the
ammunition he ever needed.
Aaron, do you remember that? yeah.
He used to do terrible things.
He would hide them, hang
them... Cut them into pieces?
Well, yeah.
I
- I know that that sounds awful,
But we just thought
That's the way kids are.
Aren't they?
I have a delivery for
Andrew's meatpacking.
I'm-I'm looking for the main office.
Third floor. I think someone's still
up there If you need a signature.
Oh, sorry about that. I'm on the clock.
Thanks. you're welcome.
No! no!
No, no, help!
Please, somebody help me! please!
Hello?
check this out. Can we talk later?
I called the brothther, Clay at home
and at work. He never called me back.
So, basically you're calling to tell
me That you have nothing to tell me.
Sort of. you said the ghost was pissed
- I'm just saying...
- oh. well, that's great.
Well, thank you. um, ok. bye-bye.
- Morning.
- hey, good morning.
How are you? I'm good, I'm good.
And this is for you.
I knew you'd be in a bit of a rush. I
wanted to get it to you before you, uh...
Ate. or didn't. it's not too late. You're
not gonna be late for work, are you?
No. no, this is...
It's really nice of you.
It's payback for all the good stuff
You got me from the store. eat up, now.
How is it? good? bad?
Did you use orange rinds in the waffles?
Good! I did, yeah. orange rinds,
Organic maple syrup, a
little fruit, Roasted pecans.
Wait. you're not allergic to those?
No.
No, it's just something my husband did.
- Sorry.
- don't be.
Really.
It's perfect.
I'm sorry I keep bringing
him up. it's just...
How could you not?
Look, you can talk about
him to me anytime you want.
Anytime.
Which is something I have loads of now.
time. Oh, that's right. I heard the news.
- I'm sorry.
- whatever.
I guess all the work's been halted.
So it goes. They found the
body of a child in that well.
You know, the well you
were so curious about.
I gotta ask you, um...
What's the deal with that?
Um, I don't know. I hope maybe
the police can find out something.
I was really talking about you. You know, all
the questions you were asking about the well.
And then when we were there,
It's like you could sense something.
I mean, it freaked you out.
You're not psychic, are you? Uh, no.
No, I'm not psychic.
You're certainly popular.
Hello, Eli. Mel. this
time I have something.
Clay's dispatcher just called me back.
Seems our ghost has been hard at work
Putting Clay on disability leave.
What happened? He had an accident.
I know you're gonna say I was getting
ahead of myself, Reaching out to the brother
Who probably killed his little sister.
Manslaughter? murder? take your pick.
How about you start a phone call with,
"can you talk, or is this a bad time?"
No. I want you to pick one, seriously.
Oh, I get it. because
Sam might be there.
And you don't want him to
know you have superpowers.
- Right.
- Got it. will do.
But come on. you gonna pick or what?
I'm inclined to go with manslaughter,
Gretchen's death being
some kind of accident.
But there's something
that keeps bothering me.
One-armed joe?
Ok, fine. that poor boy you
saw with his arm cut off.
You're thinking if
Clay did kill his sister
In some sort of weird, rough,
freak tumble play accident,
Who's the armless kid? Yeah,
and how is he related to Clay?
I called the school
looking for a yearbook.
See if you could I.d. old
joe as one of his classmates.
Then I remembered. Clay
was a little league star.
So maybe joe was one
of the kids on his team.
I don't know. maybe he's lost his arm In
some kind of freak accident that Gretchen saw.
- A double accident?
- yeah.
That's him. that's the boy I saw.
That's one-armed joe? That's
Clay Dennis, Gretchen's brother.
I'm telling you, that's him.
He can't be both Butcher and victim.
Gretchen blames him, so he
has to be involved somehow.
Well, if he wants to hang
onto the rest of his limbs,
He'd better start talking.
You know, the warning label on these
Says that you're not supposed to drive.
I don't think that's a problem.
There's another warning
you should know. um...
I see spirits. I've seen your
sister. she's angry at you.
Ok. you saw my sister's ghost.
Yes. And the fact that I talk to ghosts
Is not something I like to admit
Unless I feel like someone's
life might be in danger.
Look, lady. what happened to my arm?
That was just a... freak thing.
No, I don't think so. It's too
similar to a vision that I had.
You were a kid, 10 or 11.
And that same arm was
injured. missing, in fact.
Ok, please stop. I know exactly
what you're talking about,
But how...
Oh, my god.
Because my sister told you.
In a way.
She showed me severed arms and legs.
I had no way to connect it,
Except to her dolls and
what you had done to them.
What I did to them.
She tell you what I did to
her? Did she tell you that?
I was so mean to her.
She was such a stubborn tag-along.
She was always getting into my stuff.
Move!
There were times when
I literally hated her.
This one time, I was convinced
that she slit my tires.
What is the matter with you?
I didn't touch your stupid bike!
I didn't do it, I promise!
So I went nuts on her dolls.
Hiding them, hanging them.
She'd run, tell my parents,
And write down in this little notepad of hers,
You know, about how she hated me right back.
Writing those stupid
notes won't do anything.
Shut up and leave me alone.
One day, I don't even know
what she did To bug me, really,
But I just chopped up all of her dolls.
Mom! Clay killed my dolls!
I got grounded for 2
weeks. I was home alone,
Saw her latest entry.
She'd torn out the page,
but I could see the imprint.
She wrote, "i wish Clay's
arms and legs were cut off. "
She wished for you the
same fate as her dolls.
And when my parents were gone,
I made that wish come true.
Help me! Is this what you
wanted? what did you do to me?
I tried to stop her before she
could call my parents or 911.
I heard the screen door
to the kitchen slam.
Gretchen, come back. it was just a joke.
She was already gone.
She didn't come back that
night. Or the next, or the next.
I don't know what I was thinking.
She was 8 years old.
I heard my mom sobbing every night.
"how could this have happened?"
I knew.
But what I didn't know Was
what happened to Gretchen
After I scared her away.
Do you?
No.
But I'll find out. I promise.
I saw you talking to him.
Gretchen, he didn't mean to hurt you.
He's been scared for you ever since.
I've been in the dark, In the cold.
All this time I was afraid to go home.
Because you thought
your wish had come true?
But he's fine. it was just a trick.
- No, he's not fine.
- he's alive,
And I'm dead and it's all his fault.
He would give anything to take it back.
There are no take backs
when it comes to the well.
Ask your friend Sam.
I don't get it. why is
the ghost going after Sam?
I thought she was mad at her brother.
I'm dealing with
an angry 8-year-old
Who keeps changing
the rules as she goes.
None of it explains how
she got down the well.
She wrote a note
Asking for the well's help
in punishing her brother.
That's how this all
started. but then, Eli and i
Found this With her
dolls at the old house.
"i wish he could know she was here. "
- Did her brother write this?
- no, I don't think so.
Where are those tiles that Sam brought?
I put them over here. I
wasn't sure if you were serious
About selling it as a garden fixture.
What do the tiles have
to do with any of this?
This is how I'm gonna get
Gretchen to tell me the truth.
"make a wish of your very own.
"hide it deep within the stone".
Gretchen, you thought
the well had real powers
And that's how your brother got hurt.
Can I speak to her?
She's here. she's angry.
Like she was the time that she
made a wish Wanting to hurt you.
Hide it deep within the stone.
Is it still in the stone?
I watched it fall away over time.
Years and years I was down there.
Because of you.
Look, whatever she's saying,
Please just tell her I'm sorry.
She's sorry, too.
Even if she doesn't
remember feeling that way.
When you thought your wish had come true
And you saw your brother
bleeding, Maybe even dying...
You came here to take
back your wish, didn't you?
It was so hard to reach.
You said there were no
takebacks. You're right.
Even though you want to,
No one can change what's happened.
But you can grant one more wish.
You can help your
brother forgive himself.
All I ever wanted to do was be
with him. No matter what he did.
She always looked up to you.
She wanted to be with you.
But I was so mean to you.
And you were just a kid.
You were a kid, too. Will you tell
him I love him and forgive him?
I will. She understands now.
That it was a horrible accident.
Same goes for you.
She wasn't in the well when
your girlfriend had her accident.
There was no spirit, no magic.
You didn't make that happen.
Yeah, I didn't need a ghost's help.
I mean, I might not have gotten what I
wanted, But I definitely got what I deserved.
Allison, are you ok? Go away!
- Allison...
- get away from me!
Still, I can't help but wishing...
Wishing you did something
different. So does she.
Who?
The woman who left the note.
The one who came here
With your daughter.
Of course. The other note.
"i wish that he could
know she was here. "
Wha... what other note?
what is she saying?
I think she's talking
about your girlfriend,
Allison.
12 years. and she'd been
living here the whole time.
In Lewiston. half an
hour away. She was hurt.
Let him think that she had lost the baby
So she wouldn't force a child on him.
Didn't she think he
have the right to know?
I think she wanted him, too.
It's just, as the years passed,
It got harder to tell him.
So, the visits to the well. I guess so.
So far, so good. right.
What? is she here?
Figured while I'm here, I
might as well help people.
Like your friend Sam. Sam?
It was dark for so long.
Now it's so warm and bright.
What did you do for Sam?
I gave him what he wanted.
Something he really wanted.
Turns out it was
something he already had.
What?
A piece of his life back.
Which life?
Thank you.
It's been kind of a weird day, And I didn't
know who else I could talk to about it.
Ok.
I was going through all my
stuff, And I found a key.
I know it's strange, I've been
hoping... Wishing for a clue.
Something to tell me who I was. Right?
Guess I got more than I bargained for.
Are you sure this belongs to you?
Yeah. My name was right
on the receipt, Sam Lucas.
I bought that less than a month ago.
Question is,
Who did I buy it for?
www.seriessub.com