Melinda: previously
on "ghost whisperer"....
Zoe: that book is
the key to everything.
The book is always changing.
new things are written,
old things are erased.
You know,
carl said that aiden
Would have powers
that i don't.
What if that means
seeing things things
that i can't,
Things that are real?
Tell them why
your friends shine.
Because
they don't have faces.
They're made of light.
But they're scared.
What are
they scared of, buddy?
The shadows.
What kind of shadows
are those?
The ones they make
from the parts that
get left behind.
Parts of what?
People. broken people.
[thunder]
[indistinct chatter]
Be sure to let them
cool a little.
I will.
And save your tin foil
for the shinies.
You, too, aunt delia.
Ok, honey, i will.
The shinies?
Kind of sounds like
a new family in town.
Melinda:
pretty weird, huh?
Be grateful.
ned's imaginary friend
was named bob,
And all bob ever did
was watch tv
And agree with everything
ned had to say.
I know, but he talks to
these shiny people like
they're real, you know?
And i can't
see them or hear them.
And then they put these
scary ideas in his head,
like the shadows.
Which she can't see, either.
Not the ones
that move, anyway.
Shadows that move?
apparently.
I mean, could
a 5-year-old
even make that up?
One that lives
with ghosts, sure.
What?
He's supposed to have
abilities that i don't,
But what if talking
to these shiny people
is one of them?
You know, i mean,
what if aiden's
imaginary friends
Aren't imaginary?
I don't know.
what that be so bad?
They told aiden
this morning
That something bad
was going to happen.
Something
really bad,
really soon.
Oh.
[sirens in distance]
Man: ok, be still.
Girl: where
are my parents?
I want my mom
to come with me.
All right, ruby g.,
don't even tell me
you're nervous.
Hello, you guys
are about to cut me open
and rip out my gallbladder.
And i can't miss
the playoffs.
Time out.
Nobody's going to be
ripping anything
out of anywhere.
And secondly,
you're not going
to miss the playoffs.
Because we never
let anybody miss
the playoffs,
Do we?
hey, um,
Maybe we could
postpone the surgery?
Ruby, how many matches
have you missed because
of your stomach aches?
Too many.
all right.
So this surgery
is going to make
that problem disappear.
Uh, if i can ever
find a vein.
We should try
the other arm,
huh? all right.
Yeah. don't worry
about it.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Thanks. just relax, ruby,
it's going to be ok.
I'm scared.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Except this is going to be
a little pinch.
ow.
The surgery will take
about an hour.
And you're gonna be out,
and be able to go home
And sleep
in your own bed.
Yeah, but i'm gonna
have a big honkin'
scar on my stomach.
No. the surgery's
laparoscopic.
There will be four
tiny little marks.
All right?
now, dr. prakash
Is going to give you
something that's going
to help you relax.
Hey, um, you're not
going to let
Anything happen to me?
promise?
Promise.
What are you doing?
Uh, nothing,
dr. morgan.
I was just helping--
Dr. prakash
is perfectly capable
of doing his job.
Now scrub in.
Right. sorry.
[sighs]
[monitor beeping]
Gallbladder's out.
No bleeders.
Surgical sight
looks good.
Nicely done.
let's finish up.
Dr. lucas is going
to close.
i'm honored.
Well, you're the one
who promised her there
wouldn't be any scars.
Well, i didn't so much
as promise her that.
[monitor beeping]
end tidal co-2 is down.
What?
stats are dropping.
Could be an embolism.
give her a hundred
percent o2.
She's brading down.
bp's falling.
Releasing hemoperitoneum.
Let's get the ports out.
heart rate's dropping.
Uh, it's yours. move.
[monitor flatlining]
Cardiac arrest.
start compression.
Give her epi.
pressure's dropping.
We need to do it again.
what happened?
Let's start
a central line.
Come on.
come on, ruby.
Come on, girl,
right here.
Stay with us.
come on, baby.
ruby...
Come on.
Woman on p.a.:
dr. forrest,
Dial 182, please.
There was nothing
we could do.
She had massive
pulmonary embolism.
She was a healthy
19-year-old girl.
Not healthy enough,
apparently.
Is that how you feel?
I mean, really?
It's the truth.
That's how we cope
with things, huh?
By not caring.
No, by not getting
invested in the first place.
You set yourself up,
not to mention the patient.
She was scared. i--
I just wanted
to reassure her.
You made an invasive procedure
sound like a haircut.
The only thing
you ever say
to a patient ever
Is that surgery
carries risks.
Period.
[lockers creaking]
What the hell?
[echoing]
Oh, no.
Man on p.a.:
michael crawford, 340.
Michael crawford,
please call 340.
See you tomorrow on rounds.
don't be late.
Ruby, if that's you,
i'm sorry.
And i understand
if you're angry at me.
Angry...[echoing]
[lockers creaking]
[echoing continues]
Child, whispering:
can you see us?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Ok.
You want
your night light on?
Hmm, i sleep better
when it's dark.
Why is that, pal?
If there's no light,
There can't be
any shadows.
And i can see
the shinies better.
Do the shadows come in here?
No. i just don't
like to imagine them.
You want me
to stay with you?
No. i'm not scared.
My friends didn't say
any bad stuff would
happen to me.
Hey.
Nothing bad is ever
going to happen to you.
I love you.
Love you, too.
Good night, pal.
good night, dad.
Lockers slamming,
words repeating
on the p.a.?
Sounds like
a ghost to me.
[sighs]
Ruby grayson.
She was a sophomore.
I haven't seen her
hanging around.
It started happening
right after we lost her.
That doesn't mean
she's haunting you.
I mean,
you said it yourself
That her death
was no one's fault.
Yeah, but morgan got on me
for reassuring her, right?
So maybe she heard that.
and then she thought that...
Jim, you didn't do
anything wrong.
Has anything else
happened?
No.
But i'm telling you,
i feel like...
I could feel that she was
angry at me, you know?
I don't blame her.
Probably 'cause
you're angry
at yourself.
'cause you care.
Too much,
according to morgan.
One of the many
reasons
I'm in love
with you.
You were kind to her.
There's nothing
wrong with that.
You know, maybe...
You're being haunted
by your own doubts
More than
anything else.
Maybe.
Look, what did aiden mean
when he said that his friends
Said no bad stuff
would happen to him?
Nothing.
Tell you what,
why don't you send
her picture to my cell
And i'll take
a look at it? ok?
If it'll make you
feel better.
Yeah, yeah, it might.
Carl?
If you're around,
i really need
to talk to you.
Carl? [gasps] oh.
Do you always
have to do that?
have to keep calling?
Is it a problem?
They don't like me
to talk to you too often.
We're watchers, you know.
we're not meddlers.
I'm sorry.
i know. it's just...
Your son.
you're worried
about your son.
His new friends.
It all felt harmless
until they told him
That something bad
was going to happen.
Jim lost a patient
yesterday during surgery,
And he thinks
that she might be
haunting him.
But you're not so sure.
Ok.
Let me see the picture
on your cell phone.
How did you know that?!
Oh, right.
the watching.
Hmm. haven't seen her.
Doesn't prove anything.
Why don't you ask me
what you really
want to know?
Is it true?
The shinies and the shadows?
It just all feels
so fanciful.
Because you've never
seen them.
Hmm?
So the person
who asks people
To believe what
they can't see
Is refusing
to believe what
she can't see.
It's completely normal
for children to have
imaginary friends.
But you don't really
believe that.
Carl, please.
just once, give me
a straight answer.
I couldn't,
even if i wanted to.
It's too dangerous.
For you?
Are the shadows
that powerful?
All i can
tell you is this--
The answers are there.
But you have to know
when to look.
Don't you mean "where"?
That you already know.
If you're talking
about the book,
Ned's already looked.
Ok, there's no shinies
or shadows in there.
Maybe not now.
What does that mean?
What use would
the book be
If it got itself
destroyed?
Are you saying that
the book hides things
to protect itself?
Someday...
Someday soon,
You may want to think
about doing the same.
Please don't touch that.
President bedford.
i wasn't sure how long
i'd be waiting.
Your assistant didn't
know where you were.
Well, i was detained.
my apologies.
You wanted to see me
about something?
You honestly
don't know?
Professor sanders?
Tenure? job for life?
Well, if you want
to congratulate him,
I suggest
a nice bordeaux.
This is twice
you've passed me over.
I get published more
and invited to more conferences
Than any professor
in the entire
psych department.
Do you?
I've also been voted
best professor
By my students
three years running.
Really?
I even worked
on my appearance
And my hair since
your last evaluation.
Well, i find that
hard to believe.
It's a job offer,
From collier university.
it's not the first.
It's a good school.
you should take it.
I don't want to leave here.
I can't.
why not?
Let's just cut
to the chase.
What do you have
against me?
[scoffs]
Well, it's not so much
That i don't respect you
Or that i disapprove
of your cowboy methods
Or that i cringe
every time
You open your mouth
representing this
university in public.
Although all those
things are true,
It's just,
the simple fact is,
I just don't like you.
Well, for a minute there,
i thought it was personal.
What's not to like?
i'm likeable, right?
People like me.
Yeah, we like you.
[sighs] well,
that's a start.
Jim, could you
step it up, there?
I got a date
at the wine bar
at lento's.
Hey, count me in there.
Did you i.d. your ghost?
not yet.
And there haven't been
any other hauntings, so...
Well, maybe it's just
some random hospital ghost
Who was messing
with the lockers
and the sound system.
Yeah, that's possible.
Or maybe the ghost
was just haunting
somebody else.
What about dr. morgan?
was he surprised
by what happened?
I wondered about that.
He was surprised
at first,
But then he just turned
and walked away.
Hmm. maybe it's not
the first time.
Maybe that's why
he's being such
a sourpuss.
'cause he's got a ghost
keeping him up at night.
Hey, doctor morgan's
a good man.
He's just frustrated
he can't perform
surgery anymore.
He's in the early stages
of parkinson's.
You know,
he's hard on us
Because he wants us
to be as good as he was.
Eli: funny.
The only thing
bedford wants from me
is to dry up and blow away.
What are you--
are you crazy?
Yeah. for you.
Come on.
I locked the door.
Come on. i'll do
anything for you.
Absolutely anything.
He used me.
And then he just
threw me away.
What'd you see?
Um, let me just
put it this way--
You're not the one
who's being haunted.
Wow, so the old man
did ok for himself.
Was he by any chance
married at the time?
No, he was divorced,
and i think for a long time.
Any clues about
who she was?
Hmm, she was wearing
yellow scrubs.
Which means she was
a med student.
Damn it.
yikes.
The good doctor,
whether married or not,
Wasn't being so good.
You're not blogging this,
ok? don't blog this.
I'm offended.
I'm searching
for female med students
At rockland who have
died in the past
five years.
Here we go,
two of them,
both male.
What do you got?
Med school face page.
ooh, i found her.
"tina clark, 22,
went missing this week."
That was 6 months ago.
Is there a body?
doesn't look like it.
Wait. i know her.
She and i took
morgan's class.
She was really quiet.
i think she was his t.a.
I think you mean
t and a.
Look, whatever
their relationship,
We have to figure out
what happened between them
And why she's so angry
at morgan.
You know, i'd really
like to give this guy
A chance to explain himself.
he was a good teacher.
[pills clattering]
Dr. morgan?
oh, i'm sorry.
Can i give you a hand?
I dropped some pills.
For my parkinson's,
If that look on
your face means
It's any
of your business.
I'm sorry.
I just came by
to ask your advice
About that liver patient
who was admitted last night.
Aaronson?
yeah.
Leave the files.
I'll review it
and i'll get it back to you.
All right.
Ah, doctor,
Look, i've been meaning
to ask you about
Tina clark.
do you remember her?
Did you know her?
I knew her.
Someone i'm close to
was asking about her,
And i remembered her
from your intro
to clinical medicine class.
You know she went missing,
don't you?
Well, i knew
that she quit
medical school.
I heard she went to
new york after that.
Was that the last thing
you heard about her?
Well, i saw
her photo in the news,
Just like everyone else.
Right. i'm sorry.
I know this must be hard
for you.
I know she was
your teaching assistant.
And it did seem like
the two of you were close, so--
Did it, now?
Yeah, look, i'm just
trying to help find her,
that's all.
You should talk
to the police.
Did they talk to you?
No.
Why?
Do you think
you know something
about her, about me?
Look, dr. morgan,
The shortest answer
to that question is yes.
Something that could get
you a good evaluation,
Get you into cardiology?
Let it go. there's
no mileage here.
Doctor, i'm not trying
to blackmail you.
I'm just asking you
to help find a young woman
That i thought
you cared about.
This is all sound
an awful lot like
blackmail to me.
We're done here.
All right.
[door closes]
Blackmail?
yep.
I mean, you talked
about a missing girl
And he went straight
to blackmail?
And he said
there's no mileage here,
Like he'd been cornered
on the topic before.
Maybe someone else
knew about the affair.
Well, people gossip.
Yeah, so did you
talk to any of his
other students?
Yeah, i did.
And nobody wants to be
known as the person
Who blackmailed
their professor.
But a few of them knew tina.
What did they say
about her?
They said that
she was always tired,
like any medical student.
But that she paid
her tuition in cash.
In cash?
Her full
tuition?
Yeah. lots of small bills
in lots of installments.
And they said
she was scraping by,
You know, just borrowing
money for books and lab fees.
But, you know,
there was something else.
When i walked in on morgan,
he was taking pills.
And he looked like
he'd been caught,
he was wired.
Maybe he was just
taking something
for his parkinson's.
Yeah, or maybe he and tina
had more in common
than just their affair.
Wait a minute.
you think that
She's paying all
of her bills in cash
Because they were
dealing right out
of the hospital?
He does have easy access
to drugs.
I feel so lost.
I can help you.
Please.
Don't judge me.
What do you mean?
[indistinct chatter]
[men cat-calling,
whistling]
[men cheering]
Oh, yeah!
all right!
[door slams]
Tina...tina?
Go away, tina.
for good.
Who did this?
Who was threatening you?
It wasn't a threat.
Are you saying
that someone killed you?
He wanted me gone.
Who? was it morgan?
Yes.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Thank you.
so i tell you
That a med student
is a stripper,
And you're not
surprised either?
Well, tina wouldn't be
the first grad student
to moonlight.
That's what i said.
Tuition's expensive,
time is money.
It's maximum results
for minimum effort.
Yeah, easy
for you to say.
Well, what did
tina's other career
Really have to do
with anything?
Maybe that's why morgan
wanted to be so rid of her.
It's bad enough
for your career
to date a student.
Even worse
if she happens
to be a stripper.
What? bad enough to want
to kill her, though?
Tina said
that he wanted her gone,
But she still hasn't
told me how she died.
We gotta find that body.
Have the police tell us
what the ghost won't.
Morgan said
the last thing he heard
Is that she was on
the way to new york.
So if that wasn't
in the papers,
It'll help narrow
down the search.
Especially
if they're only
looking in the morgues.
I'll call detective blair.
She doesn't
ask questions anymore.
She's glad for the help.
Wait. where
are you going?
Uh, tina's other life,
The one she hid,
to find out what else
She's been hiding.
wait a minute.
You're going
to a strip club?
Yes. ok?
And i never thought
i would say this
to my husband,
But you're coming
with me.
Hallelujah.
What about me?!
Man: that's
all right, girl!
[indistinct chatter]
Um...
so the bouncer said
You guys were friends
of tina's?
Uh, yeah, we took
a class together once.
Did you know that tina
was in medical school?
Yeah.
You know, i used to be
an executive assistant downtown.
Thought i'd do this
a couple hours a week.
One night turned into three,
Three turned into five,
And pretty soon,
i couldn't stay awake
at my day job.
Now this is what i do.
So is that what
happened with tina?
Sure, she said this was
short-term for her,
And i believed her
because one day i came in,
and she was just gone.
Was that when
they reported
her missing?
No. she went missing later.
She left here for new york.
Didn't say good-bye?
Look, she got on
the wrong side of somebody,
And she didn't say who.
You know, we tried
to stay friends.
I even went
to visit her once.
She had a nice place.
A really nice place.
You seem surprised.
[chuckles] we don't make
that kind of money here.
I figured she landed
on her feet,
Met somebody.
a rich somebody.
Charee, do you mind
if we show you
some photographs?
Ahem, right.
have you seen
this guy?
No.
Morgan had a beard
for a while, so it might--
Wait, wait, go back.
that guy.
I've seen him with tina.
wait a minute.
Why didn't the cops
show me that guy?
That's bedford.
are you sure?
President bedford?
oh, yeah.
They were arguing
about something.
At the time,
i thought it was
because he was cheap
And they were
coming to terms.
To terms?
Because they went into
the back room after.
You know,
for a private.
The next day,
Tina was gone.
[deep voice]
shh, come on,
don't do it.
We told you.
[high-pitched voice]
what? you never told me.
[deep voice]
yes, we did.
Don't talk to him.
[high-pitched voice]
why not?
[deep voice]
you know why not.
Aiden,
what are you doing?
Playing.
Playing what?
teacher.
Is that the teacher?
Who's not supposed
to talk to him?
You.
Who doesn't want me
to talk to him?
Well, my friends.
They say the shadows
don't like it when you do.
Whose teacher
have i been talking to?
Yours?
He teaches grown-ups.
Is it your daddy's teacher?
No.
Uncle eli's.
[cell phone rings]
Hey, i was just
about to call you.
They found tina's body.
She was laying dead
in the street.
She's been a jane doe
in some morgue in
downtown new york.
Oded on
prescription meds.
You know what,
i'm not surprised.
I felt high
when i was dancing.
She must have been
doing drugs just to
make it through the night.
Cops were finally able
to search her apartment.
They found a lot
of hidden cash.
Her friend said
that she had money,
enough to od.
But then why would
she be blaming
dr. morgan for her death?
Maybe 'cause
he turned on her.
Threatening her
to make her leave town.
Except he's not the guy
they saw at the club.
It was bedford,
your boss, your teacher.
My teacher?
Yeah, it was bedford.
look, i'll explain later.
Now we just have
to figure out
how he's involved.
Think he's sleeping
with her, too?
No, it's gotta be
more than that
For the shadows
to get involved.
The shadows?
Yeah, aiden said that
I'm not supposed
to talk to bedford
Because they don't like it
when i do.
The shadows, the parts
that get left behind when
people go into the light,
They actually
want something?
Well, whatever it is,
they're scary enough
That the book decided
to rewrite itself
To erase
any mention of them.
Ok, just pretend
for a moment that
any of this makes sense.
The shadows are in bed
with the president?
That dude just gets
more and more evil.
[rumbling]
[wind blowing]
[glass breaking]
[bedford grunting]
[elevator dings]
[screaming]
[groaning]
[alarm]
It's you!
No, you're wrong.
I'm not the one
you should punish!
No!
[screaming]
Was he injured?
only his ego.
I heard that when
maintenance finally
Pried open
the elevator door,
They found the president
curled up in the fetal
position.
I only wish
i could have been
there to see it.
Eli, he's a person.
a haunted person
Who has a ghost
that we can't cross over
Until we find out
what happened
between them.
Wait a minute,
what do you mean,
What happened between them?
do we think that tina
Was sleeping with both
morgan and bedford?
I don't know
about that,
But i do know
one thing that
they both wanted.
You asked me to look
for a connection,
right?
Well, i think
i found one.
Right around
the time that tina
went missing,
Bedford became
president of
the university.
Guess who he was
running against.
Dr. morgan.
Who acted like
he'd been threatened before
About his affair
with tina. yeah.
But if bedford wanted
the affair to go public,
Why would he be
at the club
threatening tina
To get her
to leave town?
You know what,
maybe it's the other
way around.
Maybe bedford
was paying her
to go public
And morgan was
threatening her
To be quiet and then go.
Yeah, but would either
one of those guys
Threaten a girl's life
over a job?
Hmm.
What if it was about
more than the job?
What if it was
about the book?
Wasn't bedford managing
the sale of rockland's
rare book collection,
The one
with our book in it?
Till it got stolen
and ended up with us.
So you think
that bedford knew
about the book, then?
I'm sure
the shadows did.
There must be some
reason why they don't
Want you talking
to him.
Oh, if the wrong people
got a hold of that thing...
Bedford's president now.
He'd have total
control over it.
Maybe that's what
he's been after all along.
You want to tell me
why you're going around
asking questions
About me and tina clark?
And the day after
you're asking these questions,
It's in the news
that she's dead?
Doesn't that sound
strange to you?
No.
No, the only thing
that seems strange
to me is this--
From the day i got here,
You know, i've been
defending you
Against people who say
you're too hard
on your staff.
And you know
what i tell them?
I tell them
it's because you care.
You care about us,
you care about
our patients.
And because
you're an honest man.
But ever since
this tina thing started,
No, doctor, you have not
been an honest man.
You're angry at me?
No. you're
stonewalling me.
Why is that,
dr. morgan?
You're right.
i'm sorry.
I just don't know how.
if you're sorry,
Stop lying
and tell me
what happened.
Some people call it
a perk of my job.
I call it
a waste of my time,
But attending surgeons
are wined and dined
By sales reps all the time.
This one night,
The sales reps
dragged me
to a strip club.
[indistinct chatter]
I'm not going to pretend
i didn't look.
But i really wasn't
in the mood.
So i went outside
to get some air.
On the way out,
i passed
A partially opened door.
I glanced inside,
and i saw tina
Giving someone
a private dance.
It would have
ended there, but...
She looked up
and saw me.
Soon as i got outside,
She was running
to catch me.
Dr. morgan!
No, please wait!
She needed to tell me
that she only danced
to pay her tuition bills.
I told her it was
none of my business.
You've got
to understand!
But...she was so ashamed,
she couldn't stop crying.
I gave her my shoulder.
But it didn't take long
For it to turn into
something more.
Didn't you try
to break it off?
A hundred times.
I'm not saying
that i don't share
the blame,
But tina had problems.
She had an addictive
personality,
And not just
about us, either.
Do you think
she was stealing meds?
I never caught her,
but i recognized
the behavior.
And i'm pretty sure
she was using.
How did it end?
My old friend,
josh bedford.
President bedford?
you guys are friends?
Were.
Josh came to see me
Because he knew
about me and tina,
And begged me
to break it off.
for my own good.
See, he knew that i was
on the short list
for university president.
What he failed
to mention was that
he was on that list, too.
What did you do?
Well, like a fool,
i did what he told me.
I let him talk
to tina for me.
What do you mean?
what do you think happened?
She packed up overnight
and left.
And somehow, news of our
relationship got out.
And somehow,
the guy they picked
to be president
Was the one person that
knew about me and tina.
You think he got her
to disclose the affair?
They find her dead body
on a street corner
With a pile of cash
sitting at home in
a new, expensive place,
When a month before
she was lap-dancing
to make ends meet.
Now he's president,
Handing out
millions of dollars
in research grants
And construction
contracts.
What do you think?
[siren in distance]
President bedford.
Do you have any idea
how hard it was to find you?
Not hard enough,
apparently.
You're disappearing
every day.
Your staff has no clue
where you are.
Well, you could
ask my mother
If she weren't
comatose.
That's your mother?
yeah.
I visit her every day
since the liver failure.
Wow.
I'm sorry to hear about that.
So you got
something to get
off of your chest?
Look, i know all about
your meetings with tina clark.
And i know you probably
paid her off
To go public about
her affair with dr. morgan.
And i got
a pretty good idea why.
You wanted
to become president.
[chuckles]
But not just so you keep
your foot on the necks
Of professors you don't like.
You wanted to control
the book.
Look, i'm going
to give you some advice,
And i suggest you don't
make me repeat it.
Now some of what
you think you know
may be true,
But it's just
part of the story.
How do you know
how much i know?
Because
if you knew more,
You wouldn't be
babbling about it
where they could hear.
"they"?
Shut up and listen.
It's true.
I did pay off
dr. morgan's
stripper friend.
But only to make her
leave town.
Why?
I was trying
to help my friend.
It's the last decent
thing i've done
In a long,
lone time.
If you didn't leak it,
who did?
Just before i found out
about forrest--
Dr. morgan's affair,
I had a meeting with one
of my old classmates
Who was also one of
the college trustees.
We were reminiscing
about something,
And then suddenly
his face went blank.
I thought he was having
an episode of some sort,
But he wasn't.
And then he said...
joshua...
You are going to be
the next university president.
All you have to do
is nothing.
What are you talking
about, henry?
The next thing i know,
he was back to his
normal self
And apologizing
for having broken
my carafe.
Oh! i'm sorry.
Are you saying something
possessed your friend?
Look, i don't know
what happened.
All i know is,
the next day,
The rumors about
dr. morgan were
flying around.
I thought i was
the only one that
knew about it.
Well, who do you think
spread the rumors?
Two days after
i spoke to my friend,
I was recruited
by the board
To replace dr. morgan
as a candidate.
Now one by one,
Each candidate withdrew
As skeletons
began falling out
of their closets.
So you're asking me
to believe
That you had nothing
to do with the smear campaign
That got you appointed?
And who is this "they"
that is so desperate
for you to be president?
You already know
who they are.
You know what?
i'm done being toyed with.
The minute that you can
show me the slightest respect--
Why do you think
i have treated you
this way?!
Why do you think
i have tried
To chase you away
from this university?
I've been trying
to protect you.
You and melinda.
Melinda? how did you--
Look, i've said
too much.
Protect her from what?
Is it the shadows?
Are you trying to protect us
from the shadows?
Stop asking
so many questions!
Don't ask any
questions at all.
Tina?
I really need
to talk to you.
Are you here?
Tina?
My husband and eli,
They spoke to morgan
and bedford.
I think
i understand now.
You died so young,
that's hard to accept.
And you needed
someone to blame,
and these two men--
No, they had nothing
to do with how i died.
So then why have you
been haunting them?
I never haunted bedford.
And forrest, well,
i loved him.
But i was angry at him
Until i heard what
you and your friends
were saying.
That he never
asked bedford
to chase you away.
Well, forrest was weak.
Just like i was.
He could never say no.
And bedford, well...
[scraping]
He was just trying
to protect his friend.
[whispering]
but the truth is,
They're the ones
who need protecting now.
From what?
I also heard what
you said about
president bedford,
About what he could
control as president.
You mean the book?
[scraping]
So i asked some questions.
You asked questions?
about the book?
Well, who did you ask?
Ghosts.
There's so many.
[scraping]
Especially here.
In the hospital?
well, what do they say?
They were scared.
So they didn't say much.
Eli said that
something
Possessed a friend
of bedford's.
Is it the shadows?
Is that what the ghosts
are so scared of?
Is that what you're
trying to protect
bedford and morgan from?
Tina, please, what is
everyone so scared of?
[whispering]
Who's there?
[scraping]
Is anyone there?
Who are you?
is anyone there?
[breathing heavily]
[voices whispering]
[gasping]
No!
What are you?
[voices whispering]
What do you want?
[scraping]
Eli: so what was it?
a ghost?
Different than any ghost
i've ever met.
What do you mean?
It was like it could
get inside me,
And all i felt was
cold, fear and hate.
Then it just disappeared?
Sort of.
It was uncoiling like
this band of cold
slithering off me.
Tina's here.
She's just keeping
her distance.
Did you tell him
what i can do?
Yeah, i did.
A month ago, i would
have booted him
out of the hospital.
But recently,
you felt like
tina was here?
So this light
that she's supposed
to go into,
She stayed back
because of me?
You have
to ask her that.
Is she here?
I don't know
where to begin.
I'm so sorry
for what happened.
I was your teacher.
I never should have
let us get involved.
Tell him
that he's right,
But that it's
my fault just as
much as it is his.
She says
it's her fault, too.
But if i played a part
in leading her down
a path to her death...
No, i had
a pill problem
Long before
i met forrest.
Her addiction was there
long before you were.
So what's kept her here?
how can i help her move on?
I made so many mistakes.
Like not believing
in myself
And running away from
things when i really
should have faced them.
But the one thing
that i always did
Was i took
the easy way out.
You know, the easy money,
The easy relationship.
She always chose
the easy way out,
The easy relationship.
Didn't take any work.
Do nothing,
we stay together.
and it eventually ends.
Eli: just like bedford.
That's what they told him,
Do nothing and you'll
become president.
Tina: but i'm not going
to do that now.
I'm not going to leave
forrest alone now,
or bedford.
Even he's not
to blame for this.
Tina, i know
you want to
protect them,
But i don't think
you can.
How do you know that?
You said it
yourself.
Ghosts are scared.
Whatever
this thing is,
It can hurt them,
and they don't have
the power to stop it.
Well then, who can?
I don't know.
But i'm going
to find out.
Tina, whatever
this thing is,
It can't mean more
than you being
where you belong.
Can you see the light?
Look for the light.
She can see it,
she just doesn't
want to go in.
If you want to help me,
move into the light.
Why?
All the time
that we were together,
I told myself
that i was good for you.
But i really wasn't.
I want to be good for you.
Once.
Please.
Tell him i don't know
if we were good
for each other...
But he--he was
the best thing i ever had.
I will.
Melinda: she's gone.
Please, mother,
chopin isn't muzak.
Now if you don't
pipe down,
I won't read you
your jane austen.
Where were we, hmm?
Page 293.
"but no such
happy marriage
"could now teach
the admiring multitude
What connubial felicity
really was"--
[static]
[electricity flickering]
"the, uh, union
of a different tendency,
And precluding
the possible"--
[static]
Leave her alone.
She's helpless.
She can't even
open her eyes,
for god sake.
In the middle
of the night,
When no one is looking,
I'm going to go
to that machine
over there,
The one
that keeps me alive,
And unplug it.
I will slowly die, josh.
It will be painful.
And it will be
on your head.
Why are you
doing this to her?
You have no right.
I've done everything
you've asked.
You've been sharing
our business.
That's not acceptable, josh.
You will pay a price.
I won't let you hurt her.
If i have to keep
a nurse in here
24 hours a day,
I will do whatever it takes.
Do you hear me?
Do you hear me?!
[monitor beeping]
[static]
nurse!
I need a nurse!
someone, please!