Previously on...
Dave!
Is that the bathroom?
No.
I think that's it there.
Oh, okay.
Thanks.
Dave tried to eliminate
a witness to murder.
Hey! Uhh!
But Jackson survived...
I bought M.J. a fishing pole.
We're not gonna be able
to make it this weekend.
I'm kind of getting married.
- What?
I thought I heard you out here.
- Jackson.
Forcing him
to change his plans.
I'm a middle-aged guy...
Tom was searching.
And I don't know what
I wanna do with my life.
We're rich again!
Hallelujah!
Gaby's life returned to normal.
We're gonna be us again--
the old Carlos and Gaby.
I'm gonna make sure that you
walk away from this marriage
With your assets intact.
Now to accomplish this...
And Bree agreed to protect
what she felt was hers.
I'm capable of doing
whatever needs to be done.
The lawyer arrived
just after sundown.
He checked to make sure
no one was watching,
then he hurried
to the front door...
where his client was waiting.
As she poured him
the scotch he requested,
the client began to wonder
exactly how he planned
to hide her assets
from the husband
she was divorcing.
The lawyer suggested
some creative accounting.
His client agreed.
He suggest a secret bank account.
She agreed.
He suggested a
second set of books.
She agreed.
And then the lawyer looked
deep into his client's eyes
and made one final suggestion...
that she was
completely unprepared for.
You want me to rob
my own house?!
Not exactly. I was thinking we'd
hire my friend Tony to do it.
Absolutely not.
I am all up for
a little creative accounting
and some
secret bank accounts,
but hiring some thug
to stage a break-in?
It's a community property state,
babe.
Orson's going to get half
of everything,
including your jewelry,
your artwork, your antiques.
Wouldn't it be easier
to just have him killed?
As your lawyer,
I can't condone that.
That said, I have a cousin--
- I was kidding!
So was I.
Loosen up, freckles.
Well, I just never know
with you.
And don't call me
"freckles."
Look, if you're not
comfortable with Tony,
why don't we do the job
ourselves?
I bet you'd look hot
in a ski mask.
You are repugnant,
and this conversation is over.
Fine, but since I'm charging you
for the full hour,
let me make it worth your while.
Sit down and close your eyes.
What? No!
Just humor me. Come on.
Now I want you to picture Orson
after the divorce.
He owns half of your business,
half of your assets.
You see it?
Go on.
Now I want you to picture Orson
dating some young bimbo.
And don't kid yourself.
He will get a bimbo.
Now picture
your favorite strand of pearls
dangling in the 24-year-old
cleavage of said bimbo
while she is using
your first edition
Robert Frost as a coaster...
And your 19th century
french crystal vase
as an ashtray.
If you can live with that...
I will leave.
And with that,
The client offered
a suggestion of her own...
We should probably
break a window
to make it look more real.
And the lawyer agreed.
Masks--
you can find them in any home.
Some are used once a year
to scare the neighbors...
Some are needed
for the occasional chore.
Some are applied
every other Thursday.
Then there's the kind of mask
some men wear every day.
It's a friendly smile
designed to hide
the most wicked of intentions.
Hey, M.J.,
is your mom home?
She's inside talking
to Jackson.
Really?
So... what do you think
of Jackson?
I like him.
He buys me comic books.
Yeah, he's a good guy.
He was very brave
that night
during that fire
at the nightclub.
Does he ever talk about
that fire...
or anybody he saw
that night?
Have the police stopped by
to ask him any questions?
If they do,
would you let me know?
Why?
Well...
I wanna make sure they're being
nice to our friend Jackson,
'cause he's such a good guy.
It is such a stunning piece.
It's simple and elegant.
Don't you think?
I mean, I know
it was expensive,
but you can't put a price tag
on beauty. Am I right?
So when daddy finds out
how much I spent,
would it be okay if
I used you as a human shield?
You know, I should really
get you tested.
Mom?
Hey! Did you have
a fun playdate with Heather?
She's got a canopy bed.
I want one.
We just bought you a bed.
It's not even a year old.
I don't like it anymore.
I wanna sleep under a canopy.
Then go move in with Heather,
'cause I'm not getting you one.
Why not? We're rich.
Who told you that?
- I heard you telling Aunt Bree,
since daddy got his new job,
we're rolling in money.
Well, mommy shouldn't have
said that.
Just, when Aunt Bree started
bragging about her Prada bag,
mommy kind of lost it.
Whatever.
I want a canopy,
and you gotta get me one.
I don't have to
get you anything.
And stop acting
like a spoiled brat.
I am not spending a fortune
on a bed you don't need.
Oh, but you can spend millions
of dollars on a stupid vase?
That vase is not stupid.
Is that vase stupid?
Okay, you know what?
This conversation is over.
Go to your room!
You, too, bobblehead.
Okay, my clothes
are in the closet.
I'm going to put my toothbrush
in the bathroom.
Oh,
just leave the toilet seat up,
and the immigration people will
totally think we're married.
Yeah, I don't know how I'm gonna
thank you for doing this.
Actually, I did think of one way
you could repay me.
Mmm. You got it.
Uh, no.
not like that.
No, I was thinking that after
our quickie courthouse ceremony,
you could buy me a cake.
I love wedding cake.
It's the one part of marriage
that never lets you down.
Well, I can do you
better than that.
How out I throw us
a big engagement party?
What?
Well, we're not having
a wedding,
and we're gonna need
pictures of something
to put in our photo album
as evidence.
Okay. Yeah,
I guess that could be fun.
While our friends are toasting
to our everlasting happiness,
we can yell,
"surprise! It's all a sham!
Thanks for the crock-pot!"
No, no, no. We can't tell
anybody this is a fake.
The whole thing could blow up.
- Can't I at least tell the girls?
No way. I mean, they don't
call her "gabby" for nothing.
Wow.
Ah, fake marriages--
they're complicated.
I-I-I know I'm asking a lot,
Susan.
No, no. It's okay.
I wanna do this.
Truth is...
I miss you,
and the house has been kinda
lonely since you left.
Well, I hear you
loud and clear.
Not that lonely.
What are you doing?
- Thinking.
Well, think inside.
I made pork chops.
Aren't you gonna ask me
about my job interview?
Oh, right. How'd that go?
Okay... until the 30-year-old
who was interviewing me asked me
if I'd ever used twittering
as part of a marketing campaign.
And what'd you say?
Nothing...
Because I don't know
what "twittering" is.
It's a social networking tool
where you send instant updates
to anybody
who signs up for them.
So... you knew about this,
and yet you kept it from me?
I didn't keep it from you.
It's just
one of those tech things
that you don't care about.
It's for young people.
And I am a dinosaur
marching into the tar pit.
I didn't say that.
You're not gonna get
a whole lot of sympathy from me.
I just went through
the same thing. Remember?
Yeah, but you didn't tell me
how bad it was.
That's another thing
you kept from me.
50 guys showed up
for that one job,
and I was 10 years older
than every single one of 'em.
I could hear 'em twittering
as I left the room.
I think you mean
"tittering."
Sorry. Please, don't hit me.
I heard a door slam shut today,
Lynette.
It's official.
My time has passed.
I am no longer relevant.
Oh, for God sakes,
knock it off!
I am not gonna let you
feel sorry for yourself.
You are Tom Scavo,
damn it!
And?
Sorry. I got nothing else.
Come inside and eat your pork.
This place smells funny.
I don't wanna be here.
Well, you should've
thought about that
before you started acting like
such a diva. Now sit down.
Father Crowley!
This is a surprise.
What brings you
to our soup kitchen?
Well, I want Juanita
to work with the poor.
I want to teach her
to be grateful
for how good she has it.
- Oh, well, we can always use a hand.
And four hands?
Well, that's a blessing.
Oh, me? No, no.
Not me.
I'm not really dressed
for ladling,
but, um, I could stand
by the condiment bar
and spritz people
with my Chanel.
And you say Juanita
is a little ungrateful? Hmm.
Fran Schulman?
Fran.
- Huh?
It's Gabrielle Solis
from the tennis club.
Oh, of course.
Wow, it's been years!
The last time I saw you was
at that charity fashion show.
Wasn't that fun?
- Yes. Yes, it was.
So what are you doing here?
Are you volunteering?
Not exactly.
- Me either.
My daughter's gotten
so snooty,
I am forcing her to spend time
with the great unwashed.
You wanna ditch this place
for a cappuccino?
Um, actually,
I'm here to eat.
Oh!
It's Susan.
Great. We don't see
enough of her.
And she's not alone.
Hey, Jackson. Long time no see.
What's going on?
Um... we sort of have
an announcement.
We're getting married.
Oh, my God!
This is such great news!
Oh!
So... when's the date?
Monday.
Whoa. W--
well, that's kind of sudden.
Well, when you know, you know.
Why wait? And we're having a
little engagement party on Friday,
and you're both invited.
A party? Count us in.
I can't think of a better reason
to... celebrate.
Have you told M.J. yet?
Yeah. He was on board when he
found out there was cake.
Okay.
Just wanna make sure this isn't
all happening too fast for him.
You know kids. They need
a little time to adjust.
Oh, kids are resilient.
He'll be fine. I'm so excited!
Well, uh, we wanted you two
to be the first to know,
and we should probably
get going.
Got a few more neighbors
to shock.
Oh, well, we are just
so happy for you.
Yeah. Congratulations.
Now if we're going with
the Damask for the settee,
then I strongly suggest that
we do the couch in the chenille.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
The only word I understood
there was "couch."
I'll explain it to him
later.
Good, because they're
only going to hold this fabric
for a couple of days.
Well, I am off.
Ohh.
Isn't that vase divine?
I am so glad you like it.
I thought we were
just trying out the vase.
I'll explain it to him later.
- Okay.
Mm-hmm. Thank you.
Can you believe this?
Seven years ago,
Evelyn did Fran's house.
Now? No house.
That's crazy.
You ask Fran what happened?
No! I didn't want
to embarrass her.
You met her in line
for free soup.
How much more embarrassed
could she get?
Remember that dinner party
she gave?
She had 20 place settings
of Tiffany china.
How does this happen to someone
who has Tiffany china?
This is $200 a yard.
Tell Fran to save us
a place in line.
I bet I know what happened.
She drank it away.
That one New Year's Eve
where she got so plowed
she fell in the koi pond...
where she landed on you,
drunky sue.
Everybody was hammered
at that party.
Well, then it must've been
a gambling problem.
Based on what?
She never missed bingo night
at Immaculate Heart...
and she was Lutheran.
You really think
she bingo'ed her house away?
Uh, I don't know.
There has to be some reason.
You don't fall that far
that fast
without making
some really stupid choices.
Why you gettin' so angry?
It was
Tiffany china, Carlos.
Aha! There's the man
that ruined my fishing trip.
Sorry about that, Dave.
- Oh, no worries.
Hey, I am so happy for you
and Susan. Congratulations.
Thanks.
So how have you been?
We haven't had
a chance to talk since...
I don't know,
probably the fire.
Uh, yeah.
You were the big hero.
I was the doofus that got
stuck in the men's room.
Oh, that was a hell of a night.
Sure would like to forget that.
- Yeah, me, too.
Unfortunately, I have to go down
and talk to the cops on Tuesday.
Really?
Yeah. I went down to city hall
to get my marriage certificate,
And I ran in one of
the detectives from that night,
and apparently, they've been
trying to get in touch with me.
So now I get to go down there
the day after my wedding.
Some honeymoon, huh?
Wow. Those guys really know
how to put a crimp in your day.
So did they say what they wanted
to talk to you about?
I guess they just wanna know
if I saw anything suspicious.
Hmm. Did you?
Mm, no.
I mean, I was backstage.
I was headed to the men's room,
and I ran into--
Oh! Ugh!
I am so sorry.
Oh, no. Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
I mean, there's gotta be a mop
around here somewhere.
That's not coming out.
Oh, Bree can get rid
of that in a jiffy.
Now where did she go?
Okay. Showtime.
- Wipe your feet first.
I just had
the carpets cleaned.
Just because we're thieves
doesn't mean
we need to be untidy.
Are we stealing this?
Uh, yes. As I recall,
it's quite valuable.
What about this?
- Oh, God, no.
That's Orson's dental Innovator
of the Year award.
I've always hated
that thing.
Oh, here.
What are you doing?
I, uh, took some of my silver
off the mantle,
and it threw off
the balance.
Yeah.
You're right. Let me help.
There. Balance restored.
Was that necessary?
This place has to look like
it was ransacked by robbers,
not someone's personal shopper.
Fine! But do you have
to do it with such relish?
Hey, you're not paying me
to just go through the motions.
Speaking of which... are you
nailing Orson like we discussed?
That is
none of your business.
Well, we have to make sure
he doesn't suspect anything.
I do the bare minimum.
No more, no less.
So is he just missionary?
He seems like a strictly
missionary kind of guy.
Must you be so crude?
Must you always be
such a priss?
You freak out
at the mention of sex.
You never want
to make a mess.
You suppress every spontaneous
urge you ever have!
Man, it must be exhausting
being you!
Yes, being a lady
takes effort.
Well, maybe give it a rest
once in a while.
It might surprise you
how good it feels.
You wanna be a Neanderthal,
Karl? That's your choice.
I prefer to behave
with class and dignity.
Now may we please finish
robbing my home?
Bill Brown!
It's Tom Scavo.
Tom! Oh, my God!
What are you doing here?
Well, Jackson and I are in
the same soccer league.
Lynette, this is Bill Brown.
We were roommates
freshmen year in college.
Hi.
Really?
- Yeah!
God, you look fantastic.
You haven't aged a day.
Hey, right back at ya.
Liar. You didn't even
recognize me.
Back up a second.
You guys were classmates?
Yeah.
Meaning you were in
the same class at the same time?
That's what classmates means,
Lynette. We're the same age.
Actually, I think
I'm six months older.
You're older?!
I'm sorry,
I just cannot believe...
That they're out
of stuffed mushrooms.
Excuse me.
Okay, my wife's annoying,
but she is right.
What's your secret?
What is it? Diet? Exercise?
You eatin' a bowl of stem cells
every morning?
Come on. What's going on,
Peter Pan?
Okay...
You really wanna know?
Hi!
This is for you and Jackson.
Congratulations!
Aw, how sweet.
Oh! And heavy.
Score.
Yeah, well, we can afford
to be generous
now that I'm off the hook
for alimony.
Yeah. What?
You're getting remarried.
So I can stop
sending that check every month.
Everybody gets a gift.
Right!
Score for you!
Uh, can I talk to you for a sec?
Yeah?
Oh, thank you.
You get alimony?
I thought you were too proud
take alimony.
I was too proud to admit it.
I'm not too proud to take it.
I need that money, Jackson.
Well, I-I can try to chip in.
- "Chip in"?
It's not a birthday cake
for Shirley in accounting.
It's mortgage and food
and insurance.
I'm sorry,
but I can't marry you.
No, Susan,
they'll send me back.
It's Canada, not Iran.
It's like America
with free health insurance.
Okay, I know this is
important to you,
but I depend on that check every month.
- And I know you do.
I just can't believe that I
finally found a job that I love,
and now I just gotta
give it up.
Well, look, maybe...
I could talk to Mike.
I could see if we could
work something out.
You'd do that?
Yeah, I'll try.
Don't think he's not gonna
want his gift back.
And it's really heavy, too.
So...
you thought my friend bill
looked pretty fantastic, huh?
Okay, I went
a little overboard.
You know me--two margaritas,
and I need a muzzle.
No, I completely agree with you.
He looks really young.
I know, right?
He must take care of himself.
Actually,
he told me his secret,
and I'm thinking of doing
the same thing.
No, you're not having
plastic surgery.
It's my face.
Uh, we live in
a community property state,
so half that face is mine.
Fine, you know what?
You get the half below the nose.
But these wrinkles up here?
All going away.
Tom, men don't need
plastic surgery.
They look better
as they age.
Real?
Because you couldn't
stop talking
about how great Bill looked.
"you guys were classmates?
You mean the same class
at the same time?"
Okay,
that's a lousy impression of me.
Look, Bill said it really gave
him a leg up in job interviews,
and I could use that
right now.
You don't need a face-lift.
What if I went out
and got a boob job
and came home with
big, giant sideshow boobs?
How would you like that?
I'd learn to live with it
somehow.
You're not doing this.
We can't afford it!
It's an investment in our
future. We can't afford not to.
I'm calling the doctor
and making an appointment.
If you want, I can also get
a price check on a pair of--
I'm not getting a boob job.
Why don't I make you
a nice cup of Earl Grey...
Oh, dear God.
Orson,
we've been robbed!
It wasn't me. I swear.
No cuts!
Back of the line.
Oh, relax. I already
ate dinner at home...
in my box under the bridge.
Fran?
Oh, God. I was afraid
I wouldn't find you here.
Ah, lucky you,
I'm still poor.
I feel bad I ducked out
so fast the other day.
And I've been thinking
about you a lot,
and I just--
I really wanna help.
Wow.
Thank you. Thank you!
Now...
I just wanna make sure
that you're not gonna...
you know...
Drinking was never
my problem, Gaby.
I didn't think so.
You were always so classy.
20, 40, 60...
Was it drugs?
No. I never did drugs.
Good to know.
80, 100.
Because gambling is bad enough
without being high.
I never gambled
a day in my life, Gaby.
Well, then what the hell happened?
This doesn't make sense.
I was at your house.
You had such lovely things.
Yes, Mark and I lived
really well.
Probably a little...
too well.
But we were young,
and we thought we had time
to save for the future.
Then he died.
Mark died?
I didn't know.
He was sick
a really long time.
He couldn't work.
He lost his insurance.
By the time he passed away,
we were completely wiped out.
Oh, Fran, I'm so sorry.
You didn't have any family
to turn to? Any friends?
No family, and as it turns out,
not too many friends either.
Look, Gaby,
know you came here
wanting to find out what I did
to make this all happen.
But the truth is, we're all
just an accident or a tumor
or a bad investment away
from...
standing in line for free soup.
Thank you.
I don't agree, Fran.
You know, Carlos went blind
for five years.
We went broke.
We almost lost our house.
But we worked our asses off
and we made it back.
Oh, so just because
you survived that,
you think you've crossed
some kind of finish line,
that nothing bad
can happen again?
Well, no, but--
- Listen.
I hope it works out for you.
I hope you never lose that
big, beautiful home of yours.
God knows I wish I'd appreciated
mine more while I had it.
Thank you again.
Remind me again when you're
getting your teeth cleaned.
Um... the 14th.
And the 15th,
we have tickets
to that play
that you're dragging me to.
Yes. Why?
I'm just--I'm trying
to figure out
when would be a good time
to get married.
I'm sorry.
What did you just...
I know, I know.
Not the most romantic proposal
in the world.
I shouldn't have led
with the teeth cleaning.
I feel I can overlook that.
So is that a yes?
Yes! It's a yes!
Oh!
Wow! What brought this on?
It just seemed
like the right time.
Oh, Mike.
I'm so happy.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I understand taking things,
but why smash something
you're gonna leave behind?
They're robbers,
dear. Not personal shoppers.
Yeah, well, whoever did this
should be shot.
Well, I wonder if the victims
of your kleptomania
felt the same way.
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
I never realized what
my stealing put people through.
Maybe this is karma.
What is that?
Oh.
It's a picture of the mask
they stole.
I drew it from memory.
Wow.
Hmm.
Remember where we got it?
Was it Florence?
Venice.
We walked past that little shop
under the bridge,
and you saw it in the window.
Oh, that's right.
Mm.
You told me you'd been
wearing a mask all your life,
but with me, you felt--
Like I could finally
take it off and be myself.
Yeah.
Anyway, I faxed it
to the shop in Venice.
They said they could
make a new one.
I should have it for you
in about a month.
I can't believe you went
to all that trouble
then you must not know
how much you mean to me.
Hello? Oh, hi, Dave.
No, of course not.
What's on your mind?
Well, I figured it was time
to get back to work,
so I put together
a speaking tour--
Seattle, Portland,
my usual route.
Work? Are you sure it's not too soon?
- Well, I have to do it eventually.
Anyway, I was hoping
you could check in
on the house now and then.
Of course.
Oh, someone's at my door.
Let me get rid of them.
Hey, Katherine,
is Mike here?
No, he's at work.
Oh, shoot. Um...
Well, can you tell him to call
me as soon as he gets back?
Sure.
Is everything okay?
Uh, well...
Okay, you know what? Mike's
probably gonna tell you anyway,
so just can't tell
anyone else, okay?
There's not a problem
with the wedding, is there?
It's still on, right?
It depends.
Jackson and I
are only getting married
because he needs
his green card.
Oh.
And then I realized
that I would lose my alimony.
So unless Mike will keep
paying me, I can't get married.
You have to.
I mean, poor Jackson.
I-I would hate to see him
deported back to...
where's he from?
- Canada.
Oh! Oh! Brr!
We can't have that!
If you want, I could
talk to Mike for you.
That would be great.
Just tell him
I need an answer quickly
'cause the wedding is Monday.
Well, don't cancel anything yet.
You'll have your answer tonight.
Thanks.
Sorry, Dave.
Dave?
Hey.
Hey, Lynette.
How's it going?
Oh, my husband wants
to spend money we don't have
on a face-lift he doesn't need,
so... not great.
Mm, tell him to be careful.
Have you seen
Bruce in payroll?
He just went in
for a little nip and tuck.
And? How's he look?
Like he's standing
in a wind tunnel.
Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Poor Bruce.
Yep.
What's his extension?
And I'm thinking
I may have acted rashly.
I mean, every marriage has
its rough patches.
Orson loves me,
and deep down, he's a good man.
If I stick with this,
maybe we can make it work.
Are you even listening
to me?
Don't need to.
Heard it all before.
Oh, really?
I've been doing this
20 years.
And trust me,
every woman gets cold feet.
"Am I making a mistake?"
"Was he really that bad?"
"Maybe I could try harder.
And I'm gonna tell you
what I tell them--
you're not making a mistake.
He really is that bad.
And no matter how hard you try,
he's still gonna be
the same jerk
who sent you into this office
in the first place.
Oh. So I'm just like
everyone else,
and you know everything
I'm going to say.
Yep.
I even know the stuff
you're not going to say.
I doubt that.
Let me give it a shot.
You've been thinking,
"What happens if
I walk away from Orson
and everything I invested
in this relationship?"
"Will I ever find
another man?"
Will you spend
the rest of your life alone?
Close?
In the ballpark.
Well, you listen to me.
You've got nothing
to worry about.
You're a beautiful,
elegant, classy woman,
and there's no way
you're gonna end up alone.
And do you say that
to every woman, too?
No.
I mean, I get some real uggos
in here.
You know, the kind
that are gonna die alone
and get eaten by their cats.
Charming.
So are we back in business?
Send me the papers
when they're ready.
Honey, I'm glad you're home.
I brought someone me from
work I want you to meet.
w--
Ohh.
Yeah. It turns out he
got the same procedure
that you're thinking
about getting.
So I thought maybe you
could chat him up about it.
So you're finally
on board with this?
Well, like you said,
it's your face.
Come on, I'm dying for you
to meet Bruce.
Bruce, I want you to meet
my husband Tom.
Hi, Tom.
So, um, Lynette tells me
you're thinking about having
a little elective surgery.
Did she?
- Mm-hmm.
Now you may not
be able to tell,
but I've had work done.
Really?
Have they finished?
Yeah.
Now I should warn you
that, uh...
after they operate,
it looks a little weird.
Oh, I was wondering
about that. Yeah.
But eventually it settles,
like this.
Mm.
Isn't it exciting, Tom?
In a few weeks, you are gonna
look just like Bruce.
Hey, if you want, I'll give you
the name of my surgeon.
Yes. I definitely want the name
of the guy who did that.
Lynette, um, Bruce looks like
he could use something to drink,
and I know that I sure could.
C-could you excuse us
for a sec?
Very clever, Lynette--inviting
the joker over to scare me.
I wanted you to see the face
they don't put in the brochure.
I will be having my work done
by a reputable surgeon.
Bruce looks like
his was done by a bear.
That's my point.
You don't know how these
things will turn out.
Well, I am willing to take
that risk. I'm doing it.
Why are you being
so stubborn?
Why do you care so much?
Because I don't want to have
plastic surgery.
What?
Tom, if you're unsatisfied
with your looks,
someday you're gonna
be unsatisfied with mine.
No.
- Yes.
You are going to look at me
someday with your brand-new face
And say,
"when did she get so old?"
We won't look like
we belong together anymore.
Lynette, I'm just talking about
gettin' rid of a few wrinkles.
But I don't see
your wrinkles, Tom.
I see our whole life
together.
This...
is you worrying about how
you're going to provide for us.
This is Penny
falling out of the tree house
and breaking her arm.
This is my cancer.
These are
the millions of laughs
that got us through
all those tough times.
It's like
a map of our marriage,
and I don't want
to lose it.
And it if keeps me
from getting a job?
You're gonna get a job,
And it'll be because they're
impressed by your experience,
not your wrinkle-free face.
I know exactly what
you mean.
And I love your face, too.
Mmm.
And this wrinkle here,
that's when--
This isn't about me, Tom.
Come on. Mwah.
Hey.
Good news.
Looks like we're getting
fake married after all.
Really?
- Yeah.
Mike agreed to keep paying me
alimony. He just sent me a text.
Oh, man. That's a relief.
And unbelievably generous.
I'm gonna send him
a thank-you right now.
You're welcome.
You know,
I really can't tell you
how much I appreciate
you doing this for me, Susan.
And I promise,
as long as I'm here,
I'll pitch in around the house,
run errands.
You know,
just like a real husband.
Clearly, you've never
been married before.
Well, you know,
just because this is, um...
a fake marriage, doesn't mean
it can't be wonderful.
Well, I've been in some
real marriages that weren't,
so... maybe you're right.
Oh, look. Cans.
You can't have a wedding
without cans and signage!
Sweet!
Let's get to the car wash
on our way to the courthouse.
Mm-hmm.
Jackson Braddock?
Yes?
We're with immigration.
You're in the country
on an expired visa.
You're gonna have to come with us.
- Oh, no, no, no.
You--you can't take him now.
- Ma'am, I need you to step back.
Susan, there's a business card
on the dresser
with an attorney's number. Would
you call him for me, please?
Please, can't this wait?
We're about to get married.
Not today you're not.
What's going on? Who are these guys?
- Uh... immigration agents,
and I think they're...
sending Jackson back to Canada.
Hello?
May I speak with, uh,
Bree Van de Kamp?
Oh, she's not in at the moment.
Can I take a message?
Uh, yeah, this is Sheila
with Weston Brothers Storage.
It's about the storage
unit she just rented.
Storage unit?
Uh, yeah, we overcharged her
on the deposit.
Tell her not to worry.
We're gonna deduct it
from her next bill.
Okay. Uh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Everyone wears
some kind of mask,
so you must look closely
to find the truth
that lies beneath.
Hi. Mwah.
Some conceal anxiety
about growing older.
Some hide fears
of financial ruin.
Others cover up a love
that continues to linger.
And then there are those
who let their masks slip.
If you look to their eyes,
you'll see
who they really are...
and exactly what
they're capable of.
Subtitles by LeapinLar