Previously On...
Mrs. Mccluskey
Had Reached Her Limit.
Five Kids Are Tough Enough,
But Your Husband Makes Six,
And That's Where
I Draw The Line.
An Old Friend Paid Adam
A Visit.
Sylvia.
Aren't You Gonna
Invite Me In?
After You Ruined My Life?
I Don't Think So.
You Should've Told The Truth
About Us.
Mike Got Help...
From An Unexpected Source.
(Gaby) Victor!
Victorashed Out...
Come On! Get Up!
(Grunts)
And Carlos And Gaby...
We Need To Ask You
A Few Questions.
Sorry. I Guess
I Don't Remember Anything.
Finally Met Their Match.
I Remember Everything.
(Mary Alice) It Was Supposed
To Be A Beautiful Day.
Kids Should Have Been
Playing In The Park.
Husbands Should Have Been
Doing Their Chores.
Women Should Have Been
Tending Their Flowers.
But At 2:26 That Afternoon,
A Tornado Came
To Wisteria Lane...
Bringing With It...
Unbelievable...
Destruction.
No One Could Have
Anticipated It...
Especial
Given How The Day Started.
Sorry.
Can You Say That Again?
I Don't Think
I Heard You Right.
Carlos And I Are Back Together.
Gaby,
You Just Got Married.
And Some Of Us Gave You
Very Expensive Wedding Gifts.
Uh, You Want
The Fondue Set Back? Fine.
But Don't Act Like
It Cost A Bundle,
'Cause It Clearly Didn't.
I Got You The Fondue Set.
Oh. Right. It's Nice.
Oh, My God.
This Is Gonna Kill Edie.
You Would Think So,
But No Such Luck.
That Vindicte Hag
Told Victor Everything.
Victor Knows?
Yeah, And Seeing How He's
The Rich Mayor Of A Small Town
With Various Thugs And Cops
At His Dposal,
Carlos And I
Thought It Would Be Safer
If We Got
The Heck Out Of Dodge.
You're Leaving Fairview?
Yeah. This Afternoon.
No.
You Can't Be Serious.
Look, We'll Be Back...
Someday.
We Just Have To Wait
Till This All Blows Over.
I Can't Believe This.
I Know. This Is...
A Lousy Way To Say Good-Bye.
And I'm Sorry,
But I Don't Have A Choice.
Do You Guys Have Any Idea
How Much I'm Gonna Miss You?
Hey, You Heard The News?
A Tornado Just Hit
Mount Pleasant,
And They Think
We Could Get One, Too.
Y'all Better Head Inside
And Start Getting Ready.
Um, Go. You Guys Go.
Yeah, And--And We Don't Need
To Say Good-Bye Anyway,
'Cause We're Gonna
See You Real Soon.
And Everything Will Be
Just The Way It Was.
Sadly, This Was Not To Be.
Oh!
In Four Short Hours,
One Of These Women
Would Lose A Husband,
And All Of Them
Would Lose A Friend.
But How Could They
Have Known This?
It Was Supposed To Be
A Beautiful Day.
-==Http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
绝望主妇 第四季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：
校对：
时间轴:超级无敌打工仔
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
By Noon That Day,
A Tornado Watch Was In Effect
On Wisteria Lane,
And Every One Of Its Residents
Was Preparing For The Storm--
Everyone, That Is,
Except Gabrielle Solis,
Who Was More Concerned About
Another Storm On The Horizon.
Mayor Lang,
Recovering From His Injuries,
Will Reportedly Be Released
From The Hospital Tomorrow.
Until Then, The Deputy Mayor
Will Be Coordinating
Fairview's Emergency Response
As The City Remains
On Tornado Watch.
It Has Been Over 50 Years...
I Turned Off The Gas
And Locked Your Car
In The Garage.
I'm Gonna Go Gramy Passport
From The Safe-Deposit Box
Before They Close The Bank.
...We Should Understand Is
Never Underestimate
The Power Of Mother Nature.
What's Wrong?
They Said Victor's Getting
Out Of The Hospital... Tomorrow.
Relax.
We're Gonna Be Gone
Before They Give Him
His Last Sponge Bath.
And Remember, The Accountant's
Dropping Off The Papers
For My Cayman Island Account.
I Can't Deal With That
Right Now. I'm Packing.
Gaby, Those Documents Give Us
Access To $10 Million.
Multitask.
I Told You Just To Pack
The Essentials.
That's What I'm Doing.
Is That A Boa?
Carlos, If You Are
Taking Me Somewhere
Where I Don't Need A Boa,
Then I Don't Want To Go.
Fine. You Could Be
A Little Bit More Sensitive.
I Had To Say Good-Bye
To My Friends Today.
Yes, I'm Sorry.
And I Should Probably Go Over
And Say Something To Edie.
Like What?
"Rot In Hell,
You Maggoty Whore"?
That Woman Ruined Our Lives.
If She Had Kept Her Mouth Shut,
We Wouldn't Be Running Away.
I Know, But I Can't Help
Feeling A Little Guilty.
I Mean, Do You Ever Even Think
About What We Did To Edie?
Who Cares?! Thanks To Her,
I'm Giving Up My Home,
My Friends,
Half My Wardrobe.
So Do Me A Favor And Never
Mention Her Name Again
Unless It's Followed
By The Phrase,
"That Conniving Skank."
Ya Think You Can Do That?
Hey, Lynette.
Hi. Did You Hear
They Declared A Tornado Watch?
Scary, Huh?
Yeah, Well,
Don't Worry About Me.
I'm Ready For Anything.
It's Sweet Of You
To Dough.
Oh, Yeah.
Okay.
Um...
Can We Stay
In Your Basement?
What?
Well, If This Tornado Watch
Gets Upgraded To Aarning,
We're Gonna Need
A Place To Wait It Out.
"We"--Me, Tom, The Kids.E"?
That Family You've
Come To Know And Love.
All Ven Of You?
Yeah.
Well, First Of All,
I Only Love Four Of You.
And Second,
No Way In Hell.
Mrs. Mccluskey, Please?
It's A Small Basement,
Lynette.
I've Already
Invited Ida Over.
We Just Wanna Play
Some Cards
And Wait This Thing Out
In Peace And Quiet.
We Can Be Quiet...
Relative To The Storm.
Look, There's A Shelter
Over At 3rd And Grove.
Why Don't You Go Over There?
That's In The Middle
Of Skid Row.
You Think I Want My Kids
Around A Bunch Of Winos?
Ida's Off The Wagon. It's Not
Gonna Be Much Better Here.
I Am Asking You As A Friend.
Please?
(Sighs) You're Not Gonna
Let This Thing Go, Are You?
Thanks. And Don't Worry.
I'll Have A Talk With My Kids.
I Promise They'll Keep A Lid
On The Destruction.
Relative To The Storm.
Yeah. Mm.
Dylan, We're Fine.
It's Just A Tornado Watch.
No. We Paid A Lot Of Money
For This Class Trip,
And I Want You
To Stay And Enjoy It.
Tell Julie
I'll Keep An Eye On Her Mom.
Gotta Go.
What The Hell
Are You Doing Here?
I Just Came To Talk
To Adam.
I Like Your Hair Long.
This Is Harassment.
I Will Call The Police.
I Don't Think So.
You'd Have To Tell Them
What Happened
With Me And Your Husband.
You Don't Want People
Knowing About That.
In Case You'd Forgotten,
Adam Wants
Nothing To Do With You.
Oh?
Didn't Seem That Way
Yesterday.
He Didn't Tell You
I Stopped By?
I Hope He's Not Starting
To Keep Things From You...
Again.
Here. I Brought You A Few Things
In Case There Is A Tornado.
(Chuckles) Wow.
Tape, Batteries, A Radio.
How'd You Know
I Need This Stuff?
An Educated Guess.
Hey, Actually, Um,
Since You're Here,
I Was Thinking That Maybe
It Would Be A Good Idea
To Tell Orson About Mike's,
You Know...
Drug Problem.
Good, Because I Already...
Told Him.
You Did? When?
Last Week.
I Was Afraid That Mike
Might Go To Orson For Pills.
I'm Sorry, So...
Orson Already Knows
About Mike?
Did I Do Something Wrong?
No. No, You Didn't
Do Anything Wrong.
Thanks For The Supplies.
I Don't Believe
A Word You Say.
So You Still Don't Think
I Slept With Adam?
Of Course Not.
Oh, Well, Let Me
Paint A Picture For You.
Me Lying In His Arms,
Him Wondering Out Loud
How He Ended Up Marrying
Such A Cold, Hard Bitch.
Katherine,
Are You All Right?
I-I Couldn't Help
Noticing--
Of Course You Couldn't.
And Everything's Fine.
Thank You.
Hi There.
I-I Don't Mean To Intrude,
But Are You All Right?
Not Really, No.
Would You Like
A Nice Cup Of Tea?
The National Weather Service
Has Extended The Tornado Watch
To The Tri-County Area.
Funnel Clouds Have Been Spotted
In The Counties
Of Mansfield And Webster...
I Can't Believe
You're Being So Nice.
You Don't Even Know Me.
Well, I Know Katherine,
And Believe Me,
You're Not The Only Person
I've Seen Her Reduce To Tears.
Did You See Her Spit On Me?
Yes. That Was Unfortunate.
If You Need
Any Antibacterial Soap, I--
Nah, I'm Good.
So, Um, Why On Earth
Would Katherine Treat You
So Dreadfully?
Oh, She's Just Mad 'Cause
Her Husband's In Love With Me.
Really?
I Was One Of His Patients
Back In Chicago.
From The Moment We Met,
There Was
This Intense Passion.
We Tried To Fight It,
But We Couldn't.
Well, You're Only Human.
I Know He's Miserable
Without Me,
Even Though She Tries
To Pretend That They're Happy.
I Mean, You're Their Neighbor.
You Think They're Happy?
Well, They Seem...
Content.
Well, They're Not.
It Was Just
An Observation.
Yeah, A Stupid One.
Okay. (Chuckles)
This Has Been... Lovely.
We Really Should, Um,
Do It Again Sometime.
You Think
I'm Making This Up?
We Were Lovers.
I Can Prove It.
He Has A Snake Tattoo
On His Right Shoulder.
I Licked It.
Be That As It May, I Really
Think You Should Go Now.
No One Believes Me!
She Has You All Brainwashed!
Sylvia,
Whe Are You Going?
Sylvia, You Need
To Come Out Of There.
Ask Adam!
He'll Tell You The Truth!
Ll, Adam Is Not Here,
And There Is A Tornado Coming.
And As You May Have Gleaned
From The Batteries
And Bottled Water,
That Bathroom Is Where We Are
Planning On Riding It Out.
So Would You Please Be A Dear
And Come On Out?
Go Get Adam!
And... Open Wide.
Orson, We Need To Talk.
(Drilling Stops)
Susan. I'm With A Patient.
Yeah, I Can See That.
Hi. I'm His Neighbor.
Cute Shoes.
Why The Hell
Would You Give Mike Drugs?
Uh...
Mrs. Kowalsky...
(Clears Throat)
We're Gonna Step Out
For Just A Moment.
No Need. I'll Be Quick.
'Cause I'm Sure You Have
A Very Good Reason
For Giving Mike Pills
When You Know
That He Has A Drug Problem.
So... What Is
Your Very Good Reason?
Okay, This May Take A While.
You Might Want To Spit.
Mike Was Having A Lot Of Pain
With His Shoulder.
Oh, Of Course, And You Know
All About Shoulder Pain...
Being A Dentist.
I Thought I Was Helping.
By Giving Pills
To An Addict?
Does That Sound Helpful
To You, Mrs. Kowalsky?
Ank You.
Finally, Some Sanity.
Susan, You Have To Leave.
Fine.
But You Know, If I Find Out
That You Have Given Mike
So Much As A Breath Mint,
Trust Me, There Is Not
Enough Novocaine In This Office
To Numb The Pain
I Will Inflict On You.
Hi, Miss Britt.
You Need Some Bottled Water
Before The Storm Hits?
Well, Thanks, Jeremy.
20 Bucks.
Hold It.
You Are Price Gouging
Right Before A Tornado?
I Was Just Trying
To Make So Money.
You Really Wanna
Make Some Money?
Go Hit Up Gabrielle Solis.
She Hasn't Met A Price Tag
She Didn't Like.
I Already Tried.
She And Mr. Solis
Are Moving.
Moving?
Yeah. They're Loading Up
Their Car And Everything.
They Didn't Tell You?
Well, They Probably Didn't
Want A Big Emotional Scene.
Too Bad.
What Was I Supposed To Do, Mike?
Leave 'Em In Your Truck?
I'm Not Gonna Sit Back And Watch
You Spin Out Of Control.
Out Of Control? Have I Ever
Missed A Mortgage Payment?
What?
Or Disappeared For Days On End,
Or O.D.'D In An Alley?
No. I Go To Work Every Day.
I Help Out Around The House.
I Take Care Of You And Julie.
What's The Problem?
Let's See. You Lied To Me.
Uh, Your Drug Dealer
Almost Dated My Daughter.
You Lied To Me Some More,
And Then I Find Out That You
Hit Up My Best Friend's Husband
For More Pills.
You're Blowing This
Out Of Proportion.
And You're Kind Of Yelling
At Me--Also A Problem.
I'm Sorry. I'm In Pain.
You Might Think
You Have Things Under Control,
But They're Only Gonna
Get Worse...
And With A Baby On The Way.
I'm Sick Of Explaining Mysel
If I Need A Pill Now And Then,
I'll Take One.
So Where Are They?
I'm Serious, Susan.
Give 'Em To Me.
Forget It.
Hey, Don't Walk Away
From Me! Susan!
Let Go Of Me!
My Wife Needs To Be Seen
Immediately.
She's Pregnant.
She Fell Down The Stairs.
Any Bleeding?
Uh, No.
Cramping?
Uh, I Think
I Just Twisted My Ankle,
But I Would Like
To Get Checked Out Anyway.
Sure,
But For Non-Emergency Cases,
It's Gonna Be A Long Wait.
Well, She's Pregnant. Doesn't
That Make It An Emergency?
Sir, I'm Sorry.
You're Just Gonna Have To Wait.
It's Okay.
How Could You Not Have Told Me
Sylvia Was Here?
I Was Trying Not To Upset You.
Well, You Failed.
At Least If You Had Warned Me,
I Wouldn't Have Been Blindsided
When She Showed Up
On Our Front Lawn.
I'm Sorry.
Look, I'll Call The Police.
I'll Get A Restraining Order.
I'll Do Whatever It Takes To Get
This Woman Out Of Oulives.
Bree. Hello.
Hi, Katherine.
Could I Borrow Adam
For A Second?
I Have A...
Situation On My Hands.
She's Over There,
First Door On The Left,
And Please Hurry.
What Is She Doing There
In The First Place?
I Saw Her Weeping.
I Wanted To Help.
You Wanted Dirt, And I'll Bet
She Told You Plenty.
I Can't Help Having
A Sympathetic Face.
Sylvia? I Need You
To Come Out Here, Okay?
Adam?
Is That You, Darling?
Don't Call Him That!
Katherine?! I'm Not Coming Out
If She's Here!
I'm Not Leaving You Alone
Withhusb
Just Come Out!
I'll Get Rid Of Her!
Ladies.
So What'd She Tell You?
That She Had An Affair
With Adam.
Well, She Didn't.
She Was His Patient--
A Pathetic, Lonely Woman.
One Day, For No Other Reason
Than Sheer Pity,
He Gave Her A Little Kiss.
Sylvia Took This To Mean
That They Were In Love.
And When Adam Told Her
Otherwise,
She Had A Breakdown
And Accused Him
Of Sexual Assault.
Oh, My God.
What Did You Do?
We Settled Out Of Court.
I Wanted To Fight It,
But Adam Was Afraid
Of Losing His License.
Of Course,
We Lost Everything Else--
Our Home,
Our... (Chuckles) Savings
And Our Friends.
So This Is Why
You Moved Back To Fairview?
It Was Supposed To Be
Our Fresh Start.
So...
Now You Know
Our Dirty Little Secret.
Well, Katherine,
For What It's Worth...
I Would've
Spit In Her Face, Too.
What's That Noise?
Is... Is That The Tornado?
Worse. It's The Scavos.
(Lynette) Hey, We're Here!
I Know!
(Tom) All Right, Guys.
Come On. Stake Out Your Places.
(Preston) Th Is Our Spot!
We Called It!
(Parker) You Can't
(Preston) Can So!
(Boys Shouting Indistinctly)
(Boy) Ow, My Head!
Lynette? I'm Begging.
Oh. Sorry.
Kinda Get Used To It.
Come Here.
Give That To Mama.
(Shouting Continues)
Hey, Guys? Come On Now.
Knock It Off. Here You Go.
And... First Base, Second Base,
Third Base, Sit.
We Gonna Have
A Nice, Quiet Tornado Watch,
And Nobody's
Gonna Cause Any Problems.
Is There A Cat Here?
Oh, Yes. I Brought Toby.
Is Something Wrong?
I Didn't Realize
There'd Be A Cat.
Tom's Really Allergic.
It Sets Off My Asthma.
Ida, Is There Any Chance
That We Could
Put Little Toby Upstairs?
Upstairs?
Yeah. He'd Be Very Safe.
We Could Put Him In A Closet.
Sure.
Why Don't We Put Penny With Him,
Since It's Safe?
(Chuckles) What?
Toby Is Ida's Baby, Lynette.
No, Toby's An Animal,
And My Husband, A Human Being,
Will Get Very Sick
If He Stays Down Here,
So, Please,
Put The Cat Upstairs.
Look,
I Invited Ida To Come Here.
You, I'm Doing A Favor For.
If You're Not Happy
With The Accommodations,
You're Free To Leave.
Hey,
I'll Just Stay Over Here.
(Chuckles) May--Maybe It Won't
Get Any Worse.
No, That's Ridiculous.
Karen, Come On.
Sorry. Theat Stays.
Knock Yourself Out.
(Man) Start Him On I.V.
(Woman) I'll Be With You
In One Minute!
Are You Okay?
Yeah, Yeah, I'm Fine.
I'm Just Worried About You.
How Long Are They Gonna
Keep Us Waitin'?
Are You Sure
That's All It Is?
(Scoffs)
Hey! Hey, We Were Here
Way Before These People.
Sir, They're Seeing Everyone
On An Emergency Basis.
This Woman Is Hemorrhaging.
Danny, Can You Take Her In?
What, You Gotta See Blood
Before You'll Treat Somebody?
My Wife's Pregnant, And She
Fell Down A Flight Of Stairs.
I'm Sorry, But I'm Gonna
These People Are Bleeding.
I Can Absolutely Wait.
I'm Just Asking Them
Hell, You Could've Done It
While You're Standing Here
Talking To Me, Right?
Sir, We'll Get To Your Wife
As Soon As We Can.
Now Please Take A Seat.
Just Take A Look At Her!
Get The Hell Off Of Me!
Mike, Stop!
Whoa! Uhh!
I Need Security Here Now.
Hey.
When You Gonna
Let Me Out Of These Things?
When Your Wife's Done
And You're Ready To Go Home.
The Doctor
Said The Baby's Fine.
Oh, Thank God.
Yeah.
And, Uh, Your Ankle?
Just A Mild Sprain.
How You Doing?
I've Had Better Days.
I Am So Sorry.
It's Gonna Be Okay.
I Talked To The Doctor,
And,M,
They Have A Rehab Facility
Thanks.
I Don't Need Rehab.
I Can Kick This Myself.
I've Done It Before.
You Keep Saying That,
And It Just Keeps Getting Worse.
Susan, Look At Me.
I'm Handcuffed To A Chair.
I Think
I've Hit Bottom Here.
I Will Fix This.
Just No Rehab.
Mrs. Delfino?
The Doctor Asked Me
To Give You These, For The Pain.
Oh, My God.
Are You Kidding Me?
I've Kind Of Had
A Rough Day Here.
No.
(Whispers) Susan...
(Normal Voice) I've Just
Gotta Get Through Is.
No.
There's No Tomorrow.
It's Now.
You Will Quit This Now.
You Will Go To Rehab,
Or So Help Me, I Will Leave You.
I Will Take This Baby,
And I Will Leave You.
You Win.
I'll Go.
Gabrielle?!
Excuse Me?
Sorry. I'm In A Rush.
My Wife's
Alone With The Kids,
And I Have To Get Home
Before The Storm Hits.
This Is The Information
Carlos Asked For.
About What?
About
The Cayman Island Account.
Didn't He Tell You
I Was Coming?
Yeah, Of Course He Did.
Uh, He Said
You'd Be Stopping By.
Duh.
This Is Everything You Need
To Access The Money.
I Washed My Hands Of This,
So Whatever You Do,
Don't Lose That Folder.
Got It?
Believe Me, I Won't
All Right. Nice To Finally
Meet You, Gabrielle.
You're Just As Pretty
As Carlos Said You Were.
Oh, No.
I'm Prettier.
Edie,
What Have You Got There?!
Oh, Crap!
Residents Are Advised
To Seek Shelter At Once.
Again, Do Not Evacuate.
Stay Where You Are
And Seek Shelter In A Basement
Or Any Windowless Room.
You Okay?
My Throat Is Closing Up.
I Think I Gotta Go Upstairs.
No. No, No, No, No, No.
You Stay Here.
Edie, You Thief!
Open This Door Now!
I've Called The Police!
They're On Their Way,
And They Are
Going To Taser Your Ass!
Oh!
Gaby?
Oh, Good. You're Home.
Lynette! What--
What The Hell
Did I Tell You?!
I'm Not Gonna Sit
And Watch My Husband Suffocate.
Well, I Don't Want Ida To Wake
Up And Find Her Cat Missing.
Karen, After All Our Years
Of Friendship,
How Can You Choose A Cat
Over My Husband?
You Think We're Friends?
Of Course.
Really?
You Ever Stop By Just To Say Hi
Or Invite Me For A Cup Of Tea?
Ida Does.
What Are You Talking About?
I Had You Over For Lemonade
Last Week.
While I Was Drinking It,
You Went To The Store,
And I Watched The Kids
Face It.
The Only Time We're Friends
Is When You Need Something.
That Is Not True.
I Genuinely Care About You.
You Mean Like Today,
When You Came By To Check On Me?
Oh, That's Right,
You Only Wanted A Basement,
(Meows Loudly)
Damn It, Toby!
Hey, Hold It! Hold It!
You Can't Go Out There!
That Stupid Cat Is
The Only Family That Ida's Got!
Now This Is What Friends Do!
Karen!
Give Me The Damn Folder, Edie!
(Singsong Voice)
Not Gonna Happen!
It's Worthless To You!
(Normal Voice)
Oh! You And Carlos
Are Screwed Without It,
And That Is Worth A Lot To Me.
Give Me My Money!
Ah! (Scoffs) Your Money?
Carlos Embezzled It.
Oh, Now You're Moral
All Of A Sudden?
You Didn't Care
Where The Money Was Coming From
When Youhought Carlos
Was Gonna Spend It On You!
Okay, I'm Not Unreasonable.
Cut Me In For, Say, 60%,
And I'll Go Away.
How's That Sound?
No! (Growls)
Aah!
Get You!
Edie!
Give Me That!
No! Let Go!
No, You!
Let Go!
You! Aah!
Oh! Oh! No!
No!
Wh Did You Do?!
What Did You Do, Edie?!
Get In The House.
Now!
Toby!
Toby.
Karen!
You Gotta Get Inside Now!
He's Right There!
Damn It!
I'm Not Gonna Let You Die,
So Don't Make Me Drag You!
Oh, Crap.
Oh! Hurry!O! Go!
No!
Come On! Come On!
Come On, Come On!
Get In!
I Have A Crawl Space.
(Loud Bang)
I Think We Can Both Fit.
You Just Threw My Money
In A Tornado.
I Am Not Getting In There
With You.
Fine! Then Stay Out There
And Die.
Move Your Ass!
Oh!
Come On, Sylvia.
Please Open The Door.
Sylvia.
Thank God You're Here. We Need
To Get Into The Bathroom.
We Can't.
There's A Woman In There.
Well,
Tell Her To Hurry It Up.
No, No, No, She's Barricaded
Herself In There.
She's A Patient Of Mine
Who's Had A Little Meltdown.
Just Give Me Five Minutes.
We Don't Have Time. There's
A Funnel Cloud Out There.
Sylvia!
Open The Damn Door!
Go To Hell!
Quick! In Here, In Here.
Come On.
Quickly. Quickly.
Come On! Hurry Up!
Go! Get In, Get In!
Get In!
Uhh! Hang On!
Hang Onto This!
Can I Say Something?
What?
I'm Sorry
Carlos And I Lied To You.
I Know We Hurt You,
And I Wish It Didn't Happen
The Way It Did,
And I-I Just Want You
To Know That.
Why Are You Talking
Like That?
Well, I Thought
Just In Case We--
Oh, No, You Don't.
You Just Shut The Hell Up.
We're Not Doing
Deathbed Confessions Here.
We're Gonna
Get Through This.
I'm Gonna Go On Hating You
For Years To Come.
You Really Hate Me?
Yes.
(Sighs) No.
(Sighs) It's Just That
I Really Let Myself
Fall For Him,
Which Was Stupid
Because I Always Knew
That He'd Go Back To You.
Oh.
Well, I'm Still Sorry,
Though.
(Softly)
I Said Shut The Hell Up.
I Think It's Possible
Benjamin Might Need Changing.
That Went Beyond
The Hypothetical
A Good Ten Minutes Ago.
We're Giving You Shelter.
You Could At Least Be Gracious.
We Wouldn't Need Shelter If
Oh, So Now It's My Fault That
That Lunatic Commandeered
Our Safe Room?
If You Hadn't Been Dying
To Know Our Business,
She Wouldn't Have
Gotten In There.
Can We Stop Pointing Fingers?
This Isn't Bree's Fault.
You're Right.
Sorry.
But You Can Understand Why
I'm Upset,
Having That Insane Woman
Back In Our Lives.
I Can Only Imagine.
I Had To Listen To Her
Babble For An Hour.
What Kind Of Things
Was She Saying?
She Said That She And Adam
Were Lovers
And She Could Prove It
Because He Had A Tattoo, And...
What?
She Said He Had A Tattoo
On His Shoulder,
Which I Know Isn't True Because
I've Seen Him At The Pool,
And I Would've Remembered
Cause Tattooed People
Make Me Very Uncomfortable.
Did She Say What Kind
Of Tattoo It Was?
Um... A Snake.
What's The Difference?
He Doesn't Have One.
He Did...
Back In Chicago.
He Had It Removed.
Oh.
Sorry.
Katherine...
So... That's Why We Settled?
Why We Lost Everything?
I'm Sorry, But You Have
To Understand--
No, I Do Not.
Sorry.
(Whispers) Not Here.
Not Now.
Gaby!
Change Of Plans!
We Gotta Get
In The Basement Now!
Gaby?
(Sighs)
Damn It. Where Are You?
Where's Gaby?
I Thought She Was With You.
I Don't Know Where She Is.
I Guess We'll Have
To Wait For Her Together.
(Sighs) Do Youind
If I Say Something?
Look, Gaby And I Never Planned
To Get Back Together, Victor.
We Tried To Keep Away
From Each Other.
We Really Did.
But... I Don't Know.
It's Like We're Two Halves
Of The Same Person Or Somethin'.
And When We're Apart, W...
We Just Aren't Happy,
Which Is Why We...
We Never Set Out
To Hurt You, Victor,
And I'm Sorry We Did.
Are You Done?
Yeah.
Come On, Carlos!
You Better Get In The House!
You Could Get Hurt Out Here!
Adam!
Hello!
Where Is Everyone?!
Did You Hear That?
Adam, I'm Leaving!
This Is Your Last Chance
To Come With Me,
Or I'm Gonna Tell Everyone
Exactly What Happened!
Okay.
You've Made Your Choice!
Here I Go!
Aah!
It's Here.
It Was Supposed To Be
A Beautiful Day.
But Then The Winds Came
And Changed Everything...
And Not Just The Houses
And The Lawns.
Oh, My God.
The People Had Changed, Too.
While The Storm Had Raged,
Each Of Them
Had Learned Something...
About Friendship...
And Forgiveness...
And Redemption.
And Some Had Learned
The Hardest Lesson Of All...
That Life Is Always Fragile
And Very Often...
Unfair.
Oh, My God! Oh, My God!
Tom! Help Me!
Help Me, Tom!
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.Ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入