Previously on Desperate Housewives
Can we start over?
It was a surprising day for
the women of wisteria lane.
Well, I was wondering
If you might want to
have dinner with me. Okay.
He's giving her orgasms?!
Ah! Not deliberately.
I can see we're going
to be great friends.
You are a vibrant,
attractive woman, you--
Who hasn't had sex in two years.
That spells "grandma" to me.
Let me come stay with
you when I get outta here.
This guy thinks I'm
out of commission,
And I want to keep it that
way. What's wrong with you?
You've been antsy all night.
I think I left the freezer
door at scavo's open
But it was an even
more surprising night...
Crap! It's my dad! For the scavos.
Where is she? Don't. She isn't
wearing anything, all right?
Who is she? Just some
girl from english class.
I'm gonna go in the bathroom.
You got 60 seconds to
get her out of here.
That same night
Five minutes later
There was a slight misunderstanding
In the scavo house that night.
You see, someone in the family
Was having an affair
with a married wom,
And lynette scavo
suspected her husband.
False alarm. The
freezer was shut tight.
Unfortunately for
lynette, she was wrong.
Liar.
What? I always knew things
could change between us, tom,
But no matter what,
The one thing I always thought
I'd get is your respect.
Lynette, what's going on?
I followed you to the
warehouse. I know everything.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, at this point,
I think I'm gonna need a
little bit more than that.
You're right. I shouldn't
have kept this from you.
And...
You know, for what it's worth, I
wanted to bring you in on it. Huh?
But I was afraid you'd overreact.
That's what you were afraid of?
Hey, I'm upset, too.
But let's face it. Boys will be boys.
I think... I have to sit down now.
Lynette, are you really surprised?
It's not the first
time this has happened.
And it definitely won't be the last.
You know what? I have to kill
you now. Well, he's your son, too.
Who? Porter!
What are you talking
about? I found out
Porter's been hooking up with
some girl at our warehouse.
What are you talking about?
And just like that,
The slight misunderstanding
in the scavo house had ended...
Hey. What's up?
You're having sex with
your best friend's mother?!
And a huge family crisis
Had begun.
Desire...It's an emotion
designed to lead us astray,
Causing us to buy
things we can't afford...
Encouraging us to sample desserts
We don't need...
And pushing us into love affairs
We're clearly not ready for.
I want you to call that woman
And tell her you are
never seeing her again.
Her name is anne.
Her name is mrs. Schilling.
She was your t-ball
coach when you were 6.
By the way, does
your best friend know
You're sleeping with his mother?
We're keeping our relationship
from kirby for now.
This isn't a relationship.
You are being used by this woman.
No, I'm not. I love her.
Okay, that's it. I'm calling her.
No.
Hey! What if her husband answers?
Gee, porter.
That's just one of the pitfalls
of dating a married woman.
Listen to me! Mr.
Schilling can't find out.
He--he's totally violent.
He--he would kill her.
Well, then you have put her
in a very dangerous position,
Haven't you?
Okay. I'll call her.
I'll tell her it's over.
I'm not going to say that you know.
That'll just freak her out.
But you have to promise me
That you won't say anything
to her psycho husband.
I am not promising anything.
So help me, if I find out
That you do something,
and she gets hurt,
I will leave this
house and I will never
Come back! Oh, please!
You would never do that
Yeah? Well, i-i've
done a lot of things
You never thought I would do.
Wait.
We won't say anything.
But if you don't end this,
you won't have to leave.
We will throw you out.
So... You wanted to see me?
Sit.
Tell us, charlie...
Have you enjoyed working
here at mrs. Van de kamp's?
Yeah. It's great.
You don't feel you've
been underpaid? No.
Well, then perhaps you can explain
Why you stole $200 from the
petty cash box yesterday.
What? I didn't steal anything.
Charlie, we wouldn't accuse you
unless we had concrete evidence,
And thanks to my diligent
partner here, we do.
So am i, like... Fired?
You're more than "like" fired.
You're fired. And, of course,
we want our money back.
Uh, I don't have have it. I spent it.
Well, then I suggest
you return your purchase.
Do you have a receipt?
Yeah. Yeah, like pot
dealers give receipts.
Well, you've just covered
yourself in glory on this one.
Just... Please,
don't tell my parents.
I'll get you the money. I promise.
Can you believe it?
A thief and a pothead!
Well, at least we know now
Where the 2 pounds
of cookie dough went.
Too many?
Yeah. I gotta have one more. Ah!
Thank you for doing this.
Ah, well... We needed to
wipe the slate clean, right?
Mm. And honestly?
This is the best second
first date I've ever had.
Isn't it?
And knowing we're not gonna have sex
Takes all the pressure off.
That's... Something we know?
Yes.
We're starting completely over,
So this time, we're
gonna do things right.
W-which means what?
Well, it means...
No sex until at least date four.
Ah. I want us to spend this time
Really getting to know each other.
I-i do know you. What's
my least favorite word?
"phlegm."
You're just guessing.
It's "panties."
Ohh. Although some days
it's "larva" or "chunks."
Well, I will try to remember that.
Mm. Now you tell me something
I don't know about you.
Okay.
I'm a painter.
I sort of guessed that
when you painted my house.
I mean, I paint... Art.
Like... On a canvas, in a frame.
Seriously?
I went to art school in paris.
And my professor had a beret,
so you know he was good.
So now you're
painting... My bathroom?
Yeah.
It sucks.
But I've been blocked
for the past year.
Blocked? Yeah.
I mean, I keep trying to
start new pieces, but...
Nothing comes. It's...
Driving me crazy.
Well, I'm sorry things
aren't going well.
But I'm glad you told me.
See? We're getting
to know each other.
And we wouldn't have if we'd
spent the whole night in bed.
And now I'm creatively
and sexually frustrated.
First dates are awesome.
Jeez, roberta, I know you
hate to throw anything away,
But do you have the garbagemen
bringing you stuff now?
Pardon my french, but what's
french for "kiss my ass"?
So you said dave has a secret.
Now how you gettin' that from this?
It's just a bunch of
phone numbers. Yeah,
It may be just a
bunch of numbers to you
But to a savvy sleuth with a keen eye
And the nose of a
bloodhound-- yeah,
Yeah, you're miss
marple with a bum liver
So what's he hiding?
Let me walk you through it.
Around the 1st of every month,
Dave gets a string of
calls-- five or six--
From this number in boston.
They're all short--
10, 15 seconds.
My guess is he's not picking up.
Somebody's leaving him messages. You
know, buggin' him. Once a month, huh?
My guess is it's an ex-wife
looking for her alimony.
Except it's not. You see this?
After a few days,
he always calls back.
And who, you ask, is he calling?
A hospital in boston.
It's the office of
dr. Samuel heller...
Psychiatrist.
So... Once a month,
Dave whines about his life
To a beantown headshrinker, huh?
Big whoop.
I looked up your
davey's doc on the web.
He's not your garden-variety shrink.
He's a renowned psychiatrist
and published author
With a very specialized
field of expertise.
And that, my dear watson,
Is your neighbor's little secret.
Treating the criminally insane
Oh, lap of luxury,
Hoi've missed sitting in you.
Celia! Juanita!
Chef is taking fresh-baked
cookies out of the oven.
You're not gonna catch me!
Oh, I can't tell you how nice it is
To hear the sound of children's
laughter in this house.
You know what I was thinking?
Why don't you all stay the weekend?
Ooh, we'd love to. Jeez, we can't.
Why not? Celia's
birthday party is sunday.
We've gotta get ready
for it, remember?
What's to get ready?
You buy a $9 sheet cake
And fling a piata over a
tree and bam! Party time.
But I don't have a change of clothes.
My nephew left a whole
closet full of old clothes.
I'm sure something will fit you.
Well... Carlos, just nod your head,
'cause I ain't leaving this
pool. Oh, good. It's settled.
Oh, gaby. Your
margarita's getting low.
I'll send brandon
out with a fresh one.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
What? You heard the woman.
She wants children's laughter.
And I want the lobster the
chef is serving for dinner.
It's a win-win. I just don't
feel comfortable with this.
Why not?
I mean, look at this
place. It's like shangri-la.
Wow, you're right. The
pitch black I see here
Is much more dazzling
than the one at home.
What is your problem?
My problem is that it's a bad idea
To mix business and pleasure.
Says the man who massaged
her into an orgasm.
Even more reason to keep
some professional distance.
Carlos, she is just
a lonely old woman
Yearning for some
friendship and human contact.
And i, for one, am
happy to be that human.
Mrs. Solis? Your margarita.
Oh, shoot. I can't reach it.
Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
Hey. You bring beer?
Was I supposed to? No.
Tom was supposed to.
Gosh. Sorry. I thought the
two cases I bought monday
Would've lasted more
than one rehearsal.
Boys, we're better
off not drinking today.
We've got a lot of work to
do and only one week to do it.
What are you talking about?
We are playing
Battle of the bands
at the white horse!
Uh, dave? Battle of the
bands isn't for amateurs.
You gotta audition.
Uh, we don't.
Edie's got a real estate buddy
whose husband owns the club.
You're kidding. We're
playing an actual gig?
In front of people
who aren't listening
Just because I pay their
allowance? Well, this is fantastic!
Yes! But that means
the pressure's on.
We gotta really
rehearse our cover stuff
And... We need an original song.
I don't know anything
about songwriting.
I-i know a little
bit. No, you don't.
It's fine. Mike and I
will write something.
You got a little time later?
Not tonight. I got plans.
"plans
What's her name?
Can we just rehearse, please?
You know, I heard
that susan and jackson
Broke up. I heard
they got back together
It's not susan. Stop guessing.
Also, get lives.
Whatever, mike,
Just so long as you're having fun.
Hey! Who said you--
turn the board around.
Get back here. No! Come out
here and show me some moves!
Sorry to bother you.
Just wanted to see if you needed
anything before I go off to bed.
No, we're good. Sure you don't
want to order margarita number 12?
You sure you don't want
to shut your piehole?
It's so cute, how you two bicker.
Carlos, how do those pajamas fit you?
They're perfect.
I-i hope your nephew doesn't
mind that I was wearing 'em.
He'll never know. We're estranged.
Oh. Okay.
Anyway, we're good.
So have a nice night.
Oh! What's that?
Some animated thing.
I love animated movies.
The girls wanted to watch it,
So we're kind of having
a family movie night.
Ooh, that sounds like fun!
My heavens, is that penguin surfing?
Gee, I don't know. I can't
really see the screen anymore.
Oh, dear. I'm being rude.
Oh, that's okay.
There. That's better.
Did she just crawl under... Oh, yeah.
And so there I was in ninth grade,
And my boobs had not
made an appearance.
I was desperate.
Here. Let me refill that for you.
And so that's when
I got caught stuffing
At the pep rally.
And six months later... Kaboom.
I was voted prom
queen. Nice work, girls.
Stop that right now.
What?
The sex music. Turn it off.
That--that's
not sex music.
We are not having sex
until date number four,
And this is date number two.
I know what it is.
It--it's just that you
look so hot in these pants,
And your hair smells so good.
And your eyes...
Look, I made you dinner. Come on.
Jackson-- I braised
beef for you.
Do you know what a pain in
the ass it is to braise meat?
Okay, do you know how sad it makes me
To know that you only
braised it to boink me?
You're supposed to be
asking me questions.
The point of all this was to
get to know each other better.
How is it gonna make
our relationship stronger
For me to know that
in the fifth grade,
They sent you to the therapist
'cause you wouldn't
stop chewing your hair?
You know, that was
hard for me to share,
And the fact that you
just make light of it...
No, I'm am calling the
second date officially over.
And you know what?
I was going to let you
feel me up over my blouse.
But now? Nada.
So before we wrap up here,
We still need some chaperones
for the junior prom.
Anne schilling is
coordinating the volunteers,
And she could really use some help.
Nobody?
I know we're all busy,
But this is important.
We want our kids to have
fun, but let's face it.
If we don't keep an eye on them,
God only knows what kind
of trouble they'll get into.
Helen?
Marjorie? You'll help?
Fantastic. Thanks, guys.
Hey, lynette.
Do these meetings
keep getting longer,
Or do they just seem that way?
I don't know.
So...
How's the family?
I haven't seen penny in so long,
And all the kids are
getting so big now.
I guess the boys will be
going off to clege soon.
Aah! Lynette!
I know everything, okay?
Ok...
I'm sorry, but...
It's important for
you to understand...
I love porter.
So do i.
And if you ever lay
a hand on him again,
You will find out just how much.
Oh, bree. I've got good news.
Me, too. You go first.
I hired a girl to replace
that thief charlie.
Oh. Well, are you
sure she's trustworthy?
Well, she comes with
a strong recommendation
From the head of the
local f.B.I. Office--
Her father, who's mormon.
Well done, orson!
Thank you. Your turn.
"the new christian
reader" just published
An advance review of
my cookbook. Listen!
"mrs. Van de kamp's colorful
stories of her upbringing
"show her upstanding values,
But her recipes are
sinfully delicious."
They gave me four halos!
Then I think this
is appropriate--
Holy cow!
I have to admit,
I had some reservations
about us working together,
But this has succeeded
beyond my wildest dreams.
Mmm. We're quite a team, aren't we?
Yeah, and the best part is
We get to see each
other all the time.
Mm-hmm, I know, which
makes the hardest part
Keeping my hands
off you all the time.
Orson!
You can't be serious! Here?
This kitchen is the
birthplace of our triumphs.
What better place to
celebrate them, hmm?
Ooh! Oh, this counter's
hard on my head.
Do you want me to stop?
No. Get me an oven mitt.
Right.
Oh, much better.
Rise and shine, girls.
Rise
and shi--
Oh, my god!
What are you doing?!
Gaby, it's fine. We're just
doing a little art project.
I told the the girls
They could decorate the
room any way they wanted.
I'm making a castle.
It's stupid.
No, you're stupid!
You're both stupid. Stop it!
Um, mrs. Hildebrand, this
is really nice of you.
But why would you want to
ruin your beautiful room?
Oh, it's not my room
anymore. It's their room.
What?
Yes. It's the room
they'll be staying in
Whenever you come to visit.
They're getting a new tv, bunk beds.
I'll have it ready by the
time you get here next weekend.
Uh... Next weekend, uh,
Carlos and I have plans.
Well, I bet the girls don't.
I'll send a car for them.
I... Don't think
That's such a good idea.
How about it, girls? Wanna
spend next weekend here? Yay!
Yay! Thank you. Mrs. Hildebrand.
Oh! Oh! What did I tell you?
Sorry. Thank you, grandma.
Oh, come!
"grandma"? She told them
to call her "grandma"?
Yeah, and that's why we're leaving.
After you told her
you'd stay all weekend?
How we gonna do that? I
don't know. Make an excuse.
Say you ha some blind
thing you have to go to.
We have to be very careful here.
This woman has a lot of
pull at the country club.
Plus, we've got that europe
trip coming up. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're not going to
europe with grandma
Nutjob. I'm not walking
away from $100,000
We need that money.
Carlos, it's not worth it.
She's really starting to
freak me out. Damn it, gaby.
I told you it was dangerous
getting chummy with the clients.
You wouldn't listen. You
had to stay for the lobster.
Hey, I seem to remember some
melted butter on your bib, too.
Now how we getting out of here?
Look, she knows we've got
celia's party tomorrow.
I'll tell her we have
to go shopping for that.
Everything will be fine.
Sorry.
I had to wait for my
folks to go to the store
Before I could sneak
out. What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I don't know what to do.
About what? Let me help you.
It's just all such a mess.
Wait. Is this about my mom?
Did she do something else to you?
Did she call your husband? No.
Well, then what? Tell me.
I'm pregnant.
Hey,o you mind if I
cut out early today?
I don't see why not.
I mean, everything's,
uh, pretty much done here.
You can go now if you like. Thanks.
Andrew. Don't you look handsome?
Do i? Great.
Something wrong?
You remember charlie, the kid
you guys fired for stealing?
Well, he called and asked
how you could prove it,
And I said, "we've got a
surveillance tape, scuzzball."
Well, uh, guess who stole
The surveillance tape last night.
That does it. We're pressing charges.
Uh, you--you might want
to hold off on that,
Because according to charlie,
The surveillance tape
is also a sex tape.
What?
Yeah, he said it shows a
couple really going at it.
So...
Any idea who those
crazy kids might be?
Oh, dear god.
Yep. Kinda thought so.
How could this be happening?
Before anything got serious,
I made a point of
turning the camera off.
Wait, I turned it off, too.
I didn't see you do that.
No, you were looking
for the olive oil.
Obviously, you turned it back on.
We need to, um, get that tape back.
Yeah, well, break out your checkbook,
'cause he wants 2
grand for it. $2,000?!
Yeah, or he's gonna
post it on youtube.
What are we gonna do? Well,
first you need to decide
What your porn names are gonna be.
Okay, this is not a joke. My
book comes out next month--
My old-fashioned,
traditional cookbook!
This could ruin me!
All right, bree. We'll just pay him.
No! I-i refuse to pay
blackmail to some hooligan
Who's stolen from us twice!
Andrew...
All my life, I have
done my best to teach you
To respect god and the law
And never to harm
another living thing.
I want you to forget
every one of those lessons
If it'll help you get that tape back.
So... Carte blanche?
Uh... Within reason.
We are not condoning
arson or violence or--
Orson, don't cramp the boy's style.
Hey, sweetie. Now don't
forget to make a wish.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday.
Virginia! What, uh,
are you doing here?
I came to give celia
her birthday gift.
Well, she's a little busy
with her friends right now,
So just give it to me, and
I'll make sure she gets it.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
You see, for my present,
I'm gonna take her to a shop
That sells the most
exquisite antique dolls
And let her pick
whichever one she likes.
Well, she's not gonna leave
her party to go buy a doll.
Well, of course not. I'll wait
on the porch till it's over.
Uh, look, I'm sorry,
But I don't want you
driving off with my daughter.
Well, you know she'll
be safe with me.
But if you'd feel
better joining us...
You sure are making this hard.
I have tried to be nice, but I
am running out of polite here,
So I'm just gonna say knock it off.
I'm sorry. Knock off what?
This whole creepy, clingy
"i'm your grandma" routine.
But I've come to feel like
a grandmother to the girls.
In three days. That's
the creepy part.
What a hurtful thing to say,
Especially given how generous
I've been to your family.
Yeah, too generous.
It's like you're trying
to buy us or something.
Well, we're not for
sale, so just back off!
Who do you think you're talking to?
You wicked, ungrateful girl!
You're not the first greedy bitch
Who's tried to bleed me dry
and then wash her hands of me.
Okay, we're done here. Good-bye.
Am I not making myself
clear? Get off my property!
Gaby.
What's going on?
I came to buy celia a doll.
I believe you've
heard gaby's response.
Virginia, please.
Allow me to apologize.
I think it's a little late for that.
Thank you...
For a wonderful third date.
And I'm glad that you're
back on board with our plan.
Yeah, I really think
I'm starting to get
something out of it.
Mmm. Oh, pop quiz!
Why did kim beale stop
talking to me in eighth grade?
Well, you told erin connors
about her nose job. Right!
What time is it?
Uh, 10:48?
No. It's sex time!
Hey. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, susan.
What?! Stop.
We're not having sex till
the fourth date, remember?
Jackson, look at me.
I'm tipsy. I'm horny.
I'm easier than a
5-year-old's homework.
I'll call you tomorrow.
The forehead?
I hate to say anything, stan,
But you are president
of the country club.
You need to know
That the way carlos touched
me during my last massage...
Well, let's just say it
was highly inappropriate.
And that kind of behavior
Is a liability the club can't afford.
Good.
I appreciate your taking care of it.
Hello? Uh, hello. Is this dr. Heller?
Speaking. Who's calling? I'm
maggie carr at hilltop insurance.
We have an applicant
For a new term life insurance policy,
And he lists you as a
previous care provider.
I was hoping to verify
his medical history.
The name's dave williams.
Dave williams? I don't
know a dave williams.
Well, sure you do. You
call him every month.
How would maggie know
that?! Uh, I'm guessing.
Who is this?
Uh, hi, dr. Heller.
I'm, uh, lindsay thorne.
I'm maggie's supervisor.
And she's confused
and about to get fired.
And, uh, we just need you
to confirm for our records
That you're treating a
man named david williams.
What is your medicare i.D. Number?
Um... I'm not sure.
We're in the process of
converting to the metric system.
I don't know who this is,
But are you aware that what
you are doing is illegal?
Okay, look. We're just trying
to get some info on this guy.
He just moved to fairview,
And he's really creeping people out.
You're in fairview?
Yeah. Why? Does that
mean something to ya?
No, I'm just trying to
get all the info I need
When I contact the
federal authorities
To let them
know that--
Well, we really screwed
the pooch on that one.
Yeah, back to the drawing board.
Can I irish that up for ya?
It's noon somewhere.
You got the tape! How
did you manage that?
Orson, we don't need to know.
No, you don't, but
it's kind of amazing
What you can get a bunch of
bikers to do for a case of beer.
Oh, my. Well, I better destroy this.
Actually, you may
want to watch it first.
Why? I'm embarrassed enough as it is.
Humor me. I'll cue it up.
You watched it?! Well, I had to
make sure it was the right disk.
Here, just watch a little bit.
Oh, dear god. I can't look.
Really, andrew.
Wait. Bree, that's not us.
What? Well, who is it then?
Wait, wait. He flips
her in just a sec.
This is where it gets good.
Katherine!
And mike.
Just so you know, I'm--i'm
never eating anything
That comesut of that kitchen again.
Jackson?
I am declari this
Our official fourth date, okay?
The rules have been followed,
And you may begin disrobing...
Now.
Uh, I'm--i'm--i'm--i'm kind
of doing something right now.
Okay, I just ran into
your house half-naked.
The only thing you
should be doing is me.
What is on your face?
Is that paint?
Are you painting again?
Uh, y-yeah.
I thought you were blocked.
I was, but, uh...
Not having sex for a few days
Kinda got my juices flowing
in a different direction.
So now i-i really
need to finish, so--
So you've broken through
your creative logjam?
Congratulations!
Ooh, why not celebrate
By ripping off my
clothes with your teeth?
I... Can't. I'm not finished yet.
How close are you? 'cause I can wait.
Wait, wait, no. No, don't--
don't look at that... Yet.
That's me.
Yeah. Uh, it's...
Supposed to be.
That look on my face...
I've seen  before...
In the mirror, when I'm feeling...
How do you know about that look?
I-i know a lot about you.
I know your cheeks get red
when people say you're pretty.
I know that your
eyes start to tear up
Whenever you talk
about your grandfather.
And I know that when
you're really sad,
You get that beautiful, haunted look
That you try to shake off
before anybody can see it.
I can't believe I ever
thought you didn't know me.
Well, I guess I should
let you finish this.
I'm sort of missing hands.
Actually, that is one detail
I could use some help with.
Really?
Unless you have a
problem posing naked.
Oh. Come on.
I think you know the answer to that.
Hello, katherine.
Um, I thought you might
want this videota...
From our surveillance camera.
We have a surveillance camera?
Yes, in the, uh, test kitchen.
Oh, my god.
So that means you saw me and...
Mike. Yes, indeedy.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
Oh, what you must think of me!
Let's not dwell on it. Oh! I
mean, having sex in the kitchen,
Where food's prepared...
What kind of a demented
slut would do that?
I said... Let's not dwell on it.
Thanks for bringing it by.
Katherine, I'm sorry,
but I just have to ask--
Are you sure you know what
you're doing? Meaning what?
Meaning susan is your
oldest friend on this street.
She divorced him, bree, and
she's seeing someone else.
Why can't mike do that?
Because she's your
friend, and we're women.
We don't do that to each other.
Look...
I've been alone for five years.
I'm finally in a relationship,
And you're trying to
make me feel guilty?
Is that what I saw on
the tape-- a relationship?
I don't know what it is.
All I know is...
I'm having the time of my life.
Fair enough. But just be careful,
I mean, this is very complicated.
I'd hate to see it end badly.
Hey, breakfast's on the table.
Porter, this whole hating me thing
That you've got
going on right now--
Believe it or not, I get
where you're coming from.
I don't hate you.
But one day,
You are gonna meet someone more...
Appropriate.
Someone who want the same
things that you do out of life.
Then you are gonna
know what real love is.
And when you do, I hope
you will finally see
Where I am coming from.
It's me. Can you talk?
Hey, gary. I'm running kind
of late. Can I call you later?
Just listen.
I can leave town saturday.
You have the money, right?
Yeah. No problem.
I love you.
I know where you're coming from, mom.
And...
I-i want you and dad to know
That I really appreciate
everything you've done for me.
Good.
I'll see you downstairs.
Desire--
It's an emotion designed
to lead us astray,
Persuading those who crave
love to make foolish choices...
Causing those who yearn for family
To act out in anger...
Allowing those who are lonely...
To behave in reckless ways.
And when the pursuit
of our heart's desire
Becomes an obsession,
The best we can hope for
Is a caring friend
willing to come along...
Hi. I'd like to book the
next flight to fairview.
And stop us.