But sweetie,
it's an advanced class.
It's great, you studied hard,
and it paid off.
Thanks, Dad, but I mean, normal physics
in this school is hard enough.
Maybe I don't want to be accelerated.
I don't wanna put myself under pressure.
Well, pressure can be good for you.
My mother used to say
that pressure can make diamonds.
I mean,
don't you want to be a diamond?
Well, can't I just be a sapphire
who has time to hang out with friends?
If you don't have time
to take opportunities like this,
- then we should revisit the job thing.
- Dad, don't even...
Okay, you know what,
that's fine.
I'll make it work.
Yay, physics!
That's the spirit.
Sparky, mind your manners.
Sorry, he's not a morning dog.
Hey, Jo,
what's with all the dogs in here?
They're biomimetic.
I don't care what breed they are,
it's unsanitary.
It means artificial, Carter.
They're robots.
That biomimetic.
So what, the DOD has some program
to create armed robot dog soldiers?
No, but that would be so cool.
No, this isn't a GD thing.
People build them for fun.
They get really competitive
about it too.
I just don't want anything too big.
Last time was you and me at city hall.
It wasn't exactly very memorable.
Yeah, but the wedding night...
- Don't mind us.
- That was my plan.
How 'bout this: I take care of all,
and you just show up?
Yeah, with my hair done, my makeup.
My God, I need a dress.
I'll go shopping with you.
It's a wedding gown,
not a flak jacket.
I happen to like weddings.
You got a problem with that?
Okay, I'm not even insulted
that you didn't ask me
to cater your reception.
- Vincent, would you like to...
- Twist my arm!
Uncle!
Got a possible break-in on Feynman road.
If you want, I can... I can take it.
No... Hey, I'd love to sit
and talk weddings all day,
but... duty calls.
Guys, let's talk menu and theme.
I'm picturing Elizabethan ball.
Doggie!
Don't worry, Carter.
Robotic dogs don't...
ruin your pants.
Well, it's a scientific advance.
That's our reigning champion, Fifi.
Hello!
Two years in a row, best in show.
We're going for the triple crown.
Aren't we, baby?
Well, looks like the bitch is back.
Careful, Thunder, I wouldn't want you
to catch a programming worm.
Is that mange on Thunder?
- Control your tinker toy!
- You stay away from her.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my... Fifi!
Did Fifi make a mess on the grass?
- What did you do to her?
- Nothing.
This woman killed my dog!
Dr. Deacon,
good to see you back where you belong.
And it is good to be home.
I've been trying to find a way
- to say thank you.
- Good, because I have a task for you.
Good.
This is Dr. Mendel's.
He thinks he knows who did it.
Those people are ruining this town.
And who would
"those people" be, Dr. Mendel?
Those dog lunatics.
They're the ones
that broke into my lab.
They'll do anything to win.
Was there something here they can use?
What do you make?
Synthetic mucus.
Why?
How 'bout to cure every airborne
pathogen known to man?
My brew stops 'em dead.
But those fanatics just want to build
a more realistic dog nose.
All right, what makes you think
somebody's been in here?
Beakers don't jump off tables
by themselves, Sheriff.
This could've been a disaster.
I grow my mucus in super-colonies.
If those criminals had spilled
even a small amount
of the wrong compounds...
It would've been bad.
Okay...
I'll take a look at your evidence.
Jo, you wanna walk Dr. Mendel inside,
see if anything's missing?
Yeah.
Don't touch anything.
Oh, that's bad.
Season 3 Episode 03
Best in Faux (v 1.00)
Teams Projet-SG & 6th-Race.
http://projet-sg.net
http://u-sub.net
- What happened?
- Mucus happened.
- Is this stuff toxic?
- If there was any justice in the world,
it would be.
You're wearing my whole batch
of "misty green!"
What did I say about touching things?
I didn't touch anything!
They fell in the quake.
You must've felt it.
It shook the whole lab.
No... we didn't... feel anything.
None of our instruments recorded
any seismic activity.
That's why GD was built here.
There are no strike-slip faults,
no volcanic activity.
This here is stable.
- You, I'm not so sure.
- What?
I mean, they do let me carry a gun.
And I know what an earthquake is.
- What else knocked over those jars?
- Well, it was probably you.
I mean, the lab is full of fumes.
Maybe you just got dizzy.
And could you please get cleaned up?
You're dripping mucus on my floor.
Runny nose?
No, I'm fine. I'm not light-headed.
That's good to hear.
How's the Fifi situation?
The late biomimetic dog?
Yeah, that was sad.
I mean, kind of fun...
No... But sad.
So what's the status
on the investigation?
There isn't one.
I mean, it's not my job
to investigate malfunctioning toys.
Carter, they are hardly toys.
The Eureka dog show has led
to some incredible breakthroughs.
Artificial skin for burn survivors.
Compact neural computers.
Nasal spray that allows soldiers
to sniff out explosives
based on canine nose chemistry.
The dogs themselves
are a great marketing potential.
Just imagine a dog
that never eats,
never urinates,
and never dies.
Fifi died.
The owner thinks that it was sabotage,
and I need you to find out.
I've got corporate R&D people
coming to the show,
and they don't want to invest
in dogs that fall apart.
Excuse me.
Could anything be
a bigger waste of my time?
- I need you, Carter.
- The answer's yes.
Did you get the data
on the seismic motion scan?
Unclear.
Those are the details
I need to go over with him.
What do you want to know?
Everything started to shake.
Shut up, Carter.
There was no earthquake.
Jo was 50 feet from you.
She would've felt it. I need a favor.
And that's how you ask?
Who raised you?
Yep, the brains
of Global Dynamics.
The computer core.
Logic diamond processors
connected with tantalum beams.
If you networked every computer
made in the last 30 years,
it wouldn't come close
to the power in this room.
Dr. Stark,
it's so great to see you.
Usually no one comes down here
unless there's a problem.
Here, let me show you
my radial upgrades.
Actually, I'm just here
for the clearances.
Oh, yeah, that.
Fargo was supposed
to bring the paperwork.
I assume he...
Yeah, I'll go find him.
I didn't know
that they use diamonds in computers.
The aligned carbon-14 allows
hyper-dense qubit storage
in an optical quantum processor.
Diamonds can store tons of data
and transmit it super fast.
- 'Cause I had no idea.
- No one does
because they keep them all
locked down here.
Fargo, all ready for the dog show?
Don't even start with me, Tracy.
So who are you helping this year?
Jackson's Poodle?
- It could use a bigger brain.
- No, I'm actually sitting this one out.
A little too competive.
I see. Interesting.
What am I doing here, anyway?
Well, Dr. Fox is kindly giving me
one of her logic diamonds.
They're strictly regulated,
but being science director
does have its privileges.
I just need a law enforcement signature
to take it out of the building.
All right. Big experiment, I'm assuming.
Something hopefully disfiguring.
Actually,
it's just a wedding gift for Ally.
A singular diamond
for a singular woman.
It's very beautiful, Dr. Stark.
Thumbprint right here.
Thank you, Dr. Fox.
Thanks, Carter!
Sure.
Hey, I heard about Fifi.
Tragic.
Guess the field's
wide open this year.
Actually, I'm investigating
the earthquake.
Yeah, there...
There are no earthquakes in Eureka.
So I'm told.
Well, if you want a second opinion,
you can always ask Dr. Hood.
He's retired, but he used to be
the top dog in seismology,
vulcanology, geology.
Pretty much anything dirty{\,
and he was in it}.
All right, thanks.
Nice to meet you.
Dougie Fargo?
That wild man?
Did he tell you about the time
we were running those columbian drugs?
- No.
- Yeah.
Columbia med school wanted
to make mineral-based vaccines.
So Doug and I trekked all over Alaska
gatherin' eriochalcite
for those yahoos.
Crazy times.
So what can I do you for?
Well, I was at a farm near the lake.
And there was an earthquake,
but nobody felt it but me.
Is that possible?
Depends.
How drunk were you?
I'm sorry, man.
It's really not very likely.
Because there aren't in Eureka.
This place is rock solid.
I have trouble finding someone
who believes me.
I can relate.
I spent the last year of my career
being the guy no one believes.
Anyway, where are we talkin'?
- Around here.
- All right.
Nope. Sorry.
Nothing going on down there.
Dead as Toledo on a saturday night.
The next time I feel the ground shake
and see the northern lights inside,
I'll just leave the bar.
Never mind.
I gotta get back to the case
of the dead fake dog anyway.
Never mind.
Northern lights, huh?
Fifi's owner
still won't release the remains.
She's afraid we're going
to steal her doggie-building secrets.
Well, that case
gets better and better.
She still thinks Dr. Young
sabotaged her entry.
So you think you wanna talk
to Dr. Young?
No.
You wanna ask around?
See if anybody's dogs malfunctioned?
No, because this is stupid.
There isn't a crime.
- People waste thousands of dollars...
- Millions.
Millions of dollars making something
they're giving away for free
in every pound in America.
People need hobbies, Carter.
I used to collect handcuffs.
And meanwhile, there was an earthquake
which no one felt but me,
which is impossible.
Because there are no earthquakes
in Eureka.
Sheriff, you were right.
There's somethin' brewin' down there
and she's fixin' to blow.
It's just a hole. Just a hole.
Stay to the left.
Yeah, no, I already spoke to him.
He understands.
- He is really sorry.
- Sorry?
He could've killed somebody.
Dr. Hood!
Haven't we talked
about your using the tunneler?
Talk to him. He's the one that told me
about the triboluminescence.
Colored lights.
Rocks under seismic stress
can sometimes release
visible electromagnetic energy.
So I dove down. You ready?
All my readings indicate
there's a pressurized
komatiite melt under this town.
- Somewhere.
- Wait.
There's something melting
under the town? What, like a volcano?
Not like a volcano.
And it could erupt at any time.
And it's not linked
to any known fault system.
That's why your quake
was so localized.
A spontaneous pocket of magma?
That's impossible.
Did impossible cover my friend
with mucus?
He's got a point.
Okay. I'll have the geo lab
look into it.
You stay above ground.
So what, should we
start talking evacuation?
Maybe hospitalization.
Carter, there is no magma chamber.
Dr. Hood is unstable.
Not so much.
Seems like a smart guy.
Look, five years ago, Hood predicted
a 9.6 on the reelfoot fault.
We evacuated Memphis.
- Was there an earthquake in Memphis?
- No.
Hood cracked under the pressure.
He left right after that
because he kept seeing things
that just weren't there.
Carter, please, I need you to keep
your eye on him.
Don't let him do any more damage.
Acoustic physics
is a challenging class, Zoe.
So don't beat yourself up about it.
It's very complicated stuff.
Let's go back to the beginning.
There's two main sections...
- What are you guys doing?
- Rayl wave dynamics.
Careful, Jack.
It's an acoustic pressure wave.
She's trying to figure out the frequency
to melt copper ore.
So you can really
melt metal with sound.
I don't even understand it
well enough to explain
why I don't understand it.
- Do you want coffee?
- No, thanks.
I got somethin'
I really don't want to do.
- I can relate.
- Yeah. As can I.
- What are you avoiding?
- Just some troubling errand
I can no longer ignore.
- See ya later.
- Yeah.
Could you clear table number 5, please?
Why not?
I'm gonna fail this class anyway.
But that's how diamonds
are made, right?
Well, not unless you crack
under the pressure.
- You are going to have to clean that!
- What are you doin', Dr. Hood?!
I'm droppin' a shear wave probe!
- You want a turn? It's a blast!
- No! I'm good!
Can you shut it off, please?!
You can't drill in here.
I need to measure P-waves
if I'm gonna find this magma pocket.
This is the best spot
to crack through the igneous uplift.
You sure there's really
anything to find?
Oh, sure I'm sure.
I can hear the roaring,
I just haven't seen the tiger.
Oh, you've talked to Allison.
There's something happening here.
This isn't like Memphis.
Maybe. But I still want you
to pack it up and go home.
Okay? Just let Global handle this.
And I need your...
tunneling car thingy off the road.
Do you mind if I tow her home?
All above ground, I promise.
I just want to wash her up
before she gets rusty.
Sure. Sure.
Okay. Thanks.
That's too bad.
It was fun getting dirty again.
This... this map has gotta be, what,
70 years old?
What is it you...
you're gonna build here?
A hotel.
Our corporate visitors are used
to a certain level of service.
This spot is perfect.
But I found records
that showed some traces
of radiation.
Well, you know,
radiation is like penny candy.
It comes in...
all different kinds of flavors.
You think you can scan
something for me, correct?
Oh, absolutely. Yeah.
You know.
But a wide-spectrum survey,
it's a very complicated process.
- You're my man.
- Absolutely.
She's a liar!
She actually accused me of sabotage?
Your name came up.
I wouldn't touch her crappy stuffed
animal with a ten-foot pole.
But you're happy
Fifi's out of contention?
Are you joking?
This was my year to finally
crush her in front of everyone.
My dog is perfect.
Yeah, he's a champ.
You should see him run.
It's like Seabiscuit.
Here. Toss him one.
All right.
Hey, buddy.
You wanna run? You wanna run?
I'm telling you right now,
he's a winner.
What can you say?
He's such a great competitor.
Yeah. And the second one to blow.
I sent Fifi to GD.
Take what's left of Thunder
and see what you can find.
Wa... Wait.
I get to look inside?
Yeah. I want a complete dogtopsy.
- Thank you.
- Oh, no.
Just... And down, Fargo.
Hello.
Is everything okay in there?
I can't believe you convinced me
to try this on.
No one wears a big white dress
their second time around.
But tell me you don't love it.
It's fabulous for an amazon.
Honey, you can't tell anything
without a fitting.
I don't have time for a fitting.
My job is not planning a wedding.
It'll just take a second.
And presto.
Aren't you the beautiful bride?
Can I try it on next?
- Was that an earthquake?
- No.
A tunnel-drilling lunatic.
Just get me out of this.
It's... It's not working.
Triboluminescence must've
shorted the circuit.
Forget it.
You called?
You have something to tell me?
I do.
Hood has been tunneling again.
I told you to keep an eye on him.
I am. He promised me
he wouldn't do it any more.
Promised? Promised?
Okay, let me be perfectly clear here.
I need him to stop.
All right.
Dr. Hood!
We gotta pack it up.
A little fancy for the afternoon,
but you pull it off.
- Do you know why I'm in this dress?
- Laundry day?
Because you knocked out
half the circuits on main street.
There was a temblor?
I knew one was comin'.
When exactly?
Ten minutes ago.
And you knew because
you've been tunneling again?
No. I was here ten minutes ago.
That quake was the real deal.
- Pressure's building.
- There is no magma pocket under Eureka.
Please take the nice Doctor home.
Hey, Vera Wang, you want proof?
I'm out here trackin' a vent.
It's ready to pop.
Come on. Give me 30 seconds.
- You look pretty.
- Thank you.
A little princessy,
but I like the neckline.
Yeah.
- Okay, your time's up.
- Come on, a little grace period?
I'm trying to nail a fumarole eruption
down to the second here.
- Oh, no.
- What's a fumarole?
A mud volcano.
You see that?
I'm back in the game, baby.
All right, you...
You go that way and then meet me...
I like the neckline,
but not so crazy about the color.
We're sinking zero-balance
P- wave detectors all along the ridge.
I re-tasked the geo satellites
to look for ground deformations.
Sounds good.
What's all that gonna tell us?
Nothing.
We just like sounding smart.
The fumarole proves
there's pressurized magma down there.
We have to find out exactly where it is
and how big of a problem we have.
Maybe Hood's our problem.
Sure made quite a prediction,
and seems to like being top dog again.
Really?
- You think he could cause this?
- The instruments are gonna tell us.
Hopefully
before they reach critical mass.
Carter.
Yeah, look, Fargo, I...
Fine.
Gotta go.
Thorne's... Doggy dissection.
Let me know if your probing
produces anything.
Fargo, I have
a lava problem right now.
I don't have time to worry
about fake dogs.
Well, do you have time to worry
about national security?
Logic diamonds.
That's how these dogs always won.
They were juicing.
But the neural nets
couldn't handle the load.
But all these diamonds
were supposed to be locked in a vault.
Exactly, so not only are they cheaters,
they broke federal law.
Have fun in gitmo, ladies.
- Relax. I'll talk to 'em.
- I already tried that.
They said they have no idea
how the diamonds got into the dogs.
Likely story.
Okay, first,
leave the interrogations to me.
And second,
if they both have diamonds,
we need to go to the source.
- It looks like a logic diamond.
- Yes! J'accuse Fifi.
I thought all the diamonds
were under your supervision.
These aren't from our lab.
The manufacturing facility in Pensacola
puts a code
on every diamond they make.
The inventory's continually checked.
So someone else can make these?
There's several countries
with covert programs.
China, North Korea.
I'll check with intelligence,
see if they know of any missing stones.
All right, let me know
as soon as you get an answer.
- Stupid.
- Can't find the zipper?
I got an MD.
And two Phds, and I can't get
myself out of this stupid dress.
Thorne wants to see me
five minutes ago.
- Can you...
- Yeah.
- Can you help?
- Thank you.
Used to be pretty good at this.
The micro lock is damaged.
Yeah, it's like...
Super-velcro.
I know.
So... I should have believed you
when you told me about the earthquake.
No, you didn't feel it.
I know it sounds crazy. Lean back.
Coming from you, I should have listened.
I don't know. It's just the pressure.
I feel like I've got a million things
pushing in on me.
- Yeah, a little more.
- It's like I can't breathe. Like...
Like you're trapped in a wedding dress?
A little more.
Okay, it's just...
- Yeah. There. Got it.
- You got it?
Oh, thank...
Thank you.
So is this why you called?
No, I...
We haven't been able to pinpoint
the magma pocket yet.
But the resonance indicates
that it could be manmade.
You're thinking
by a disgraced geologist
looking to fix his reputation?
Well, pressure makes you do
crazy things.
There is this remarkable jumble
of radiation.
I mean, here, where you want
to put your hotel, there's everything
from x-rays all the way
up through gamma.
I mean, I'd love to know why it's there,
but it's very powerful,
and the source is right here.
Interesting.
And I'll give you all the specific
frequencies once I've run the samples.
That's not necessary.
You've given me
all the information I need.
It seems that my hotel project's
gonna have to go back to square one.
Wait.
- That's it?
- Oh, that's it.
All this clean-up
is gonna cost billions,
and my intention is to make money,
not waste it.
So I'm just gonna have to find
an alternate site.
And Henry, property development
can get very contentious.
So can we keep this between us?
For now?
Yeah, don't worry.
I'm good at keeping secrets.
- How's it going?
- We could get some nasty lava bombs.
It'd be easier to predict
if I could find the pocket.
Yeah, unless you already know
where it is.
Allison thinks it's manmade.
By some old volcano man who wants
one last ride on the Ferris wheel?
- I'm just doing my job.
- Some things you don't mess with.
Well, somebody did.
Take a pretty fancy machine
to liquefy bedrock.
Ah, this town loves
its fancy machines.
Yeah, no joke.
They build dogs, they could probably
figure out how to light a volcano.
Well, they both explode.
Some of the owners have been cheating
with logic diamonds.
I got dogs exploding all over town.
- That's a dog show I could get into.
- Yeah.
Have you tried finding out
where the diamonds were mined?
Yeah, yeah, no luck so far.
Well, I could shoot yours through
the old gas-liquid chromatograph.
Only take a second.
Might tell you where they're from.
- All right.
Every mine in the world
produces diamonds
with a unique molecular structure.
- Like a fingerprint?
- Yeah, or a really expensive snowflake.
So it looks like our little friend here
is all the way from...
Something's messed up here.
The carbon signature is from Eureka.
Is there a diamond mine here?
No.
But they used to mine coal.
We've been down here an hour.
If we're looking for diamonds,
shouldn't we be in a spooky,
old diamond mine?
You mean instead of a spooky,
old coal mine?
Yeah, but the system told us it came
from this anthracite vein.
It's weird, I know.
Sheriff, look at this.
- That's not coal.
- Raw diamonds.
But they're not natural.
Someone's transforming
the anthracite
into isometric-hexoctahedral
carbon-14.
Someone's cooking logic diamonds.
Watch out.
- I'm okay. It's just my arm.
- What was that? A security system?
No, I'm an idiot.
It's an acoustic wave generator.
They're using intermittent bursts.
We just happened to get caught.
Somebody's growing these diamonds
with rayl pressure waves.
And they're doing it on a massive scale.
Hold on. Rayl waves?
Zoe was studying with one
of those things today at Cafe Diem.
And it could melt metal.
Could it melt rock?
I'm with you, Sheriff.
I'm not.
The diamond oven is shooting waves
into the ground.
And rayl pressure waves can melt
iron ore in the rock strata.
Melted rocks make magma,
and where the magma's under pressure...
There's a volcano.
Yeah.
But who's cooking diamonds?
I talked to Dr. Zedler
at the Pensacola facility.
There are only six people in the world
who know how to make logic diamonds,
- and they're all on his team.
- So they're all 3,000 miles away?
- Yes. Confirmed by DOD security.
- Your people'll turn up something
- from one of the other programs?
- What other programs?
You know. I don't know.
North Korea, China.
Carter, no one else
has a logic diamond program,
not even in the theoretical stages.
- We are 30 years ahead of the world.
- I gotta see your personnel files.
You spent three years in Pensacola
while the neural core
was being designed.
Dr. Zedler said you asked questions
about how to grow logic diamonds,
said you became a real expert.
You spend your entire career
creating something amazing,
and when you finally succeed,
they just lock it all away.
Are there any more diamond farms?
I only grew them because
I didn't want to steal them.
Don't you see?
These diamonds could change the world.
But the DOD wanted them
to make better weapons.
GD is a science facility,
not a weapons factory.
It's a top-secret lab.
I could never test my diamonds.
That's why I put them in the dogs.
To test them?
Those dogs have the most advanced
neural processors around.
Mimicking a biological organism
is the best way
to test the diamonds
under real-world conditions.
I was helping out
a few of the entrants.
I just built the diamonds
into the circuits.
I had no idea they would overload.
Or that you'd caused a volcano?
Pardon?
Even though we've shut down
the generator in the mine,
the seismic activity
is continuing to increase.
That magma's under incredible pressure.
If it blows, Eureka could be
scattered over four states.
There could be thousands of casualties.
- We should begin evacuation.
- No, it could explode at any time.
I don't want people out on the street.
It'll be much safer if they're inside.
Could you drill in
and relieve the pressure?
You know, just lance the puppy.
Well, we have no idea
where this puppy is.
Thermal energy travels along
the rock strata until it finds a pocket.
- Could be anywhere.
- Wait a minute.
What if we cut a tunnel? Get close to
the pocket, bore straight to the lake.
Then use remote explosives
to fracture the containment rock.
- That would divert the magma?
- And we still have to find it.
Well, you guys have got to have a gizmo
in this building that can help.
Right? Start knocking on doors.
Just put a note in the elevator.
Yeah, Carter, there's no gizmo
for sniffing out magma 2,000 feet
below the earth's surface, but
maybe we can get the director on that.
Well, I'm not talking about sniffing...
I got an idea.
Just tell me
if it's incredibly stupid.
Yes.
Is it possible?
This technology can help
soldiers sniff out explosives.
We can fix Fifi to help us.
It's similar technology.
But real dogs can't sniff out magma.
If we reprogrammed her
and jacked up the sensitivity.
That would take weeks.
Well...
With this.
It's Dr. Mendel's artificial mucus.
It could supercharge Fifi's nose.
I think...
Fifi...
was born...
to be a hero.
Heroine.
Don't you?
Smell the lava. Good girl.
Smell the lava.
Oh, good girl!
I hate to interrupt puppy school,
but the seismic pressure is building.
Fifi's almost ready, although
I don't think she's that thrilled
about carrying
live explosives into a volcano.
I know, but you'll need 'em
to release the magma.
Can't we just poke a hole in it,
relieve the pressure?
Sure, if you wanna be
a charcoal briquette.
The magma's 3,000 degrees.
It's gonna break through and fire down
the tunnel to the lake at 80 ft per sec.
You want to be long gone
when that happens.
All right. All right.
Breaking through, bad.
Running away, good.
Fifi. Let's go!
In you go!
All right, Fifi. Ready for this?
Yeah, she's got a new nose.
It's topped off with mucus.
Ready to find
- some lava.
- It's not lava.
Which way, girl?
Here goes nothing.
Nathan, what's the status down there?
I think Carter's dog
has us chasing our tails.
Fifi. Don't make me stop
this tunneler, Fifi!
We have methane vents
popping all over town.
Nice, big ones!
Still nothing.
Wait... Wait,
we might have something.
All right, Fifi.
Come on. Come on!
Let's go find some lava.
Magma.
It's magma.
It's lava when it's above ground,
magma when it's below.
What, you think I'm confusing the dog?
- Well, you're exhausting me.
- We got heat.
All right, let's just set
these explosives right by the melt...
We're not gonna need 'em.
Come here, Fifi. C'mere!
Magma's breaking through... Run!
We should be long gone
when this happens?
Yes, I did! Drive, Carter, drive!
The pressure's dropping.
Did you find something?
Oh, you could say that!
Where's the lake?
I can't get a bearing.
The instruments are all over the place.
- Smack it.
- Seriously?
Smack it.
All right!
I got a bearing.
Turn right 15 degrees.
- Should be straight ahead.
- Should be?
Next time, Fargo's driving.
They made it through.
So what do you want to do tomorrow?
- Vincent, iced coffee, please.
- On the way.
Steamy out there tonight.
Well, get used to it.
That magma's gonna be venting for days.
I think, technically, it's lava.
So you guys did good work today.
You should team up more often.
- Yeah.
I'm thinking this town
should buy you boys a drink.
Well,
you know, it was kind of fun.
And besides almost dying,
I can see why you miss it.
Honestly, I don't.
I like the quiet life.
Living with that kind of pressure
isn't for me anymore.
Hey, Carter.
Good driving today.
Thanks.
I'm the king of the world!
Hey, congratulations,
robot dog show champ.
Thank you, thank you.
I'd like to thank everyone who made
this possible. Mostly, myself.
Yeah, well, nothing like
a gracious winner.
I gotta tell you.
He's absolutely amazing.
Come here, buddy.
Yeah.
It's so...
real.
I thought fake dogs don't...
Yeah, I'll see you later.
That's nice.
Interested in a game?
Nah, I should go home
and change my pants
because Fargo is a cheater.
Sparky?
Well, you know, pressure can be
a very destructive force.
Did... you ever finish
that troubling errand?
I certainly did.
How was Thorne?
You're very perceptive, Jack.
I do know the type,
and they don't do good deeds.
She had me run a...
radiation survey outside of town.
Now, have you ever heard of
baryogenetic radiation?
No.
Well, that's because it doesn't exist.
It's a theory. At least I thought so...
Until today.
- You found some?
- Just...
a trace.
Great, great.
Is it dangerous?
I have data in my garage.
I'll run you through it tomorrow.
- Great. Thanks...
- All right.
Thanks for being on my side with this.
I do not keep secrets from my friends.
Anymore.
Sheriff Carter, you planned
to do aerobic exercise tonight
from 8:00 to 9:30,
followed by bill paying.
- Yeah, I'm taking the night off.
- Good idea.
Stress is America's number one
health problem.
Oh, drop dead.
Followed closely by sarcasm.
Hey!
You want some chips?
I was sit down and watch the game.
No, I had a powerbar at the library.
I'll see ya.
Where you going?
To study.
There's a physics quiz tomorrow and,
I really, really, really
want to get an A.
Okay.
Just... do your best, all right?
Thanks.
You need some help?
Sure. How much you know
about calculating electron mass?
Nothing.
But I do know
that everything's a little easier
if you're having some pizza.
So...
sit down.
Crack the books and I'll order.
Okay.
I'm proud of you.
Extra mushrooms, right?
You know me so well.
Awesome.