Previously on Eureka.
Say hello to your daughter.
Hey, baby.
So, Tess, you think you can
handle this place on your own?
Me?
Don't forget the quarterly reviews
are due this thursday.
So I'll make sure Fargo
has the proper documentation.
With Henry away at NASA, you will be
in charge of the senior staff meeting.
Watch out for Burke,
because if she starts talking...
We'll be ordering dinner in.
I got it.
Good, good.
Don't forget. Make sure that...
Would you trust me?
I know this is kind of my first day,
but I'm thinking
I got everything under control.
Yeah. Okay. I'm sorry.
I really appreciate
you filling in for me at GD.
GD's gonna be fine.
Now, would you go be a mom already?
All right. I can take a hint.
Bye.
Thought you finished your homework.
Yeah, I did.
I'm doing college research.
But... you're a junior.
Which puts me like five years
behind the other kids at Tesla.
- They took the SCAT in grade school.
- The SCAT?
The Student Career Assessment Test.
It's supposed to point us
in the right direction.
I didn't take it till last week.
So, what did it say?
I haven't gotten the results yet.
But after helping Allison with the baby,
I know I just want to be a Doctor.
You did really like that.
I loved it.
I hate the thought of you leaving.
- I'll always be here, Sheriff Carter.
- Yes. Not the same.
Speaking of being alone...
- How are you and Tess doing?
- Good.
Really good.
You know,
if she ever wants to like...
Stay over...
Not having this conversation
with my daughter.
Dad, I'm just saying...
life's short.
Thank God.
You need a hand?
It's not really a two-person job.
You hate this kind of work.
Not today.
Zane's coming home.
He's been gone a long time.
A month.
This is getting serious.
It's been a while.
I mean, there was Callister.
- And, well, he was a...
- A robot.
Then there was Taggart,
and, well, he's...
Taggart.
I mean, I'm not used to the...
Normal relationship thing.
So what about you and Tess?
Have you guys exchanged keys yet?
Why is everybody
asking me that today?
So, what are we doing
on the mountain service road?
I need a straight shot
for some transport headed to GD.
Traffic duty with no traffic.
Feels kind of silly.
Maybe not so silly.
That's a really big truck.
Why the face?
I'm just confronting my future.
You got your test results?
Cool! What did they say?
I'm too afraid to open the email.
Why?
The SCAT is, like, 99.8% accurate.
That's the point. This could tell me
what kind of medicine I'm cut out for.
You know, I was thinking ob-gyn,
but pediatrics could be cool.
This'll help you decide.
Okay. I can't click it.
What?
Robotics engineering?
Look at those data points!
It's a perfect aptitude
match for you.
Very cool.
No, that's not cool.
That's totally not what I want to do.
It's just a stupid test.
Order up.
I've got a welcome home
present for you.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Let's try this again.
I've got a lot of work to do.
Things seem pretty quiet.
Why are you calling me down here?
Things are pretty quiet.
I need you to keep them that way.
- I need your help with some security.
- Security for what?
We got a very special
delivery today.
What exactly is this delivery?
It's about 750,000 years...
Give or take a few millennia.
Pretty impressive, huh?
You need security...
for a giant icicle?
It's an ice core.
The longest one ever recovered.
A GD team just drilled it
out of the Arctic sheet.
You see, snow has been falling
in the arctic for millennia.
And this core
is a record of each year,
layer by layer by layer,
stretching all the way back into time.
And that's valuable why?
Snow traps things as it freezes...
Spores, bits of volcanic ash.
So we can actually see
what the atmosphere looked like
thousands and thousands
of years ago.
Kind of cool
when you think about it.
Not the temperature kind, but the...
- I should go do something.
- Bye, Fargo.
Okay, look.
You see each of these bands?
Each one of them represents
up to 10,000 years.
Like tree rings.
Exactly!
And all of human history...
Takes up about this much
of the core.
Kind of makes you feel insignificant,
doesn't it?
Like we just don't have
as much time as we think we do.
So, uh, we should probably
make the most of it then, huh?
I'd say so.
Maybe dinner at my place...
Just you and me?
Yeah, that sounds...
Oh, no... I can't.
It's my first day covering for Allison.
I have so much to do.
But soon, okay?
Sure, sure.
So this is the first time we've had
an intact core to study in the lab.
Zane developed a nanoparticle
refrigeration system
just to get this thing down here.
That guy is the king of cold.
Tell me about it.
So, security?
The team leader will fill you in
on what he needs.
He should be here any minute.
The Iceman Cometh.
Good day.
Projet-SG (1.00)
Grand to have
the old team back together!
Jo. Good to see ya.
You too.
I'm assuming
you all know each other?
Eureka was my home for a spell.
I did some fine zoological
work in these parts...
And it hasn't been
the same without you.
Where you been?
Ambled from Melbourne to Minsk.
I was doing a polar bear count
when I heard about the ice core project.
Couldn't turn down a chance
to study primordial life, now, could I?
Well, you never know
where a walkabout's gonna lead ya...
Sometimes you end up
right back where you started.
Not so bad, eh?
Morning, Doc.
Your fridge has still got
some temperature fluctuations.
- I'll take a look.
- Aren't you freezing?
- Petrotech.
- Who-tech?
He's wearing petrotech.
It's a reactive thermal barrier.
Best cold weather insulation
in the world.
All of GD is insulated with it,
along with every building in town.
Making cloth out of it is
an incredibly expensive process.
Waste of time.
Men of the Arctic
should respect the Arctic ways.
Everything I'm wearing
I killed and skinned myself!
Right down to my walrus skivvies...
We'll take your word for that.
Not to worry.
Just a bit of international business
that needs attending to.
Our drilling camp
was on Russian ice.
They're sending over
a commissar-type to sign off
before we can start
experimenting on the core.
I'll do it.
Welcome home.
So what's the story
with Jo and Taggart?
They dated for a while.
I know that seems hard to imagine.
Not really.
Attraction's a funny thing.
Excuse me.
Sir, hello.
Welcome.
You are in charge.
Dr. Blake, correct?
No, I'm actually Dr. Fontana.
Dr. Blake is currently on leave.
Substitute.
Wonderful.
But, I see you do not take time
to personally greet out of town guests.
I apologize about that.
Sheriff Carter,
this is Captain Yuri Gregor.
Captain and chief security officer
for northern district.
Good to meet you, Captain.
You have papers.
Yes. Yes, I do.
Just need your John Hancock.
Your signature, sir.
And then you can be on your way,
and we can begin our research.
- We're very eager to start.
- I'm sure.
But this ice is
important piece of history,
so I need to be sure
that she is safe in your care.
Well, Captain, I can assure you
here at Global Dynamics...
I need facts, Doctor,
not your sweet-eyed assurances.
Sheriff, you will verify this list
for security information.
This'll take a while.
It is required before
we turn over this ice to you.
No checklist, no John Woodcock.
Months with no daylight at all.
The only sound is the keening wind
as it scours the ice,
looking to punish a man
for the least mistake.
They say...
the North changes you.
Keeps a part of your soul.
The man who returns...
He's not the man who left.
'Scuse me, mates.
Here you go, kid.
I'll be back in a jiff.
We haven't had yet a chance to talk.
But even when we did, we didn't.
You left town without
even saying good-bye.
Two years ago.
I didn't think you wanted
a good-bye from me.
You and Zane were already
well on your way
to becoming a happy little couple.
I guess we were.
He's... an odd fellow,
if you don't mind me saying.
Moody type.
Chatty at first, but after a while
he turned downright...
icy.
My audience awaits.
It is good to see you again, Jo.
Fargo. Hat.
Now... where were we?
What you just saw...
between Taggart and me...
That wasn't romantic or anything.
Well, you know that, right?
Don't worry about it.
Somebody looks tense.
What's the matter?
Captain Yuri has me going through
Eureka's library of disaster plans.
I mean, tsunami, missile attack.
Genetically modified
super-intelligent ferret infestation.
Cool.
And apparently we have
an emergency pneumatic vacuum
tube communication system.
No, we don't!
I mean, what's it behind
some picture in some wall?
And I mean, look at these plans...
Yeah, but... I mean...
Doesn't actually work, right?
Wait... that's...
that'll be really handy if we ever
need to send anyone a baseball.
You okay?
Zane...
He's just...
He's being so cold.
Think after a couple
of weeks with Taggart...
anyone would need
a little alone time.
Just try to be patient.
Captain Yuri!
Everything you asked for.
I reviewed disaster plans
from 15 years,
and we are prepared
for every possibility.
Could you maybe... a hand...
This is for you.
Oh, this...
This is very excellent.
Thank you. Great.
So... I don't mean to be rude...
Where is my manners?
Please, you must have pastry!
I was down
in your beautiful commissary.
There was such selection!
I overindulge.
That is good.
With all due respect, sir,
a lot of people are eager
to get working on the core,
- so if we could sign?
- Of course.
There's just one more thing
our bureau of standards requires...
Precise measurement
of ice core itself.
I'm sure Taggart's
come up with some sort
of super-accurate
laser measurement thing.
No doubt!
But men like us...
We do not trust
this kind of technology.
- Sure.
- We are, how you say...
old-school.
There's way more ice in here
than there was before.
Now I know
you're around here somewhere.
Can I get some help in here?
I've never experienced
anything like it!
One minute, I was standing there
measuring the density of the core.
The next minute...
it was upon me.
What was?
The ice!
Like some icy anaconda.
Dr. Taggart, the thing is,
ice doesn't really attack.
Maybe it's a malfunction
in the cooling unit.
Well, nanoparticle refrigeration
is an incredibly new technology.
It could be interlopers
of a more mythical nature.
Spirits of the North.
I'm gonna call Zane
about those cooling units.
I'm telling you, Jack.
There are strange things
under the midnight sun!
But before we go looking for yetis,
we're gonna check out
the refrigeration machine
- and the ice itself.
- Right.
Right.
The ice is everywhere.
It's even growing up the walls.
That's weird.
You ever seen ice
with black streaks in it before?
Then again, I've never paid
that much attention to ice before.
I got you a present.
- Robotics kit.
- A college-level robotics kit.
Pretty neat.
Right?
I already told you
I'm not interested in this.
Have you ever even tried robotics?
No. I don't have to. I mean,
I already know what I wanna do,
regardless of what
that dumb test says.
Yeah, this week you do.
I'm just saying...
I just don't want you to miss out on
something that you might really love.
Who else was in here around
the time you found Taggart?
As far as I know, only Zane.
He's the one that designed
this cooling system, right?
I figure one of these things
probably just went haywire.
They're fine.
I checked them. Twice.
Okay. Any ideas?
Whatever happened in here
has nothing to do with my equipment.
Excuse me, but I've got work to do.
Hey, Carter.
Hey, Henry. How's NASA?
- It must have been nice to get out...
- Afternoon.
- How you feeling?
- Tip-top, thank you.
Amazing what the body can achieve
with a couple hours in a hot bath.
Good.
I was worried about you.
More of the same, I guess. But...
About before...
I was wrong...
to leave town...
without saying goodbye.
To leave things between us
unsettled.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
It's important to me
that you and I remain friends.
I wouldn't want to lose you
from my life.
- Hey, look, I gotta go...
- Me neither.
Back on your feet, I see.
And on the case.
I checked out
all the refrigeration units.
Yeah, they're fine.
All operating at 100% capacity.
I don't know
if that's good news or bad.
I did find something interesting
in that bit of ice you gave me.
Those black streaks...
Malformed ice crystals.
Evidence of incredibly fast growth.
Fast enough to grab a man?
Ask me tomorrow.
Wait!
Why tomorrow?
The ice...
is still spreading.
What did the defrost crew do
with all that ice from the core lab?
Section Three refrigerated storage,
waiting for analysis. Why?
Taggart said that the ice isn't normal.
It grows fast.
I don't know the credence you can give
to a guy who wears a beaver on his head.
He's really good at what he does,
and he says that the ice contains...
black maladjusted crystals.
- What does that mean?
- It means that it's spreading.
That's impossible.
It's just regular ice.
Or not.
Oh, my God.
So Dr. Fontana, I have gift.
Scarf for you.
- Cashmere, to keep you warm.
- Thank you.
And for you...
Is beer hat!
Thank you!
Captain, we want to assure you
and your government that we are doing...
everything we can to help.
I have instituted a level four lockdown
to control the spreading of the ice.
We would like to sample the core
to make sure that it wasn't damaged.
So sir, if you could just
sign these papers...
Are you joking me?
I can't sign papers till I've confidence
you can protect core, and right now...
is no confidence.
- Captain...
- I must go.
I have tee time at mini golf.
Somehow, I don't think
he really wants to leave.
One day.
One day, and I've caused an ice age
and started
an international incident.
Yeah, it's like the cold war
all over again.
It's fine.
We'll figure out what's happening.
You promise?
I know just the man for the job.
So... Progress report?
We're not gonna be able to contain it
till we know what's causing it.
Well, considering we've only known
about this for a few hours,
I'd say we're making great strides.
The only thing making strides
is this ice.
If you choose to focus
on the negative...
Oh, there's a positive?
What's the positive?
The elevator shafts
are filling with ice.
I'm using iridium blowtorches
to melt frozen doors
because my scientists
are trapped inside section three,
so I would love to hear
something positive.
Righty-o!
I think we're good.
This ice just grows back
as quickly as we can melt it.
Everyone is working on this.
Everyone is talking with everyone.
But we still can't find an answer.
Maybe the person who's not talking
is the person with the answer.
Artificial intelligence?
Yeah, right.
- Did you check the power converter?
- Yeah, I checked it.
This is why I like people
instead of machines.
People don't have power converters.
Actually,
the human digestive system of...
Forget it.
Why do you care about this so much?
I think you could really
enjoy robotics, that's all.
Well, it's been a ton of fun so far.
And there are some amazing
college programs around.
Like MIT?
They have one of the best
robotics programs in the country, so...
Yeah, they do.
And they don't have
a medical school.
- We could go together.
- That's not the reason.
That's not the only reason.
I really think
you could be great at this.
The test is right, like,
99.8% of the time. Remember?
Okay. I'll just check
the converter again.
- Can we ask you a few questions?
- I'm kind of busy.
We need to know
what you figured out about the ice.
Nothing.
I thought Taggart was working on it.
Well, everyone's working on it.
We don't seem to be getting anywhere.
And you don't seem to be
as worried as everyone else.
It's not my problem.
I'm concerned with maintaining
the integrity of the core
through temperature control.
- So far so good.
- Have you seen the rotunda?
And again, that doesn't affect
my responsibilities.
What the hell is going on?
You go away for a month,
and you come back acting like the thing.
What's going on with you?
I'm fine.
He's not fine.
That's not him.
He's different.
Something's going on.
Look at the coffee.
- I don't care about...
- It's frozen solid!
He's so cold.
How is he?
Not bad.
Considering we literally found
ice crystals growing inside of him.
Is he gonna make it?
We were able to melt the ice deposits
using an ultrasonic patch.
But if it's anything like the ice
that's been around GD...
It's gonna grow back
as quick as you can melt it.
Well, the patch will help him
for a little while.
But then...
Could it be the ice
that was making him act so strangely?
Yeah, we think so.
The black crystalline structure
is present throughout his body,
including tiny concentrations
in the limbic area of his brain
which controls emotions.
This ice is all over GD.
If it can infect people...
No, it isn't contagious.
We've already done preliminary scans.
Okay, so why Zane?
Honestly, Jack, I have no idea.
I've got teams tearing apart
those refrigeration units.
The answer has got to be somewhere
in those nanoparticle drivers.
Maybe not.
What?
What if it's what's in
the refrigerator?
The core?
- There you are, you little bugger!
- You found something?
- Dikarya basidiomycota.
- Di-di-what?
Fungi.
Looks like we dug up
a little stone age hitchhiker.
Basidiomycota couldn't spread
like this on its own.
Something must be affecting it.
Agreed.
I'll drill out a little sample.
I'm sorry. I cannot allow this.
'cause the ice
is still Russian territory.
No, captain, we have to analyze
this organism, please.
I'm not satisfied with your procedures.
I could not possibly sign paper yet.
I mean, this place is like madhouse.
Stop pretending this is about security.
It's about shopping.
What? Is crazy person!
The captain is an important man.
He's in charge of the Northern district.
- He didn't come here to shop, Jack.
- But if you sign, you're headed home.
No scarves, no beer hats,
no fancy pastries.
Nothing.
Do you know
what Northern district is?
Nothing but ice, snow,
and more ice, for miles!
Our one town
is tiny research station.
Do you have any idea
what it's like to be security officer
in town full of crazy scientists?
Actually...
I do.
We need that signature or the whole
West coast is gonna be covered in ice.
Of course, I sign papers.
Great. Let's get a piece
of this ice into the lab right now.
On it.
Why is it that every guy I date
ends up in this infirmary?
'Cause you're bad luck, obviously.
A joke at my expense.
Glad to have you back.
About that, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I should never have
suspected you of...
Suspected me?
Of what?
Taggart got frozen, and I...
And he and I used to...
Well, you know...
Really?
You thought I loved you that much.
You know, after the way I acted,
I would have suspected me too.
So, what's the prognosis?
You're gonna be fine.
As soon as they figure out
why ice with black lines in it
is growing all over GD
and inside of you.
Black lines.
You mean striations.
Yeah, I guess.
I came across something about that,
during research for my cooling units.
- Is Taggart working in the core lab?
- Yeah, but...
- I need to help him.
- No!
You need to stay here
and get better.
Jo, I'm not going to get better.
Not unless I help that crazy australian
find out what's happening around here.
It's my only chance.
Have you seen my pants?
- I thought maybe you could use a hand.
- That I could.
You up to it?
So use me while you can.
How's it going?
That good, huh?
What's that?
It's her first day.
Trying to keep her
in a positive frame of mind.
- That's nice of you. Is it working?
- Yeah. I think so.
- We are so screwed.
- Come on.
You got two of the greatest minds at GD
working on it.
One of whom is about to become an ice
sculpture if we don't figure this out.
We still don't know why Zane
was affected but Taggart wasn't.
Jack, we're nowhere.
Did you think the job
was gonna be easy?
You got a chill?
We can't have you freezing to death
before we come up with a way
to prevent you from freezing to death,
can we, mate?
- Chivalry isn't dead.
- Yeah, but the coat is.
Guess petrotech isn't as great
as everyone thinks.
No, that's just the ice crystals.
It's making him cold
from the inside out.
Even petrotech can't keep him warm.
Wait.
The difference between
Zane and Taggart...
is the petrotech.
You nailed it.
The regenerative insulation in petrotech
is like the sheaths
around the fungus spores.
The petrotech is like a fertilizer,
and the fungus is, well, like a fungus.
Well, the ice is using the petrotech
as a base to spread everywhere...
It's started to compromise
the integrity of the building.
- Good news, then, right?
- Good news?
The building is about to fall down.
I broke a building!
But the ice doesn't have
anyplace left to go.
We got this polar bear cornered.
- Maybe not.
- Maybe not what?
Fargo said the entire town
was made of petrotech.
It's bonded into the walls,
the windows,
even in the roads
to keep them from icing over.
Roads?
I don't like the sound of that.
Dad, something weird
is happening here.
We can't get out.
And it's freezing.
We're in trouble.
How are you feeling?
Ever heard of brain freeze?
Try that times about a thousand.
Good and bad news.
We've isolated the fungus
and figured out a way to kill it.
But the bad news is the bug is showing
the first signs of mutation.
It's a natural process,
but we let it get a few more generations
down the road,
and our fix won't work.
That mutation means an unstoppable
worldwide ice age in a matter of days.
We're gonna stop this bug now.
The modified fungicide
might kill it.
It's getting at it that's the problem.
We can't spray it from the air.
The fix needs to literally
get inside every wall in town.
Now you know why I had you
looking at emergency plans.
Was there not one for this?
Will the emergency communication system
be able to reach everyone?
According to this, the network leads
from here to every building in town.
The tubes go into the walls
where the petrotech is, right?
We create a aerosol version
of the fungicide
and pump the cure all over GD
and then the town.
- You're a genius.
- Well, not so much.
We'll need to build a pump
with exactly the right kind of pressure.
Yeah, before the building falls.
I'll run an algorithm to figure out
how to disperse the fungicide.
I'll go to Cafe Diem.
The roads are all iced over.
You'll never make it.
I might be able
to lend a hand with that.
Just like old times, hey?
I hate old times!
Damn it!
Why did I waste my butane
on creme brulée?
Zoe, can you see if there's
any more cartridges in the back, please?
Sure.
We're gonna be okay.
Vincent will get us out.
No, he won't.
The ice is growing faster
than he can cut through it.
Your dad is coming, right?
The temperature's dropping 15 degrees
every ten minutes.
I mean, we'll freeze to death
before anyone gets here.
Death?
Death!
GD wasn't built for this.
I hate to be Chicken Little,
but the sky might actually fall in here.
Start a backup.
Open up the vents on system branch B.
- How many buildings in town is that?
- Maybe half.
We're getting there.
Iridium laser blowtorch.
A man's best friend.
Crikey!
Must be 30 below in here.
Where is everybody?
Think they found a way out?
Maybe they found themselves a toasty
corner to wait for the cavalry, huh?
Toasty corner...
Dad!
You okay?
Staying warm in the walk-in fridge.
Downright brilliant!
It was Zoe's idea.
- Everyone else was freaking out.
- That's my girl.
Yeah, frozen girl. Hugs.
Wait, wait.
What is that noise?
Sounds like a gas leak.
Vince, where's your emergency pneumatic
vacuum tube communication system thingy?
There's a wall panel,
but it's frozen.
It's just over here.
Right there.
It's working.
Get along, you fungi!
So glad you're feeling better.
Your hands are still freezing.
I ordered you a soup and a hot tea.
I really missed you.
Looks like things have warmed up
around here.
I'm sorry for the way
I was acting the last few weeks.
No worries.
You weren't yourself, that's all.
Yeah, well, thanks
for bringing me back.
My pleasure, mate.
Worth it to see this one
smiling again.
Ready to get back to work?
We've only got a few centuries
of history to defrost and study.
What do you say, mate?
You'll have to get started
without me.
I think I owe someone
a proper hello.
You got it to work!
A little solder here,
some logic circuit rewiring there.
You're right.
I do have a knack for this.
Forget it.
You're going to med school.
That's what you thought you should do
before I gave you stupid advice.
I mean,
that was just my gut feeling.
- I didn't think...
- Like getting in a fridge to stay warm?
Your gut feeling saved everyone
in this place, including me.
- What about the test?
- Forget the test.
I'm even gonna help Dr. Deacon
with a space data project
that isn't about physics.
So I guess
the test isn't so accurate.
Sure it is, but...
I've always known you were different
than 99.8% of everyone anyway.
That was delicious.
- Thank you.
SARAH, you can take the night off.
Would you like to hear my selection
of after-dinner cordials?
No, thank you. We're good.
So, good night.
Sorry.
I should go.
- I still have a lot of work to do.
- Sure.
Was that okay?
Did you like everything?
I'm good. Thank you.
But let's do this again soon,
you know, when things get
a little less crazy.
Not looking. Not looking.
Just passing through.
- Where you going?
- Pilar's.
- I'll be back tomorrow.
- Zoe, you don't have to leave.
You two kids have fun.
I guess you have
to get back to work.
I probably should.
Or work can wait till tomorrow.