Previously on Eureka...
It's your anniversary.
One year in Eureka.
- Thanks, Callie.
- I can't remember the last time that
I had a good date.
- I'm waiting for somebody.
- Who's the lucky lady?
Henry, you said something the other day
when you weren't yourself.
Something about Kim.
And what Beverly did to her.
I wasn't myself.
Kevin?
He controls the field now, Allie.
He's evolving.
Henry, you said you had a proof
that someone sabotaged
- the experiment that killed Kim?
- No, I said that I'd found
something that proved
you weren't responsible.
It's hot today, huh?
You're looking pretty hot
in that uniform.
Very hot.
Excuse me?
Well, I'm just saying,
if you want to get comfortable,
you could...
take something off.
It's fine.
We're alone.
All...
alone.
Come on, Jo.
I'm sorry. "All alone."
No, forget it.
Forget it. This is ridiculous.
Sexual harassment is anything
but ridiculous, Sheriff.
Gender dynamics are something
every organization has to contend with.
Now, I appreciate your kind attention.
Let's thank our role players, shall we?
Especially Sheriff Carter for offering
such a despicable example.
No problem. Thank you.
If you excuse us,
we have to head back to work.
Thank you, Dr. Young,
for a very informative presentation.
Well, if I can spare at least one person
the humiliation of sexual harassment,
then I've done my job.
I think I'm with Sheriff Grabass.
Seems to be a ridiculous waste of time.
Nathan, as long as Global
is funding your research,
you have to follow the same
rules as everyone else.
And that attitude is precisely why
this traing is so necessary, Dr. Stark.
You people think a high IQ
means you can just forget
3.7 billion years of evolution,
but you're wrong.
We are apes.
Male apes are driven to reproduce
with as many partners as possible,
and female apes will use any means
to possess the male as her protector.
These are unequivocal,
biological truths.
I believe the people of Eureka are
a little more evolved than that,
which is why we've never had
a sexual harassment case
in the history of the town.
Well, we've been very fortunate.
You've been lulled into complacency.
There are huge pressures under
the surface, and one day, they'll erupt.
And woe be unto you when that happens.
Woe be unto me?
Well, we have to admire her commitment.
Speaking of which, I'm gonna
get back to our little project. It's...
it's going quite well.
- I'll check in with you later.
- All right.
- Hey, got a minute?
- Sure.
You look hot in that uniform.
Thanks. I am hot, actually.
What's up with the A/C?
- It's not working.
- Yeah.
Actually, you know what?
I could use you.
I don't know. I'm not a piece of meat.
I've got feelings, emotions, needs.
Yeah. Our biology systems
engineer Dr. Stone
has not been answering my pages,
and I'm getting worried about him.
He designed Eureka's air conditioning
system, and he does all the repairs.
What does a biologist
have to do with the A/C?
Well, the rest of the world
has "room conditioning."
Eureka has "air conditioning".
The cooling unit is part of
an integrated, underground system.
You know, water, gas,
waste... It's all recycled.
It's a biological model based on
the human digestive system.
So it's a billion degrees
out there because...
- the town has blockage?
- Kind of.
Dr. Stone has been overhauling
older parts of the system,
but he's behind on upgrading
the new schematics.
Henry's down in the tunnels,
trying to figure it out.
Henry will fix it.
It's not that easy.
The systems work in equilibrium.
With the cooling systems down,
we have water leakage,
- methane buildup in the sewers.
- All right. I'll find Dr. Stone.
There's something else
I need to talk to you about.
I need...
files from the explosion
that killed Kim Anderson.
Why?
To find out what happened.
I don't think that Henry's been
completely honest with me.
We know what happened.
It was an accident.
It looked like an accident, yeah,
but it's been implied that...
Beverly's involved.
I just want to be sure.
I know you do too.
Well, the... the files are classified,
- but I'll get you what I can.
- Thanks.
And, Carter, if you find anything,
will you let me know, please?
Of course, yeah.
Thanks.
Stone? Don't believe I know him.
Yeah... he keeps the place cool
and keeps the toilets running.
Works in the tunnels.
Oh, him.
The mole.
- Strange fellow.
- Yeah.
When was the last time you saw him?
Tuesday. The A/C was a bit hinkey.
He put in some priority cooling ducts
for Fred and Wilma to keep them comfy.
Beautiful dogs.
Just... Aren't ya? Huh?
Hi, buddy. Yes, you are.
They're not dogs.
Canis lupus albus.
Hybrid Siberian tundra wolves.
Yeah, nice...
Tundra wolves.
- What was the shot for?
- A hormone cocktail.
Trying to encourage
a little lupine l'amour.
I gave fred every combination of
cloned linoleic pheromone in the book.
Nary a nuzzle.
Well, if all else fails,
there is Barry White.
Would you like some sugar, Sheriff?
No, no. I'm good, thanks.
Has your husband disappeared before?
Into his work.
Some men play golf,
some collect egg cups.
My man loves his tunnels.
Egg cups?
And you think
that he's down there somewhere?
I'm sure of it.
He probably just lost track of the time.
He can be down there
for days on end sometimes,
and I don't hear a peep out of him.
Has to be tough on a marriage.
Bob says marriage is like a
palladium-lined
geothermal heating system.
Beautiful
and complicated.
You just never know when the pressure
is gonna rip the whole thing apart.
Bob sounds very romantic.
Callie called.
Thanks.
Hey, you got... I left...
- From Zane.
- Yeah.
You gonna call her?
Yeah.
You call Zane?
No, not yet.
It's hard to dive back in.
Tell me about it.
I feel like such a guy.
Me too.
I was just down this way,
so I thought I'd bring you this.
Thanks.
I'm gonna go... freshen up.
You two kids excuse me.
So...
good day?
Average, strange.
So...
What are you up to this weekend?
Climb into my freezer,
try to get away from the heat.
Well, I was thinking,
my uncle has this great cabin
on the Payette River.
Cool breezes,
warm fire.
What do you think?
Cabin, breeze, and fire.
- It sounds like--
- She's gonna blow!
What did you eat?
The Projet-SG Team
presents:
Timing: Golgi,
Linwelin, Moochie, Ricana.
Transcript: swsub.com
Edition: Golgi,
Linwelin, Moochie, Ricana.
Proofreading: Golgi, Linwelin.
- Season 2 | Episode 11 -
Maneater (v. 1.0)
Methane backed up in the waste matrix.
Must have found an ignition source.
Well, I think Jo was
laser-plucking her eyebrows.
- That'll do it.
- Yeah. What's the smell?
Which one...
The sulfur dust or the phosphorus
that's coming off of the sewage biofilm?
This is no place for anybody
with a respiratory disease.
Welcome to the bowels of Eureka.
You guys should give out hats.
Hey, do I need to give out
a toilet alert?
No, not yet.
I've got a couple of teams
from hydrogeology
cutting vent holes in the surface.
That'll relieve the gas
and buy us some time.
Okay. How long do you think
it'll take to fix?
Not a clue. I mean,
we're missing tons of data.
Good, look. It's done.
All right, so these are
the water treatment pools.
This is the main vibrator to create
an inertial wave so the water flows up
instead of down, and...
That is where we are.
Keep your eyes open.
Stone's wife said that he was
probably still down here somewhere.
I'll do the best I can.
Just tell Jo to lay off the laser
in the lavatory for a while, because...
it's probably gonna get worse
before it gets better.
All right.
Left then right, then left.
Hey, Zane.
- I haven't done anything.
- No, well, the day's young.
Vince, could I get
a burger, please, rare.
I have a great special today.
Serbian cevacice.
Lamb patty, garlic, paprika.
A little hunk of Balkan heaven.
Yeah, it's pretty awesome.
You should try it.
That sounds great. All right.
I'll have the burger, please, rare.
With some ketchup.
I freaked you out, didn't I?
A little. Yeah.
But, I mean, you got to admit,
having Jo explode a toilet
was a pretty good diversion.
Look...
this whole dating thing...
- Uncharted waters.
- Yeah.
Judy, your order's almost ready.
Listen, I think the important thing
is that we just
keep talking.
An open exchange of information.
- That sounds great.
- Sheriff, hello.
This is a pleasure.
So when you coming
back out to the house?
Callie, I gotta go.
Could we
exchange some information later?
Sure.
All right... I'll call you. Bye.
Sorry. This have something
to do with your husband?
Oh, poo.
We talked about Bob all morning.
I wanna talk about you.
I wanna know what is
going on in here.
Here you go.
And I just want to say thank you.
It's adventurous customers like you
who make what I do worthwhile.
That's me. Adventurous.
Up for anything.
I'll see you soon...
The heat's getting to people.
Vince, you know her husband, right?
Dr. Stone?
The mole? Yeah.
A weird guy, but a loyal customer.
I hate this heat.
I'm loving it.
Can I buy you some ice cream, beautiful?
I don't think so.
Haven't seen you for a while.
What are you talking about?
You and me.
Our partnership.
What?
Get everybody out of there now!
Hey, Henry, I'm at lunch.
I know where you are!
There's an inertia wave propagating
into the vent line of the pizza oven!
Get everybody out of there now!
- What's up?
- We gotta clear this place out.
Everybody, grab your things and
head to the door as quickly as possible,
that would be great.
Go.
Everybody. Yeah, that's... And you.
Come on.
Yeah...
That's great. Quick as you can.
That would be fantastic.
- Vince, you too. Go.
- What's going on?
Henry said that there's
an inertia thing coming.
- An inertia wave?
- Yeah.
Is that bad?
Yeah, it's bad.
Hey, Jo, you still with me?
Hey, you okay?
You...
I'm good.
Are you hurt?
- Carter, listen...
- Forget it.
It was an "in the moment" thing.
Good, okay...
Are we still in the moment?
Because I'd really like to do it again.
We're gonna lie you down.
Yeah, let's lie down.
Okay. Zane, could you take her to
the sheriff's office
and just put her on the cot?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
You're gonna be good.
It's hour 4, and the female
is definitely showing
more interest in the male.
We've had a bit of nuzzling,
some tail whipping.
Seems like love is finally in the air.
I'm gonna head back to work.
I've got a point particle scan
that'll crap out if I don't tweak it.
So...
you've felt this way
about Carter for a long time?
Yeah.
No...
I don't know.
It sure sounded like it.
- I guess so.
- Okay, then.
Hope that works out.
Do me a favor and
don't invite me to the wedding.
I'm really confused.
I'm not.
Could have been the reed valve,
or the magnetic diaphragm
might have failed. Or...
Okay. We're gonna need a few
nano-sutures. I'll be right back.
Honestly, I am not sure
what happened down there.
Well, you're hurt. You can't go
poking around down there.
That wave nearly blew Cafe Diem apart.
We have to find someone
who can solve it now.
Still don't know what happened to Stone.
When the valve kicked, I saw a lunch box
so he could still be down there.
Okay, hold on.
- Hey, Carter.
- First off,
I was totally insane before.
For the record, I do not now,
nor have I ever wanted to jump you.
- You believe me, right?
- Well, I don't know.
I mean, maybe you just
got tired of staring
at Lake Carter,
and you had to take a dip.
Okay, you're making me nauseous.
Probably from your head.
Might want to get that checked out.
Later. We've got bigger
problems to deal with first.
Like what?
Like old faithful in our backyard.
Eureka lost bladder control.
Shooting out of main street.
It's probably the pressure
from the ion purification pools.
You see, you plug up
one hole and then, bam!
- Another one bursts someplace else.
- Can we stop it?
I don't know, maybe, but,
the sewage system's gonna get backed up.
Awesome.
GD has nine departments working on this.
Geomorphology is tracking
the pressure pockets in the bedrock.
Cartography is trying
to extrapolate maps from
Stone's incomplete data.
It is nuts!
Where did you see his lunchbox?
I have to get back upstairs.
We have super-pressurized water
venting on the main street.
Just tell me what he said.
He wants to look into what happened.
He's not gonna let this go.
Carter is following a road
that goes right through Henry
and leads right to Kevin.
Maybe we have to trust Carter,
bring him into the loop now.
It isn't about trusting Carter, Allie.
This is about the DOD.
Look, I know you work for them,
but you don't know them
the way that I do.
If they get a hold of Kevin,
he will never have a normal life.
They will quarantine him and study him
until they have the answers they want,
and I'm not letting that happen to him.
But we have to get
that thing out of him.
We will.
But I need access.
Kim's lab, the data,
everything we know about the artifact
and I had when I was the head of GD.
The DOD will never
give you that clearance.
Who's asking?
Left, left, right.
You gotta be kidding.
At least you're still here.
Where are you?
Yeah?
Hey, you sound annoyed.
I what?!
Whatcha doin'?
Long, weird story.
Okay.
Hey, what do you say we rewind?
Just go back to the "great first date"
honeymoon period.
Holy crap.
Callie, I'm sorry,
I'm gonna have to call you back.
What were you doing down here?
- Bones?
- Yeah,
and they're human.
We don't know how old,
but Taggart's taking a look.
So your theory is,
Dr Stone is Hannibal Lecter?
- Yeah.
- Dr. Blake, sorry to interrupt,
but I need you to sign off
on the seminar attendance sheets.
Carter, the man we're talking about
is a Nobel laureate in biochemistry.
Yeah, and maybe a psychopath, so...
like you, but violent.
- Give me time.
- You gotta admit, it's a little weird.
- Oh, sorry. Do you need something?
- No, I'm good.
I just love the way
your lips move when you talk.
Excuse me?
Dr. Blake, that is a wildly
inappropriate comment.
- Yeah.
- Not to mention bizarre.
Go ahead, say something else.
- What?
- Or don't.
- Yeah.
- Talk is cheap.
I've been wanting to do that all day.
Well, do it again,
and I will beat you down.
All right. Easy, easy, easy. A little...
A little help?
A little... Okay. Okay... No, no, no.
Just...
So ladies, how are we feeling?
- Humiliated.
- My head is much clearer now.
When he was in here, I couldn't think.
I just wanted him.
It was horrible.
I can only imagine.
You done yet?
No, I'm not kidding, Carter.
It was frightening.
I was out of control.
Yeah, it's been happening all day.
Jo kissed me,
but I didn't put it together.
Deputy Lupo kissed you, and you didn't
think there was anything wrong?
Well, I've been working out.
I'm looking pretty good.
Dr. Young, this is
supposedly your field.
- Do you have any thoughts?
- Yeah, sure,
my thoughts are, my reputation's
destroyed, 'cause I frenched the sheriff
- in front of my boss.
- Anne, it's okay. Just
- get yourself under control.
- Of course.
The biochemistry of human sexual
attraction isn't well understood.
It could be a glandular disorder,
an enzyme overgrowth,
a fungal infection even.
You know what, we need to draw blood.
And you need to stay in the infirmary.
Well, I can't sit still.
I mean, I got toilets exploding
and geysers shooting out of the street.
I think Eureka's got bigger problems
at the moment than me.
I can't have you
running around out there.
You're too irresistible.
I thought I was gonna tear you apart.
Good point.
All right, but until we figure this out,
let's just keep it quiet.
Keep your distance, ma'am.
Step away from the sheriff.
You keep your hands
where I can see them.
Hot lunch coming through.
Hey, do not pierce the bubble.
You, back that way.
Hey, back in the elevator.
15 feet, Missy.
- All right, come on, it's clear.
- Very subtle, Fargo.
Thank you.
So Stone uncovered 9,000-year-old bones?
There were early human settlements
all through this area.
And these were particularly
violent buggers.
Well, that looks like a head wound.
Good eye.
Fractures and weapon marks
all over these bones.
I'd say they had a bit of a dust-up.
- And then killed each other.
- Oh, your dogs are wrestling.
That's not wrestling, Fargo.
Isn't it beautiful?
They've been at it all day.
Gonna have to re-jigger
the formula bit though.
Fred's gonna be naked.
Made him a wee bit too irresistible.
- Wait, you did what?
- Can I get some of that?
Sorry, Romeo.
Canines and humans do have
a similar hormone chemistry,
- but it wouldn't work.
- Are you sure?
I asked first.
Besides, you got all you can handle.
Exactly, Taggart, I think somehow
your pheromones got transferred to me.
I've been accosted
ever since I touched Fred.
Fascinating. If I touched Fred...
Wait, wait,
I touched Fred lots of times.
I haven't noticed any extra...
Charisma.
Well, how would you know?
You work down here alone.
How many women have even been down here?
We gotta test your mojo.
Not sure I'm entirely
comfortable with this.
That makes two of us.
Okay, release the hounds.
Go ahead, ladies. Don't be shy.
Feel free to touch.
G'day.
You in the gray skirt.
How do you feel?
Intensely uncomfortable.
Wasn't this covered in the seminar?
Twenty different women,
they had absolutely no interest in him.
What's this stuff you found in my blood?
It's androstadiene.
It's one of the hormones involved
with sexual attraction.
According to the blood tests,
your eccrine gland is producing
more than 379 parts per milliliter.
Okay. Is that a lot?
That's 15,000 times more
than the usual amount.
I take that as a "yes."
A woman exposed to such
high levels of androstadiene
could experience delusions,
erotomania, violence.
It could overload the female brain.
And how much is Taggart making?
- Oh, he's normal.
- But, and this is weird,
the male wolf's levels are sky high.
Something over-stimulated
his eccrine gland as well.
So why is this potion
affecting us differently?
Well, because it's not
the pheromone serum, Sheriff.
Taggart's cocktail affects a different
peptide chain. It can't be causing this.
Great. Okay...
And I still haven't found the guy who
can stop the town from exploding, great.
Please keep me posted if you find out
I have anything else
in common with the wolf.
And...
get a bullhorn.
Carter, Dr. Young is gonna need
to take some more samples
from you before you leave.
Okay, take as much blood as you want,
but let's do this as fast as we can.
Actually, I need a sample
of something else.
Need a magazine?
Just a few more minutes, everybody.
Please, please, be patient.
I just need to talk
to Carter for a second.
Sorry, no can do.
He's off-limits to the ladies
until further notice.
He's been getting
way too much action lately.
Okay, well, just tell him
that I came by.
Yeah, okay, I'll put you on the list.
Everybody, just stand back
a little while longer.
French ham with tarragon mustard.
Now can I please have
my female customers back?
Yeah, just trying
to figure out a timeline here.
Do you remember the last time Dr. Stone
came in here to pick up his lunch?
Yeah, he comes in every day.
Until today, that is.
Too bad too.
Cevacice burgers are his favorite.
Unlike some other culinary
philistines I won't name.
Wait... today?
Did Mrs. Stone pick up cevacice burgers?
Two orders.
Thanks.
Wait.
All right, we're clean.
Fantastic.
- I'd feel better if I was packing heat.
- I'm not giving you a gun, Fargo.
What if some woman attacks?
They're like ninjas.
It's a low charge perimeter fencing.
I can shut it down. I just need 3.7 MW
of power, a couple of platinum rods...
Or, yeah, okay. You just do that.
Champagne, chocolates...
- Someone's been getting busy.
- Honey, did you find it?
Dr. Stone.
Sheriff.
I'm... I'm...
I'm guessing you didn't find
the massage oil.
The system is going haywire.
But the cooling system was fine!
You didn't notice how hot it was?
Sure, but Judy just said
she was keeping it warm
because it was sultry,
like, cat on a hot tin roof.
I may regret this, but,
you wanna tell me
what happened with you and Judy?
We were eating dinner, and Judy
looked at me over the tuna casserole.
I hadn't seen that look in 15 years.
We were like newlyweds again,
you've... no idea what it was like.
Actually, yeah, I think he does.
You and Judy?
No!
I mean, yes. But...
No. I...
I can't even walk down the street.
It has something to do with...
a gland producing too much of something.
Okay, so...
what happened with Judy and me,
it... It wasn't real then?
It had a little help.
I just thought
it was the old spark coming back.
You didn't think it was a little extreme
when your wife imprisoned you
in your bedroom?
I... I guess I just wanted to believe
that she loved me that much.
I'm sorry things got so out of control.
There's a substation monitor
on main across from Watson and Crick.
- Let me get a system update.
- All right, let me give you a lift.
And how are my little lovebirds doing?
- Oh, yipes.
- What "yipes"?
The stirling cryocooler is down to
162 kelvin. You know what that means.
It's gonna get hot.
It's already over 100.
No, I mean, it's gonna get hot.
If I don't reroute some coolant pronto,
this is gonna feel like a snow day.
Get out of sight now.
Some place safe.
What's going on?
Whatever's happening,
it's getting violent.
Sheriff...
Wilma...
ate Fred.
Sheriff.
Thanks.
Come on, we're leaving.
Shotgun!
Back away from the vehicle.
They're not backing away
from the vehicle.
Happy place.
You're a great bodyguard, Fargo.
I rerouted the liquid nitro.
But I don't think the pipes
can hold the pressure much longer.
There's a lot of
particulate matter in the air.
Don't you want a mask?
Oh, no, thanks.
Love this smell.
Just gotta know how to talk to 'em.
Sorry about Fred.
He died for love.
There are worse ways to go.
Yeah.
Yeah, there are.
Look...
Dr. Stone and I are affected as well.
The only thing that we have
in common are... your... wolves.
I know it's tenuous,
but I didn't have anywhere else to go.
Where's Wilma?
I had the vet tech take her for a walk.
Not healthy for her to sit around
after such a big meal.
Sorry.
Taggart, what is this stuff?
Animal cage, lots of dust and dirt.
I think I've seen this somewhere before.
- Where?
- Down in one of the tunnels.
There were mineral deposits
and stuff all through the rocks.
The dust was everywhere.
I don't see how a mineral
could have this effect.
- Well...
- 'Cause it's not a mineral.
It's a pre-mitotic haploid.
Better known as your basic spore.
Hardy little biological
bugger too.
Just napping until
the right host came along.
That would be Dr. Stone and then me.
We were both down in that chamber.
I gave it a quick how-do-you-do.
Mostly hydrocarbons.
Some trace aminos.
And you ready?
Thymosin.
That's a peptide.
Could that mess with my eccrine gland?
In large concentrations, definitely.
Carter, you and Stone were down there.
How did the wolves get exposed?
Well, because they're Siberian wolves.
Yeah, tundra. Siberian tundra wolves.
Stone patched an emergency vent to
keep them cool if the system shuts down.
They must have found a way to that vent.
Probably down there
for thousands of years just waiting.
Yeah, but could they still really be
viable after all that time?
Anthrax spores can survive
in the soil for centuries.
When they're uncovered,
they're as deadly.
Looks like this one's deadly too.
It might explain what happened
to our prehistoric friends.
Taggart could you bring
those samples to my lab?
- Good job, Carter.
- Thanks.
- I'll work to counteract the effects.
- Thank you.
You feel that?
- Oh, my god.
- What?
He fixed the air conditioning.
Spores are gonna spread.
Getting all this?
Spore concentration looks pretty bad.
Yeah, just drive to the next waypoint
and take the next reading, all right?
All right.
- How bad is it?
- Well,
according to Fargo's measurements,
it's all over town.
Great. How's Dr. Young
coming on her antidote?
She'll have enough serum for you
and Dr. Stone by the end of the day.
Well, that's great, but we need some
for every male in town.
Well, it's gonna take some time
to grow the cultures.
A couple days.
Days?!
We'll have ripped
each other apart by then.
I think that we're gonna
have to consider evacuation.
All female residents can be transported
to Ellsworth Air Force Base
until we can produce
a viable counteragent.
Wait...
How do you feel about Henry?
- What?
- He's my friend?
You were in the tunnels before.
How come she's not all over you?
My mask, my dust filter.
- No, you weren't wearing a mask.
- No, I was. You couldn't see it.
- An electrostatic filter.
- What does it do?
I have asthma. This is a casein-based
suspension that coats foreigns particle.
Okay... No, what does it do?
It binds with the spores,
it makes it impossible
for them to be absorbed into the body.
How much of this stuff can we make?
The production isn't the problem.
It's the distribution.
We can't get a spray bottle
into every man's hand.
Not before they breathe in
enough spores to be affected like you.
What if we spray it everywhere?
Use crop dusters, helicopters...
- Will that clean the spores?
- Yes, if they breathe it in,
but we can't use helicopters because
in order to get it into every lung,
we have to get it into every building.
Well, you know what?
This town needs an enema.
I'm on it.
So we're gonna pump asthma medicine
through Eureka's cooling system?
Yeah, and it'll neutralize the spores.
This one? This goes everywhere?
You pump it, it'll wash out the system.
But look, I don't like this.
I just got her all healthy again.
It's the only way to make sure
the electrostatic filter's distributed.
- It feels like a violation, you know?
- Don't worry, we'll be gentle.
Make sure the seal is good.
We have enough for one time.
Let me know when you're ready.
Okay. Let it go.
I'm at the perimeter.
If the spore count goes down here,
Eureka is safe.
Six parts per million.
Still steady.
Stone, how's it going down there?
- We have critical pressure.
- Jack, it's leaking.
The valve software
isn't calculating the volume.
Not looking good. Numbers are climbing.
6.1 parts per million.
Stone, grab the other wrench.
We'll see if we can stop this thing.
Wow, this is fun.
Pressure's rising. Hang in there, guys.
You're containing the leak.
Okay, it's working.
Come on.
There it goes. Pressure's moving
through the cooling system.
Come on.
Still steady. No change.
Steady.
Wait, wait, 5.8.
5.3. Still dropping.
It's getting there.
3.4. 3.3 parts per million.
It's working. You did it.
Carter, we almost had a town full of men
just as attractive as you are.
You sure this is gonna reach everyone?
Well, the flow
distribution grid is solid.
Anyone who's breathing should be safe.
- Who wouldn't be breathing?
- 2.1 parts per million.
- Fargo, take it off.
- What?
You know what. Take it off.
You know, some of us
still believe in love.
- Hey.
- Hello, Henry.
The air conditioning's fixed,
but my thumb pad is broken.
This place is falling apart.
Can you let me in?
I'm sorry, Henry, I can't.
Of course you can,
just use your override.
It isn't broken.
I'm shutting down all research
into the artifact and the accident.
You'll be getting a new lab space.
What are you talking about?
Just what I said.
I think that it's time for you
to start moving on to other projects.
What?
Why are you doing this to me?
I have to.
I'm sorry, Henry.
You're dripping all over my floor.
"Hello" usually comes first.
Wipe your feet.
Where's your boyfriend?
What? Sounded like true love.
No, it sounded like temporary insanity.
Okay, so how you feeling now?
All your neurons firing again?
Well, I'm fine.
Did you need something?
Yeah.
I just wanted you to know
I didn't like that.
Seeing you kiss Carter,
I didn't like it at all.
No?
I think I've been
pretty clear about that.
The question is what would you like?
Stop playing games.
Meaning what?
This.
That, I liked.
What the hell's going on?
There are things going on
which you just don't understand.
Then explain it to me.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
- But it's the way it has to be.
- No.
No, it doesn't.
Can I get a double
non-fat cappuccino, please?
Foaming up as we speak.
Thanks, Vince, that was fantastic.
You're very welcome.
Sorry about hanging up before.
It's okay.
No need to explain. Fargo filled me in.
Yeah.
Prehistoric love spores,
the oldest dodge in the book.
You know, you could have called me back.
I really put myself
out there with that invite.
Yeah, but you were
under the influence, right?
- What are you talking about?
- The invitation to your uncle's cabin.
Don't worry about it.
Just never happened.
Probably would have been a bad idea.
Yeah, I was serious about this weekend.
Just for your information,
you went to see Henry in the tunnel
after I asked you, yeah.
I am a moron.
So...
Tell me about this uncle's cabin.