Previously on Eureka...
There's an unexpected visitor
at the door.
- Auntie Lex!
- Shall I let her in?
- No!
- Yes!
A wedding gift for Ally.
None of us may make it through
the next time wave.
I'll see you around, Jack.
He's gone.
Are you strangling something?
Oh sorry.
Is the music too loud?
That's music?
Yes, I composed it in India.
It's supposed to relieve stress.
Really? Yeah, not working.
Give it a chance. Sometimes
you have to let art flow over you
before you can appreciate it.
I'll make you a copy for your car.
Take your time.
You should be doing that
in your condition?
Yoga's good
for the pregnancy.
And since I don't have
a Lamaze partner...
You might if you told the father.
He's halfway across the world...
Curing cholera.
Where he belongs.
This baby is my choice.
All right.
You want some coffee?
- Dad, you okay?
- Yep!
Sorry.
I rearranged a few things.
For a smart house,
the Feng Shui was really dumb.
No offense, SARAH.
None taken,
it's really opened up my flow.
- What's in my coffee?
- Soy milk.
Aunt Lexi says
that lactose gives you gas.
Oh, Lex also says
that her cat is grandma Lil.
Same old Jack.
You always hated change.
And you're always trying
to fix things that aren't broken.
You're telling me
everything in your life is perfect?
Nothing could be improved
just a tiny bit?
Well, no.
When are you leaving?
God, I wish I had a sibling.
Oh, problem at GD.
So no more Feng or Shui.
I don't think the lettering
is big enough.
Fargo, if it was any bigger,
it'd cover the whole building.
- Your point is?
- Hey, guys.
You seen Thorne?
Section three at the big tomb opening.
There's a protester
in the preservation lab.
What if we changed the font?
What's the plan in here?
We're turning this into
the Nathan Stark memorial hallway.
I was hoping for it to be done
before Dr. Blake returned, but...
close.
Allison's back already?
She said she was feeling better.
Henry, I'm gonna go grab
the other color swatches.
Come on,
I can show you where Thorne is.
Don't do anything until I get back.
Wouldn't think of it.
Here we go.
Sheriff, finally.
Nice to see you too.
What's... the problem?
People have no respect for the past.
That's the problem.
You know that isn't true.
We're only attempting this project
because of our fascination with history.
And Dr. Wilding is standing
in the way of progress, literally.
I want him arrested.
And you are?
Dr. Sebastian Marx, archaeologist.
- I'm sure you've seen my documentaries.
- You're a disgrace to the discipline.
Dr. Wilding is
our resident egyptologist.
Sheriff, they can't be allowed
to open this tomb.
That's a tomb?
For Queen Nyota.
Eureka had a queen.
No, Sheriff Carter,
we brought the whole tomb
from Egypt.
Had to use a superconductor to generate
a massive antigravitational field.
It's protected by a thermoplastic
multi-filament polymer.
Air bags.
Thank you.
Couldn't you just open it
when you were in Egypt?
Not under perfectly controlled
environmental conditions.
Here we can use a metasomatic ray
to protect the rock composition
so the tomb won't crumble.
I mean, this is gonna be
an unprecedented achievement.
Then we'll send it out
on an interactive 3D world tour
that will make King Tut look tame.
If you won't listen to me,
listen to them.
The message on that door is a warning.
Those are the symbols
for danger and death.
You mean like a curse?
Curse, legend,
lore.
I mean, this tomb has it all.
Inside, a doomed queen lies
shrouded in the cloud of darkness.
A queen who vows to one day rise again.
I think I just gave myself the chills.
I am really,
really sorry,
but these people have a job to do.
And I don't wanna have to take you in.
Fine.
I've conveyed their warning.
I strongly suggest...
that you listen.
I warned you.
Thank you.
I knew I could count on you.
Oh, just be careful.
It's all fun and games
till someone gets cursed.
Heard you were back.
Yeah, just trying...
to catch up on everything.
You sure you're ready?
I mean, it's only been a couple weeks.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Keeping busy, you know, it helps.
But I appreciate you
checking in on me.
Listen...
I have something for you, but
I'm not sure if now is the right time.
What is it?
It's...
a wedding present from Stark...
He...
asked me to give it to you.
I could've waited.
No, it's...
Thanks.
Power sequence initiated.
Metasomatic ray activated.
Tomb pressure equalized.
Now the tomb has been
untouched for 3,000 years.
Now, we must take great care
to protect this holy site
from being contaminated
by our presence.
To ensure that Queen Nyota's body
and spirit are preserved forever.
Come along.
Yes, yes, look at that.
It's wondrous.
This is wondrous!
- Eileen, are you getting this?
- You stepped out of your light.
What?
Why didn't you say anything?
Look, we gotta start from the top.
Is this guy for real?
You have to admire anyone
who can bring the wonder
of scientific discovery
to the masses.
Especially if the masses
will pay top dollar to see it?
Doesn't hurt.
We've just removed the cover.
And there she is.
Queen Nyota, entirely intact.
Now the linen that once enshrouded her
has completely dissolved,
but the queen herself
lives on...
in all her splendid glory.
Will the legend come true?
Will the queen rise again
to walk the night?
Only time will tell.
Season 3 Episode 05
Show Me the Mummy (v 1.00)
Teams Projet-SG & 6th-Race.
http://projet-sg.net
http://u-sub.net
Fargo, I swear, if this a joke...
It was the mummy queen,
and she tried to strangle me.
You've seen too many horror movies.
Hello?
Any mummy home?
We've desecrated her tomb and woke
her up, and now she's out for revenge.
Go find Zane!
He's the one you want.
Relax, Fargo.
You can't wake the dead
unless you play my sister's music.
Oh, God! Queen Nyota got him.
No, it's Dr. Marx.
He's alive.
He's not the only one.
The sarcophagus.
The mummy's gone.
Is that you?
I will always love you.
Okay.
- What happened?
- You passed out, Sebastian.
Probably dehydration.
After two weeks in the desert
and all day in the tomb,
it's no surprise.
Can I have some water, please?
Was it the mummy? Did you see her?
Fargo, come on.
Oh, no.
The mummy.
- My queen is gone.
- Yeah.
So you don't know where she is?
No.
I went to dinner.
When I came back to get more footage,
the sarcophagus was empty.
It must've been your egyptologist,
Wilding.
- We have to get her back.
- I'm telling you, it's the curse.
Fargo says that he saw
the mummy in...
Stark's memorial hallway.
It has nothing to do with that.
I know what I saw.
The queen is alive,
and I'm gonna prove it.
Marx accused me.
You should arrest him for slander.
Well, you did make quite a scene.
Disturbing Queen Nyota's remains
goes against everything I stand for.
Yeah, and yet Marx did it anyway.
That doesn't mean I'd resort
to desecration to make my point.
I respect the ancient Egyptians
far too much for that.
You know they're dead, right?
They're the first scientists and should
be honored for their achievements,
not turned into a circus sideshow.
Okay, well, what can you tell me
about Sebastian Marx?
It's not even his real name.
It's Paco Lopez. And he's been involved
in more than one scandal.
I'll say. "Bribing customs officials.
"Transporting sacred relics
without proper permits.
"Tomb raiding."
Marx sold out long ago.
He cares about the spectacle,
not science.
Well, a resurrected mummy would build
a lot of hype for his little movie.
I wouldn't put it past him.
Yeah, but a mummy hoax?
Fargo said that he saw something.
Fargo is afraid of his own shadow.
Given his state of mind...
Yeah, but still,
we should talk to Marx again.
Well, he's doing a book signing
at Café Diem.
It's part of Vincent's
pharaoh-palooza event.
All right.
Pharaoh-palooza?
Is nothing sacred?
Greetings, fellow Egyptians.
Enjoy this nectar of the Nile.
Thank you, Pharaoh.
Nice costume.
So where's Marx?
Good question. He's an hour
late for his own booking signing.
Oh, celebrities can be
such prima donnas.
Mmm... is this coffee?
- With pomegranate creamer in it.
- It's pharaoh-licious.
It's disgusting.
Can I get some real milk,
like from a cow?
Absolutely.
I shall resurrect some from the tomb.
That would be the freezer.
- I love theme day.
- Sheriff,
prepare to be proven wrong.
- Are you drinking this?
- Uh...
- no, enjoy.
- Is that blood?
Fish blood. Herring, to be exact.
Fargo, people are trying to eat.
The cells were found in a fossil pocket
in the paleontology lab.
- They're thousands of years old.
- So it's dead fish blood.
Not dead, regenerated.
A geology experiment brought
the cells back to life.
Oh, but how, you ask?
Metasomatic rays.
Just like they used to open the tomb.
And you think a few fish cells proves
that the mummy was resurrected.
You can't ignore the evidence, Sheriff.
Here, take a closer look. They're alive.
- And they smell.
- Yeah, I'm gonna be sick.
Oh, scratch that.
Now I'm gonna be sick.
Hi, guys. Do you like it?
I have free copies.
- Did you compose this?
- Mm-hmm, it soothes the soul
on a wide range of frequencies, and
there's a  lot of tension here.
- Especially from that area.
- I'll say.
Tell you what.
You want to relieve some stress?
Talk to Fargo.
He's got some serious mummy issues.
- Let's go see Marx at the B&B.
- Wait, take this.
Take it for the drive. You need it.
All right.
So... tell me about your mother.
You do nice work, Dr. Deacon.
How's it going
with that missing mummy?
The Sheriff's on the case.
I'm sure she'll be home soon.
Anything I can do to help,
just let me know.
Actually, there is one thing.
Do you have any idea what this is?
A cryptex.
It's like a type of combination lock.
Although I don't recognize the symbols.
- Do you think you could open it?
- Where did you find this?
In an alternate location
for the hotel I want to build.
First it's baryogenic radiation,
and now it's this.
What are you looking for?
Unfortunately,
the details are classified.
That is unfortunate.
So I guess I'm gonna have
to find another way.
Marx has been staying here
since he got to town.
Dr. Marx, it's Sheriff Carter!
You sure he's in there?
No one's seen him leave
since he came in last night.
- He say anything?
- No, just asked for some water.
How much water?
This place is a sauna.
More like a tomb.
I think we found our mummy.
That's not our mummy.
That's Marx.
- Is Sebastian really dead?
- Really dead.
I'm afraid he makes
Queen Tyota look good.
Nyota.
What happened?
We don't know yet. Henry's quarantined
the body while he does an autopsy.
Quarantined?
Does he think this is an infection?
The rapid deterioration of the body
is similar to flesh-eating bacteria.
Sebastian just got back from Egypt.
Maybe he picked something up there.
Or from the tomb
with the fancy "danger" signs
on the door.
Maybe we should've listened to Wilding.
Anything?
The body is severely drained
of all its fluids.
Well, how do you die of dehydration
in a tub full of water?
Aggressive bacterial infection.
Fungal spores, poison.
Poison?
So this could've been deliberate?
Because Dr. Wilding
was very upset yesterday.
No, it wasn't him. I spoke to him.
It's... it's not in his nature.
And more than likely
it's spread through contact.
If it had been airborne,
we would've seen victims.
- Was anyone else in the tomb with him?
- Just his camerawoman,
and I haven't heard from her
since yesterday.
- Jo and I are on it.
- What about the missing mummy?
Shouldn't we be more concerned
about who killed your friend?
That's my only concern, Sheriff.
If the mummy's infectious,
more lives are at risk.
We've already lost
one great scientist today.
I don't want to lose another.
Excuse me.
Oh, dear.
I will never leave you again.
Allison, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm...
I just thought I...
Yeah, I'm fine.
Sorry.
Listen...
I know what you're going through.
I lost my husband too.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- It was a long time ago.
But still, I know how difficult it is.
And there'll always be reminders.
And the hard truth is,
you can get past it,
but you'll never get over it,
even if you have
all the time in the world.
I just want you to know
you're not alone.
Thanks.
Marx's camerawoman, Eileen Michaels.
Professional documentarian.
She's been with Marx
for the entire excavation.
- You haven't seen her since yesterday?
- She left early.
- Said she wasn't feeling well.
- She never made it back to the hotel.
Can you see when she logged out
of the building?
She... didn't.
According to security,
she's still here.
Let's hope she hasn't
ended up like Marx.
About that.
I've been doing some research.
These are hieroglyphics from the tomb.
They're an obscure dialect,
but I think they're describing a plague.
- You mean like a disease?
- Maybe he got infected inside the tomb.
Call Wilding, we need to know what
the symbols mean. I'll look for Eileen.
Not to be all doom and gloom,
but if she's still alive,
wouldn't someone have seen her by now?
Maybe someone already has.
Okay, show me where she was.
Right over there, but I don't think
we should be in here.
What if the mummy comes back?
I don't think that's what you saw.
Well, you said you believed me.
No, I believe you saw someone
last night,
but just not the walking dead
out for revenge.
Tell that to Dr. Marx.
Henry hasn't finished the autopsy,
but it seems
that Dr. Marx
was killed by an infection.
Some kind of dehydration sickness.
So it makes...
- You need... water.
- What are you... Don't go in there!
It's not done yet!
This looks bad.
You're not getting the full effect.
You gotta imagine colored lights,
and pink water lilies, some koi.
- I don't think you want to see this.
- What?
It's the mummy queen!
No.
It's Eileen Michaels.
Well, the camerawoman was here
all along.
- She was in the fountain.
- She must've gotten in there
after Fargo ran,
like Marx in the bathtub.
That curse got her.
We're all doomed.
For the last time,
there is no curse.
- Then where's the mummy queen?
- I'm working on it.
I'm ordering tests on all GD employees,
make sure no one else is infected.
Well, she and Marx
were the only ones
who actually had physical
contact with the mummy.
That we know of.
Someone took her.
Who knows how many people are at risk?
How many more people are gonna die?
Okay.
Okay, well, we'll do the tests.
We'll keep our eyes open for the signs.
And what are the signs, exactly?
I don't...
Being really, really thirsty?
So that's what we're depending on?
People are dying, Carter!
Are you okay?
- I'm fine. It's...
- Come on, talk to me.
I know this is gonna sound crazy,
but I swear I keep hearing...
What?
- Oh, no.
I knew that stupid curse
would get me too.
Don't worry, Fargo.
We're gonna take care of you.
Oh, sure, like you took care
of Dr. Marx and Eileen Michaels?
You're not gonna end up like that.
How did he get infected?
Apparently Eileen touched him
on the neck before he ran off.
We're checking everyone
that Fargo came into contact with first.
Make sure no one else
has any symptoms.
Wilding and Zane are trying to learn
all they can from the symbols.
- That's gonna take time.
- Where's Henry?
He's doing an autopsy
of Eileen Michaels,
but if that doesn't provide
some answers, we're in trouble.
Let's hope it does.
She just disintegrated
before I could even get started.
Without water to keep her hydrated,
her body just turned to dust.
- That didn't happen to Marx.
- No, he was different.
I found hundreds of small
masses inside his stomach,
- growths of some kind.
- That's pleasant.
- Tumors?
- Not that I'd ever seen before.
- I'm gonna keep testing.
- Check Fargo's blood against Marx's.
We have a couple hours to save him.
We need to find out what kind
of infection we're dealing with.
I'll work on finding out
what the symbols to the tomb mean.
Maybe there's a cure for the plague,
whatever it is.
All right.
Any progress?
Some.
See, every language has its pattern.
It's just a matter
of cracking the code.
Zane's been filling in the blanks
where the symbols have
faded over time.
- I've always been a puzzle guy.
- Well done.
So, did queen what's-her-name
die from this?
No.
The high priests apparently
killed her themselves
to save her from the plague.
Not exactly a cure
we can use on Fargo.
There's still pieces
that we don't understand.
Like this symbol.
It keeps popping up over and over again.
That looks like a few clouds.
I don't understand who could've taken
the queen without anybody noticing.
There's nothing on the video.
No security breach.
It's like she vanished
into thin air.
Maybe because she did.
I think the reason
why we can't figure out
where the queen went is because
she's been right here all along.
Well, this is different.
Potassium, 35%.
Carbon, 18%.
Phosphorous, 1.0.
Calcium... 1.5.
Sheriff, you're right.
It's all organic matter.
It's human remains.
How did you know?
Henry said that Eileen
had turned to dust.
I figured
maybe the queen had as well.
If you'd only heeded the warning.
Well, at least nobody else had contact
with her. So this should be contained.
Yeah.
To Fargo.
How do I look?
Is that supposed to cheer me up?
Just hang in there.
I mean, Henry's still working on it,
and we haven't given up.
Neither should you.
I though you said
rehydrating him would help.
It should, but the more fluids
we give him, the weaker he gets.
- All right, if you stop?
- He dies of dehydration.
Here, look at his blood.
These are microbes.
They're replicating
at an incredible rate.
They look like...
little bugs.
It's not like any bacteria
I've ever encountered.
What if we're thinking
of the wrong kind of plague?
What do you mean?
Well, so far we've been thinking
about the disease kind.
What if it's...
an insect kind?
You think Fargo's been invaded
by microscopic insects?
Well, he showed me this fish blood
that had been regenerated
by a meta-whatever ray.
Could the same thing happen
to some ancient bug?
Well, under certain conditions,
insects can enter cryptobiosis.
It's a natural state
of suspended animation.
They can survive
indefinitely until rehydrated.
Like... like sea monkeys?
Same principle.
Which explains why rehydrating Fargo
is making him worse.
The insects are multiplying.
And if they're exposed to a large amount
of water, like an overflowing bathtub?
It could speed metamorphosis, like
a caterpillar turning into a butterfly.
Okay, take care of Fargo.
I gotta warn Henry.
Henry, I need to talk to you
for a second.
Hey, we need to lock down that tent,
make sure nothing can get out.
Well, nothing can. It's designed
to contain the tiniest of microbes.
What about something bigger?
How much bigger?
Quite a bit.
Why couldn't it have been butterflies?
Jo, keep everyone inside.
They're heading your way.
- There's nothing left of Marx.
- Except what's flying towards town.
Let's get back to GD.
We can't do this alone.
It's a swarm.
That's what the cloud stands for.
Yeah, what kind of threat is it?
The bugs lay eggs,
hatch larvae,
and then seek out new hosts.
Us.
How did the ancient Egyptians
deal with the problem?
They killed the infected
and burned their city to the ground.
Let's call that plan B.
According to our guys in entomology,
these bugs
are gonna grow exponentially
now that they've emerged.
Hold on, how could the bugs
grow in Marx but not Eileen?
Probably incubation.
To fully develop,
the larvae need water.
They were both in water.
Eileen in the fountain, Marx in the tub.
Maybe there was something
in the fountain that killed the larvae
before they could
undergo metamorphosis.
I'll go test the water.
Sorry.
Hey, Zo, just stay in doors.
We got a little bit of a bug problem.
A little bug problem?
Stay away from the windows, people!
Looks pretty big from where I am.
What happened to lights?
They must've gotten
to the circuit breaker.
Can't hear you.
Can you turn that down?
Aunt Lex, kill the boombox.
The bug swarm is huge and...
It's leaving.
Turn it back on.
Tell Lex to turn the music back on.
Dad wants the music back on.
I knew he'd come around.
It's weird. They're...
They're coming back.
Okay, keep the doors closed,
keep the music on, and hang tight.
It's Lexi's music.
The bugs actually like it.
It could be the harmonic frequencies.
Yeah, or they have no taste.
The point is that we can attract them.
How do we kill 'em
before they lay any eggs?
Without gassing the town,
I have no idea.
Even then they could be resistant
to traditional pesticides.
All right, what killed
the bugs in Eileen Michaels?
- Did you test the fountain?
- Purified water. Not even chlorine.
Well, what about the pH levels?
Oxygenation, alkalinity?
All completely normal.
Just regular H2O.
I mean, no different than the water
that Marx was found in.
No, Marx was found in hot water.
The bathroom was filled with steam.
Yeah, but the fountain water comes from
an underground spring. It's ice cold.
So maybe the bugs can't take the cold?
That's a reasonable hypothesis, and...
we have the perfect way to test it.
Save Fargo, save the town.
Wait.
It's okay, Fargo.
Maybe for you.
Just let us take care of you.
The anesthesia's taking effect.
And...
he's out.
We're ready.
Okay, his vitals are really weak,
so let's take it slow.
Starting cryo-freeze...
Now.
How long till we know?
Until I can confirm all the larvae
inside of him have been frozen to death?
Will...
Will he be all right?
If he doesn't freeze to death first.
Internal sensors are
still detecting movement.
Okay, almost there.
No more movement.
They're dead?
Or they could just be hibernating?
That's what we're gonna find out.
Bring Fargo out.
Defrost sequence...
Underway.
Pulse rate not responding.
Fargo, don't you die on me.
Still no change.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Pulse rate... 45...
53...
Normal rate and rhythm.
He's coming back to us.
Still no movement.
That's it.
They're dead!
So... he's okay?
I swear I almost lost it there
for a moment.
Yeah.
And now I have.
I will always love you.
I see him too.
So do I.
When you moved your hand
from your necklace.
Is that a logic diamond?
Yeah, yeah it is.
Stark had it made for her.
Of course, I should've known.
I will always love you.
Then it's a holographic projection
activated by certain spectra of light.
Nathan must've programmed it
in the diamond.
I didn't know.
It's okay.
I'm in Heaven.
Fargo's temperature is normal.
- It worked.
- All right.
Let's get this working on the swarm.
Freezing the bugs in Fargo is one thing,
but we can't freeze the whole town.
Oh, we don't need the whole town.
Just one really cold tomb.
Okay, Zane, plugging it in...
now.
Copy that. Everything
in a five-mile radius should hear it.
You don't have much time.
If the bugs start to reproduce,
we'll never get them under control.
- Way ahead of you.
- Good luck, Sheriff.
Here they come.
They're coming.
Door!
Boombox!
That's part of the plan?
Are you crazy?
Everybody, hold on!
Vince, freezer!
I'm on it!
That's all of them.
Freeze 'em.
Zero degrees Kelvin, baby.
Bless you, fusion reactor!
- Everyone okay?
- A little creeped out, but fine.
Yeah, but my food isn't.
- I'm gonna need some grief counseling.
- Better that than being the food.
That's true.
- Not too shabby, bro.
- Yeah, not too shabby yourself.
Does this mean that you like my music?
I appreciate it on some level, yeah.
Well, I'm glad you guys made up,
because if you think I'm cleaning
that freezer all on my own,
you are sadly mistaken.
Welcome back.
How you feeling?
Like I just came back from the dead.
It was close.
I saw a bright light...
and Dr. Stark.
He's okay, Dr. Blake.
You don't have to worry.
He's okay.
I'm sure he is.
They just finished sterilizing
the sarcophagus.
Good.
An outbreak on tour
would create terrible buzz.
So to speak.
I have...
a new puzzle for you to solve.
A cryptex.
Yeah, I've read about these,
but I've never actually seen one.
You think you can crack it?
You kidding?
I broke into my dad's safe
when I was five.
Well, then I picked
the right man for the job.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
Well, Nathan left me a message.
I need to hear it.
You want me to stay?
I think I need to do this by myself.
Surprise.
I know what you're thinking.
"I can barely handle one Nathan.
What am I gonna do with two?"
Well, don't worry.
All I've done is imprint
a small part of myself
onto this diamond.
The way that you...
have imprinted yourself...
onto me.
If marriage is about joining
two people for eternity,
I wanted to be sure...
that no matter where you are...
or where I am...
I will always be with you.
I made mistakes the first time, Ally.
I know that.
But I promise you...
this time...
this time is forever.
I will always love you.
And I will never,
ever...
leave you again.
Goodbye, Nathan.