this place rots.
Stupid boring,quiet boring,one-horse boring town.
Why do I have to burn my saturday volunteering?
You're not volunteering.
It's called community service.
And you wouldn't be doing it if you didn't
pull the fire alarm during your I.Q. Test.
I wouldn't be doing it if you hadn't arrested me.
Sometimes it sucks having a dad
who's the town smokey.
Sometimes it sucks having a daughter
who's the town delinquent.
I take it back.
Gee,thanks.
It always sucks.
please don't make me do this.I hate old people.
you don't do this,you won't live to be one.
Can't we just discuss this?
You're going.End of discussion.
I will do jail timE.
Go. Scoot.
I can't tell you how much I appreciate this,sir.
No need to thank me,fargo.You've earned it.
Having your own office is a right of passage.
It's a symbol of status and rank.
It tells the world you've arrived.
Not yet.
Section five?
Pace yourself.
What's down here?
You...
and your new office.
Congratulations,fargo.
You deserve every square foot of it.
Thanks.
what did you do to get put down here?
I earned it.
Having your own office is a right of passage.
It's a symbol of status and rank.
Rank's the word all right.
It smells like something died in here.
Like,say,the 1970s.
You have no vision.
Once all this junk's gone,
this will be an exemplary office space.
- Just lacking - a woman's touch?
Style.
well,you got a lot of great stuff in here.
It just deserves our respect.
The dumpster's down the hall to the left.
Dumpster? No-no-no-no.
One man's trash is another man's treasure.
Been nice doing business with you.
Check this out!
What do you think?
Stereo?
Sure.
First generation ipod.
how do you turn this thing on?
On?
It's got key holes.
And we got keys.
I saw some in his desk over here.
Hey,these two match.
Here.Go unlock your side.
Ready...set...go.
Just another old piece of useless junk.
primary firing sequence initiated.
Weapon will deploy in 24 hours.
I don't think I like this station.
Car or no car,this is a 30 mile an hour zone.
Don't you have anything better
to do than harass me.
No. Not really.
Now you do.
Yeah,that can't be good.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
Proudly Presents
SYNC:YTET-heta_lee
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
SYNC:
Eureka S01EP06
what's going on,sheriff?
I was hoping you could tell me.
This sort of thing happen often?
Not to my recollection.
I've never seen anything like it.
It's some sort of I.C.B.M.
I. C. B.M?
Please.
Look at the circumference.
Clearly,that's an I. R. B.M.
So you guys have seen this before?
- Nope. - Nope.
Thanks,guys.
Big help.
What do you think it is,sheriff?
Oh,I know exactlywhat it is.
Trouble.
Carter.
It's allison. We've got trouble.
That's exactlywhat I said.
Trouble.
Well,hello.
I'm doris stokes,the director.
You must be zoe.
Unfortunately.
I've heard a lotabout you.
But everyone deservesa second chance,right?
Or a third or fourth.
Let's put you right to work,okay?
Actually,doris,I usually ease into my day
with a latte,maybe some sort of pastry.
Funny.
I understand we have youfor the next 13 saturdays.
13?
100 hours dividedby eight-hour shifts.
I'm afraid thatthree months of saturdays
is not gonna work for me.
So why don't we say we'll justget the
whole thing over in one fell swoop?
let's start with the rec room.
Holy crap!
This is the rec room?
It's a nice placeto die.
Even nicer placeto live.
The residents of eurekagive so much.
This facility is our wayto give back.
run out of tennis balls?
I guess all the massagesin the world
can't stop you from losing your mind.
So,doris,are there any age restrictions
on getting a room here?
You've got a darlingsense of humor.
Come on.I've signed you to eugenia.
Eugenia,this is zoe.
She's going to assist you today.
If I desired assistance,
I'd be living inan assisted living facility.
Don't mind her.
She has a teence ofan attitude problem.
do not!
You two should get onjust fine.
You smoke?
No.
Drink?No.
You lying?
Maybe.
What kind of a nameis zoe anyway?
It's a popular one.
You know,probably as popularas eugenia
was back inthe great depression.
For once,doris may be right.
How's my hair?
Your hair?It's fine.
How's my hair?Why are we whispering?
What matters most is the matterof
how we handle anti-matter.
That used to be me.
Anti-matter,unlike matter...
you used to talk to yourself?
No.
He used to talk to me.
It had to comefrom somewhere.
Keep looking.
Yes sir Dr.***
Allison.Glad to see you.Sheriff.
Scientist.
Which of your guysis responsible for
the cuban missile crisispopping up all over town?
They're not missiles.
Really?
Cause I have a town fullof extremely anxious
people who think they looka lot like missiles.
what are they,nathan?
And why do they looka lot like missiles?
We're working on it.
So you don't know?He doesn't know.
Don't touch the buttons.
I have to call this into the D.O.D.
Not yet.
We have plenty of timeto figure this out.
I can only wait so longand
I'll need to have answers.
Cause I have a town fullof extremely anxious
people who think they looka lot like missiles.
give us a little room,people.
Sir,henry's a lot smarterand faster than me
fargo,that's the best decisionyou've made all day.
Henry.
It's definitely a weaponand
this machine controls it.
- Tell me you knowmore than that.  - It's set to discharge a  hugeionosphere particle beam.
- oh,jeez.
- Okay,thision-beam-thingy.That is what exactly?
Irradiated,uranium isotopes.
oh,god.
Oh,death ray.
Why didn't you just say"death ray"?
I searchedyour entire database.
There's not one single recordof silos,
irradiated isotopes,or ionosphere particle beams.
Try "death ray"?
It's as if the machinenever existed.
Did you try turning it off?
Why didn't I think of that?
Fargo,turn the machine off.
And that's a stupid question?
I mean,you did justturn it on,right?
That was an accident.
Jack,this machine was built atthe
height of the cold war.
There is no off switch.
Could you cut the power source?
And risk there's a fail-
safeand it fires immediately?
I'm gonna take thatas a no.
How much timedo we have left?
weapon will deploy in 23 hours.
Finally,a straight answer.
we need to arrangefor transport trucks
and establishevacuation routes.
make emergency contingenciesfor
every location that could be hit.
area hospitals should
be preppedfor emergency overflow.
and we'll need to estimatecollateral damage in
and aroundthe target perimeter.
Good.
You can hear us right?
Unfortunately.
You're panicking.
We're not panicking.We're reacting.
You say "death ray",we have a reaction.
You said death ray.
It's a ray,right?It causes immediate death?
Yes,it could causeimmediate death.
It could simply blow up
and people here wouldimmediately die.
It could strike moscow and people
there wouldimmediately die.
Then moscow would retaliate
and people everywhere wouldimmediately die.
Evacuation is moot.No place is safe.
You choose a great timeto be indifferent.
I'm not indifferent,sheriff.
I'm focused.
We have 24 hoursand we happen to be in the most
advanced scientificfacility in the world.
Housing the largestsupercomputer in the world.
Populated by the smartestscientists in the world.
We have plenty of timeto figure
this out as long as we don't panic.
but we've downloaded,scanned,
and decrypted every file every schematic,
and every piece of paper of every
projectever developed here.
And there's nothing.
Well,maybe not everypiece of paper.
This is every piece of paper
I pulled from fargo's office.
This has to tell us about that machine.
Come on!Scientists are so smart.
How come they don't know
anything about penmanship?
Pardon the alliteration,but which would prefer?
Penmanship or progress?
Tequila.
Scotch.
Really?
What's "it"?
It what?
I.T.
It's scribbled at the bottomof all these pages.
I don't know.Maybe information technologyperhaps
from the department from
which these documentsoriginated?
Looks more like someone'sinitials.
Well,you are the detective.
Marshal. Sheriff.
That sounds like a demotion.
Hand me some pics.
What's the shiny thing?Is that a solar flare?
that shiny thing is a mirror.
You do rememberthe moon landing,right?
Do not tell methat didn't happen.
No,it happened but we didn't
goto the moon just to walk.
We put mirrors all over the moon
to bounce signals back to the earth.
Telescopic images,satellite communications.
Death rays?
They weaponized the moon.
I mean,they can bounce a laser off the moon
and wipe out any targetthey want.
What,like tanks and stuff?
No,cities and stuff.
So you're telling me while the world watchedneil
armstrong take one small step for man
N.O.R.A.D. Took a giant leapfor themselves.
With the help from someoneat global.
Someone with the initials I.T.
I.T.
Oh!
Irvin thatcher.
It has to be irvin thatcher.
Irvin thatcher was thisbrilliant
scientist behind M.A.D.
M.A.D.D.?
Mothers against drunk driving?
Mutually assured destruction.
Oh,that M.A.D.
You said he wasa brilliant scientist.
Was...or is?
this is Xplained.
The atom nucleus is comprised of positively-
charged protons and neutrally-chargedneutrons.
When a nucleus is bombarded by a neutrally-
chargedparticle,the result is fission.
Um,you lost me right after"
this is easily explained".
Okay.Let me try it another way.
Your father is a proton.
Your mother is a neutron.
You are a free radical.
You're caught stealing cds in the mall.
You hit your parentswith that news.
What happens?
They go nuclear?
Exactly.
And spliT.
You think that I'm the reasonmy parents split?
no-no-no-no.
zoe.
Zoe.
What? I'm doing the job.I'm helping people.
I'm assistinG...people.
Be right back.Please...carry on.
This isthe "oppressive jerk
who's all up in yourbiznezz?"
I see you've found somethingto talk about.
Hi.Sheriff carter.
Nice to meet you.
I'm looking fora retired scientist.
Swing a cat.
A dr. Thatcher?
Irvin? Room 101.
But why do you want--
Wait for it.
Hey,room 101.That would be?
room 101?Right this way.
What do you need him for,sheriff?
There's a situation.
Even the brainiacs at globalcan't figure it out.
But there is one guyin town who can.
And apparently,this is the guy.
Dr. Thatcher?
this is the guy?
The question remains,fusion of fission?
Fission?Certainly not.
I haven't been fishin'since I lived on lake erie.
You think that's erie?
How do you explainquasar energy paradox?
Or baldness among musicians?Hmm?
This is the guy.
right this way,dr. Thatcher.
Right this way.
give the doctor some room.
Sir,sir!Right this way.
Dr. Thatcher,it's an honor.
I'm henry deacon.
This machine of yours.It's really something.
It's like a riddleinside an enigma wrapped
in ten inchesof titanium alloy.
It's like a riddleinside an enigma
wrapped in ten inchesof titanium alloy.
using a singlechannel transponder package.
Or maybe asurvivable low frequency
communication system.
In which casewe'd have
to reassess certain aspectsof our approach.
Guys...go easy.
we need that launch code,sheriff.
Easy's not gonna get it.
Neither is browbeating the man.
Just give him a minute.
dr. Thatcher?
We think the controls arebehind this panel.
I just can't figure out how to get to them.
These locking bolts.
Are they some kind ofproprietary threading?
Reverse the hex.
Excuse me?
If you want sex,reverse the hex.
Sheriff,at any pointwhen you picked him up,
the car ride,the long walk down here--
Yeah,there may have been signs.
Righty loosey,lefty tighty.
Got it.
Bang up job.
Reverse the hex.
The screws recede.
It's brilliant.
Okay,dr. Thatcher.
All I need is a code to suspendthe launch signals.
Charlie,tango,lima.
No.Charlie never tangoed in lima.
you must be tired. Have a seat.
Don't give up.
Up,down.
The windows on the bus goup and down up and down
- any luck?
Windows on the bus goup and down up and down
is there gonna bea missile strike?
do we need to evacuate?
No reason to panic,folks.
I heard it was a death ray.
That's ridiculous.
That's obviouslya rumor.
Started by an idiot.
Who's he?Is he responsible?
Folks,listen up.Just go on home.
Situation's completelyunder control.
It could also bethermal conductive resistance.
Let me take a look.
Yeah,it look likethey used the classic formula.
Red for hot,blue for not.
Yellow's usually the ground.
So I guess...it's pretty safeto cut the blue.
- What do you think? - weapon will deploy in 20 hours.
Do it.
launch code override initiated.
Yes!
weapon will deploy in seven hours.
No.
Let's not cutany more wires.
dr. Thatcher,I know it's in there.
Just give us a hint.
Gravity.
The natural force of attractionexerted by a
celestial body upon objectsat or near its surface.
That's great.
Give me a second.
Look,we have our best peopleworking on this.
You don't know nathan,
but he will find a wayto shut it down.
Nothing againstyour husband--
ex.Soon to be ex.
But the man with the
answersis sitting right there.
We just need to figure out
how to get them out of him.
What?What what?
You got that look on your facelike you know
something I should know,but you're not telling me.
Spill!
I can'T.It's classified.It's nathan's turf,
- and there's no waythat he is gonna - allison,if we don't stop this thing,
there won't be any turf.
What is it?
Okay.Gravity. Got it.
What?
Hey,allison.
Absolutely not.
That technology is highlyexperimental
and far too dangerousfor anyone to
carter?Really?
That's just a riskwe may have to take.
So this is basicallya vulcan mind meld?
The px-24 allows one personto probe
the consciousnessof another.
In theory,anyway.
In theory?
Well,we haven't performeda human test run yet.
Oh.
"In memory of skippy."
Oh,he was everyone's favoritetest chimp.
Did he die on this thing?
No.
Autopsy was inconclusive.
Carter,listen.
I'm not gonna thinkany less of you
if you don't wanna do this.
What am I looking for...again?
Sequences,equations,codes.
A kiss for luck?
Oh.
Last chance to be a hero,doc.
You just say the word.
Eh,worth a shot.
- the wheels on the bus go round and round carter,
- are you okay?
The wheels on the bus go round and round
eugenia.
Okay,I'm stopping this. No!Keep going.
stockholm.
Linus pauling.
Eugenia.
Who is eugenia?Carter.
Did you see howto stop it?
No.
But I saw what happensif we don'T.
Irvin,we're gonna goand see that girl of yours.
Would you like that?
All right,don't play coy with me,okay?
Ve been inside thatbig brain of yours.
I know how muchyou love her.
That doesn't go away,does it?
Well,I don't thinkit does.
And I know that whenyou're not thinking
about nuclear holocaust,
you're thinkingabout eugenia.
That's what I thought.
Got you with the nuclearholocaust thing,didn't I?
I put a trace on the hot wire.
The power source leadsout the back.
That's where the machineis vulnerable.
Now,if we can reach that,
then we can getto the guts of the thing.
I got a team in section 5working on
a laser bombardment drillthat
will bore right throughthe titanium shell.
Yeah,unfortunately,your guys in
section 4 tell me it's not titanium.
It's arconium carbonide,which is--
impenetrable.But.
I believe we can getthere from here,
through the baseof the machine.
If we tunnel down,under,and up,
we'll be directlybehind it.
And then I thinkwe got a shot.
Tell fargo to give youanything you need.
And not to touchanything you don'T.
bad news,good news.
We didn't get anythingfrom thatcher.
But carter wasn't hurtin the process.
And the good news?
Here you go,buddy.Take a seat.
I'll go lookfor eugenia,
and you enjoy,uh,the view.With a room.
Where is that?
Linus pauling.
Uh,royal palace.Uh,stockholm.
Sweden.
How do you know that?
I don't know.
I was there. When?
Recently.
Uh,um,do you knowwhere eugenia is?
She's notto be disturbed.
Her words,not mine.
Come on.
This is her.
Eugenia?
Eugenia,it's zoe.
Has she donesomething wrong?
No,no.
Eugenia,it's sheriff carter.I need to talk to you.
Is there somethingI should know?
No.
There is,isn't there?
Actually,yeah.
Yeah,that crack I madeabout
your being a delinquent.
Yeah.
Didn't mean it.
You're my girl.
It's really bad,isn't it?
No.
eugenia!
Eugenia?
eugenia.
Come in,jo.
Where are you,jo?
Come on,jo,talk to us.
We all live here.We have a right to
knowwhat's going on.
What is the trajectoryof the weapon?
is there a sea-basedboost phase intercept?
have the launch protocolsbeen initiated?
Don't know.
Don't know,don't know.
Go home.
We've got everythingunder control.
Except for that.
zoe,think.Did she say anythingabout
going anywhere,doing anything?
- Not that I remember.
- Well,how about family?
Some kidspicking her up,something?
It never came up,okay?
Where is that?
the mensa thing.
Yeah,I seriously doubtyou can compete.
No,the sundial.Where is that?
- Copernicus park.
- I can s
it's on the south sideof
the distilled water tower.
Come on,that's wherewe find my girl.
I thought I wasyour girl.
Wait,that sounded weird.
Henry,how's--
Henry,how's the--
Henry,how's the drillinggoing?!
This laser bombardment drill cuts
through quartz like butter.
I should be done drilling in,what,
uh,five hours.
Weapon will deploy in four hours.
Drill faster.
Yeah.
oh,my god.
Eugenia,what--
what are you doing?How--how'd you even get here?
Henry souped upmy chair.
I can go 50 milesbetween charges.
So why have I been pushing youaround all day?
I wanted you to feel goodabout yourself.
Like you were assisting.
Fine.
I didn't hatethe company.
Dad,are you okay?
eugenia.
Dad,what the hellare you doing?
Why did you do that?
Uh...I'm not sure.
Mind your own business,zoe.
Uh,sorry.
Uh,your anniversary.Our anniversary.
Anniversary.
Of what?
You and me.H-him.
Thatcher.
Anniversary?
He never even proposed.
Yes,he did.
Uh--
I saw it.
Trust me.Never happened.
Is dementia contagious?
No--uh,okay.
In--in--in his mind,he proposed.
I mean,right here.That's why you come here.
I come here...
for lunch...
every day.
This is wherewe first met.
We'd sit...
and look at the sky.
He told me howthe stars shined,
how the planets revolvedaround the sun.
How his universe revolvedaround me.
And then his universecame
crashing down and mine with it.
What happened?
We were goingto get married in
stockholm after irvin won the prize.
The nobel prize?
No one imaginedlinus pauling
would win a second nobel.
It was devastatingto irvin.
He had a completemental break
the dayof the announcement.
The day he was goingto propose.
The day I lostthe love of my life.
The picture.
The virtual stockholm.
You must thinkI'm a fool.
Pining over a lovethat's gone.
It's not gone.
We just have to pick upwhere we left off.
Did I say we?Mm-hmm.
Sorry.
weapon will deploy in three hours.
Well,there's gottabe something.
I mean,use explosivesto blast
through the rest of the bedrock.
This machine was programmedas
a second-strike,dead man's weapon.
Any kind of explosion and--
I cannot believewe built
this thing to protect ourselves.
I'm gonna have to puta call in to the D.O.D.
- You can'T.
- I have to.
You can't!
I think that they'll notice
if we startworld war iii.
allison,think about it.
What are you gonna say?
"We may accidentallyblow up
"moscow,beijing,pyongyang,and stockholm?"
Okay,I know how fondyou are of stockholm,nathan.
But this is biggerthan you.
If you tell themthat we can't stop it,
they're gonna tryand stop it.
They'll nuke us and--
and,I know,any kind of explosion
can trigger the device.
I get it.
But we're runningout of options.
Beg to differ.
Gonna need to borrowyour nobel.
It was open.
Oh. Sorry.
What in the hellare you doing?
We're gonna partylike it's 1962.
I miss sheriff cobb.
You should wear that dressmore often.
Do you think this'll work?
Works for me.
Let's hope so.
Oh,sheriff.
When a light bulb goes offin your head,
what are we talking?
15,20 watts?
If you have a better idea,I'd love to hear it.
No? Yeah.
Better get started.
Jo? Wow.You look--
no,you look.
...Joining us here in stockholm.
Robert oppenheimerfamously said,
"the atomic bomb"made the prospect of
future war unendurable."
One man never forgotthose words.
A man we welcome among us today.
A man whom
the nobel committee and the norwegian parliament
have selected for this year's
awardof the nobel prize,
dr. Irvin horatio thatcher.
Fargo.
Dr. Thatcher.
I got that.
Thank you.
He's been carryingthat speech for 40 years.
The wheels on the bus go round and round
round and round round and round
the wheels on the bus go round and round
a simple littlechildren's song.
But it was this songthat inspired
my concept of mutually assureddestruction.
We build an a-bomb,they build an a-bomb.
We build an h-bomb,they build an h-bomb.
Round and round,round and round.
The wheels on the busleading us towards
an unending escalationof newer,
more powerful,more deadly weapons.
Which is what led me to my greatestachievement.
The ionosphere particle beam.
In order to ensure peace on earth,
I built the deadliest weaponin the universe.
But that's the endof the story.
Let me take you backto the beginning.
We don't have timeto go back to neverland.
Uh,dr. Thatcher.
There's an urgent situationwith your weapon
that needs your attention.
Oh.Sorry.
I would just like to end by thankingthe committee.
And eugenia,my love,
without whom this achievement
would nothave been possible.
We have a lotof catching up to do.
I don't like that look.What's wrong?
My crew.
I've gotta get my crew to fix the device.
Your crew?
Eastern world is exploding violence flaring
and bullets loading you're old enough to kill
but not for voting you don't believe in war
what's the gun you're toting
even the jordan river has bodies floating
don't you tell me over and over
and over again my friend
- that you don't believe
-oh,my god.
30 secondsand counting,guys.
Ready.
Set.
Go!
launch code override initiated.
yes!
Oh,crap.
dead man's protocol activated.
Launch sequence initiated.
Weapon will deploy in five minutes.
Did somebody cutthe blue wire?
Not good.
Very not good.
This is the onethat assures mutually
assureddestruction.
How do we stop it?
You can'T.
It can't be shot down.
Henry,how much timedo we have left?
30 seconds.
*******
********
- ten.
- Will it work?
I think desperate timescall
for desperate measures.
Henry,when you outfittedmy jeep,
did you put inany air bags?
Carter.Carter,where are you
4.3.2.
Zap!
Henry,you got it?
I got it.
It missed!
We missed the moon!
carter,carter!
Great job,man.
We missed the moon.We missed the moon.
We missed it!Ha,ha,ha!
Little help?
But where did it go?
the zephyr rover is making
its final approach to jupiter.
pasadena,we have a problem.
That's gonna be a shiner.
Yeah,well.
One small step for man,one giant weltfor me.
So,when are you gonna
tell him my nobel isn't histo keep?
I don't know.He saved your .I think he earned it.
No,I earned it.
It's mine.
Take it away.Lose a great scientist.
It's not a difficult equation.
You never know,you might need thatcher to
dismantle the nextticking time bomb.
Good point.
Really?
You did a good job,carter.
Thanks.
I had a little helpfrom my crew.
You remember that feeling?
Yeah.
It's nice to knowthat it lasts a lifetime.
Yeah,kind of depressing.
A little.Yeah.
I'm just grateful that wefinally got together.
I said "we" again,didn't I?
Yeah.
How long is this supposedto last?
I'll see you tomorrow,carter.
No,seriously.