No.
Nope.
Oh,my god,no.
Carter,the xg-55 assault cannonuses
a 30-round magazine?
- On what planet?
- Less commentary,more addition.
What's my score?
53%.
Yeah!
Third time's the charm.
Third time's the "f," again.
No advanced weaponry for you.
I have to knowevery gun in the rack?
And what? You should get special treatment
because you're the sheriff?
I see what's going on here.
I know you feelyou were passed over
when they brought me in as sheriff.
And yet I aced the examfirst time.
Jo,it's not a contest.
I was assigned hereby washington.
If you an issue,take it up with them.
And give me the remote.
Happy to.
After you pass the exam.
It's regulation,carter.
Okay,jo,I'm the sheriff.
Which means I needyour trust,
I need your respect,
and most importantly,I need the
remoteto the freakin' gun rack!
Sorry.
You can't enforce the rules if
you're not willingto follow them first.
Better hit the books.
***********
Nothing yet,mate.
Spencer,start the moviealready.
I'm working on it.
- Crikey.
- Hd.
So many pixels thatyou and
I can't even see them.
when that satellite reorients
another seven degrees-- ho ho!
- Tv heaven.
- spencer,how do you work this thing?
Nobody touchesthe master commander.
Vincent,we need food.
Grub,grub,grub!
Patience,heathens.
Roasted jalapeño maize kernelswith demi-glace.
Get 'em while they're steamy.
But it's movie night.
I need my popcorn.
Expand and indulgeyour palate,fargo.
Philistine.
We're locked on!
In seconds,a first-run flickdestined for the
multiplex will be comingto your local spencerplex.
Oh,ripper!
You're the sheriff.
It must be for you.
jack carter.
********
Spencer? Yeah,it's friday night.
Did you ask himto keep it down?
No,I'm not shirkingmy responsibilities.
As a matter of fact,
I'll sendmy deputy over right away.
Not a problem.
All right,bye.
Spencer's movie night'sgetting a little rowdy.
And I handled it last time.
Oh,good,then you know the way.
You know what they sayabout payback,right?
She's a bitch?
spencer!
Spencer!
Hello!
Officer of the law!
What's wrongwith you people?
Turn it down!
What?
Why?
Your neighbors arecomplaining about the noise.
Which neighbors?
The state of idaho.
Turn it down!
Have a sit,jo.
Like a tinny?
- Vinnie,get jo a beer.
- I'm on duty.
I can respect that.
Like it to go?
looks human,but it's just a guise.
I've seen it.
Hideous under the skin.
my god.
What do they want?
**********
*****
who's that?
what are we watching?
They came to conquer.
When did that come out?
N-next week.
Picture's amazing.
Yeah,it is.
he's just the host.
The creature's protected inside.
how do we get it out?
we cut it out.
******
Maize kernel?
I mean,that is like--
unbelievable.
Yet believable.
- Definitely.
- Like being there.
And now I gotta go.
Hey,you guyskeep it down,okay?
Ugh,we'll walkyou out.
You know,just in caseof alien invasion.
Strength in numbers.
Right.
Spencer,that wasa life-altering experience.
Hey,guys,hey!
Don't forget,next week's noir night.
********
Six hours tillI have to go to work.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-gagegao
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Eureka
Season 01 Episode 04
Nathan?
Allison.
It's late.
It's 7:00.
In the morning.
Have you been hereall night?
Yeah.
Guess I gota little caught up.
How's the budget going?
It's not.
I have to justify a number that
will keepglobal cutting-edge.
No.
And still give congresssomething to slash.
You saw what they didto nasa.
So when doescongressman faraday get in?
He's in.
Flew in from mcchordair force base last night.
And he expects hard numbers and a field
testof the px-319 project at 9:00 A.M.
Hopefullyhe'll be impressed.
No,hopefully he's forgotten that
you called hima shameless grandstander
in front of the defenseappropriations committee.
He brought thatupon himself.
The man's smart,but the likes the
soundof his own voice too much.
Who does thatremind me of?
Oh,maybe a littlegroveling will help.
Whatever it takes.
Global's futureis all I care about.
That sounds familiar too.
This has to go smoothly,allison.
And not just for global.
Maybe you can talkto sheriff carter.
See if he can keep thingsquiet around here.
For a change.
I'll see whatI can do,nathan.
Nothing like a little vincespresso
to start the day off,huh?
I'm waiting.
- For what?
- Aw,come on.
You're a woman.
You're making small talk.
You're buying me coffee,which means either,"a,"
you're into me,or,"b," you want something.
Could you be more sexist?
Come clean,or I'll makemy own assumptions.
Okay.
Allison blake,really into me!
- All right!
- Spread it around!
We have a visitorin town.
- See,was that so hard?
- We do?
Congressman faradaygot in last night.
And you'retelling me this why?
We're underbudget review.
Faraday's tourhas to go smoothly.
Nathan would just like youto keep a lid on things.
He has great faithin your abilities.
No,he doesn'T.
No,he doesn't,but we still needa
day or two of quiet.
In this town?
That's easier saidthan done.
Sheriff,something'shappened to spencer.
I didn't hear that!
What's wrongwith the monkeys?
They should be at each other's throats,
but they look fine.
They are fine.
The device isn'T.
Are you tryingto sabotage me?
Stark's on his way nowwith the congressman.
- I'm runningdiagnostics,but--
- no "buts!"
If you can't getthe job done,dr.Sharat,
I'll find someone who can.
You realize I don'twork for you,right?
In fact,you workfor everyone else.
Now I have to tell stark we have
nothingto show faraday.
If I go down for this,I'm taking you with me.
- Fargo,I thinkyou're overreacting.
- Stop making this about me!
Sabotage.
Dr. Stark,I'm afraidthere's been a delay.
my office,15 minutes.
I want a detailed explanation,
and it'd better be good,fargo.
So,congressman,as you can see,
everything we do hereat global
dynamics is about pushingthe boundaries--
of the scientificfrontier.
Yes,I read the brief.
But we both knowwhat it's really about.
Cranking out the best war toysbefore our
enemies do.That'll primeyour funding pump.
I know.
And our px-319 projectwill revolutionize
the way we engageenemies in battle.
So you keep telling me.
How about we skip the sciencefair
and get right to it then?
We're preparing a simulatedfield
test as we speak.Should be ready...
a little later.
Then I suppose we'll seeabout your funding...
I may be overreacting,but four years,
he has never,ever been late.
Let's do this.
jo,put the gun away.
And walk intoa potential trap.
I don't think so.
She's not normallythis high-strung.
She has some issues.
No signs of a break-in.
Wow,what a relief.
Did you see anythinglast night?
- Last nht?
- Movie night.
Ah,right.
- jo?
- What are you implying?
Nothing.
Can you killthe flashlight?
I'm investigatinga crime scene,
following procedure.
Maybe you shouldtry it sometime.
Can you maybe dial it down till we
figure out that there's been a crime?
Obviously I can't dust thatfor prints now.
Or that.
- Wallet and pda.
- Well,he probablyhasn't gone far.
Unless he was taken.
By force.
Against his will.
Okay,no more coffeefor you.
- Is that blood?
- Yeah.
And it leads that way.
Let's go.
Yeah,he's justpulling in now.
Good.
Beverly,I am not asking you to do
anything inappropriate.
Of course not. I'll just keep my eyes
and ears open like you said.
he has a tremendous amount of say over our funding.
It's all in the town's best interests.
I completely understand.
What do you thinkyou're doing?
Nothing,congressman.
Then what's in your hand?
Nothing.
Really?
Don't lie.
I was just looking for-- you're hurting me.
Then scream.
You scream.
You remembered.
You're hard to forget.
Spencer!
Taggart,for god sakes,pick up.
Tag,where are you?
We're too late.
Spencer!
It's too narrowfor a tractor path.
Yeah,these crops have beenflattened,
not cut.
- Do you hear that?
- What?
What?
Spencer!
- Spencer,are you all right?
- What happened?
I can't--I can't talk about it.
Why not?
They're watching.
********,Your hands?
- They left me here.
- Who?
I--I can't-- I can't--
spencer.
You're not alone.
He's clearlytraumatized.
Well,maybe beverlycan reach him.
Yeah,all right,I'll take him there.
You okay?
No,but I will beonce he is.
********
- What do you think?
- He probably passed out.
Some friends playeda prank on him.
really?
Come on.
There's alwaysa logical explanation for...
these things.
Yeah,that soundedvery logical.
Okay,jo,what's your theory?
Well,it's a crop.
Yep.
And there's a circle in it.
No.
No,no,no.
I don't care how weirdthis town gets,
there's one thingthat I know,
and that's thatthere are no aliens.
Yeah,jack carter.
Oh,hey,allison.
That makes two today.
I know,I know,I know.
You don't want to hear about it.
Okay,I'm on my way.
Someone else disappeared.
Fargo.
That's one thing I canscratch off
my "to do" list.
Or keep it on therefor later.
We're clean?
Nothing about whatwe just did is clean.
You know whatI'm talking about.
I sweep every roomevery hour.
No one can hear us.
The consortium believesthe artifact
was excavated and moved.
- To eureka?
- To section five.
Well,even you can't getaccess to that.
No.
But nathan stark can.
You think he'll justtake you on a tour?
If there's somethingworthwhile in it for him.
You'll need leverage.
That's why I'm here,dr.Barlow.
You know him betterthan anyone.
You'll need to barter with the one
thinghe loves more than anything.
- Allison blake.
- Science.
Stark livesto push boundaries.
To leave his mark.
He can't do thatwithout funding,so--
so his sin is pride.
I heard somewhere it comesbefore a fall.
please...
h-help him.
Spencer.
Spencer,you know me.
You're safe here.
You can talk to me.
No,let the bill die.
I'll reintroduce itwith my name on it.
We'll attach a rider.
That'll makeour mutual friends happy.
Okay.
Spencer,what is it?
Nothing.
I didn't see anything.
Okay,dr.Stark,I'm ready to be impressed.
You will not bedisappointed,congressman.
Allison,could you--
oh,okay. I'll catch up.
This way,congressman.
Hey,so,um,how's spencer?
Uh,he's been better.
How's fargo?
Last person to see fargowas dr.Sharat,and he missed
a critical meeting with stark.It's not like him.
Spencer was acting odd too.
I need to talk to dr.Sharat.
Uh,you know,that's gonna have to wait.
She's kind of in the middleof something important.
Well,so am I,and you called me,so--
by decade's end,wars will befought from
command screens such as this one.
There will no longerbe a need for
massive troops on the ground.
Dr.Sharat?
The px-319 transmitsa low-frequency signal
that delivers a subconsciousmessage of fear
and paranoia to amygdala deep in the brain,
causing the enemy turn against one another
in a violent rage,as this demonstration will show.
Um,just one moment.
a violent rage?
This is worth 80 million?
dr.Sharat?
The satellite's telemetrymust still be off.
- Still?
- Fargo didn't tell you?
We had a meeting.
He didn't show up.
Just--just give me a few minutes.
That's all right,dr.Sharat.
I've seen enough.
Dr.Stark,a word.
So I understand you spoketo douglas
fargo this morning.
The man's lost his mind.
If you find him,shoot him.
I'll take that as a yes.
Thank you for your time.
Nice monkeys.
Carter.
Whoa,whoa,whoa.
Vincent did what?
Perfect.
- Vincent just--
- no,I don't want to hear it.
Jo,I need you to get downto cafe diem.
Vincent disappearedduring the lunch rush.
Jo,come in.
Over.
Jo.
Okay,today's officiallymissing persons day.
But you don'twant to hear it.
A day or two of quiet wasn'tan
unreasonable request.
Look,nathan,you need an allyon
the defense committee.
I'm ready to be that ally,but you've
got to show mesomething worthwhile.
And I will have that demoready
for you shortly.
Forget the demo.
I'm talking aboutsection five.
Access to section fiveis by special
clearance only.
Which you can give me.
Nathan...
I want youto get your funding.
But I'm not justgonna rubber stamp a multibillion
dollar budgetlike my predecessors have.
And I can'tin good conscience
support something I've never seen.
It's that simple.
There you are.
Been trying to raise youall morning.
Got it under control.
Really? Because every timeI turn around
someone elsehas gone missing.
Fargo.
Now vincent.
Okay,look,I know.
And I know what needsto be done.
What I don't knowis why you insist
on telling mehow to do it.
- What is your problem?
- My problem is you.
Sheriff cobb treated melike a partner,
not an appendage.
When something goes wrongaround here,
people look to me.
They don't know you.
They don't trust you.
Because you don't trust me.
You've been on a tearsince day one.
I think you needto back off.
Okay,I'm sorry you're pissedbecause
you didn't get the job.
But right now,I really don't care.
We have to findthese people.
And I know,we're going to,but we
have to work together.Okay?
Are you with me?
All right.
We'll work together.
Okay.
Good.
So we're okay?
Yeah.
We're okay.
Okay.
Carter
Carter,wake up!
What the hell are you doing?
What am i doing?
I found it outby the crop circle.
I think spencer spentthe whole night
rolling it all overthe fields to make them.
That explains whyhis hands are so messed up.
It's a little difficult to breathe
with you camped outon my diaphragm.
Right.
Sorry.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Jo.
It was jo.
Jo hit you?
Yeah,with the butt of an mps auto
assault12 shotgun.
Or a model 50tactical takedown rifle.
Damn,I'm nevergonna pass the test.
Oh,no.
Tell me this wasn'tfilled with weapons.
- No,no,it wasn'T.
- You're lying to me,aren't you?
- Oh,big time.
- What is going on?
Well,let's see.
Um,spencer thinks alienshave landed.
Vince and fargo are missing.
And jo's gone...
G.I. Joe.
You think they'reall together?
I think they were togetherat spencer's party,
and something happened.
That,or we are beinginvaded by aliens.
Henry,please tell meyou don't
believe in aliens.
I believein occam's razor.
It's the basis formethodological reductionism.
Oh,yeah.
Slowly,still dizzy.
Okay,given two equallypredictive theories,
you choose the one thathas fewer assumptions.
So,a tree has fallenin the forest after a storm.
First hypothesis holds thatthat tree
was blown down by the storm.
Second rivalhypothesis claims that that storm
forcedan alien spaceship to crash into the tree.
- See?
- No.
I need to look closerat spencer's trailer.
I'll go.
Okay.
That'll give me a chanceto get over to beverly'S.
What for?
We've got four people who are
probably together,and definitely armed.
Spencer's the missingmember of that team.
I think they're headedover there.
- Be careful.
- You too.
welcome to section five.
You're doingthe right thing,dr.Stark.
I'm counting on it.
Step onto the gridfor identity verification.
Um,that'sa radiation symbol.
Once you enter the chamber,
we'll breach containment.
You'll have 15 secondsto view the artifact.
Any longer will exceedexposure limits.
You're notgoing in with me?
We could onlyafford one suit.
Openingthe doors now.
believe it or not,congressman,
it's terrestrial in origin.
We just don't know who created it.
My god.
That's one theory.
Then...
we strike.
Hard and fast.
Your basic grab and go.
He won't be alone,so watch your asses.
Let's move out.
What makes you thinkjo and the
others are coming for spencer?
Occam's razor.
You're spending way too muchtime with henry.
Borrowed thisfrom section four.
I want to stop 'em,not vaporize 'em.
It's a pep.
Pulse energy projectile rifle.
It's for crowd control.
Completely non-lethal.
- Did you passthat weapons test?
- It's notthat hard,carter.
- Allison,sheriff,what is going on?
- Where's spencer?
Inside.
He's getting worse.
- What happenedto your head?
- Had a trust issue.
Their leader is here.
He looks human,but it's just a guise.
You can see it.
Hideous,under the skin.
We will not let anythinghappen to you,
spencer.
Will we,sheriff?
No.
I'm gonna stay in positionedhere in the foyer.
Allison,why don't youtake the back and pep
the hell out ofanything that comes from behind.
Okay.
He picked eurekafor a reason.
"He"?
he can't be trusted.
I--I need to--I need to go.
We have to captureand interrogate him.
He must be stopped.
- Who?
- Their leader.
He's infiltratedour government,
and now he's herehiding in plain sight.
- Oh,jeez.
- what?
He's talking aboutthe congressman.
He is?
Spencer's not their target.
Faraday is.
That...
I don't even knowwhat to call it.
It could changeeverything.
It already has.
Fargo?
What the hell are you do--
Have you lostyour minds?
Deputy!
Fargo!
Who are you people?
The question is,who are you?
All right,that's--
No.
Nope.
Call carter.
Henry,give ussome good news.
They were watching a moviecalled
they came to conquer.
Don't tell me.
Alien invasion.
Invasion,abduction,dissection.
This movie's got it all.
okay.Still,it's a big leap from watching
a movie to thinking it's the real thing.
we're talking about spencer here.
I'm assuming he didn't get this at blockbuster.
Not even close.
Looks like he hijackeda satellite
signal to intercepta digital broadcast.
Then he bounced the signal...
off a global dynamics satellite
to cover his tracks.
Oh.
"Oh." Is that a good "oh"or a bad "oh"?
the number of the satellite is gd-85.
Oh,no.
Don't tell me. That's the one thatscrewed
up your monkey test.
They lost the satellite signalfor
a few hours friday night.
- I'm assuming--
- spencer got it.
- There's nathan's car.
- henry,we gotta go.
Nathan.
- Are you all right?
- ********
What happened?
Taggart,his deputy,and my assistant--ohh--
took faraday.
Yeah,they're infected with your
paranoia-inducingmonkey beam.
Oh,impossible. It was sent from a
secureglobal dynamics satellite.
No,possible.
Spencer hacked into it.
If anything happensto faraday--
well,it won't now that we know
where they took him.
Where did they take him?
Well,where would you go if you were
about to doan autopsy on an alien?
Taggart's lab.
I'm callingglobal security detail.
No,you're not.
A crazy cabal is aboutto dissect
a U.S. Congressman. I am.
They're not crazy.
They're paranoid.
And if they see a bunchof people with weapons,
this is gonna get wacoreally fast.
My point exactly.
They're armedand dangerous.
I don't seeanother choice.
Can't you just reversethe paranoid thing?
You don't know how.
I know how to savea U.S. Congressman.
Carter!
This is stark.
Tell tactical commandI need a detail
sent to taggart'scompound.
Code black.
How many are you?
We know what you are.
We know where you're from.
And believe me,by the timeI'm done with you,
we'll knoweverything else.
- Have you come to harm us?
- What do you people want?
We want answers.
Set up a perimeter!
Standard breach formation! Let's go!
- Sheriff carter,please stay back.
- I need to get in there.
- No,he does not.
- Let me negotiate this.I know these guys.
So do I. Look,sheriff,
I don't like thisany better than you do.
But if something happensto that congressman,
what do you think'sgonna happen to eureka?
- We just need more time.
- Give us a chanceto talk to them.
Sorry,allison.
I can't risk it.
Okay.
If that's the waythis has to be.
Thank you for yourcooperation,sheriff.
Carter!
Sheriff,stop now!
Hold your fire.
Repeat,hold fire.
Tell your peopleto lay down their weapons.
I don't have any people!
He's right.
He's just the host.
The creature'sprotected inside.
How do we get it out?
We cut it out.
- Who is it?
- It's carter.
I'm unarmed.
Open the door.
And,uh,what is thisin reference to?
Taggart,I know you havethe congressman in there.
Copy that.
We have the shot,dr.Stark.
Don't do it,nathan.
Give him a chance.
You alone?
Oh,yeah.
Should we take the shot?
Hold fire.
We lost the target.
come in.
I hope he knowswhat he's doing.
Come out of the housewith your
hands on your heads.
Jo,any minute this placeis gonna be
swarmed by the only peopleon the planet
who are better armedthan you.
- We'll do what we have to.
- No,you're gonna get hurt.
Or worse.
we can't trust him.
He's one of them.
Then don't trust me.
Trust your own common sense.
oh,so what,I'm stupid now?
I know what I saw.
You guys...
are sufferingfrom a mass delusion.
Nice try,mate.
Think about it,jo.
What makes more sense?
That he's an alien?
Or that you guysare delusional?
Shots fired.
We need to move in.
- Not yet.
- I'm sorry,allison.
Go ahead.
Okay,who gave fargo a gun?
Prepare for full breach.
You were all watching a moviein spencer's
trailer called they came to conquer,right?
In which aliens invade a small bucolic
town in the pacific northwest.
Spencer saw their ship.
And he is their emissary.
Taggart,taggart!
What spencer saw was congressman
faraday'shelicopter arriving.
His trailer is directlybelow the flight path.
What time did you arrive?
Congressman.
Just after midnight.
Okay.
About the timethe party broke up?
Vincent?
Spencer bounced the movie off
a global dynamics weapons satellite
that was being used to beamwaves
of paranoia into lab monkeys.
There was a malfunction,wasn't there,fargo?
It failed.
That's why you took off.
Unfortunately,it didn't fail.
When spencer bounced the signal,
you became the lab monkeys.
We have the alienright here.
Get out of our way.
Maybe you do havean infiltrator.
But it's not him.
It's me.
I'm the new guy,right?
I didn't pass your test.
I didn't see how muchthis town needs you.
Fair.
But I need you too.
You're not an appendage,jo.
You're my partner.
And there's no onein this town that I'd rather
havewatching my back than you.And that's the truth.
So...
please.
Trust me.
We're coming out!
Hold your fire!
Hold fire.
Everyone stand down.
They're unarmed!
Everybody's okay!
So everybody's okay?
Oh,no,they'refreakin' bug nuts.
Restraints now.
We reprogrammed the signal to stimulate
the brain'spleasure center.
I chose delivery footageeach should
find benign and peaceful.
Well,you sure know jo.
Congressman.
I trust thisunfortunate incident in no
way will affectour budget considerations.
I was abducted,threatened,and humiliated
by your people in your town on your watch.
But in spite of this incident,
what I saw in there yesterday takes precedence.
Dr.Stark.
- We'll be talking.
- I'm sure we will.
Ms.Blake.
So are we funded?
For now.
Guess I owe you one,sheriff.
Getting the congressman outrelatively unscathed.
a big one.
Thank you,carter.
By the way,I didn't do it for you.
You don't say.
multi-velocity xk exterminator.
Very good.
Bmfg liquidator.
- Type and sizeof magazine?
- Trick question.
It usessingle-chamber artillery.
Wow,carter.
Keep this up,you're gonna pass the exam.
Yeah,I don't know.
I tend to choke the exam.
Well,this is the exam.
The manual didn't say anythingabout
it having to be written,so I...
thanks for the tutoring.
Don't mention it.
You gonna get that?
I didn't think so.
Jack carter
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-gagegao
Eureka
Season 01 Episode 04