okay,this one's from me.
I told you guys,no gifts.
Who ever believes that?
Come on.
Open it already,bren.
Now we're spinning empty bottles oh!
It's the five of us oh,dana,this is adorable.
I told you you'd like it.
How can you tell it's a girl,mommy?
'Cause when I do this,she sounds just like you.
give me a hand,sweetie.
time to pack it on,girls.
Oh,and I'm supposedto be dieting.
One of the few good perks of being this huge is you can eat like a horse.
bring it on!
right here.
Dana
Hey.
No boys allowed!
I told you this wasa girls' party,babe.
from the national guard.
Oh,my god.
I'm being deployed?
But you havea kid.
How soon?
Uh,three weeks.
Who's goingto take care of lindsey?
I will,baby.
Hey,I'm a baker.
Probably get stationed in oneof saddam's old palace sgrilling filetsfor the generals.
Right.
Well,here.
I'll slice the tart.
Here,honey.
You're goingaway,mommy?
I'll be backbefore you know it.
In no time at all.
That veronicain the car?
We're on our wayto school.
She's pouting becauseI won't let her come with.
Eight-year-old wantsto see a crime scene?
She's a weird kid.
- Hey,boss.
- Morning.
We got a floater?
Not exactly.
Marine unit was doing a trawl of the delaware,turned this up.
Is that an arm?
Ran the serial number.
Matches the prostheticof a missing iraq war veteran.
Guy couldn't catch a break,huh?
Gal.
Dana taylor.
Went missing three months afterreturning from the middle east.
How long could someonewith a missing arm stay lost?
You ever see the fugitive?
These things don't come cheap.
It's a custom fit,titanium.
Not somethingyou'd just toss.
Not on purpose.
So where'd the rest of her go?
Well,if the armwas in the river,odds are the body is,too.
Divers are coming out.
Not really a "bringyour daughter to work day."
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-colleen3684
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Cold Case
Season 4 Episode 02
lady soldier,huh?
Yup.
Asgot to wonder.
wonder what?
Remember the girl in iraq,had that guy on a leash?
Yeah.
what's your point?
I just don't get these chicks that want to tote guns and take prisoners fora living,no offense.
Dana taylor,30.
Three months in iraq.
Joined the guard to payfor cooking school.
Seven and a half years into an eight-year bid.
Yeah.Probably never thoughtshe'd get called up.
Lost her right armin a grenade attackon her truck outside fallujah.
Ribbon of valor for heroism-- pulled anothersoldier out of the wreckage.
When'd she get back?
June 2004.
Disappeared octoberthe same year.
Last to see wasthe husband,geoff.
Says she went for a walkthat night,never came back.
Lame story.
Yeah,so lame it could be true.
Though he and dana were goingthrough a rough patch.
So maybe she took a headerinto the river on her own?
Or maybe the husband pulled a scott peterson.
Valens upstairs?
Taking lost time.
Didn't say why.
Uncle scotty's here!
What's up?
How you doing,em?
Oh,you're so big.
Where's your momand dad,huh?
hey,scotty
What?You run out of corn flakes or something?
I can't visit my own brotherwithout being abused,hmm
orange juice was sour.
We had to throw it away.
No kidding.
Yeah,enoughwith that,emilio.
- What's up?
- Hi,mommy.
Uh,you know,maybewe could take a walk,or...
oh,papi,a walk.
I won't rough him uptoo bad,hmm?
So,something happen?
you remembercoach fitzpatrick?
What,the boxing guywho taught classes at it's okay.
Give your moma hug.
Well,I will go down with this ship He... got picked up.
A lewd act with a minor.
Da's really gunning for him,and he's got a long listof...
witnesses.
Are you serious?
you're on the list,mikey.
你在名单上
That-that don't make sense.
- No?
- No.
But to put this guy away,they're gonna need all the ammo they can get.
Hey,god bless 'em,but I can't help.
Okay.
- I just told 'emI'd check with you.
- Told who?
The peoplewho got it wrong,I guess.
Dana never tookoff that arm.
She wanted to be as normalas possible.
Like before.
Before iraq.
She come homedifferent?
If you had your arm blown off,wouldn't you?
Just asking a question.
Yes.She was different.
When I got back from vietnam,my wife and I had some troubles.Adjusting.
We were working it out.
Till she walked out the doorthat nightand I became a widower.
She happen to mentionshe was headedtoward the river that night?
She used to go onlong walks alone.
Never said where she went.
Any problemswith friends,neighbors?
No way.
Fishtown'sa military neighborhood.
Dana went over,did her duty.
People respected that.
I hate to ask,butsuicide?
I thoughtwe were finding our way back.
Maybe dana couldn't make it.
Like you said,she came back different.
And it...
threw me.
*I know you think thatI shouldn't still love you*
You know whatI miss the most?
Your leg?
the chow?
The danger.
*Well,I'd still have felt it  where's the sense in that?*
- Hey,linds!
- Mommy!
*I promise I'm not tryingto make your life harder*
they couldn'tput your arm back on?
Or return to where we were
no,baby,they couldn'T.
It's okay.
Give your moma hug.
*Well,I will go downwith this ship*
We're all goingto get used to it.
Yeah,sure.
I don't like it.
It's weird.
Lindsey!
Hey,it's just an arm,okay?
- I got another one.
- Okay.
I'm so glad to be back.
很高兴可以回来
We're glad,too.
*I know I left too much mess *
hey,tommy.
Neighborhood'sbeen pretty sleepywithout you aroundraising some.
Been busykicking iraqi ass.
Whoa,tommy.
Sorry.
You...
forget.
It's okay.
*I understand if you can'ttalk to me again *
When are you coming home?
In a week.
I'll have a prosthetic by then.
Be 100%.
*And if you live by the rulesof "it's over"*
well,90%.
*Well,I will go downwith this ship...*
I couldn't look at her.
And she knew it.
So,maybe that hurt enough,she put herself in the river.
The person who'd knowbetter than me?
Tommy.
Tommy from the hospital?
Yeah,he wasjust a guywe knew from the neighborhood,
but after whatthey went through,he was her new best friend.
Was he in the rpg attack,too?
He was the one she saved.
If dana had any secrets,it's tommy who'd know 'em.
Yasasme and dana fought in iraq,93 days and nights.
Brings you together,huh?
In a wayyou can't understand.
Her cell phone records showa lot of calls to you,tommy,after you both got back.
Includes the nightshe disappeared.
Uh,it's 'causewe talked every night.
It's not whatyou think.
We talked about the war,rehab.
Frank.
Who's frank?
Our friend.
Died in the attack.
That you anddana survived?
What'd youtalk aboutthe nightshe disappeared?
Well,the usual.
Night terrors.
Seeing frank in our dreams.
How the thanksyou get for fightingis people back here lookingat you like you're a freak.
Sounds hardto live with.
No one else gets it,so we'd tell each other.
This is the straw,final straw in the...
I wrote the guard.
Yeah?
Asked them to send meback over.
- You're kidding.
- Nope.
I'm walkinggood as new.
Why not?
- you okay?
- Yeah.
It was just...
oh,dana,they're precious.
It's the best I can doat the moment.
They're sweet.
- Brenda?
- No.
Look at that face.
I see frankevery time I look at her.
Missed you at his memorial.
I heard it was beautiful.
Out on the bridge...
I guess you had somethingbetter to do?
I didn't thinkyou wanted me there.
Oh,you got that right.
So what should ihave done?
Just don't actlike we're friends.
We're not.
And we never will be again.
Brenda,you've had a few...
you blew it off,too,tommy,so you just save it!
It's hard on us,too.
You didn't lose anyone.
We lost frank.
You don't have a babywith no father.
I can't standto see you alivewhen he is nothingbut ashesat the bottom of that river.
*A simple mistakestarts the hardest time I promiseI'll do anything...*
why was brendalaying this on dana?
Dana was driving the truckwhen...
so she blames herfor her husband dying?
But brenda wasn'tin her right mind.
She was drinking all the time,and half crazyover losing frank.
Crazy enough to kill someone?
what,are you tryingto smoke us out?
A nudge wouldhave worked.
I was tryingto make breakfast.
Oh,maybe I'll takea rain check.
in my family,"cooked" pretty much meantwhatever was spinningunder the heat lampat 7-11,so...
so I guess this is it then.
go ahead,pack your bags and leave.
It's been nice knowing you.
Get the dooron your way out,huh?
Yeah,sure thing.
Adios.
Cut and run.
You wouldn't be the first.
Who left you,lil?
What?
My dad.
I was six.
Yeah.
I always thought he'd come back.
My high school graduation,I'm sitting there,looking for min the bleachers.
Did he show?
What do you think?
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Like I said,you wouldn't be the first.
Yeah,well,you know,maybe I'll stay,see if I can't be the last.
We appreciate youtaking the time.
You said it was about dana.
Did you find her?
Her arm.
We're thinking the restof her might be dead.
you missed the sensitivitytraining,did ya?
Fourth of july,2004,things got ugly between you two.
I was reelingover frank's death.
Not for nothing,I wasa few glasses into the chablis.
That can fuel the fire.
I was grieving,not homicidal.
And I was homewith my six-month-oldthe night she went missing.
Well,a six-month-oldcan't alibi you,bren.
How would killing dana help me?
Wouldn't bring frank back.
Murder ain't logical like that.
Look,I apologized to her.
After the hangover.
Yeah.
Things got back to normalfor us again.
Of course,going"back to normal" not so easy.
No.
Like a lot of guys coming back,it seemed like part of danawas stuck in iraq.
said mr. Dalai lama  another sister'sshooting heroin tomorrow...
how come daddy'snot driving me to gymnastics?
'Cause mommy's home now.
And this was alwaysour thing,right?
Daddy always lets me situp front.
Why don't youbraid lucy's hair,huh?
So I stopped drinking.
Yeah?
After the wayI talked to you...
oh,come on.
It was understandable.
I'm goingto grief counseling,to talk about frank...
- missing him.
- Sure.
You thought about it?
Counseling?
Me?
For what?
Geoff says you nevereven talkedabout the attack.
No.
I'd like to knowwhat happened.
We were driving.
Like we are now.
Orders are you keep moving;you never stop.
What was frank doing?
He was looking out.
You always have to look out'cause the one thingout of placecan be the thing that...
"the thing that" what?
********* what are you doing *********
Mommy,don't!
********* kill me? *********
*****,stop!
********* ******freak.
I'm sorry.
I keep *************
it's okay,sweetie.
She's always doing that,making people mad.
From happy homemakerto road rage case.
That's quite a flip.
Combat vet,classic ptsd.
I realized that day thatthe dana I knew was gone.
T1I wonder who elseshe went off on.
Sounds like this daughtercould tell some tales.
Do you know where my mom went?
We're tryingto find T.
That's why we're here.
Do you rememberwhen she came backfrom the war,lindsey?
Yeah,she didn'thave an arm.
We heard she'd getupset sometimes,make people mad.
Yeah.
Do you rememberany of those people?
No.
You won't get in troubleif you tell us.
Maybe one man.
Okay.
At my school assembly.
He sat behind my mom.
In this time of unrest,we honor our own war heroes,
who put themselves in harm's wayto keep you safe.
There are currently...
what's with you?
My petition to go backwas rejected.
I got medically discharged.
It was a long shot.
It was also my last shot.
- At what?
- I just...
got nothing,no one.
Here.
Hold this for me.
And her daughter is inmiss connor's third grade class.
Please welcomelindsey taylor's momcorporal dana taylor.
I was in iraq for three months.
I drove a supply truck.
I was scared going over,but was ready to do my duty.
Then,this happened to me.
Now I...
I have confused feelingsabout the war.
So instead of giving youa speech,maybe I'll justtake some questions.
Did you ever waste anyone?
No.
But I watched my good friendget wasted.
His name was frank.
One second,he was telling a joke,and in the next,his...
his blood and his insideswere all over the truck...
all over me.
It's not like a video gameor a movie.
It breaks your heartright in half.
Our next guest has beenin the navy his entire career.
What kind of soldier are you?
The kind that tells the truth.
I'm going backfor my second tour in a week.
How do you thinkmy kid feels now?
Maybe we shouldgo,linds...
You should have stayedin the damn kitchen.
You know that?
You got no businesstrying to do a man's job.
I'm a soldier,same as you...
His son charlie is inmr. Levin's fifth grade class.
Someone oughtto teach you a lesson.
So please welcomelieutenant jamal ross.
who was this man?
Penny kozlowski's dad.
That helps alot,lindsey.
Maybe my mom went away'cause of me.
Why would she do that?
'Cause maybe she found outI thought her arm was scary.
You know what,lindsey?
If you were my girl,I'd be so proud.
You would?
Yeah,becauseyou're brave.
I know your mom could see thatjust like I can.
Thanks a lot,sir.
Sounds like this kozlowskididn't like girlsfighting his war.
What say we find outhow much?
Josh kozlowski?
Who's asking?
Philly homicide.
It's about dana taylor.
Homicide,huh?
Not surprised,the mouth on her.
We heard you werea real fanof her speechat your daughter's assembly.
Gi janes.
Some jobs women just can't do.
Not disagreeing,but why go after dana?
'Cause that bitch traumatizedevery kid in the place.
So maybe you retaliated.
Agg assault does seemto be your specialty.
That taylor broadneeded to be shut up.
And if I was the one who did it,I'd tell you.
All the same,we got to verifyyour whereaboutswhen she disappeared.
I keep great calendars.
You tell me the date,I'll tell you where I was.
Deal.
They sayyou're onlysupposed to cutto the first five-leaf.
Is that right?
My grandma wasa green thumb.
Always said that's how you getdouble the bloom in return.
That's a good tip.
Got any tips for me?
You know yourhusband's temperall too well,I bet.
Got anything to add?
- I knew that woman. - Dana.
Well,I knew of her.
- Meaning? - I knew her husband.
paula,who's your friend?
This is geoff.
His wife dana's a soldier.
- Hi,jeff.Hi,jeff. - Hi.
Welcome to oursupport group.
Tell 'em about her.
Dana-- well,she's been my girlsince we were 15.
We got a kid.
Thank god 'cause that's allI have to hang onto right now.
I mean,I'm not even allowedto know where dana is.
Just that she'S...
over theresomeplace.
I worry all the time and...
I...I guess,just feel kind of lost.
Why don't we takea coffee break?
*Time and time again I'm half stalled*
helps to talk,right?
- Feel like a fool. - Why?
'Cause I'm a man,paula.
Sitting aroundexpressing feelings...
I know you're a man.
*Just give a second thought what if we don't get caught.*
So geoff had a side dish.
A lot of people have jodys.
Jodys?
Someone to keep company withtill your soldier comes home.
Meaning it wasn'tserious between them?
Except paula's husbandkept re-upping,so she was alone a lot.
My opinion,she wanted something realwith geoff.
So his wife coming homewas a problem.
And when paula wants something,she's pretty determined.
Your husband'soverseas,paula?
Ass-deep in the sunni triangle.
Not exactly a garden spot.
Desert air mustappeal to him. He keeps re-enlisting.
lonely nights?
I keep busy.
Like with geoff taylor?
Me and geoffmight've had a thing.
A thing.
Like an affair?
No,we'd get togetherand do crosswords.
And dana,being your friend,didn't count for much.
Wartime. Rules change.
So you and geoff are hitting it,then dana comes home,and he startsflying right.
You're out in the cold.
You know the old sayingabout the woman scorned.
Except I wasn'T.
The affair kept going?
Geoff was patient.
But a month aftershe came home,dana still wouldn'tlet him touch her.
So pretty soon,he's back in your arms.
And then it all blew up.
Button up already. Got to get out of here.
My house tomorrow?
what are wedoing,paula?
Living.
Yeah.
We could make it permanent.
Sometimes I think...
what,baby?
I get dark thoughts.
About changing my life.
no.
I-I thoughtyou were at rehab.
Lindsey's school called. She has a fever.
Look,dane...
so I've been busting my asstrying to learnhow to brush my teeth again,
and this is what you're doing?
- I'm sorry. - Yeah,me,too.
But,hey,let me make it right.
I'll pack up and get lost. Leave you to it.
- That's not gonna happen.
- And I'll take lindsey with me,
'cause there's no way I'm letting this bitchset an examplefor my little girl.
Dana...
I can't believeyou threw it all away.
You probably thinkI'm some bimbo home-wrecker.
Pretty much.
He was lonely. So was I.
And then danacleared the way for you.
Once she busted us,it was over.
Over for her,too.
She disappeared that night,leaving geofkind of single.
Like I said,that wasthe end of him and me.
But no worries,I've got a new jody now.
Congratulations.
You can go,paula.
Didn't geoff say his little girlwas all he had to hang onto?
Yeah.If dana was gonna leaveand take the kid...
maybe those dark thoughtsgot the best of him.
didn't tell us about your girlfriend,jeff.
excuse me?
***** Paula.
Sounds likeyou found out anyway.
Didn't want to sharethat piece of the puzzle?
Would you?
If a murder copwas asking,yeah,I'd come clean.
Ashamed enough of something,you do a lot to hide it.
Not to mention it gives youmotive for offing your wife.
I didn't kill dana.
I loved her.
You lovedyour daughter,too,and dana wantedto take her away.
Look...
whatever punishment I had comingmy way,I was gonna take it.
But something good actuallycame out of all that crap.
Oh,yeah? What?
We finally talked about it.
About...?
What happened over there.
How's she doing?
Fever's down.
Helps her sleep.
She always loved this.
Still does.
You're going,huh?
What happened,dane?
I don't know.
It's like I lost you over there.
I'm sorry.
Look,I'll goif that'swhat you want.
But first...
tell me...
what happenedover there,when you got hurt.
- You don't want to know.
- Yeah,I do.
You'll hate me.
I could never hate you.
that ribbon of valor--I don't deserve it.
Why not?
What happened to frankwas my fault.
how's that possible?
We'd just madea delivery.
We weredriving back...
frank was tellinga stupid joke,and then suddenly,there was something in the road.
- Someone. - Who?
a little girl.
And they tell you,you see anyone in the road,you...
you just run 'em down.
Even a kid?
They use kidsto get the convoys to stop.
but I didn't see a trap;I saw a little girl,who could'vebeen lindsey.
So I slowed down,and that's when we got hit.
Dane. Dane.
Typical girl soldier,right?
That wasn't a girl thing.
It-it was a human thing.
I would've done the same.
Baby,an rpgkilled frank,not you.
I don't want that ribbon.
It's keeping me in a placeI don't wanna be.
- So get rid of it. - And frank.
We gotta say good-bye to him.
Okay.
Can you stay with lindsfor a couple hours?
Sure. Of course.
I'll be right here.
Yeah. Good.
Dane?
You're my girl.
I was praying she'd come homeand want to start over.
But she nevermade it back.
You didn't go with her?
No.
So what did she mean by "we"?
I don't know.
I always assumedshe went on her walks alone.
tommy.
He didn't go tofrank's memorial either.
And he hadthe ribbon of valor.
So where would they goto say good-bye?
Ashes were in the river,right?
We know why dana wentout that night,tommy.
Oh,yeah?
To ditch that ribbon of valor.
Put the war behind her.
Any thoughts how shemight've done that?
Not really.
Want my guess?
She threw itin the river.
Where danaended up,too. Probably.
Why are you telling me?
'Cause she called youthat night.
Asked you to meet her.
Bring the ribbon.
She knew you both neededto lay frank to rest.
So what if that's true?
Seems like somethingyou'd mention,unless something wentreal wrong that night.
What I don't get?
Dana saved you.
Pulled you from that truck.
Why would youwant to hurt her?
I wouldn'T.
That is the last thing I'd want.
Well,I believe you,tommy,'cause I think you wanted moreof her than you could have.
What do you mean?
Iraq. Rehab.
All those late-night callswhen you got home.
Brings you together in a wayother people can't understand.
Hard not to get attachedto someone after all that.
But she was married.
Geoff was messing around on her.
She told me that night.
And you saw your opening.
seemed likeshe felt the same.
When we'd talk,you know?
I got her...
and she got me.
And no one else did.
I thought it was gonna bethe start of a new life.
Instead it was the end.
what are you doing?****** of danger again?
river looks beautiful from up here.
Yeah.
did you bring it?
what are you going to do with it?
Move on.
This is about what was.
Memories,right?
I guess.
It's time to leave 'em behind.
Rest in peace,frankie.
New chapter,huh?
Right.
So how about you and me?
You and me?
There's a reasonwe talk every night,dane.
Why we never wanna hang up.
Tommy...
we went through a lot.
And now it's part of our lives.
- I have a family. I can'T...
- he cheated on you.
I know.
And maybe we'll neverrecover from that,but we're gonna try.
When I'm standing right here?
Tommy,we almostdied together.
Of course thatbrought us close.
I got nothin' else,dane.
You got me.
- As your friend. - No.That's not enough.
We're vets. That's special.
Oh,bull. That's nothing.
I can'T... hold on to that.
We're findingour way back,tommy.
And we're gonna make it.
You will.
Not me.
Not me!
No...!
Dana! No!
Dana,no!
Dana!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-colleen3684 -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-