- Previously on The O.C.:
- Are we doing this?
It's not like we haven't before.
You can't drink, you can't have sushi.
What are you, pregnant?
One of our partners went behind
our backs to a friend at city council...
...and got them to deny us
the liquor license.
So he's profiting from our loss.
He's Caleb Nichol.
You're upset because
she's marrying Dad.
Yeah, for his money.
Last time I talked to Marissa,
she was planning on moving in with us.
Manipulate me?!
Hold my daughter hostage?!
Theresa's pregnant.
And it might not be Eddie's.
Thor. It's a strong name.
- No one's gonna mess with Thor.
- Thanks.
Seth's a good name for a boy too.
Although, at Camp Tokaho,
I was often referred to as a girl...
...so I guess it works either way.
- Can we not play the name game?
- Right. Sorry. It's premature.
She's probably not even pregnant.
- Maybe you shoot blanks.
- I feel much better.
Sorry. If you're in no mood to kid,
l..."Kid."
That's an unfortunate choice of a word.
- We don't even know if this kid is mine.
- We don't even know if there is a kid.
How much faith can you put
in a pee swab?
Seth, don't say "swab."
Ryan Atwood just made a joke.
Yeah. Gotta keep
a sense of humor, right?
Hey, stuffed in a locker, shoes full
of the water-polo team's urine...
...never funnier.
- Good to know.
Yeah. In fact, having you around
to defend me...
...I've kind of gotten soft
not having anyone picking on me.
So really been no need
for the Seth Cohen retaliatory zinger.
My dad hates cilantro.
If you put cilantro on anything...
...I may be uninvited to the wedding.
Somebody get me some cilantro.
Colored lights? No way.
White lights only...
...because colored lights remind my father
of a carnival, and he hates carnies.
Note to self: Hang with carnies.
Yeah. Great.
I'll see you on Saturday. Thanks. Bye.
Well, the wedding rehearsal is confirmed.
This wedding is actually happening.
Never have people deserved
each other more.
I can't believe my dad is
walking with a black eye.
I know. That's because
Jimmy punched him.
If I had, he'd be walking
with a broken nose.
What are the odds of you
making up before the wedding?
I would say not good at all.
It's important to me.
A daughter wants her father to be happy
on his wedding day.
And here I was thinking it was
supposed to be the other way around.
Well, what if I...
...begged?
Groveled?
- Maybe cajoled?
- Oh, honey, come on.
He sabotaged my restaurant.
He committed fraud. There's no way
I could possibly forgive him.
Well, maybe I could pretend...
...to forgive him.
Maybe I could apologize
with my fingers crossed.
Hey, you're not at school.
Yeah, we were at the doctor's office.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah. It's fine.
I'm pregnant.
Well, except for that.
So it's official?
Yeah. It is.
And does she know who the father is?
No.
They don't like to do paternity
tests until the baby's born.
Too dangerous, I guess.
But there's a chance
that it could be yours?
- We were broken up.
- Oh, right.
No, totally.
- We were broken up for, like, a week.
- I'm sorry.
I wish I could take it back. Believe me.
If you wanna...
- You know, I'll understand.
- Like there's a choice.
I mean, if you're the father, then...
...well, you and Theresa...
- No. No, I want to help her out...
...but I also...
I want to make this work...
...between us.
These are decaf, right?
If they're not...
...I'm gonna be up for days. Thank you.
Thanks.
- I'm freaking out, Cohen.
- You're freaking out?
You hear about Ryan and Theresa?
What about my best friend?
- Princess Sparkle is freaking out?
- Marissa, dumb-ass.
I always get those two confused.
They have really shiny hair.
How can you even joke about this?
Because, I don't know, I have to.
I'm not emotionally equipped
to process this information.
It's not bad enough she has to live
with Lucifer and Julie?
- I get those two confused as well.
- What'll happen to Ryan and Marissa?
They're, like, the perfect couple.
Based on your parents' marriage,
I sort of understand that.
- I'm holding hot coffee, Cohen.
- Look, I don't know what's gonna happen.
I just wish there was something
I could do to help him.
We just got past all this drama...
...and this summer was supposed
to be all-time.
Yeah, well, now it's all up in the air.
- We're not having sex, by the way.
- Excellent.
There's not enough pain
and suffering already.
Excuse me.
Sorry about the wait.
Hi.
I wanted to see if you wanted to talk.
We're a little understaffed.
Eighty-five cents. Great. I'll put it
towards baby's college tuition.
If you want to talk about it... That.
Theresa, the register's broken.
Sorry.
Now, there's a portrait of a man
headed to the altar.
- What the hell do you want?
- No, it's not what I want.
It's what Kirsten wants.
D Átente. Peace.
- The promise of a feud-free wedding.
- You've come to the wrong groom.
You wanna apologize, do so,
but do it quick.
You have no idea how much cajoling
it took to get me here.
- I'm only here because of Kirsten.
- It's always because of Kirsten.
When you railroaded my dinner...
...was that because of her too?
- No, that one was for you.
So, what are you gonna do...
...when I'm not around to make you
feel better about yourself?
- You going somewhere?
- Maybe.
Like, say, San Quentin.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- What did you think I was doing in Vegas?
Besides flipping my restaurant
for a tidy sum?
I was trying to save the Newport Group.
Selling that property was supposed to
keep this company from going bankrupt.
Kirsten never said anything.
That's because residential real estate
is our only profitable division.
She doesn't know anything about the
bad investments, the debts, the losses.
Sell to somebody else. Robert Campbell
can't be the only buyer in town.
It doesn't mean as much to anyone else.
Campbell owns the rest of the coastline.
This property was the last piece
of the puzzle he was missing.
So that's why you wanted us
out of the restaurant so fast.
You sneaky...
...not-so-successful son of a bitch.
Enjoy it while you can.
I got the DA all over me again.
Must smell blood in the water.
Have a nice day, Sandy.
- Hey, kiddo.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
You know, preparing to move
into the house on Haunted Hill.
You know...
...you don't have to do this.
I'd sooner give back the check...
...than have you move in with your mom.
- Then you're left with nothing.
You'd have to move to Phoenix.
Well, at least this way,
I can still see you.
Life just wasn't this complicated
when I was growing up.
Yeah, I know. It feels like we're
constantly being punished for something.
- Mom just keeps on ticking.
- Hey.
Your mom has to wake up every
morning and be Julie Cooper.
That is punishment enough.
Come on. Let's take a break.
What do you say?
Go down to the pier and get a Balboa Bar?
I can't.
I've just got so much to do.
- Does Theresa's mom know?
- No, not yet.
Theresa's not ready to tell her.
Besides, it'll make it feel too real.
I have news for you. It's real.
- Sandy.
- There's no point in sugarcoating it.
You know how many unwed mothers
come through my office?
We all know how real this is.
- Can we just eat dinner?
- All right.
Hey, look...
...we are what we are,
and we'll help you through this.
- We can do it together.
- Hey, man.
They raised me, okay? Proof pudding.
Speaking of pudding, Mother,
do I have any tapioca on tap?
- You are king of the segue.
- I just love pudding. It's so fun to say.
Pudding. Pudding.
Our child-rearing skills speak
for themselves.
Pudding.
Oh, hi, sweetie.
I have my secret recipe, takeout.
- No, thanks. I ate at work.
- Pudding.
- Ryan, can we talk?
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
So, what's going on?
I've been thinking.
We haven't really talked about it.
You're not ready for this.
- I'm not ready for this.
- Yeah, I know, but we can...
I can't do this.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna have it.
The baby.
You're not?
You can tell the Cohens...
...but I can't tell my mom.
Hey, you're off the hook.
I have to go down and renew
my dock fees for my boat, man.
You wanna go down there with me,
maybe take her out for a spin?
- Sure, sounds good.
- No, it sounds great.
Come on. We haven't even been on
since last summer.
Remember last summer? We were
just getting to know each other.
Now look at us. Best friends.
Brothers, even.
What do brothers do, Ryan?
You know what brothers do?
Brothers sail.
What brothers sail?
The Wright Brothers.
Before they invented airplanes.
How do you think they got everywhere?
The Ringling Brothers...
...with their chimps and their tigers.
It was like Noah's Ark on that boat.
- Hanson. Playing cruise lines.
- Okay, we'll go sailing.
No, get excited, okay?
You dodged a bullet.
Not that... Not that... It's... You...
Bullet.
I just think that it's cool.
Not so much cool, but...
Okay, I just... I don't know.
I thought you'd be relieved.
No. No, I am. It's complicated.
Too complicated for banter
about boats and Hanson?
- Hey.
Can I get you anything?
Tea? Toast? Dramamine?
No, thanks.
I don't want to be late.
I'm only working a half-day today.
I have an appointment
at Planned Parenthood.
Is Ryan gonna go with you?
No, I haven't told him.
He's freaked out enough as it is.
What about your mother?
No, I can't.
She's extremely religious.
Well, you'll need someone there
to listen to the doctors...
...because you're gonna have
a million things on your mind.
You won't want to drive.
I'm an excellent driver
and amazing parker.
Thanks. I hate parallel parking.
So how are you doing with it?
- Are you relieved, sad, disappointed?
- All of the above. Yes.
- Well, did she say when she was gonna...?
- Soon.
I guess.
Well, then at least maybe everything
can go back to normal.
Not that anything around here
ever is normal.
More normal than this.
I think we should spend this whole
summer just being normal.
- We won't hold Seth to that, will we?
- No. No, that would be impossible.
I was talking more about us.
You're just full of surprises.
I hear water. And by the way, Caleb...
...we should hold on to this blindfold.
- Oh, gosh.
- Good to know.
Oh, my God! It's a palace.
Fit for a queen?
Oh, Cal. It's amazing.
I built it just for you.
It's more than I ever
could have imagined.
I want to live here forever.
Oh, I've missed you.
It's been too long.
- You're talking to a boat, Seth.
- I talk to a plastic horse too...
...but that never worries anyone.
- It worried me.
Hey.
I forgot about this.
This compass is gonna lead me
all the way to Tahiti.
Yeah, whatever happened to that
big plan to sail to Tahiti?
You showed up, man.
Suddenly, I had much less reason to flee.
Newport became kind of...
- Kind of all right.
- Yeah?
- Could've done it in 42 days, though.
- Guess we'll never know.
Yeah, but now that we've got...
...the Summer Breeze back in action,
we can sail to Catalina.
We can take our ladies.
Catch fresh fish right off
the side of the boat.
Cook them right there.
Sounds good, man.
Sounds great.
So I'll take you
to your appointment tomorrow.
You're not taking any anesthetics, so you
don't have to worry about what to eat.
We'll get there about
a half an hour before...
...and fill out some forms.
Everyone there seems really nice.
I can't believe I'm actually doing this.
You don't have to.
Yeah, I do. I mean...
...I'm in high school, or I should be.
I make $ 11 a day in tips.
Not having this baby...
...makes the most sense.
You don't have to make the decision
that makes the most sense.
Right. Coming from you... I mean...
...your life is so together.
You know, you have
an amazing family...
...great job.
It's perfect.
Nothing's perfect.
Sometimes...
...things just happen.
Yeah, but never to someone
like you, right?
- I'm sorry. L...
- It's okay.
I don't regret the decision I made.
I just wish that when I was
trying to choose...
...there was someone there for me.
Whatever you decide...
...we're here for you.
Hi.
How you feeling?
Pretty lousy.
Remember that part last night
about me not having the baby?
As hard as it is to imagine
having a baby...
...I can't really imagine not having it.
So you're gonna have it.
I have to.
Well, what did you say to her?
I didn't say anything.
So all of a sudden she just decided
to change her mind?
No, it's all of a sudden that
she made all of her decisions.
What? You talked her
into having this child.
So I should let her make
a totally uninformed decision?
They're kids with nothing.
How can they start a family?
That's not our choice.
You know what Ryan's going through?
Not as well as I know
what she's going through.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
It's just, she's alone. She can't talk to
her mother. She's scared and confused.
All I did was listen.
- Oh, hey. You want some breakfast?
- No, thanks. I'll get something later.
I just want to see if Theresa
wants anything.
I should call my dad.
He has to be here by 8.
Have you talked to him?
He doesn't seem himself.
I can't blame him.
I wouldn't want to be him either.
He's about to be bound by law
to Julie Cooper.
Don't remind me. Denial is a
very effective coping mechanism.
It should be some weekend.
Hi.
Want some breakfast? Pancakes?
Waffles?
- You're leaving.
- I'm going home.
I talked to my mom.
I told her everything.
I should have left last night
when I saw the look on your face.
You don't have to leave.
We can figure this out together.
Then come with me.
Never mind breakfast.
I'll grab something on the road.
This place is huge.
It's a castle.
The torture chamber must be
in the basement.
Jimmy, what...?
You should not be here. Caleb's due
back any minute, and thanks to you...
...he has to take his wedding photos
with a black eye.
It'll match the black lump of coal
where his heart should be.
Why can't you be happy for me? I am.
Julie, you can't be happy.
- And that makes me happy.
- Classy choice, Jimmy.
Although, it's obvious you're with her
because you can't be with Kirsten.
I think, in psychology,
that's called "transference."
And you marrying Caleb,
I think, in psychology...
...that's called "shameless gold-digging."
- No.
- That's what his youngest daughter's for.
- Don't make me...
Make you what? Go back to life
as a stripper or a coke whore?
- Someone forgotten about the '80s?
- At least I'm not a criminal.
- Yeah, you're just marrying one.
- Okay, stop it.
Just stop it. No more fighting, okay?
Look, you're getting what you wanted.
I'm moving in with you.
Well, that's what you wanted too,
right, sweetie?
I've got some more stuff in the car.
I'll get the rest of my stuff
out of your house tomorrow.
I can't believe your boat's name
is Summer. What a coincidence.
My name's Summer.
Your boat's named Summer.
- It's kind of crazy.
- Yeah, it's just crazy.
Well, it's the only Summer
you'll be riding for a while.
Right. Yeah, no sex. I got it. Thank you.
- Hey, Seth.
- Hey.
- You got that paperwork?
- Yeah.
So it's still in really good condition.
I got a guy, I think he'll offer 6000.
He's been bugging me a while.
Great. Will you remember to get cash?
- I told him.
- All right. Thanks.
- Come by tomorrow.
- I will.
Six thousand dollars in cash?
- Are you fleeing the country, Cohen?
- No, it's for Ryan.
What? For vintage wife-beaters?
It's actually for Theresa.
For Ryan to give to Theresa.
Listen, don't say anything, okay? Because
I don't even think Ryan's told Marissa yet.
But...
...I think Theresa's gonna have her baby.
What?
- Oh, my God.
- I know.
And she's gonna need money, and, you
know, I spent all mine on Vegas hookers.
So this is the only thing
I have that's worth anything.
I just don't know how else to help.
Cohen...
- What the hell's he doing here?
- He's family too.
- Hey.
- How you doing, Caleb?
- Get away from me.
- Dad.
- Well...
...congrats. She's a hell of a woman.
- Congratulations, Mrs. Cooper.
- Oh, thank you.
Seth. You excited
about being a groomsman?
It's the fulfillment
of a lifelong dream, yeah.
- Hey, guys.
- Marissa.
- You look beautiful.
- Thanks.
Hey, have you guys seen Ryan?
He didn't call me back earlier.
- Do you think he's okay?
- Yeah.
- He takes a long time with his hair.
- His hair, yeah.
- Bangs. I don't know. Mousse. Product.
- You should see him. It's weird.
So, Cal...
...I talked to the DA.
- Otis?
- Yeah.
What did that pantload have
to say for himself?
It's over.
What the hell am I supposed to do?
Well, have you told the future Mrs. Nichol
about your financial situation?
What are you saying, Sandy?
That Julie's only marrying me
for my money?
No, never.
Course not.
But you might think...
...about postponing this thing.
- Impossible.
The wedding is tomorrow.
I have never let anyone push me around,
and this is no exception.
But thanks...
...for trying.
I appreciate it.
It's ironic.
Julie leaves Jimmy, marries you.
Now he's worth millions...
...and you're gonna be broke.
I don't believe in irony.
Well, that's too bad...
...because it might be just the thing
to get you through this.
Hey. What are you doing?
I'm just...
...you know, hiding.
Yeah. I can't blame you.
- So where's Theresa?
- She went back home.
To have the baby.
Well, did she and Eddie make up?
So she's having the baby alone.
I'll keep it brief, I promise.
First, I'd like to thank Kirsten
for hosting a wonderful dinner...
...and to say...
...tomorrow is a truly important event.
As a father, it's a great joy to have
a family and to watch that family grow.
We've all been through
a great deal together...
...for better and for worse.
But tomorrow...
...the Nichols, the Cohens
and the Coopers become one family.
And I feel very lucky to be
at the head of that family.
Cheers and many thanks.
Cheers.
Hey, are you okay?
I just need some air.
- Hey.
Everything okay?
- Can we just get out of here?
- Please.
You know, Ryan, I...
I think it was this very stretch
of beach...
...where we first got our asses kicked
by the water-polo team.
Yeah?
Could be.
Yes, it definitely tastes the same.
Wait, when was that?
- When I first got here.
- Yeah, it was after that fashion show...
...at Holly's beach house.
You guys were at that party?
Those were the days.
Hey...
...you feeling better?
I've been thinking.
I think...
...I need to go back.
I can't let Theresa do this by herself.
I'm leaving.
Hey.
So we all good? Proof of purchase?
Bill of sale?
Yeah, so the guy called me
this morning, said he...
...couldn't come up with the money.
- What?
What the hell, man?
You told me it was a done deal.
- He said give him a couple of months.
- I can't do that. I need it right now.
- Just forget it. It just figures...
- Sorry, man.
Yeah, well...
...that's the way it's been
going for me lately.
Hey. Okay, I have a plan.
Listen, Ryan doesn't want
to leave, right?
We don't want him to leave. So...
...let's not let him.
We can all get jobs. We can pool
our salaries and cover his apartment...
...an apartment up
in the numbered streets.
Except Theresa wants to be with
her family, and Ryan has to be with her.
What? You wanna give up?
You wanna let him go?
Look, there's nothing else we can do,
other than kidnap him.
If there was something I could do,
I would.
Well, I think you've
done enough, so...
- What does that mean?
- I don't think Ryan...
...would be back with Theresa
if it wasn't for you and Oliver.
- Cohen.
- Really...
...all you ever did was drag that kid
into your messed-up life. I just...
Right. You used him to meet girls
and get out of fights.
- Okay, you guys, come on.
- I don't really care.
I've gotta get ready. So as long
as you're cool with him leaving...
- Hey.
- Hi.
We'll probably leave in an hour
if Kirsten can get ready in time.
It is a mystery what goes on
in that bathroom.
- Think you'll be done by 6?
- God, I hope so.
That's what time I told Theresa
to pick me up.
You know, as your guardian...
...I can stop you.
But if you taught me anything...
...you gotta do whatever it takes
to protect your family.
- She's my family now.
- We are too.
You can stay here. So can she.
We can make this work as a family.
I can't.
I can't ask that of you.
You've done more than enough...
...more than I ever could've asked
of anyone.
I told you...
...you could've done worse.
- No.
When you took me in, I had nothing.
No family, no hope.
I don't want this kid
to grow up like I did.
Well...
...just because you're leaving...
...doesn't mean I'm letting you go.
Now, come on, get dressed.
We gotta witness the most
unholy of all unions.
You want to dance?
I just want you to know...
...I understand why you have to do this.
Thanks.
But I wish you didn't have to.
Me too.
I love you.
- Hey.
They sent me out to find you.
Found you.
I figured you'd be stuffing your pockets
with cocktail weenies.
You're still gonna see him.
Chino's not that far away.
I just can't believe he's leaving.
He's the first real friend I've ever had.
He's the only real friend I've ever had.
I know.
- You have me.
- Yeah, but that's not the same thing.
You don't get it. Before he got here...
...I was the biggest loser.
This place was hell for me, okay?
And I can't help him, and...
I can't even imagine...
...what it's gonna be like
here without him.
We'll make it through it. I promise.
Could you tell them that I'll be back
in a few minutes, please?
Sure.
Yeah, for the record...
...the boat was named after you.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Is Theresa here?
Should be soon.
A little something for the road.
Don't worry, I didn't make it.
But if I did learn to cook...
...could we convince you to stay?
Thank you for...
...inviting me into your home.
You guys...
This year was...
For us too.
And Kirsten's not even a hugger.
You always know how to ruin a moment.
That's what I do.
I'm gonna say goodbye to Seth.
- Hey, man.
- Hi.
Gotta jet.
Cool.
You really gotta go?
Yeah.
Well, if you need a nanny,
I'll take the graveyard shift.
I think we'll manage.
I was afraid you'd say that.
You can come down and visit me.
Hey, so I...
I got you something.
It's yours, you know.
- Always good for ideas.
- Map of Tahiti.
Cool, man.
So I'll see you, then.
See you.