Previously on The O.C.:
- You gotta have a plan.
- Who are you?
I stole a car. Then my mom threw me out,
so Mr. Cohen took me in.
- What is it about this kid?
- I was this kid.
- Ryan's gonna stay with us now.
- That's awesome.
- Do you wanna do something tonight?
- You're not, like, into him, are you?
What are you doing with my girlfriend?
Do you know what girls find sexy?
Confidence.
Might I remind you of something
that I call:
"The time that you kissed me
at my grandfather's party."
What are you talking about?
I never should have
broken up with you in the first place.
- I don't know what I should do.
- Let me know when you decide.
Jimmy's been siphoning money out of his
clients' accounts to cover his own debts.
- Daddy!
- Put your personal feelings for him aside.
He's one of my oldest friends.
This whole community thinks
you're a criminal, Jimmy.
- You're getting a divorce.
- I'm so sorry, kiddo.
- What are you doing?
- I didn't know. I'm sorry.
- I have no one.
- She's gone.
And so are my stepmom's painkillers.
Wake up.
I have three sesame and one plain.
I'm okay.
Look, we're not gonna hear
from the hospital for a while.
You guys get showered and dressed.
And you can't be late
for your meeting with the dean.
- I'll take them to school.
- You can't be late for your first day.
Well, if we're not gonna eat,
let's just go.
Oh, hey. Hey.
She just fell back asleep.
But she was awake and aware.
Thanks for calling the hospital.
And finding her.
If they hadn't airlifted her out, she...
- When can she go home?
- They said in a day or so.
- They wanna keep her under observation.
- That's hospital policy.
So I guess there's no need
to worry, right?
I mean, a teenage girl palms
a dozen painkillers...
...and washes it down with tequila.
That's perfectly normal, right?
What are you doing here?
I called them.
What Marissa needs right now
is to be with her family. No visitors.
Well, let's go. We should go.
- Lf you need anything...
- Thanks.
Don't take it personally.
Julie's just been through
every parent's nightmare.
- I'm sure she'll apologize.
- You are?
It's Julie Cooper we're talking about.
Excuse me.
Ryan, can I talk to you for a sec?
I don't know what happened in Mexico,
but here's what I do know:
Since you showed up,
Marissa's been a wreck.
Comes home crying,
doesn't wanna go to her cotillion...
...having problems with her boyfriend.
And now you can add another
shining accomplishment...
...to your list of achievements.
In addition to stealing cars,
burning down houses...
...and befriending
would-be assassins...
...you've almost killed my daughter.
You can blame me all you want...
...but I would never do anything
to hurt Marissa.
Well, you're not going
to get the chance...
...because you're never
going to see her again.
You even try, and I'll make sure you're
thrown back in juvie, where you belong.
Wait. I don't get it. Luke's the one
she should be blaming, not you.
- She doesn't know that.
- So why don't you tell her?
I'm just glad Marissa's okay.
I'll check in with the events committee.
I'll catch up with you at the dean's office.
Ryan, don't be nervous.
You're gonna do great.
This is school?
Registration week, Ryan.
It's my favorite time of the year...
...because fellow students
aren't around to ruin it. Except them.
You guys have tennis courts
and a swimming pool?
I'm guessing you didn't
at your old school.
Well, we had a basketball hoop.
- Oh, hi, guys.
- Dr. Talley, Miss Kimrey. How are you?
Okay.
My mom's more popular than me.
That's a little bit pathetic, I realize.
After your meeting, we gotta get
your photo taken for your school ID.
- Another mug shot?
- Lf you must be so cynical.
Oh, yeah. That one's a keeper.
- So when do we do the retina scan?
- Friday.
- I was joking.
- So was I.
Good thing we didn't hire you
for your quick wit.
Well, God doesn't give with two hands.
Come on.
Time for you to meet your team.
You'll have a researcher,
two paralegals...
...and a file clerk to do
all the heavy lifting for you.
Speaking of which,
let me show you our gym.
- Oh, you guys have a gym?
- You didn't at the PD's office?
Well, we had a basketball hoop.
Everything's gonna be fine.
It's just...
...at Chino Hills,
you sort of showed up.
No essays, interviews, tests.
The Harbor School is one of
the best private schools in the country.
If you graduate from here, you can
get into any college in the UC system.
Maybe even an Ivy League.
I don't think I'm an Ivy League
kind of guy.
- After a year or two here, you will be.
- College, huh?
Yeah.
What did you get?
AP History, English, calculus
and physics. And French 4.
Good thing I don't have a life.
What is wrong? Are you nervous?
Seth, would you please tell Ryan
that Dr. Kim is very nice.
Oh, yeah. She is sweet.
- Kirsten, how are you?
- Hi, nice to see you.
Seth. Always interesting to see you.
And you must be Ryan.
Why don't we step into my office.
Well, this doesn't suck.
That eloquence will serve you nicely
on the stand.
Like you guys ever actually
go to trial.
You're one of us now, Sandy.
Better start wrapping your head around it.
So is your family all excited
about your first day?
My wife loves being married
to a corporate sellout.
Right, right, right.
Wrapping my head around it.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Yeah.
I figured you'd wanna dive right in.
Chemical peel gone awry. Fascinating.
Bad Botox injection.
Noise complaint on a yacht.
- Scintillating?
- In the purest sense of the word.
- Don't be a snob.
- Just defend them. Right.
Rich people need lawyers too.
Weak grades, truancy.
Notation regarding some criminal activity.
It was a misdemeanor. Probation.
Nonetheless, not exactly
Harbor School material.
Dr. Kim, Ryan's had a lot to overcome...
...but Sandy and I feel that in the right
environment, he could really excel.
There's no doubt that Mr. Atwood
has extraordinary promise.
I'm just concerned that he hasn't had...
...adequate preparation
for the rigors of our curriculum.
Or are you concerned about
the pressure from parents...
...who don't want Ryan here?
That's definitely a consideration.
But not a decisive one.
Kirsten, you know as well as I do how
bright and motivated our students are.
Those that aren't bred for USC
go off to Harvard and Yale.
I just think a place like Newport Union...
...might be a better fit for a student
with Ryan's background.
My background?
I can't change where I'm from,
but I can change where I'm going.
Ryan, you understand
that if you did fail...
...you'd lose a year,
not to mention self-confidence.
With all due respect, Dr. Kim...
...if you think not letting me in
is gonna inspire self-confidence...
Give me a shot.
You got great test scores.
I definitely responded
to your personal essay.
Your grades are borderline,
but acceptable.
If you could pass a placement exam...
It's not an aptitude test.
It measures your preparedness...
...not how bright you are.
Just tell me where and when.
Summer, hey.
Hi.
It's so weird being in school right now...
...surrounded by all these people
who have, like, no idea.
I know. Have you talked to Marissa?
I spoke to her mom. You?
We went by this morning,
but she was sleeping.
- They said she's gonna be okay, though.
- I still can't believe it, you know?
- I thought she was dead.
- Me too.
Maybe when she's feeling better, we'll
take her out and try and cheer her up.
Take her to a movie.
Or Six Flags, I don't know.
Yeah. I guess.
Maybe before then, if you want...
...I don't know, you and me could
go see a movie or something.
- Hey, Summer.
- Hey, Summer, how's it going?
Hey, you guys.
What a nerd.
Look, Cohen.
This year's all messed up.
I mean, Marissa's in the hospital,
I'll never speak to Luke or Holly again.
- You and I...
- No, I get it, it's fine.
We're back in school now,
old rules apply.
Sorry.
Strong sedative, huh?
Yeah, she needs to sleep.
And we need to talk.
Look, Jimmy...
...you and I, we need to
present a united front.
It's hard enough, this forcing us
to be in the same room together.
Thanks. You got a great bedside manner.
Calling the Cohens was
completely inappropriate.
- You know I don't like that Brian.
- Ryan.
- I don't want him near Marissa.
- Marissa said it was an accident, okay?
There's no one to blame.
That's a convenient position to take,
since you let her go to Tijuana.
Oh, so now it's my fault.
You're the one
who destroyed this family.
You lied to us. You stole money
from your clients and friends.
Why do you think
she took all those pills?
You cannot honestly believe that.
I left her in your care for one weekend
and look what happened.
Which is why I'm asking the judge
for sole custody.
Julie, come on. You can't.
Getting the girls away from you is my only
chance to give them a semblance of a life.
And if you fight me on this...
...I'll take you to court and you'll be lucky
to even get supervised visitation.
Yeah, well, you're gonna have to,
because I am not giving up my kids.
You may not have a choice.
I'm going back to check on
Kaitlin and the sitter.
You should get cleaned up.
You're a wreck.
Good thing I never
throw anything away.
The questions will be different,
but you get it.
- Yeah, but I'm gonna fail.
- You're not gonna fail. You have to get in.
I won't spend another year
at that school alone.
Please, thank you, study.
Especially, though, if all it takes is
a couple of cheerleaders walking by...
...and suddenly it's like Summer and I,
we just didn't happen.
I'm sorry. You study.
Here's the thing, though.
We connected. And it was awesome.
Especially the part
where she kissed me...
Seth. I have two hours
until I take this test.
Unless you plan on going to
Newport Union...
Right. Got it.
Less talking, more studying.
Don't move. I'm gonna get that.
And you keep studying.
Hello?
Hey, Marissa. Hi.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sorry. Sure.
Hi.
Okay. All right.
Okay, I'll be there. Bye.
She's upset.
Something with her parents.
And her mom's going home, so...
- What about the test?
- I'll be there.
- I'll just do the best that I can.
- But what if that's not good enough?
Well, then Dr. Kim was right.
I'm not Harbor School material.
Hi.
These are for you.
It's all they had left at the gift shop.
I'll just...
I'm sorry.
I was so dumb.
What I did, I wasn't...
Hey, come on.
I didn't want to kill myself.
I didn't.
I just wanted to...
...escape.
- I know.
Excuse me, nurse.
When you get a chance, lunch, please.
You should...
Oh, sweetie, you're awake.
How are you feeling?
Your sister sends her love.
My throat hurts.
That's because they had to
pump your stomach, honey.
Where did that thing come from?
I...
I don't know.
It's from him. He came here, didn't he?
After I told him not to.
- After everything he's done to you.
- He didn't.
- It wasn't his fault.
- You keep saying that...
...but before he got here,
you were happy.
You think I was happy?
If you weren't,
you never told me about it.
- I tried, but...
- I need to talk to the nurse.
The security in here is appalling.
I'm sorry about that.
You know, about her.
That's okay.
I should go and take this test.
But I'll be back first chance I get.
I don't know. With my mom...
I'm not afraid of your mom.
Well, I am.
Did you ask Ryan
what he wants for lunch?
He doesn't wanna eat.
He's on a diet.
Why's he on a diet?
- Why is he on a diet?
- I'll ask him. I wanna see how he's doing...
Mom, Mom. He's in a state of deep, deep
Zen-like concentration right now, okay?
Well, he still needs to eat.
He's naked. All right? He's naked,
he studies in the nude. It's a Chino thing.
I think that if you were to walk in on him
naked and Dad was to find out...
...I think suspicions might be raised.
A house divided will not stand.
You and I still need to talk about
your little surprise trip to Tijuana.
Okay. I can't wait.
Jimmy, hi. Is Marissa okay?
Yeah, she's doing better, thanks.
It's Julie who's giving me the problem.
Is Sandy coming home for lunch?
No, he just started a new job today.
Why? What's going on?
She's suing me for sole custody.
Maybe even supervised visits.
- Why would she do that?
- Well, my question is, can she?
I need to know what shot I have
at joint custody...
...given what I've put my family through.
- I wanna know what kind of case she has.
- Come in. I'll get Sandy's new number.
I'll just... I'll wait out here.
I mean, you know...
Jimmy, we have been friends for too long
to let something like this...
It was just a...
It was stupid.
It was monumentally stupid.
And I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I mean, it's not okay, but it's okay.
I mean, you and Sandy are
the only friends I have left.
- And I definitely don't wanna lose you.
- Won't.
So are you coming in or what?
Hi, you've reached Jimmy Cooper.
Please leave a message and I'll get back...
Security said they'd do what they can,
but I don't know.
You know, this is exactly why I thought
San Diego would be good for you.
- San Diego?
- Dr. Burke has a facility there.
- Who's Dr. Burke?
- Well...
She's a psychiatrist.
Highly recommended.
She runs an institute
for young women who are troubled.
You're sending me
to a mental institution.
It's a recovery center.
Honey, I know you don't understand...
...but I would rather have you hate me
now than risk losing you again.
Does Dad know about this?
Well, I think some time away from
your father would be good for you too.
- Well, what if I don't wanna go?
- That's for Dr. Burke to decide.
She'll be here after lunch
to evaluate you.
Please, honey, just talk to her.
Let her help you.
And then we can get you out of here
and you can start to get better.
Yeah. If it's okay,
I just need to use the bathroom.
Of course.
Not now, Mom. I'm studying naked.
Summer?
- Come in.
- No way.
- I'm not naked.
- No, no, no!
Okay. I don't get it.
What kind of family do you have, Cohen?
The kind where mothers and sons
wear clothes.
Always. Even in the shower.
What is this?
I don't know.
I've never seen it before.
- What's his name?
- I don't know.
Captain Oats. What are you doing here?
Coop just called. She's freaking out.
Her mom's threatening to ship her
to the insane asylum.
- Really?
- Yeah. I'm serious.
I've gotta do something, Cohen.
I need to get radical.
- I need Ryan.
- You can't have him.
He's taking an exam. What's wrong
with me, not radical enough?
Well, that depends.
Are you ready to take on Julie Cooper?
- We need Ryan.
- Yeah.
- That's my bed.
- Okay.
Just wanted you to know.
- I have a feeling you'll be...
- Okay, let's go.
It's a very fair offer,
given the merits of the case.
Okay. Well, think it over.
Goodbye.
My wife does that with her hands
when she's pissed off at me.
Your wife and I have a lot in common.
You've been here half a day...
...and you've booked
court dates for five of your seven cases.
Do I win the free set of steak knives?
Sandy, this isn't how
they do things around here.
And I can keep this off the partners'
radar, but you gotta understand...
Understand what? I'm going to court. I'm
taking them on, I'm bringing them down.
Especially this bastard who won't let his
neighbor grow hedges over his own fence.
Look, you know how much time
and energy goes into trying one of these.
If you settled, you could handle
twice as many cases.
- And we're in a volume business here.
- Like Costco.
I thought the reason you brought me here
is because you wanted a trial attorney...
...who's committed and passionate and...
Yes. And when one of these cases
actually deserves to go before a jury...
...the courtroom is all yours.
But in the meantime...
...I need you to pick up the phone and
passionately negotiate some settlements.
Come on. I put my ass on the line
to get you this gig.
Please. Do it for me.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Dr. Kim will be back any minute.
Yeah, I know this isn't the best time,
but Marissa needs you right now. Or us.
Her mom's gone psycho.
She's having her committed.
- What is going on in here?
- Hi, Dr. Kim.
This isn't what it looks like.
It's an emergency.
We need to borrow Ryan for a while.
- He's not going anywhere. You two, out!
- You don't understand!
- There's an emergency...
- Goodbye!
Okay. We'll be out here.
Actually, I gotta go too.
- Have you finished the test?
- No. But I...
Ryan, if this is too difficult, tell me.
If the Cohens are pressuring you...
- They're not. I wanna be here.
- Then prove it.
- Sit down, finish the test.
- I can't.
Ryan, if this is the level of commitment
you plan to bring to your studies...
- Dr. Kim, I really don't have time to argue.
- There is no argument.
You walk away from this test,
you walk away from this school.
You're probably right.
It wouldn't have worked out anyway.
Sorry for wasting your time.
Let's go.
So your mother tells me you struggled
with anorexia in the ninth grade.
My mom's convinced it was anorexia.
It was just tennis season,
I was really stressed.
That's all.
And in 10th grade
you were caught shoplifting?
It was just a lighter
and a pack of cigarettes.
Do you still smoke?
Not really.
Drink?
Would you say you drink a lot?
I guess. I mean, what's a lot?
Have you ever had so much to drink
that you blacked out?
Tell me about this past year.
Your dad's legal troubles,
bankruptcy, your parents separating.
Home's probably the last place
you wanna be, right?
Your mom mentioned a boyfriend. Luke?
- He's not my boyfriend anymore.
- Really?
You wanna tell me what happened?
Anything I say, you'll just use against me
to prove to my mom...
...that I'm troubled, right?
I'm not here to judge.
I'm here to listen and try to help.
You're here because my mom
would rather ship me to an institution...
...than deal with what's really going on.
I'm here because, accidentally or not,
you nearly killed yourself.
And you wanna tell me what's actually
going on with you and your mom?
How much time do you have?
Not good. Summer should've
been here by now.
She better be here soon.
What if something happened? Right?
Marissa's dad can't even get her
out of here. How are we supposed to?
Not by waiting for Summer.
Hi. We're here for Marissa Cooper.
It's okay, Denise. They're with me.
Good Lord.
What? I told you I was a candy striper.
- I thought you were kidding.
- It's for charity. All the girls do it.
- I should be hospitalized more.
- Lf you need any help...
Okay, guys. Can you get us
in the psych ward or not?
- Just try to keep up with me.
- Cool.
Seth, you're on lookout.
Hi, Gloria. I know it's my day off, but
I just cannot get enough of sick people.
These guys are helping
with the sponge baths.
Dibs on that guy.
We don't need to keep her
on suicide watch...
...but there are underlying issues
she hasn't been dealing with.
- But you can help her?
- I can recommend treatment.
- Psychodynamic therapy, group work.
- At the institute?
At the institute or here in Newport.
I see patients, or I can refer you.
No. I want her to get out of Newport.
It's too chaotic for her here.
She can't leave now.
She's got school, her friends.
Uprooting her will do
more harm than good.
She almost died, Jimmy.
How much more harm can she do?
All right, you decide.
I need to check in with the institute.
Thanks.
- She's going to the institute.
- She's not going anywhere.
- Don't make me call my lawyer.
- Go ahead. I'll call mine.
I'm gonna go talk to Marissa.
Excuse me, doctor.
Marissa's father and I have discussed it.
I've got a bag for her in the car
and I can drive her down myself tonight.
I'll make the arrangements.
Thank you.
I know this may be difficult
for you to hear...
...but Dr. Burke and I think
it's for the best.
Well, what about Dad?
Well, he just wants
what's best for you too.
Now, Dr. Burke and I
have some paperwork.
So you should get dressed, okay?
I'm glad you're taking this
so well, Marissa.
Yeah, well, if it's for the best, right?
I love you, honey.
- Okay. Get dressed. I'll be back.
- All right.
- How'd I do?
- Almost had me convinced. Here.
It's Summer's idea. It's for cover.
Sure. Summer's idea.
Hey, no peeking.
Hey, Madame Bovary.
That Flaubert could really turn a phrase.
I guess. It was kind of a bummer.
I know Emma got her heart,
like, totally broken...
...but why'd she have to
go and eat arsenic?
- You've read Madame Bovary?
- Five times.
It's Tom Shayle's favorite book.
I should go check on him. He's two
floors down. He's, like, incontinent.
You're a strange and mysterious
woman, Summer.
The most important thing is that
we make sure Marissa feels safe.
I don't know what that means, Cohen.
I wasn't in Panama.
- It means...
- Just go and I'll run interference.
Yeah, that's what I said. 10-4.
- Hi, Mrs. Cooper. How are you?
- Hey, Summer. You here to see Mariss?
Yeah. I was just volunteering today,
I thought I'd stop by. How is she?
Well, she's going to be fine eventually.
- Are you her doctor?
- Therapist. We're on our way to see her...
Therapist? Do you have a second?
Because I keep having this dream.
I'm in the woods, trying to find this
restaurant, but I'm lost and so hungry.
I have a reservation, can't be late.
You following?
You ready?
Yeah.
Go away.
I just wanted to see you.
I'm so sorry about everything.
- Yeah, that's what you said in Mexico.
- That was a mistake.
No kidding.
What are you doing dressed like that?
Hey, your mom and the doctor
are on the move.
You're running away?
Look, Luke, please, l...
Take the stairs.
Are you sure it's okay?
I don't wanna interrupt.
His office said he was having
welcome drinks with a few of his...
Thank you.
Associates.
- Can I have another one?
- Sure.
Hey!
Hey. What are you two doing here?
When I couldn't reach you, I called the
office. Jimmy needs some legal advice.
- I'm Kirsten.
- Hi, I'm Rachel.
- Oh, so this is Rachel.
- This is Rachel.
I'm Rachel.
- Hi, Rachel. I'm Jimmy.
- Hi.
So are you suing a tequila company?
Doing some research?
- Apparently, we don't sue anybody.
- Now, you say that like it's a bad thing.
Kirsten, you're lucky to be married
to somebody so hilarious.
I am.
You know what, I'll just take care
of this myself. I'm gonna go.
- Jimmy.
- Stop by the office tomorrow.
Yeah, no, tomorrow's gonna be too late.
Thanks, Kirsten.
I'll see you at home,
when you've finished work.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
Hey, Dad.
What are you doing here?
I checked out.
Does your mother know about this?
- We're gonna wait in the car.
- Yeah. Yeah. Right.
You ran away?
- I didn't know what else to do.
- Sweetheart.
Mom was getting ready to
drive me down to San Diego.
What?
What...? You didn't know.
I should have guessed.
Look, I don't want to go to San Diego
and I don't wanna live with Mom.
- I wanna stay with you.
- Look, I want that too. Okay?
But I don't know if that's possible.
Your mom is suing me for sole custody.
And after everything I've done,
she kind of has me over a barrel, kiddo.
Look, if I do even the slightest thing
wrong, I could never see you again.
Okay?
And I don't ever want to lose you.
Hold on.
- Just give me a second, okay?
- Yeah.
Hey. Yeah, hi.
No. She's here.
Look, I didn't have anything
to do with this, Julie.
Well, you were gonna take her to
San Diego without telling me about it.
All right. I'll keep her here.
What do you wanna do now, Coop?
I don't know what to do.
What can I do?
I could hide you in one
of my mom's developments.
I'm kidding.
I mean, how is any of this even possible?
My mom wants to lock me up
in an asylum...
...while my dad can't do anything
about it.
- We'll figure something out.
- Well, we better hurry.
She just escaped from a psych ward
in a candy striper outfit.
If they didn't think
she was crazy before, they...
- Sorry, Coop. I'm gonna get another slice.
- As will I.
Well, if you wanna skip town,
I guess I could go with you.
My mom would love that.
Look, if your mom's doing all this
just to keep me away from you...
...I'll stay away.
I don't want that.
So, what are we gonna do?
If I could just get her to listen.
- Hey.
- Back from work?
I don't understand why you're so upset.
I mean, I understand, but it's nothing.
She works at the firm.
She doesn't look old enough
to be served in a bar.
She's 33. She graduated Berkeley
four years after you.
- What's her favorite color?
- Pink.
Oh, Kirsten.
Sandy, I'm not saying
anything's going on.
Good, because you spent the weekend
painting Jimmy's house...
...and I said nothing,
because I knew nothing was going on.
- Right?
- Right, of course.
So, what were you two
doing together tonight?
Jimmy's got custody issues with Julie.
Well, I guess we're all having issues.
So, what are we gonna do?
I have to work with this woman.
- I trust you.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Hey, it's Ryan.
Hey. What's going on?
I'm with Marissa,
and I need your advice.
Well, if I've learned anything today...
...you don't wanna go to court
with this.
You're gonna want to settle.
- What is going on?
- Come with me.
What does this have to do with Marissa?
Do you know where she...?
Well, no surprise
you're involved in all this.
Where is she?
I don't know. At a bus station.
On a tropical island somewhere.
I cannot believe
you're chaperoning this farce.
- Julie, sit down.
- No. I don't want to sit down.
All right, let's all talk.
Talk about what?
What is there to talk about?
Well, if you ever wanna
see your daughter...
Watch it.
Julie, I know you've been through a lot,
but Ryan isn't the problem.
What is that supposed to mean?
You tell me where she is
and then I am taking her home.
- She just ran away from a hospital!
- She ran away from you.
Look, you're from Riverside, right?
Well, that's not too far
from where I grew up.
I am calling the police...
And I know this place has
everything we never had...
...and I know you're afraid
you're gonna lose it all.
I'm done.
But you and Marissa
want different things.
- You don't know what she wants!
- I know what she doesn't want.
She doesn't want to go to San Diego.
And she doesn't want to live with you.
I don't know what
I'm supposed to say to any of this.
Just say yes.
Oh, honey.
- No, no, you don't mean that.
- Yes, I do.
Look, I know you're only trying to help,
but you're just making everything worse.
You have no idea how scared I was.
I'm sorry.
But, look, I'm not gonna hurt
myself again.
And I'll even see a therapist if you want.
But I wanna do it here.
And I wanna live with Dad.
I mean, at least for now.
This isn't over, Marissa.
I'll let myself out.
You okay?
So you still think that,
after everything that happened today...
...when we get back to school,
you're gonna be able to ignore me?
- Well, all I can do is try.
- I admire your will.
Hey!
Hey. How'd it go?
- Oh, it's over.
- Yeah?
Somebody should take Marissa home.
To her dad's.
Bye, Summer.
It's just a little thing we do.
Okay. Now, let's talk about
that surprise little trip to Tijuana.
It's pronounced "Tijuana."
You're so white, Mom.
- I've never heard you talk so much.
- I like to save it for when it counts.
Good.
So I heard what happened
with your test today.
Or what didn't happen.
You're suddenly not so talkative.
Look, I get it.
Marissa needed help,
you were worried about her.
Believe me, I understand.
I'm worried about you.
I'm okay going to public school. It'd be
a hell of a lot better than where I went.
- Go to Dr. Kim and explain yourself.
- I don't think she wants to hear from me.
Ever again.
You're afraid of her.
You, who went toe-to-toe
with Julie Cooper, the dragon lady.
You can take Dr. Kim. Talk to her.
If there's a problem,
you'll have your attorney present.
I got your back.
Now, you and Summer seemed
pretty chummy yesterday.
Dad, "chummy"?
- It's okay, you can tell me.
- No, really, I can't.
If you can't tell your dad,
who can you tell?
Gee, I don't know. Ryan, Mom.
That tree over there.
- You're gonna miss me when I'm gone.
- When are you leaving?
- What's the verdict?
- He passed. He did very well.
Congratulations! Dude, you're a Pirate.
- You guys are the Pirates?
- Yeah, it's a bit minty.
Thank you for giving Ryan
another chance.
Mr. Cohen, I told Ryan that if he ever
pulls a stunt like that again...
...he's going to need a much better
lawyer than you to get him out.
Welcome to the Harbor School, Ryan.
I'll be watching you.
You thought juvie was tough.
You ready to get your photo taken
for a student ID?
- Another mug shot?
- So cynical.
Hey. Check out my new mug shot.
God! Dad, those eyebrows
are out of control.
It's a sign of power, you know.
Then you must be the most
powerful man in the world.
Yeah, well, brace yourself, son.
It's genetic.