- Previously on The O.C.:
- I can't do this anymore. I don't trust you.
Oliver's not stable. He's dangerous.
Oliver has not done anything to Marissa
except be her friend.
Look, you guys may not believe me.
No one may believe me.
- Theresa.
- Ryan Atwood.
- So you two were...
- We grew up together.
I always had a crush on you.
You should go.
I'm not gonna stand here and pretend
like I'm your girlfriend when I'm not.
At least not anymore.
Put the gun down,
you get a second chance.
- I'm sorry. You were right.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Someone just got struck by cupid's arrow.
- Valentine's Day's not till tomorrow.
- You're not excited?
I am. I am. I'm just still thinking
about Oliver with that gun.
- I know.
- Who knows what could've happened?
But it didn't.
And Dr. Kim lifted Ryan's suspension.
So the best thing is for
everything to return to normal.
And in this house that means
celebrating the holidays.
Valentine's Day is not a holiday.
Rosh Hashanah, that's a holiday.
Memorial Day? Yes, a holiday.
You know who invented Valentine's Day?
- St. Valentine.
- Hershey's and Hallmark.
If you're single, it depresses you.
If you are in love, start shelling out.
Chocolate. Flowers.
- Lingerie.
- You never bought me lingerie.
See how upset you are?
I hate this holiday.
- Must be talking about Valentine's Day.
- I am. I hate it.
- Hey. You got me.
- Guess who got shot by cupid's arrow.
Is someone going overboard?
You're one to talk.
Chrismukkah, anyone?
- At least that's a real holiday.
- Tell her, Dad. It's two.
- Seth made that word up when he was 6.
- It's an important...
This is an important holiday.
It's Valentine's Day.
- Where Jewishness fuses with Christianity.
- Do the math.
- How you doing, kid?
- You know. Okay, I guess.
You're about to be great. Tomorrow
is the big Valentine's Day Singles' Gala.
A benefit for Newport Memorial's
Heart Department.
Big party. You guys are gonna dress up.
Everyone's gonna be there.
Just like normal, huh? Yes!
I'm gonna go.
- Ryan. Hey.
- Hey.
Were you able to sleep at all?
- Not much.
- Me either.
- I kept going over everything in my head.
- Yeah.
He's in the hospital,
so hopefully he'll get better.
I hope so.
I'm ready for everything to just
go back to normal. The way it was.
Great. So, Valentine's Day tomorrow.
- Yeah?
- What were you gonna do? Because...
...I didn't know if you wanted to...
- Yeah, no.
- Kirsten's hosting this singles' dance...
- For the hospital.
I told her I'd go.
I didn't know if you wanted...
Of course.
Right. Well, then I'll go too.
Who knows?
Maybe we'll meet somebody there.
Yeah. Who knows?
- All right. I should get to...
- Yeah. No. Me too.
Hey, Summer.
God, Cohen. You made me mess up.
- I'm going for the high score.
- Hey, it's good to see you too.
- Tomorrow's Valentine's Day.
- Oh, really?
God. I didn't know tomorrow
was Valentine's Day.
But thanks for reminding me.
Have fun with Anna.
- Anna's in Pittsburgh for the weekend.
- On Valentine's Day?
Hey, now that's commitment.
Actually, Anna and I broke up.
And I wanted to see
what you're doing tomorrow.
- So you guys broke up.
- Yeah.
Coffee. You're single now and you want
to know what I'm doing for Valentine's.
- Yeah.
- So Anna dumps you...
...and you think you can choose me
and I'd still be interested in you?
First of all, what makes you think
that Anna dumped me?
Never mind. Second of all...
...kind of. Yes.
- Yeah. No. No way.
I'm not gonna be your
sloppy seconds, ass-face.
Besides, I'm busy tomorrow.
I'll be at the singles' dance.
- So will I.
- I don't care.
- See you there.
- Not if I see you first.
- Maybe we'll both meet someone special.
- Yeah, as long as his name isn't Cohen.
Snap.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Crusading for the rich and dysfunctional
is time-consuming.
Let me just dot my I's and cross my T's.
Come on, I'm starving. I've been thinking
about crab cakes for the last hour.
Will you be around tomorrow
to help set up?
- For what?
- The Valentine's Day Single Dance Gala.
No. I can't do it.
I got this petty nuisance lawsuit. In fact...
...I'm pretty booked this weekend.
So I might be a little late to
the Valentine's Day Dance Singles' Gala.
- Singles.
- Singles' Dance Gala.
Why?
- We said we'd go together.
- It's restaurant stuff.
Got the zoning inspectors coming by
before we can expand the deck.
- On Saturday?
- I guess these city council guys are busy.
- No. I forbid it.
- You what?
With whatever wifely authority
I have vested in me...
...on this most holy
and romantic of days, no.
- It's only a holiday. Not even a real one.
- Not this again. Not on an empty stomach.
How about Arbor Day? Trees?
That's a good cause. Or Secretary's Day.
- How about our anniversary?
- Which we might not make it to.
You know you'll have more fun
without me.
No. You're going.
Sandy, this is important to me.
There's a lot of things
important to me that you don't do.
- Like what?
- Like golfing.
- Lots of couples golf together.
- Shortly before dying of old age.
Surfing. How often have I tried
to get you in the ocean?
- With the fish?
- And still I'm patient. I'm forgiving.
- You're joking.
- I put up with your father.
- You're eligible for sainthood any day.
- I forgive your snoring.
- I do not snore.
- Yeah, you do.
Like a freight train
roaring through the house.
You wanted to do this restaurant,
I supported you.
You wanted to go into private practice,
who had your back?
- I put up with your father.
- You never wanna do anything I like.
Everything's a fight, an argument.
- My life, my job.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, and I'm still here.
- Don't do me any favors.
- I won't.
- Fine.
- Perfect.
- What are we fighting about?
- I'm not sure.
But it's serious.
You're on your own for lunch.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Hey, kiddo.
Plasterer came to the restaurant today.
Made a total mess.
But progress is being made.
- How's school?
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- Hey, you got something.
It was left for you at the door.
Well, it's not ticking,
so it can't be from your mom.
"Hope you're not too Ionely
this Valentine's Day.
X O, X O. Your Secret Admirer."
Marissa, you're so sweet.
You didn't have to do that.
- I didn't.
- Well...
...who else would've left something nice?
- Good question.
This year I'm doing my best
to avoid Valentine's Day completely.
- What? You and Ryan are...?
- I don't really want to talk about it.
- And neither does he.
- Well, it is Valentine's Day.
Sometimes the big romantic gesture
is more effective than talking.
There's no way your mom
gave me these, right? No.
She doesn't make her disdain for me
a secret. Much less her admiration.
Well, have you kissed anyone recently?
Previously on The Valley:
I just don 't feel like I fit
here in Tarzana.
I'm busy. Studying...
...naked.
Is that supposed to keep me away?
Cohen?
- You're at my house.
- And you're dressed.
I wonder who's more disappointed.
- Can I come in?
- No.
Thanks.
What are you doing here?
Who's this?
- No one.
- "I'm not no one."
- Princess Sparkle. What do you want?
- She's Captain Oats' type.
You tell him to keep his hooves off.
As for you...
Wait, wait. Before you kick me out, can
you please give me a second to explain?
Okay, listen. Summer...
...it's not like...
...now that me and Anna broke up
I'm now choosing you.
Okay?
Because the whole reason
that we broke up...
...is because for me...
...it's always been you, Summer.
It's always been you.
I've tried to fight it,
and I've tried to deny it.
And I can't. I can't do it.
You're undeniable.
- Cohen?
- Yeah.
Do you happen...
...to have...
...you know...?
- Oh...
...yeah, I do. In my wallet.
- Yeah?
I was beginning to view it as sort of
a rabbit's foot, for good luck only, but...
You're about to get lucky.
Whatever you say, Summer. Yes.
Yes.
- Luke. Hi.
- Hi, Mrs. Cooper.
What are you doing here?
Do you know...? I was wondering,
did Marissa bring her bio textbook home?
Marissa doesn't live here anymore, Luke.
You know that.
Right. I must have forgot.
Right. Okay. Well, good night.
Tomorrow is the Valentine's Day party.
Are you gonna go?
Because I'm gonna go.
And I thought if you needed a ride...
Actually, everything that's happened
with Caleb and me...
...I think it's best I stay home.
Avoid this holiday.
Yeah.
It's just another day of the week, right?
Okay.
- Good night, Mrs. Cooper.
- Good night.
So...
...that was sex.
Yep.
- I'm gonna go.
- Me too.
But you live here.
I meant downstairs.
Okay.
Perfect.
Hi.
I love you so much.
We've waited a long time to...
...you know, and I thought maybe
we could start Valentine's Day early.
- No. Wait. Wait. Hold on.
- What?
Don't you want to?
No.
No. I mean, yeah.
Yeah, of course.
But with everything that's happened,
it just...
- It seems a little soon.
- I just wish it hadn't happened.
That we could still be like we were...
...and I wanted to make it up to you.
- You don't have to...
...do this.
No. You're right.
So I guess I'll go.
- Because this is just really...
- Wrong?
I was gonna say "embarrassing."
But I guess "wrong" works.
So it was nice to see you.
And I guess I'll see you again tomorrow.
- Hey, buddy. Got some big news.
- I was about to go set up. You coming?
It's a lot of lifting. It's not my thing.
I don't know if I just mentioned this,
but I have some big news.
- Yeah, so I heard. What's up?
- Ryan, I'm a man now.
Not just like an after-your-bar-mitzvah
man, but a "man" man.
I had sex with a girl.
Summer, to be more specific.
How was it?
- I had sex.
- That bad?
No, not that bad...
...just kind of weird.
- Weird?
Yeah, but not kinky weird.
More like weird awkward.
But, hey, it was my first time.
She's a more experienced woman.
That's to be expected.
And I did make some faces in the middle
that I wish I could take back, but I can't.
There was also sort of a whiny noise
that came out towards the end...
...that probably wasn't my finest hour.
I sucked so bad.
I was like a fish flopping around
on dry land.
Ryan, I was Nemo.
And I just wanted to go home.
- Don't worry. You'll get another chance.
- That's the thing. I'm not sure I will.
The situation with Summer is murkier now
than it was before the awful fish sex.
I wouldn't refer to it as fish sex.
Good point. That's something
I was hoping to get more of: Tips.
Tricks of the trade. Summer's used to
driving a higher performance vehicle.
Don't know if I'm the guy
to talk to about romance.
- Why?
- Me and Marissa.
- It's different now, post-Oliver.
- Yeah? You wanna talk about it?
- No, I should get over to set up.
- Hey.
So do you have tips
or words of wisdom for me?
Do it again.
That's what I was afraid of.
And then we both just decided to wait.
Because, you know, we were really tired.
Well, you know how it goes.
- I wish we had waited.
- What? Who?
Me and Cohen.
- We had sex.
- Wait, what?
You guys did what?
I've been with you an hour.
How did this not come up?
I must have forgotten.
Okay, so I lied.
Things last night with Ryan went terribly.
I think he hates me.
- He doesn't hate you.
- He turned down sex.
He might be onto something.
Hey. You can't beat yourself up over it.
No one knew that Oliver would
turn out to be such a Looney Tune.
Except Ryan, and I didn't listen.
I don't know.
Maybe we just weren't meant
to be together.
Maybe we're just chasing after
the wrong boys.
Hello.
- How long will this continue?
- You've ruined my favorite holiday.
So until Valentine's Day is over,
we have nothing to talk about.
- All right.
- Hey, Dad. Are you busy?
- Just enjoying your mother's company.
- Awesome, I need to talk to you.
- What's going on?
- Nothing. Just need to talk to you.
- Girl stuff.
- Well...
...you've come to the master.
Hey, I got you.
I was young, impressionable and drunk.
Yeah, only child. Right here.
I'll get it. I need a little fresh air.
I never thought that I would have to...
...say this, but I think that we...
...need to have the talk.
- Now?
- It'll be as hard for me as it is for you.
Hey. Happy Valentine's Day.
That's what I like.
A little holiday spirit around here.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
I love these.
You know what they're called?
Forgotten Kisses. And you know
who used to make these? Hailey.
Hailey?
And how's she doing?
You heard from her at all?
No, and I don't expect I will.
Because when she left, she left angry.
Who knows, she's probably in
Asia or New York.
- Quite the globetrotter.
- Sometimes.
Once we thought she was in London,
but she was on a friend's boat...
...just down here in the harbor.
- Boat, huh?
Well...
...did you, you know...?
Did you...
...wear protection?
Oh, my God. Yes.
God, yes. I don't believe
you asked me that.
I'm sorry, but I had to.
It's so good that you did.
If you're gonna have sex,
you gotta be responsible.
- Yes. Responsible and awkward.
- Well, that's to be expected.
- It is?
- Yeah.
- That's what I thought.
- Listen...
...you were lucky to be able to hang
in there after all that foreplay.
Fore-what now?
Foreplay.
Oh, yeah. You know.
Massaging. You know...
...or nibbling the neck. Here's the point,
just because you're ready to go...
...it doesn't mean she is.
- I'm always ready to go.
Well, you're my son.
We Cohens are very sexual beings.
- Oh, my God.
- Virile. Get used to it.
Just disgusting.
- Foreplay, huh?
- I'm telling you...
...the appetizer is as good
as the main course.
Just swallowed a bit of throw up.
Well, I'm gonna pretend we never
had this conversation...
...but thanks, Dad.
- Hey, Seth. Seth, so...
...do you mind my asking?
Who'd you...?
Who'd you sleep with? I mean,
you got so many girls these days.
Summer?
You dog, you.
So, man, how's everything
with you and Marissa?
- Is she coming to the party tonight?
- I don't know. Fifty-fifty.
What about her mom?
You think she's coming tonight?
I have no idea.
I was just trying to get a head count
for the event.
Whoa. Whoa. Sorry.
- Ryan.
- Theresa.
- What are...? Hi.
- You always had a way with words.
- Are you working here?
- Yeah.
What better way to celebrate Valentine's
than serve p ğt Á to a bunch of rich people?
Oh, these are your friends
and neighbors. Sorry.
It's good to see you.
Cohen. What are you doing?
I need to talk to you...
...about what happened.
You remember the...
...sex?
- I'm trying to forget.
Right. Right.
That's actually why I'm here.
I feel you didn't get your money's worth.
Make a bang-for-your-buck joke,
you're gone.
No jokes.
There should be nothing funny about...
...what goes on right here.
You want another shot?
That's what I'm saying.
Pretty good.
Not as slobbery as yesterday.
- A little tense there.
- Ow, what are you...?
- What's up with the Vulcan nerve pinch?
- A little massage.
Okay. No. You're totally tickling me.
Stop.
- Stop.
- Stopping. Stopping.
Okay, what the hell are you doing?
A little something
that I like to call foreplay.
No.
I knew not to listen to my dad.
Not that I listen to him.
I'd never talk about that with him.
- You know what I'm saying.
- No more talking, Cohen.
Whatever you say, Summer.
So now he's in the hospital.
He'll be there a while.
Wow. That's unbelievable.
- No wonder you're so pissed off.
- No, I'm not.
Sure you are. I'd be.
Your best friend didn't believe you.
People you live with didn't listen to you.
And your girlfriend didn't trust you.
When you put it that way...
Sorry, it's none of my business.
No, it feels good to talk about it.
I haven't, really, with anyone else.
Hey.
Luke didn't know if you'd...
Hi, Marissa.
Theresa. Thanksgiving. We...
- Yeah. No, I remember.
- I'm helping cater the event.
She's a caterer.
Oh, well, that's really great.
So I guess I'll just talk to you tonight.
- You'll be here?
- Yeah.
- And so will you.
Okay. Bye.
- I should get back too.
- Yeah, see you tonight.
Sorry.
One day, when I'm reflecting
back on my life...
...I think I'll remember these chats
before big events as my favorite times.
What's this one about?
- What did you do to your eye?
- It's just a little bit blurry.
- Summer poked me in it with her big toe.
- What? Why?
Accident. There were limbs everywhere.
I'm lucky I can still see.
- So you guys did the deed again?
- Technically, yes. But it wasn't pretty.
- I think I suffered a spinal injury too.
- Next time you should wear a helmet.
- Mouth guard.
- I don't think there will be a next time.
Not after this latest debacle.
I think it might be over.
And what sucks about that, though, is
that I know I have so much more to give.
- I don't need to know that.
- Fair enough.
What about you?
Wanna skip the event?
I would, but there's someone
I wanna see.
Just an old friend.
If you want to skip it,
I'd be more than happy to. Believe me.
- I don't want to go either.
- Great.
But I have to.
Ryan's ex is gonna be there.
- She's a caterer tonight.
- And you want to what, spy?
Not exactly.
Yes.
Look, I don't know, Summ.
I don't know what's going on between us.
And now this girl is gonna be there.
Hug?
- Are you limping?
- Yeah. Cohen kneed me in the leg.
- Why?
- Must've read it in the Kamasutra.
- So you guys had sex again?
- Lf you can call it that.
There were, like, limbs everywhere.
- Love hurts.
- Yeah, tell me about it.
- You a cop?
- No.
No, I'm just looking for someone
who's staying here.
- Jimmy.
- Hey. Hailey.
Okay. Interesting company
you keep there.
You tracked me down. I'm impressed.
Those cookies were so good
that I couldn't let you leave without...
...giving me the recipe. Definitely gonna
be on the menu of my new restaurant.
- Your new restaurant?
- In fact, I was wondering...
...if you wanted to be
the first customer.
I'm experimenting with some dishes.
And I thought maybe, you know,
you could be the guinea pig.
Okay. Let me go get changed.
I'll be right back.
Maybe a couple months.
He's only in...
Take care. I'll see you soon.
All right.
Hey. If I teach you guys anything,
don't ever get married.
- I've heard that from you before.
- You'll hear it again.
I'll be at the bar.
No sign of our opponents.
- You ready to go?
- Yeah. Since before we got here.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi, there.
Want some of this...?
I actually have no idea what this is.
Odds are, mushroom leek crescent,
crab and brie phyllo. Usually is.
Seth, this is my friend Theresa.
Oh, this is your friend Theresa?
Hi. How are you? I'm gonna go with...
- That's her.
- That's her?
She's hot.
For Chino.
No. She is. She's beautiful...
...and nice and smart and funny, and did
I mention they've been friends forever?
- Only a few times.
- They did musicals together.
- And went to the winter dance.
- Ryan did musicals?
She was Peppermint Patty.
Ryan was Snoopy.
God, I hate Valentine's Day.
I don't know why we celebrate anything
around here.
- My dad didn't show up, huh?
- Nope.
I'm gonna go home, run a bath, and either
slit my wrists or drink a bottle of wine.
Wine. Definitely.
Good thing Kaitlin's at a sleepover.
I'll be blasting Bob Seger tonight.
We'll keep our windows closed.
- Bye.
Can we just start over?
Start over?
Hi. I'm Marissa.
You go to Harbor, right?
I know what you're trying to do.
And I can't.
I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you for a second?
- Look, if you want another shot...
- No. No. Believe me.
I get it. Clearly...
...something's not working.
It's me. It's fine. It's my fault.
- What are you trying to say?
- Maybe in a few years, you know?
I'll be...
I guess I'll be ready for you,
I don't know.
But in the meantime,
I think I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna bow out.
No, that's not asbestos.
Those are called floaties.
Asbestos and champagne.
What could be more romantic?
It's a work in progress. There's actually
nothing on the menu right now.
But the cookies are good.
- This place is gonna be great, Jimmy.
- Yeah. I know.
I feel for the first time in a while
that my life is... It's coming together.
So I don't understand, you know...
...I thought you couldn't
get out of here fast enough.
Yeah...
...until I realized I had nowhere to go.
- No one to see.
- Hailey, you can get stuck here.
You drive down the same streets,
go to the same places. It feels like...
...time isn't passing, but it is.
And it'll pass you right by.
You owe it to yourself.
Get out. Get free.
- Make a life for yourself.
- Why do I need to leave?
You're here.
Exactly.
I mean, you know, we can't...
Well...
...why not?
- Because I feel guilty enough...
...lying to Kirsten about the cookies...
...let alone...
Right.
But believe me...
...I wish we could.
I believe you.
Hey.
You okay?
- Cigarette?
- I quit.
Ryan Atwood. Look at yourself.
New clothes. New haircut.
Dating the homecoming queen.
Was dating?
I guess. I don't know.
- I like the haircut, by the way.
- Yeah?
You ever think about coming home?
Sometimes.
More lately.
You ever think about leaving?
Yeah. All the time.
But I don't know how.
So when you took
this particular catering job...
I needed the money.
And, yes...
...I was hoping I might run into you.
Home's Ionely these days.
Are you on a break?
Yeah. I'm free until cleanup.
You wanna get out of here?
Is it okay if I hang here?
Yeah. Sure. Of course.
Valentine's Day is wonderful, isn't it?
- You know, the thing about Ryan...
- No, this isn't...
- It's not... I'm fine.
- I know.
But the thing about Ryan is,
whenever things have gotten tough...
...everyone in his life has abandoned him.
- That's what he thinks I did.
Surprise him. Show him you didn't.
- That you're not gonna give up on him.
- He wants me to.
Well, only because he expects you to.
It's crazy.
Love is crazy.
It's always challenging. It's never easy.
- Yeah, but is it always this hard?
- Sometimes.
But you hang in there anyway.
If you're having the worst fight
in the world...
...or some stupid argument that neither
of you can remember what it's about.
Because it's...
It's worth it.
You guys have been
through so much already.
Why quit now?
- Hey, Mr. Cohen.
- Hello, Summer.
- Hi. Coop, you ready to go?
- Yeah.
- You okay, kiddo?
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Sometimes you make it hard to hate you.
- I know.
It's all... It's all... It's part of my charm.
Sometimes you make it easy.
- Charming too, no?
- Let's go home.
You tried to jump that fence
and your pants got caught.
I was pretty graceful.
- Yeah, especially when you face-planted.
- Glad to see you enjoy my pain.
We had no ice and we had to use
that bag of frozen peas.
Yeah. Frozen vegetables.
The miracle cure.
It's pretty amazing, us running into
each other on Valentine's Day.
I gotta get back. Help clean up.
So do you go to a lot
of these kinds of events?
Pretty much every week.
Well, then maybe I'll run into you again.
Plus, I know where you live.
- Oh, God.
- I know I shouldn't be here.
- No, you shouldn't, Luke.
- But it's just...
I don't know,
you looked so sad when you left.
I couldn't bear the thought of you
being alone on Valentine's Day.
Most people would enjoy that thought.
Not me.
Mrs. Cooper, you are an amazing girl.
Woman.
Lady.
- Lf Mr. Nichol doesn't appreciate you...
- No. He sure doesn't.
That's because he's too old to see
what he's lucky enough to have.
And you should also know that
you have always been the coolest mom.
- Luke.
- It's true. You let us listen to...
...whatever we wanted to in the carpool.
And you let us watch R-rated movies.
- And whenever we played Ultimatum...
- Ultimatum?
You know, who, of all your
friends' moms, would you rather do?
- That's a game?
- And whenever we played it...
...you always won.
- Really?
- I beat Kirsten?
- I thought you should know the truth...
...on Valentine's Day.
- Good night.
- Wait.
Thank you.
Would you like to come in?
I guess you're happy that today is over.
Absolutely.
Oh, my God, Sandy.
Somebody's got to keep
Hershey's and Hallmark in business.
- So you want to be my Valentine?
- Yes.
Just as soon as I have some of these
caramel chocolates. They're my favorite.
The square ones.
I like the ones with nuts.
Not to rub it in, man,
but I think Princess Sparkle is your type.
Yeah, I blew it for us both.
What's that?
Yeah. Are you kidding?
Great hooves.
- Cohen?
- Summer.
- Hey.
No.
The other night...
...when we...
...had sex.
- Yeah.
You weren't the only virgin in the room.
There was someone else in the room?
Like, filming us?
Me, jackass.
I'm a virgin.
Or I was a virgin.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know.
I guess I felt like
I had this reputation to uphold...
...and I figured you'd think less of me.
- No.
Are you kidding? Not at all.
I'm just... I'm shocked.
God. Never in a million years would I
think that you, of all people, not that...
That is not what's important here.
This was a huge moment in our lives
and we just blew past it.
- Really quickly.
- Hey, not that quickly.
Pretty quickly, yes.
And it was a big deal.
I think that it should've been special.
And we rushed it.
What if...
...we were to slow it down a little bit?
Maybe...
...start from the beginning?
What do you mean?
- You are so cheesy, Cohen.
- Come on.
I'm sweeping you off your feet.
Well, the sad part is...
...you kind of are.
- Where is she?
- What?
Theresa. If she's here, I want her
to know I'm not gonna lose you.
I'm not gonna give up on you.
She left.
- I'm so sorry.
- I know.
Can't you just forgive me?
How?
I don't know...
...if we should be together.
I mean, look how easy it was for someone
to come into our lives, come between us.
- How do I know it won't happen again?
- It won't.
- You have to trust me.
- Like you trusted me.
Ryan.
So that's it?
I can't pretend it didn't happen.