- Previously on The O.C.:
- This is school?
If you graduate from here, you can
get into any college in the UC system.
What happens in Mexico, you know,
stays in Mexico.
You don't deserve her.
- I didn't want to kill myself.
- I know.
- I'm so sorry about everything.
- Go away.
- Our chemistry is undeniable.
- I don't have a date to the cotillion.
Would you be my escort?
- Good news! I'm available.
- No.
- Who's Rachel?
- She works at the law firm I met with.
- So if I did take this job...
- You already have.
- This is Rachel.
- I'm Rachel.
You and Marissa want different things.
- You don't know what she wants!
- She doesn't want to live with you.
I wanna live with Dad.
At least for now.
Ryan's had a lot to overcome.
- Not exactly Harbor School material.
- Give me a shot.
First day of school. Excited?
You know, I ask you questions in
the hopes of eliciting an actual response.
- I feel I convey more with a look.
- You look adorable.
- No.
- Cute?
- Dope? Rad?
- Please, this is so painful!
I'm sorry.
- How was surfing?
- Cut it short.
I wanted to see the boys off.
Doesn't Seth look rad?
Oh, you do look rad! Mad props, son.
Thank God. Are you ready to go?
First day. You excited?
Enough said.
How do you do that? How do you
convey everything with just a look?
And again.
- How are you doing? Nervous?
- Why would I be nervous?
Because we're going to school
with, like, 300 Lukes...
...minus the redeeming social qualities.
I got it. Sorry.
You meant you were nervous.
- Don't be nervous.
- I'm not nervous. I'm just not going.
You have to go. You own the school.
What about Kickoff Carnival?
You're the social chair.
Let's see. Be humiliated
in front of the entire school...
...or hire someone
to do balloon animals?
Hire the guy who makes
the balloon octopus.
So your boyfriend cheated on you,
and, yes, you almost died in Mexico.
And the scandal with your dad...
If you're trying
to make me feel better...
Okay. The point is, there's
no such thing as bad publicity.
- Is that something burning?
- Okay, so...
...new oven. Haven't quite figured out
how to make French toast.
Not in the oven
would be a good place to start.
Since no one will hire me,
I've got plenty of time...
...I'm gonna go out and buy a cookbook.
Come on! It's good, they're crunchy.
- See?
- No, thanks.
I don't know who I'm more
worried about here.
I think it's safe to say that
this year is going to be different.
- Maybe this year will be different.
- That's the mantra every year.
And every year some big water-polo
player pees in one of my shoes.
Just kidding. They pee in both.
Ryan has Mr. Schmidt for pre-calc.
- What's wrong with Mr. Schmidt?
- Nothing. Say hi to his mole for me.
At least you have each other.
- Very wise, Dad.
- Thank you, son.
We're doomed.
The master race has been perfected
and they all go to our school.
Hey, fellas.
All right, don't get
your Speedos in a bunch.
- This is a nightmare.
- I bet, like, no one even knows.
- Are you kidding?
- I heard she died down there.
- She looks pretty good for a dead girl.
Hey, whores!
Why don't you go work another corner.
Summ, maybe I should go home.
Help my dad unpack.
Coop, that is as bad as it's gonna get.
I spoke too soon.
Hello, Summer. What does
your schedule look like today?
- Full.
- Really?
- A friendly face.
- How's it going?
- Not good. You?
- Worse.
So why don't we just get out of here?
Right now. Go down to the pier.
I can't. Dean Kim would call my dad.
Or worse, my mom.
- Okay. How about after school?
- I'm chairing the carnival committee.
- I know. I've been looking for an excuse.
- I think you found one.
- I'll meet you out front.
- Something to look forward to.
Coop! Can we go, please?
Hey. Could we maybe talk or...?
Stay away from her.
How?
We all go to the same school.
You should've thought about that...
...before hooking up with one
of her best friends! Ass!
- You okay?
- Yeah. I just have to get used to it.
This, I guess.
- But we're still on, right?
- Yeah. Something to look forward to.
Coop!
See you, Summer.
Slowly I thaw her icy heart.
- Look at you.
- Lf I must.
- New suit. New scent. New look.
- I feel like this is heading somewhere.
- New girlfriend.
- And there it is.
You're still all bent out of...
Oh, God! I should've found
an attractive co-worker years ago.
- It was a figure of speech.
- Rachel's attractive?
Is that her name? It's context.
Only, you know, in relation to which
she invokes amorous feelings...
...in my far more, extremely more,
attractive wife.
Good answer.
- Mornings used to be our time.
- I remember them well.
What happened?
Work happened.
Just hang on one sec.
Wait a minute. I can't get it.
Hang on one sec.
Just hold on. I got it.
Wait.
How did she know?
You're not gonna answer it, are you?
It's my dad.
Hey, Rachel.
Hi, Dad.
So if you'd care to join me
for lunch today...
...I can arrange for an empty chair.
There's nothing but empty chairs
at your table.
Seth Cohen?
Anna! Hey, how are you doing?
Excuse me, we were talking here.
So insulting him
counts as conversation?
If it doesn't, then we've never spoken.
Remember Anna from Pittsburgh?
- How could I forget?
- We're still on for lunch today, right?
- She probably didn't even hear me.
- Seth, what are you doing?
I thought you got past
this whole Summer thing at cotillion.
Right. And I know it seems like
not a lot of progress has been made...
...but I have to tell you... Yeah, not that
much progress has been made.
Despite all my best judgments,
I cannot not like her.
- You're such a boy.
- Well, whatever.
- I'm nothing but available for that girl.
- All right. Right there.
That's your problem. Girls like to be
chased by guys that aren't into them.
That sounds a little bit
like a game to me...
...and I don't really like to play games.
Unless we're talking about
Saturday-night Jenga...
...a little Magic: The Gathering.
I love Magic: The Gathering.
Maybe you just don't know how to play.
- Well, you're a girl, right?
- Yeah.
- And we're friends, right?
- Sure.
Then train me in the ways of women.
I don't understand chicks like Summer.
I'll teach you how to play Jenga.
- You really like her?
- Since I was 10.
Fine.
- But I make no promises.
- Trust me, I cannot do any worse.
That I trust.
You're my girl.
- Hey.
What were you doing this morning
when I called? You sounded...
Did I wake you?
- I was spending some time with my wife.
- Yeah? How'd that go?
- Well, I got to work on time.
- Too bad.
It might be a while before your wife
is in the mood for love.
Yeah? Something you know I don't?
I know lots that you don't,
but in this case...
...are you familiar
with the Balboa Wetlands?
Yeah, the largest coastal wetlands
in California.
Home to the blue heron,
the brown pelican and the swamp rose.
Right.
The wetlands are key
to water quality in the county.
- Not to mention, they're kind of pretty.
- Naturally, they must be destroyed.
The Balboa Heights are 250 acres
of land that sit above said wetlands.
- Every developer's after the Heights.
- Somebody got it.
And they're looking to tear it up,
put in condos, a golf course.
Thank God. The lack of golf courses
around here, it's tragic.
This is a policy-changing,
career-making piece of litigation.
A tree-hugging crusader, like yourself,
would kill for a case like this.
- And you want to share this with me.
- Yes.
Why?
Oh, my wife's company is the plaintiff.
It's her father's company.
Why even tempt me with this?
It's a conflict of interest.
I'm not even sure it'd be ethical.
The client, the Balboa Land Trust,
not only waived the conflict of interest...
...they insisted you take the case.
Your politics, your passion,
your dislike for your father-in-law.
- You're the ideal advocate.
- My wife will have a different spin on it.
You came to this firm...
...because we have the resources
to help you make a difference.
They're gonna teach this in law school.
So, what's it gonna be?
Your sex life? Or the swamp rose?
Did you know that
she overdosed on Vicodin?
You are not quitting your post
as social chair, Marissa.
You were elected by the students,
you've held the position for two years.
I know, Dr. Kim. But that was before
everything that happened this summer.
I understand you are going
through a lot of change right now...
...but you're a leader here at Harbor,
that doesn't have to change.
You're a wonderful example.
Students look up to you.
Not anymore.
Putting aside the issue of how walking
away from your responsibilities...
...will affect your college transcript...
...people are always going to talk.
You may as well give them
something good to talk about.
Don't disappear, Marissa.
This is your school, your life.
Your future.
Hey, what are you doing?
You never told me
about summer reading.
Who does summer reading?
- Apparently, everyone in my class.
- Oh. Yeah. Sorry about that one.
Anna here has convinced me
to join The Plank, the literary magazine.
I needed an extracurricular activity,
and apparently...
...you don't have to wear a
sports bra.
It's appealing on many levels.
Plus I feel...
...I have a few limericks
to share with the world.
Have fun.
I'm gonna hang with Marissa.
School might not suck this year.
Hey. I have to plan
this carnival thing after all.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
I talked to the dean, and...
...I think getting involved in school again
might not be a bad idea.
- I know, that sounds lame.
- Yeah. No, it's cool.
- So...
- Can we reschedule?
- Absolutely.
- What about the carnival?
I'll save you a ride on the Ferris wheel.
No Ferris wheels. I don't do heights.
- But we'll figure something out.
- Are you sure you're gonna be...?
I'm fine. I just got a lot of reading to do.
Like 500 years of it.
Okay. So I'll see you.
- Morning.
- I didn't hear you come in last night.
I didn't want to wake you.
You look nice.
Dad's demanding a company breakfast.
Some kind of crisis.
If this is how it's gonna be,
after a couple of weeks of work...
...we're gonna be like...
- Two ships passing in the morning.
What have they got you working on?
A big high-profile case.
How about lunch today? I'll pay.
No, actually, you can pay.
You're the one that's working
on a high-profile case.
How about Friday?
I'll have my people call your people.
I love you.
I love you too.
Hey, kid.
- How did school go for you?
- Fine. Just behind.
After one day? Nice work.
It's brutal. You're brave to face
those preppy little savages.
I mean the teachers.
I don't think it was a good idea,
me in private school.
- You're one of their smartest kids.
- It's not the work. It's just...
...everybody's got something,
except me.
- Well, you got Seth.
- Seth's got his women.
Seth Cohen?
Okay. So...
Really?
So you need something.
An activity. A sport.
- Ladies.
- Don Juan, we're trying to find...
...an extracurricular activity for Ryan.
- Okay.
- Harbor's got a great archery program...
Archery, no.
Absolutely not.
Fencing?
What century are you in? Open your
mind. This isn't me we're talking about.
With Ryan, we have an opportunity
to have a real athlete in the family.
Somebody to achieve...
...all that your Jewishness has
prevented me from accomplishing.
- I always wanted to play soccer.
- I used to play.
- Done.
- Glad I could help.
I didn't get around
to getting those cookbooks.
I guess it's better
to play it safe, then.
So how's sleeping on the sofa?
It's fine.
- It's just temporary.
- I can handle it.
Did you talk to your mom?
I'm sorry about all this, sweetheart.
- I just wish you would've told me.
- I know, I know.
But things will be different now.
Hey, don't get too excited.
The phone company is installing
an actual phone line.
A very big day.
- Hey, Mr. Cooper.
- Luke.
So is this your new place?
Looks great.
- Not buying it, Luke.
- Right. Can I talk to Marissa?
- No. You can't.
- Come on, it's me.
If I could talk to her...
Yeah, she told me what happened,
and she doesn't want to talk right now.
Come on. If anybody knows
about being in the doghouse...
Don't say it.
What can I do?
You can leave.
Well, tell her sorry.
Okay.
Thanks.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How did it go with the carnival?
- Oh, very exciting.
If I get out of my meeting early...
We're voting on cotton candy
versus funnel cakes.
- Cotton candy, no question.
- My thoughts exactly.
But I can't today. I got soccer practice.
- You do?
- Yeah, I'm gonna try out.
I figure getting involved in school
might not be such a bad idea.
Yeah. Plus, now we both get out
at 5, right? Meet you in the quad.
See you then.
- Hello. Is this seat taken?
- It is now.
Cool.
You can sit here
if you want, Summer.
Thanks.
Seth, come sit here by me.
Are you sure? You don't mind
one cheek on, one cheek off?
Sit!
Sitting.
Oh, my God!
Okay, so tell me about Tahiti.
- Oh, it was incredible.
- Anna just sailed to Tahiti.
Sailing is, like,
so not the fastest way to get anywhere.
If you'd flown,
you would've gotten there a lot sooner.
You should be on the debate team.
- Hi.
- Nice office.
- It came furnished.
- I brought you lunch.
- Well, it's not a lump of coal.
- When were you going to tell me?
- Soon.
Not soon enough.
I signed a deposition this morning.
Oh, honey.
I'm not even sure
if I'm gonna take this case.
There is no case!
You're talking about destroying one of
the world's most productive ecosystems.
It's like selling off the rainforest
to profit a few individuals...
...and asking generations
of others to pay for it.
We have proposed to protect 350 acres
of wildlife refuge and a natural park.
You'll still add 30% more traffic
and 10 tons of air pollution daily.
Not to mention
what you'll do to the water supply.
- You're gonna take this.
- No...
Sandy, it isn't even ethical.
I feel comfortable comparing ethics
with your father.
Well, as long as you're comfortable.
I gotta go.
I gotta keep this off my father's radar.
He's going to lose his mind.
All right, move! Don't wait for it!
Hey. You Atwood?
- What position you coming out for?
- Striker.
You see that kid out front?
That's Luke, the captain and striker.
Let's go! Show me something!
Hey, Ward!
You got a little competition!
Thanks.
Tomorrow we'll figure out the parking.
Make sure the band's booked.
No last-second surprises.
We need to talk.
You do not want to hear
what I have to say.
- Yes, I do.
- No.
All you want is for me to tell you
that everything's okay now. It's not.
I know, and I'm so sorry.
I don't care how you feel
or what you're going through.
- Because you didn't care about me.
- That's not true.
I slept with you. Then you slept
with one of my best friends.
I waited for you and you lied to me.
You humiliated me.
Marissa...
It's just...
I'm so sorry.
Do you have any idea how hard it is
to not be able to talk to you?
- You think it's easy for me?
- Let's just start over.
Please?
I don't know what I'd do without you.
Just because I ruined everything,
it doesn't mean I didn't love you...
...because I did.
I do.
You know what the worst part is?
If I hadn't caught you...
...I'd still love you too.
I gotta go.
I know that look.
I was trying to keep this from my dad,
and now it's on the front page.
I thought we could settle this privately.
- This was not to go to the press.
- It's your firm!
And now the entire
community knows we're fighting.
Well, I guess
they got the story straight.
- What are you doing?
- Morning ritual, Ryan.
- Coffee, bagel, Arts & Leisure.
- You have a morning ritual?
Something I've been crafting
for a while.
So, what's up, dude?
How's life? We never talk anymore.
Who are you?
- We had dinner 12 hours ago.
- Fine. Keep it all bottled up.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
That wasn't nothing. I saw
thoughts forming and words percolating.
It's just...
- Never mind.
- Come on! What was that, dude?
Last night, I saw Marissa with Luke.
- Making out?
- Making up.
Luke was crying.
Luke was crying?
- That doesn't sound like anything.
- It didn't sound like nothing.
Looked like they were
getting back together.
So ask her about it.
If nothing's going on, she'll tell you.
- Do not tell him!
- Shouldn't I just be honest?
Never. You guys haven't even gone
on a date yet. You'll freak him out.
Trust me, what he doesn't know
won't hurt you.
- Hi.
What happened to you last night?
I tried calling.
Sorry. I got slammed last night.
I'm behind.
After two days?
What did you do?
Nothing. My meeting went long.
- How'd it go?
- Good. I think it'll be good.
What did you do after?
- After I couldn't find you, I went home.
- Sorry.
Yeah, but you've got soccer
practice later. Maybe I'll stop by.
I gotta get to class. I'll see you.
- I mean, ew!
- That's my girl.
- Cohen, you're a good dissector.
- Hands of a surgeon.
It's decided, then.
You'll be my lab partner.
You can write up the lab reports.
Actually, Seth already has a partner.
He's promised himself to me, right?
Yes. I am betrothed.
Good.
She wanted to be my lab partner.
You're supposed to help me get her.
Watch and learn, Cohen.
Follow my lead.
Scalpel!
Where shall we begin?
The heart.
Well, Sanford, you're all anybody's
talking about around here.
Did you bring me into this firm
because of this case?
We didn't have this case
when we hired you. Don't worry.
You've already convinced everyone
that you're really torn.
This could go
to the state supreme court.
Yeah. And I know I could win.
It's a question of what I'm gonna lose.
Well, if your marriage
can't survive this...
...what kind of marriage is it?
Hey, Atwood, good!
Good! Take a shot!
- All right.
- Good hold, guys.
All right, let's keep it moving.
Let's go! Line up!
Hi.
Sorry about yesterday.
That was kind of intense.
The last time I cried was when
Macaulay Culkin died in My Girl.
Yeah, the bee stings.
You were a mess.
Kick! All right, good, good.
All right, guys, let's go.
- Hey, Ward! Get over here!
- I will...
Sorry, coach.
I had to tape up my ankle.
Excuse me.
All right, we're finally all together?
I wanna see some hustle now.
Hey! Illegal!
Get in my office. Right now!
Don't put any weight on it.
Nice job.
What's your problem, dude?
How was soccer?
So, Pops, how's the new job?
Hey, Mom, I...
I'm just going to be quietly eating now.
Hey.
What was that about?
- What?
- You attacked him.
He beat me to the ball.
It was a clean tackle.
- Why are you lying to me?
- What are you talking about?
- You and Luke.
- I saw you yesterday. I heard everything.
- I didn't know what to say.
Why not tell me the truth?
Why didn't you just tell me,
instead of hurting him?
- You're as bad as he is.
- I don't need any more lies.
I didn't lie to you. What happened
was between me and Luke.
- It has nothing to do with you.
- Right, it has nothing to do with me.
It just isn't gonna happen.
No, it's not.
Your coach called.
He wants to suspend you
for two games.
- Great.
- He thinks you got talent.
He also thinks your attitude sucks.
- It does.
- Sit down and listen to me.
You can stand if you want,
but you know how lawyers love to talk.
You don't need this blowout
on the soccer field...
...to turn into a suspension from school.
- This school can do great things.
- For Seth, not me.
You're angry. I know that.
I don't blame you.
Every day at that school,
you're gonna run into spoiled rich kids...
...whose ass you are gonna
want to kick.
You've gotta find a way
to work it out right now.
Let's forget about suspension.
We're always one mistake
away from...
...from someone taking you from us.
You know, Seth was never
really big on organized sports.
I'd love to see you play.
Go to some of your games.
And women usually find
stark brutality so romantic.
- I messed up.
- Yeah, well.
In my experience,
you should always apologize.
Even if you've done nothing wrong,
your shoes get peed in so much less.
- That was a metaphor.
- Apologize. Right. And to Luke?
That crybaby? No, man.
He can drown in his own tears.
They're all the same.
It's too bad, because I could tell
you really liked him.
Hi.
- Do you mind? Can we...?
- We have to get to class. Come on.
I do love Mr. Solomon Burke.
Hey.
I was...
I was gonna bring you
a bouquet of swamp roses...
...but apparently they're endangered.
I'm gonna take it. I gotta. I'm sorry.
It's who you married.
I know.
You know, I've been
pissing you off for years.
Why stop now?
My father, my husband...
It's gonna be a long year.
Could be a couple of years.
Yeah. Well, I couldn't be married
to a man who wasn't a man.
I'm all man.
We'll get through this.
There's a reason why we're together.
I have that suspicion.
Okay.
Okay?
- The kids are at that carnival.
- I heard that rumor.
- Are you getting out?
- Are you getting in?
Maybe.
Maybe. Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- Why do you keep this thing on?
Emergencies.
It's my dad. And it's an emergency.
Hey, Dad.
Rachel, hi.
- Lf only Skee-Ball were a school sport.
- A boy can dream.
- Let's see you take a shot.
- I'll pass.
Take one shot!
Take a shot. It's very easy.
Okay? Concentrate.
Lean to the left a little bit.
- Any luck finding Marissa?
- No sign of her. You guys?
Nothing. We have to let
Anna concentrate...
...as she dares to step up to the master.
Okay. Clearly, you're a lesbian.
I'm gonna go trade in my tickets
for some cash prizes.
Hey, do you think I should get Summer
something? What would she like?
I can figure it out.
Seth doesn't understand
the whole hard-to-get strategy.
- That's because he's not.
- Oh.
Why are you helping him
with Summer?
Why not?
Seth doesn't see me that way.
When he looks at Summer,
he sees lips, hair and boobs.
When he looks at me, he sees...
...a lab partner.
- We're friends.
- And you're gonna let that slide?
Anna...
...guys wanna be chased by girls
who aren't interested in them.
Come on!
Summer, it's right here.
So do girls.
She's heading for the Ferris wheel.
Gotta go.
Good luck.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Actually, I'm glad we came.
It's not half as bad as last time.
- You're going with me.
- Yeah, okay. Let's go.
Do you mind?
Not getting involved.
- What are you doing?
- I wanna talk.
I thought you were afraid of heights.
But this is important.
Oh, boy.
Look. I said some things last night,
and I just want you...
Whoa.
- What's going on?
- We're stopped.
Why are we stopped?
Keep them up there a few minutes.
Let them work it out.
You are the master.
Cohen, there's something
I wanna tell you.
All right. More advice.
I'm ready, bring it.
Was this all part of the plan?
Because it looks like it's working.
Yeah.
It was all part of the plan.
So are you gonna go?
Yeah. Thank you.
I got this for you.
It's all I could get with my tickets.
Thanks.
Hi, Summer.
What's going on?
Coop's stuck on the Ferris wheel...
...and I was looking for someone
to go on the Tilt-A-Whirl with me.
I'll go on it with you.
Okay. I may vomit.
I like those odds.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
You had to get
the cheap Ferris wheel!
What kind of carnival is this, Cooper?
Okay.
Look...
I don't talk a lot about stuff...
...and I really don't trust people.
But I trust you.
And I want to make it, this, work.
No matter what. If we ever get down,
maybe we could talk about it.
- Who knows when that'll be?
- Please don't say that.
Maybe you just need something
to take your mind off of it.
Fifty feet in the air,
how do you expect me to...?
One more time.