Previously, on 90210....
We have a new faculty advisor, Mr.
Cannon everyone.
He said if I wanted back on
the Blaze I had to sleep with him.
- There's going to be a hearing.
- I don't want a hearing.
You go in there, you tell the truth,
and everything's going to be fine.
I saw you at a cafe with
a handsome man.
That kiss was a mistake.
I'm going to tell Harry everything
the minute he gets home.
- Are you sure that's a good idea?
- I wish I could bet on the Lakers.
- They're about to go on a roll.
- Someone's got the gambling bug.
Why are you doing this?
Nothing happened.
- Why are you ruining my life?
- Nothing happened.
- I lied. Where are you going?
- Back to my mom's.
But you said that was the last
place in the world you want to be.
I definitely don't want to be here.
I'm gonna have to talk to the school
board to determine your punishment.
But trust me, there will
be severe consequences.
How's it going?
- Sticky.
- Grab this.
I have some graffiti
I'd like you to paint over.
Kids can be cruel.
She's a beauty.
Don't know how the hell you built her
all by yourself, though.
Lot of hours.
Guess I would come out here to work when
I got upset or pissed or whatever...
Looks like it hasn't been
the best year for you.
You could say that.
It's all gonna turn around.
Always does. Two weeks ago I was sharing
a cell with nine finger Nick,
and now I'm in CA getting ready
to go sailing with my kid.
You should've never been sent away.
You were framed.
I know, but what's done is done.
Besides I'm here now.
For good.
- You're staying in L.A.?
- Hell, yeah.
I'm thinking about opening up a
tackle shop down by the marina.
Could be pretty nice.
Just need a little seed money,
is all.
And then I can start looking for a
place for you and me to live nearby.
Really?
I'm not gonna let you stay here
with that bastard of stepdad?
Come on. Not an option.
I'm here for the future
zoologists of America meeting.
What's the only mammal that can survive
its entire life without drinking water?
- It's the rule.
- I'm your girlfriend.
Fine.
Kangaroo rat. Happy?
See, was that so hard?
All right! Ladies and gentlemen,
our dealer is here.
- That's everybody?
- Everyone on the evite.
- You sent out an evite?!
- Chill. Kidding.
Hilarious.
Everybody ready?
Who's that?
- No idea.
- Go find out.
- Why me?
- 'Cause you wanted to be the door guy.
Go ahead.
Who is it?
Kangaroo rat.
Let me in.
So this is it.
West Bev's very own
little underground speakeasy.
Nice job. I didn't know you had it
in you to organize something like this.
- What are you doing here, Mark?
- I want in.
You're not invited.
Maybe this will change your mind.
Wait, you're not scared
you're gonna lose, are you?
Have a seat.
It'd be a pleasure
to take your money.
- Deb, you pick up the dry cleaning?
- I'm fine. Day was good, thanks.
I didn't pick up the dry cleaning.
I understand.
Obviously, you were very busy.
- What's going on?
- I jusy expected my dry cleaning.
I'm not talking about the dry cleaning.
What's going on with us?
All this bitterness.
All this sniping.
We should go to counseling.
What?
We don't need to go to counseling.
That's for people that have problems.
- We have problems.
- No, we have issues.
Issues that any couple is gonna
have after 20 years of marriage.
- We don't.
- We do.
I kissed another man.
That didn't come out right.
He kissed me, actually.
It was my yoga teacher.
And it didn't mean anything.
When did this happen?
Two months ago.
And you didn't say anything?
And that's the third queen.
Looks like it's just you two.
All in.
Call or fold?
All right, I'll match that.
And...
I will raise you.
$6,175.
I don't have that here, but,
will you give me a marker?
I'm good for it.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure, trust me.
- Will you give me the marker?
- That is not a problem.
I would be glad to take your money
in whatever form you'd like to give it.
All right.
Show your cards, boys.
Full house.
- Nice.
- Nice! Full house.
Nice hand.
Thank you.
Unless...
Wait...
Do four queens beat a full house?
I don't know, I'm asking you guys.
Does that...?
Does it...?
Don't worry about
getting the money to me right away.
As long as you have it to me
by the end of the day tomorrow,
I won't have to have the guys on
the baseball team break your legs.
Peach pit team
www.forom.com
Season 02 episode 19
Multiple Choices
This seat is saved.
- For who?
- My boyfriend.
Have you seen him?
Blond, blue eyes, chiseled jaw.
Muscles everywhere,
even in his ears.
Sounds like a
pretty good-looking dude.
You're way more my type.
What's up?
You've been all AWOL lately.
I got a big tournament coming up. I'm on
the court before and after school.
Good thing I took notes
during SAT prep course.
You wanna come over tonight?
Go over some strategies?
I've got conditioning.
This is exigent.
The Sats are in two days.
It means urgent or pressing.
See, this is why you need to study.
I'll be fine.
Come on, Sats are important.
You gotta think about college.
College isn't for everyone.
What?
I'm not planning on going,
at least not right away, anyway.
If I want to play professional tennis,
I have to do it now.
Sounds to me like you're
throwing away your future.
It sounds to me like
you're really judgmental.
Tennis is my future, Silver.
And if you don't understand that,
maybe you don't understand me.
We come in from the bay,
and then we paddle out to this cave,
and out of nowhere, this tortoise
comes up to me, tips my kayak...
And so, I clobbered the tortoise,
and then I ate it.
- What was that for?
- You're a million miles away right now.
I thought you'd be a little bit
more excited to go out, since...
You were the one who asked me.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I am excited.
Really.
There's nowhere I'd rather be
than right here with you, right now.
Honest.
I got to take this.
I'm so sorry.
- Hey, Mark.
- Little Dix,
got your message. Really hope you
were calling 'cause you got my money.
Sort of.
I was thinking...
I got a pretty dope laptop
and some DJ equipment
that's fairly new, so...
I don't want your old crap.
Do you have the money or not?
Look...
I just need a little more time.
You know...
I could forget about the money.
What?
As long as you do me a little favor.
It's my girlfriend's birthday tomorrow,
and I want to decorate her locker
so she's surprised when she
gets to school in the morning.
What? You want me
to get you streamers?
No, smart-ass.
I need the key to the school,
so I can get in after hours.
Your dad's the principal. You can
figure out a way to make that happen.
If you don't want to help me,
that's fine.
Just have the six grand in
cash for me tomorrow morning.
It's no New York pizza,
but it's pretty good for L.A.
- How did the job search go?
- No luck.
Surprise... turns out
nobody's interested in hiring an ex-con.
- You'll find something.
- Maybe I should take a page
out of your mom's book and
marry my own billionaire.
You think Oprah would have me?
Or maybe your mom's
billionaire could fund us.
Stick with the Oprah route.
Can't ask that guy for a dime.
Who said anything about asking?
I'm just kidding.
This is what happens. You hang around
criminals, you end up thinking like one.
You got the key?
Of course.
- Can I have it?
- I'm not just going to give it to you.
I'm going in with you.
Whatever. Suit yourself, man.
- What's going on?
- I forgot...
My girlfriend's birthday
is next month. My bad.
- Tonight, we're stealing the Sats.
- Stealing...?
What the hell are you doing?
You really are as slow
as you look, aren't you?
We... are... stealing...
The tests aren't even here.
The tests are not usually here,
but you see, this year,
West Bev is a test center,
- and rumor is...
- They're not here.
I heard my dad saying they don't get
delivered until the morning of the exam.
You can keep searching if you want.
You're not going to find anything.
Let's go!
The tests aren't here.
You guys are real idiots.
I'm outta here.
Dude.
What the hell?
I'll see you guys later.
Good morning, Wilson.
Did you guys really do this?
That test was going to bring
us some serious lettuce.
My buddy Jason was pissed.
Plus, he's got to get into Stanford.
He's not much for studying,
so he was double pissed.
Come on! That's funny.
Have a sense of humor here.
Or a trophy.
Here... have a trophy.
It's not funny.
How am I supposed to build an outfit
around florescent orange?
I don't want to take
a class with Mr. Cannon!
- What a pervert.
- Did you hear that?
It's not blowing over.
It will, I promise.
Just give it some more time.
I have a better idea.
Get everybody's attention.
Fine, I'll do it myself.
Excuse me, everyone!
I have an announcement
I have to make.
Mr. Cannon is not a molester.
He's not a pervert.
I am the pervert.
I perverted justice.
I perverted morality.
I perverted his life.
He didn't do anything wrong.
And I apologize again
for spreading such a vicious lie.
And trust me, I get it if you don't
ever want to speak to me again.
Like I said,
I am the pervert here.
Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
Come on down from there.
You really shouldn't have done that.
- You really shouldn't have done that.
- I had to.
We're proud of you.
A little embarrassed to be seen with
you right now, but definitely proud.
Does that mean you forgive me?
- We've all done bad stuff.
- Speak for yourself.
Of course we forgive you.
Clearly, you know what
you did was wrong, so...
Perverted, actually.
I missed you guys so much.
Hug! Group hugs!
- You wanted to see me?
- Take a seat.
Dad, I wasn't...
- I broke into the school, but...
- But what?
I didn't do any of the vandalism.
That wasn't me.
It was your friends.
You just went along.
They aren't my friends. I had
no idea what they were gonna be doing.
- I didn't even wanna be here...
- Then why were you?
- I was just...
- Dixon, why were you there?
I didn't even mean...
I've been gambling.
For a while.
At first it was sports,
then it turned into poker, and,
I guess
I kind of got a little over my head.
'Cause I lost a lot of money to a kid,
and I couldn't pay him back.
He asked me to break into
the school, and I agreed.
Because I had no other choice.
I owed him money.
So,
I stole your key to the school,
and I broke in.
Turns out that the kid and his
friends just wanted to steal the Sats.
When they found out
that it wasn't here,
- they vandalized the school.
- They?
Who are they?
Who are the kids in the masks?
I got all day.
Mark Driscott,
Nat Frazier,
Jason Brewer,
Steve Peterson.
I heard about what you
did in the cafeteria.
A rather unorthodox
approach to repentance,
but fundamentally courageous of you.
So, thank you.
I really am sorry.
I never meant for
all this to happen.
I know, and I appreciate that.
Don't be late for class.
What?
I should've been honest a long time ago,
but I would like to be honest now.
Novel idea.
Fine, I deserve that.
Good thing our project's graded
on a curve?
Cause I'm pretty sure the tall kid
with the fauxhawk can't even read.
The reason I didn't tell you
about kissing Kai was because I...
I felt something for
him when he kissed me.
Maybe I should just...
I can't believe that I'm
hearing this.
- How could you be so selfish?
- Wait a minute this isn't all my fault.
I'm not the one that's kissing
other people!
You're just the one who goes to work
flirts with them
and then comes home
and doesn't talk to me.
You're selfish, too. And...
- And you're cold.
- Cold?
I'm cold?! How dare you!
How dare I what?
State what's been obvious for months?
You have been living in
your own world.
Completely oblivious
to everything that I have been feeling.
It's like you're not even here.
And Kai...
Fine... my yoga teacher... was.
He was compassionate
and understanding,
and he listened to me when I spoke.
And he wanted to know
what I was feeling.
I stopped that kiss because it was
the right thing to do.
Not because I wanted to.
Come on, let's get out of here.
We need to go to counseling.
This sucks.
At least your family
just started sucking now.
Mine's sucked since I was seven.
- That's when my parents got divorced.
- You were that young?
I guess it was good, in a way.
Less time to think
my parents were great,
and more time to realize
they're just people.
It still sucked, though.
It's not fair.
You know, none of this is fair.
I just, I want to kick something
or scream or just,
you know, run away
or I don't know, I just...
Annie, what...
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I don't know!
I don't know why I just did that.
But I just felt really frustrated
- and I had to do something.
- That was something.
Here.
Are you okay?
It's cold!
- I think it's great!
- Yeah, you're crazy.
Come here, crazy.
How come when I get out of
the water, it's so cold?
Come here.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
You should be with Naomi.
What?
I know what she did was messed up,
but she did the right thing in the end.
And, and she's sorry.
And that's gotta count for something.
So, you should forgive her.
Ace.
It's a serve where the tennis ball
is not touched by the receiver.
I may have added a couple,
tennis flashcards to my vocab deck.
You love tennis, so...
I'm going to learn to love tennis.
You were right,
I was completely judgmental.
The fight was all my fault.
Which also happens to be a serve
that fails to be placed in the
correct area of the court.
And this is a huge opportunity,
once in a lifetime.
You should see where it takes you.
- Really?
- Really.
And I'm gonna be at your big match.
I appreciate it,
but you don't have to stay.
Just knowing you support me is enough.
Yeah, but I want to.
I don't think you even believe that.
You hate sporting events.
I don't want you to have to sit
through a boring three-hour match out
in the sun just for me.
Besides, it is more exigent
that you use this time to study.
Okay, are you sure?
Cause I want to be here for you.
I'm positive.
Game, match, set.
You win.
You're here.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. It's my fault. I...
No, what you did was wrong,
but you did the right thing in the end.
And... that was brave of you.
I should have been there for you.
I missed you so much.
Believe me, I will never do
anything like this again.
I love you, Liam.
You, too.
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
I thought you weren't coming.
I wasn't,
and then I changed my mind.
I really want to support you.
And I brought some sat study cards,
in case I get bored.
I guess I should go
sit in your section.
I assume I just follow
the cell phone cameras
and ogling stares to your father.
Is that him over there?
Yeah, that's my dad...
I don't think it's...
Just go do your thing.
I'll go sit with him, okay?
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Silver, Silver, wait!
- Hi, I'm Silver.
- Hi.
You want an autograph?
- You have a pen?
- I'm Erin Silver.
I'm sorry.
I'm Teddy's girlfriend.
So Teddy has a girlfriend?
Yeah, he does.
It was really nice to meet you.
I just, I realized that I gotta...
I gotta go.
- So, enjoy the match.
- Okay, thank you.
So?
So, the superintendent called
and said she was gonna expel
whoever was responsible
for the break-in.
And I said that there was
a glitch on the security tapes,
- so we couldn't see who it was.
- You did?
If you get expelled, it ruins
your chances of getting into college.
I'm not going to let that happen.
No, don't, don't thank me yet.
As of now, your life
outside of school is over.
No going out, no car, no cell phone
except for in emergencies.
And no more video games.
And obviously, you mention
this to none of your friends.
You got it?
Did you tell mom?
No, your mom's got a
lot going on right now.
If she asks why
you're not going out,
just tell her you're
focusing on your schoolwork.
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, me, too.
Me, too. I thought you were
better than this.
What are you doing here?
Actually, this is my house,
so I can go wherever I want.
I'm actually thinking
about turning
the carriage house into a gym.
Put my elliptical machine over there,
the free weights there in that corner
- But this is where I work on my boat.
- Not anymore.
- What are you gonna do punch me again?
- You deserve so much worse than that
for cheating on my mom. Believe me, it's
a matter of time before she leaves you.
Then you don't know
your mother very well, do you?
Cause believe it or not,
Colleen and I are closer than ever.
And we're very worried
about you, son.
See, it's not normal for a young man to
spend all of his time alone in a shed.
That's why, when she goes away
to Europe next month,
I'm gonna start my renovations.
- Mom's going to Europe?
- What, she didn't tell you?
Yeah, she's going on a
spa week in Switzerland.
You know, at first
she was actually hesitant
to leave us here alone.
But I promised her
that we'd be fine.
So it's just gonna be you
and me alone, for a week.
I can hardly wait.
So, how was your day?
It was fine.
You know, some challenges, but fine.
- How was your day?
- Good.
Funny thing happened.
I ran into Cindy at Trader Joe's.
Do you remember her
from the fundraiser last month?
- Yes, how is she?
- Good, she looks good.
I think she put
some highlights in her hair.
May I be excused?
But we just sat down.
You hardly touched your food.
I'll take my plate with me. I just have
a lot of studying to do for the Sats.
- Sure
- Okay. Thanks.
Look, I'm sorry, but I gotta
cancel our plans for tonight.
Okay. Why?
I'm grounded.
You're grounded for what?
Nothing.
If you're not grounded for anything,
then why can't we hang?
Look, I... I can't really
talk about it right now.
Okay?
Fine, whatever, Dixon.
I'll see you tomorrow at school, okay?
- What's up?
- So, dinner was pretty awkward.
And listen, I think it's because...
I'm sorry,
I've had a really bad day.
Can we not talk about this?
Yeah, sure.
No problem.
Dad, listen, I've been
thinking about the tackle shop.
Don't worry about it, kid.
I'll figure it out.
- It's just gonna take some time.
- Maybe I can help speed things up.
I appreciate the gesture, but it's gonna
take a lot more than 30 cents.
These are worth
a lot more than 30 cts.
They're from
my stepdad's collection.
- Like how much more?
- Ten thousand dollars more.
I just can't stay here anymore.
Use the money to open the tackle shop
and get your own place.
Then I can get the hell out
of here and move in with you.
You've reached Liam.
Leave a message.
Hi, it's me.
I mean, it's Annie.
Look, I just wanted
someone to talk to.
My parents are acting
like nothing's wrong.
And Dixon doesn't
want to talk, and...
I just really don't
wanna be here anymore.
I just feel trapped.
But anyway, call me?
To send your message with
normal delivery, press one.
To erase, press two.
Message erased.
- Hey, did you just call me?
- Oh, my God, no.
I must've pocket dialed you
or something. I'm sorry.
Okay, cool.
- So...
- So, I will see you tomorrow at school.
Sure, see you at school.
May I please get five
brain booster smoothies
with acai extract
and an energy boost?
And can you label four of them "Silver,"
"Adrianna," "Annie" and "Liam"?
Anything for you.
So, what's all this
brain boosting for?
- Sats.
- You nervous?
Actually, I'm not.
I'm feeling pretty good about it.
Are you now, sweetie?
Do close your mouth, Naomi.
That's really not
a good look for you.
So, do you like what
I'm doing to the place?
- What are you talking about?
- Oh, the beach club.
It was a wedding
present from Olivier.
He really is too generous.
We decided to give our
marriage another go.
I forgave him for cheating,
and in exchange
he told me we could live
anywhere in the world.
I guess there is no place like home.
- You moved here? You're back?
- Please.
I wasn't going to
let you keep me away.
I suppose I should let you know,
I'm a little upset with you.
You turned your back on me.
That really wasn't very nice.
And you know me,
I do tend to hold grudges.
Call me karma, babe.
And karma is a bitch.
Okay, five smoothies
ready to go, Ms. Clark.
You want a power bar?
My mom made me take
like six this morning
just in case I got hungry
during the test.
I'm cool, thank you.
I just gotta say it kinda feels like
you were blowing me off last night.
Look, I swear I wasn't.
All right?
Things at home, they...
just aren't great right now.
- I really like you, Ivy.
- Okay.
No, I'm serious.
I really, really like you.
You have to know that.
But, I have to go.
I'm so sorry and I'll make it up to you.
I promise.
- Good luck on the test.
- Right.
What's up, little Dix?
You got my money?
- What?!
- "What?!" Come on, man.
I got the shaft in this deal.
No money, no Sats, nothing.
Dude, I got you into the school.
I held up my part of the bargain.
You should be thanking me...
you could've been expelled.
My dad has tapes of us in the hallway
that night. He knows it was you.
He could've gone to the
superintendent, but he didn't.
So I think we're kind of even.
Interesting.
Why are you smiling?
Now I know the principal
covered up to save his son.
That's gonna come in handy someday.
See ya, bud.
You haven't returned
any of my calls.
Take your seats, everyone.
So, are we okay?
Seriously?
No, we're definitely not okay.
Go sit down.
The test is gonna start.
Please be sure to mark
your answers clearly
on the answer sheet.
And be mindful of the time.
Every second counts.
If you have any questions,
raise your hand, and I will come to you.
Good luck to all of you.
You may begin.
Peach Pit Team
www.forom.com