previously on 90210...
I wanted to get something
permanent to symbolize our love.
We just had sex in the media room.
You and me in the
storage room right now.
Being your friend?
I'm over it.
I already beat you to it.
Us getting together didn't
work out for either of us, okay?
But don't punish my sister.
West Beverly high doesn't revolve
around Kelly Taylor's love life.
If anybody should be
pissed here, it's me.
Brenda? Really?
I wanted to ask you something.
- Will you be my valentine?
- Yeah.
- I don't want to keep fighting.
- Me, neither.
Let's end this.
I want to show a film
as my presentation.
- I'm in it?
- Just you wait.
You filmed us having sex?
What's wrong with you?
I love you so much, Dixon.
Just stay away from me.
Silver did this?
Silver, what are you doing?
I want you to fix all of this.
Silver, listen.
okay.
- Silver, please.
- Don't you move.
- I'm not.
- We both know you tried to turn Dixon against me.
Okay. How can I fix things?
You can start by telling him the truth.
You can tell him how you were manipulating
him and feeding him lies about me.
Okay. No problem.
Do you want me to call him?
- Stop!
- Silver...Silver!
Calm down. It's okay. It's okay.
- Silver!
- Let go of me!
Okay. It's okay
Get off! Get off. Get off.
Silver, listen to me.
It was because of the movie.
He really hated the movie, didn't he?
I thought he would love
the movie, but he hated it.
I don't know Dixon  at all.
He was the one person
that I loved the most
and I don't know who he is.
I don't understand.
Come on. You don't have
to figure it all out now.
- Yes, I do.
- No. You don't.
You need to get some rest.
Listen, let's call Kelly. Okay?
Why are my hands bleeding?
I might get blood on your couch.
Okay, doesn't matter.
Let me get you a bandage. Okay?
Then we'll call Kelly.
Okay. Then we'll call Kelly.
Bandages... uh, bandages.
Yeah, I know that I have them in here.
Okay, got it.
Let's see that hand.
Silver?
I thought we were meant to be together.
But if you want to be alone...
then just go.
mom, can I call you back?
Is everything okay?
No, I'm not with her.
Why? What happened?
Is Dixon all right?
Yeah, no, I'm coming home now.
- Is everything okay?
- No!
I don't know. It's Silver.
I have to get home.
and I didn't drive.
I'll take you.
* I sit and hear
sentimental footsteps... *
You need to tell us exactly
what's been going on.
Don't leave anything out.
What? What do you mean, Silver
broke into your apartment?
I mean, I come home and
the window is smashed, okay?
- And Silver is there.
- No way.
She got a giant tattoo of your name?
- And you didn't think this was worth mentioning?
- I'm sorry.
Believe me, Kelly, all right?
Something is going on with her.
No, I would know.
Do you know about her movie?
What movie?
She kind of filmed us...
having sex.
I think I'm going to throw up.
I had no idea.
- You had sex?
- You made a movie of it?
Freaky.
Totally, totally freaky.
- What?
- Silver apparently made...
har-gow, flower scallion rolls...
And
lor-mai-gai.
- Don't eat the leaf.
- What?
- Got it. Thanks.
Uh, so Silver apparently what?
Um, hold up.
Can we get some sesame balls, too, please?
thanks.
Oh, it's Naomi. Hold on.
We have to talk.
Crazy night.
- I know, I heard.
- Heard what?
That Liam's a psychopath
and an awesome kisser?
- I was talking about Silver's movie, but wow.
- Wow what?
Liam is a total psychopath
and an awesome kisser.
What happened with Silver?
Apparently, she made a porno of herself
and showed it at some theater.
Naomi: What?
- Naomi?
- Um, no, Silver.
Why would she do that?
I don't know.
Unless...
- it's drugs.
- It's got to be drugs.
- No, no way. - I'm guessing
cocaine. - Maybe meth.
- PCP?
- Or LSD.
- Could be speed.
- Weed?
- Methadone, mescaline, amphetamine, ketamine...
- ecstasy.
Stimulants, sedatives...
no! Stop!
All right? She's not doing
drugs. I would know.
Why else would she
break into my apartment?
- Or set a fire?
- Or get a tattoo?
Why else would you film
yourself having sex?
Oh, well, to improve your moves, of course.
What? Athletes watch replays.
It's the same thing.
I don't know.
Sesame balls?
Is that your pet name for Navid?
I should call Dixon.
it's Kelly.
I'll take it.
- Hello?
- Nope, Dixon's not answering.
What did sesame balls say?
No, we don't know where she is.
- I'm worried.
- I'm scared.
We have to find her.
Before she hurts someone or herself.
Oh, God, what is happening?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-¿¨»Ò corrections: aydin1954 – addic7ed.com
90210 Season 01 Episode 18
We need to divide up.
Debbie and I will
check out the peach pit.
Dixon, I'm going to drop you off at home
- so you'll have access to another car.
- Got it.
Somebody should check out the school.
Annie, here are the keys.
Ethan, you go with her.
Uh, sounds good.
Kelly, you want to stay
here in case she comes back?
No, I have to do something.
Harry: Okay, well, at least
let somebody drive you.
- No prob.
- No, that's okay.
Let me be your chauffer.
Sammy. What about Sammy?
Adrianna and I can watch
him. It's no problem.
- Okay, good. He's upstairs, sleeping.
- Okay.
- We should go.
- All right.
Everybody stay in touch by cell phone.
- Really? Babysitting?
- Why not?
I think it would probably be safer for me to
be out searching drug infested neighborhoods.
You kidding me? Sam's
asleep. It will be cake.
oh, loud, screaming cake.
I checked around back, too.
There's no sign of her.
You okay?
Harry, Dixon had sex.
Yes. He did.
That...he did.
And we had no clue.
Which is normal.
Teenage boys don't run and tell
their parents when they've had sex,
and if they do, well, they're peculiar.
I guess.
Look, sweetheart, a lot of
what's going on is not normal,
but Dixon not telling us is. Trust me.
Think. Where would she go?
I am thinking.
It still doesn't make sense to me
why she would go to your apartment.
It doesn't make sense because
Silver wasn't making sense.
Okay, you know, sensible
was not the overall tone
of that particular interchange.
Yeah, but there's got to be
some reason that she blames you.
I'm telling you I didn't do anything.
That you know of.
Some people aren't aware
of how they hurt people.
Aren't aware or don't care.
Your sister breaks into
my apartment, threatens me,
throws a wine bottle at my
head, and you're blaming me?
You are the one who left her alone.
You are the reason we are out
here looking for her right now.
She lives with you, Kelly, not me, okay?
You're the one who's supposed
to be taking care of her.
- Maybe we should check the pier.
- Yeah, fine.
Is he asleep?
Eyes closed, drool flowing.
you're like the baby whisperer.
What can I say?
I'm impressed.
I do not understand baby.
I do not speak baby.
I don't know from baby.
Well, lesson number one?
Sammy's not a baby, okay?
He's four.
exhibit A.
It's not my forte.
I'll incubate the little
thing and after that,
I think it's probably best that
I pass on the baton, you know?
Pass baton?
You mean...adoption?
Yeah, I'm leaning towards it...
pretty strongly.
Pretty much horizontal
toward adoption, yep.
- What?
- I was just...
oh, nothing. It's just...
we never really talk
about this stuff, do we?
About the pregnancy, I mean.
Well, it's not like it's your baby.
There's no reason you
have to deal with this.
So, adoption, huh?
That's the plan?
I don't know what else I should do.
I mean, you saw me with Sammy.
We will not grow old
when he started crying...
I was even more scared than he was.
- Silver?
- Dixon?
Dixon, I just, I just had to call
you because I want you to know
that I know that I don't know you,
and so I'm going back to the source.
The source of everything.
- What?
- You're all that I have.
The only thing that I...
the only thing that matters to me.
You're all that I need.
Without you, life isn't worth living.
Dixon? Dixon? Dixon?
DiX...?
- Dixon?
- In here.
We've been trying to reach you.
Yeah, I turned my phone off.
- Why did you turn your phone off?
- Silver called.
- What?!
- Where is she?
Who knows? Who cares?
She's a manipulative drama queen.
I'm not buying her crap anymore.
- Hey, Dixon...
- damn it.
What did Silver say?
Um, who knows?
When she called, she was so hysterical,
I could barely understand her.
She was just ranting on and on
about how all she has is me
and how life isn't
worth living without me.
So she's going back to the source.
What's the source?
Beats me.
Silver's a freak.
I got better things to worry about.
We should call the police.
I love you.
One shade the more, one ray the less...
- it's Silver.
- Come on.
which waves in every raven tress.
I love you.
One shade the more, one ray the less...
God!
What are you doing here?
Looking for Silver. I
was in the parking lot.
Ade told me she went AWOL.
Heard about her little movie,
so I figured it'd shed
some light on the subject.
Gotta say it's pretty creepy stuff.
A little arty for my taste.
Not exactly a sunset five kind of girl.
How did you get in?
We have my dad's keys.
Well, if you dress a little more like me,
the janitor opening the door
for you is only the beginning.
Although I don't know if it'd help.
I mean, you'd still be
stuck with that face.
Have you checked the whole school?
No, this is the first place I came.
Do you think she's okay?
Please, don't pretend to be concerned.
You guys are not friends.
For you information, we've been
hanging out quite a bit lately.
Oh, since when?
Nice valentine’s.
- It's really none of your...
- stop it!
Focus on Silver.
Look, the school's really
big. She could be anywhere.
- Well, then we should probably split up.
- Are you sure?
I mean, it gets kind creepy
around here at night.
Oh, that's really sweet, E.
Couldn't be any
creepier than hanging out
with my ex and his little girlfriend.
- Actually, we...
- know,
know that Silver's not in the east wing.
We already checked, FYI.
Right. Fine.
I'll check the auditorium.
I-I'm sorry about that.
I guess the thought of Naomi
finding out we broke up...
yeah, whatever. It's fine.
- I'm gonna go check the cafeteria.
- Cool.
Okay, the source. What
are we talking about here?
A water source or, uh, the power source,
uh... she said life isn't
worth living without him?
Don't go there, okay?
What kind of source? I mean, a fuel
source, a source of information,
a news source, the
hip-hop awards show, maybe.
Or the source of her pain.
Okay, sure, what's, what's, the
source of her pain?
Kelly, what a surprise.
- Is Silver here?
- Silver? No.
Mom, we have to talk.
- Dierk doesn't know I have kids.
- Dierk?
Hey, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too, Dierk.
Kelly is my niece.
My older sister's daughter.
And this is Kelly's boy toy.
Uh, what did you say your name was?
Ryan. And he's my colleague.
Colleague, sure.
Do you two enjoy working together?
- Yeah, yeah
- uh, Silver is missing.
I wouldn't worry.
She is probably out partying somewhere
or slutting it up with some guy.
That's what Kelly always did.
I think Silver is in
trouble, real trouble.
So if she shows up here, I
want you to call me right away.
do you think this is funny?
Yeah, I do actually, because
you pranced in here,
all holier than thou, talking
about how bad a aunt I was,
and that you could do a
better job with Silver.
Well it looks like you
are no different than me.
And at least when she lived
here, I knew where she was.
Okay, we'd better go.
Uh, you'll call if you hear anything?
Yeah, you got it, boy toy.
Bye, mom.
Actually, I have a kid, too, which
makes her a grandma.
oh, that woman!
Every time I think she can't get
any worse, she gets so much worse.
- hello.
- Is this Kelly Taylor?
Yes, this is Kelly Taylor
this is officer Lewis, ma'am.
We found your sister's car
abandoned in a parking lot downtown.
No sign of your sister.
if Silver's not in her
car, then where is she?
I can't believe this. She's gone.
I-I did this. I... I don't know.
I tried. I mean, maybe I
gave her too much freedom,
but I had breakfast
with her every morning
and I checked to make sure
she was doing her homework.
I've just been too focused on
myself and my work and Sammy.
Kelly, no, okay?
- You can't blame yourself.
- Why not? You did.
You said it yourself.
I'm the one that lives with her.
I should have been taking care of her.
Oh, my God, I can't believe this!
After everything I've been
through with my mother,
here I am just like her!
No, no, are you kidding?
You and that woman,
you're night and day, okay?
You're Tolstoy and Dean Koontz.
You're Baryshnikov
and, and Michael Flatley.
I kind of like Michael Flatley,
but what I'm trying to say, Kelly,
is that you are not your
mother, okay? You are kind
Okay, you know what?
If this is you trying to comfort me,
just don't, all right?
Because you have done
nothing but try to avoid me
since you came back to school,
so you're not here tonight as my friend.
You're my chauffeur, that's it.
- Debbie: Dixon!
- What? I'm busy.
Harry: We want to let you
know they found Silver's car.
It was abandoned downtown.
Yeah? Well, big deal.
Let me know when you find a body.
Dixon!
What? I told you she's playing you.
And I'm not falling for it.
Now can you leave me alone?!
You're blocking my view.
Excuse me?
Last train to San Bernardino.
Train 416 departing platform A.
Yes! Kansas.
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it.
What's in Kansas?
Oh, it's where Dixon's from.
Wait, you don't know Dixon.
Of course not.
Well, neither do I, apparently.
That's the problem.
How do you know anybody?
You have to go backwards in order
to understand how to go forwards.
So, working backwards.
Why didn't Dixon react to the movie
the way that I thought he would?
Because there are fundamental things
about him that I don't understand.
It's like chemistry.
Li baking soda and vinegar.
You can put vinegar with something other than
baking soda and it won't react the same way.
So, my movie, in this example, is the vinegar,
which means, inherently, that it's not a
bad movie because if-if Dixon was sugar,
then everything would have
been fine, but he's not.
He's the baking soda.
Hence his eruption.
So, I have to understand
what makes Dixon baking soda.
And how do you understand how
anyone becomes who they are?
You have to go back to the past, all
of their previous chemical reactions.
Imagine all the moments in Dixon's
life that made him who he is.
All the moments and-and the moments
that lead up to those moments
because there are no
disconnected moments.
Every moment is connected
to a million other moments.
God, it’s... exhausting.
But if you track them back,
you find the original moment,
the source of everything, which is...
Next in line.
Kansas.
I'm going to Kansas.
Here. I have to get to Kansas.
11:35,track 12.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Next in line? Sir?
I want my mommy.
Quick, baby whisperer, do something.
- Hey, Sammy. It's okay.
- I want my mommy.
- Adrianna can help you.
- Hey, Sammy.
Everybody, stop crying. Stop crying.
He's turning pink. Is that normal?
It's okay. look. Look, look.
- Big smiling face!
- Put it away.
Okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Uh, I am dying here.
- Couch.
- Okay.
Those are really cool PJs.
You look sharp. Is that.
What do you have on
them? Is that trucks?
Oh, my gosh. I love trucks.
- That's my favorite mode of transportation.
- Tractors.
Except for tractors.
I was going to say that.
I just, I love them more.
Sammy, do you know what
Adrianna’s really good at?
What?
Opening my hands like A...
oh, reading books.
I'm really good at
reading books to kids.
It's actually a secret
talent of mine, actually, so...
you want... you want us to read this one?
Picture book about, um, trucks?
Tractors. Get with the program.
Okay, uh...
Sammy, Adrianna does
a great tractor voice.
Hit it.
I'm a tractor!
I like to tract things.
Professional actress right here, Sammy.
You should hear her do a dump truck.
anyways, let's get started.
Do you want to move closer to Navid?
Would you be more comfortable? Let's go.
Okay...
once upon a time, there
lived a grouchy old tractor
named Mr. Grumples
Look, it's Mr. Grumples.
What are you doing?
Just trying to open Silver's locker.
Here. She's had the same
combination since sixth grade.
I don't know what I'm looking for.
- This is all so weird.
- Yeah, I know, right?
Oh, my God. I can't believe she has that.
- That's you?
- Yeah, me and Silver.
With what seems to
be pots on your heads?
Yeah, we were alone at
my house, hanging out.
I think we were,like,12.
We suddenly felt this huge
earthquake and totally freaked out
and got a bunch of pots and ran
and hid under the kitchen table.
Was it a big earthquake?
Oh, no, it wasn't an earthquake at all.
Apparently, our neighbors decided
to upgrade to a pebble driveway
and had been jackhammering
the pavement up next door.
How long were you under the table?
At least an hour, maybe
two. I don't remember.
Oh, I don't know how long
we would have been there
if Ethan hadn't shown up to
tell us about the jackhammer.
Anyway...
yeah, anyway, my dad said
we should keep looking.
Yeah, I'm going to go check the gym.
- what are you doing?
- Honey, I'm trying to figure out Dixon's password.
I've tried his name, his
birthday, the chiefs...
why do you need to get into his...
because I have no idea who he is, Harry.
Deb, what's going on?
I have no clue what's going on.
Our son is acting like a stranger.
You saw him down there.
He is hostile and
callous and having sex.
Okay, fine. Maybe that's normal,
but the rest of it is not.
It's this place.
It's L.A., Beverly hills.
The morals are different here.
I mean, kids grow up way too fast,
and we made a huge
mistake by coming here.
Deb...
- Silver.
- Uh, no. Uh, my name is Kevin.
But I'm here with a
girl named Erin Silver.
She's in a pretty bad way,
d I-I just thought I should
call someone and let them know,
and you know, this was the
last number she called.
Where is she? Where are you?
Union station.
Uh, Erin here bought
herself a ticket to Kansas.
You know, her train hasn't left yet.
Right now, she's kind of passed out,
but she's acting pretty erratic and,
I mean, who knows what she might do?
- We're on our way. We will be there as soon as we can.
- Yeah.
- look, we can't break up.
- What?
Relationships are work and
that's all we need to do.
We need to work on things.
We shouldn't give up so easily.
But, Annie, things haven't been good.
- We haven't been happy.
- I-I know, I know that.
Okay, but we will be. We-we
just have to fix this.
Okay? We have to.
We have to work at this.
- Why?
- Why? Because... because of Naomi.
Naomi's going to find out eventually.
Naomi's going to find out about what?
This isn't about Naomi finding out.
This is about Naomi.
When I first moved here,
she reached out to me and we h the
potential to be friends, to be real friends,
and then she asked me not to go out
with you, but I...I didn't listen.
I went behind her back
and I started dating you,
which is a really jerky
thing to do. But I did it.
Because I had a good reason.
I believed that you were the one.
I thought... I thought
that we were the ones.
Our relationship, you and
me, it was worth anything.
It was worth sacrificing friends
and even some of my self-respect.
But if we're not together, and
we break up, then what?
Then I didn't make these
sacrifices for our relationship.
I was just being a jerk.
If we can't make things work, then I
have to accept everything that I've done.
And... and...
and we are.
We are...
we are broken up.
And... and I've been a jerk.
I've been a jerk, and...
me and Ethan?
We're broken up.
It's okay, Erin.
How do you know my name?
What time is it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got to go! I got to go.
Erin! Wait!
no! Stop, stop, stop!
Don't leave without me! Stop! Please!
Silver! Silver, get off the tracks.
It was my train.
First Ryan drained my gas
tank, and then I missed my train.
And I am never going
to make it to Kansas.
Harry: Okay, Silver, calm down.
It doesn't matter if
you missed your train.
She's such a drama queen.
- It's unbelievable.
- How could you say that?
Well, I had it all figured out.
I was going to go to Kansas
because Kansas equals Dixon,
and Dixon equals baking soda.
Doesn't make sense...
but it did it did make
sense, and now it doesn’t.
- I know.
- Don't! Don't come near me.
Okay.
Everything was making
sense, but now it doesn’t.
Everything was so
great, but now it's so dark.
It is so dark here.
It is always, always dark.
- Silver, please get off the tracks.
- I am so confused.
Come on.  Silver.
- I don't know what's going on anymore.
- Silver, get off the tracks.
- Silver!
you don't understand!
- Silver, no!
- No!
- Dixon!
- Wait, wait. I got this.
Silver! It's me.
It's Dixon. Listen,
i do understand.
I do! Everything was so good for you,
and now it feels like the
world is crumbling around you.
Everything made
sense, and now it doesn't,
but it's okay, Silver.
I know what you're going through,
'cause my mom used to go
through the same type of thing.
Some days, she was so happy, she
couldn't contain herself.
Like, one day, she just
took me out of school.
Just showed up in the middle of the day
and took me out of school.
Said we were going to Disneyland.
But she didn't stay happy.
By the time we got there,
she was just sad and confused.
We didn't end up leaving the motel room.
That's how she was.
Up and down, up and down.
But that wasn't her fault.
She just needed help, Silver.
It's okay, all right? I'm here.
And I'm going to help you get help.
All right?
everything's gonna be okay.
Kelly, I'm so sorry.
I screwed it all up, didn't I?
You let me in your
house, you gave me a chance,
try to make things better, and
I screwed it all up.
You're gonna get rid of me, aren't you?
- You're gonna send me back to my mom.
- No, no, no.
I'm not going anywhere, and
neither are you.
- Are you okay? -
She's manic-depressive.
It's not drugs.
Silver has bipolar disorder
just like my birth mom.
That has to be it.
Well, I'm just glad she's safe.
Yeah, it's a huge relief.
I'll drop you off at home.
- Okay.
- No, I'll take her.
- Are you sure?
- I mean, it's on the way home.
- Well, sort of.
- Thanks.
- Bye, Ethan.
- Bye, Annie.
So, there are a lot of
other fish in the sea.
- Equally cute fish.
- Yeah, well, thanks.
And, um, I really am
sorry about how I acted.
I get it. It's okay.
Trust me, I wasn't exactly
the nicest person either.
I mean, nice is not really my thing.
No, it's not.
- But still, I'm sorry, too.
- Thank you...
I guess.
okay, not to gossip or anything,
but have you heard what
Adrianna calls Navid?
- Sesame balls.
- What?
- Sesame balls! - No
way. - Sesame balls!
And what is your
relationship to the patient?
I'm her sister.
"And he went into the barn
and who did he find
there but Mr. Grumples,
looking all spiffy with a shiny
new coat of bright red paint.
The End.
Aw, he was a nice tractor after all.
He's out.
When did he fall asleep?
Back when Mr. Grumples was
crossing the bridge to jersey city.
Oh, I wanted, I wanted to
see how it turned out.
This was actually kind of fun.
We make a pretty good team.
Yeah, we do.
- How is she?
- She's gonna be okay.
You didn't have to stay.
A chauffeur is not done until
his charge is safely back at home.
Look, Ryan, I owe you an apology
for the way I treated you.
No, Kelly, I owe you an apology.
I haven't really been your friend.
I slept with Brenda, which
I knew would hurt you...
which is why I did it.
I had feelings for you, Kelly, and
then you went to see Dylan and...
it doesn't matter 'cause
you didn't owe me anything.
And I was stupid and spiteful...
and I'm really sorry.
And I realize it's completely unprofessional for
a chauffeur to try and befriend his charge, but...
I'd like to.
I'd like that, too.
- But I'm still gonna sit in the back seat on the way home.
- Okay.
- Dixon was great out there.
- I know. He was.
Can you imagine what that would be like?
First your birth mother, and then your
girlfriend both being manic-depressive?
It'd be like lightning striking twice.
- It's no wonder he reacted the way he did.
- Oh, yeah.
Listen, I'm sorry I
kind of lost it before.
Oh, no, honey, it's okay.
It's understandable.
But I think that we
should talk, you know?
If you're unhappy in L.A., We can leave.
- But you can't keep bringing it up every time something goes wrong.
- I know.
We haven't taken the bid on the house.
We can move back to Kansas
if that's what you want.
But we can't have one foot
here and one foot there.
We have to decide.
What do you want?
Me?
I like it here.
And I think it is a great
place to raise our kids.
And I think the kids
in Kansas have sex, too.
I know, I know they do.
And I like it here, too.
But the most important thing for me is
whether or not this is a
good place to raise a family.
And I think it is.
There are opportunities and culture and all sorts
of things here that you can't find in Kansas.
Museums and galleries and theater and...
gluten-free bread.
And I don't even know what gluten is, but
I like the option of not having to eat it.
I like options.
And Beverly Hills has options.
It's a bigger world here.
And I think that's a good thing.
You think we should
stay in Beverly Hills?
I think that we should
stay in Beverly Hills.
Well, it sounds like
you were pretty amazing.
And not at first, for sure.
When Silver called, I totally bugged out.
You know, she just kept going on,
saying I was the only thing
that made her life worth living.
And it was that kind
of manipulative thing
that my mom used to say to me.
You know, so I just had a bad
reaction and just freaked out.
Did you know that then?
I mean, did you know why you were upset?
No,I had no clue.
I mean, didn't put it all together
until we were at the train station.
Then I guess I saw how she shifted from
being so happy to being so despondent.
It all made sense.
Geez, what a night.
- You can say that again.
- What a night.
- You can say that again and again.
- what a night.
Debbie: Ooh, French toast.
I'm starving.
- The bread is gluten-free.
- I will explain later.
- How about some French toast?
- Drown it!
I say, drown it.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-¿¨»Ò corrections : aydin1954 – addic7ed.com
90210 Season 01 Episode 18
www.tvsubtitles.net