I will be going
to California University.
- CU isn't going to happen.
- You're going to focus on the SAT's?
No, I'm gonna date the dean's son.
Are you Richard?
I'm Jamie, by the way.
- There you are.
- Jamie, this is...
My roommate Richard.
I wish you weren't dating
Richard because...
- I really want to kiss you.
- You can go home, Marilyn.
My date's arrived.
I want the same stuff
I got last time.
Navid Shirazi told me
that you were a drug dealer.
What?
I am not a drug dealer,
but if I was, I wouldn't be the kind
of guy you want to mess with, would I?
I love you.
And I want my first time to be with you.
Time to wake up.
I need an ambulance.
- What do we have?
- 60-year-old female
found unconscious in her home.
Status:post cardiac arrest.
BP's 110/70.
- Medications?
- One milligram of epinephrine.
- She's on Bactrim and Gabapentin.
- Where are you taking her?!
Wait in the lobby.
We'll find you when there's news.
- I was texting you.
- Good. Me first.
I am here to rescue your little
news broadcast thingy.
I'm going to join.
Come on, I just want to pad
my resume with some extracurriculars.
You're just going to flake
whenever there's any actual work to do.
Please, Navid,
I really have to get into CU.
Please, please.
Pretty please.
- I'm gonna keep on until you say yes...
- All right, fine.
My segment's going to be called:
- You're not getting one.
- Clark After Dark.
I'll give people sex advice.
I'm getting new high-def video mixers,
and you can help me unpack those.
Ex-squee me?
I you're serious about the Blaze,
you can meet tomorrow by 6:00.
Can I talk now?
I have something very
important to tell you.
This better not be
some hazing ritual.
It's about Adrianna.
I think she's back on drugs.
What?
Of course I'm not on drugs.
I've been clean for
so long, you know that.
Why would Navid say it?
I don't know.
Things have been
pretty bad with us lately.
Maybe he's mad because
I've moved on since the breakup.
You have to believe me, I'm clean.
I want to believe you, I really do,
but you've lied to me
about this before.
I'm not lying now.
Do you remember what
I was like when I was on coke?
Am I acting anything
like that right now?
- You're not.
- Exactly.
I'm going to talk to Navid and
I'm going to get to the bottom of it.
- How is she? Is she okay?
- I don't know.
When I woke up this morning,
she wasn't breathing,
so I called 911.
She was in cardiac arrest.
But they gave her CPR and
her heart started beating again,
but she's been in there
for over an hour.
Everything's going to be okay.
It's not!
You don't know how sick she's been.
I know that she has cancer, but...
It wasn't supposed
to happen like this.
Thank you for being so patient.
Are you a relative?
We're her daughters.
Your mother suffered
a cardiac arrest.
And I'm afraid with
the chemotherapy treatments,
She's too weak to fight much longer.
She's conscious. It would be
a good time to see her.
Aren't you coming?
I can't.
Just go.
I'm sure she'll be happy to see you.
Is anybody coming?
I am.
- Morning, Dixon.
- I'm getting a ride from Liam.
Do you want any breakfast?
He'll get over it sooner or later.
- Morning.
- You're in a good mood.
- Things are good.
- Can we get some details?
- Dirty deets, as the kids say?
- Seriously, Dad?
- Regular details would be just fine.
I've kind of been seeing someone.
Who's the lucky guy?
His name is Jasper.
- Does he go to West Bev?
- Yes.
- What's he like?
- He's amazing.
He's a filmmaker,
but more like a genius.
I will check his transcripts
just to be sure.
Can we meet him sometime?
Actually, I was hoping that
maybe he could come over for dinner?
Sure. That's a great idea.
How about tomorrow night?
- Perfect.
- Shouldn't you be getting to school?
First period.
Study hall.
It's Friday, remember?
- Dirty deets?
- That's what they say.
I can't believe
she's seeing someone.
I can't believe she's
actually telling us about it.
How did it go?
You're coming over tomorrow night.
Do you think Jasper would like Chicken
Tarragon or Mahi Mahi for dinner?
- Mahi Mahi.
- You got it.
I can't wait.
Mahi Mahi?
Should I come in
through the window for dinner,
or should I use the front door?
Peach Pit team
www.forom.com
Season 02 episode 10
To Thine Own Self Be True
Ivy's mom has
a recording studio, right?
You finally gonna make
an album as DJ Mr. Big Dix?
It's D-I-X.
Anyway, what I was trying to say
was maybe we could use it
to bring down Naomi's sister.
All we have to do is
get Ivy to say exactly
what Jen said in that recording
that you deleted.
Mix it down so it sounds like Jen...
Let Naomi hear it.
I know you're just trying
to help and everything, but...
Mix it down a little bit
so it sounds like... Jen.
- What's up?
- You figure anything out yet?
We figured out
DJ Mr. Big Dix is a big moron.
You're the one who deleted
the recording.
That would make you both
morons then.
DJ Mr. Big Dix? Really?
How about you guys come by the media lab
and help me unpack some video mixers?
Dinner on me.
Anytime, anywhere.
Including and limited to
In-N-Out Burger. What do you say?
- Fine.
- Sure.
You in?
I don't know. She's been spending
a lot of time with that freak.
I'd keep an eye on him.
I saw that dude dealing drugs.
Let's go.
Hello, and
welcome to Clark After Dark.
Today we're here to talk
about all the best ways
to make a woman reach ecstasy.
We have our first caller.
Hello. You're on with Naomi.
Hi. I need some advice.
You see, I'm dating
this wonderful girl,
I want to do filthy,
terrible things to her.
What exactly did you have in mind?
My new boss at the Blaze.
- Ignore.
- Why is he calling on the weekend?
Because I have to go there
tomorrow at 6:00 and unpack some crap.
I think Katie Couric got her
start unpacking crap.
- Thought you were at your parent's.
- I just forgot my laptop.
Hey, Dean Carter.
This is Richard's mom.
This is Naomi Clark.
The girl who was supposed to
be Richard's date for my cocktail party.
- Kind of.
- And now you're with Jamie.
Classy.
Can we go now?
After the Bonhams
and Butterfields auction
- we have a table at Entitlement.
- Is that another night club?
The name's ironic, obviously.
We'll be sitting with a
South American coffee magnate,
Manuel Fonseca Veloso de...
You don't speak Portuguese, do you?
"Nao."
And tomorrow night is
the benefit concert...
- Who does that benefit?
- I forget.
Either a village in Africa
or a degenerative spine disease.
Is something wrong?
Everything is fine.
I'm looking forward to...
All of it.
But?
It's just that,
we've been spending a lot of
time in your world and it's been fun
but I just someday would like
to show you my world.
I'm a West Beverly alumni.
I know everything about your world.
I was thinking more along
the lines of planning a weekend.
Maybe even this one.
What exactly do you have in mind?
What about camping?
We could go up to Los
Padres and do a little hiking
and we could sleep out under the stars.
Enjoy the peace
and the quiet and each other.
It does sound romantic.
I'd love to.
- Really?
- Really.
It sounds,
great.
What's the matter, babe?
Forget it. Just go back
to your carbo loading.
What's wrong?
You said Richard wouldn't be here.
Are you still caught up on that?
He knows that we're dating.
We can't avoid him forever.
It's not Richard I care about.
Then who? His mom?
I can't believe you didn't
tell me they were coming.
I didn't know.
- Why do you care what she thinks?
- I don't.
What do you think she thinks?
I don't know.
She probably hates you.
Great.
That's awesome.
Why is this such a big deal?
- You didn't even like Richard.
- She's the freaking dean of admissions.
Is that why you were dating Richard?
- To get to his mom?
- Of course not.
Then why?
You were just using him?
- How could you treat him like that?
- Like you're so noble.
- You stole me away from him.
- At least that was something honest.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to give myself the
best possible shot of getting here.
Because my dream was
to always meet someone like you.
And now I have.
I realize I made a mistake.
Can we just move on?
Please?
I don't think you even get it.
Richard has been beating himself up,
wondering what he did
to screw things up.
You're a user.
And I don't want to see you anymore.
This week on the Blaze,
we'll have an exclusive interview
with Mr. Lichtenstein about
his lifelong battle with hypoglycemia.
Even I'm bored by that promo.
Maybe I should let
Naomi do the sex show.
- What?
- No, I mean...
Why did you tell Naomi I was using?
I'm gonna go away from here.
I saw you, Ade.
- I saw you buying drugs from Jasper.
- I wasn't buying drugs.
What was he doing walking out of
your car with a wad of cash?
Why are you doing this?
Because I care about you.
- I'm not using.
- You clearly are.
When we broke up, you were totally
devastated. Sleeping in all day, crying,
singing me love songs.
And then I see you walking around school
and you're perfectly fine?
Yeah, I am.
You know why?
Because you really weren't
that hard to get over.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
The more I thought about things,
the more I realized that we were
only together because I needed you.
And that's not love.
So, yeah, I do feel
completely different.
It has nothing to do with drugs.
I guess I was never
really in love with you.
What is all this?
I stopped at the Beverly Center
for some wilderness accoutrements.
Be warned though, I bought a knife
so powerful that I could
butterfly you in 15 minutes.
Interesting.
That is an air mattress.
King size when inflated.
But don't worry, I bought a pump.
- What else do you have?
- Just a few small necessities:
a portable GPS,
a Burberry raincoat...
We can't bring all this stuff.
The beauty of camping
is that we don't need much.
Don't you worry, 'cause
you're gonna be comfortable. Trust me.
What about the fondue set?
We can manage without it.
Do you want to help me
bring this stuff inside?
Morning.
Just the way you like it.
No cream, no sugar.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
For staying late at the hospital
and driving me home.
I'm glad you decided to stay here.
Are you hungry?
You want me to make you some eggs?
You always take such
good care of me.
Sometimes I...
I worry that no one's
looking after you.
I can take care of myself.
One cream, two sugars.
Just the way I like it.
I really think that
you should go see Mom.
You're gonna regret it if
you don't say good-bye.
Mom and I really don't have
a relationship anymore.
- And I'm okay with that.
- That's what I used to think.
I can't tell you how much better
I felt since we reconnected.
And I'm glad you did.
But it's different with her and me.
How?
Because I have 20 more
years of bad memories than you.
And I'm not talking about
just your run-of-the-mill,
falling down drunk memories.
But lifetime of never being good enough.
She's different now.
She's sober.
Her sober wasn't much better for me.
When she was sober,
she'd remember to give me my diet pills
and make my nose job appointment
and remind me of what a colossal
disappointment I was.
I got the message, loud and clear.
You have to forgive her.
For your own sake.
I don't.
Look, I'm happy to pick you
up at the hospital, drop you off,
whatever you need.
But that's it.
Jamie's at football practice.
I came to see you.
Can I come in?
I need to apologize to you.
- For a lot.
- It's fine.
You liked Jamie more; it happens.
I was just surprised you know? I thought
you and I were really connecting.
I was dishonest
with you from the start.
I'm not really into
the whole environment thing.
Watching that movie
on industrial meat production
just gave me
a craving for Kobe sliders.
Why didn't you say something?
Because...
I wanted to date you.
But...
the whole reason
I wanted to date you,
the reason I hired you
as my tutor even,
was so I could meet your mom.
I'm sorry, what?
I've always wanted to go to CU.
And I guess I thought
if I dated the Dean's son, then
that would guarantee that I'd get in.
I'm really sorry.
I realize how awful that is.
What were you...
planning to do?
Just lead me on until
you got your acceptance letter?
- I would take it all back if I could.
- Stop.
Just... stop.
Okay.
So, Dad,
you are not gonna tell
any stupid jokes during dinner.
When you say "stupid," you
mean "hilarious"?
I mean, no telling Jasper you're gonna
check his transcript or whatever.
Don't worry.
I already checked it.
Okay, crudités and my famous dip.
So, you guys know that Jasper's
the one wanting to set all this up.
He's been wanting
to meet you guys real bad.
You may have
mentioned that once or twice.
And you're gonna love him.
He's so sweet
and sensitive, not like all
those typical high school boys.
We look forward to meeting him.
Is that what
you're wearing to dinner?
This is what I'm wearing to help
Navid move some stuff into the Blaze.
Can that wait until later?
I was hoping you could join us.
This dinner's important
to your sister.
What's your problem?
Nothing. I just don't want to have
dinner with your weirdo boyfriend.
At least he's not
some 40-year-old psycho.
At least Sasha wasn't a drug dealer.
Jasper is not a drug dealer!
That's what Navid told me.
Navid doesn't know
what he's talking about, okay?
- Enjoy your dinner.
- Hey, Dixon.
Mom, Dad, this is Jasper.
Isn't it nice to get out of
Beverly Hills for a change?
I'm just glad your idea of roughing it
includes a bottle of Pinot Grigio.
What'd you expect,
a jar of moonshine?
We're campers, not savages.
What are you doing
with my New York Times?
Starting a fire.
Don't worry, I didn't
touch the Style section.
- Did you check the weather?
- Not exactly.
- It never rains in L.A.
- Yeah, apparently it does.
I'm so happy I wore my suede boots.
- What do you want me to do?
- Obviously there's nothing you can do!
Just, pull the...
Give it a... Yeah, that's...
Okay.
This is going well.
What about this?
All you have to do
is get Naomi's sister
alone in her bedroom.
Seduce her. Get her to admit that she
slept with you on prom night.
Meanwhile... No, you hide Naomi behind
a curtain until she hears everything,
just like Polonius in Hamlet,
my friend.
Doesn't Polonius get stabbed?
Spoiler. I haven't even started
my English homework.
Guys, I'm not seducing Jen.
That is the worst idea
we've had yet.
It's a brilliant idea. Maybe we should
just forget about the whole thing.
- You're not giving up, are you?
- I don't know, maybe.
- Hamlet. We'll figure something out.
- We'll figure something out.
We'll figure something out.
The dip, it was excellent,
Mrs. Wilson.
Thanks.
So...
I haven't
told you guys, I don't think,
but Jasper and I are
working on a film together.
That's great.
Sweetie, could you hand me a napkin?
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, I've seen some of the footage,
and it's gorgeous.
He's a genius.
Annie's my inspiration.
Jasper, what else do you
do besides filmmaking?
Not a whole lot.
And who are your friends
at West Bev?
Well, it's... pretty
much just Annie.
Yeah, 'cause the kids
at West Bev suck.
All right, they're all
lemmings and-and spoiled brats.
All right? We don't want to
be friends with them.
Come on, they're not all bad.
Just because you had a falling-out
- with your friends doesn't...
- Okay.
Those people were never my friends.
Annie, look at me.
We talked about this, right, and
we just got to forget about it, babe.
I know. I know.
You're right.
Sorry.
I bet dinner is almost ready...
I'm gonna check on that.
Oh, no, no, please. You sit,
we've got this, thank you.
I feel like I'm totally blowing it.
Did I do something wrong?
No. No, you are...
You're perfect.
It's them.
Look right before you got here,
Dixon told them that stupid rumor
about you being
a drug dealer or whatever.
Dinner's ready.
It doesn't really matter
I hope you like mahi mahi.
Look, I know that you think
I'm a drug dealer.
- It's not true.
- Well, obviously.
It's been hard for me
to fit in at West Bev.
People, they're always
talking about me behind my back, and
I never...
used to care
what anyone even thought about me.
But now... that I'm with Annie,
Everything has changed.
Cause when I'm with her,
I feel like I have a place in the world.
I care about her so
much, and I just know
that if you...
Just give me a chance,
you'll see that all I want is
what's best for your daughter.
I'm glad to hear you say that,
because that's all that we want, too.
- Great. Thank you.
- Why don't you try some of that. Here.
Sounds good.
Yes, please! Dig in.
Navid, I'm here to unpack your crap.
Could you give me a hand?
Please, I'm gonna drop it.
Okay.
All right let's just set it
over there. All right.
Oh, God!
Thanks.
I tried to find the crushed ice.
All they had was cubed.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What?
If I could take back what
happened last year, I would.
I think about it every single day.
Well, well, well,
she finally showed up.
I'm sorry, I...
Let's get back to work?
Yeah let's get back to work.
It's your ride calling.
I was waiting outside for you;
you never came out. So
now I'm here in the hall
outside Mom's room.
Only I don't see you anywhere, so...
Hope everything's okay.
Call me when you get this...
or just come find me.
Okay.
What happened? Where is she?
I just clean the room.
Great. So, can we go home now?
It'll let up soon.
Oh, come on,
the car's all packed up.
Let's... cut our losses here.
This was clearly a huge mistake.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know,
I just thought maybe once we could
do something that I wanted to do
instead of always doing what you
want to do, but I guess I'm the one
who makes sacrifices
in the relationship.
Sacrifices? What,
- you don't enjoy...
- The extravagant auctions,
the lavish night clubs,
the charities where people
don't even know what charity
they're supporting? No, actually,
I don't. But I go, anyways.
You know, and I let you tell
me who I have to impress,
and squeeze my elbow whenever
I do something wrong,
which is all the time. I walk around
on egg shells, and it's not fun.
But I put up with it...
Because it's what you want to do.
I had no idea.
I thought you were
enjoying yourself.
Yeah, I know you did.
Look, we can't drive down
the mountain in this weather, all right?
As soon as it lets up,
I'll take you home.
You okay?
You were right. You said I should say
good-bye, and I didn't.
Now it's too late.
It's not too late.
What?
No, they moved her
to a private room.
You still have time to say good-bye.
Okay.
So I know that the first half of
that was kind of totally unbearable,
and maybe we did need one of dad's
corny jokes to break the ice,
but I think it really turned
around when we started the fish.
Which was delicious, by the way.
And I want to thank you both so much
for just, you know, listening to Jasper
and giving him a second chance.
What?
Annie, we don't think
you should see Jasper anymore.
You don't think I should?
I know you're upset,
but we're doing what's best for you.
Is this because
of that stupid rumor?
Obviously, that concerns us.
We know Navid; we trust him.
- But it's a lie!
- No, it's more than the rumor.
Jasper is... odd.
How can you say that?
You don't even know him.
He doesn't have any friends.
Yeah, because the kids
at are school suck!
Annie, you are not yourself
around him.
You're not a... a loner
or an outcast.
You have no idea who I am anymore!
Hi, Kel.
Hi, Mom.
I'm so glad you came.
Sorry it took me so long.
You shouldn't apologize.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I've been... a terrible mother.
It's just...
You didn't turn out at all
like I expected.
- Mom...
- And...
Thank God for that.
Because you are so much better.
The way you have raised Silver.
I don't know how you learned
how to be such a good mother.
But you are.
You're such an amazing
person, Kelly.
You are so beautiful...
Strong...
And caring.
I'm so proud of you.
And I am so sorry...
... for everything that happened.
I forgive you.
Thank you...
... for coming.
I've been so tired,
but I knew that I just had
to hang on till you got here.
I love you, Kelly.
Did you get all that crap unpacked?
I wasn't much help.
What are you doing here?
Well, I...
I heard that you
apologized to Richard.
And I have to say, I'm
impressed.
You were right.
I needed to be honest with him.
Oh, come on, you made a mistake.
So what? So did I, you know?
I totally overreacted, and I shouldn't
have gotten so upset.
But you did the right thing.
And once I heard that,
It was hard for me to stay mad
at the girl I'm falling for.
And I am,
I'm falling for you.
I need to be honest with you, too.
It was my dream
to meet someone like you.
But the truth is...
I'm still hung up on someone else.
Someone I thought I was over.
I hope he's worth it.
You know, that mahi mahi wasn't
half bad, Annie.
When can I come back
and try the chicken tarragon?
Look, they said that
I can't see you anymore.
- I'm here.
- I mean, they still believe Navid.
Otherwise, I know that
they would have loved you,
I know that, but...
Just calm down, Annie.
There's no point
in getting mad at anyone.
It's not gonna help anything.
What's done is done, right?
Yeah, but what are we gonna do?
We'll figure something out,
okay? I promise.
Okay.
Yeah, we'll figure something out.
I know I should've called
first, but your mom let me in.
I had the perfect guy, Ade.
He went to my dream school,
he plays football,
he's SAE.
What is wrong with me?
Would you mind shutting the door?
Oh, yeah, sure.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
So, what happened with Jamie?
What's in your purse?
- Stop it! Stop!
- Give it to me.
It's private.
Are you kidding me?
You lied to me again?
I'm sorry.
Are you ever gonna stop this?
You know what?
Do what you want.
I'm over it.
How long have you been out here?
Since the rain stopped.
And how did you start a fire?
The Style section.
Look, I'm sorry that I forced you
to go all those... parties.
No, I mean, you know, how would you
know I hated them? I wasn't honest.
We're in a relationship.
I wouldn't expect you to be honest.
- You don't really mean that.
- Come on, Ryan. I know the cliché.
Tell each other everything,
no secrets, blah-blah-blah.
But in the real world...
It doesn't work.
- Jen, come on. That's...
- Honest.
No, it's sad.
- If you really believe that...
- Of course I do.
You say that you want
to know everything,
- but you really don't.
- I do.
I really like you.
- It's my point.
- And there's nothing you could tell me
short of a Charles Manson streak...
that would make me like you less.
I'm broke and living off Naomi.
So?
What do you mean, "so"?
It's not like
I'm dating you for your money.
I mean, if anything,
I'm dating you despite your money.
How'd you lose it?
I blew it trying to land my husband.
Your husband?
Well, I'm getting a divorce,
but yes, he is technically
still my husband.
Okay, that's...
Why didn't you tell me that?
Because then you would ask me why
the relationship ended.
And...?
He cheated on me.
Sorry.
There you go.
Whatever.
It happens.
No, it doesn't happen.
I mean,
it shouldn't happen.
Look, I, for one,
would never cheat on you.
Honestly?
Honestly.
I got it.
I know what to do.
I know how exactly what we're gonna do
to take down Naomi's sister.
Somebody help!