Clark,I know hunting down
zoners is your top priority,
but if you haven't found
anything in south america,
we still have a situation back
here in kansas we need to deal with.
No,he'll be here in 15 minutes.
Okay. Great.
I'll see you in a few.
Dr. Casselli.
You're early.
You are annoyingly persistent,
miss sullivan.
I've already told you
I don't know anything.
Don't sell yourself short,
doctor.
I think you're
a very knowledgeable man.
In the last few months,
over a dozen patients have been transferred
out of the high-security wing at belle reve.
I believe that's your signature
on all the paperwork.
Patients are transferred in and out
of mental facilities all the time.
Even ones that exhibit
unusual abilities?
Where are they transferred to?
Is luthorcorp involved?
Does this have anything to do
with 33.1?
Okay. I'll take that
as a "no comment. "
I didn't want any of this.
But it was so much money.
Chloe? You okay?
Yeah.
Just in the nick of time,
as always.
It wasn't me. He was already
down when I got here.
What?
Well,if it wasn't you,
then who -
he's open! Pass the ball!
Pass the -
oh! What's the matter
with you,man?
Still too slow,stretch.
Bart.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
SMALLVILLE
Season 06 Episode11
He got away from you?
I thought you were
the fastest man alive.
He saved your life,
which is more than I can say.
Oh,come on,clark.
It wasn't your fault.
Even with all your powers,
you can't be everywhere at once.
I have to be.
I'm the only one who can round up
the prisoners from the phantom zone
and stop lex from experimenting
on people with abilities.
What did you find out
from casselli about 33.1?
Nothing,
and I'm not going to.
Casselli was
in and out of prison
before the ink could dry
on his fingerprints.
How'd he get out so fast?
I don't know,but a luthorcorp lawyer paid
casselli a visit right before his release.
Lex.
Casselli could be stashed
halfway around the world by now.
I'll get in touch with lionel.
Maybe he can tell us something.
I'll keep sifting
through my luthorcorp intel.
Maybe we'll get lucky, and I'll
come up with a few bread crumbs.
Hey,gorgeous. What's up?
You miss me?
I'm bart allen. We had a moment
on the town last time I was here.
Two years ago,
before you had a boyfriend.
Oh! Right!
Wow.
It's good to see you again,
bart.
The pleasure's all mine,
seÑorita.
I'll see you around.
Muy caliente.
Knock it off.
What's with the spanish?
I just grabbed lunch
down in mexico,man.
They got this burrito down
there - el intestine-o buster.
You got to take a run down there
with me to try one.
What are you
doing here,bart?
I'm hanging out with my
amigo,man. What's it look like?
That's what
I'm trying to find out.
Last time you blew through town,
you stole my dad's wallet
then swiped a priceless artifact from
lex. You nearly got yourself killed.
Yeah. Yeah,those were
the days,huh?
Yeah,all right.
Look,man,
I already told you, things
are different now,okay?
I mean,back then,I needed a super-kick
in the butt, and you laid it on me,
and ever since then, there's been no
more stealing for this gringo,I swear.
Am I really supposed to
just buy that?
I could squirt out some tears
if that'll help.
No,but the truth might.
What were you doing
at the daily planet?
I saw chloe-licious
had a byline a while back.
And I was in town on business,
figured I ought to check it out.
What kind of business?
I'm a courier. I pick
things up. I drop them off.
Lickety-split. Don't have a fit.
All right. Look,man,whatever.
You don't trust me. That's fine.
Okay,I'll be gonebefore you can even blink.
I don't know.
I can still blinkpretty fast.
Mexico,huh?Want to go get that burrito?
Excelente.
Now,that is what I call
a three-martini lunch.
It wasa four-martini lunch
if you include the onethat
you spilled on my shirt.
Right.
Well,how am I ever going
tomake it up to you?
I don't know.
Because,uh...
it's my favorite shirt.
Well,then,I think we
shouldget it into the laundry
so that it doesn't stain.
Yeah. That's a good idea.
I got to take this.
Go ahead.
Give me five minutes.
I,uh...
you know,what I had in mind
is gonna take a little
longerthan five minutes.
Rain check?
Sure.
I'll just put it nextto the rest of
the umbrellas you keep handing me.
Lois -
I mean,is it just me
or is this relationshipall
interruptus and no coitus?
You're always running off
just when thingsstart getting interesting,
and I like being interested -a lot.
Yeah.
I know. You're right.
It's,uh...
it's not fair to you.
I think we should takea break.
You mean like,what...
see other people?
Uh,well,okay.
Yeah,I mean,if that's what you want.
I was actually thinkingmore along the lines
of taking a vacation...
together.
Really?
Yeah,really.
No rushing outin the
middle of the good stuff?
No. None.
It'll be you,me,and...
monte carlo?
There's just a few thingsthat
I do need to take care of
before we go,and I think once we get -
god,you're good at that.
- I'll start packing.
- Okay.
Bye.
GAME ON
I need to talk to you. You alone?
Just meand my shadow,dad.
Lana's in paris with
nell,shopping for a wedding dress.
That's goodshe's out of the country
consideringwhat's happening.
Look,if this is aboutdr. Casselli -
casselli?He's the least of our worries.
Another luthorcorp facilityhas been hit.
That's six.
Each one of them hassome
connection with 33.1.
The only thinghoused in those facilities
was peripheral research.
All the vital data isstill
secure in the mainframe.
How long do you think beforethat
location is compromised?
If it ever became publicthat
luthorcorp is experimenting
on peoplewith abilities -
it won'T.
What's this?
A single framepulled off a security camera
from one of the break-ins.
Whoever is responsible
has the ability to move
fasterthan a speeding bullet.
Such a unique individual would make an
interestingtest subject to add to 33.1,
don't you think?
What do you plan to do?
Protect our investment.
Come on. I'll walk you out.
Yeah,I got it.
Meet me at the rendezvous.
Hey,are we gonna do this or are you
gonna lurkin the shadows all night?
Just being careful.
After all,I'm not as fast as you.
Clark.
I was,uh,just thinking about you.
You got a funny wayof showing it.
I've left youhalf a dozen messages.
I'm sorry. I've been preoccupied.
Helping that doctorfrom
belle reve get out of jail.
Clark,my involvementwith
belle reve is past history.
But it appearsthat you still have
a very active interestin
breaking into luthorcorp.
Where was this taken?
Mexico - the luthorcorpprocessing plant.
If you're going to
continueplaying games like this,
you should be more careful.
This isn't me.
No?
Who is it,then?
God,mrs. K,thank you so much.
This was so good.
Where do you put it all?
You eat more than clark,and
he's twice your size.
Yeah,well,you know,I burn a lot of calories.
Well,there's plenty morein the fridge.
I have to runto a meeting.
Would you mindcleaning up?
Yeah,anything for you,mrs. K.
It's niceto have you here,bart.
I hope you stay longerthis time.
Hey,what's up,man?You just
missed a killer spread.
You can cut the act.
I know about luthorcorp and the
break-ins by somebodywho's as fast as me.
Yeah. Faster,actually.
You know what's funny? I actually believed
your storyabout how I changed your life.
Look,it's not a story,clark,okay?
Really,I'm not the same guy.
You stole from lex before.
You're stealing from him again.
What's the difference?
It's just - ugh! -It's complicated.
I'm a smart guy. Explain it to me.
I can'T.
Why not?I thought we were amigos.
We are.
Then tell me why you're
stealingfrom luthorcorp.
I JUST  I CAN't
I'll find outfor myself,then.
Look,I'm sorry I can't tell
youall my secrets,clark.
Okay?
I thought a guy like youwould understand.
I know it's justa vacation,but -
what? Vacation?No,vacation is palm springs.
Monte carlois a fairy tale.
Yeah,hopefullywithout prince charming
having a disappearing actevery five minutes.
Um,I think you'll be
keepinghis full attention,lois.
Yeah,you know,I'd better. It's not
like I govictoria's secret for anybody.
What do you think?
Should I have gone with the blk lace?
No.
Something tells me greenis
definitely his color.
Hey,chloe.
God. Smallville. Learn how to knock.
What if I'd been naked?
Lois is jetting offto
monte carlo with oliver.
Oliver?
I'll send you a postcardif I'm not too busy.
No,lois,you should,um...
get a couple new bikinis.
Good idea. Thanks,smallville.
Maybe it wasn'tsuch a good idea
to help oliverkeep his secret from her.
What,that he's the green arrow?
No offense,but you weren'texactly honest
with lana about your secret,either.
Look how that ended up.
Maybe all keeping secretsdoes sometimes is
force you to lieto the people you care about.
Are we stilltalking about oliver?
The guy who saved youat the planet -
he didn't exactly get away. It's bart.
What? Wait a minute.
Bart can superspeed,too?
He's actually a lot fasterthan
I am. That's the truth.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
It's fine. You were
protecting him. It's okay.
I mean,if anyone gets it,it's me.
But why are yououting him now?
I think he's headed for
trouble,and I need to find him.
Can you gps his cellphone?
Yeah,I can try. Do you have his number?
He broke into a luthorcorp
plantdown in mexico.
Now I think lexis on to him.
If he tries to break intoanother facility...
no good. His phone must be off.
What about call history?Can
you pull up a record?
Legally?Absolutely not.
There's over a dozen callsto that number
in the last 24 hours.
Let's see who's onthe other end.
Artemis global
consortium?Never heard of them.
It's as subsidiaryof J.L. International,
which is a satellitecompany
currently orbiting...
queen industries?
It's oliver.
He's using bartto attack luthorcorp.
I'm in.
Not so fast now,are you?
Oliver.
Look,clark,whatever's gotyour
tighty whities in a bunch,
now is not the time.
Where's bart?I saw his phone records.
I know he's working for you.
Not for me. Working with me.
There's a difference.
It's not gonna matter whenhe
ends up in jail or worse.
Yeah,you don't knowwhat
you're talking about.
I know how muchyou hate lex.
Is that whyyou recruited bart -
to help withyour little vendetta?
No. To stop 33.1.
You know about 33.1?
Why didn't you tell mewhat you were up to?
Clark,do you check in with me
every time you run offto save the world?
Oh,that's right. For a
second there,I forgot.
You like to wait for troubleto
show up on your doorstep.
That's not true.
Then why haven't you
doneanything to stop 33.1?
I was busywith another problem.
What could be more urgentthan lex luthor
developing an armyof superfreaks,clark?
That's what he's doing.
He's starting a war.
What have you found out?
Not enough.
Last nightbart infiltrated a place that
was supposed to housethe mainframe for 33.1.
That's the last timeI heard from him.
So I reconnedthe target this morning.
The placehad been stripped clean.
Everything's gone.
The whole thingwas a setup.
Lex has bart.
We have to find him.
- My team's already on it.
- Your team?
Not everybodyflies solo,kent.
Morning,sunshine.
I know you.
You've stolen from mebefore.
I want a lawyer.
And I want a ponytail.
Disappointment abounds.
Who do you work for?
What you see is what
you get,there,goldilocks.
You're a low-level thief.
Swiping corporate dataisn't your style.
Now,tell mewho you're working for,
and this won't have to getunpleasant.
All right.
I work for a guycalled mr. Kiss-my-butt.
Would you like meto introduce you?
The floor of your cellhas been outfitted with
pressure platesdesigned to track movement.
Stop in one placefor even a
millisecond after I activate them,
and you fry.
Last chance.
Well,maybe you'll feelmore talkative
when you get tiredof running.
Aah!
A.C.,Checkthe luthorcorp manifests.
Gotcha.
How long have you guysbeen working together?
I joined upabout six months ago.
Ollie and bart had
alreadybeen doing their thing.
What about your girlfriend -katherine?
Dude,don't even go there.
She gave it her best shot.
But with all this hardwarein me...
I'm sorry,victor.
Ollie found me. I was living on the streets.
He gave me a warm meal,roof over my head...
and a reason to go on living.
Did he just saysomething nice about me?
Maybe he's startingto rust.
A.C.,How'd you fallinto all this?
I got into a little troublesinking a whaler
off the coast of japan.
A little trouble? That'swhat
you're gonna go with?
Ollie had to save your
scalybutt from getting filleted.
I would have gottenout of it.
Before or after they packed
youinto a thousand little tin cans?
Well,at least he wouldhave
been dolphin-safe.
Fish jokes.
That's all I ever getare fish jokes.
So how's lois doing,man?Is she all right?
I think you'd have to askyour boss.
Now is not the time.
We need to focuson locating bart.
And how exactly did you
get himinvolved in this?
He's never beenmuch of a team player.
Looks like you two
havesomething in common,huh?
Actually,I was out on
patrolin star city one night,
and I came across bart.
He was helping himselfto a free meal.
I could tell he was a good kid,you know?
He just neededa little direction,
so I offered him a job.
Look where that got him.
I underestimated lex.
It won't happen again.
I've compiled a listof all luthorcorp
holdings within a 100-mile radius.
Bart could be heldin any
one of those facilities.
That's a lot of real estateto cover.
I think I know someonewho
can help us narrow it down.
Victor stone and arthur
curryare working for him,too?
Yeah,oliver's been busy.
Is there anythingin your luthorcorp intel that
can help us find outwhere bart's being held?
I don't know.
Uh... wait.
When I had my feelers outfor dr. Casselli, I
managed to shake loosesome internal documents.
In the last few days,
there's been a flurryof equipment transfers
to the ridge facilitieson
the outskirts of metropolis.
Doesn't luthorcorpmove
equipment all the time?
This isn't just a coupleof forklifts,clark.
Half a ton of lead
shielding,electrical pressure plates,
more than $20 millionworth of equipment
to measure high-velocityparticles.
Bart. Take everythingand bring it to oliver.
Me? Clark -
I can get to the ridgefaster myself.
I can't let anythinghappen to bart.
Mr. Queen,it's chloe
sullivan. Clark sent me.
Where's clark?
He went to rescue bart.
He told you about bart?
We trust each other.Clark
tells me everything -
well,almost everything.
I did have to figure out about your
green-leather fetishon my lonesome.
Don't worry. I didn't say anything to lois.
Although,you mightwant to consider -
hey,let's just stick tothe
main plot,there,sidekick.
So,what do you got?
Hopefully a solid leadon bart.
Where are victor and A.C.?
Guess we're not that good
at the whole "secret" partof this yet.
Yeah,but you're great
atgetting caught by the villain.
Anyway,I think bart'sbeing held
at a placecalled the ridge facility.
That's down by the docks.
It's on our listof possible 33.1 targets.
All right,boys. You know the drill.
Let's gear up and get out.
Oh,no.
What now?
Lead shielding. This isn't just for bart.
I think the ridge facility'sbeing used
to refine meteor rock.
Clark's in trouble.
restricted
Green arrow to watchtower.
We're in position.
Okay,there should be a securityaccess
panel near the east door.
According to this schematic,
you need to very carefullyrewire the sys-
or...
I could just jack in andshut
the whole perimeter down.
You can do that?
Queen industries upgrade.
Accessingperimeter security.
Perimeter neutralized.
Aquaman,you're up.
Perimeter breached. Proceeding to target.
You'd make one hellof a can opener.
You'd look good on a bag of green beans.
All right,we're in. Which way?
The refinement vault's100 meters southwest.
Still no word from clark.
If he's in there,we'll
get him out. Let's go.
You've gota different mission.
You're the boss,robin hood.
What mission?What are you doing?
Watchtower to green
arrow. What's your status?
Switchingto silent running.
Stand byfor instructions.
Aquaman,do your thing.
Hey. You're not supposed to be here.
Neither am I.
Come on.
- I'm all right.
- You sure?
Green arrow to watchtower.
Boy scout'sout of the woods.
Boy scout?
If you hadn't ran off,you
couldhave picked your code name.
You don't want to playfor
the team,that's fine.
Point taken. Where's bart?
"Impulse. " He didn't get to
pickhis own code name either.
Watchtower will guide you
towhere he's probably being held.
What are yougonna be doing?
What I do best.
Watchtower to boy scout. Let's find impulse.
Cyborg to aquaman.
Where the hell are you,fish stick?
Dude,what took you so long?
Nice.
But,please,put a shirt on.
I swim fasterwhen I'm naked.
I bet you do.
You're lucky I still gotmy pants on.
Impulse located.
Bart,you okay?
Muy bueno,amigo.
I don't care. I want a level-one lockdown.
No one gets in or out.
Little late for that.
You got 10 minutesto clear
your people out of here
before I blow this placeoff the map.
You.
You remember. I'm touched.
Well,it's a little hardto forget.
Last time we met,you
put an arrow in my chest.
You put a bullet in mine. Bygones?
Go to hell.
You first.
Can you superspeed?
Yeah,I just
- I need a minuteto catch my breath.
You know what? You're
gonnahave to catch it later.
Aquaman,cyborg,rendezvous alpha confirmed.
We're on the move.
Watchtower,have all luthor'speople
cleared the building?
The last heat signaturesare
moving away from the north.
Wait a second. What are you doing?
What do you thinkI'm doing?
You want more of your
friendsto end up in here?
Yeah,I'm voting noon that one.
Watchtower,are you sureeveryone's
out of the building?
100% positive.
All right. Let's do it.
have the jet fueledand ready.
I want to be in the airas soon as possible.
Hey.
I hope your bird's gotsome serious lift,
'cause this thingweighs a ton.
Aren't you packed yet?
Where's your stuff?
Lois,um...
don't even think about sayingwhat
I think you're gonna say.
I'm sorry.
I,um,I have to go awayon business.
Postpone it.
It's not that simple.
Nothing with you ever is.
You're like two completelydifferent people.
There's the charming,romantic guy
that I fell in love with,
and then there'sthis other guy
who can't stick aroundin one place
long enoughto see what he's missing.
Ever sincemy parents died...
...I've jumped aroundfrom city to city,
from continentto continent.
And... in all those years...
...not once have I regrettedleaving anyone.
But then I met you.
Then stay.
I can'T.
Because there are more importantthings
in this world than what I want...
and what I love.
I hope somedayI can explain why.
Don't expect meto be waiting around for that
when you get back.
I'm not coming back,lois.
At least not anytime soon.
I'm sorry.
I never wanted to hurt you.
Well,you finally got
aroundto it anyway,didn't you?
This is the... the moment,right?
The moment that I'm gonna regretfor
the rest of my life, isn't it?
Yes.
I loved you.
Bart allen - gone. He escaped.
A multimillion-dollarinstallation destroyed.
33.1 irrevocablycompromised.
But,son,at least you found out the jolly
green archerand his extraordinary cohorts -
they're not yourrun-of-the-mill adversaries.
Which is exactly whywe
have to continue with 33.1.
If terroristslike green arrow
are recruiting peoplewith abilities,
the only way to protect freedomand democracy
is to fight firewith fire.
Freedom and democracy?
Well,I hadn't realizedyour
goals were quite so lofty.
Well,there's a lotthat escapes your
attention in your declining years,dad,
but not mine.
The security footage
from the ridge facilitywas destroyed.
However,several guards
describeone of green arrow's men
as someone that
soundedremarkably like clark kent.
Clark. Impossible.
A word that always seems to popup
when talking about him, doesn't it?
Lex,it was not clark.
How can you be so sure?
Because I was having dinnerwith him
last night when all this happened.
Martha made pot roast with new
potatoesand tiny little baby carrots.
It was delicious.
Clark had three helpings.
Don't worry,son.
You still haveplenty of enemies out there
plotting your downfall.
Okay. Thanks.
So the daily planetis running with the story
that a gas explosion destroyedthe vacant
luthorcorp building down by the docks.
Vacant?
Looks like the luthor
cover-upmachine is in full swing.
Well,at leastwe got bart out
before lex ran himinto an early grave.
Come on. No worries. I
had plenty of juice left.
Could have fooled me,
the way you cleaned outmama kent's fridge.
That's 'cause I like to stayfueled up.
Just in case I need
to,uh,spring into action.
I still have a boyfriend.
Yeah. Well,a man can dream,can't he?
Now you knowwhy we call him impulse.
Impulse,cyborg,aquaman,green arrow.
What do you guys callyour team?
I don't know. I've been
thinkingthat we need something cool.
We need something like -like -
I was thinking about somethingwith
the word "justice" in it.
After all,that's what lexis
gonna get a big dose of.
Victor and A.C. Were able tohack into the
33.1 mainframe before we blewthe building.
That wasyour other mission.
Haven't met the computer
yetI couldn't crack wide open.
What did you guysfind out?
That lex isn't satisfied
playingin his own backyard anymore.
Luthorcorp is starting updivisions
of 33.1 all across the globe.
Wherever there's evidenceof
people with abilities,
there'll be laboratoriesto
do experiments on them.
We can't let that happen.
We won'T.
Gentlemen,our first target is a large
facilityon the island of corto maltese.
You guys know the drill.
Wheels up in 30 minutes. Get your gear.
You coming,amigo?
Yeah,you got to comewith us,man.
We could usethe big guns.
They're right,you know
- you'dbe a major asset to the team.
I want to be a part of
this,guys. I really do.
But...
that problem I told you
about -the one that I caused -
I have to take careof that first.
This isn't the endof the story,clark.
This is just the beginning.
Chloe.
Come on,boys.
Let's go save the world.
You know,you have some
prettyamazing friends,clark kent.
Yeah. I do.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
SMALLVILLE
Season 06 Episode11