dad,please,you d't have...
go on. You say one more word. Just one.
okay,if this is what you want...
I work for the strachan
family in rosedale.
They have a son.
He's going to kill mr.
Strachan. He's got a gun.
oh,my god,rolland,what have we done?
This is the police
strategic response unit.
Everyone in the strachan house
needs to stay where they are.
Clear on your count.
Three,two,one.
three,two,one.
2 hours earlier
comfy there,samo?
I'm very comfortable,sir.
Get you some more coffee?
All good,sir,but thank you for asking.
What are you doing here,anyway?
'Cause you just had to bring it up?
Well,constable callaghan,that
would be because yesterday I got...
Tightest grouping at both long range
and short range firearm practice.
Meaning you get to do monthly
cleanup,and I get to do this.
- Missed a spot there,ed.
- Yeah,whatever.
Actually,what I meant
is,why are you down here?
Why aren't you upstairs training,you
know,at something dangerous and exciting?
Sam,everything okay?
Yeah,I... I just gotta go do something.
Final Homecoming for Three Heroes
Wake up,boy.
Rj?
Hello?
Jay,it's braddock.
Sam,the hell time is it?
0600,soldier.
You out of special forces now or what?
No,no,uh... in-between tours.
Back to the sand in a week. You?
Police force.
Got tired of working for a living,huh?
Yeah,I guess.
So,dave haverlik... you hear?
anyways,figure I'll go
up on the highway tonight.
You will?
Died in the field,didn't he?
He wasn't in the field; he was at camp.
They hit the camp?
Come on,man. You gonna make me say it?
All right,chris geordie found him.
Own sidearm and everything.
I just know I ain't going up there.
Just like we said,right?
Right.
What are you talking
about? Where up north?
It's a surprise.
What are you so up about?
What do you have in there?
Uh,you know,a little fun and games.
I guess it's me that gets to
tell them your travel plans.
No,man.
Why do you think I'm here?
I'm getting you out of
here. You're coming with me.
Where,up north? Why... why
would I want to do that?
Are you serious?
Don't forget your bank card.
The units canceled mine.
Dude,no. I just got
my acceptance letters.
- U of t,mcgill,yale...
- yale?
- Wow,what,you get into harvard,too?
- No.
Dummy.
Yeah,'cause nothing says "scholastic achievement" like
the baden-highsmith military academy for young men.
Yeah,well,bh and I decided to reassess
our educational relationship yesterday.
You had one year,rj. One
year,and you were home free.
Have to toughen you up,obviously.
So,you gonna do what
your big brother says?
- You gonna come with me?
- No.
No? Oh,okay,well,sure.
That's the way you feel,but why are
you hitting yourself there,buddy?
- It's okay,don't beat yourself up.
- Rolland?
What are you doing here?
Hey,ma.
Rj,you can't be here.
He doesn't know.
I don't care.
Hilary? What are you doing out there?
Well,he's up now.
Margarite will set you
a place for breakfast.
I'm not sitting down with
you and him for breakfast.
There's no way.
So,uh,maybe later we can all
go for a walk in the ravine.
I mean,we haven't done that in
forever. Or maybe we could...
why,I'm fine,dad. And how are you?
Could we please not do this,just once?
What I am doing is exerting every ounce of
self-control I have not to ask the obvious question.
Oh,well,the answer is,uh,no.
Your tie doesn't make your ass look fat.
You idiot.
This is what I mean.
You contemptible,ungrateful,
stupid,vicious idiot.
oh,it's funny,is it? You think
it's funny? Well,then,laugh at this.
Fully taxable,non-refundable.
$36,000 we spent to send you to that place,
and if you think you are gonna drop out,
then you will pay us back every
single penny,do you understand?
- do you understand?
- no.
No,you don't understand?
Even you can't be that stupid.
No,I'm not gonna pay you back
because I never wanted to go there.
Rolland,where else could you go?
They were going to press
charges for the fire...
so,then,let them press
charges. Or don'T.
Protect the precious
strachan family name.
Do what you feel. Send me a
postcard. I'll be in the yukon.
Who do we know in the yukon?
Oh,hilary,shut up.
Simon's coming with me. He's the only
reason I'm still here. Right,simon?
No. Simon is going to a real school.
Simon is going to do
what's expected of him.
Because he is not a liar and
a stupid fool and a coward.
Dad,please,you don't have to...
go on. You say one more word. Just one.
Okay,if this is what
you want... here it is.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season01 Episode07
Rj,look at me.
You think i won't do this.
You don't think I'll do this?
If you had the guts,I might be afraid.
Rj. Rj,look at me. Rj!
You are so far in over your head.
You have no idea what
you're doing,do you?
I work for the strachan
family in rosedale.
They have a son.
He's going to kill mr.
Strachan. He's got a gun. Hurry.
So,I saw the paper. Is
that guy from your team?
Brave guys.
Did I miss something?
He wasn't brave. He did it himself.
I'm sorry.
Were you close?
Spend enough time,
think you know someone...
and you had no idea,huh?
Sam,I'm just trying to help.
So,you gonna go to the highway
and watch the procession?
- No.
- No? Don't you usually go?
On our team,the only thing protecting
you is each other,so we made a deal.
You give up like that,you don't
mean anything to us anymore.
Team one,team one,hot call,gear up!
Sam,if you want to talk after...
take your truck?
Absolutely.
Team leader,talk back.
Go ahead,boss.
Stealth approach,low prof E.
Absolutely no noise,you copy?
We copy,boss.
Okay,rj.
Okay,it's you and me.
- We can work this out together.
- Yeah,how?
Yeah,simon,please,
come on,tell us all how.
Okay,rj.You're gonna give me
the gun,we're gonna put it back,
and then you're going back to bh.
No,I can't go back.
It's only for a few more
months,you can hand it.
No,I mean,I can't
go back-- ask mom.
Oh,well,what a surprise.
Dad,shut up!
Rj,you can trust me,okay?
Whatever it is,we can do this.
Please,just give me the gun.
oh,dear lord,no. Now
look what you've done.
Rj,it's okay.
This is it.
What's he doing?
So much for the stealth approach.
Sru on the scene.
Speak to you for a second?
Yes,sir,there's an armed teenager...
I assume you're new on the job.
Yes,sir.
Here's today's lesson: Armed and barricaded subjects
tend to get freaked out by sirens and flashing lights.
You get me?
- I'll turn the lights off.
- All right,move your car.
I'll move my car.
Sam,take the back entrance.
Rolland strachan.
Recognize the name?
Crown V. Porter,trial of the century?
Right,right. The defense attorney.
Right,hence the mansion.
Well,the family was loaded
from way back. Gold mines.
Anything you don't know?
Okay,that's it. I've had enough of this.
- Dad!
- Rolland!
Your great-grandfather carried
that gun across the chilkoot pass.
Your grandfather wore it on juno beach.
Does that mean anything to you at all?
It means that that gun was
meant to be used by a man,
which is why you can't
do anything with it!
- Dad! Dad! Dad!
- Simon,listen to me. Get out of the way!
No! Simon!
shot fired. Sam,you
cover that back entrance.
Team will attempt phone contact,
but be ready for immediate entry.
no more.
Rj,no! What are you
doing? Get out of the way!
Wait,we can fix this! Okay?
team,you have eyes on subject?
Negative.
All right,prepare for entry.
Oh,my god,rolland!
This is the police
strategic response unit.
Everybody in the strachan house
needs to stay where they are!
Clear on your count.
Three,two,one.
I've got action here,smoke
bombs! I need backup here.
I'm blind. I repeat. I need
backup. I'm completely smoked out.
stop! Police!
Team,subject's in the ravine.
Looks like we've got a manhunt.
Wordy,containment?
Can't really block off a ravine,but we've
got all the bordering roads contained,
checkpoints at every exit,uniforms
are already out beating the bush.
All right,good.
We've got a few dozen hikers,
bikers and family strollers.
Let's clear them out,keep them safe in case
our subject decides to do something stupid.
Spike,how's the new toy?
Acoustic detector's good to go.
He fires anywhere within
earshot,we've got him.
- Excellent.
- Yeah.
Wordy,I want you inhe hummer.
The rest of us,we will be heading
into the bush,diamond formation.
One dog per unit.
Let's keep to the grid.
Let's clear it quad by quad.
keep in touch with the
cp and the other uniforms.
Boss,how's the infrared coming?
Chopper arrive?
Yeah,it's messing up my hair.
Better you than me.
Infrared,two minutes away,eddie.
Outstanding.
Yeah,well,let's not forget
our subject's 18 years old,
emotionally distraught and afraid.
He may be armed,but he isn't rambo.
Let's see if we can bring him back
to his family in one piece,okay?
I'll try,boss.
But those smoke bombs
were pretty clever.
This guy's from around
here. He knows the area.
All right,infrared coming at you.
Gentlemen and lady...
this is our forward looking infrared.
Every dot is a heat signature,every
heat signature could be our subject.
Don't suppose they have an armed
18 year old filter for that thing?
'Fraid not. Quad by quad.
hey,doc.
What do you know about the
baden-highsmith academy for young men.
The military school? Not
much. Your shooter from there?
Yeah,he was expelled recently.
A fight with another
kid,the mother's saying.
Expelled just for a fight?
You know,I was wondering the same thing,
too. The parents aren't talking a lot.
Preliminary profile?
Pretty textbook: Well-to-do family,
successful parents... one sibling.
He's got a history of antisocial
acts begining in adolescence:
Fights,petty theft,and,uh,last year he was
accused of starting a fire at his private school.
Steady escalation.
You want to know,is this kid just a danger
to himself,his family,or everybody else,too?
I love it when you read my mind.
- Just call when you know.
- Okay.
- If we could just go over what happened,mr. Strachan.
- No.
Remember who you are.
Infrared's up and running.
I'm headed east along the
main road by the ravine.
What's your problem?
Woods. My people don't like them.
Your people? From woodbridge?
No,romans.
Few times we fought in the forest
against the huns didn't go so good,okay?
Team one,I've got two sigs
northeast of your position.
Heads up,25 meters and closing.
20 meters. 18 meters... 17...
sixteen. 15,they're right on you.
Wordy,we've got two
more negatives. Jules.
All right,girls. Come
on,time to go home.
Dozen more hot spots out
there. Keep at it,guys.
Mrs. Strachan. My mom's exhausted.
I can tell you everything.
My dad was sitting right there.
He was showing us our great-grandfather's
old gun-- it's a family heirloom.
I know you're supposed
to check if it's loaded.
I guess they didn't,and my
brother took it,it just went off.
I mean,thank god it only
hit my dad in the arm.
It was really just an accident.
All right,well,if it was just an
accident,how come your brother took off?
Uh,well... my brother's
had a rough year. I guess...
when he saw my dad
hurt,he just panicked.
But,but he honestly didn't
mean it. I know my brother.
Okay,one more thing.
You're saying your father and brother
were sitting here when the gun went off?
Yeah.
Okay,well,if he was hit here, and
your brother was sitting there,
then the bullet would
be somewhere around here.
But if they were standing,and your
brother was pointing the gun...
then the bullet would be about here.
You want to try this again?
yeah,yeah,fine. Just,do you
mind if I check something?
Where the hell are you?
You've got to help me,simon.
What am I supposed to do,huh?
I mean,the cops are here
and they've got,like,
an entire army out looking
for you,just come home.
Mom's freaking out,
dad's in the hospital.
Is he going to be okay?
- Yeah,I think so.
- That's too bad.
Rj,what's going on with you?
Hey,don't worry about me. I'm fine,okay?
We just got to get up
north and we'll be okay
what "up north"?I don't
even know what you mean.
Come on,you remember those stories
that dad told about the chilkoot pass?
And his grandfather being up there,
and how he made his name up there?
- Remember?
- Yeah.
That's what we're gonna do; we're gonna
go up there,we're gonna make our name.
Making our names? What
are you talking about?
- what's going on?
- It is,right?
We lose the trail?
There's ammonia splashed all over
the place. Throws off the dogs.
I mean,what? This kid's holding
ammonia in case of a manhunt?
Ammonia's good for a lot of stuff:
Fertilizing,cleaning,bombs...
you getting this,boss?
Yeah,copy that.
I mean,we can be whatever
we want to be up there.
Nobody will know us.
Okay,you'll be safe.
I've just got to get you away from them.
Yeah,but I am getting away.
I'm going to school,remember?
Rj?
Yeah. Yeah,yeah,yeah. You're right,um...
what about me?
That's fine. You know what? It's fine.
Don't worry about it. Do what you want,um...
the least you can do
is help me out,though.
I'm trying to help.
No,I need money to get up there.
You know what? Meet me at the
place. You know where,by noon,okay?
Do it or else... I gotta
do something else,you know?
Where are you going,simon?
Uh,I don't know. I have to go out.
Yeah? Where? Mind if we tag along?
No,it's... nah,it's not that important.
your phone's buzzing.
Is that your brother,simon?
- No. I don't know.
- You didn't even check it.
Let's get a listing of all the strachan
family phones,including rj's cell.
You... you know I'm not
going to tell you anything.
You might not mean to,but you are.
We're just trying to help
your brother. You can help,too.
Of course we want to
help in any way we can.
Then it would be helpful if you could
tell me more about why you expelled rj.
And as I've already explained,
all I can tell you is that he was de-enrolled
following an altercation with his cadet team leader.
Well,was he alone in the altercation?
Any other boys involved were
dealt with appropriately.
To say anything more...
requires written consent of his parents.
We don't have time for that right now.
If you want to help rj,you'll help me...
I'm sorry,doctor, I've
told you all I can.
Now,you're welcome to
take cadet strachan's file.
And please,give my regrets,
and regards to his father.
It's about rj?
You know rj?
We're heading north
on those coordinates.
Triangulated signal from the
kid's cell phone's up ahead.
Only you guys showing
up on infrared. Sorry.
Got a visual on a domicile,
50 meters from our position.
Still no infrared,guys.
The kid's got survival
training,knows about camouflage.
He gets enough cover on top of him,he
can hide his heat signature,so be careful.
this is the strategic response unit.
Rj,come on out,we don't want
to hurt you. We can help.
Give him a blast of cs gas.
Boss,you sure about that reading?
He hasn't moved. Kid's playing possum.
we've got some news about rj.
Is he okay?
Did you know he's been using
crystal methamphetamine?
no,no,there's no way.
Right now he's in an unstable
state-- euphoria,paranoia,mania.
The fact that he's been using
in the middle of all this,
that tells us that he's bingeing,and
he's headed for a major crash,okay?
So,we need to bring him back
before he hurts himself anymore.
Or anyone else.
I can't deal with this right now.
Mom,please,what am I supposed to do?
You should leave. While you can.
Before your father comes back.
All I can do is say I'm sorry.
What else have I ever done?
Hold it,I can help you with this.
Okay. How?
I can show you where
my brother's hiding.
just around that bend.
No trail here.
He's saying go through the thicket.
All right,it's pretty heavy brush.
Extended line formation,ten
to 15 meters apart. Let's go.
Hey,sam. Walk away from the kid.
Jules told me about your
buddy. My condolences.
Anyway,you and the kid seem to
have a good connection going.
He may open up more to you,and if he does
I just need you to listen for some things.
I don't... that's really
not my thing yet,boss.
No,no,no,you're doing fine. You're
doing fine. Just trust your instincts.
This secret trail,hiding place
from when they were kids,you buy it?
Yeah. He knows his
brother. Where he's going.
Okay then.
I think you need to ask him something.
Whether he answers or not
here's what we're looking for...
I've been worried about him. Is he okay?
Hard to say. Cops haven't
brought him in yet.
He's in a lot of trouble.
So you want to tell me
about the meth,torley?
Look,I could care less about
the "how" and "who" of this.
I just need to know "why."
Rj was different from the rest of us.
He worked hard,stayed out of trouble.
Kept saying: One year and
I'm outta here,one year.
Was a good guy.
Then one night he comes
to me,he can't sleep.
He's having nightmares.
It turns out he doesn't want to sleep.
- He wants to stay up.
- So he starts taking meth?
Taking it and making
it; he loves chemistry.
But he didn't really lose it until the
thing with the cadet leader,simpson.
Two nights ago,it's me,a couple
other guys,rj,we're partying.
Simpson finds us,goes berserk,we're
all going home,blah,blah,blah.
Of course he comes at me first.
Why of course?
Because I'm half his size.
He's just a douche that way.
But,so he-he grabs me, and
rj just goes off on him,
starts kicking his ass,total hardcore.
Simpson's still in the infirmary.
I guess that was enough for the school.
And that was it for rj.
I hope he's got good friends out there.
'Cause none of us were
much good for him in here.
I've got his shoes again.
You're not at the trail yet.
I know. And they're
heading that way,but...
sam,lines of force are supposed to go in
the opposite direction of the track,correct?
Yeah.
Well,these are going the same way.
Doesn't make any sense.
Unless he's wearing his shoes backwards,
and bringing us on a goose chase.
Ed,you want to follow
the footprints back?
Good plan,sam.Let's go back
500 meters,if nothing we turn back.
Sam,bring the hummer around and meet us.
Good,deeper.
Why are they going that way?
The trail's the other way.
My boss... he's a really smart guy.
He can tell things about people.
He wanted me to ask you...
your old man--
he hit you and rj?
So you grew up around here,huh?
Running around,hide-and-go-
seek,that kind of thing?
Okay,team,heads up,eyes sharp.
This kid's headed for a crash.
When he does,it's
gonna be fast and ugly.
I never had a brother. Must be nice.
It kind of depends.
When he shoots your dad and gets the
cops coming after him,not so much.
a lot of guys I know,same
thing-- out of control.
They just needed a little
guidance. They turned out okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Sure.
This one guy I knew,basic
training-- loud,dumb,fat.
Everybody says,this is the guy who ditches
out in a week. We took bets and everything.
Six months later,he was at
the head of the grad parade.
Wasn't a guy there who
wouldn't follow him anywhere.
I spent a week on a
mountainside with him.
He told me about his family.
Believe me.
I figured,"man,if you can get through
that,you can get through anything."
So he turned out okay?
Yeah. Sure he did.
Somewhere you need to be,simon?
shot fired.
Anybody see the flash?
- Negative.
What's happening? What are you doing?
If that was rj,we're
gonna find him with this.
Please don't hurt him. Do not hurt him.
got it!
Okay,team,shot signature's coming from
quadrant 4-c,that's 100 meters due east.
We're gonna do a pincer formation.
Ed,jules,wordy,you're alpha,head
northeast around 25 degrees,100 meters.
You'll be in quadrant 4-B.
Spike,lewis-- bravo,southeast
120 degrees,hit him from below.
Alpha,we got a sig coming right at you.
Jules.
Okay,you're okay. You're okay.
Can you tell me what happened?
I was running,and-and-
and he had a gun,
and I didn't have any money and he went to
hit me and so I ran and then he shot at me.
Bravo team,you're almost
on another sig,be careful.
- Hold up,hold up.
- What?
You hear something?
- Lew,I'm on fire! I'm on fire!
- Spike!
Officer down! Officer down!
Quad 4-c! We need assistance!
officer down! Officer down!
I'm fine.Thanks.
Ammonium trilodide.
Homemade explosive of every
anarchist jackass and troublemaker.
Kid hits me with ammonium triiodide.
Unbelievable.
I'm sorry,man. I should
have seen him. I'm sorry.
Bro,seriously,shut up.
But I will say,this one
last time-- romans and woods.
All I'm saying.
All right,I'm here.
According to the doc,the kid
didn't just attack the cadet leader.
He attacked the cadet leader
after he saw him grab another kid.
Abused kids lash out.
But this looks like a kid who got used to lashing
out to protect someone else,like a baby brother.
The path simon marked for us was the
exact opposite of where rj was headed.
Kid lied to us. I guess I was wrong.
I got a man down.
And I could care less about
this kid's psychodrama.
This game is over now.
I don't want you
rushing back in angry, Ed.
It's a little late for that,boss.
Let me talk to the kid.
You know what? I appreciate
the effort,sam,but...
this is their bond.
You're never gonna get brother to
turn on brother. The kid's a lost lead.
No. I just didn't get it
before. Let me try one more time.
You just gonna let him hang,
like everybody else has?
You don't know anything about us.
I know this: Your
brother's gonna get killed.
Maybe that's what he wants.
Is that what you want?
Whether it was A...
belt,or a cane,or
sometimes just a fist...
rj was always there,standing right in front
of me,taking the worst of it every time.
He'd say,"what are you so scared
of,huh? I'm still here,aren't I?"
How am I supposed to turn
him in after that,huh?
I-I can't tur...
you'll be saving him by bringing him in.
Or you're going to spend the rest of your life
wondering what might have happened if you just tried.
Look,I...
I promise you this: Together,we
can bring your brother back alive.
Because so long as he's alive,
there-there's hope,right?
Hey,I knew you'd come.
Remember this place?
- Remember the summers we used to have here?
- Yeah.
- Remember that?
- Yeah. Sure.
- You burned up that cop pretty bad,rj.
- Yeah. Okay,well...
he shouldn't have come after me then.
You know,that's what you get.
it's okay,man. It's me,buddy.
What are you so scared of?
Meth? Blowing up cops in the woods.
I mean,who does this? Who are you now?
The same guy who was there for
you every night... every time.
Do you remember him?
Yeah. I just... that guy
never scared me before.
I am... I'm just tired,simon. You know?
Yeah. I know,man.
I was up there,and,uh...
well,I was doing good. I was.
I started getting these nightmares,and I just figured
if I stayed up,you know,I'd just... I'd be okay.
You know,I'd just get through the year.
Come back to you. We'd get out
of here. We'd be safe,you know?
Rj,no matter where we
go,it'll still be us.
Okay. Good. Okay,well,
let's go then. Come on.
No,rj,just listen.
Remember that time dad lost
his watch and he blamed me?
Yeah.
And he came at me at dinner,
and he had that old belt.
You jumped in and you
grabbed it,remember that?
Yeah,sure. Of course.
- It hurt like hell.
- Yeah.
And you grabbed it even though
it almost ripped off your hand.
- You wouldn't let go.
- Yeah.
He was pulling on it,
and he was going crazy,
and mom was crying and I was
crying,but you wouldn't let go.
Okay.
I just want you to know,
I'll never forget that.
- Yeah,okay.
- That you wouldn't let go.
I'm never going to let you go,either,
rj,no matter what happens. All right?
Okay. Sure.
I don't know what you're talking about,man,
but,uh,we should really get out of here.
No,no. No matter what happens.
What do you mean,man?
I just,I'm...
- no way.
- Rj... rj...
- Rj,just...
no way
rj...
rj!
No,rj! Rj,no!
- Settle down,settle down.
- Rj! Rj! No!
Hey,hey,I got him. I got him.
- It's okay.
- Rj!
- Let go of him! I'm sorry!
- It's okay now. It's over.
- Get off of him!
- I'm sorry!
I got you. It's okay,
soldier. I got you.
Excuse me.
Yeah,I'm sorry,sir. That's just,
uh... that's not gonna happen.
And why is that exactly?
That's a good question.
Here's a better question,sir.
Who does the big-time lawyer call
when he needs a big-time lawyer?
I've had just about enough of this.
Haven't we all.
Lewis and spike are out of
the hospital. You seen sarge?
Yeah,he met up with a doctor.
They're gonna get that
kid a psych evaluation.
They don't think he belongs in jail.
Where's sam at?
Oh,had,um,he had some personal stuff.
* You...you and I made a pact *
* a deal that as we lay dying *
* we'd think about each other then *
* and smile as we're taken in *
* I...I listen like a little child *
* to the story of
your earthbound pilot *
* he plummeted so violent *
* a parachute not opening *
* and rushing to oblivion *
* he broke into that knowing grin *
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
* and I...I think about that a lot *
* 'cause a lot is what I've not got *
* a smile is what I least expect *
* from the clutches of this darkness *
* you billowed like a bowl of silk *
* and slowed me from my ruining *
Flashpoint
Season01 Episode07