I told you what I had to do.
Derek, I know where you
are. Wee coming there now.
Stay away.
Alpha team on our way.
Bravo on two. East stairs.
You got to trust yourself,
derek. You don't want to do this.
No, I don'T. But I have to.
No way. It's not goingppo haen.
If you guys want to do this, you're
going to have to go through me.
******
All right, bring it. See what you got.
Go ahead, go pass. What
you got? Oh, the fake!
What you got?
Oh, nice one! Schooled me.
Good job. That was good.
Okay, nash and shaq, all right.
My dinner's getting cold,
but good teamwork, guys.
Derek.
Mattie, how many times I got to tell you to
lock the door behind you when you get home.
mattie, come on, volume, please.
Hope you're hungry. I stopped at
burger shed, picked you up sdoublepicy.
Oh, gee, derek, thanks,
man. My favorite.
I mean, I know you had classes all day.
And you gotta work at the hospital in
a few hours-- but, hey, thanks, man.
You can have some fries, but you
got to finish your salad first.
- And then I want to see some homework.
- I'm not hungry.
Not hungry?
You okay?
What's wrong? You sick?
- Mattie, what happened?
- Nothing.
Whu do yo mean nothing? Don't
tell me nothing! What happened?
Nothing. It was an accident.
Mattie, talk to me.
Come on, it's a bullet wound.
I know a bullet wound when I see one.
- got to get you to the hospital.
- No, I can't go to the hospital. If the cops find out...
if you don't go to the hospital, this
could open up and you'll bleed to death.
- I'm not going. I'm not going.
- We're going.
All right, hold on.
Tug man, move your ass.
- It's shane, it's shane. It's shane.
- What?
Go, go, go, go.
- What floor you say he's at?
- Eight I think.
- You think?
- I mean, yeah, eight.
All right, come on.
shane thomas. He shot you.
What the hell you
doing with him, mattie?
With all that we have been through, tell
me you're not running with these guys.
I'm sorry, D. You've been working
so hard and I wanted to ...
come on, mattie.
When you was my age, you was already
running with the east side crew.
Yes, and look where that got us.
I'm sorry, all right? It
was an accident, I swR.
Derek, we can't tell
nobody. Derek, please.
I know someone at the hospital
who can help us. All right?
- I got your back.
- You got my back.
reyou' not doing it right.
I'm doing it how you told me to do it.
No, you're doing it like someone who
didn't listen to how I told him to do it.
- Okay.
- Communication, repetition, affirmation.
The secret to every great marriage.
boss, we up for a
drink tonight, or what?
I can'T. I got to finish this
article-- critical incidence newsletter.
Who says greg parker doesn't
know how to have a good time.
Spike.
I don't get it. I gave her a new gyro
just last week. I thought we were good.
Maybe it's not you, maybe it's her.
- Officer callaghan, how you doing?
- You really want to know?
Well, unless the answer is
"outstanding," not really.
I get it. I mean, eight gun calls,
two warrants a day-- it's exhausting.
- what?
- It's been a long week.
Copy that.
- But it's what we do though, right?
- Yep.
- He's gone, man.
- I can see that.
Looks like you tagged him pretty good.
Obviously not good enough.
Yo, give me some of that.
Man, it's a spicy burger. You
don't even eat spicy burgers.
- Don't tell me I don't eat...
- y'all shut up? God!
Yo, I say we wait for him here, man.
Whatever. Shane what do you want to do?
It ain't about what I
want. The kid's a loose end.
Yeah, the kid's a loose end. So?
So we chill. Wait for him to come home.
We're going to him.
It's okay. Come on.
You all right, buddy? Hold
on. Let's go find trudy.
- Trudy.
- Hey, you're early.
Trudy, listen...
are you mattie? Your brother
talks about you all the time.
Listen, I need a favor.
What's wrong?
Can you just look at my
little brother, please?
But I need you to keep
it quiet. He's been shot.
What?
He was just in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
D, what's going on?
Can we just fix him up
and get him out of here?
Gunshots have to be reported.
Tru, I can't do that.
You know how it works.
You said you were done with all that.
He didn't do anything.
It's okay. Look, I just
need you to trust me.
He's my little brother.
I can't have social services
take him away from me.
Please.
This needs sutures. We need a doctor.
- Can't do that.
- Derek...
hey, I will make it up to you big time.
Supply room in e wing.
Get me some butterfly
bandages and some saline.
- We're going to have to flush it out.
- Okay.
Just don't let anybody see you, okay?
Oh, don't worry.
Be back, okay?
Make it up to you big time?
Quiet.
ttie ma, get the hell out of here!
matt! trudy!
Can we get some help here please? Help!
Tru, tru... tru, I'm so sorry. Tru.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- Get some pressure dressing.
- Got it, got it.
Let's clear trauma one now.
Sir, sir, give us some room.
We've got some work to do here.
Code red. Code red. O.R.
Mattie!
team one, hot call. Shots
fired. Saint patrick's hospital.
Once staff member
down-- criticalonditi.
Active shooter at large.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season02 Episode13
Jules, you spent a lot of time
here after you got shot. You goah?
Ye, kind of hoping not to
see this place again so soon.
Uncontrolled entrances,
hundreds of rooms.
Pete, we've got a major
containment challenge here,
and we need all the
extra uniforms we can get.
Metro's sending everyone they
have. Calling people off shift.
Good. Put team four on alert.
And let's reach out to our
neighbors in york and durham regions,
see if they can spare any
brothers and sisters in blue.
- Copy.
- What do you got?
Hospital's in partial lockdown.
Uniforms are checking
people coming in and out.
Not all the entrance points have
been covered yet. Not enough bodies.
Reinforcements on their way.
How long since our
shooter's been active?
They said 12 minutes of quiet.
Quiet is good. We like quiet.
Jules, talk to any contacts
you might have in there.
- We need more intel here.
- Got it.
Pete, you got the name of
the nurse that got shot?
- Trudy vargas.
- I know her.
Okay, let's see what
kind of shape she's in.
Maybe she can tell us what happened.
I understand, but there are
armed men in my emergency room
getting in the way of patients who
need treatment. Now who's in charge?
I am.
Sergeant greg parker with the sru.
- Dr. Redfield.
- Hi, doctor.
We need to set up a command post.
Okay, you can do that in the admit office.
It's just through the E.R. I'll take U.
Thank you. How's trudy vargas doing?
We're stabilizing her. She's
going to or in a few minutes.
It would help us if we
could have word with her.
Don't get in the way,
don't stay too long.
That's her right there.
We tried to contain the panic, but...
but gunshots are loud, word gets around.
What if we evacuate the hospital?
400 patients? Ten in surgery as
we speak, another dozen in icu.
Now one of my best nurses
is out commission. No way.
What if we put the patients in a
secured area with lockable doors?
Sounds like a plan.
You'll need to close shop for a while.
Already rerouting calls to the mount,
but they're at capacity as it is.
I set up a triage area in the west
parking lot for more critical cases.
I know it's not ideal.
City hospital, sarge. It's never ideal.
- Through there to the right.
- Thank you, doctor.
All right, good luck. Excuse
me. I got to get back to my team.
Kinda reminds me of you.
- Really?
- A little bit.
Shane, man, five-o's all over
the place, man. We should bail.
- Give me your nine.
- My nine? But there's cops...
man, give it to him.
I know the kid saw what you did, but...
what I did? What I did?
You better believe anyone
finds out, we're all going down.
What, you think mattie's
gonna go to the cops?
The cops? I don't care anything
about the damn cops, all right?
Those...
we need to silence that
kid, you understand me?
We need to do it now
before he talks to anyone.
You think he talked to his brother?
Well, if he did, then, uh...
we gotta take care of him, too.
You got a better idea?
All right then.
- hector!
- Mattie, you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- All right. We gotta get outta here.
There's too many cops. We can'T.
Okay. Uh, upstairs.
5:17 P.M. Establishing command post.
Single shot fired, gunman
at large, but gone to ground.
We got a central building, four wings.
Ten floors, 16 stairwells.
North wing, most vulnerable
patients: Icu and maternity.
- Lewis, wordy, you guys cover icu.
- Copy.
Sam and I'll go take maternity,
work our way downwards.
Clear each floor till
we flush the subject out.
Leave a uniform sentry behind each secured area
after we've cleared it, okay, so it stays that way.
Spike, any visuals on our shooter?
Sorry, boss. Limited camera coverage.
He must have been in a blind spot.
Okay, that's not a lot
to go on here, gentlemen,
so let's make the priority anyone not
wearing a hospital gown or a unifo, ok?
- Let's get this guy while he's still quiet.
- Copy that.
There. That should hold for now, anyway.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know yet!
Mattie, what the hell is shane
and his boys after you for?
I'm tired of this! What did you do?
- Nothin'.
- Nothing?
Put these on. We gotta blend.
These are girls.
You worried about the clothes?
They're trying to kill you, and
you're worried about the clothes?
And they shot my friend who
was just trying to help us!
I know. I know. I'm sorry.
Look, mattie, you need
to start talking to me.
What's going on?
Shane wouldn't be coming at you like
this unless it was something serious.
I di't steal anything!
I didn't do anything.
You saw something, didn't you?
Did he pop somebody? Mattie?
- Yeah.
he said he's gonna kill me.
He's gonna kill me. He's gonna
kill me. He's gonna kill...
mattie, mattie, mattie, mattie, relax.
He's not gonna kill you.
Look, look, I'm not gonna
let that happen, okay?
Little brother, I'm not gonna
let that happen to you, okay?
- Okay.
- All right? Okay.
Excuse me.
- You can't be in here right now.
- I know. This is only gonna take a minute, though.
It's very important, okay?
Okay. Okay.
Hey, julianna.
Hey, trulianna. How you doing?
- You're back?
- Yeah. Wearing the cool pants this time.
Can you tell me what happened?
There was yelling. A-a fight.
Okay, did you see who was it was?
Derek. Is he okay?
- Who's derek?
- Medeiros.
He's a, he's a night
orderly. Is he okay?
- Tell me he's okay.
- You're gonna be okay.
Please.
- Did you get that?
- Yeah, copy.
- Boss, maternity's secure.
- Copy that.
Derek medeiros, he's has a record: B and e,
vandalism, all from a couple of years ago.
Anything violent?
Not that he was arrested for, but it says
here he was affiliated with the eastside crew.
If this guy's eastside, he probably
did a lot worse than he got busted for.
Gangbangers don't usually work
the night shift ospi a htal.
Sounds like he got out of the life.
If he did, he's one of the few.
Once you're in, they make it real
hard for you to get out in one piece.
Yeah, I hear you, lou, but we have to consider
him armed and dangerous until we know more.
If this is some kind of gang payback,
we got more than one party at play here.
Got a picture here of derek.
From the employee file.
Sending it out.
- We'll be moving her to surgery now.
- Okay.
Trudy, do you know if
this was a gang fight?
He brought his little brother matt in.
It was a gunshot.
He wanted me to keep it quiet. But...
he's been, he's been taking
care of matt since his mom died.
He's been, he's been
turning himself around.
- Is he in trouble?
- We're gonna do everything we can.
- Please, please, julianna. Keep him safe.
- All right.
sounds like maybe the little
brother is the gang conneioN.
Peter, anything on him?
No juvie file on a matt medeiros.
Looks like he's never been picked up.
Okay, team, let's
assume multiple subjects.
Peter, you focus on the brothers.
Let's find out if anyone
has a beef against them.
Okay, hold on a sec. Boss,
there's a call asking about trudy.
Nurse at the front desk says
it sounds like derek's voice.
Okay. Line two.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Is this derek?
Hey, derek, my name is
sergeant greg parker.
I'm with the police
strategic response unit.
- You wanted to know about trudy?
- Yeah.
Uh, how is she?
She's doing okay. They're
taking good care of her.
Did you see who shot her?
Okay, can you tell me this.
Was it the same person
who shot your brother?
Eah.
Okay, how many guys we
talking about, derek?
Three.
And is matt still with you?
- Yeah, he is.
- Who is that, the cops?
And you guys are still
inside the hospital?
- Yeah, we are.
- We can't go op the cS.
Great, derek, okay.
I know you're trying
to protect your brother,
but if someone's after him, you'll
both be safer with us, buddy.
You just think about this: Your
brother's injured, he needs treatment.
You tell me where you are, we'll get him out
of there safely, give him the help he needs.
You can come to us?
You, you promised.
You bet, buddy, right away.
North wing, fourth floor supply room.
That's it, I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead!
Mattie, what are you doing?
Okay, guys, north wing, fourth floor
supply room. Let's bring him in.
Copyalpha team on the move. Bravo?
Closing in.
Matt! Hey, where do
you think you're going?
I'm not going to the cops!
Listen, I got to get you to
a doctor and get you safe.
Come on.
Run. Run!
Don't stop! Don't stop!
Run! Keep running!
Gunshots reported in
geriatrics, third floor.
Jules?
Bravo moving.
on my way.
Shane, this is crazy!
Medeiros, man, you shouldn't
have got yourself involved.
This had nothing to do with you!
Listen, listen, you
don't have to do this!
You think I want this?
It ain't nothing personal, man,
it's just... it's him or me!
And it ain't gonna be
me, man, that's all!
Come on, shane, listen,
nobody has to die, man, okay?
Let's just chill! Let's talk about this!
All right, let's talk.
Go ahead. I'm listening.
No joy.
My brother, he didn't
see anything, okay?
He wasn't there. You've got my word.
Man, I want to believe you.
But when his boys start asking, how I
know mattie won't crack under the pressure?
When whose boys start asking?
T-T.J.'S.
T.J.? You saw shane pop
T.J.From the dragons?
Oh, mattie!
Talk and he knows he's a dead man!
Second floor! Let's go.
Eddie, what the hell was that?
- Police! Freeze!
- Come on, man, let's go!
Put the gun down! Stay where
you are! Put the gun down!
come on, man, let's go!
Sam, get the fire.
Wordy, lewis, take the door.
Right there, let's see some hands!
Let's see some hands.
- I got matt.
- What about derek?
Negative. He's still out there.
6:31 pm, fire from explosion contained.
Four armed subjects still at large.
One subject in custody.
- Subject's headed to ward six.
- On my way.
Freeze! Police! Get your
hands up! Get your hands up!
Get down! Hands against
the wall! Hands on the wall!
Lou.
I got it. I got it.
subject contained.
Gun's out. Your pants
sliding a little bit?
Let me get that for you.
yeah, don't mention it. Come on.
Lou, wordy, good job.
Sam, jules, two subjects west corridor.
- Wordy, east.
- On it.
- Get him down to the boss.
- Copy that.
- Wordy, I'll catch up.
- Copy, lou.
Boss, we're bringing down two subjects.
Eddie, stay with the kid. See if
you can get anything out of him.
I'm on it.
It's mattie, right? I'm ed.
Let's get you somewhere safe.
- getting any deja vu?
- Yeah. Mostly the smell.
Spring blossom meets
industrial disinfectant.
You in that hospital
gown and bunny slippers.
Panda slippers.
Couple hundred times around these
floors, you leaning on my arm.
Yeah. You did always like me
best when I needed you, huh?
Come on. Everyone needs to be needed.
Gives you something to shoot for.
- Ward five clear.
- Copy.
Very impressive, matt.
It's very impressive.
How many guys after you?
Three? You're what, 14?
You want to tell me why
they want to shoot you?
I spent a lot of time
on the street, matt.
They want to keep you quiet.
I get why you don't want
to talk to me. I get that.
It's just, I'm worried
about your brother.
Name's theo watts. Street name tug.
Works as muscle for a meth
dealer named shane thomas.
What crew they run with?
Oh, they're independent.
They're trying to make a name.
That's not good.
Okay, spike. Keep talking to the guns
and gangs guy. Get peter on it, too.
Any red flags they might
pull for today, today.
- Copy.
- Okay.
Mr. Watts. How you doing? Okay?
My officer said...before
he arrested you,
he said that you reached behind
you, the back of your pants.
Now, I can interpret that two ways.
One, you were hitching-- you
were hitching your pants up.
Or you were drawing the concealed
weapon you had back there.
Now, wearing big baggy pants,
that's not a serious offense,
but drawing a gun on one of
my officers, that really is.
I wasn't going to draw on anybody.
Tell me why you shot
a kid earlier today.
- Man, I didn't shoot no one.
- No? 'Cause somebody did.
And now here you are, running around
with a gun, shooting at that same kid.
You trying to finish the job?
- Shane shoot him?
- I don't know. Go ask him.
No, son, I'm asking you.
Robocops, man!
- Yo, what is that, aks they're carrying out there?
- Calm the hell down.
No, man! They can shoot through
walls with that stuff, man!
Yo, yo, I'm out of here, man.
Come on, remo, you know I
can't let you do that, man!
Look, I already shot three people today, so I'm
kind of running out of things to lose. You feel me?
So I need you to stop and think about what it is
you're really trying to say to me right now, bro.
You know I got yck, r baman. Always.
- What about t, man?
- What about him?
He still hasn't called,
man. What if he got busted?
Then he better know how to
keep his damn mouth shut.
All right. We need to split
up. Might find them faster.
No, man.
You see them, you holler at me.
Yo, shane, you got my piece, man.
It's nothing to do with him.
Derek didn't do anything.
So, it's just the two
of you guys, right?
Yeah.
Since our moms got killed.
I'm sorry to hear that, matt.
But you guys are doing okay, right?
I mean, your brother's got a job.
And he is trying to look out for you, but
right now, he's in danger of getting shot.
Matt, of getting shot. Okay?
And if you can just tell me
what happened, I can help.
It doesn't matter.
Me and my brother are dead.
If it's not today, it's tomorrow.
That's the way it is.
You cops can't do nothing about it.
Let's go.
Boss, got something from the guns
and gangs unit. Could be relevant.
Yeah. Go ahead, peter.
42 division found a bo about an
hour ago ided as one john chen.
Aka tj chen, riverside dragons.
Oh, yeah? I'm guessing
it wasn't natural causes.
That's right. Single
gunshot to the head.
Body was in an alley off queen and pape.
Okay. Copy that, eddie?
Officer. I need you to stay
here with this young man.
I need you to get a doctorooto
lk at him immediately.
Mattie, I'm going to be
back to get you, all right?
Tj chen's head of the dragons.
They run the meth trade,
broadview to woodbine.
So, if shane and his crew were trying to do
business down there, they'd have some friction.
Yeah, but taking out tj's
asking for serious payback.
The dragons find out it's shane,
he won't live to see the weekend.
Unless there weren't any witnesses.
Or the witnesses disappeared.
And we're sure this relates to tj?
I don't know. Let's find out.
Okay.
Mr. Watts. A couple more questions.
Whatever, man. I ain't talking.
Right. I get it. Okay.
I thought you might know something
about a body they found today-- tj chen.
I don't know nothing about
that. So, I can't speak on it.
Okay, so you don't mind
if we double-check that?
Spike, let's get a picture of mr.
Watts here down to guns and gangs.
Have them pass it around, see if anybody
recognizes him from the neighborhood.
Copy that.
Should probably run it by the
dragons, too, just to make sure.
- Copy.
- Hey, hold up.
Man, I wasn't there. I swear.
I found out after it all went down.
Okay. It was shane.
And the kid saw him do it.
Get him out of here.
Look, it was that kid's own fault, man.
He wasn't supposed to be
there in the first place.
Let's go talk to the kid, ed.
Sarge, somebody raided a supply
closet, lost a lot of blood.
It's got to be our subject.
Hey, guys. We found derek's locker.
Uh, looks like he was taking
his medical career seriously.
He's making plans.
Got a life ahead of him.
At least, this morning, he did.
Can I have just a second?
Thank you. Hey, matt.
I'm sergeant parker.
You remember ed lane.
Matt, does your brother know
that you saw shane shoot tj?
- It's all right.
- Matt, it's important.
And does your brother know
that you saw tj get shot?
Yeah.
Okay. Okay, good man.
We're going to leave this
officer here to look out for you.
No, you got to let me...
got to find my brother.
Listen to me. Matt, we're
going to find him, all right?
We're going to make sure he
gets safe. That's our job.
- Sergeant parker.
- Hey, doctor. You got time to take care of our friend here?
- Absolutely.
- Thank you.
I need the cuffs off to treat him.
Hey, matt, how you feeling?
so, matt saw too much.
Now he's the only thing
linking shane to a murder.
He's got to get to him before
it gets back to the dragons.
So derek's going after
shane to save his brother?
Yeah, his only family. Wouldn't you?
Derek? Greg parker again.
Where's my brother?
He's safe. Doctor's taking care of him.
And I want to keep you safe, too.
We can protect you from shane.
Even if you find him, he'll
be back on the street tomorrow.
No. We're not going to let that happen.
Listen, the system is broken.
Only one way I can make
sure my brother is safe.
Do this, you'll throw away
everything you've done.
I'm sorry. I got to do this.
he's left the life.
But he still won't trust cops.
Matt said their mom got
killed. It's personal.
Spike, let's find out
what happened to their mom.
- Copy.
- We step this up, guys. Okay?
Derek's a good kid. He's worked
hard to get where he's at.
We got to stop him before he crosses
a line we can't pull him back from.
It's over.
N't keep the hospital contained, doctor,
we lose the integrity of the sweep.
All I'm saying is other
ers are at capacity.
They're overwhelmed out there in triage.
We need the building back as soon as
possible or people are going to die.
Okay, doctor.
Guys, I got info on the
boys' mom. Serena medeiros.
Fatally wounded in a
shooting three years ago.
Place called pete's top slice.
- Pete's?
- No wonder he doesn't trust us.
What happened?
One night, a gangbanger named johns walked
into pete's looking for a guy who snitched on M.
He sprayed the whole place.
Six dead including a little girl.
And serena medeiros.
He shouldn't even been on the street.
After the guy snitched on him,
cops busted him. Didn't stick.
24 hours later, he's back on the street.
- North wing's contained. Keep it locked down.
- Yes, sir.
- Police!Don't move!
- Don't move!
Stay where you are!
- Have you been shot?
- No.
Derek do this to you?
- Where'd he go?
- How do I know?
So he just tied you
up and left you here?
Nk acould've capped
me. Just took my phone.
Boss, we've contained another
subject. His name is remo benzina.
Derek's still on the
run. He's got reme.S phon
********
- what's up?
- Remo's text message. Check it out.
The message was sent at 6:42 P.M., And
jules and sam found him at 6:39 P.M.
- He'd already had his phone taken by derek.
- Yeah, yeah.
West basement? Boiler roo west stairs.
I told you what I had to do.
Derek, we know where you are
and we're coming there now.
No, no, no, stay, stay away.
Bravo, alpha team, boiler room.
West-most stairs.
Derek, I know what happened to your mom.
Then you know why I don't trust cops.
I'm not talking to you as a cop.
I'm not talking to you as a
man who wants you to succeed.
And you made a choice
to be somebody different.
Don't quit. Don't quit on that choice.
Don't quit on the guy that you set
out to be, who matt needs you to be,
and who your mom would
have been so proud of.
You gotta trust yourself, derek.
You don't want to do this.
No, I don't, but I have to.
Remo.
you ought to know better.
Get down! Get down!
Stay down! Stay down!
Stay down on the ground!
Esm, jul, keep him contained!
Eddie, take that catwalk.
Who's got a 20?
No joy.
Police! Don't move! Don't move!
Police! Freeze!
- Stay down!
- Let's see some hands!
- Hands behind your back!
- Stay down!
Let's see some hands!
Okay. Nice work.
Sam, let's get some medical
personnel down here right away.
Hey, derek.
Mattie, where's mattie?
I need to talk to him.
He's doing okay.
Multiple shots fired, west
boiler room. Sru on scene.
I need help!
officer, I need a hand. Come
over here. I gotta get an iv in.
Here, hold him. Pressure. Don't let go.
You did the right thing.
You took care of your brother
the best way you could.
I just need to talk to him,
let him know I'm all right.
You will. You just stay put. We're
gonna have you taken care of first.
Hey, eddie, let's keep our
friend here inside a cruiser.
- I'm gonna stay here with derek.
- Copy that.
Good man.
Whoa, matt. What are
you doing with that gun?
You shot my brother.
Matt, your brother's gonna be okay.
No, I heard about the
gunshot. You're lying.
No, he's getting fixed up.
I wouldn't lie to you about that.
No, I gotta finish this now.
Matt, this isn't the way to do it.
Yeah, well, you guys ain't gonna do it.
He's going to jail.
Yeah, yeah, like the guy
killed my mom went to jail?
- I hear you, matt.
- You don'T.
You don't know nothin' about that.
You're right, I don'T.
But I do know how it feels when
I see these guys out on the street
who have no right to
be and it makes me mad.
It makes me feel like thing's not safe.
Okay, then! So then you
know why I gotta do it!
I do.I do, but matt, listen,
infive mgoutes a, your brother derek
had the same choice to make, matt,
and he put the gun down. He put it down.
And I know that he would want
you to make the same choice.
You guys made it this far
because you stuck together, matt.
You stuck together. You
looked out for each other.
Now, derek's been there for you, matt.
He's been there for you. Now
you gotta be there for him.
matt, it's okay, matt.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
we're gonna get through this, matt.
I'm not gonna let you down.
T I'm nogonna punch outat
the end of this shift.
You have nothing to be sorry about.
JJ Grey &
Mofro "Sun Is Shining Down"
okay, no way, no way.
I'm tired. I'm going home.
I'm not doing the greg parker
review from hell. Simple as that.
- What the...
- What about the review?
You guys want a review?
How's this?
Officers callaghan, braddock performed
admirably in securing assigned areas
and gathering key intel without
any public displays of affection.
Officer scarlatti's skill in
computers and other geeky toys
was augmented today by a
truly spectacular takedown...
Of a dangerous subject.
Officer young provided crucial backup and insight
into the psychology of yet another subject.
And officer wordsworth, well,
he's just plain and
simple the toughest sob
I have ever had the
privilege to command.
Thank you.
And that leaves uswith officer
ed lane, who, truth be told,
has always been a bit of
a problem for team one...
let's have it.
'Cause when everybody's
struggling, he's pushing through.
When everyone's lost, he finds our way.
And when we falter, he picks us up.
The problem is is after he's done
all that, who picks him up, right?
You saved that kid today, eddie.
At one time or another, you've
saved every person in this room.
Yep.
So, today is ed lane's fifth
anniversary as team leader.
All right!
- cheers to that.
- Cheers.
Five more years.
Yeah, finally shut him up.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season02 Episode13