35 foot cabin cruiser currently
docked in slip number 127.
Sam, we don't have eyes yet. You?
Almost there.
He's gotta be in the
cockpit or down below.
Guys, I got 'em.
Where are they, middle, stern or bow?
Standing in the back,
they're under a tarp.
- Say it!
- Go to hell.
She's on him. Ed,
she's right in his face.
Rebecca kessfield, this is the
police strategic response unit.
Get back!
- Rebecca, please.
- Go!
- Relax!
- Go inside!
4 hours earlier
just let me in, okay?
come on, I know you're there.
Honey, please, just let me in.
sadie?
sadie? Honey? It's just me. Okay?
It's just me.
Sweetheart?
I told you not to come.
What are big sisters for?
come on, let's get you up.
There's nothing glamorous about
the bathroom floor. Come here.
Here. Hang on, hang on.
sadie.
you must release me...
for if you do not, I
cannot be held accountable.
My lord, you have shattered my heart.
You have... awoken my soul.
Yo, dude, you've awoken my soul!
Wordy, this is the sru; you can't
be watching "lady in waiting".
It's a good movie, it's historical.
I got four women in my house, all right?
Anything that helps me get closer
to shelly and my girls, I'm there.
If this is what they're
watching, I wanna know about it.
Got no secrets.
I think you need to shoot something.
Well, after you, siskel.
You're the one that
recognized the quote.
- Oh, yeah.
- Ohhh, snap!
Hey, you know what, it's on friggin'
pay-per-view, every hour on the hour, all right?
Well, maybe you and I should sit down, watch
it together, compare our favourite scenes...
I can braid your hair.
That's tricky business.
Naw, not really.
I do it for allie all the time.
She's got less hair
than either of these two.
It's okay, bring it. Come on.
Sadie, you know what
I'm going to say, right?
Yeah, I don't want to hear
it. Just not right now.
Okay, I'm gonna go check on caitlin.
- She was in her crib the whole time?
- yeah.
- You want her in here?
- Yeah.
you really sit around and watch those
sappy movies with your kids, or what?
Yeah.
Well, I got girls.
It's different, right, you got a boy.
No, I know, I know.
You know, he's a good kid. Great
kid. It's just it's awkward.
You know, I love rock
music; he plays the cello.
Loves basketball, hates hockey.
Last week, he came home...
big fat lip, won't tell
me what happened, right?
Turns out this...
this kid at school, they had a
hassle and he told the teacher.
Kid waited for him after school and...
what're you gonna do?
Well, what are you gonna do?
I dunno. You know, soph wants to...
"we'll go to the school
and we'll take to him."
So go to the school about
it, find out what's going on.
Nah. I mean, it'll just make it worse.
Clark needs to stand up on his own...
his own two feet.
He's
13-years-old.
Exactly.
Well no wonder he doesn't
wanna talk to you about it.
You know what, wordy, you
got three girls, okay? So...
oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Three girls, a real walk in the
park, they never do anything wrong.
You know what? You know what?
Whatever, okay? Forget it.
oh, yeah, that'S... that's mature.
it's okay. you're okay now. Hang on.
enough fighting, sadie.
what the hell happened?
Uh, he didn't touch her.
So why does this have blood on it?
It was me; I felt sick,
so I picked her up.
Do you hear yourself? Do you?
- Do not judge me.
- This cannot continue!
Well, tell me how it ends then? Tell me.
We both know how it ends.
I call the cops, they show up,
he's got a fat lip
because I fought back,
he tells them I'm crazy,
and they turn out to be
buddies from 58 division.
So you leave!
Where is he, sadie?
Please. You can'T.
If he finds out that you know about this,
any of this, he's gonna kill me, or you, or...
oh, just... just leave!
I don't know.
I just don't know anymore.
this is going to end.
I get it.
You can't do it.
I just need to sleep.
Okay, everything's
fine, just go to sleep.
I'll give caitlin a bottle.
Rebecca?
I'm sorry.
So am I.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Flashpoint
Season01 Episode04
we got no calls yet, but tonight
there's gonna be a full moon, so...
so?
So, full moons, they make people
crazy, it's a proven fact, so...
I'm gonna call tonight patrol night.
- All right.
- Yes!
All right, do a little team one
pr, let the city know we're here,
keep the bad guys on
their toes.Yeah, spike.
- Club district?
- Me and lew?
What, there's all kinds of
troubles there, all the time.
Fine. Patrol happy hour.
All those very threatening
young women in tube-tops.
But just uh... button up, huh?
Be good. Look good. Jules? You're
still representing the force.
Eddie? Mr. Wordsworth?
East end.
Roving gangs of families,
runaway strollers and whatnot.
It's all yours. Sam? Jules?
We'll take west.
I'm thinking chicken
roti at island foods.
Hey, we'll take west.
- You got
tube-tops. - Yeah.
Let's go keep the peace.
All right, it's petey time.
school's in, franky. Triple twenty.
- Vodka soda?
- You got it.
Ah, triple one!
that's on the board.
That's on the board.
Hold up a sec.
What? Where's he goin'?
What're you doing here?
Long day. Having a drink.
Thanks.
- Uh, rebecca, I don'T...
- relax.
Don't worry, I'm in a good mood.
Nice day, sun's shining.
Spent the day planting trees.
Well, un-planting trees, actually.
This uh, this blue-hair in forest hill's trying
to tell me she didn't mean to order purple lilac;
she wanted white lilac.
Now I've got $3000 bucks worth of purple trees
sitting in my truck, but hey, she's paying.
I guess.
So... you talk to sadie lately?
We're not really, no, I
mean, not in a few weeks.
Everything okay?
Yeah, sure, everything's
great, you know.
I'm kinda keeping my distance these
days. She'S... got a lot on her plate.
You could say that.
then I will.
Sit down, have a drink.
I mean, if you want.
hi, matt? It's sadie.
I need your help.
Wordy, at least let's take
parliament street, all right?
Somebody's gotta be beatin'
someone up over there.
well, can you go any slower?
Look, do you wanna just stop?
Let's just stop, I'm cool with
that. We'll just stop the car.
what is your problem?
I don't have a problem.
It's my opinion. All right?
Your kid gets into some trouble, you...
go into the school, you figure it out.
What? That's how I feel.
Shelley teach you that?
Just go, go braid some hair, express
your emotions, all right, wordy, whatever.
No, you know what shelley taught me?
No, wordy, what'd your wife teach ya?
Don't be a victim, don't be a perpetrator,
and above all, don't be a bystander.
- Vote for ed.
- You're an ass.
Eddie. Matt mcdondrick, here.
Matty! What's going on, buddy?
Well, my partner in narcotics, pete fitzhaven,
his wife just called, her name's sadie.
I'm stuck in court on a heroin case,
she needs a little help on the qt.
I don't know who else to ask.
What do you need?
I don't know yet.
There's um...
there's a little bit
of trouble over there.
Pete's gun's missing,
she can't track him down.
All right, where is she?
You sure you're okay to stop by?
You know, I figure if there's a firearm
involved, you guys might get called anyway.
Better if it's you, right?
Yeah, yeah. We're just on
patrol, it's no problem.
Gimme her twenty,
we'll be there in five.
See?
It's nice to turn your
phone off once in a while.
It's old school.
No one can find you, no
one knows where you are.
Hey, how'd it go with the review board?
You get bumped up?
I did.
No way. Congratulations, sergeant.
Hey, mickey, we need another round here.
You got it.
You, uh... you still
playing with that thing?
'Cause it kind of looks like
your boys wanna finish their game.
I don't know. It's up to you, I guess.
Pete, it's nice to see you.
It's good to catch up, you know?
All right, I'll be
back. Finish that drink.
just soda from now on, okay, mickey?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I don't want to make him feel bad,
but it's a little early for me.
Check out the window.
Sadie fitzhaven?
Hey, I'm ed. This is kevin. We, uh...
we got a call from matt mcdondrick.
Oh god.
he said he'd send a friend,
he didn't need to call the sru.
No, it's all right, we're friends.
We're uh, we're just on
patrol, it's nothing official.
Do you mind if I just...
- not at all.
- Fine.
Do you want to tell us what's going on?
My sister came by.
She was upset, she was very emotional.
Your sister. And you didn't let her in?
Well, I was upstairs,
I was with the baby.
I was nursing, so I didn't get the door.
I guess she just figured I was here.
So what'd she want?
- To talk to pete.
- Talk to pete?
Did you tell her where he was?
Oh, I didn't have to.
Chances are if pete's not
here then he's at the lion.
Look, I was upstairs, you
know, in the baby's room,
and she was storming around
for a while and then she left.
With your husband's gun.
And you're sure he
didn't have it with him?
No, I saw him put it in the closet.
He's very particular
- one place; that's where it goes.
Look, I'm sure that everything's fine.
You know, and I wish that
matt hadn't called you.
You know, I just wanted
to make sure that...
No way.
I agree.
Pete's voicemail.
She's leaving stuff out. She's
leaving all the good stuff out.
Maybe she doesn't know any good stuff.
- Matty, it's ed.
- You talk to her?
- We did.
- And?
I don't know. There's
something going on. There's A...
there's a broken door,
there's a missing gun.
Who broke the door?
Her sister, rebecca kessfield.
That ring any bells?
You sure it was rebecca?
What's the story, matt?
Off the record, she's
been stalking the guy.
She's been obsessed
about him for months.
She's out of her sweet mind.
Pete's told me crazy stuff,
stuff he hasn't even told sadie.
I'm out.
What? Where are ya going?
You're bailing on our game.
Ah, guys, I'm calling it a day.
Got a baby at home.
told ya I wasn't leaving.
Just didn't want anybody talking.
Pete, why don't I just drive
you home. It's been a long day.
I'm fine.
Come on, you've had a few.
Hey, if you wanna walk home,
that's cool, but I'm good to go.
Okay, I guess I'll walk.
You know, it was uh,
it was good to see you.
Where's your car?
I didn't drive.
You want a lift?
- Sure.
- I don't mind at all.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
you're such a lightweight.
- oh yeah?
- Yeah.
I could, uh... I could do
another drink, you know.
I'm not scared.
what about the patio at o'malley's?
It's a beautiful sunset.
Well, we could, uh...
we could go to your boat.
guys, this may be nothing, but we have a
potential incident involving a police officer
and a missing firearm at the lion bar.
Copy that. I've got nothing
goin' on, I'll meet you there.
South street and beacon.
- Bravo, charlie?
- Copy.
You guys stay put, we'll
call you if we need you.
This way.
it's just up here on the left.
Careful, don't fall in.
I did that once. In venice.
Came out of this restaurant,
a couple glasses of wine,
thought it was the reflection of the street
or something, I stepped right in and...
bam, I'm in the canal.
You know, there's no...
no fences or anything.
Aw, man, you are lucky. I wish
I had a chance to, you know...
to what?
Travel! See the world! Get drunk.
Help pretty ladies out
of the water. Well...
here we are.
uh, yeah, they were talking at
the bar, but, uh, she said goodbye,
left without him,
everything seemed fine to me.
She really wasn't even drinking.
She had one drink and then
after that it was soda water.
Hey, eddie.
Rebecca kessfield's clean.
No priors, no tickets, no nothing.
- What about the wife?
- Haven't checked yet.
- Eddie, any news?
- Nothing.
Guys, this woman's out of her mind.
Yeah, but so's his wife.
The whole family, I mean, I
feel bad for the guy, I do.
Ed. Three weeks ago...
pete said rebecca
showed up at the office.
You know, sat outside in her car for
an hour waiting for him to come out.
Apparently, he didn't return her call.
Matty, they having a thing here or what?
I don't know. Not my place. Sorry.
Maybe.
The wife's sister? Boss.
Hold on a second.
I don't know for sure, okay,
but there was something there.
I guess I figured maybe they had had a
thing, he ended it - obvious reasons -
she was pissed off, confused, I
don't know. Don't ask, don't tell.
Got a little domestic
situation on our hands?
And he's hammered.
She's got a gun.
I hear you.
Hey, frank, where's he going?
Uh, I don't know, he
said he's going home.
Well, he's not at home. Anyone?
He's got a boat.
Let's start with the boat.
team one, let's gear up.
Thanks.
You could've.
Coulda what?
Gone to italy. You know, this, uh...
this boat alone would've bought you a couple
of trips, there and back, you and sadie.
Nah, I need this.
It's good to have a place
to go, you know? Get away.
There we are.
Sit down, relax.
Sunset, right?
Don't want to miss it.
Let me just uh...
- pull this back so we get a better view.
- No, uh...
it's kinda nice.
It's cozy, you know?
Security guard said that he pulled in
in a blue pickup with a blonde passenger.
It's gotta be them.
Let's check with matt, see if
he knows which slip he's in.
So, are you seeing anyone?
Not right now.
All the good ones are taken, right?
Anyway, I'm not really sure I'm
cut out for the marriage thing.
Ksloo pretty hard.
Oh, come on.
No sex, no fun, no sleep, no slack...
what's not to like?
So why do you stay?
I don't know.
Looking for somethin' better to
come along, I guess. You know?
Matty, are you sure about this?
I was here two weeks ago,
he's moored in 127. That's it.
Okay, well, parallel to the end
of the dock, that's not good.
- No, it's harder to contain.
- Contain?
Well, that's what we're starting with.
We want all our options,
and that's the only way out?
Yeah, on foot.
Sergeant, just walk your
guys down to the boat.
No. We don't wanna spook
the girl with the gun, right?
If they don't see us,
we control what happens.
Sam, we need to find a high point,
parallel and east of this guy right here.
So, let me know when
you got eyes on him.
Yes, sir.
All right, the rest of us, we're gonna go
stealth 'til I hear something different.
Jules, get matty into the command truck.
I want priors on the wife.
I want priors on the husband.
Priors on the husband?
Sergeant, this way.
Wordy. We need to get
sadie fitzhaven down here.
What, the wife? Why?
Because she was lying.
- Okay, I...
- won't let her past the truck.
All right, good. 'Cause I don't
want her anywhere near this thing.
Copy that.
Lewis! Spike! Let's hit it.
We used to be good.
Things were good for
the first couple years.
It's, it's complicated.
Used to be us against the world.
then she had caitlin and...
the day she was born, sadie's
all grumpy, she's on the edge.
That baby doesn't stop crying.
You know, she's
five-months-old.
Sir!
Let's go, let's go. Let's hustle it up.
7:57 pm, team one on the scene of a
possible domestic, marina quay west.
35 foot cabin cruiser, registered
under one peter fitzhaven,
currently docked in slip number 127.
My job takes it out of me, I haven't
had sex with my wife in six months.
I'm sitting next to a girl and uh...
well, I chose the wrong one.
They're either in the cockpit
or they're in the cabin.
Lewis, see if you can
get eyes from down here.
Sarge, what if nothing's happening?
What if he's in there all alone?
I hope so.
False alarm's my
favourite kind of alarm.
Spike, see if this guy'll
let you use his shortwave.
Maybe we can contact him through that.
Yeah, it'll work if pete's radio's on.
Okay, I'll check it out.
Lewis?
There's plastic all around the
front, I can't see anything.
If I got near the actual dock, maybe.
No, back off. I don't
want her spottin' you.
- Hello there.
- Hello.
I need to use your radio.
So leave... yifou're unhappy.
- Maybe I will.
- Maybe you should.
Hey, don't tell me what to do.
I'm not, I'm just...
pete, it's not a secret, you know?
You married my little sister
at this very marina, what?
Three years ago?
- When's the first time you hit her?
- Excuse me?
I'm guessing about five months later, I'm
thinking maybe it was that first halloween?
She got dressed up for a party
- sexy nurse.
- I remember you didn't like it much.
- You know what? You...
took me a little while to
figure it out, but I did.
- She doesn't have the energy to lie to me anymore.
- No?
Because she's pretty good at it.
nothing. Thanks.
We had a few fights, we had a kid,
she got fat, we had a few more fights!
- She's my wife!
- She's your prisoner!
don't you laugh! Don't you dare laugh!
I think it's time that you left.
Sam, we don't have eyes yet. You?
Almost there.
You know what? How come
you haven't left yet?
Guys, I got 'em.
Where are they, middle, stern or bow?
Standing in the back,
they're under a tarp.
It's not like she's asking
for the moon. You know?
It's not like she's asking for flowers,
or diamonds, or trips to italy...
she's just asking you to be nice.
Thing is, you can't do it!
You can't do it, pete, 'cause
it's not in your nature.
You're gonna leave, tonight.
Okay, you're gonna go to a friend's
place, she's gonna get a lawyer,
- and you're never gonna see her again.
- Rebecca.
Say thatyou'll do it.
Just say that you'll do it!
- Give me my gun back.
- Say it!
- Go to hell.
- Say it again.
She's got a gun. She's
got it pointed at his head.
Either way this is gonna be over.
Today, it's gonna be
over, it's gonna be done.
She's moving in, she's on him.
Ed, shright in his face.
Rebecca kessfield, this is the
police strategic response unit.
We have got everything
under control out here.
How's everything over there?
Get back!
Rebecca, my name is greg,
and I wanna help you.
Undo that rope.
Pete, undo the rope!
We're concerned about your safety, so,
if you could tell me what this
is all about, we can all go home.
- Do you got a cellphone?
- Do it!
Maybe you can turn it on and
we can start talkog abinut this.
That's pete.
He's cuttin' the boat loose.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Get back. Get back, pete.
Go inside.
- Go inside!
- Rebecca, please.
- Go!
- Relax!
Looks like they're going inside.
Okay, easy.
We can't help you this way.
You have to stay calm, you have stay
there and you have to talk to us.
They're inside the cabin.
Inside the cabin? Buddy,
they're floating away.
Maybe it's good, you know.
Maybe they'll finally...
maybe they'll finally listen.
Except you probably... you
probably set me up, right?
Your guys probably think I'm crazy, huh?
Sergeant, we do not need you out there.
Now I need you tell us everything
you can about pete fitzhaven.
If we can't figure out why we're
here, we can't start talking.
Good. Go lethal. Please, I
told you everything already.
- Jules, can you take over?
- Yeah. In the truck.
The wife's here.
Luria's stuck in a parole hearing,
she's gonna keep us posted.
Sadie, hi.
I'm kevin wordsworth,
we met at your place.
I'm sorry, I had to drop
caitlin off at the neighbour'S.
What's happened?
Well, nothing's happened.
We're just trying to make contact
with rebecca, with your husband.
We're working on it, okay?
But, sadie, right now,
I really need your help.
We need to understand
what's going on here.
If you want us to get your husband
home to you, safe and sound tonight,
you need to tell me what rebecca wants.
You good to keep talking?
If I can get her on the phone. There's
only so much I can do with this thing.
All right, well they can still hear you.
Okay, until we get a better plan.
Gimme lewis as my second?
Fine, I'll take sam.
Lewis, you copy that?
- Copy.
- All right, spike, I need ears on that boat.
Get the parabolic mic.
Sam, I need a canister of non-pyrotechnic cs
ready to fire, and you might be going for a swim.
Boss, I need you to talk this thing down,
so we don't have to go on a boat ride.
- You got both cell numbers?
- Yup.
All right, start dialing.
Rebecca, this is sergeant greg
parker we're not going anywhere.
We can't go anywhere until
we resolve this thing.
I'm sorry, okay? I'M...
Rebecca, can you hear me?
I'm so sorry. Just...
- Hey, hey, what're you doing?
- Easy, easy!
- What're you doing?
- I will leave the house.
- Okay, I will get counselling.
- Liar!
I'm not lying!
I will never see her again if
that's what she wants, okay?
- Rebecca, can you hear me?
- Bec...
it's me, it's not her.
You remind me of this girl.
A girl from my neighborhood, growing up.
She was smart, she was
funny, she was... beautiful.
And then she got
married - real young -
to this guy who beat
the crap out of her.
Both phones are off.
All right, keep dialing.
Hey, jules, jules...
get luria, find out what
this guy means to her.
Maybe she has a past psych
history, anything you got.
I'm on it.
The thing about shelley was, well,
she's such A... a tough cookie.
But it took us...
I don't know, two years...
to figure it out. Two years...
before I realized why she
wore turtlenecks in the summer;
before I figured out why
she's always looking so scared.
Two years before I could help
her get out of that marriage;
before anyone could help her get away.
And you know what?
If I'd been given half a
chance, I would've killed him.
Ike, what do ya hear?
Nothing. Water. Very loud water.
Ed, what do you wanna do?
I wanna go in there. I wanna get ears
on that boat, or I wanna gas them.
Sam?
Six rounds of cs, ready to roll.
Rebecca, we can't keep doing this.
We need to make contact with you.
We're trying to call you right
now, please turn on your cell phone.
my, um...
my, my phone, it's in my bag, it'S...
it's on the deck.
Let me go get it for you, okay?
No, no-no-no,
where's your phone?
Where's your phone?
It's right here, it's in my pocket.
Okay, turn it on. Turn it on.
It's right here.
it's on.
Put it on the floor.
Kick it forward. Kick it over!
Okay.
drop it, or I'll break your wrist.
I said...
jules, what do ya got?
Luria sent me rebecca's chart,
but there's nothing there.
No meds, no shrink, no history.
What about her sister?
Not yet, but wordy's with her right now.
Sadie, we're preparing a
lethal solution for your sister.
If you can think of anything
that might help us, anything...
I told her to leave me alone.
I didn't want her in the middle of this.
she hates me for not leaving him.
it is not your fault, it's his fault.
Take care of her. It's his fault!
Look, just... just
don't hurt her please!
self-defense.
It's a cop's best friend.
Dude, can't swim in your gear.
Sam, I know it's a little unorthodox;
no time for a wet suit. You good to go?
Ready, freddy.
That side of the boat,
hatch-side of the cabin.
This isn't a rookie thing, is it?
No sir.
so much for patrol night.
Swimmer in the water.
In a few minutes we're gonna have ears.
He's not exactly a fish.
Rebecca?
- please! Please!
- Pete?
Stop, I'm begging you.
Just tell me what I can do?
Hey, it's greg parker, I'm glad you...
rebecca? Pete?
- spike, get me a zodiac.
- All right.
Sarge? He's beating sadie up.
Sister feels responsible;
she introduced them.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Sergeant,do not leave.
Today, sadie got defensive, it all went south,
and I guess rebecca decided enough is enough.
Wordy, you sure?
Wait till you see her neck.
That's from today's
good times, apparently.
What're we hearing?
Nothing yet.
I thought we were getting ears?
Guys, we are running out of light.
mic is in place.
got it.
Now this is gonna work out pretty
well, 'cause my ass is covered.
I've already told anyone that's listening
that you're a crazy, psycho bitch.
I'm going to kill you
right here, right now.
guys, it's not her, it's him.
And when you stop breathing...
you're gonna know that it's your fault.
pete, you're a police officer,
you know where this is going.
The phone is ringing, you need to
pick it up before it goes to voicemail.
Guy, I'm comin' to ya.
It's okay, wordy, we're gettin' her out.
Rebecca, if you won't talk
to us, we're coming in.
yeah, I got it. I hear you.
Pete, what's going on in there?
It's okay, I got the gun back.
I got her contained.
What do you mean, you've
got her contained, pete?
She's unconscious.
If he's telling the truth and she's
out cold, we can't use the gas.
All right, fine... , buy me 90 seconds.
Lewis, spike, let's go.
- Pete, how's she doing?
- You heard her right?
You saw her...
you saw her trying to kill me, right?
Yeah, that's right, we saw that.
Hey, pete, how's she
doing, is she breathing?
I dunno.
Well, just turn e thboat around and
come on back, buddy. It's all good.
I can'T. I can'T. I don't
know what happened, I just...
that's okay, buddy. That's
okay. okay, we're good.
Your wife's here, she's telling
us everything that happened.
Sadie? She is?
She's telling us. She's telling us that
rebecca broke into your house today.
She's confirmed it.
you listen to me, okay? It's done.
The woman's out of
control. We all get that.
Your partner's already said it.
She took your gun, she came after you.
now, you're a good cop.
So let's not let this situation
get in the way of that.
Okay, whatever you had to do, you
did in self-defense, I get that.
Please, buddy, let's just...
let's just stop this from getting
out of control. Come on back.
Okay, we bring her in, we slap a restraining
order on her until she goes to jail,
no questions asked. You
hear me? Are you listening?
better for you all the way
around if she makes it, pal.
Pete? Pete, talk to me.
Put the gun down! Put
the gun down! Down!
Interlock your fingers behind your head!
Thank god you guys are here.
Down on the ground! Down
on the ground! Come on!
what the hell are you doing?
Cuff him!
She's the one, right?
You saw her, right? you got her?
I mean, we got her, right?
We got her. We get her good?
All right, you're gonna be okay. You're
gonna be oka Y. You're gonna be okay.
I'm sorry I have to do this.
All right, you're okay.
You're gonna be all right, rebecca.
Okay, okay, the facades over,
you can take these off now.
- Where is she?
- Sadie?
Keep her away.
Don't worry about this, it's just...
it's a part of the procedure.
How's caitlin? Where's caitlin, honey?
Don'T.
Go. Go.
Okay, how far are we taking this?
I mean, come on
- that was good.
- Now, how about you take these cuffs off?
- Pete.
- How 'bout we take the cuffs off now?
What?
Have a listen.
We got her, all right? This is good.
you know, this is gonna work out
pretty well 'cause my ass is covered.
I am going to kill you
right here and right now.
and when you stop breathing, you're
gonna know that it's your fault.
Matty? Come on. Please, matty.
We clean up after each
other, that's what we do.
Guess I didn't really know what
I was cleaning up after, did I?
say it!
Say it, bitch.
You lying piece of garbage.
- I want my lawyer.
- You're gonna need one.
Rebecca.
rebecca.
I'm so sorry.
Please, please, don't be sorry.
It's me, it's my fault.
I think it's broken.
We're going straight
to the hospital, right?
She needs a doctor.
I'm sorry, I...
this wasn't what I...
I just wanted him to stop, you know?
I know. It's okay.
- get him outta here, wordy.
- Come on, let's go.
Watch your head.
9:33 pm, incident
contained. Two arrests.
One heading to hospital.
* When I'm awake *
* and when no one else can see...*
* how I feel *
* when the night comes meddling *
* I was movin' along...*
- so, I heard you're a really good swimmer.
- yeah.
No, I did. Were you on the swim team?
yeah, I admit, I'm not the...
I'm not the biggest fan of water.
- No?
- No.
I was raised in the desert.
Hey, buddy. Listen, tell your
mom I'm on my way home, okay?
Wanna play some driveway games?
* I was movin' along *
* you can rely on me *
* we were only...*
hey, shelley.
* Loving you alone *