Where is he?
What do you want
from joel graves, stan?
I want him in here.
You know what i think
you really want?
What you really want,
You know he can't give it
to you.
You got ten seconds.
This isn't the way, stan.
It's not the way.
Your friends know that.
Your friends know
when it's time to stop.
You get him in here
Or this ends right now.
Just don't do it, stan.
Just don't do it.
No!
Okay, explain this to me.
Flowers in a hospital.
Wow, thanks so much,
they're so pretty.
Now you get to leave
and i get to sit here
And watch them die.
It's a gesture.
It's the thought.
Mm.
Short term thought.
That's why i got you
the plant;
I'm thinking long term.
How long you thinkin'?
As long as it takes,
i'll be here.
Well, i don't plan on staying
here for very long.
Good.
That's good,
we're missing you bad.
Oh, yeah? How bad?
Really bad.
Yeah?
Not so bad that the team's
not looking for somebody
To fill my spot.
Final round of recruiting
is today.
Anybody good?
They're down to six.
From?
From three hundred, so...
yeah, they're good.
308 round projectile travelling
at 2750 feet per second,
Projectile weighs
168 grains...
Eyes on the target.
Target sierra
at 100 yards.
Use standard atmospheric
conditions at sea level.
What's the drop
at 200 yards?
Drop at 200 yards?
3.8 inches.
Double the weight
of the projectile.
What's the drop?
3.8. Inches.
The drop is constant.
Donna sabine.
You looking for a change
of scenery of what?
Change of wardrobe.
Trying to get in
the cool pants
A long time.
Nice to meet you, donna.
Nice to meet you, sir.
I'm not spying.
Yet, he's taking
digital pictures
With a zoom lense.
Personally,
if i've got a gun to my neck,
Your promise comes
from your heart, right?
Right.
So you see where i'm going
with this?
You gotta put the gun down
So he can think straight.
Right down.
Nice.
I'm telling you,
You can't just walk in herelike this.
-You're trespassing.
Look... i'm working,
i'm working on it
Registered letters have been
delivered to this address.
And i've been telling you
for weeks
That if you just give me
a little bit more time
And you just...
out of the blue?
It's not my call, mr. Wilks.
It's not my call.
Right.
Look, you might want to look
into some storage options.
The weather's
not looking good.
Lorne.
Kira, i don't want the kids
to see anymore of this.
Why don't you go upstairs
and get your things?
You're gonna stay
at nana's.
That's a good boy.
I'll call you tonight.
We'll turn it around.
Hey, brian?
Lorne.
Okay, great.
I'll call stan
and i'll call you back.
Yeah.
Good.
I'll see you there.
Ready?
Yeah.
Stan?
All the way.
Let's go.
Can i help you?
Excuse me,
can i help you?
Morning.
Hey, cover me,
i'm gonna check this out.
Meanwhile, some retail giants
are suffering
As a result of debt-Funded
stock buybacks,
Now having to deal with...
I'll take that again.
Excuse me, sir?
Hey, how you doing?
Um, i'm going to have
to ask you guys to leave.
Oh, i-I'm sorry, um...
Really, i don't want
to inconvenience you,
But, uh... look,
we'll be out of your hair,
But first we want to talk
to joel graves.
Here, this guy.
Ceo of the year?
You'd be doing us a big favour
if you just...
Radio that request upstairs
for us, all right?
Right, right.
Okay.
Sector 2, i'm gonna need
some assistance
In the media center.
That's not code for
you wanna kick me
And my friends
out of here, is it?
No-No, no.
Account holders.
Excuse me,
i'm celia westfall,
I'm with the cwgt
money report.
Do i understand you want
to talk to joel graves?
Yeah, i do. Can you turn
that camera off, please?
No, keep it rolling.
We're gonna push back
on your print proposal, john.
We're gonna go
exclusively digital.
It's lower cost and,
uh, research shows,
The internet is one of the last
"give-Ups" of the consumer.
????Your future first.
Sorry to interrupt, joel.
Yeah, howie?
You might wanna hear this.
There's a situation at
the stock exchange media centre.
Some kind of protest.
Okay... so?
They say they're grayson kearns
account holders;
They want you to come down
and talk.
"Homeless,
thanks to grayson kearns."
Thoughts?
Well, you could go down,
Put in some face time before
this turns into something.
Yeah, i could.
You know,
you wanna gift-Wrap me
Before you send me down there
to be a scapegoat, howie?
They're calling your bluff
on live tv
And they've got a headstart.
Look, i'll go down there,
But what am i supposed
to say to these guys?
Listen, fellas,
i'm really sorry.
This is just the price you pay
for not planning ahead.
Yeah, they're going to enjoy
hearing me say that, right?
Look,
all i'm saying is...
Ooh, or maybe i'll go down there
And tell them that
we're in a mental recession;
That, uh, we're all turning
into a nation of whiners
And we all have to stand beside
the choices we make.
The choice not to rent.
Joel.
Howie, i'm joking.
Joking.
Go down there,
give 'em my personal regrets,
Tell them i'm tied up
for a little bit.
Which is the truth,
okay?
Listen, howie,
There's gonna be camera's,
so, you know... be nice.
I'm always nice.
So, moving on...
Oh, i see.
So, we're free to access
the customer relations section
Of your website.
Come on.
That could be a problem
'cause i don't have a computer.
Or a house to put one in.
Mister...?
Do you really care
what my name is?
I'm sure mr. Graves would
consider a written request
For a private meeting.
As i'm sure you
can appreciate,
These are busy
and challenging times
For us all.
We look forward to you
getting in touch.
Thanks so much.
We'll remove them.
No, let them stay.
They don't wanna
see that on tv.
That's not supposed
to happen.
It's the same old
brush off.
I thought joel graves
was a lush for the media,
Couldn't resist
the spotlight?
Yeah, well, it's fine.
It's fine.
Plan b.
We have a "plan b"?
Yeah. I'm going up.
Then what?
Then you'll see.
Come on up,
i'll tell you on the way.
You stayin'?
Right here.
Stay tight, stay tight.
Okay, go-Go-Go, go!
Code 113.
Elevator 1.
It's not gonna work.
Yes, it is.
He won't come down.
Let's call it off.
No.
This is "plan b."
All those nights
we spent talking about this,
I'm not walking away.
You do this and we're
in deep. Sit down with us
And someone is gonna do
this right.
Good morning.
I'd like to speak
to joel graves.
Make the call.
Do it now!
Flashpoint
Season 02 - Episode 05
** Business as Usual **
Probably the same as you.
There's no place
like this.
No work like this.
With your skills,
You could work any number
of different places.
You did well
in undercover.
Yeah.
I've done my time
behind enemy lines.
Enemy?
Sorry, i don't mean...
Now, you know,
the whole war zone imagery
Doesn't really fly
around here.
Okay, sorry.
You know what i mean.
Do i?
It's an expression,
come on.
Uh, oh yeah,
It's a pretty revealing
expression.
You're mirroring me.
What?
Your body language.
You're showing me
"me" now.
Do you know
you're doing that?
Or is that just
reflex by now
From all your time
among "the enemy"?
Constable sabine,
You got the bonding
moves down,
Belonging,
Being what someone
wants to see,
And that's all very,
very useful.
But it concerns me
a little...
When your psych eval
shows inconsistencies
On self-Reporting.
It's like you can't keep
your story straight
About who you are.
This job,
connecting to people,
I need to know you've got
something to draw from.
Team one, suit up.
Hot call, hot call.
Gunmen at large
in the commerce tower.
Someone to draw from.
Pick this up later.
Awesome.
Awesome, yeah.
Kira,
how many gunmen?
We have multiple witnesses
reporting a single gunman
Or pair of gunmen,
At different areas
on the 11th floor.
Could be one suspect,
could be a team.
What are they carrying?
Handgun, rifle, shotgun?
Take your pick.
Joel graves.
Just need a minute
of your time.
Joel graves, do you know
where his office is?
Commerce tower will be
under lockdown
We're not here to hurt anyone,
we just...
We just wanna talk
to your boss.
Do you know where
his office is?
Just wanna talk
to your boss.
Where's his office?
Graves!
Second floor.
Let's go.
She rappels like a spider.
Thinks on her feet.
Is it time for a vote yet
or what?
I'm thinking i need
to think some more.
She's a no-Brainer.
She's got the chops,
no question about it.
But...
Boss, needs to think.
Copy that.
Boss needs to think.
Let's go.
I'm gonna just, uh...
I'm gonna call security,
see what the deal is.
Joel.
It's the men
that wanted to see you.
One of them's got a gun.
Hey!
Come here! Hey!
Get out of my way!
I don't know
how this could happen?
How anything like this
could happen?
I think you'll find out
everything you need to know,
Find out
when he gets down here.
If i were you,
i'd stand back.
Go on! Get out of here!
Stand back!
Number of suspects?
2 guys split off
from the older one
In the media centre,
Demanding to see
the grayson kearns ceo.
The media centre,
what's that?
It's down the escalator,
off the trading floor.
It's where the reporters do
all their stand-And-Talks,
Lots of big screens,
tickers,
It's like they're
right there.
Subject in the media centre,
is he armed?
No. No, visible weapons.
My guys are
holding him there.
Cops just showed.
I've got cctv tapes.
Eddie, i'll take the guy
in the media centre.
Spike, you're my second.
Set up a command post
at that security desk.
Where were the gunmen
last seen?
Grayson kearns head office,
11th floor.
Lou, sam, wordy,
with me.
We need one of those
elevators unlocked.
Keep the rest of them
shut down tight.
He what?
The guy's spilling gasoline
everywhere!
Hey, buddy,
what's going on?
What're you doin'?
Don't touch the camera.
Camera stays on.
I'm not gonna touch
anything.
What're you doing
that for?
Come on,
just put that down.
Stay back!
Okay, okay.
But why don't we
just go outside,
We can talk about this?
I warned you...
stay back.
Nobody comes any closer.
Okay, okay.
All right, let's all
just move back.
Let's give this man
some space.
Give him some space.
11:09 a.M.
Sergeant gregory parker
initiates negotiation.
Subject is level red,
threatening self-Immolation.
Hi, my name's greg parker,
I'm with the police
strategic response unit.
And i'm here to listen
To whatever
you have to say, sir.
I'm here to help you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Nope, no one's gonna force you
to do anything.
Spike, let's get
the fire department on standby,
But no entry.
Repeat,
no entry until my command.
And let's get ambulances
in the area on standby as well.
Copy that.
Let's evacuate the area,
And then i need you
in the security room
With my guy,
all right?
Miss,
did you talk to him?
I want you to stay
right there, okay?
Spike, we've got
a gentleman here
Releasing gasoline
into an enclosed room
Without any ventilation.
The concentration of vapours
is high and growing
And he's holding
a lighter.
Well, it's not just the lighter
i'm worried about.
Anything sets off a spark,
you got a fireball.
Firearms for instance?
???Lethal, non-Lethal.
Muzzle flash
would be all it takes.
All right, copy that.
See if you can get some airflow
going in here too, okay?
Sir?
It's greg again.
What's your name?
If you don't want to tell me
that's fine,
You don't wanna talk to me
that's...
Not a problem,
no pressure.
In fact, i tell you what?
I'll give you
one less thing
To worry about, okay?
I want everyone
with a firearm
To leave this room.
Everyone with a firearm.
Fast is good.
Right now.
Got it? Officers out.
Everybody out. You too.
That's it, guys.
Sergeant,
is that everybody?
Okay, all done.
You all right?
Got cctv of our subjects.
Portraits of the gunmen...
coming at you.
I'll be right here.
Can we cut the video?
We can't reach our cameras
from here.
And i don't think he's gonna
want us to turn them off;
That's sort of why he's here.
Oh yeah?
What'd he tell you?
Well, he and two others
Have been trying to get
joel graves's attention for a long time.
Joel graves? He's the guy
who collects a fat bonus
While rome burns, right?
Mm, this is the guy.
Okay, i want you to tell me
about his company,
"Grayson kearns."
Okay.
Sru. Which way did they go?
Clear.
Everyone stay calm.
We're with the sru.
Stay calm, please, everyone.
Stay calm.
Hands where we can see 'em,
folks.
Stay calm.
Thank you.
Clear.
Hands where we can see 'em.
Folks, need to see
your hands please.
We're with the sru.
Let's see some hands.
Clear.
Which way did the gunman go?
Sru, please stay calm.
Clear.
All right,
let me get this.
"Grayson kearns" gives away
mortgages like it's candy.
When the market slides,
They dump high risk clients
to the highest bidder, right?
??Who re-Offer it at rates
these guys can't afford.
You know they seem
like regular guys.
They probably just want
their houses back.
Yeah, i think our friend
wants more than that.
He tell you his name?
Stan matthews.
Okay, thanks.
You can get out of here.
Thank you very much.
Fire department's
on standby, boss,
Waiting for permission
to deploy.
Negative.
Negative,
if he sees fire hoses,
He just needs a split second
to beat 'em the the punch
And spark an explosion.
Copy that.
They gotta stay out
of the line of sight.
Gotta keep thinking
outside the toolbox.
All right, sir,
I understand, uh...
You're looking for
some information
From joel graves.
He's been in the... spotlight
quite a bit these days, huh?
He's doing okay
for himself.
You talking about
the $22 million dollars?
His bonus?
Yeah-Yeah,
something like that.
Here's a guy who's got
four houses already.
Books a 5-Star caribbean resort
with his buddies
To brainstorm
how to make the most
Of these troubled times.
What can you do?
What do you want from him?
I want him down here.
Okay.
All right,
let's work on that.
Spike, let's get a 20
on joel graves.
It's not too late.
What do you mean?
Maybe we walk away,
before the cops find us.
Lorne...
I'm just saying.
All the times talked about it,
We never talked about it
happening like this.
Hands, please.
Let me see your hands please.
Sit down, take a seat.
Thank you.
Ma'am, let's see
your hands please.
Let's see your hands.
Take a seat.
We have id on one of our guys.
Stan matthews.
He's a grayson kearns
account holder.
They all are.
I've narrowed the national list
by city, male account holders,
There's still a lot.
Might wanna try
recent foreclosures.
Foreclosures...
Here he is, stan matthews.
There's another one
who lives on the same street,
A lorne wilkes.
Good.
See any other connections?
Hold on...
There's a brian baumann,
Same employer as lorne wilkes.
Ex-Employer.
They were both recently
laid off from the auto plant.
Copy that.
You know what'd be
really great, kira?
Some cell numbers fror these guys.
Copy-Copy.
You need to send someone now.
Right now!
Think of stan.
You remember that night,
right?
Yeah.
You with me?
Hey. Hey!
I'm gonna need
your keys.
Elevator.
You'll need this one
for the elevator.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'm telling you,
they're at my door.
Okay.
Mr. Graves.
Uh...
What can i do
for you guys?
You're coming with us
downstairs.
You're gonna go
on camera.
Uh, and then what?
Oh, we'll talk about trust.
Some promises you didn't keep.
"Your future first."
You-You don't care
about our future.
His family's out
on the street,
I'm livin' out of the car
the past few weeks,
So, whose future's
coming first here?
No-No-No,
we're going downstairs.
Okay, listen to me,
I'm sorry to hear
about your losses,
I am, but...
I've been juggling
thousands of losses, guys.
It's my job.
I'm just doing my job.
You know what
your job is now?
It's to own up.
Take responsibility.
Hunh?
Let go!
Get...
Okay, okay.
We need to end this,
huh?
We need to end this.
Brian.
It's right there.
Thank you.
We're gonna need
your pass key.
Those guys took it.
How is that fair?
Can you explain
that to me?
I don't know.
You tell me, stan.
It was just me and carol.
39 years.
I hated math,
she hated power tools,
So we had a deal:
She managed the books,
i worked.
We scraped together
everything we had
And we found this little...
mutt of a fixer-Upper.
Didn't look like much,
but we knew what it could be.
And i'll never...
I'll never understand
why she would do
Something like that.
What do you mean?
What-What happened, stan?
I loved that woman.
I loved her.
I'm so fed up.
Stan, stan, it's okay.
It's okay.
Really is okay.
Why don't we take
a break?
Huh?
Tell you the truth,
I'm getting a headache
from all the fumes.
Why don't we just step outside
and just get some air?
No! No!
Okay, you don't have
to do that, stan.
No!
It's locked.
Okay?
Police, don't move!
Police!
Clear.
Ed, we got a hallway.
Ed, elevators are locked down,
right?
Affirmative.
Well, elevator 3
is on the move.
Floor 12, going down.
Hang on.
Where are the other
elevators?
Ground floor.
Stairs are faster.
All right, head's up, guys,
subjects are on the move,
They probably have
security cards and keys.
Spike, get me uniforms
on all the elevator exits,
In case they step out
before they reach bottom.
Security has reported two men
entering the elevator,
Just two?
Where's graves?
Kira's got cell numbers.
You wanna give it a try?
Negative,
you make the call, spike.
I need my full attention
on my subject here.
They're not responding
to the phone.
They've stopped the elevator
between floors.
Floor 7, floor 6.
Sam and lou,
cover the 6th floor exit.
We'll go above.
Copy that.
Bravo team proceeding on foot.
Bravo team in position.
Still no response
on the phone.
What can you tell me about
overriding manual controls?
Listen up, guys,
we got a window of opportunity.
There's a trap in the ceiling.
I don't feel like dropping in
without a distraction.
I hear you.
Cs gas standing by.
No 555's.
9 cubic feet of air
in there.
What about 517's?
Still overkill in that space.
Ditto flashbangs.
Serious risk of eye
and ear damage.
Hey, how about this,
uh, training flashbangs?
Used them on the recruits
this morning.
You got training flashbangs?
Sure.
Just open the doors
a little first.
Reduce the concussive effect.
I like it,
let's do it.
Okay, the elevator has two
emergency override patterns:
A ground floor
And a nearest floor
cycle pattern.
Dropping down a floor,
we'll deploy from above.
Sam, lou, meet and greet
when the doors open.
Copy.
Got it.
Boss, you good with this?
Just go careful.
These guys don't have records,
It just sounds like
they've been pushed too hard.
Wordy.
Copy that.
Distraction standing by.
Standing by.
Spike,
countdown override procedure.
5...
4... 3...
2... 1...
Triggering override.
Distraction on my go.
Back off.
Back off!
Hold.
Hold, eddie.
He's got graves.
11:36 a.M.
Armed subject with hostage
in elevator.
We have one subject
in the elevator with joel graves.
He's armed
with a snubnose.38.
Fall back.
New deal.
Hostage situation.
Decrease pressure.
Copy that.
Wordy, i'm coming up.
Spike,
keep trying the phone,
Maybe they're ready
to talk now.
No-No-No-No.
See if we can get
the ventilation going in here,
And keep your guys
out of sight.
All right, change of plans,
spike.
Go for the ground floor
override sequence.
We'll have more tac options
in the open lobby
Than in one of these hallways.
Freeze! Freeze!
I'm giving up.
Put your hands on your head!
Hands on your head!
Stay right there!
Stay right where you are!
Come here.
We got a subject
who has surrendered.
Copy that.
Sam, you're sierra.
And, lou, let's bring the guy
down here.
Copy.
Okay, got him.
What's he gonna do?
That depends
on your friend.
Please don't hurt him.
We don't want to.
Why don't you
help us out?
What's that smell?
<What's going on?!
I'm trying to help
your friend.
What happened?
You don't know?
He's soaked the room with gas,
including himself,
And now he's threatening
to light it up.
Oh my god. No, no.
None of this was supposed
to go like this.
Let me talk to...
do that.N't let you
Lou, i got him,
it's okay.
You wanna help
your friend?
You need to keep
talking to me.
Spike.
The gas in the media room?
I think we got another option.
Talk to me, lou.
How close can we get
to the subject?
You gonna answer that?
You know, you don't seem
like the kind of guy.
What kind of guy?
The kind of guy
who makes his point with a gun.
And what would you know
about that?
In my line of work,
you meet a lot of people,
You get a sense.
You know,
i got two kids.
My buddy lorne has two kids.
They went out
for a drive today,
Cross-Country,
To go live in a house
that smells like other people.
They got to watch their dad
sell everything that they owned
For less than what you pay
for a business brunch.
Do you think about what
kind of guy lorne was
Before you sold out
his family's future?
No one's accountable.
We're all just pieces of paper
crossing his desk.
He sells a piece of paper
and we lose everything.
And that's what happened
to stan too?
Brian and me worked
at the plant 11 years
'Til it closed 5 months ago.
Stan lives on brian's street.
We've all been buddies
a long time.
Brian thought...
He was doing us a favour.
Here's these amazing
mortgage deals.
And he talked you
and stan into it?
Me and carol.
Carol is stan's wife?
Late wife.
Now, stan...
Stan fixed his place up
with his own hands.
Did it for carol.
Did it to give her the home
she always dreamed about.
Then one day they get
a letter in the mail,
Her payments have
been tripled
And there's no way
they can pay.
Their pension's already...
decimated.
What're they gonna give up?
Heating?
Groceries?
She sees it's coming,
right?
All he put into it,
all he did for her,
It's all gonna be gone.
But she can't bring herself
to tell him,
So she hides it, right?
And hides it...
And one day,
she's out of time.
Makes no sense.
I mean... you love someone,
you stick around,
You fight, but...
She couldn't.
He comes home
after work one day
And he finds her...
He finds his wife.
That wasn't a great day.
You really think graves
is gonna care?
Or you just want him
to see what he's done?
We want him to see the people
he's wrecked, up close.
We want his face
on camera saying,
"I made this choice,
I sold out a thousand families
For the price
of my $22,000,000 dollar bonus,
I knew what i was doing
and i did it anyway
And i'm sorry."
Okay.
Constable.
Eddie, i need to stay here
with stan.
That's all it'll take!
I want you to meet the elevator
to start negotiating.
You catch that conversation
i had with my friend, lorne?
Yeah, i copy.
Okay.
Spike,
start the override procedure.
Okay, listen to me,
please.
No, you listen to me.
You are gonna do this,
do you understand me?
You are gonna do this
Or you're not walking
outta here,
You're not going home.
Okay.
Do you understand?
I can't hold the elevator doors
open when they hit the lobby.
It'll cycle open
automatically.
And we're at 5...
4... 3...
2... 1...
Move away.
Move ayay.
My name's ed lane.
I'm with the police
strategic response unit.
How you doing?
Get out of the way.
It's brian, right?
Brian?
We're coming through.
What's going on?
Have you got him?
Is he coming?!
Just try and understand
where we're at, stan.
Boss, me and lou
are working on option b.
Big reno on the main floor.
Big paint job.
We may be able
to neutralize the lighter.
Could buy you a few seconds.
Yeah, i hear you.
That's good.
You better get him here.
I'm done waiting!
Just calm, just calm, stan.
Just stay with me.
Lou's got uniforms
moving on it.
Okay, but move fast,
move real fast.
And give ed whatever background
you can on brian baumann.
Okay.
Still workin' on it.
We're still workin' on it.
5 more minutes, stan.
5 more minutes.
I got the solution.
Copy that.
He's gonna talk.
You gonna talk, right?
I know what's going on here,
brian, okay?
And i gotta tell you
right out of the gate,
I'm sympathetic.
Laid off from the auto plant
five months ago.
Lost his house
to foreclosure.
No listed address.
No family.
We got a lot of people here
who are very sympathetic.
They understand exactly
what it is you're going through.
No, they don't.
They don't.
Yeah, they do.
No, they don't.
That's why we're going in there
with the cameras,
And he's gonna say
what he's done.
That's what we're here for.
I get that, brian.
Okay, i get that.
When i was a kid,
I saw my folks go through
the very same thing.
You feel helpless.
You get it?
Then you get why this guy
has to go in there
And own up
to what he's done.
Where is he?
What do you want, stan?
Why aren't you
letting him through?
Brian and lorne...
They want to make things
right again.
Lorne wants a house
for his family,
I get that.
But what do you want
from joel graves?
I want him in here.
You know what i think
you really want?
What you really want,
you know he can't give it you.
You know he can't
bring it back.
Lou, you gotta hurry,
You gotta hurry,
lou.
Okay, copy.
On our way.
Don't try to stop me.
I owe this.
I owe this to carol.
To carol?
Stan's wife.
"Recession suicide."
He found her
in the garage.
She had her good coat on.
Her good coat,
like she was going somewhere.
She left a note
on the hood of the car
'Cause she couldn't tell him.
And she, she thought
she let him down.
I hear you.
That's not right.
Yeah,
it's not right.
It's not right.
You hear me?
You get it?
Then you let me through.
Now, listen to me, brian.
In this job,
i hear a lot of people
Asking for a lot
of crazy things,
And what you're asking for,
it's not crazy.
It's not.
It's just not something...
It's not something
that we can do, okay?
We can't do it like this.
You know, i get it.
I get it.
You just, you just wanna
do right by your friends.
You just wanna do right
by stan.
Brian, stan is down there
right now,
Doused gasoline,
with a lighter,
And he's gonna light himself
on fire.
No. No.
Now, i know you've
lost a lot,
But you don't want
to lose stan too.
So i'm asking you,
Show him that this
isn't the way.
Just show him that there's
another way to end this.
Okay?
Please?
Please.
Thank you.
Weapon's down.
Thanks.
And i know how hard it is
to lose someone.
To lose someone you love,
To lose something that's
so important to you
And have it ripped
out of your life.
You got ten seconds.
This isn't the way, stan.
It's not the way.
Your friends know that.
Your friends know
when it's time to stop.
You get him in here...
Or this ends right now.
Just don't do it, stan.
Just don't do it.
Thank you,
you did the right thing.
You did the right thing.
Mr. Graves.
Hi.
What do you have
to tell us about today?
Hi, uh...
i'm joel graves and...
In response to today's events,
I'd just like to say
a few words,
Um...
I'm moved by the losses
of these men.
Eddie...
And i understand the need
to turn to someone
For an explanation.
What these men lost was more
than four walls and a roof,
But that's the part
that i took from them.
It made sense on paper,
but up close...
It's a different story.
Let's go.
Up close...
it's not the same,
I'm sorry.
Stan, i'm sorry.
If there's anything
i can do to help?
Mr. Graves! Mr. Graves!
Well, he got up there,
Came clean,
said he was sorry,
That's what you wanted,
right?
It's not enough.
I know.
I know, nothing's gonna
take that pain away.
Now he wants to help.
How's he gonna do that?
Being sorry gets him
off the hook?
"I wanna help"
makes things better?
What's he gonna do?
Is he in the business
of giving back lives?
What about my wife?
Just don't do it,
stan.
Just don't.
Ready, serge.
Go.
Carol...
Carol... carol...
12:16 p.M.
Third subject,
stan matthews, contained.
You know what?
She blew by everbydody in there.
Nobody can touch her.
Greg, nobody.
So what's the problem?
You don't think
she'll work?
You don't wanna
let jules go?
Mm...
Constable sabine?
Sit down.
Good call today?
Well, no one died.
This guy wanted to die today,
but he didn't get to.
This other guy,
he's got a family
Who's gonna go without
a father for a while.
This guy's going to jail
'Cause all he wanted to do
was help out his two friends.
I get it.
Yeah?
It's not black and white.
Everyone's a constable here.
There's no rising up
in the ranks.
You don't make more money
Because you risk your life
everyday,
You make less.
I know.
Mm-Hmm.
Not gonna be out
in the field alone,
You're gonna be in it
with a team.
I'm not gonna lie to you,
If jules makes it back,
she's got a place here.
Fair.
But that doesn't mean
i won't put my faith in you.
I'm not gonna let you down.
Okay.
Yeah? Okay?
Yeah, let's keep
the peace.
Okay,
let's do that.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
We're gonna get through this.
www.tvsubtitles.net