- Who are you?
- It's a pity you'll never know.
Sloane is part of this.
He works with Prophet Five.
This is my chance to stop him.
We were expecting
to hear from you sooner.
I ran into a few complications.
And Sydney?
She's dead.
Langley can't know what Sydney's doing.
We should continue to act
on the assumption
that Prophet Five has moles
inside the C.I.A.
Contact Michael Linz in Berlin.
He'll send the body back.
I'll get right on it.
Come with me.
Anna's dead.
Sydney seized the opportunity
to infiltrate Prophet Five.
Sydney's presenting herself as Anna?
Do you think that's wise?
It was Sydney's call.
I wasn't consulted.
What's your status?
We'll be up and running in a minute.
Sydney embedded a tracker into the chip
that Anna was tasked to retrieve.
We'll be able to follow her from here.
We suspect Prophet Five
had intended for Anna to do
some task only Sydney could perform.
Learning what that is
may be an opportunity
to determine their endgame.
- That's if they believe Sydney is Anna.
- I know.
Patching Vaughn through.
Vaughn, can you hear me?
You're clear.
Where is he?
Hamburg. He and Sydney uncovered
a storeroom of information...
material that Vaughn
and Renée Rienne's fathers gathered
during their investigation of Prophet 5.
You'll join Vaughn.
Transmit the documentation back here
for analysis.
Vaughn, it's Dixon.
It's good to hear your voice.
You, too.
I'll see you soon.
Marshall, how we doing?
I'm triangulating the coordinates.
Just give me a sec.
You know, I cried at your funeral.
- Sorry about that.
- No, no, thank you.
I need a good cry now and again.
Okay, tracker's hot.
Got her. There she is.
She's on...
Tiergartenstrasse.
I have the chip in hand.
Of course. We're en route now.
Our superiors were quite pleased
with your performance.
You seem surprised.
Not at all.
Your reputation's well-deserved.
To the great Anna Espinosa.
"Great" seems a little strong,
doesn't it?
Don't tell me you're getting modest.
It's this body.
I have this uncontrollable urge now
to act like a girl scout all the time.
Well, let's get you back to Zurich
before you start trying
to sell me cookies.
I'm sure our superiors are eager
to get their hands on that.
This?
This is an inconvenience.
Nothing more.
- What just happened?
- I'm not sure.
I think the tracker crashed.
Crashed? What does that mean, crashed?
- We've lost Sydney.
- Marshall, find her!
I can't. I think it must've fritzed out.
Patch into a traffic cam.
Do something! Just find her!
Don't worry, I'm on it.
Okay, I got her.
They're headed south on A7.
The airport.
Marshall, I'm on Doverkamp,
headed east. I need directions.
Wait, give me a sec.
Left at the next intersection.
You're closing in.
Marshall, I'm gonna need
a green light in a hurry.
Easier said than done.
It's all in German.
- Anschlag?
- Grun. Green.
Shall we?
You finished the translation of page 47.
"The circle will be complete,"
"when the chosen one
finds the rose in San Cielo."
Congratulations, Mr. Sloane.
Thanks to your work,
we're closer than we've ever been
to comprehending Rambaldi's
greatest mystery.
You understand the meaning
of the deciphered message?
Enough to proceed.
However, I do have one concern.
Rambaldi's prophecies
have always taken into account
the smallest variables.
This is a man who predicted events
hundreds of years before we were born.
The rose in question is indeed unique...
as unique as Sydney herself.
What is unclear, however,
is whether Anna Espinosa,
posing as Sydney,
is  able to complete the task.
Well, then I guess you've got your work
cut out for you.
After you.
Sloane's here.
Of course.
You didn't think we'd dispose of him
this soon, did you?
I  hear your mission was a success.
I suppose I should offer you
congratulations.
Thank you.
Did you encounter any complications?
Just one.
But I've dealt with her
once and for all.
We should celebrate, Arvin.
Sydney Bristow is dead.
Sync by Anyone, Sixe, Guilamu
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
Remarkable likeness, isn't it?
So this is why you needed her.
Or should I say me?
In his prophecies, Rambaldi referred
to Sydney as "the chosen one."
He foretold that she would bring forth
his final works.
And you really believe that...
that a man who lived 500 years ago
had intentions for Sydney Bristow?
Excuse me.
I may be mistaken,
but I always believed you
to be a follower of Rambaldi's works.
Only when it suits my checkbook.
I'm not someone who'd guide my life
by some perverted sense of faith.
But as long as I have to look like this,
I might as well make some use of it.
What does Rambaldi want me to do?
Retrieve an artifact from San Cielo...
A monastery outside Rome.
Monastery? That sounds fun.
Do I get to wear a habit?
I think I've told you
all you need to know for now.
We leave within the hour.
Does this mean you're sending me
to my room?
There's a change of clothes for you
upstairs.
Second door on the left.
Sadly, he did, yeah. Can you imagine
what happened when they got home?
Could I steal you for a sec?
The new encryption module
for the comms...
...think my math is wrong.
Go ahead. I can handle this.
She'll be back in a second.
Didn't Langley just convert
all of our comms to...
This isn't about the comms.
Marshall, what's going on?
Last week, when Sloane infiltrated
the network,
I built a bot to monitor the servers,
you know, flag any abnormal activity?
This morning a message came through
this office without any I.D. Tags.
Intended for Allen Korman.
Korman?
- You mean the guy that...
- Yeah, him.
I mean, why would Tom be contacting
a guy who killed his wife ?
So, I did some digging.
Travel itinerary.
Korman's flying into L.A. Tonight.
This doesn't make any sense.
Look, I talked to Tom myself.
He said he came to Korman
to confront him,
but when he saw Korman with his family,
he changed his mind.
Rachel, Korman doesn't have any family.
I checked.
Tom's been lying to you.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you first, but...
I have to tell Mr. Bristow.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, we have to.
Look, you said it yourself...
The contact is anonymous...
Tom is not a bad guy!
- How do you know that ?
- Because I know.
Look,
just let me check into it first.
Give me 24 hours.
I promise, if we don't have an answer
by then, we'll go to Jack together.
All right. 24 hours.
Hey, it's me. I don't have much time.
- Where are you?
- Zurich. An estate, highly secure.
Sloane is here.
- What is he telling you?
- That page 47 references San Cielo...
A monastery outside Rome.
We're going there.
Where are you?
Right now, in your kitchen,
playing with Isabelle.
You are?
How is she?
Happy.
- Dad, did she just...
- Giggle? Yeah.
Apparently, I'm funny.
She hasn't done that before.
That was a first.
Of which there will be many.
I know.
I'll notify Vaughn and Dixon about Rome.
If you learn anything more...
I have to go. Tell Isabelle I love her.
You  ready?
Hey.
You're shorter than I remember.
This is all regarding Prophet Five?
This entire bunker contains
evidence of...
mysterious  deaths, assassinations,
car bombings,
all of them involving people
who were investigating Prophet Five.
They basically killed anyone
who got too close.
But they didn't get you.
No. They might have, if not for Jack.
When I was in the hospital,
he convinced me that Prophet Five
wouldn't rest
until they killed me, and that I was
in no condition to fight back.
How'd he manage it?
Sodium morphate.
It slowed down my body functions
to a point that mimicked death.
Apparently, I spent four hours
in a drawer at the morgue
waiting for Jack's contact reach me
to administer the antidote.
Then a couple days of traveling
before I made it to Nepal.
You know, it's funny, it's the 1st time
I ever felt Jack accepted me.
Or else, he manufactured
a very elaborate scheme
to postpone your wedding
to his daughter.
I have something for you.
Fortunately,
she looks more like her mother.
Yeah, she does.
Dixon, thank you.
Yeah, Jack.
Of course.
We'll contact you when we arrive.
Jack's sending a team
to box all this up.
Sydney's en route with Sloane.
We're gonna provide backup.
Where are they headed?
Rome.
Well...
I made our arrangements.
Your contact will be meeting you
on the ground.
He'll provide you with access
to San Cielo.
No more than I need to know.
Well,
I am sure you have questions.
So do I.
Tell me...
How did it happen?
How did I kill Sydney?
Why do you care?
Sydney was a remarkable agent.
I imagine it wasn't easy.
Sydney wasn't a martyr or a legend.
She was just a person...
who deserved nothing more
than to be shot in the back...
and so she was.
The Chosen One.
She died just as easy as anyone.
I see.
Well, thank you.
We'll be landing shortly.
I know what you have planned
for Anna after this mission is over.
You have reservations?
Oh, no.
I want to be the one who kills her.
You smell nice.
So we looked into
the monastery San Cielo.
- You're sure about that name?
- Yeah, why?
Marshall couldn't find any record of it.
I'm  meeting someone inside the O.T.B.
He's supposed to brief me on the rest.
I saw a picture of Isabelle.
I don't know how we do this anymore.
We do it the way we've always done it.
It's the only way to keep her safe.
We end this.
Okay.
Dixon and I will have your back.
If anything happens,
we're gonna pull you out.
So who's this contact?
Sloane said I'd know him when I saw him.
Syd, be careful.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
If you want my advice,
take Tokyo Rose in the third.
It's a sure bet.
Julian, last time I saw you,
it was at Venice...
where, as I recall,
you betrayed me to the C.I.A.
They took me into custody.
And yet, Anna, here you are.
Looking better than ever.
That's, for a year spent
in a federal holding facility.
Now what was that one for?
I'll get back to you.
Right.
So what are you drinking?
Did you find him?
The Cardinal?
I wouldn't be here if I didn't.
I'm gonna give you to "three"
to start talking.
Not here.
Somebody might be watching.
I didn't lie to you.
Korman killed my wife.
But the order came from somebody else.
The closest I've gotten is a name...
The Cardinal.
Well, you two seem to be pretty chummy.
He works freelance.
We did a job once...
deep cover op.
He doesn't even know my real name.
Look, I've gotta find out why, Rachel.
She was a schoolteacher.
She wasn't a part of this life.
If somebody wanted to hurt me,
why didn't they just come after me?
And Korman knows?
He does now.
He found The Cardinal.
What does he want?
- Money?
- His car...
it was seized
when he turned himself in to witsec.
You could've told me, tom.
I would've kept it to myself.
No, I couldn't have.
I've spent four years,
and this is as close as I've got
to an answer.
I couldn't trust anybody.
If I hack into the federal database,
I should be able to find the car.
I couldn't ask you to do that.
You didn't.
It's Sark.
The contact?
Yep.
Better the enemy you know...
She can handle Sark.
Another?
Perhaps you shouldn't.
We're on the clock.
We are.
Here I thought we were just
catching up on old times.
Well, in that case, maybe it's time
you fill me in on the plan.
What has Sloane told you?
Just  that our target is San Cielo.
Well, that's not entirely true.
The rose that you're suppose to acquire,
if you're to believe page 47,
is being held in a facility
known by Rambaldi as San Cielo.
The rest of the world now refers to it
as La Fossa maximum security prison.
We're breaking into a prison?
According to Sloane, Milo Rambaldi,
in the days leading up
to his execution, was held there.
He believes he hid the rose
in the northwest isolation wing.
The text specifies
that only the Chosen One
can obtain the item in question.
I guess you'll have to do.
An explosion?
I suggest you take cover.
Wait, this is your plan
for getting us into La Fossa?
Yes.
Grazzie.
Follow my lead, will you?
Have you been able to access
the prison's internal network?
Not yet. Vaughn and Dixon
are moving through the sewers now.
Right here--prison internet connection
runs out through a junction box.
It should be vulnerable.
Merlin, you there?
Yeah, Vaughn, go ahead.
We're about 70 meters in.
Still no sign of the junction box.
You're almost directly
under the switch room.
- You should be close.
- Got it.
It's a standard IP-X node.
Good. You should be able
to splice the line
- and access the surveillance feeds.
- Doing that now.
Do it quickly.
I don't like the idea Sydney being
in a maximum security prison
with Sark as her backup.
Being my friend
will make your time more pleasurable.
Lucky for you, I won't be here for long.
Otherwise, I'd pull out your tongue
and choke you with it.
You realize we just broke
about a half dozen federal laws.
Unless they moved it, Korman's car
should be right down this aisle.
Look, just stay low,
check for V.I.N. Numbers.
You ready? Let's go.
This is it.
This shouldn't take long.
Can I help?
Yeah,
just keep an eye out for the guard.
Is there any particular reason
you're connecting
the carburetor to the intake tube?
This is the carburetor?
Yeah.
Maybe, uh,
I should keep an eye out for the guard.
All right. You should be tied in now.
Yeah, we're hot.
You getting a picture?
Copy. It's coming through.
See if you can isolate
the women's block.
Wait a minute. Was that...
was that the women's showers?
No, that's men.
Definitely men.
There she is.
Wait a minute. She's in isolation.
You think that's part of a plan?
We have to hope so.
Hold him down.
This is gonna hurt.
Marshall, what happened?
- Did we lose the signal?
- I don't know.
Everything just went wacky.
We've been kicked out.
Looks like somebody else
is trying to hack into the system.
Sark.
Is there any way to regain our tap?
We have to keep track of her.
You could look for the alarm lines
and then
try to cross-wind 'em
and get a Von Eck signal.
Know what he's talking about?
50%.
This is it.
Sark, where are you?
I've been waiting for you
for a very long time.
I think you have me confused
with someone else.
I can't imagine confusing you
with anyone else.
As difficult as this must be
for you to understand...
I know you.
We've never met.
No. We haven't.
We don't have much time.
Come with me.
I'm not going anywhere with you
unless you tell me who you are.
"The circle will be complete
when the chosen one finds the rose."
I am the rose.
Now...
if you will come with me...
And, Mr. Harvey, how can I help you?
You have two suspects in custody
who are wanted fugitives
from my country,
and we would like
to have them extradited
with your permission, of course.
Then I'm afraid we have a problem.
Why is that, sir?
These two have committed crimes
on Italian land,
and I cannot possibly release them
before their first judicial hearing.
But you could release them
if you got the permission
of the general prosecutor,
Adriana Micelli.
Well, yes, of course.
But signora Micelli...
Mrs. Micelli is expecting your call.
Pronto.
Signora Micelli, Buongiorno.
Well...
looks like we may be almost there.
I was supposed to meet her.
Who?
My wife...
night she died.
It was our half-year anniversary.
I was gonna pick her up at work...
take her out to dinner.
But contact called.
I never made it.
I was working five investigations,
and maybe I screwed up,
got my stories confused.
Or maybe somebody from my past...
revenge.
I don't know.
You'll find out so enough.
Thanks for doing this.
Honestly...
this is the closest thing I've had
to a night out since I joined the C.I.A.
You want to hop in and give me some gas?
Who did this?
You don't need me to tell you.
He told me you'd be coming.
All I had to do was wait.
This is yours for the time being.
What is it?
His greatest gift...
and also his greatest curse.
Meaning?
What you hold in your hand is simply
a defiance of the natural order...
The end of nature itself.
Some very bad people
want what's in this amulet.
I can't stop them
if you don't tell me what it is.
You don't understand.
You can't stop them.
You don't know me very well.
You're more charming
than I could have imagined.
I used to believe as you do,
that there were decisions to be made.
But in the end, it's just fate.
It's out of our hands.
And now it's just a matter of time.
A matter of time until what?
Until the stars fall from the sky.
Until the end of light.
You have gotten what you came for.
The guards will be making rounds soon.
You need to go.
Will you be all right?
I'm not a part of the battle to come.
Go.
Dixon, I got her.
I'll call you back.
Looks like she's heading back
to the women's block.
She must have got what she came for.
Maybe she's headed for extraction.
Good luck with this one.
He's all yours.
Thank you.
Where's Anna?
Anna won't be joining us.
Were you successful?
Tell me, Anna...
Did you retrieve the rose?
There was nothing there.
I don't believe you.
Sydney deserved better
than an anonymous bullet.
You didn't even have the courage
to face her.
At least I look you in the eye.
Marshall, talk to me!
There's a grate to the iso ward
about 30 yards ahead of you.
He'll never make it in time.
We need to distract Sloane!
Marshall, the surveillance feed
they're tapped into,
can we use it to get into
security controls?
Marshall, hurry!
Got it.
I don't die that easy.
Sir, we've had a breach.
You better get out of here.
Stay in your cell.
Stay back!
You okay?
Yeah, let's get out of here.
Thank you.
Why was the hit ordered on my wife?
If I tell you, you'll never let me
walk away from here.
You have my word.
I don't believe you.
Go ahead.
Shoot me.
First, tell me why she had to die.
Truth is, she was just
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
I don't understand.
My information said
you were picking her up at her job.
I was waiting
t the bottom of the stairs.
You were supposed to be with her.
It was a mistake.
She died because I thought she was you.
I'm going to disappear now.
If you come after me, I'll know.
And I'll do what I set out to do
four years ago.
This is pretty amazing.
Have you ever seen anything so perfect?
No.
You did good.
Thanks.
You're gonna be just like your mom,
aren't you?
Oh, I hope not.
I hope she's a doctor or a teacher
or just anything that does not involve
wearing a wig.
I don't know. I think she'd look
pretty cute in a little pink wig.
Maybe not.
You okay?
Yeah, it just...
I'm still a little sore, I guess.
We came so close, Vaughn.
Sloane and Prophet Five...
They're still out there.
Hey, I thought we agreed
tonight it's just us, okay?
Oh, my God.
All right, the snoring... it kills me.
Hello?
It was you, Sydney.
Of course.
How could I have ever thought otherwise?
I saw it in you the first time we met.
You're a survivor... just like me.
And now thanks to you,
I have everything I need.
Suggestions critics insults :
aliassub@gmail.com