Marshall counted 12 sources
that make up Prophet Five.
They killed Vaughn.
I'm not sure if I can do this, dad.
It's hard being without him.
You've got an active one there,
just like mommy.
You're suggesting
that we abduct Sydney Bristow.
Prophet five has Sydney.
Synchro: Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : Raceman
Suggestions critics insults :
aliassub@gmail.com
There!
This is field agent I.D.
Black, seven, niner, three, sierra.
Confirmation Foxtrot...
Repeat, confirmation Foxtrot One.
Status, M.I.A. I'm being held aboard
a cargo freighter, registry unknown.
Do it.
Organize a deck-by-deck search
and find her.
Damn it!
What did you find out?
I have confirmation that Prophet Five
is holding Sydney.
I believe they've had designs on her
from the beginning.
They knew precisely where and when
she'd be most vulnerable.
They must have been tracking her.
Have they made any demands?
None. But whatever their intentions,
for now,
I have reason to believe
they need her alive.
Listen, Jack, we've seen Sydney
come through some bad situations.
Whatever you need, I'm here.
For now, contact everyone you know,
official or otherwise.
I'll do the same.
I'll let you know if anything comes up.
Mr. Bristow!
I just recovered a field transmission.
- It's from Sydney.
- Where is she?
This is field agent I.D.
Black, seven, niner, three, sierra.
Confirmation fox...
...repeat, confirmation foxtrot one.
Status, M.I.A. I'm being held...
- Held where? What happened?
- I don't know.
Looks like the file's
just corrupted.
I can't seem to pull 'em up.
You know what?
It's okay. I just need the tags
to triangulate the signal of origin.
Then I'll have the exact location
Sydney sent it from.
Wait a minute. You know what?
They're being deleted.
This doesn't make any sense.
It's like someone just wiped out
the archive...
Marshall, what archive?
- Whose system are you logged into?
- This must be wrong.
It's not wrong.
Gather everyone in the briefing room.
No, we haven't located her yet.
No, that won't be necessary.
Should we prepare to welcome company?
The transmission's been taken care of.
We've cleared the lower deck.
Still nothing.
Then why are you still standing here?
Moments ago, we receive
a field communication from Sydney.
>From the little we were able
to decipher,
it appears she's still being held
in the custody of Prophet Five.
However, before we were able
to resolve the entire transmission,
someone deleted it.
Someone at Langley.
Based on our current intel,
we already have reason
to believe that Prophet Five's network
has infiltrated
the intelligence agencies
of several foreign governments.
It now appears they may
have infiltrated our own.
Someone within the C.I.A.
did not want us to receive that message.
It's standard protocol
for all incoming signals
priority three and above
to be automatically backed up
on Echelon's comm. archive.
Unfortunately,
the only way to gain access
to this archive
is on the premises itself.
Not an easy task,
given security measures.
Wait, are you suggesting
that we break into C.I.A. Headquarters?
Yes.
Wouldn't it be prudent to consider
other possibilities?
Maybe the message was purged
accidentally.
We could ask Langley
for a copy of the archives.
I appreciate your concerns,
but at this point
we have no way of knowing
how deep this conspiracy reaches.
We can't risk tipping them off
to our agenda.
Effective as of this moment,
all information relating
to this task force
and its activities is to be strictly
compartmentalized
even from the C.I.A. Itself.
I understand what I'm asking
of all of you.
An action of this kind
could be considered treason.
Given that, if anyone feels
they need to take
a leave of absence,
you're free to do so,
No questions asked,
but now is the time to speak up.
All right then.
We're wheels up in an hour.
I want a visual inspection
of every container on that deck.
Post four, do you copy?
Post four, reporting in.
You tracked me with the radio.
Not really.
You're just predictable.
A woman in your condition,
shouldn't you be resting?
Thanks.
I don't plan on staying long.
Turn around. Give me your radio.
Whatever.
But you should know
that no one's coming for you.
- We intercepted your message.
- Nice try.
My message didn't go through a relay,
but directly to my people.
That's not true exactly.
Technically, it went to Langley.
That's where it was intercepted.
You're bluffing.
If you really had an undercover asset
within the C.I.A.,
Why would you risk admitting it to me?
Because you're not
getting off this ship.
Dixon just called.
They're in position.
We're ready out here.
I'd like to welcome everyone
to the C.I.A.'s
new headquarters building
here in Langley, Virginia.
Comprising 1.1 million square feet
of space and resting on 258 acres,
this building was an expansion
of the original structure
completed in 1991.
Aside from the obvious human presence,
there are over
5,000 surveillance cameras
that watch over
very inch of the complex
and chemical and biological weapons
detection sensors
that monitor the air quality
as well as various other
state-of-the-art technologies that...
if we told you, we'd have to kill you.
Now if you'll follow me, you'll notice
the commemorative plaque
off to your right.
It honors the unsung
heroes of World War II,
the intelligence gatherers of the C.I.A.
Sidewinder, we're almost ready here.
Roger that.
Near security on my way to payroll.
Hi, I have an appointment
with human resources. Emily Higgins.
Right. Just need an I.D.
Sure. Sorry.
Job interview. I'M...
- I'm a little nervous.
- I'm sure you'll do just fine.
Please place your purse on the table.
Excuse me,
do you know where payroll is?
I'm sorry, ma'am. We don't allow
camera phones on the premises.
You can pick it up
at the security office on your way out.
Okay, thanks.
The third floor.
Elevator's to your right.
Sorry, there's a problem
with my check.
Yeah, just a sec.
Ma'am, I'm actually...
- I'm kind of in A...
- Name?
Thomas Grace.
it says here you're no longer
an employee of this agency.
Yeah, that's actually why I'm here.
I've had several back checks owed to me.
I never received them.
Well, our records show
that all your checks went out,
and they were cashed.
That's impossible.
It's usually the spouse
that cashes them.
I suggest you check with your wife.
Look, I'm sure if you check
your file again,
you'll see that you're mistaken.
Mr. Grace, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize..
maybe there's something I can do here.
Sidewinder, we're logging
in to the server now.
Look, I don't have six months
to wait for the claim to be processed.
- I understand, but...
- I've got a mortgage to pay, so
could you please just...
just help me out?
Connection's established.
Sidewinder, stand by
for the access code.
All right, I'll check
with my supervisor.
Maybe he can help clear this up.
Access code is Alpha, 7,
Delta, Lima, 22.
Copy that.
I've got access.
Outrigger, I'm approaching your 20.
Copy.
I'm going to need item number two.
And here's another one of our
display items.
It looks like ordinary pocket change,
but spies used devices like these
during the cold war
to smuggle tiny microfilm and messages.
You can only imagine
what's in use today.
Oracle...
you're clear to the server room.
Call us when you get there.
- She's in. I'm done here.
- Copy that.
Log out and move
to the rendezvous point.
Affirmative.
I'm on my way.
I'm at the server room.
Guards are in position.
Copy that.
Stand by for the signal.
Merlin, you're up.
Titled "Kryptos," this sculpture
was designed in part as a monument
to the code breakers who helped
crack the German Enigma cipher.
In fact, as you can see,
the sculpture is itself a code,
apparently a very good one.
To this day, no one has been able
to decipher the message.
- Now, if we move on...
- I got it!
Sorry, It just came to me.
I play a lot of Sudoku.
Excuse me, I'll just... if you could...
I'll tell you more.
The letters that are overlaid
onto the coding sections,
well, they act as a key to the cipher.
Based off that, you just need
to transpose the letters.
Right? That's all you need to do, see?
What's that?
Maybe they found out
I decoded the message. We should run!
- Take it down a notch, Hamlet.
- Please, everyone,
we need to move quickly to the exits.
Anthrax alert!
All report to deck.
I'm in.
I need the server number
- for Syd's transmission.
- We're looking for 8577.
8577. Copy that.
I found it.
I'm pulling the archive now.
Sydney's transmission
is time-stamped 9:55 A.M.
The archive's been purged.
The message isn't here.
Could you pull the hard drive?
We still can recover the data.
Okay, hold on a sec.
It's no good. The hard drive
is patched into the security grid.
If I remove the drive,
- it'll trigger the alarm.
- Pull the hard drive.
Langley will initiate a lockdown, Jack.
We'll never get them out.
Pull the hard drive now!
I'll get you out.
Make the call, Jack.
Excuse me.
I'm going to have to ask you
to hold it right here.
We're locking down the facility.
Four in the north corridor.
Sorry, everyone. It appears
we're having a minor security incident.
No one will be able
to leave the building just yet.
A lockdown?
30 seconds ago I got a call about
an evacuation due to an Anthrax attack.
There's a big difference.
Evacuation means everyone has to leave.
Lockdown means everyone has...
No, he's with the delegation.
I'm not gonna disturb him.
And what could I tell him?
I've got a great idea.
Why don't you get your facts straight
and then call me back?
Great.
Put in a call to state. Cancel my 4:00.
And I cannot believe this,
but I have to cancel my Pilates again.
Eric, it's Jack Bristow.
Sydney's in trouble. I need your help.
What?
Whatever you need.
Outrigger, you copy?
What's going on out there?
The building's locked down.
Are you at the rendezvous point?
I'm stuck in the witness protection
archives.
The door must have sealed
because of the lockdown.
Hold your position.
I'll see what I can do.
What is it?
Think he's here to arrest us?
He looks like he's coming to arrest us.
Ambassador Utland...
- Yes.
- How are you, sir?
And you must be Mr. Cornish.
it's a pleasure to meet you, sir.
I am, Eric Weiss.
I'll be your liaison.
I apologize for the security problems
that we're having today.
Please, it's not a problem.
I understand. These things happen.
And I understand you have a meeting
on the hill in 30 minutes.
I'm here to make sure
that you make that meeting.
Thank you.
I'll escort our visitors from here.
All right, Jack briefed me.
What's going on?
Tom's trapped in witsec records.
Rachel is still
in the Echelon server facility.
You know what, witsec records
is in the northeast corridor.
This should get you in through
the door,
and Marshall and I can handle Rachel.
- It's good to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
Tom?
What were you doing here?
I got detoured.
I needed someplace to hide.
Come on, we need to move.
Okay, got it.
That's not good.
- Where is she?
- There.
Okay, what's her call sign?
- Oracle.
- Oracle, listen to me very carefully.
- Who is this?
- Right now I'm your superior.
I need you to do exactly as I tell you.
There's a guard that's about to go
right down the row that you're in.
I need you to turn left.
Make a left right now! Make a left!
Good, good, good. Okay, go straight.
Keep going straight.
- Weiss, look
- Okay, stop right there! Stop.
Marshall, how long
with that door?
Just give me 10 sec.
All right, when I say "go," run as fast
as you possibly can towards the doors
at the far end.
Don't stop.
We will have those doors open
by the time you get there.
- Okay, got it!
- Okay, go!
Sorry. I forgot to hit "enter."
Okay, now go.
How'd it go?
Not well.
Don't worry.
He's with us.
Eric Weiss.
Rachel Gibson.
Thank you for the help back there.
Oh, my pleasure.
Any luck with Sydney's message?
They wiped the backups.
We may be able to run data recovery
on this,
but if they went to all the trouble
of deleting the message,
I don't think they'd be careless enough
to leave any traces behind.
Better get a move on.
Take this tunnel to the end,
it leads at the southeast edge
of the complex.
I have to go back inside
to delete the surveillance footage.
Oh, if you hear anything
about Sydney...
- We will.
- Okay, and one more thing.
Next time, just call.
Care to tell me exactly
where we're going?
This ship has lifeboats.
We're taking one.
Good idea. You'll be spotted
the minute you step on the deck.
Not if you order your men
to search the lower decks.
Do it.
Get in there, go.
Make a sound, and you're dead.
Something's wrong, isn't it?
Move.
Whatever you say,
but you don't look so good.
Stop, stop!
Come on.
What is this?
Why is this here?
You have until three
to start giving me some answers.
One...
two...
Oh, no, no, no, no, you must not move.
What are you doing to me?
Just be still.
The doctor is on the way.
What doctor?
Just tell me what's wrong.
Is something wrong with my baby?
I need to tell them you're awake.
You should be still.
Wait, please don't go.
- I will come back soon.
- Wait!
You can crack into this hard drive
and find Sydney's transmission?
Uh, cracking Langley's encryption
won't be a problem.
I wrote a program that can handle
anything under 512-bit encoding.
I can't seem to recover
Sydney's transmission.
Whoever wiped it
used a secure deletion program.
Basically, it rewrites
random junk over it hundreds of times.
Yeah, but the original data's
still there,
so it should be retrievable, right?
Well, yeah, if I had
an electron microscope
and two weeks, maybe.
I think we found something
in the hard copies of the server logs.
Check line 522.
Looks like an authorization tag.
That's what I thought.
Well, this tag has an "A.B." Prefix.
But that means
whoever authorized the deletion
of Sydney's transmission
had Alpha Black clearance.
What's alpha black clearance?
Alpha Black is the highest
clearance level within the C.I.A.
If Prophet Five has ties to the C.I.A.'s
upper echelons,
that would give them unlimited access
to all classified operations,
undercover agent rosters,
our entire infrastructure.
The good news is
that if whoever deleted Sydney's message
had Alpha Black clearance,
well, that narrows our list of suspects
down to just a handful of guys.
Only seven people
in the entire agency have it,
all of them division directors.
Aside from that,
the only other thing
that these guys have in common--
they were all assigned
a modified version
of the standard S.T.U.,
- A secure cell phone.
- What are you thinking?
Well, each cell phone
broadcasts a unique device I.D.
Now it took some digging,
but I was able to match
the Alpha Black authorization
code from the server
logs to the cell phone I.D.
Of the person in question.
So does that mean
we know who it belongs to?
Not exactly.
I mean, for security purposes,
Langley doesn't put names to numbers,
but if you can get within just 50 feet
of that person's cell phone,
I might be able to scan it
and see if it matches.
We'd have our guy.
We could divide into teams,
put all 7 of them
under surveillance.
That could take days.
Whatever Prophet Five
has planned for Sydney,
we can assume we don't have much time.
I have an idea.
- Gentlemen.
- Jack!
It's been a long time.
How's life underground treating you?
Good,
always full of surprises.
I can imagine.
Can't say I miss it.
Scanner's hot.
Jack... we've got connection here.
So, Jack, you care to enlighten us
as to why
you called an operations meeting
at 8:00 on a Friday?
I didn't call you all here
for an operations meeting.
Given that all of you
have Alpha Black clearance,
most of you may already
be aware that A.P.O.
has been investigating an organization
known as Prophet Five.
What may, however, come as news to you
is we have reason to believe
that someone within our own agency
is in collusion with this organization.
Someone with Alpha Black clearance.
What have we got so far?
Four down, three to go.
Still nothing.
The reason I've gathered you all here,
if it isn't obvious by now,
only seven people in the entire agency
have this level of clearance,
and all of them are sitting
in this room.
Oh, come on!
Jack, this is absurd.
Are you suggesting that one of us
is working for a terrorist organization?
That's exactly what I'm suggesting.
I got a match.
Jack, we've got a signal match.
One of you is working for Prophet Five,
and we have your number.
That's enough. This meeting's over.
Go.
Jack, what in the hell are you doing?
Tell me where Sydney is.
Do yourself a favor. Stand back.
I'm going to give you one chance.
- Where are they holding my daughter?
- What the hell...
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wrong answer.
Stop, for god's sakes, Jack!
I sealed the doors!
Where she is?
You're crazy!
Answer me!
"the Athena"...
cargo ship...
Where is the ship?
The north Atlantic...
Did you get that?
We got it, Jack.
We're on it.
- What is that?
- Something to make you relax.
But...
Marshall, can you find the cargo ship
where Sydney's being held?
There are miles and miles
of ocean here.
It's like looking for a needle
in a haystack.
What if you patched into the radarsat?
Overlay it on the optical feed.
Right. That's genius!
Okay, it looks like
multiple radar returns.
No, ignore those.
It's a commercial shipping route,
heavily patrolled.
They wouldn't run the risk
of random inspection.
Right.
There, that one.
It's in international waters.
A ship that size wouldn't typically
be that far out.
Got it.
- Hello?
- We have a hit.
Marshall's uploading the coordinates
to your onboard G.P.S.
You're clear to go.
Understood.
All right, let's move out!
What else besides abdominal pains?
Dizziness. Her complexion was pale.
Any trouble breathing?
Yes.
Hello, Sydney.
- You...
- I understand you've had some trouble.
Don't worry.
We're going to take care of it.
It's good you called me.
Let's take this off her.
You bitch.
What did you do to me?
My job as your doctor,
Sydney, nothing more.
I understand this must be hard
to accept,
but it would be much better
if you could just relax now.
Sydney I'm going to need you
to hold very still.
I have to draw a sample
of amniotic fluid.
You can go to hell.
Please, I need you to listen.
This is a delicate procedure.
Any sudden movements could risk
the health of your baby.
Please don't.
This might pinch a little.
Prep the room.
We need to start right away.
Sierra one, what's your status?
We're en route and closing!
E.T.A. 2300.
You're sure she gave us
the wrong information?
What if you...
no, I'm not doubting you.
I-I just don't see how that's possible.
What do you mean? How far out?
I'm not sure that gives us
enough time for what...
Of course.
Yes.
I'll let you know as soon as it's done.
Our timetable's changed.
You're going to need to work quickly.
- We're just about to start.
- How long?
About an hour.
We've got about 40 minutes.
Let me know the second you're finished.
Please...
Just relax.
I'm going to take care of you.
I don't like this. Where are they?
They've probably taken
a defensive position below deck.
We'll split into teams.
You start clearing from the aft forward.
We'll come around the other side.
- Outflank them.
- Let's go!
Where is everybody?
It's all clear.
Bravo, we're all clear here.
They must have known we were coming.
The ship's been abandoned.
Not entirely.
What do you mean?
Come down to the infirmary.
Syd, are you all right?
I can't move.
Get the helicopter ready. We'll need
to medevac her out of here.
Dixon, is the baby okay?
It's going to be okay, Syd.
I'm sure you're quite pleased
with Sydney's return.
You, however,
made a grave error, Mr. Sloane.
You should have contacted us
the second your agency
identified our ship.
If you recall, I tried contacting you
earlier regarding this matter.
- I was told...
- Don't play games with me.
I am aware of your fondness
for power,
so I imagine this arrangement
is less than desirable for you.
If you value your own
daughter's life,
from this point on,
you are not to take a single action
without clearing it
with us first.
As far as you're concerned,
we own you.
Is that clear enough?
Yeah, yes, that is perfectly clear.
You may consider this a victory
right now,
but you should understand
every action has consequences.
We'll be in touch soon.
- Hey, do you have a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
You know that decryption program
I wrote?
Somebody accessed it
when I was out of my office.
We should tell Jack about the breach.
With all that happened...
I was able to recover the data
that was decrypted.
When you were in Langley,
tom accessed the witsec archives.
- Amanda Grace.
- Yeah.
Did you know he was married?
No.
This is the guy that did it.
Yeah,
I think that's who tom was looking for.
Hallo, Karl.
Dr. Meither to C.C.U.
Sweetheart...
I'm sorry it took me so long.
They just keep running tests,
but nobody's...
they won't tell me...
I know. They wanted to be sure.
And?
It's okay.
Whatever it is, I can handle it.
It seems there was a crisis
with your pregnancy
while you were on that ship.
Sydney, the baby's fine.
It's fine.
What they did to you on the boat,
you were suffering from something
called placental abruption.
They corrected the problem.
They weren't harming the baby.
They were saving its life.
Why?
Why would they do that?
We're not sure.
We don't know what it means,
but I promise you,
we'll get to the bottom of it.
Oh, Sydney.
While I was on the ship, they...
they tried to extract information,
but I lied to them.
Not here.
Mr. Bristow, I'm sorry, sir.
That's time.
It's nothing.
It's just a small matter
I need to tend to.
www.forom.com