It looks like Austin is going with...
...an astronaut.
And Kelly's drawing a police officer.
I'm not sure "elephant"
counts as a job, Laurence.
What about you, Sydney?
Are you having trouble getting started?
That's okay.
I can help you.
I want you to close your eyes
and tell me the very first thing
that pops into your mind
when I ask you this question:
What do you want to be
when you grow up?
I just spoke with Zurich.
Sloane hit the twelve. They're all dead.
- He's solidifying power.
- I must contact Sydney.
Get Marshall and Rachel.
We'll rendezvous at Mikro storage.
Trust no one else.
You'll be all right.
Rachel, we have to leave.
We don't have time to mourn right now.
One, two... three.
Come on! Come on!
One, two, three...
Come on! You're stronger than this!
Excuse me.
Something's happened.
Your mother was in an accident.
Her car skidded off the road, and...
She's gone.
Your mother...
She's dead.
sweetheart, I need you
to be strong right now.
I need you to be... strong.
It's okay. You're okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I saw the news reports on Los Angeles.
Good work.
I'm not certain "good" is
the proper word for it, but thank you.
I've dispatched a team to the location
you acquired at Mt. Subasio.
I want to be airborne
as soon as they find something.
Understood.
Were you able to make contact
with our friend in Hong Kong?
Yes. She sends her regards.
Should I tell her we have a deal?
Let her know the transports will leave
just as soon as they're ready.
Am I to understand that we're still
going through with this?
Don't tell me you're having
second thoughts.
Of course not.
It's just it's not every dayone gets
to be a part of global genocide.
If I can get a signal down here, I may
be able to tap into Langley's network.
I can spoof the origin.
They won't be able to trace the hack.
Sloane will try to seize control
of Prophet 5's operations
as quickly as possible.
We should look to identify
any unusual activity in their holdings.
It's me. We're in Siena.
So Sydney is with you?
Yeah.
We're both okay.
Thank God.
We've had a situation here.
Homebase has been compromised.
Tom... didn't make it.
Stay at the safe house. Once we gather
some more information,
we'll forward it to you there.
Got it.
How is she?
She took a pretty big hit,
but she'll bounce back.
Dad?
You did this?
Can you show me how you did it?
- What?
- It's a test,
called an "indicator."
People in my line of work use it
to identify people with a highly developed sense
of 3-dimensional reasoning.
Very few people can do it.
I can't do it.
You can't?
What it means, Sydney, is...
You are a very special...
...girl.
Twelve hours ago,
two intercontinental
cruise missiles were stolen
from a storage facility in Moscow.
We think it's Sloane?
Whatever he's up to,
he said it was too late to be stopped.
He also said that he'd wipe out
everyone at A.P.O.
He was wrong.
Still, how can we find him?
It's impossible.
We don't have a single lead.
- We can't trust the C.I.A.
- Sydney, stop, alright?
Let's not overlook the fact
that you basically died today.
You and I have gotten pretty good
at impossible.
I'm gonna have to deal with this wound.
I don't have any anesthetic.
It's gonna hurt.
Just hold still.
Sorry.
Why would Sloane steal the missiles?
- What?
- He just wiped out the Twelve, right?
Which means that he controls
their assets.
He wouldn't steal missiles.
He'd just buy them on the black market.
I think I know how to find him.
We start with the money.
If we can hack into the system,
we can I.D. who the payoffs went to.
Then all we need are phone records.
If I'm right, they'll lead us
right to Sloane...
Or at least, someone
he's been working with.
We know you're working
with Arvin Sloane,
and we know about the I.C.B.M.S
he's recently acquired.
What we don't know is where they are
or where they're headed.
Now I'm well aware that you're tough,
that you've been conditioned
to withstand torture.
But I have something you don't have.
I have your former best friend.
And I know what you're afraid of.
If I were you,
I would stay extremely still.
She has no idea
where those missiles are.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
What she does know:
Sloane is planning to target two cities
with high civilian concentrations.
He's not interested in the devastation.
He plans to profit off
the reconstruction.
Sloane controls Prophet 5's network,
communications, pharmaceuticals,
finance, he'll make billions.
It gets worse.
Sloane's in Mongolia.
Put on your dancing shoes.
We are going out tonight.
I can't tonight.
"Can't" is not an option.
Charlie got us passes
for that new club in Silverlake.
That job fair is tonight.
I really wanna go.
Job fair? What? Syd.
You have four years to figure out
what kind of job you want.
I just had a meeting with my advisor,
and she yelled at me 'cause
I haven't picked a major yet.
Education. Done.
You can be a teacher like your mom.
I mean, you always talked about
how happy she was.
I thought about that,
but I've always thought about
teaching as my safety net.
Teaching's no safety net.
You know how dangerous it is
to be a teacher?
Kids bring knives to school these days.
I hate the thought
that I could make a decision now
that would affect the rest of my life.
Well, I say go with education.
Charlie is bringing a friend tonight,
Danny something.
- We'll pick you up at 8:00.
- I'll see you later.
I was hoping I might have
a moment of your time.
Tell Dixon we'll touch base
as soon as we cross
into Mongolian airspace.
Marshall and I are gonna hack
into the N.R.O.,
See if we can use
their optical satellites
to locate the missiles.
Rachel, listen.
Prophet 5 is gone.
Your family is no longer in danger.
You don't have to do this anymore.
People have given their lives for this.
I'm not gonna bail on them now.
I'm in this until it's over.
Of course, if we don't find Sloane,
that may not be very long from now.
Did it have to be so filthy?
I mean, really, if Rambaldi
can prophesize the future,
he might have advised me
not to wear $500 shoes.
Structural imaging shows
that there's a chamber
about 200 feet below us.
That's quite a climb.
You needn't worry.
The next step is for me alone.
At last,
after almost 30 years.
Is it everything you imagined?
I'm so glad you're here.
If I didn't have someone
to share this with,
I may have doubted my own eyes.
You're talking to your dead daughter.
This is an odd time
to question your sanity.
Perhaps.
So that's it?
All this time, that's what you wanted.
This, sweetheart,
this is what everybody
has always wanted.
And I've found it.
It's over, Sloane.
Correct me if I'm wrong, Mr. Vaughn,
but aren't you supposed to be dead?
I suppose we'll have to rectify that.
Well, then,
it appears we have a predicament.
Don't move.
No! Sydney, don't.
What is this, Sloane?
Sydney, please don't be rash.
Give me one reason why
I shouldn't destroy this right now.
Suppose I were to give you
two good reasons.
He's gonna strike the U.S.
Can you purge the virus?
No, not from here.
But I did pinpoint the origin.
Someone uploaded it from Hong Kong.
Who's in Hong Kong?
Who are you protecting?
Should I get the snake?
Don't.
Sloane had to call in a partner.
He needed something he didn't have.
What's that?
Hand me the sphere, Sydney.
I'll let you all walk out of here.
I won't insult you with pretense,
Sydney.
We know each other too well for that.
Oh, I know you're trying
to figure a way out.
Just hand over the sphere,
and I will let you all walk away.
If I give this to you,
what's to guarantee
you won't shoot us anyway?
Despite what you may think,
I'm not heartless.
Come on, take my offer.
It appears that Vaughn is back.
Go. Be a family.
Frankly, I don't think
you have any other option.
If you want this, we'll walk out of here
together, and then we'll talk.
Well, remember, Sydney,
it's your choice.
Dad!
Dad? Dad?
Dad? Are you home?
That's right, they're having problems
with their tail rudder controls.
Yeah. Okay, well, I'll get back to you.
Hello, Sydney.
What's this?
Open it.
You've been paying my tuition.
I thought I should at least help out.
What'd you do, rob a bank?
Sort of.
I got a job at a bank.
It's just part-time for now,
at least. It's...
It's, a French bank.
It's called Crédit Dauphine.
They have a very international
clientele.
Crédit Dauphine?
Yeah, they have 12 branches
around the world.
You're already working there?
About a month.
I wanted to make sure
it would work out before I told you.
A month. Good.
It's not too late to quit.
- What?
- Sydney, listen to me.
I'm not quitting this job.
I like it. I'm good at it.
I imagine you are.
That's not the point.
What is the point?
- God, if mom were here, she...
- If your mother was here...
If your mother was here,
she would want you to focus
on school, which is
what you're going to do.
I didn't come to ask your permission.
- I've already made my decision.
- This is not your decision to make.
Sydney, come back...
- Right here.
- All right, Syd.
You're okay, you're okay.
It's okay.
I'm gonna go call for help, okay?
Okay, just be still.
Look, you're gonna be okay.
We have a problem. Jack's been shot.
- How bad?
- It's critical.
We need air support.
Contact Salim Behari in Ulaanbaatar.
Have him send a medevac unit.
Tell them to hurry.
Dad, keep talking to me.
I'm doing fine. It's...
It's just...
It's just a scratch.
I'm just gonna take a look.
You're gonna be okay.
Chopper's on its way.
Should be a half-hour.
- Did you hear that?
- Yeah
Listen.
Sloane's dead, Sark got away.
He's got the artifact.
I think we know where he's going.
Sorry.
Medevac's on its way. How's he doing?
His heart rate's up.
I think the bullet penetrated his lung.
He's not getting enough air.
Sloane has a partner.
We know who's behind this.
I have the artifact.
I'm on my way.
Good.
See that it gets here intact.
Listen to me.
Dad, you have been shot in the chest.
The medical team is on their way. You...
I can't risk moving you. Right?
I can't...
Vaughn,
get the transport ready.
Wait, Vaughn...
Wait, Vaughn, wait!
Dad, what are you doing?
You can't go anywhere.
Sydney, your mother's not the type
to make empty threats.
If she's acquired missiles,
she intends to use them.
You can't even stand up straight.
How do you expect to confront mom?
I'm not coming with you.
You have to go to Hong Kong.
There's no other way.
I am not leaving you here.
You're the only one
who can get to Irina in time.
who can beat her.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
I never wanted this life for you,
you know.
I never wanted you to bear this kind
of responsibility, but you...
you were a very...
...difficult little girl...
You were far too driven,
far too strong to let someone
like me stop you from becoming
who you are.
Dad, the medical team is coming.
- If you'll just sit tight...
- Sydney, listen to me.
There's no one
in this world
that can do the things that you can do.
I can hold out until help arrives,
but you have to go.
You have to stop your mother.
Okay...
Just...
Okay, good. Just...
Keep applying pressure, please.
You... you can't afford
to lose more blood.
Just get moving.
I love you, dad.
I love you, Sydney.
I don't want to leave you.
G o.
Did everything go according to plan?
Your daughter arrived,
mucked things up a bit.
Sloane's dead,
and we lost the tomb.
But the artifact's intact.
There's a reason my fees are so high.
Sloane's death doesn't change
our agenda.
Contact controls.
As soon as the satellites are down,
launch the missile strikes.
Have you decided on the final targets?
Washington and London.
Right away.
What's our status?
Mil-sat one just hit atmosphere.
The rest of the satellites
are right behind it.
Initiate the countdown.
Oh, my God.
They've started the launch.
So that's it.
It's the Horizon, isn't it?
You shot the man I loved.
You betrayed my trust.
You risked my daughter's life,
all for that.
I don't expect you to understand.
We're very different, Sydney.
You still cling to naive ideals.
I learned, at a very young age,
the only currency worth
anything in this world is power.
And the Horizon gives you that?
You've never seen Rambaldi
for what he is.
You dismissed his work
as the labor of a madman.
You blind yourself
to his true potential.
I've spent a lifetime acquiring power.
With this...
And I'll never have to give it up.
Rambaldi is life, Sydney.
Through him, we can live forever.
I offered you an out.
I gave you your daughter.
I was hoping you'd settle down,
leave me to my affairs.
You don't know me very well, do you?
Sadly, I think I do.
After all, I'm still your mother.
That doesn't mean anything.
Not anymore.
I am through being disappointed by you.
I hate that it's come to this.
I suppose it had to.
I've come too far
to let anything get in my way.
Then you'll have to go through me first.
You wanted to see me, sir?
I've been reviewing your evaluations
since you arrived at SD-6.
To a letter, they're nothing
short of exemplary.
I've upgraded your clearance,
and I'm considering
promoting you to field officer.
Really?
Now, Sydney, I want to know
that you have given this job
its proper consideration.
I realize that you have
a romantic notion
of the espionage trade, but this job...
...is more than just brush passes
and dead drops.
You will be facing life and death
situations on a regular basis.
Do you understand that?
You will be forced to make decisions
that will haunt you
for the rest of your life.
This job requires sacrifice,
and you need to know
that you are able to live with that.
I can, sir.
For as long as I can remember,
I have been searching...
for what I'm supposed to do,
for what I'm supposed to be.
This is my purpose.
It's in my blood.
It's who I am.
I have never been so sure
of anything in my life.
Why are you fighting me on this?
The defense satellites are destroyed.
The stars will fall from the sky.
Even if you manage to beat me
on this rooftop,
it's still too late to stop the launch.
You think I came here alone?
Sir, beginning final preparations.
Excellent.
Proceed according to...
It appears we have a predicament.
You did it.
You were right all along.
I will never forget your sacrifice.
I promise.
The Horizon is gone.
Your mother is probably dividing up
my spoils as we speak.
Then we should get moving.
We don't have to hurry anymore, Nadia.
We have all the time in the world.
Give me the override codes.
I don't have the codes, I swear.
- You shot me!
-Yeah,
and I'll keep shooting
until you either give me the codes
or bleed to death. Your choice.
You know, I didn't want any of this.
Mass extermination isn't exactly
my passion, Michael.
I'm a businessman.
You know, I simply wanted to come out
on the winning end.
I'll give you the codes,
but you have to let me go after I do.
Codes first, then we negotiate.
3-9-8-alpha-4-tango-6-4-7.
Come on. Come on!
Launch aborted!
I'm afraid I can't allow you to be such
a complication in my life any longer.
For whatever it's worth,
I truly do love you.
I owe you an apology, Arvin.
I never gave your faith in Rambaldi
the credit it deserved.
There's no need to apologize, Jack.
You're a practical man.
I'd always admired that in you.
Jack, I didn't wanna shoot you.
Sydney forced my hand.
She can be very...
stubborn at times.
You're dying.
I can help you.
I don't want your help, Arvin.
You've...
caused my daughter so much pain.
I could have prevented it.
I won't
continue to make that mistake.
I think you've overestimated
your position, Jack.
You can't hurt me anymore.
True.
But I can keep you down here with me.
What are you doing?
You beat death, Arvin.
But you couldn't beat me.
The glass won't hold you.
Mom, you need to come back.
Mom.
You can make it. Give me your hand.
I'm sorry, Sydney.
Mom, come back!
I can't move.
I don't think there's anything I can do.
Well...
as you've said, you have
all the time in the world.
Unfortunately, I think
you'll have to spend it here.
Well, at least you're here with me.
No, Nadia, don't leave me here.
Daddy!
Uncle Dixon!
How are you, sweetie?
Deputy director.
Please, this far from Langley,
you can just call me "sir."
Good to see you.
Did you have a hard time
finding this place?
What, are you kidding?
I had an impossible time
finding this place.
Well, I guess that's sort of the point,
right?
Hello, stranger.
Hello, Sydney.
And this must be...
Hello, Jack.
Marshall sends his best.
He wanted to tag along,
but Carrie’s stuck at home on bed rest.
Another baby?
Oh, God, I don't know how she does it.
This makes four. All boys.
Well, come on inside.
You'll just have to pardon the mess.
Speaking of mess, didn't someone
promise to finish unpacking
her toys before dinner?
Go on.
Go on, Isabelle.
Can I get you something to drink?
Why do I get the feeling
this isn't a purely social call?
Truth be told, I could use
some field assistance.
A merc team hit the national research
facility in Paris yesterday.
I need someone to intercept the seller
and retrieve the hard drive.
Can't you put Rachel on it?
She's on deep cover assignment
in Santiago. I can't risk pulling her.
Besides, this job has...
...sentimental value.
Don't look at me.
You're the one that let him go.
We've already prepared
the mission specs.
Low risk insertion,
simple areas.
Who knows, it could be fun.
That's what you say every time
you show up on my doorstep.
Then next, you know, I'm jumping over
canals and tree and shield while Napalm
explodes around me.
Yes. That's how I define "fun".
Why don't we finish this conversation
over dinner?
And you haven't lived
until you've seen our sunset.
Isabelle, dad and I
are going for a walk.
What have you been doing back there?
Nothing, mom.
Transcript : Raceman
www.forom.com
Sync :
Anyone, Sixe, Guilamu.
Suggestions critics insults :
aliassub@gmail.com