Previsouly on Alias...
Hello, Arvin.
Hello, Gordon.
So you're my mysterious benefactor.
Your security clearance
hasn't been reinstated.
My chances of returning to A.P.O.
are slim.
I need you at A.P.O.
I had to dig through my friends
yesterday
because of Gordon Dean.
If I can help you stop him,
then that's what I need to do.
Hey, dad, Fiona wants to know
if I can come over and study for awhile.
Maybe tomorrow night, okay kiddo?
I left another message.
Look, you know she's always travelling.
I mean, where is she now, Europe?
Yeah, but she usually calls.
Come... that's okay. I got it.
It's probably just, you know,
a circuit breaker.
How much do they know?
Not much...
that this is a government facility,
that they're here
for their own protection.
- I've ruined their lives.
- That's not true.
They can't go home.
They can't go back to work.
They can't even say good-bye
to their friends.
Because it's not safe. You know that.
There were taps on their phones.
There was surveillance equipment.
Witness protection is the best way
to ensure their safety.
They say I won't even be able
to call them.
How am I supposed to do this alone?
You do it because
you don't have a choice...
because you want the world to be safe
for the people you love.
I know some people think I'm crazy,
still working like this,
but I can't go home and sit there
and just be pregnant.
Not when the men who killed Vaughn
are still out there.
It's my responsibility to stop them
so this baby can be safe...
so you can be with your family.
We're kind of a weird family.
We actually like each other.
Then go in there
and let them see you're okay.
That's all they care about.
Okay.
My God! Rachel!
I wanted to call. I just... I couldn't.
We were worried
something had happened to you.
Something did happen,
and that's why you're here.
Where do I begin?
Okay...
Rachel Gibson's family has been moved
to a witness protection program.
We knew that might happen.
I will not hurt Rachel
or anyone else from A.P.O.
It was not part of our agreement.
Our agreement is whatever I say it is.
I'm the one who got you out of prison,
and I can easily put you back.
Let me say this again.
I will not hurt those people.
I'm not telling you to...
not yet, at least.
But we both know you'll do
whatever it takes to save your daughter.
If that means you have to hurt
a few people along the way, so be it.
- Are we finished?
- Almost.
Have you heard of a weapons designer
named Janos Vak?
No.
We've been after him
for some time. He's disappeared.
I want you to use
your resources at A.P.O. and find him.
What would your colleagues do
if they knew you answered to me...
that you were betraying them
on a daily basis?
Same thing I hope to do to you someday.
Call me when you find Vak.
Now that Arvin's returned
in the capacity of Assistant Director,
I've asked him to read
Rachel Gibson's debriefing.
I believe his
unique insights
into a covert organization like The Shed
will be extremely useful to us.
Thank you, Jack.
This is an extremely well insulated
organization.
Of all the names
mentioned in the debrief,
there was only one
that I recognized immediately...
a weapons designer named Janos Vak.
Mr. Vak is a Hungarian national.
For the past decade, he has specialized
in designing targeting software.
His present obsession...
he calls it "lasso technology."
D.O.D.'s been worried about this.
It's a software program that would allow
an incoming missile to be
electronically intercepted
and redirected.
Right. Basically,
you could lasso a missile
that was headed
for a military target, say
in the Middle East, and then
redirect it to Switzerland, you know?
And then the Swiss call,
and they're like,
"Hey, we're neutral, remember?"
Thank you, Marshall.
I think we all understand.
Right. That was just a hypothetical...
Based on Ms. Gibson's statement,
Gordon Dean has been trying
to locate Vak for the past six months.
Arvin has suggested, and I agree,
that if we can find Vak first,
we can then use him as bait
to catch Gordon Dean.
In the past, he has been known
to frequently partner
with an Algerian arms broker.
Evidently, they had a meeting
a few months ago.
Nobody has heard from Vak since.
The Algerian underworld is particularly
difficult to penetrate.
I think I know someone who can do it.
- Renée Rienne.
- Yeah.
Make contact with her.
See if she can get a lead on Janos Vak.
Sydney, I haven't had a chance
to thank you
for the letter of recommendation
you wrote to the tribunal.
I know it helped persuade the judges
regarding my release.
You're welcome.
Look, there's something
I need to confess to you,
and I hope you don't judge me
too harshly for it.
Every day, I go to the hospital
to visit Nadia.
I get off at her floor,
talk to the doctors.
And yet, I cannot set foot
into her room.
I can't bear to see her hooked up
to all those machines,
knowing that it's my fault.
I know you'll do
everything in your power
to find a cure for Nadia.
Yes, I will.
I will do whatever it takes
to save my daughter.
Translation : Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Guilamu
Suggestions critics insults : aliassub@gmail.com
www.forom.com
Sorry.
No, you can use the bag. I'm done.
No, I don't really like to work out
around other people.
Hey... I could use somebody
to spar with.
I don't really... spar.
I don't either.
Which is why
I could really use your help.
Don't want to get my ass
kicked in the field.
What do you say?
How many fights you been in?
I don't know. Enough.
You win?
Of course.
Mostly.
Why, what did you hear?
Nothing. I've just never been
in any real fights.
I kind of want to know what to do.
Not that. Don't ever do
that spinning kung fu crap.
You'll get yourself killed.
Okay, fine. What should I be doing?
All right.
For real?
- I fight dirty.
- Dirty?
Go for the eyes, the throat, the nuts.
The nuts?
Cause as much damage, inflict
as much pain as humanly possible.
I don't know if I can do that.
Well, then you shouldn't be here.
I'm serious! Look,
everybody is taking care of you.
If they can't depend on you...
just go pack up your playthings!
Go home to mom and...
That was better.
I want to see more of that.
Tom Grace.
Got it.
Briefing in 15.
Renée located the Algerian arms dealer.
The lasso technology
is no longer a rumor.
Janos Vak designed a program
to intercept and redirect missiles.
According to the arms dealer,
three months ago,
Vak met with a Chinese official
who bought the new weapon.
Do we know where Vak is now?
No one's seen him since the meet.
He's just dropped off the planet.
Which is why we're going
to pursue the Chinese official.
His name is General Li Yum Sung,
and he's staying
at the Chinese consulate in Bombay.
The General is marrying
an Indian woman next month.
The consulate is throwing them
an engagement party.
I've checked with our contact
in Indian intelligence.
He says the General
keeps an encrypted copy
of his contacts and schedule
in a safe in his room.
They should lead us to Vak.
Sydney, you're to break
into the General's safe
and acquire the intel.
Agents Dixon and Grace
will offer support.
Marshall and Miss Gibson
will run op tech. Good luck.
The General is still upstairs.
Doesn't the man know it's kind of hard
to break into his safe
if he's sitting right in front of it?
I don't think he's coming down tonight.
See that woman over there?
That's the General's fiancée.
She looks pretty unhappy.
I think the General
might be having second thoughts.
- Hey, Marshall?
- Go, Phoenix.
What's going on upstairs?
Wait for uno momento, por favor.
Okay, looks like all's quiet.
Just one soldier outside
the General's door,
very sharply dressed.
We've got to go about this
a different way.
Remember the prince in Bahrein?
The guy with the harem?
- Let's try and do that.
- What are you talking about?
I'll need your watch.
It's okay, I'm not really here...
Just follow my lead.
I am sorry, but I cannot allow you
to marry the other man.
You belong to me.
It is time we told the world the truth.
Our love cannot be denied.
Marry me, Naomika.
Let us share our joy with everyone!
Let go of me!
I know that you love me!
Uh, the lady said let her go.
- What?
- Let her go! Hey!
We are destined for each other, Naomika.
Tell them! Tell them!
Ours is a forbidden love!
She improvised that whole thing.
Yeah, who'd think you could turn
a pregnancy into an alias?
And in chinese.
Listen, I've had to do
little alias magic myself
to save the day a few times.
- Do you know what a spork is?
- They're letting her in.
I just need more time.
I just...
need more time.
It's okay.
It's still early.
Okay, Marshall, I'm ready.
Okay...
You know what?
I'm not getting a reading, Phoenix.
There must be too much shielding
in the building.
Are you saying you can't do it?
Well, no. Of course not.
All right, Phoenix,
this is gonna take a sec.
I need to set a relay
closer to the building
so I can boost your signal.
- Copy that.
- Got it.
I can do it. You'll need to be here
when it's activated.
It'll be faster this way.
Thanks.
Okay.
Thank you for your help.
He's not a bad guy.
He's just had his heart broken.
I'll get him home.
Thanks.
Heads up, Phoenix.
Fiancée's moving your way.
Marshall, what's the E.T.A.?
Oracle, what's your status?
- Relay's set.
- Okay.
Hang on a sec.
Great. We're at five by five. Way to go.
I've got it. I'm on my way.
I'm busted.
East side of the building.
Wait for Sydney.
Get down.
You okay?
If by okay you mean freaked
and embarrassed, then yeah, I'm great.
Finding everything okay?
Yes, thank you.
Oh, I'd like to get this, please.
Okay, great.
We get so many dads
in the store these days.
I don't think my husband
ever bought so much as a diaper.
Yeah.
My dad wasn't exactly hands-on either.
What about your husband?
Is he doing his part?
He's been great.
Wishes he could do more.
I love hearing that.
Times sure have changed.
Yeah.
Hello.
You altered a suit for me.
Here's the ticket.
Oh, yes, why don't you wait in the back,
and I'll bring it to you?
Thank you.
You should've told me
about the Chinese Consulate
before your team went in.
There was no reason
to complicate things.
Anyway, I assumed that you wanted A.P.O.
to do the heavy lifting.
You don't get to assume anything.
Did you locate Janos Vak?
The intel was encrypted.
I'll have an answer for you
before the end of the day.
Call me when you do.
I don't have time to explain.
Yeah, she's here now, thank you.
- Hey.
We found Vak.
He's secluded on an oil platform
in the South China Sea
while he finishes his software program.
Marshall's still pinpointing
the exact coordinates.
Great. How are we going in?
We're not.
We're backup.
- Who's my dad sending?
- Rachel Gibson.
Rachel?
He's sending her in solo?
Why would he do that?
The Chinese government has suspended
all shore leave for the men
working on the platform.
No one gets on or off until Vak is done.
The sole exception is that
every other weekend, Vak is allowed...
female companionship.
We can't send her in alone.
Rachel's incredibly bright.
You've seen it yourself.
You saw what happened
on our last mission. She ran.
The mission was a success, Sydney.
You may not want to hear it,
but this isn't an assignment you can do.
You know it as well as I do.
She's not ready.
At least, delay the mission a few weeks.
Just give her time to train.
That's not an option.
If we're going to use Vak and his weapon
as bait to catch Gordon Dean,
we can't afford to wait.
This is no different than
when you were sent back into SD-6.
It's completely different.
I had Vaughn.
And Rachel will have you.
Okay, once you see Vak alone,
you'll need to knock him out, right?
You know, I don't mean, you know,
like, rock 'em, sock 'em, knock him out.
It's more of a, um,
actually, here we go.
Okay, take a look.
Righ, this looks like a normal lipstick.
It's a very nice shade of red.
I think it would look good...
but, anyway,
touch it anywhere on his skin,
it'll knock him out
for at least two hours.
By the time he wakes up,
he'll think he had the time of his life.
You... you'll be on a chopper
halfway home.
Oh, and, also...
I spring-loaded an ice pick into here.
You know, just in case.
But you're probably not gonna...
need that.
I mean, I'm sure you'll be...
you'll be fine.
Are you about ready?
I've been going to the firing range
every night
so that when the time came,
I'd be ready.
Of course, on my first solo mission,
I have to go in unarmed.
Rachel...
Jack wouldn't send you in
if he didn't have complete faith
in your ability to succeed.
I appreciate you saying that,
but I know what everyone is thinking.
I'm the new girl.
I panicked on the last mission.
And everybody is asking whether or not
I can do it. And the truth is...
I don't know.
I'm terrified.
But I'm more terrified of not trying.
So...
I'm gonna put on my strappy shoes
and my teeny dress, and I'm gonna try.
and by this time tomorrow,
we'll know whether I can do it or not.
Janos Vak has been found.
The details are in here.
A.P.O. is send in your former associate
Rachel Gibson.
She's going in solo
to get the weapons design.
Gibson?
- Alone?
- Once she acquires it I'll swap it out.
I'll get you the real program.
Did he just say they're sending Rachel?
I don't trust Sloane.
We're not gonna wait.
I want you to get the weapon yourself.
Is there a problem?
It'll just be strange
if Rachel and I cross paths.
She thought I was her best friend.
Look, if we could've convinced her
to play on our side, we would have.
But things didn't go that way.
So if I run into her?
Show her the professional courtesy
of putting a bullet in her head.
This is a mistake.
I've never done anything like this
with the wig and the dress and...
What am I gonna say to him?
Well, it isn't what you'd say.
Remember, you're playing a character.
It's what she would say.
Who was the sluttiest girl
in your high school?
Mandy Camarillo.
You didn't have to think very hard
on that one.
Tramp stole my date at junior prom.
She had red hair and a pierced tongue.
Okay, so you're Mandy Camarillo,
and Janos Vak is your prom date.
Just say what she'd say.
You're not gonna be alone, Rachel.
Not for a second.
I'll be on comms the whole time,
the way Vaughn was for me.
It helps a lot...
having you.
I can do this, right?
Absolutely.
Sydney?
Okay, I'm with you, Rachel,
just breathe.
You're so cute.
They didn't tell me you'd be so cute.
You do speak English, don't you?
I mean, they told me
you would speak english.
Of course, English. I love English.
Nice to meet you.
I am Janos.
Ray-- Mandy.
Raymandy?
A beautiful name.
So this is where you live, huh?
It's pretty sweet.
Only for a few more days.
My business here is almost done.
You must get very lonely.
Well, yes, which is why
I'm so happy to see you.
Perhaps you would be more comfortable
over here on the bed, Raymandy.
No, I'm, uh, I'm good.
Come on, Rachel. What would Mandy do?
Do you know how to make daiquiris?
- I have champagne.
- Even better.
Idiot.
Uh-oh.
- What do you mean, "uh-oh?"
- I dropped my lipstick.
Not a problem,
your lips are absolutely perfect
just the way they are.
Don't let him kiss you.
You're the one in charge.
Let me show you.
Has baby been bad?
This is gonna be too easy, Rachel.
Raymandy, you're driving me crazy!
Did I say you could talk?
You've been a very bad boy.
I'm sorry.
But you know what?
I'm gonna be honest with you.
This whole "baby talk" thing
kinda creeps me out.
So I'm just gonna cut to the chase,
okay?
I gotta go.
- Downloading now.
- You're doing great.
Phoenix, I've got the data.
I destroyed the original.
Copy that. Almost home.
Phoenix, I've got a small problem.
There's a dead soldier
and the boat's gone.
Copy that. I'm sending in
an emergency extraction. Outrigger?
We heard, Phoenix. We're on our way.
Rendezvous in approximately
five minutes.
Did you hear that, Rachel?
You're gonna be fine.
Just make your way to the helideck.
Copy that.
Surprise.
- My God, you're...
- Not dead?
I was gonna say evil.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Let's just say
we work for different teams.
You knew this whole time.
You were in on it with Dean!
I wanted to tell you.
You blew up that building
and you killed all those people.
It wasn't personal. I...
I always liked you.
It was a lie-- everything we did!
That's enough!
And now you're gonna kill me.
That's what Dean wants.
You've made it really hard for him
since you left.
Like I said--
I always liked you.
I don't want to kill you.
Just give me Vak's software program
and you walk away from this.
Rachel, we can always track Peyton
after she leaves the platform.
If you believe she'll let you live,
give her the data.
Your life is more important
than the mission.
Come on, Rachel.
You're in way over your head.
Don't make me shoot you.
Give me the disk.
Okay.
You've got two seconds. One...
Here.
You bitch!
You should've given me the disk.
You were gonna kill me anyway.
Yeah.
But I would've felt bad about it.
Now it's gonna be fun.
Still having fun?
You're late.
I told you none of my people
were to get hurt.
I do what I want, when I want.
Now where is it?
You didn't trust me
and you nearly ruined
the entire operation.
- I want the weapon.
- You don't get to have it.
That's my price for your mistake.
My mistake?
I'm not the one responsible for
100,000 deaths.
I'm not the one
dangling on the end of a fish hook.
I'm the one who decides
if the little fish
gets thrown back into the pond,
or if it gets flushed down the toilet.
Am I being clear?
You don't get Vak's weapon.
How's your daughter?
Nadia has nothing to do with this.
Sure she does.
I want a copy of the lasso software
first thing in the morning.
Your father's kind of scary.
Tell me about it.
But he said we all did good so...
No, you did great.
Thanks...
for being in my head.
You're welcome.
I know how important that voice can be.
Vaughn talked me through
all my early missions with the C.I.A.
Sometimes his voice was the only thing
that kept me going.
I wish I could've met him.
I'll see you tomorrow.
You okay?
Just having some trouble
picking the lock.
My fingers are kinda numb.
Look, you're almost home.
Just get inside and plant the bug.
That's easy for you to say.
It's 20-below out here.
You're nice and warm.
I'll tell you what,
I'll talk to Langley,
see if we can send you
someplace warm next time.
It should have a beach.
Absolutely.
I'll find a bad guy who owns
a really nice beach resort,
and you'll have to go undercover
for like, a month.
You know what?
That sounds pretty dangerous.
Maybe we both should go.
You'd do that for me?
Hey, we're in this together, right?
Translation : Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Guilamu
Suggestions critics insults : aliassub@gmail.com
www.forom.com