What is going to happen with my family?
My orders are to deliver you
to the airfield.
I have no information beyond that.
Could you find out?
Wha...
What's happening?
Why are we stopped?
It's all right. We're on our way.
Oh! They're here!
- I'm going.
- God, they're here!
Charlie-Echo-One, this is Foxfire.
We're under attack.
Don't shoot!
I'm coming out!
Don't sh...
Oh, God! Ohh!
Irina...
You've compromised our agenda, Jeffrey.
No, I...
I didn't do anything.
This is all a mistake!
Okay, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Tell me exactly what you said
to my husband.
Did you tell him about the Horizon?
No, of course not!
No! You have to believe me!
I swear!
I do believe you.
Synchro: Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : Raceman
Suggestions critics insults :
aliassub@gmail.com
Sorry to keep you waiting,
agent Bristow.
I know Langley's anxious to debrief you.
Is my baby okay?
Yes.
You're sure?
I can't imagine what you went through
on that ship.
But having said that,
the surgery they performed
probably saved the pregnancy.
You and your child are in great health,
agent Bristow.
Well, thank you.
And call me Sydney.
If you're going to deliver this baby
in the next couple of weeks,
we might as well
get to know each other.
Hi.
They told me you were done?
See you next week.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, can I borrow your phone?
- I want to get Marshall...
- the C.I.A. released your father.
They did?
Davenport confessed.
Apparently he cut a deal.
Your father wants to see us,
before you contact A.P.O.
Where is he?
Thanks.
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
- You want to go for a walk?
- Yeah.
Rain check.
I'll... find you when I'm done.
...authority here is no way in question.
This is merely temporary...
Of course. I understand that.
Davenport and I came up together.
- I'm godfather to his oldest son.
- Yeah.
How were these people able
to corrupt him?
I have no idea.
Agent Tom Grace,
this is director Devlin.
The director and his team
will be auditing
our investigation of Prophet Five.
You'll assist him, please
with whatever he needs.
- Sure, of course.
- Thank you.
I'd, uh, for starters, like to see
all your sit reports and...
operation files.
I can get you the sit reps,
but we're performing diagnostic
on the computer network.
The files will take longer.
It's... it's just routine.
Who can provide me with
admin privileges to your access logs?
That's... Rachel Gibson.
She's over there.
Thank you.
What just happened?
He wants to review
the computer transmissions
to see if anyone provided Prophet Five
with Davenport's travel route.
He thinks the leak
came from this office,
and the phone logs
will reveal who it was.
Apparently so.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
Okay, what's going on?
Why are we meeting out here?
Davenport's been killed.
His transport was ambushed.
That transport route was classified.
- The only people who knew...
- Were C.I.A.
You think Prophet Five has another mole
inside the agency?
It seems so, yes.
There's more.
As a condition of my release,
director Devlin is insisting
we suspend our investigation
of Prophet Five until Langley's
had a chance to review our findings.
We can't do that.
I agree, which means as long as Devlin
maintains a presence inside A.P.O.,
we have to stop documenting our work.
Operations will be compartmentalized
to senior staff only.
When I came to see you in the hospital,
you wanted to tell me something...
the reason Prophet Five abducted you.
When I was on their ship,
before the operation,
they performed some kind
of regression therapy.
They wanted me to remember a cipher...
Leo 47 Norte.
It was an entry on an Alliance
organization chart
Vaughn showed me years ago.
And did you give them the intel?
I changed the phrase.
That's good.
"47 Norte"?
That's a territorial designation.
It refers to France.
"Leo" designates a specific mission.
I'll review the Alliance archives.
Someone on that mission
might still be alive.
I want you on a plane to Paris.
Assuming I'm successful,
you'll be in position to act quickly.
Make contact with Renée Rienne.
Ask her to provide Dixon
with whatever documentation
he may need once he arrives.
Okay.
Then I want you to go home
and pack a bag.
- I'm moving you to a secure location.
- No.
- It's just temporary.
- Dad, don't be silly.
- I want to help.
- Help, yes, I know.
For now, you need to go underground.
Prophet Five abducted you.
We can't risk them doing it again.
Don't blame your dad, Syd.
He's only trying to protect you.
Yeah.
What?
Do you remember what Dean said?
That Prophet Five had plans for me.
They saved this baby for a reason.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe that's why Jack wants you
in a safe house.
I can fend for myself.
But you're not just fending
for yourself.
You're fending for two.
And let's be honest, Syd.
Right now you waddle.
- I don't waddle.
- Oh, yes, you do.
I'll admit I may be a little less
graceful,
but I don't waddle.
You're right.
Actually, it's more of a teeter.
Hello, Sydney.
Mom.
You look beautiful.
I'm here now.
Everything is going to be fine.
Mom...
I am so glad you're here.
Believe me, there's no one else
I want to go through this with,
but...
it isn't safe.
- Sydney...
- No.
Mom, we're involved
in an investigation.
The C.I.A. Is everywhere.
- If they find out that you're even--
- I know about Prophet Five.
I know they abducted you.
That's the reason I've come.
They've been rumored
for over 30 years...
an organization so secret
most of us thought they were a myth.
Then six months ago,
a contact of mine told me
they'd become active again,
that after all this time
they'd finally found someone
who they believed could lead them
to what they'd been looking for.
The reason they came together--
to pursue something they call
"the Horizon."
You've never heard of it?
No.
Prophet Five believes you have.
They believe you know where it is.
What are you thinking?
When Prophet Five abducted me,
they tried to get me to reveal
information
about an old Alliance mission.
What was the mission?
Well, I don't know the details,
just the code name.
But dad is looking into it.
You told your father?
That's good.
How's Jack?
He's good.
Prophet Five killed Vaughn.
I know.
I'm so sorry.
It was an Alliance mission...
designation Leo 47 Norte.
"47 Norte," got it.
All Alliance files are backed up
on Langley's archives.
Can you do it without being traced
back to this office?
So Devlin can't find out about it?
Sure, I can use a proxy
to spoof the origin.
I love secret conspiracies.
You know, as long as
I'm a co-conspirator.
Okay, here it is.
Operation originating back in 1999,
coordinated by a Jean Bertrand.
Let me see if I can find him.
You know, back in high school,
we took apart
my calculus professor's car
and reassembled it in his classroom.
Actually, my friends did it.
I would have helped,
but they couldn't trust me.
Said I had loose lips, which is,
you know, ridiculous.
- Hey, Marshall.
- Uh, nothing!
We're not doing anything.
Yes?
The diagnostic on the server,
tell me when it's done.
You got it.
Thanks.
Good to see you, Tom.
That is unexpected.
I'll be there shortly.
Was that Syd?
Well, your voice-- it modulates a little
when you're talking to sydney.
Is everything okay?
What do you have on Bertrand?
Right. Secret.
Okay, latest intel
places Bertrand in Paris.
Okay, forward the intel to Dixon.
He's joining up with Renée.
Use tac-3.
I don't want it
going through A.P.O.'S servers.
Got it.
She still here?
Jack...
you look...
well.
I got your messages. I wanted to reply.
But I sensed it might be a C.I.A. trap.
Look at us,
about to become grandparents.
I'm doing my best to ignore that.
Did Sydney tell you?
I fear for her safety.
Yes, she did.
Did Dixon find out anything?
Not yet, but he's with a source now.
Bonsoir, Jean.
Thanks.
No, I'll take it from here.
That was Dixon.
He couldn't confirm what the Horizon is,
but we know
it's in a safe deposit box in Vancouver.
The Queen's bank.
We need to act fast.
Prophet Five has probably
figured out by now
I gave them the wrong information.
Yeah, that's a safe assumption.
We can't use A.P.O.
Devlin's men are everywhere.
If you're being watched, I can go.
I have contacts in Vancouver.
We'll go together,
retrieve the Horizon ourselves.
Can your contacts
make the travel arrangements?
Make 'em for three. I'm going, too.
I know what you're going to say.
You're worried about my safety.
It's a 3-hour flight, a bank.
- We'll be in and out.
- Sydney...
Listen, the Horizon is why
Prophet Five killed Vaughn.
It's why they kidnapped me.
If we can get it before they do,
we can finish this thing, for good.
Make the arrangements.
Peyton!
We just got a message
from Irina Derevko.
The Horizon is in Vancouver.
She's on her way to retrieve it.
Assemble a team. We're going, too.
You question Derevko's loyalty?
No, I don't, but I'm not willing
to take the chance that I'm wrong,
now when we're this close.
Mr. And Mrs. Visconti,
my apologies but the bank is closing.
Perhaps we can find another time
to endow your grandchild's trust fund.
My daughter is never late.
It's that clown she married!
Of course, darling,
it's never our angel's fault.
Papa!
Mama. I'm sorry I'm late.
Sorry, sorry.
Where is Roberto?
He's not coming.
He says he doesn't want your money.
Papa,
it is his job to provide for our baby.
And how does he expect
to provide for my grandchild?
- He's a clown!
- He is an artist.
Brigitte, we agreed that the trust fund
would be a safety net
in case things don't work out.
But they will. We love each other.
Of course, the two of you will be
as happy as your father and I have been.
Let us do this for you.
Let us help.
Okay, for the baby.
Signore, we would be grateful if you
could assist us with the deposit now.
I'm sorry, but it's too late.
Here is a cashier's check
drawn on the trust account.
That is a very generous amount.
He said "no," my darling.
Bank Lissor is open until 6:00.
- Maybe if we hurry, we can...
- That won't be necessary.
It would be a privilege to help
you plan for your family's future.
I have a daughter myself.
Then you know that it's a parent's job
to take care of their children.
Mama...
Is now a good time for that rain check?
Yeah, sure. What's up?
I know about Alan Korman.
I know that you broke
into witsec to find him,
that he killed your wife.
Please promise me that you're not
going to do anything stupid,
that you're not going after him.
I already did.
I saw him last night.
I followed him to a parking garage.
I watched him get out of his car.
And then there he was.
I was 10 feet away from the man
that killed my wife.
Then I watched his wife
get out of the car
and their little son.
And I watched his life.
And then I just walked way.
I mean, killing him...
it's not going to bring back my wife.
No, it won't.
I should have told you about her.
I guess we just we get so comfortable...
keeping secrets around here.
And congratulations.
Thank you.
Papa, if Roberto finds out,
he'll be very angry.
Then it will be our family secret.
We'll find a place
to keep the trust documents safe.
Perhaps il Signore Moreau can help us.
Do you have a safety deposit we can use?
Of course.
Everything all right, my dear?
Yes, it's just...
your grandchild keeps kicking me.
You had a very busy day.
Would you mind if our daughter
waited here?
Not at all.
If you'll follow me...
It's so sweet how your daughter
wants to please you.
She's our pride and joy.
I'm sure she'll be a wonderful parent
- to her own child.
- Thank you.
She has two such lovely role models.
Excuse me.
Hey, Tom, I need your help.
Hey, dad.
- What's going on?
- Backdoor into a secure database.
These are the files right here.
Yeah, I know.
Computers are tricky. You're right.
I'm going to put you on the phone with
our tech support. Her name's Rachel.
She'll be able to help you out. Hold on.
Hey, my dad's on the phone.
He kind of needs your help.
We've taken great pains to ensure
the security of this facility.
In fact, we pride ourselves on being
too careful with our clients' assets.
That's good to hear.
Rachel,
it looks like 512-bit encryption.
I can open a port
if you need to run a program.
That's okay. I think I got it.
What about emergency response?
If an alarm is tripped, how long before,
the authorities respond?
The building
has round-the-clock security.
Our drills place it at four minutes,
but to be honest,
it's never been activated.
Good.
Let's keep it that way.
Syd, we've got him.
What's the box number?
Wait. Hang on, dad.
Try this. 8438220.
Someday you have to show me
how you do that.
A magician never reveals her secrets.
- Be safe.
- Thanks.
Okay, dad, box 135.
I can't open it.
Why?
A countermeasure.
Looks like it's acid-based.
- Can you disable it?
- Not without the combination.
It'll destroy the contents.
I'll have to take it back to Marshall.
He'll be able to...
Peyton's here.
Talk fast!
They're here as backup.
You're working for them, aren't you?
Answer me!
That was you... on the ship.
Wasn't it?
Behind the glass.
You orchestrated the whole thing...
because you wanted this.
And when...
when you couldn't torture it out of me,
you came to me as my mother.
I am your mother.
Call off your team right now.
- They're not my team.
- I don't believe you.
- Dad...
- You need to believe me.
'Cause if Peyton's here,
she's here to kill me, too.
She's going to be very disappointed,
because I'm about to beat her to it.
I thought I killed you once.
This time I'll be more thorough.
Hey, dad!
The baby's coming.
We have a problem.
Devlin's men
are accessing our server logs.
They believe there's a mole
within A.P.O.
responsible for leaking
information to Prophet Five.
You think they're right?
No, I don't.
However, Sydney and Jack
are in the field without clearance.
I've been assisting them.
So have I.
Yes, I know.
I've already tried purging
the logs myself,
but the files are read-only.
I can do it.
I can crack the logs
and delete the entries,
make it untraceable,
but it will take a little time.
Then get to it right now.
You should sit.
Look, we need to get out of here.
What's their approach?
What?
Their plan, what is it?
How are they going to attack us?
I don't know. I already told you,
this wasn't part of my operation.
You want to escape?
Give me the Horizon.
- I'll tell them you're already gone.
- That isn't going to happen.
Jack, don't be stubborn.
The baby's coming.
I'm trying to help.
I'm giving you a way out.
Okay, I'm in.
We've got control of their system.
Can you see them?
The bank
has its own dedicated security feed.
If they enter any of the stairwells,
I'll see them.
Lock down the building. We're going up.
How were you going to do it?
Once you took the Horizon,
what was your extraction?
Look, they're coming!
How were you going to get away from us?
There's a helicopter.
It's waiting for my signal.
Does Prophet Five know about it?
The elevators will all be grounded.
It's four flights of stairs to the roof.
I can make it.
Move!
Peyton, I've got a visual.
Go ahead.
They've just entered the main stairwell,
15th floor.
But they're not coming down.
They're heading up.
The helipad...
redirect those cameras
to exterior surveillance.
I'm going to keep going.
I'm six floors behind.
What's the signal to the helicopter?
A beacon.
It's in my bra.
Keep moving.
We're almost there.
I've got a chopper approaching inbound
from the northwest.
Damn!
Out here.
Quickly!
This building has to have
a freight elevator.
- Sydney...
- If we hot-wire a junction box,
we might be able to restore
emergency power to one of the cars.
Even if we could,
they'll be waiting for us
- as soon as we override the elevator.
- We have to try.
We need to set up a defensive position.
I'm not interested in your opinion.
She's right.
Even if we could outflank them
down the stairwell,
you wouldn't make it.
Here,
cover your mother.
I'll go down and take care
of Peyton and her men.
I'll be right back.
Whatever happens,
keep that pointed at your mother.
If she even blinks...
I'll shoot her.
Okay, I'm in.
- The logs are online.
- Have they found anything yet?
No, they're still working
on the tasking logs.
I'm going to start
with the comm entries.
Here we go.
This is Sydney's communication
from Vancouver.
And Paris,
this is Dixon's pbx communication.
Okay, I think that's it.
- Nothing else looks...
- No, there's one more.
I had to pull satellite imagery
for the building in Vancouver.
We'll have to delete that as well.
Time stamp should be somewhere
between midnight and 2:00am.
There.
"Tindle" isn't your log-in name.
No. My network account timed out.
I had to create a temporary one.
- I can't do it.
- What do you mean?
They're on the same page of entries.
That's them now.
If we delete this one, they'll see it.
- Devlin.
- It's me.
It seems you don't have
the latest server logs.
What's the time stamp
on your last entry?
Scroll to the end of the list.
10:37 this morning.
Okay, it matches up.
Sorry about the interruption.
Good work.
"The truth takes time."
That's what you said years ago.
Is this what you meant?
You like it to be simple.
It's never simple.
Did you put out the order
to kill Vaughn?
I'd known about his investigation
for a long time.
In sovogda I tried to warn him.
He didn't take my advice.
I fell for you.
Even dad fell for you.
But Vaughn never trusted you.
This is Alpha team. We're on 16.
We have a possible target.
Copy that.
Alpha team, report.
Alpha team, do you copy?
Barker, where are you?
I just swept 17. Moving on to 18.
Roger.
Finish up there and report in.
Exhale through your mouth.
- I'm only offering advice.
- Don't!
I know why you saved my pregnancy.
You want my baby, and I don't know why.
Frankly, I don't care.
I just want you to leave us alone.
You should know something, Sydney.
I never wanted to have a child.
The K.G.B. demanded it.
They knew it would ensure
your father's allegiance to me.
You were simply a means to an end.
And then when the doctor
put you in my arms,
and I looked at you,
so fragile,
all I could think was,
"how could I have made
such a terrible mistake?"
And at that moment,
I was sure of one thing.
I couldn't be an agent and a mother.
I'd rather fail at one or both.
And I chose to fail at being a mother.
Give me the gun.
Syd, they're coming.
In time you'll learn
you can't do both.
Watch me.
The only reason I saved the baby
is because you're my daughter.
Now do exactly as I tell you.
Get in that chair.
This really is no place for you,
grandpa.
By the way, where's Sydney registered?
I'd love to get her a gift for the baby.
Sydney, don't push!
God, mom, I have to!
No, listen to me!
Don't push.
I know you want to,
but you can't.
Sydney, listen to me.
The baby is coming out backward.
What does that mean?
What is it?
Her muscles are locked.
She needs to relax.
The baby needs oxygen
if it doesn't come out right now.
Squeeze my hand.
This is important.
As hard as you can.
- Dad!
- Just keep breathing.
Breathe.
Okay, good.
In and out.
Okay, now again.
Look at me.
You can do this.
I can't, dad. I can't!
Yes, you can.
I don't want to do this here!
That's okay.
Tell me where you want to be.
I'm scared.
I know. That's why we're here
to take care of you.
Now tell me where you want to be.
I want to be on a beach.
That's good, okay.
Just go there.
Now tell me about it.
Vaughn is with me.
Vaughn is there, with you on the beach.
Good.
Vaughn is with you.
I miss him.
I know.
I know you do, sweetheart.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Okay now, Sydney, push.
Sydney, you can do this.
Now, again.
Push.
Sydney, as hard as you can!
Good!
You have a baby girl.
- She took the satchel.
- I know.
We'll find her.
Sweetie...
She's so beautiful.
Listen to me very carefully,
Marshall.
Jack and Sydney are in Vancouver,
Queen's bank.
They need extraction.
Okay, is this who I think it is?
Tell the team they'll need diapers.
I just spoke to Dixon.
He's in contact
with Europol and the S.V.R.
So far, nothing.
We'll find her, Sydney.
Would you like
to hold your granddaughter?
Yes, I would.
She has Vaughn's eyes.
Yeah, she does.
Dad...
I'll take care of it.
www.forom.com