Previously on Alias...
Sydney, this woman is an assassin.
Vaughn trusted her.
They worked together for seven years.
- Sydney's contact is Renée Rienne.
- Really?
Ms. Rienne has been helping Sydney
with her investigation
of the Prophet Five conspiracy.
Michael always told me
I could come to you.
Yeah.
These people killed my fiancé,
the father of my child.
Our agreement is whatever I say it is.
I'm the one who got you out of prison.
I can easily put you back.
How's your daughter?
Nadia has nothing to do with this.
Oh, sure, she does.
I'm at the archive. Your turn now.
Got the key.
It's transmitting now.
Insert key template.
Perfect.
I'm entering the archive.
I need the lock number.
So what are we looking for?
All I know is it's intended
for Gordon Dean.
The intel I received said
it will be left for him
at the University of Rome
inside a package shipped
to their museum archive.
Well, how will we know which package?
It will be sent from Milan,
from an alias...
Marcello Demasi.
I found the alias. Can you give me
a minute to find the name?
Here it is. Marcello Demasi. Num...
Sydney?
Sydney Bristow?
I don't believe it.
Professor Choi.
Sydney, I need the lock number.
Look at you. You look great.
Thank you.
Sydney.
What are you doing in Rome?
Sabbatical. I'm teaching classes
and doing some research.
And what about you?
Oh, I've just been traveling...
12 countries in 22 months.
Got it. 1222.
I know that's a lot, but I won't have
much of a chance after the baby's born.
Now get out of there
before the Chancellor gets back.
Well, I should let you get back
to your class.
No problem. I'm on a lunch break.
We have plenty of time.
Great.
You know, uh,
I don't wanna be presumptive,
but, uh, you married?
Newlyweds.
Ah, eager to start a family then?
I guess you could say we dove right in.
Well, he must be some guy.
You seem really happy.
He is.
I found the shipment.
I'm retrieving the package.
I'll take that.
Put it down. Step back.
Got it.
I'm on my way to the extraction point.
So is he here with you, your husband?
He's at the hotel.
I'd love for you to meet him.
We'll take you to dinner,
if you'll just write down your number.
Sure, I would like that.
Here, take my card.
It was inside the sculpture.
Any idea what it's for?
No.
So who was that man?
- Choi?
- No one.
He was from another life.
She's still unresponsive.
There's been no change since yesterday.
I'm afraid the xylenol didn't work.
The drug is still
in the experimental age.
It deserves more time.
Mr. Sloane, we've kept Nadia
in a medically induced coma
for five months now.
None of our procedures
have shown any promise.
When we bring her out, she displays
the same violent propensities.
Now these treatments
are extremely costly.
Expense is not an issue.
We've simply run out of options.
At this point, anything that we may try
is unlikely to inspire change.
It may even do more harm than good.
I am not prepared to give up.
Neither are we.
In the meantime, I think
you should consider alternative care
in a place a little more comfortable.
Okay, thank you, Doctor.
Yes?
How is she doing today?
I feel for you.
I can't imagine how hard it must be
looking into the face of your own sins.
What do you want, Dean?
Sydney Bristow has taken something
of mine... an access card.
I want you to get it back.
Why? What is it for?
That's none of your concern.
48 hours. Don't let me down.
Are you sure this is the right move?
The right move?
If they find out what you're up to...
They won't.
Besides, I don't think
I have the choice at this point.
You're being paranoid again.
You're too important to this operation
to be dismissed over a few setbacks.
Well, maybe you're right,
but some life insurance
will help me sleep better at night.
You too, I imagine.
Odds are if they terminate me,
they'll decide our entire cell
is a security risk.
I'll let you know
when Sloane contacts me.
Hello, Jack.
Arvin, good news.
Sydney's mission in Italy was a success.
Yes, I already knew that.
Did you?
How?
Gordon Dean told me.
Translation : Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Guilamu
Suggestions critics insults : aliassub@gmail.com
www.forom.com
Marshall ran analysis
on the card you retrieved?
He suspects it's an access key
for a secure network.
So we just have to figure out
which network.
Luckily, there are only
10 billion secure networks in the world.
We may have a dead end on that side,
but we intercepted Dean's property.
I'm guessing
he's not too happy about that, so...
I'll take what I can get.
- Delivery for Sydney Bristow.
- Hey, come on in.
Just put it in the nursery.
It's right through there.
Thanks.
Crib.
You know, the, uh,
the nursery could use a little work.
I don't know. I think it's kind of airy.
I'll grab my bag.
We can head in to work.
I thought you were taking the day off.
I was.
That was before we had ten billion
secure networks to analyze.
I have a better idea.
First, let's set up the crib, and then
at least that way,
we'll know we got something
accomplished today.
It's okay. I'll do it later.
What could it take, half an hour?
I used to think that stuff
would be so fun...
decorating a room
and picking out colors.
It hasn't turned out exactly the way
I thought it would.
Yeah?
I was first contacted a month ago.
It was during my sentencing hearings.
As I told your father,
the terms were simple.
They offered to sway
the committee's decision
for my release...
and I, in turn,
would be indebted to them.
It was not made clear
what that would entail,
but I had an idea.
You've been lying to us this whole time.
There's no justification.
However, faced with spending
the rest of my life in prison
while my daughter
was in the hospital, I...
Nadia hasn't made any improvement.
Why admit this to us now?
What's changed?
Nadia won't be getting better, Jack.
If I have to face a life
without my daughter...
I still have to live with myself.
It sounds hollow, I know,
in light of what I just told you...
but I consider you both to be my family.
You expect us to forgive you now?
No, Sydney, not at all.
I know how much pain
Dean has caused you
as well as Rachel Gibson.
I have damaged your investigation
enough.
Ironically, Dean's arrangement
puts me in a unique position.
The last thing he expects of me
is to double cross him.
You'll help us arrest him?
Yes.
He's tasked me
with recovering something
you took from him... an access card.
I can use that as bait.
Understand something.
If this is a setup...
It's not, Sydney, I assure you.
Once we have Dean in custody,
he will be forced
to expose his organization,
and you will have all the answers
you're looking for.
You have a way to contact Dean?
Hello?
It's me.
I have what you wanted.
Good. I knew I could count on you.
Where should we meet?
Get a pen. Write this down.
The meeting place is a racetrack.
Dean may trust Sloane,
but he's still being cautious.
He picked this location
because it's safe...
several exit strategies,
a large crowd to blend in with.
That or maybe he's got
Lollipop in the second.
We'll have to grab him
before he has the chance to slip out.
That won't be easy.
Dean doesn't go anywhere
without a security detail.
It'll most likely be two men
heavily armed, nearly invisible.
We can assume that one
will shadow Dean, the other Sloane.
Um, sorry. Is anybody else
having déja vu here?
I mean, first Sloane was good,
then he's bad, now he's good again?
Although I guess he was bad at first,
I just thought...
We have a significant
tactical disadvantage.
Dean knows what we look like.
He can I.D. every one of us.
Not everyone. He's never seen me...
but I look forward
to making his acquaintance.
Good. Tom, you'll take lead.
Dixon, Sydney, Rachel,
you'll provide support in the field.
I want a plan drafted within the hour.
Wheels up at 1500.
We may not have another chance
like this. Let's make it count.
Dean's reserved you a seat
in the grandstand.
He won't arrive
until he's confirmed you're alone.
If we put a transmitter on you,
his security countermeasures
may detect it,
so I'll be tracking you remotely.
You'll need this.
It's a facsimile, I assume.
No, it's the real card.
Dean may verify it with a reader.
We'll move in as soon as
we've intercepted his men,
but until then, you'll have to stall.
Okay.
I hacked into the closed-circuit feeds.
We're ready to go.
Okay, you're up.
Look, Sydney...
I may have lost the opportunity
to save my own child.
I only hope that by taking out Dean,
I will have helped to save yours.
Good luck.
Okay. Dixon and Tom are in position.
No sign of Dean yet.
He won't reveal himself
until Sloane is in place.
Excuse me. Mama comin' through!
Watch out. Don't jostle the package!
How y'all doin'?
You gonna help me
pick a winner today, skinny?
Ha ha. He's cute...
for a Sheik.
Excuse me that's my seat.
Okay, laser mic's on target, Phoenix.
Reception's good.
Hey, Base. You got a visual?
Affirmative, Sidewinder.
Good, 'cause, uh, I was wondering,
what do you think of this suit?
Pretty sweet, huh?
Yeah, it's a nice suit on you.
Blue's a good color.
And for you as well, Director Bristow.
Thanks. Oracle, can you get us
a closer look at Sloane?
- How's that?
- Fine.
I got him.
The package has arrived. East concourse.
There.
Sloane's in position.
Sidewinder, we're headed your way.
Ten four. Let's do this.
We've got you.
Sidewinder, you're up.
How ya doin', mate?
Well, I'm fantastic. Thanks for asking.
You know why?
The Tasmanian Devil
is straight as a string.
Gonna make me a rich man.
The thing is, I'm short 2 grand.
What do you say you front me,
and I double it for you by dark?
- Not today.
- Come on, mate.
That watch alone
would get me 2 grand across the card.
We need an assist here.
This way.
First security detail down.
The second one hasn't shown.
But this guy's wearing an earpiece.
Which means
Dean's communicating with him via radio.
He could be anywhere.
Outrigger, until we I.D.
the second detail,
we'll have to proceed with the meet.
Copy that.
You search crowd. Someone you know?
Yes, I do.
Lovely day.
Yes, it is.
Outrigger, if Dean's following
his standard protocol,
that second detail shouldn't be any more
than 50 feet away.
Do you have something for me?
I do.
Outrigger, I've got him at 12:00.
Blue cap, binoculars.
I'm on it.
Excuse me, Sir.
I believe you have my seat.
Drinks too much.
Filthy habit.
Second security detail is down.
Good work.
Outrigger and Sidewinder, move in.
It's been a pleasure.
Post one, what's your status?
Outrigger, Sidewinder, move in.
Post two, what's your status?
Oracle, I've lost sight of him.
Post two, do you copy?
Sidewinder, come in!
Outrigger, do you copy?
Their P.A. System must be bleeding
into our channel.
I'll try to find an open frequency.
Oracle, do you copy me? I've lost...
- Outrigger? Phoenix?
- Come in! We've got a problem!
Stand up.
What?
We're gonna take a walk.
Do it now.
Base? Anyone?
Phoenix!
Damn it.
You don't need to do this.
I'm telling you, I came here by myself.
Just keep going.
Stop.
Well, isn't this a surprise?
What are you doing here, Rachel?
You gonna fight me?
Why do you think we never put you
in the field?
Because we knew you weren't equipped.
Well, then...
that was your loss.
Oracle, come in. Do you have a visual?
Yeah, actually on... on Dean.
- What's he doing?
- Eating dirt.
I just hit him with a shovel.
A shovel? Is he conscious?
Yeah, I think so.
Then hit him again.
- We got Dean.
- That's good.
What happens now?
He tells us everything.
And we get the truth about Prophet Five.
You seem very pleased with yourself.
I'll keep this simple.
We have a few questions for you.
We want to know who you're working for
and what their agenda is.
The only other question is
whether you'll cooperate willingly
or unwillingly.
The ironic thing is, Ms. Bristow,
you and I may not share the same agenda,
but we have the same goal.
I want to know who I'm working for
as much as you do.
Unfortunately, for both of us,
you robbed me of that opportunity.
The access card.
You were making a power play.
The people I answer to...
their power stems
from remaining anonymous.
I was hoping
to balance the playing field.
All the information you want
can be accessed off a communication hub
using that card.
But before I tell you the location,
you have to agree
to do something for me.
And what is that?
I want $10 million,
as well as documents to authenticate
half a dozen false identities
and dental implants capable of fooling
facial-recognition software.
In short,
you're going to make me disappear.
- Not a chance.
- I wouldn't be so hasty.
That access card will expire
in just under 12 hours,
at which point
the information will vanish
and I can no longer help you, so...
I suggest you talk
to the people you answer to
and share with them my offer.
I don't need to.
I don't think it's gonna take that long.
- What is it?
- L.S.D.
Well, sort of.
See, I started with a lysergic acid
diethylamide-based serum
and, you know...
flinkmanized it.
Of course, he's not gonna see
any dancing bears on this trip,
I promise you that.
Not that... I mean, I heard about it
from a guy once. I've never...
Hey, Mr. Bristow.
How long until we can interrogate Dean?
Not long. In about an hour,
he'll think you're God.
He'll tell you anything you wanna know.
Of course, if you'd like,
I could facilitate the process.
Let's do that.
I see you've done this before.
- Peaceful, hmm?
- Yeah, it is.
I imagine you're having quite
a difficult day. Am I right?
Excuse me, do I know you?
Nope, you don't know me, Mr. Sloane.
But I do have one small favor
to ask of you.
My associates and I are aware
of your adventure in Dubai.
We also know that Gordon Dean
is still in custody,
presumably at A.P.O.
We need you to eliminate him.
Eliminate him?
Yes, and we have every confidence that
you'll be able to overcome any obstacles
that stand in your way.
I see.
You can go to hell.
I've already confessed
my bargain with Mr. Dean,
you people no longer have
any power over me.
That may be.
But we do still have plenty to offer.
I doubt there's anything
that you could do for me.
Uh, you should answer that.
Yeah?
My God.
What did you do?
Nothing. It just happened.
The nurse came through on rounds
15 minutes ago and found her awake.
Dad?
I'm right here, sweetheart.
I'm right here.
Where am I?
You're gonna be okay, Nadia.
You're gonna be okay.
Well, his brain waves
are all over the place,
which I guess explains
why his heart rate's off the chart.
Maybe Twisted Sister
wasn't the way to go.
- Cut it.
- Right.
You know, I think I gave him
too much diophorazide.
My bad.
I mean, he is hallucinating hard.
Whatever he's seeing,
it's scaring him to death, literally.
We have to stabilize his vitals.
He won't talk otherwise.
Well, no, I don't think his body
can withstand any more drugs.
Then what do we do?
Well, not that I would know or anything,
but...
well, he needs to feel safe.
I mean, maybe if somebody
comforted him...
You!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I know you're scared. Just relax.
They want me dead.
They'll kill me.
Well, that won't happen. I won't let it.
I'm taking care of you now.
Okay, his heart rate is coming down.
It's working!
I'm gonna ask you some questions.
When you answer me,
I'll make sure no one can hurt you.
Okay? No one.
Do you understand?
They want my eyes.
Don't let them take my eyes.
No, I won't. No one can hurt you
as long as I'm here. No one.
Listen, the access card...
it was designed to patch into
a specific network. Tell me which one.
Which network does the card access?
I can help you.
When you see the watchman,
you'll need me. I can help you.
Listen to me, you need to focus.
How do I get
into your organization's network?
Get away from me!
It's your fault!
I needed to find the secret.
I needed protection!
I'm protecting you now.
Tell me the secret. I'll keep it safe.
Stay with me, Gordon.
The watchman is on the roof.
You need to go...
to the roof.
Okay, which roof?
Where do I find it?
Glenheim.
Okay, what is Glenheim?
Okay, there's a Glenheim corporation
in Seattle.
The Glenheim Towers.
Pull up the building schematics.
I'll pull up the building schematics.
Okay, there's a satellite on the roof
connected to the network of servers.
Rachel, we need a plane fueled
and ready to leave for Seattle
within the hour.
Hello.
When?
I shouldn't have done it.
I didn't mean to.
They insisted.
You didn't want to do what?
They insisted to kill Michael Vaughn.
I can help you defeat them,
but you have to hurry.
They have plans for you.
What plans?
Sydney, you need to go.
I'll take over from here.
It's Nadia.
You've never looked more beautiful,
Nadia.
Sovogda?
What happened?
I'll tell you about it in time.
Just rest for now.
- Dad?
- I listen.
Where's the doctor?
Just stepped out for a minute.
What's happening?
Oh, God. Please, I need help here!
Please! Help! I need help here! Doctor!
I need you to step back, Mr. Sloane.
Nadia! Please!
Blood pressure 70 over 50.
I need 500 milligrams of detropine I.V.
We were forced to induce coma again.
Look, I'll be honest.
Waking up without any signs
of her disease was, frankly, a fluke.
Without an explanation,
it's likely this is never
gonna happen again.
Of course, we'll watch her closely.
Thank you, doctor.
You've done everything you can for her.
Beyond that, it's out of your control.
Thank you, Sydney.
This is Outrigger. We've touched down.
Copy that.
I heard. Are you okay?
Yeah.
- How's Sloane?
- Not well.
We figured out what Dean
was talking about.
The network his organization's using
is mobile.
Meaning?
Their communications are piggy-backed
through a series of telecom satellites.
The Glenheim people
don't know they're being used,
which is exactly the point.
They wouldn't know the network was there
unless they were looking for it.
Further, the network is rerouted
every few days
as a precautionary measure.
If we lose them now,
we won't find them again.
How much time do we have?
12 minutes, 58 seconds.
Sidewinder, what's your status?
We're at the dish.
We're cutting through now.
When you open up the panel,
let me know what you're looking at.
I'm looking at a keypad
and an L.C.D. readout.
Okay, um, any access ports?
Affirmative.
Uplink should be coming your way.
Got it.
- Marshall, what are we looking at?
- I'm not sure.
It looks like the network's
not tracking back to just one source.
Meaning?
Meaning when I try to locate the origin,
several addresses keep popping up.
It looks like the information's
being fed by a number...
wait a minute, that is weird.
One of the nodes streams
to Credit Marquis.
- What's that?
- Public front for French intelligence.
That's not all. I mean,
there's a stream to the Russian S.V.R.,
a European pharmaceutical conglomerate,
the C.D.C.,
MI-6, this list goes on.
So they're hijacking government servers?
No, if that were the case,
I'd be able to detect it.
I mean, this suggests...
they are government.
Dad?
Gordon Dean didn't bribe
someone on the inside
to get Sloane out of jail.
His organization
is already on the inside.
Marshall, can you trace those nodes?
Yeah, let me see what I can do.
Right on time.
Network diagnostic is up and running.
You got two minutes to grab that coffee.
Oh, and get me a cup, too? Little cream.
Arvin.
For the next minute and a half,
no one knows I'm here.
Good. Get me out of these.
That isn't exactly what I had in mind.
Okay, I've narrowed the network down
to 12 isolated nodes.
I think I can trace
their point of origin.
- 12?
- Yeah.
"If there was never a one,
there was ever the 12."
In the Caymans, that was one
of Dean's account protocols.
What just happened?
We're locked out.
Let me try to bypass the encryption.
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
"Grade three watchman encryption."
There's no way around this
in six minutes.
The program's requesting an access code.
Dean mentioned "watchman."
He said when I find the watchman,
he would help me.
This is what he meant.
He has the access code.
Go.
Don't do this, Arvin.
I have the access code.
You can take down Prophet Five.
God forgive me.
Help! Somebody, please!
These walls are soundproof.
There's no point in shouting.
According to medical services,
Dean took his own life.
Apparently with a cyanide pill
he had subdermally implanted
inside his cheek.
I don't understand.
This morning he wanted immunity.
He wanted to live.
Clearly, Dean thrived on power.
Once the drug wore off,
he must've realized
he was facing a life sentence.
Death was easier to accept.
Marshall counted 12 sources
that make up Prophet Five.
12, dad.
It's like the Alliance all over again.
I know.
If they are embedded
inside global government,
where do we even start?
We've already started.
I guess I'll see you tomorrow.
Do you have any plans for tonight?
What did you have in mind?
You're sure you won't join me?
We can drink to your success.
Or perhaps, if you like,
to soothe your guilt.
Guilt isn't one of my driving emotions.
To your success then.
As we agreed,
Dean's operation is now yours.
But with one warning...
I appreciate ambition.
But if you're considering
any further betrayals,
they will come at your own expense.
I understand.
I'll be right back.
A job well done, Mr. Sloane.
I'm so glad you took our offer.
I didn't have much of a choice, did I?
- There's always a choice.
- Yeah.
My daughter...
when will she be cured?
- Soon.
- Soon?
Perhaps you could be
a bit more specific.
I wish I could.
But there are a few more things
we need you to do first.
- We have a deal.
- No.
We have an arrangement,
which you don't seem
to understand very well.
You son of a bitch.
We'll be in touch.
Till then,
I want you to remember one thing...
you have something now
that you didn't have this morning.
- What's that?
- Hope.
- Okay, that's the headboard.
- That's the footboard.
That's what I said.
Have you ever actually built
anything before?
Yes, in fact. I built your crib.
Really?
Well, your mother and I did it together.
Done.
Done?
Why? Did you doubt me?
No, of course not.
Get me the screwdriver.
Translation : Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Guilamu
Suggestions critics insults : aliassub@gmail.com
www.forom.com