My Name is Anna.
I am the leader of my people.
They're calling themselves
"The Visitors."
- You watching?
- Yeah I'm watching.
You all seem to be what
we consider attractive.
- You're not so bad yourself.
- Whenever Anna has something
significant to say,
we would like her to say it through you.
They knew we were coming.
Someone tipped them off.
We need your help.
- I'm not gonna put my fiancée at risk.
- Welcome to the New York mother ship.
Have you heard about our new
peace Ambassador program?
You two are obsessed with Visitors.
- They call it spreading hope.
- Take this and go to this address.
- All the information's inside.
- The visitors didn't just get here.
They've been here for years.
They'll take over
unless we can stop them.
You were right to fight.
There's others out there like me.
- We'll help.
- They have a big head start.
They're arming themselves with the most
powerful weapon out there.
- What big weapon?
- Devotion.
I don't know who to trust anymore.
I can't get the image of dale
just lying there out of my head.
What do we do now?
We help build a resistance.
We recruit.
We have to be careful.
We'll be careful.
Are we the only ones who got away?
No, there were others.
- What's going on?
- It's going to the warehouse.
- What are they doing?
- They're cleaning up.
What?
We have to do something.
No. It has to be anonymous.
9-1-1. What's your emergency?
Oh, my God.
It's a massacre. Please.
Please, they're killing people.
You have to come.
Where are you?
It's a warehouse...
4400 Pier avenue, Brooklyn.
Please send the police.
- Go. We're sitting ducks out here.
- I'm contacting dispatch now.
- How many people were killed?
- I don't know a lot. Look,
just send everyone that you've got.
Okay ma'am, don't hang up.
I need to confirm
that address with you again.
You're at 400 pier avenue?
Yes. How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm gonna stay with you on
the line until help arrives.
- What's your name, ma'am?
- Hang up. Hang up! Hang up!
- They must've seen us.
- No.
They intercepted the call.
- What?
- The Visitors they traced the call.
- How is that possible?
- How is any of this possible?
Dale was my partner.
He was one of 'em.
He's been my partner
for seven years,
long before the ships showed up.
Anyone could be Visitors.
Jack, go home.
What?
Go home. Act normal.
Pretend this never happened.
Wait we can't just
walk away from this.
We can't attack it head-on, either.
It's too dangerous.
I have to figure out what to do.
Go home.
Don't trust anyone.
Anyone.
God!
I thought you were...
where have you been?
- With Brandon.
- All night?
My bike broke down.
Are you sure you're okay?
Ty, I need to talk to
you about yesterday.
It is really important to me that you
don't get involved with the visitors.
With the Visitors.
I know they're exciting
and Kinda cool, but...
for me, can you do that?
You're just saying that.
Promise.
Yeah. I mean,
if it it's that big of a deal to you...
No more visitor stuff.
You know, I...
I promise.
Good.
I need you to be safe.
I am.
- Can I go to bed now?
- Yeah.
I love you, Ty.
After three weeks of evaluation,
a decision on whether the U.S.
will Establish diplomatic ties with
the Visitors may come as early as today.
The decision will be based in large part
on a recommendation
from the Visitor threat
assessment joint task force.
Establishing relations
would grant the Visitors
full freedom of movement
within our Nation's borders.
There's been much debate
over the last few weeks as to...
Establishing ties with the Visitors
is a good thing, Jack.
More souls to save.
You'll see.
Though high ranking Visitors
have been granted limited...,
The police came by last night.
They wanted to talk to you about that
poor man who was stabbed
to death yesterday.
Said they'd be back this morning.
You left your gun in my car.
It's Paul. Have you seen Dale?
Dale?
Not since yesterday. Why?
I need you to get in here.
He's missing.
Last night was great.
Better than great.
You know, maybe I should
hide rings all over the house.
How's your arm?
You think I'm gonna let some scratch
from filing cabinet get the best of me?
Hey, hon,
there's some, ointment
in the medicine chest if you need it.
Thanks, baby,
but it's not that bad.
And please feel free to ask
anything and everything.
I'm here to discuss all
topics without reserve.
And please feel free to ask
anything and everything.
I'm here to discuss all
topics without reserve.
Morning.
You're in rly.
Just watching the interview.
Why are you beating
yourself up over this?
Because my dad's not here
do it for me?
If you'd gone after anna on the air,
you'd never get access again.
80 million viewers
watched you last night.
80 million watched Anna.
- No formal response yet from India.
- Be pient.
The US is the Lynchpin.
Once they grant us freedom,
the remaining countries will follow.
I'm told in Japan, the conveys both
a respect for tradition
and the allure of submission.
I'm not sure that's
the message you want to send.
You still don't understand humanity.
Team Lézards
- 102 -
"There Is No Normal Anymore"
VO By:
¤Aka¤, kaiser66, Visitor#Kµ
We're ready for ya.
His wife's pretty upset.
She's been here a couple hours.
Dale never made it home last night.
She says he always calls,
even on stakeout.
Timing's terrible. Half my team's been
reassigned to this visitor task force.
I don't really care
about the visitors right now.
We're all worried about Dale.
Any agent goes missing,
it's a big deal.
You wanna ask me anything
before we go in?
It's just a few questions, right?
Agent evans, please. Have a seat.
Father Jack Landry?
I'm special agent Sarita Malik
with the FBI Visitor Threat
Assessment joint Task force.
That's a mouthful.
Can I as you some questions
about the man who died here yesterday?
You were the last person
to talk to him.
I was expecting the police,
not the FBI.
The victim was on a bureau list.
He made dozens of calls to us
over the years
about a supposed alien invasion.
Remember when that was crazy talk?
There's still plenty of crazy
out there.
We've logged thousands of calls
like his over the years.
It's just now we have to
pay attention to them.
Makes sense.
- We really appreciate your help.
- Of course. Where do you want to start?
The last time you saw
agent Maddox was...
Around 9:00 last night. We grabbed
some dinner, then he dropped me off.
His wife said you
were working together.
That's true. Then we grabbed dinner,
then he dropped me off.
Had you ever seen him
before yesterday?
I don't think so.
You sure?
No, I don't think.
Not before yesterday.
Were you aware
of any marital problems?
He loves Joselyn.
Any drug or alcohol issues?
Dale doesn't even drink.
So he didn't come here to see you?
People come to see priests
all the time. I'm a priest, so...
Did he say anything
about the visitors?
Take this and go to this address
and give it to the people there.
He just...
- He seemed really scared.
- Stressed out?
There's a spacheship above the city.
He's been my partner for seven years.
He's always had my back.
Were the two of you
romantically involved?
We have to ask.
Dale's like a brother to me, so no.
How much more of this do we have?
Dale's missing.
I'd like to look for him.
I have a few more questions.
Paul? What's going on?
They found Dale's car.
- What?
- That address.
- Mean something to you?
- It came up
in an investigation
into a terrorist cell.
- Maybe dale was looking into it.
- And you didn't think to tell me this?
Nobody in or out until we get the
all clear.
There's possible suspects in there.
Get on the radios.
Stay on the radios.
If we need backup, we'll call NYPD.
Nobody gets hurt.
Everybody stays aware.
Find anything?
Dale's phone.
And we wait with great anticipation
for russia, india
and the United States
to follow their lead.
- Really?
- Hopefully, a decision is forthcoming.
Until then, we are of peace always.
Poll numbers.
Country's split about the visitors.
50% are still undecided.
People don't have enough info.
That's my fault.
I didn't ask anna the hard
questions. I got played.
- Chad, we talked about this.
- I know,
but I need to show Anna
she's not the only one
who can get what she wants.
You gonna ask another interview?
I don't need Anna.
When I'm done,
she'll be the one calling me.
What's this?
I want you to give me this ring
in your own time,
when you're ready.
I'm still mad at myself
for not trusting you.
I was sneaking around
buying you this engagement ring.
Like I said, give it to me
in your own time.
I had a client cancel today.
Wanna meet for lunch?
I wish I could, sweetheart, but I
have to go out to Jersey for a meeting.
Rain check?
I still can't believe
you joined up last night.
Dude, you've got
some serious brass clankers.
- Keep it down around my mom.
- What? About the brass clankers?
No, dumb-ass. About me joining.
My mom doesn't get it, man.
Dhe'd totally freak.
Mine, too. Must be a parent thing.
Seriously, who doesn't wanna hang out
with someone from another planet?
I know.
That jacket
looks really good on you.
Thanks.
I remember you. Brandon, right?
Tyler told me you wanted
to become a peace ambassador.
The thought crossed my mind.
Come on.
Let's see if we can get you
to the front of the line.
This way.
Two words man. Awe. Some.
Is everything all right?
I'm not sure I did
the right thing, father.
The man who died
was ranting about the visitors.
I should've mentioned that.
That poor soul
was clearly disturbed.
Didn't the FBI agent say as much?
She wasn't just with the fbi.
She was...
with the Visitor Threat
Assessment joint Task force.
Tread carefully, Jack.
There are sensitive talks going on
between our government
and the visitors.
You wouldn't want to upset
the applecart now, would ya?
I'm sure you're doing
the right thing.
You never answered
my question before.
Why this the first time I'm
hearing about this warehouse?
We were afraid there was a mole.
Someone kept typing off
the cells we were tracking.
I guess dale came here
to investigate.
Why would he do that alone?
Didn't he trust you?
I've kind of had enough, sir.
The questions, the tone.
My partner, my friend
could be out there somewhere.
Then go find him.
Canvass the area!
Get in touch with justice, DEA, ATF.
Do we know if any of these people are
from the first attempt at a resistance?
Not yet, but we'll get
the information from him.
I want answers.
Who else was with you
in the warehouse?
Give me the names, and I'll make
the snakes go away.
I don't know.
I never saw them before.
Make it stop!
He was the only human
we captured alive.
A new resistance
would be unacceptable.
I want names.
Hello?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Angelo.
Don't know any Angelo.
Angelo Russo.
Never heard of him.
I told you never come back.
I missed you, too, Angelo.
Jack?
- What are you doing here?
- I work here.
- You're an FBI agent?
- You're a freakin' priest?
Father Landry?
We're ready for you.
What are you doing here?
Upsetting the applecart.
You two know each other?
- No.
- Yes.
We just met.
Father?
Malik.
What's the priest doing here?
He's got info on a murder.
And that's my bike.
And that's my bike in Tompkins Park.
- And, that's me and my bike.
- You really like your bike.
That's Verducci's pizza.
That's the best slice in the city.
You ever had pizza?
You're gonna love it. I'll take you
there as soon as they let you out.
What makes you think
I'd go anywhere with you?
You space girls are funny.
You were joking, right?
Can I see that?
Did I do it right?
Perfect.
Whoops!
What are you gonna do
about it, V boy?
What are you gonna
do about it, V lover?
- Wait, Tyler.
- You got a problem, man?
You're the one with the problem.
Your boy's littering.
Let's just forget about this Ty.
You always make
your girlfriend do the talkin'?
The peace ambassador
just punched a guy!
Dude, you got
a little somethin' right there.
Lisa!
Heard something about a fight
at a warehouse in Brooklyn last night.
Little bird told you?
I keep my ear to the ground.
How do you think
I stayed alive this long?
Can't believe you're involved
in that again.
You should be hiding.
I was.
Then I got a phone call.
Remember Georgie?
Yeah, I remember him.
Guy's a hothead.
He'll get you killed.
Maybe,
but I can't walk away.
Looked up in the sky lately?
- Wasn't suppose to happen yet.
- But it has.
And whatever they're
gonna do to the humans,
it's nothing compared to what they'll do
to traitors like me and you.
Take my advice, head for the hills.
I can't.
There's a woman.
Human.
Oh, God. Don't tell me
you're in love with her.
You know anybody looking to
get back into the fight?
That's really why you came,
isn't it?
Just give me some names.
I know there's some others.
I'm sorry, Ryan.
I can't trust you.
I can't trust anyone.
This way, father.
You gave them the pictures.
What the hell were you thinking?
I wanted to do the right thing.
The right thing?
Stick to preaching.
A man died giving me those pictures.
I gave them to the task force
'cause I thought they could help.
They're supposed to be on our side.
So was my partner.
Look where that got us.
What if those photos
can stop the government
from getting into bed
with the visitors?
What part of "don't trust
anyone" did you not understand?
You walked away from me last night.
What the hell was I supposed to do?
Don't trust anyone?
You got it.
Evans.
My office, now.
Sit down.
I just keep wondering why Dale would go
into that warehouse all by himself.
Me, too.
Any idea why your case notes
and his aren't matching up?
What are you talking about?
I want you to tell me why
you're lying about last night.
I'm not lying.
Really?
Oh, my gosh. It's a massacre.
They're killing people.
- Slow down, ma'am. Where are you?
- It's a warehouse...
4400 Pier avenue, Brooklyn.
Please send the police.
I'm contacting dispatch now.
How many people were killed?
I don't know, a lot.
Tell me that's not you.
I was at the warehouse.
I made the call.
You lied to me.
You could have compromised
this entire investigation.
- Erica, explain this to me or...
- I think that dale is working
with one of the terrorist groups
we were investigating.
Dale's a traitor?
I couldn't accuse him
without hard evidence,
so I followed him to the warehouse.
I saw him meet with them.
You never called for backup?
If I was wrong,
I could have blown
a legitimate investigation.
So I called 9-1-1.
If Dale needed help,
he would get it,
If he didn't, I would get
backup. But it didn't work.
- They never showed.
- No, they never showed,
because the emergency call center
has no record of your 9-1-1.
You just played it for me.
I got this recording from D. E. A
Every pay phone around that warehouse
is tapped for a smuggling crackdown,
and it's the only reason I even
half believe you right now.
If they're tampering
with 9-1-1 calls,
then this goes deeper
than I thought.
You know how all this sounds?
Awesome and airtight?
Dale is a traitor.
I don't like it
any more than you do.
But I'll prove it.
I just need some time.
Okay.
I just hope to hell you're wrong.
Good afternoon.
I'm Chad Decker.
Today "prime focus" takes a look at
the question that's on everyone's minds.
Do the visitors deserve our trust?
Are they the saviors
they'd have us believe,
or are we in danger of rushing
to a premature judgment?
Joining me in the discussion are
congressman Harold Stern,
a Pro-V advocate,
and Marion Geiger
taking the Anti-V position.
Marion, let's start with you.
Why exactly don't you trust the v's?
I'm sorry. I can't stop thinking
about what you said...
- that I walked away from you.
- I'm kinda busy.
I know. But you were trying
to do the right thing.
If you're trying to apologize,
fine. You're forgiven.
- Excuse me.
- I just keep thinking
about all of these years,
all of the people that Dale fooled.
Not just me, his friends,
our friends, his wife.
A wife?
She's a visitor, too?
I don't know.
They lived together, slept together.
She saw him at his most vulnerable.
Even if she's not, she might
know something that can help us.
"Us"? No.
I'm done.
I'm taking your advice. Remember
what you said? "Go home. Act normal."
There is no normal anymore.
I need your help.
Erica, you're an FBI agent.
I am just...
I don't know.
You're the only person I can trust.
I'm sorry. No.
If I'm gonna do any good,
it is here.
We checked dale's phone records.
We couldn't find any calls to you.
He had a personal phone.
Said he wanted to keep work
and family separate.
I came across these
a few months ago.
All of these calls,
they're to two numbers?
Yes. That one's mine, and...
He called that other one a lot.
Have you noticed anything?
Has dale been acting oddlately?
You know my husband.
He gets lost in work sometimes.
He can be distant.
Did the visitors'arrival have
anything to do with it?
Maybe.
Everyone's life has changed
in some way since they got here,
all the excitement.
All of dale's calls went to the same
trunk line, dead end by design.
Untracable.
There is something we can trace
the pattern of the calls.
Every time we went to nail
this terrorist cell,
Dale would make a tip-off call
to thisnumber, 20-30 minutes before.
I ran it all down,
number by number, case by case.
I just can't believe Dale
crawled to the other side.
You can't believe it?
Seven years, joined at the hip.
The scary thing is
he's still in the wind.
I don't think
he'll show his face again.
Angelo?
What's with the drugs?
- I can't trust anyone.
- I had to check you out.
- And?
If you really care about this woman,
get as far away from her as possible.
That's not gonna happen, okay?
I can protect her,
so I'm not going anywhere.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah, 100%.
Valerie Stevens, psychotherapist,
works at graden medical,
598 east 35th street.
She grew up in detroit,
Father was an autoworker,
mother a homemaker.
She graduated NYU
she has a heart condition.
Did you do something to her?
No. I wouldn't touch her.
But they will, if they find her,
and if I can do it, so can they.
You say you really love her?
You real want to put her
in the cross fire?
They won't let me in.
I know.
The counsel wants to kick you
out of the ambassador program.
What?
Your country is nervous
about us as it is.
If youwear that jacket.
Listen. Tell me what to do,
and I'll do it.
I'm already in trouble.
I'm the one that recommended you.
It's up to the counsel now.
Good-bye, Tyler.
This was nothing less than
a complete abrogation of our agreement.
Abrogation? Nice.
You have one of those
word-a-day calendars?
We'll be looking for a journalist
who knows better than to bite
the hand that feeds him.
I didn't hurt you with my show today.
I helped.
The public trusts me.
Watch the tape. Sure,
there were pros and cons,
but in the end,
I made people feel
comfortable with the idea
of embracing diplomatic relations.
You really believe that.
Check the insta-polls.
You got a nice uptick
right after my show.
And you did that because you have
our best interests at heart?
I can't control
what our government does,
but I can and do influence
public opinion, and in the end,
that's what'll make the difference.
I did this to help you,
and it's working.
Are you done preening, Mr. Decker?
Not quite.
This one was a freebie.
The next time you want my help,
it'll be on my terms.
After weeks of investigation,
the state department announced
moments ago
the united states and the visitors
have agreed to the commencement
of diplomatic relations.
As a first step, a limited number
of visitors will be able
to apply for visas that will allow them
to travel freely within our borders.
We are going to take you now
to the visitor mother ship
over manhattan,
where the V high commander Anna
is addressing the crowds below.
On behalf of all visitors,
I want to extend my warmest appreciation
to the United States.
We are humbled
by the generous faith,
the courage and the good will
you've demonstrated.
Thank you for your trust.
It will be rewarded.
We are of peace always.
It's a great blessing.
I just wanted to thank you.
You're welcome.
And listen, maybe...
You undercover, father?
Just off duty.
Do you want to walk with me?
When I heard the announcement
about the visitors,
- It made me feel...
- Sick to your stomach? Me, too.
You know we can't win this war
picking them off one at a time.
"We"? I didn't know
that you reenlisted.
This afternoon I was afraid of what
I might have to do if I got involved.
But the only thing that scares
the hell out of me now is doing nothing.
That's the second time
I've heard you curse.
Must be hanging out
with the wrong kind of people.
Diplomatic relations with the visitors
isn't gonna make our job any easier.
Neither is the fact that v task force
ignored the pictures I gave'em.
There are probably visitors
on the v task force.
They could be anywhere.
At least we have this.
What's that?
I swiped it from the v task force.
Anyone and everyone who's ever
contacted the FBI
about aliens or visitors.
Maybe we can find other people
who want to fight,
even some people from the warehouse.
We can't be the only ones
who know the truth.
Say what you want about the visitors,
but the therapy business is booming.
Can I look at your arm?
It's not so bad.
See? I told you.
It's almost healed.
That's weird.
Did you do that?
The picture's upside down.
Who's Cyrus?
Some guy I used to know.
Guy you used to know?
Some guy...
I used...
to know.
Come in.
Ty, thanks for keeping your promise
about the v's.
Don't stay up too late,
even if it is for school.