Tyler?
Did you feel that?
Tyler!
Yeah, Mom?
Yeah, you're in big trouble.
No, huge.
- I'm not kidding.
- Yeah, I know.
Good morning, Roy.
Morning, Father Jack.
Foreclosures
are on the rise,
up another 6%
in the last month alone.
And housing prices
continue to fall...
Even as the latest
economic stimulus package...
- Thanks for coming in so early.
- Oh, it's a pleasure.
It's the only time
I could make it down here.
Ah, don't even mention it.
All right. I'm a little excited.
You got the ring?
Oh, of course
I got the ring.
She is gonna like this,
isn't she?
She's gonna love it.
You know, I was gonna do
the whole
"get down on one knee" thing.
That's not too corny, is it?
Knee's a classic.
Can't go wrong with the knee.
- Knee it is.
- Good.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
Morning, Haley.
Hey!
Good morning.
- Here.
- Thank you.
You pitch Freddie
my idea?
He loved it,
thought it was a great take
on the vice president.
And let me guess--
he wants Martinez to do it.
They love you and all...
Hey, it's cool.
I get it.
Shut up, Chad,
and read the news.
How exactly
did you get into a fight?
Crashing a party
in Soho.
So you snuck out in the middle
of the night to go to a party?
Well, it was Brandon's
dumb-ass idea.
Who's a dumb-ass?
Where are you?
Some clinic off
of Bloomfield.
I'm coming to get you.
Yeah, I-I'll just
take my bike home. It's...
What's going on?!
What is this?!
- Tyler!
- Mom, what is this?!
Roy!
Look out!
It's coming down!
Mom? Mom?!
Tyler?
Stay where you are.
Tyler, are you somewhere safe?
Mom?
- Mom! Mom!
- Tyler?
Tyler! Stay where you are!
- I'm coming for you! Tyler!
- Mom?
Something's wrong, man.
I gotta go.
I'm not going anywhere.
Oh, my God!
Idiot!
Hey!
Let's go, kid!
Let's move it! Come on!
It's the only way
I can get home!
- Let's move!
- I mean, all the streets
- are blocked, man!
- This area is restricted, kid! Move!
But w--I mean,
what about my bike?!
No more! Let's go!
Move out, people! Move, move!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- What is that?
Since their arrival,
there's been no contact
with any
of the 29 ships,
now hovering over
the major cities of the world.
Come on, Ryan,
pick up.
Streets are jammed.
People are trying to flee--
The sheer mass of the ships
moving through
New York and L.A. was enough
to rock both cities for miles--
And N.O.R.A.D.
is now confirming
the first jet
to encounter the spacecrafts
experienced
full electrical failure.
Dude, this is
"Independence Day"!
Which was a rip-off
of any number of
alien invasion predecessors.
Oh, thank God!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Good.
Oh, thank God!
- I need to get through.
- Nobody is getting through.
Look again, Sergeant.
- I'm FBI.
- Counterterrorism division. I can read.
- You're still not getting past.
- I'm looking for my son.
Everybody is looking
- for their son right now.
- My son is in there.
If you will let me in there,
I can find him.
I'm not gonna
tell you again.
Turn around.
Nobody is getting through.
- Turn around.
- Please! He called me an hour ago.
He's in there!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Come on, now!
Tyler?
Ty?
Mom?
Tyler!
- Mom! Oh.
- Oh!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm okay.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
"Pilot"
Don't be frightened.
We mean no harm.
Please accept
our apologies.
We're truly anguished
by the turmoil
our arrival has caused.
This is
a momentous day.
Until now,
we believed we were
the only intelligent life
in the Universe.
We're overjoyed to find
that we're not alone.
My name is Anna, and I am
the leader of my people.
We're delighted
to meet you,
but we need your help.
We're far from home...
After we've
replenished ourselves
and shared with you
what we can,
we will leave you,
hopefully better
than we found you.
We look forward to getting
to know our new friends.
There will be
more communication
with your world's leaders
in the hours to come.
Until then,
we are of peace
always.
"We're all God's creatures"?
That's how the Vatican explains
the existence of aliens?
Yes.
- They decided that in a day?
- Yes.
Rattlesnakes
are God's creatures, too.
Doesn't mean
they're good for us.
- Have faith in our leaders, Jack.
- I do, Father.
It's just that there's not a lot
of scripture on the subject.
Meaning?
I'm at a loss to explain
how God and aliens
exist in the same world.
Aren't you?
What do you want
to do, Jack?
Call the Vatican and
question their position?
No, I just...
I don't know what to do.
All we can do is
pray and minster
to our congregation.
Our congregation
amounts to two bag ladies,
a heroin addict
and Roy.
That may be, Father Landry,
but we will minister
to any size... congregation.
And it appears
- there's some kind of translation...
- Look at that.
It--It's opening up.
Oh! Dude--Dude,
that is so cool!
I was right there, man.
I was right
underneath that thing.
Ohh! Why didn't
I come with you, man?
They're calling themselves
"the Visitors."
You say that
like it bothers you.
Visitors are old friends
who drop by for a drink.
Did you see that we got
a COMSAT alert today?
Uh, no, I was a little busy
looking at the spaceships
outside my window.
You're looking
at terrorist alerts?
The chatter among
terrorist cells worldwide
dropped like a rock
when the V's showed up.
Except for one of the cells
we've been tracking.
Their chatter--instead of
falling off, it actually spiked.
So what, you think
there's a connection
between the two?
We intercepted an uncoded
message from them.
As of yesterday,
they're suddenly looking to
acquire large amounts of C-4.
Why do that unless
you're going after a target?
Like say us,
while we're distracted?
I'll run the databases. I'll put
together a profile on them.
Thank you.
You watching?
Yeah, I'm watching.
Anna and her entourage
will be escorted
into the building where she...
Hey, how are you with all of this?
Are you and Tyler okay?
We're fine.
Did you hear
from the ex?
He, uh, he left a message.
He wanted us to know
he's okay. Um.
I'm not bitter. It's fine.
I feel good, happy.
Hey, you know that
I'm here for you,
anything you need.
Look, we'll hit the ground
running tomorrow.
Go be a mom.
You rock.
These are live pictures
coming to you from the lobby
of the United Nations...
- Hey, Mom, it's starting.
- Yeah.
Here--here is Anna.
She is now approaching
the mike for a statement.
- Let's listen in.
- Anna, please! Anna!
- Damn, she's hot.
- I know, right?!
Right here, guys.
This is
an inspiring moment
for us all--
Mankind and visitors coming together.
We are honored
by your friendship.
We will cherish it,
nurture it,
and never abandon it.
We are
of peace always.
Anna! Anna!
Anna,
how long have you been...
Anna, what do
you have to say
about the damage caused
by your arrival?
Explain the similarities
between visitors and humans.
Our scientists say
it's impossible.
Our scientists
can explain it.
That's not an answer.
Why don't you explain it?
Hey, why don't you
show some respect?
Ooh!
Do you have a question?
Yeah. I have a question.
Is there such a thing
as an ugly visitor?
I don't understand.
Oh, you all seem to be
what we consider attractive.
Thank you.
You're not
so bad yourself.
No, I'm sorry.
No one allowed past this point.
Come back here! Anna!
It was a truly
remarkable moment.
In the midst of all the chaos
and, yes,
even hostility from some,
came something unexpected
from our new friends--
a sense of humor.
Should the press
be so tough on the V's?
They did just get here,
after all.
When we come back,
I'll be joined by a panel
of media experts
to discuss that
and much, much more.
Stay with us.
We'll be right back.
I want him.
It's been three weeks
since the Visitors' arrival
yet thousands
are still flocking
to see the mother ships
in person.
As a result, host cities
find themselves in the midst
of a mini-economic boom--
Tourism, spending
on V merchandise--
All a welcome shot in the arm
to local economies.
The newly opened
visitor healing centers
are drawing huge crowds.
People afflicted
with one of the 65 ailments
the V's can cure
are jamming the centers, hoping
for their own personal miracle.
And government officials
have begun talks
to open
Visitor embassies.
But not everyone
likes the idea.
Violent protests
denouncing the V's
have broken out
in numerous host cities.
And more demonstrations are
planned in the days to come.
More on this...
We finally got
a real lead on our cell.
Our cell?
- I've heard that one before.
- No, this is a good one.
That's my coffee.
A truck suspected
of hauling drugs
was impounded by N.Y.P.D.
last night.
They searched for residue--
no drugs.
But they did find
traces of...
C-4.
Uh-huh. See this?
The truck came from here
on Long Island.
- Nice!
- Field trip?
Can I drive?
No.
- Copy that.
- Silos are empty.
We're still searching
the grounds,
but I gotta tell you, E.,
this feels like another dead end.
- Yeah.
- What's this,
20 leads we found
on this cell so far?
- Every one of them's fallen through.
- Uh-huh.
What?
Look at the sat photo.
- Yeah?
- That's our truck.
What is a white truck doing
parked in front of that shack?
Nothin'.
I think we can
rule out suicide.
C-4.
Yeah, this is Ryan.
I need your help.
How'd you get
this number?
They're here.
It's starting.
I'm not that guy anymore.
Don't call me again.
Hey.
- Ready for lunch?
- Hey. Oh, yeah.
I'm hungry.
What if
that was important?
Sweetheart, there is nothing
more important than you.
How'd you get tickets?
Dude, I can't believe
we're about to see
the inside
of a freakin' spaceship.
You rock.
Holy!
This is awesome.
Dude!
This is incredible, man!
- It's like an amusement park.
- ...To the main docking station
Will only take
about two minutes,
so hang on tight
and enjoy the ride.
Wow.
Unbelievable, man.
Step this way, please,
and welcome.
Hello.
Welcome to
the New York mother ship.
My name is Lisa.
The examiner says the body's
been dead less than a day,
but he was tortured
before he was killed.
They've been printing
fake docs--passports, I.D.s.
Best fakes
I've ever seen.
It's a major operation,
but no one was here.
They cleared out
like they knew we were coming.
We'll get the prints
off the victim,
see if we can get his I.D.
Our ability
to manipulate gravity
is essential
for long-term space travel.
Dude, dude,
check it out.
Oh, dude. That V girl's
coming over here.
Be cool.
Having a good time?
Having a great time.
Good.
Have you heard about our
new peace ambassador program?
Peace ambassador program?
Yeah. You sign up,
hang out with V's,
learn about our culture,
and you act as V ambassadors
to your own communities.
You even get a uniform.
Ah, it sucks. You have to be
18 years old to join.
We're only 17.
You can still join. You just
need your parent's signature.
Yeah. Well, that's, uh,
kind of a tough sell right now.
Our parents don't even know
we're here.
It's too bad. I just got assigned
to the New York chapter.
We could've spent
some time together.
We're all so quick
to jump on the bandwagon.
And a ride on
the bandwagon, it's...
It sounds like fun.
But before we get on,
let us at least make sure
it is sturdy...
and sound.
Let us
at least examine it
to really make sure
it is something that we want
to climb aboard.
No one is saying,
"Don't trust the Visitors."
Don't they need to earn
our trust?
It's something we all need
to think about.
I thought we were clear
about this, Jack.
People need to hear the V's are
part of God's plan.
They hear it from you,
Father.
They need to hear it
from you, too.
I thank God for the Visitors
every day, Jack.
This church stood empty
for years. Now look at it.
The Visitors are not
driving people away from God.
They're driving people
back to God.
People are scared, Father.
That's why they come.
But they come, and that's
the blessing in disguise.
It bothers me
that they showed up
right when we needed them
the most.
The world's in bad shape,
Father.
Who wouldn't welcome
a savior right now?
I agree they're a godsend,
and we should be grateful.
But that's the danger.
Under the right conditions
and with enough time,
gratitude can morph
into worship...
Or worse--devotion.
Hey.
I thought you priest types
would like to see somethin'.
They healed me.
I got no pain.
My God, Roy.
It's amazing.
Yeah.
Ty.
Come here
for a second.
Your principal sent me
this link to this...
awesome video.
What are you doing
on my account?
Check it out.
More, more, more!
Come on!
V's rule! Come on! Hurry up.
There's gonna be people coming.
- V's rule!
- V's rule, man!
First and foremost, the fact
that you're tagging now--
So proud.
I called Brandon's folks to kind of,
you know, spread the joy.
They weren't surprised.
They said that you two
are obsessed with the V's.
I'm not obsessed.
Really? Because this looks
very obsessive to me.
Texts, instant messages.
And here's
an--an entire page
about how to spread their word
through tagging.
Those aren't even
my links.
Brandon sent them to me.
Oh. Well, that's okay then.
Brandon sent them to you.
So you're gonna do whatever
Brandon or--or the V's
or who--whoever
tells you to do?
- You have to think for yourself, Tyler.
- I do think for myself!
Tagging someone's property
because a web site tell you to
- is thinking for yourself?
- You call it tagging.
But you know what? The V's--
They call it spreading hope.
Okay.
You have to talk to me.
Talk to me.
You and me, we talk.
What's going on with you?
Is it
because of your dad?
Is it because he left?
You're blaming him?
At least
he has an excuse
to be out of touch
with his kid.
He left me.
I did not leave.
I am here for you.
Oh, when you're here.
There he is--
the man of the hour.
Hello, Mr. Decker.
Hello.
- What's going on, Freddie?
- You've been selected.
For?
Anna would like to do
a live broadcast from the ship,
and intimate one-on-one to help
ease the protests against us.
She'd like you
to do the interview.
I-I-I got it.
Who was that?
It's no one.
- No one?
- Yes. No one.
You've been getting
a lot of calls from "no one."
It's nothing.
Okay?
We don't do this,
you and me--
Keep secrets.
Talk to me.
What's going on?
Sweetheart...
Just... don't read things
into things, okay?
It was no one. Really.
So pretty...
- I forgot my spoon.
- Yeah.
Uh, can I get
an extra spoon?
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
What do you know?
Another fake one.
Others like this.
Solve the case yet,
Sherlock?
Not one name,
not one photo,
not anything
from these passports
matches anyone
in our system.
How can you not find this guy?
He's very creepy.
If only "creepy"
were a biometric parameter
in our facial recognition
software.
You're kind of sexy when
you talk all computer-y.
- I am?
- Absolutely.
What's this?
Progress. I I.D.ed
our victim from the silo.
His name is
Owen Chapman.
This is a search warrant
for his house.
All right.
Clear here!
Yeah, I'll check...
They knew
we were coming again.
Someone tipped them off.
Who are you calling?
Owen.
Owen--our victim Owen?
Text.
"To: All attending tonight.
"Location: 400 Pier Avenue,
Brooklyn, 10:00 P.M. Pass code.
"If you're new,
be prepared for the test.
Any info you can share
about this cell is important."
Owen was going to a meeting
about a sleeper cell?
If you have info
about a sleeper cell,
you call the cops.
You don't go to a meeting.
Ryan.
Stay away from me,
Georgie.
Ryan, please.
Look, I told you I'm not
that guy anymore, okay?
- Stop calling me.
- We need your help.
"We"?
Who's "we"?
There's about 25 of us.
We've only met a couple times
but we're still recruiting.
Again?
You're trying that again
after all those people
got killed the last time?
We're being a lot more careful
this time.
Please, you gotta help us.
Look, I'm about
to get engaged, okay?
I'm not gonna
put my fiancé at risk.
If I get involved,
it puts her at risk,
and I'm not gonna
let that happen.
So you're just gonna sit
there on the sidelines?
You know how many lives
are at stake?
She doesn't know
about my past, okay?
I'd like to keep it
that way.
That's where we're meeting
if you change your mind...
Or grow a conscience.
I liked your sermon
the other day.
You're right
to question the V's.
Are you all right?
I know the real reason
they're here, Father,
and I am not
the only one.
The real reason?
The V's are
gonna obliterate us.
You're bleeding!
I was coming to see you.
- The V's did this to me.
- Let me get you some help.
No, no, no, no.
Take this
and go to this address
and give it
to the people there.
All right,
all the information's inside.
- Promise me.
- Okay.
Please, it's important.
Okay. Okay, okay.
I'm gonna get you some help.
I'll be right back.
Thanks again for choosing me
to do this.
- I'm really excited.
- So are we.
Do you have any questions
before we go to air?
No. Just be sure
not to ask anything
that would paint us
in a negative light.
Excuse me?
Don't ask any questions that
would portray us negatively.
Ask ones like you did
when we first met.
Oh, I think
there's a mistake.
I'm a journalist.
It's my job
to ask questions
even if they make
the other person uncomfortable.
That was not
my understanding.
Standing by to go to air.
Afraid I don't have
a choice.
This interview
is now canceled.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
hang on. Hang on.
Look, this is just
how it's done.
I swear I'll be fair.
You'll need to be more than fair
if you want to proceed.
Two minutes to air.
We can't be seen
in a negative light.
This interview
would elevate your career,
wouldn't it, Mr. Decker?
Don't you want
to elevate your career?
You don't even know
what this meeting is,
and you're just gonna
go in like you're invited.
They're expecting people they
haven't met before, so, yeah.
This is stupid.
Why don't we call for backup?
You know why.
Because you think that
there's a mole tipping off our cell.
It's a closed loop
if it's just you and me.
All right, then
I'm coming in with you.
No. It's a bad idea.
I need you
to watch the perimeter.
I will be back
in 30 minutes.
If I'm not,
you can call in the cavalry.
I'm here
for the meeting.
This is a word-of-mouth group.
You're here because
someone we trust
personally referred you.
This is how we do things.
This woman is a doctor.
She'll be injecting a small dose
of anesthetic into each of you.
Wait--wait a minute.
Anesthetic for what...
exactly?
Good evening
and welcome.
Tonight,
"Prime Focus with Chad Decker"
is proud to present
an up close and personal
interview with Anna,
the Visitor high commander.
On behalf of all of us,
I wanna thank you
for this opportunity to get
to know you a little better.
Thank you, Chad,
and please, feel free
to ask anything and everything.
I'm here to discuss all topics
without reserve.
I want you to confirm
that you see skull bone.
Take a good look
at it.
It's important.
You're next.
What is life like
where you come from?
We come from a place
of great beauty,
vast cities,
massive oceans.
Much like Earth.
Though unlike you,
we don't divide ourselves
into countries.
We're one united people.
You've all
passed the test.
Test for what?
To ensure
that you're not a Visitor.
In order
to walk among us,
they disguise
their appearance
by cloning human flesh
over their own reptilian skin.
I thought everyone here
was up to speed.
The Visitors
didn't just get here.
They've been here
for years.
You've said we're
the only other intelligent life
you've encountered
in your travels.
Yes.
Humanity is a rare gift,
one we hold
in the highest regard.
For decades, they've been
implementing a plan
that will result
in the extermination
of every man, woman and child
on the face of this earth.
We're honored and privileged
to be able to assist mankind
with our knowledge
and technology.
Truth be told,
it stirs great emotion in us.
So you are emotional beings?
We are,
but we've evolved
to quickly process and expel
all negative feelings.
Happiness, we've learned,
comes from tranquility
and peace.
V's posing as humans
established themselves
in all facets of life,
whether it be business,
government,
religion, the military.
It took years.
And once
embedded among us,
they set out to cause
worldwide instability--
Unnecessary wars,
economic meltdown,
faith twisted
into extremism.
If you could speak
to the protesters,
what would you say?
That embracing change
is never easy,
but the reward
for doing so
can be far greater than
anything you can imagine.
Tonight
we're announcing
the expansion
of our healing centers.
The goal is to open one in every
major city across the world.
The final stage
of the Visitors' plan
began with them
revealing themselves to us.
They gain trust
with the promise
of friendship and technology.
And, of course,
all they're really doing
is positioning themselves
as the saviors of mankind.
The intent goes beyond
just healing.
We want to provide complete
medical services to all.
You're talking about...
universal health care?
I believe that's what
you call it, yes.
By the time
people figure this out,
it'll be too late.
They'll take over...
unless we can stop 'em.
I see the looks.
It's the first time hearing this
for some of you.
You think we're crazy.
Right?
Do you have any proof?
You know,
other than scary stories
being passed around
the Internet.
Who are you?
Who referred you?
It doesn't matter.
I'm leaving.
Wait, wait. I have proof...
I think.
It's a bunch of photos--
Supposedly
Visitors living on Earth.
- This guy is a visitor?
- Yeah.
This guy is
a terrorist.
He's part of a sleeper cell.
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
A sleeper cell of visitors.
Yeah, a sleeper cell
of visitors.
You did a brave thing
coming here tonight.
Well, if I'm so brave,
why am I scared to death?
I think
that makes you human.
I'm Erica.
Jack.
Get down!
Ryan!
What the hell, Dale?!
Aah! Aah!
No, Erica!
Let's go!
Where the hell
did they come from?
- We were so careful this time.
- Georgie--
No. You were right
to walk away.
- What hope do we have?
- There is hope.
But they are animals!
No. No.
Not all of them.
I was wrong to walk away
from this, Georgie.
You were right to fight.
There's others out there
like me...
Other traitors, deserters.
We'll help.
Ryan.
Where you going?
I gotta go tell Val
I'm leaving.
It's not safe for her
to be around me anymore.
Mr. Decker?
Mr. Decker, may I have
a word with you, please?
Anna loved you.
I'm sure she did.
She wants you to know we intend
to call on you again.
She trusts you.
Yeah, I'm not so sure
I trust her.
Look, I'm sorry for
the misunderstanding tonight,
but you did the right thing.
Compromising one's principles
for the greater good
is not a shameful act.
It's a noble one.
Really?
I find that hard to believe.
Your people
are easily threatened.
What you did tonight
went a long way
toward reassuring them.
What's the harm?
She backed me
into a corner.
She could've chosen anyone
to interview her.
She chose you.
We would like to continue
with the arrangement.
Whenever Anna has something
significant to say,
we would like her
to say it through you.
Unless you have
an aversion
to a worldwide audience
hanging on your every word.
Val?
I hate myself.
You just--you kept getting
these calls from "no one," and...
I thought there was
somebody else.
I-I looked around
and I found this.
You were gonna ask me
to marry you.
I was even gonna
get down on one knee.
Do you still love me?
More than
you'll ever know.
I don't know
who to trust anymore.
I can't get the image
of Dale just lying there
out of my head.
What do we do now?
We help
build a resistance.
We recruit...
Bring more into the fold.
We have to be careful.
We'll be careful,
but we have to fight.
Oh, we'll fight.
They have
a big head start.
They're arming themselves
with the most...
powerful weapon out there.
Yeah?
What's that?
Erica, what big weapon?
Devotion.
To the dawn
of a new day.
We are of peace always.
Sync: YesCool
[Addic7ed.com]
Final Edits: VeRdiKT
[Subscene.com / Addic7ed.com]