- Paige, where you been? You're late.
- I know. I'm sorry, I got tied up.
Where? At Richard's?
No, I was at work.
Get your mind out of the gutter, missy.
Hey, you're the one that orbs home
to find lingerie.
Two times. I did that twice.
Yeah, it's about the only time
we ever see you anymore.
- Why did I come? To get picked on?
- Because we love you.
We kind of miss you.
I am not at Richard's that much.
Fine, maybe I am. But I am just
an orb away if you need help.
The thing is,
we just gotta be careful.
If we stray too far from each other,
demons take advantage.
We've learned that lesson
the hard way a few times.
I know, I know, I get it.
I just really don't wanna think of us
living together in 50 years.
Twenty, 30 years, tops.
We can move to Hong Kong
so I can see Jason whenever I want.
How do you say "dream on"
in Chinese?
- Impressive.
- Berlitz.
Okay, what about you, missy?
- Spill it!
- Spill what?
Come on, you and Greg?
Put out any fires lately?
Is that supposed to be
a fireman reference?
- Yeah, you like it?
- Wait a minute.
You're going out with a fire-fighter?
Proof positive
you haven't been around much.
Let's see, they've been seeing
each other for about three weeks,
and someone, I won't say who,
although it's not the fireman,
is avoiding taking it to the next step.
I'm not avoiding.
I'm just a little reluctant, that's all.
My dear, it is time
to get back in the saddle.
Now a cowboy reference.
Piper, you just need to relax
and let it happen.
Easy for you to say. You weren't
sleeping with an angel for three years.
Yeah, but you were nervous when you
and Leo first started... You know?
I seem to remember that you used
to freeze him during all the good parts.
Hey, maybe you should...
No. I'm not freezing Greg.
I'm so nervous,
I'd probably blow him up.
- Well?
- Gutter, gutter, gutter.
What are you guys talking about?
Stuff.
- Hey, where you going?
- I gotta go work on the next demon...
...stration.
Why don't you relax
and have a drink with us?
Thanks, but I didn't
come here to relax.
That is one bitchy whitelighter.
You're telling me.
Hey, Piper, why don't you go talk
to the guilt machine over there?
Bianca.
I don't understand.
What are you doing here?
There'll be time to explain later.
But for now...
You know, all work and no... Hey!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
What happened? Who was she?
I don't know.
- Is that the mark?
- No, it looked more like a bird.
A bird? So maybe the Audubon Society
sent the demon after us?
Just keep looking.
Guys, I'm telling you, I'm fine.
Don't sweat it.
- You sure she wasn't a darklighter?
- I'm sure.
What else would be after
a whitelighter?
I don't know.
That's what worries me.
Piper blew her away,
what's the big deal?
The big deal is someone
tried to kill you, Chris.
Look at me. Not a scratch, nothing.
How did she get that close
to you anyway
if you didn't even know
who she was?
- We really ought to fix that, you know.
- Come on, who's after you?
Has it crossed your mind
that maybe she wasn't after me?
Maybe she was trying
to get to them.
- Kind of makes sense.
- Finally, somebody's listening.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've got some work to take care of.
- He's not telling the truth.
- Leo, maybe there's nothing to tell.
- Could you sense anything?
- From Chris?
No, I can never sense
anything from him.
- What are you thinking?
- I'm thinking
that if we figure out who she was,
we might figure out who Chris is.
Well, we're not gonna find it in here,
at least not until we have
more to go on.
So you guys know where
I'm gonna be if you need me.
Yeah, I gotta go too.
Wait, you're just gonna let them go?
What do you want me to say?
They have lives too.
Besides, what more can we do?
Figure out who the demon is and
make sure nobody else is after him.
I'll get it, you just keep checking
on the Book, okay?
No, Leo, really, I'd rather you...
Can I help you?
Yeah, is Piper home?
Who's asking?
- I'm Greg. She's expecting me.
- Leo, I got it.
Sorry. Running a little late.
- Leo? As in your?
- Yeah.
One and the same.
Leo, Greg. Greg, Leo.
Nice to finally meet you.
Thanks. "Finally."
So are you gonna be okay taking care
of everything? Wyatt and Chris?
Yeah, absolutely.
Really, everything will be fine.
If anything comes up, I'll call you.
Okay, thanks. Good night.
Will you marry me?
You're asking me now?
Here?
This is still our spot, Bianca,
no matter what he's done to it.
Marry me.
On one condition.
You come back to me. Safely.
Have I ever let you down before?
What's that?
Chris!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I don't think
it had time to transmit.
I cannot believe he's sending
probes after us now.
I'm gonna kill that son of a bitch.
No. No, you're not.
- You're gonna stick to the plan.
- But he knows.
No, if he knew, he wouldn't
have sent the probe.
You have to go back, Chris.
It's the only way to stop him.
It's the only way to change all this.
Morning.
- Wow.
- Wow?
One of the most powerful witches in
the world and all you can say is "wow."
I don't know, maybe I just need
a little more inspiration.
- Well?
- I...
I still think "wow"
pretty much covers it.
You better be careful,
because a girl could get used to this.
That's the plan.
Did you tell your sisters
you were moving out?
- No.
- Look, it just...
It hasn't really been the right time.
Things have been a little funky and...
There's never a right time.
You don't understand. Piper would
probably blow a major gasket,
and then we've got
all the family obligations
and, like it or not,
we're stronger together.
You gotta do something for you.
Can I get that?
It's the house.
Hello?
Yeah.
When I said I needed you,
I meant a fully clothed you.
Oh, please, Leo.
What's the big emergency?
What would you say if I said whoever
attacked Chris was called a Phoenix?
Well, I would say "What's a Phoenix?"
And then you'd probably tell me.
Well, they're a family
of assassin witches
who are very elite, very powerful and
were born with a distinctive birthmark
symbolizing the rise
from Salem's ashes.
Does the Book say what they want?
Just whatever bounty they're after,
which in this case is Chris,
which means they're still after him.
They won't stop until they succeed.
Did you call Phoebe and Piper?
No. Phoebe's at work
and Piper came in kind of late,
so I didn't wanna disturb her.
Did she come home alone?
- I don't know.
- Hey.
- Talking about me?
- Morning. Hi. No.
Listen, Wyatt's been fed,
and I'm gonna get some coffee
and Paige will fill you in.
What's going on?
Oh, Leo just found out
that a coven of assassin witches
called "the Phoenix" are after Chris.
So that's what you guys
were talking about?
Yeah, in the beginning,
and then I just kind of asked him
if you'd maybe come home
with anybody.
- I see.
- Did you?
Oh, come on! If a girl can't ask that,
what can a girl ask?
Actually, no.
I'm sorry.
Maybe he's just not the right guy.
No, it's not Greg. It's just me.
It's just weird now that I'm a mom.
I feel like I'm
betraying Wyatt somehow.
I think you're just betraying yourself.
Yeah, I know, it's just weird.
So a coven of assassin witches?
- Yep.
- Maybe we should call Phoebe.
No, I think we can do this by ourselves.
I don't think you have to bother her.
What if we need the power of three
after we find them?
You didn't need the power of three
to blow up the last one.
No, but...
So we need to try this whole
power of two thing,
learn how to be flexible, right?
So you stay here,
I'm gonna go get the scrying crystal.
Phoebe, I offered you the time off,
take it.
Go see Jason in Hong Kong.
It's just another airport, another city.
You can always send in the column.
E-mail, fax machine!
It's the 21 st century
and I'd like to welcome you to it.
When I say "take time,"
I don't mean a vacation.
Go live there for a while,
give it a shot.
- Elise, l...
- Go!
I want you to listen to me.
It's time I gave you
some advice for once.
Don't let it be work.
What do you mean?
There's a whole generation of women
out there who followed the dream,
built successful careers,
but at the expense
of everything else.
I'm not saying I think
they all made mistakes,
because some of them
are very happy.
But some of us aren't.
Trust me,
you don't wanna
wake up one day and realize
that all you've got is your career.
Hi, how's it going?
- Can I help you?
- Hopefully.
Yeah, see, we just moved in
from out of state,
and wanted to get to know
our neighbours.
Oh, well, welcome.
- Where did you move from?
- Phoenix.
Really?
Please, come in, come in.
Thank you.
- Nice place.
- Yeah, real nice.
Thank you.
Mommy, Mommy.
Mommy. Mommy, can I play with...
Bianca, can you give Mommy
a minute, okay?
Okay.
Go and play with your toys.
- I'll be right in, okay?
- Okay.
Now what?
Look out!
The kid.
Hurry, Bianca.
They can re-form?
Apparently. Which means the one
that attacked Chris can too.
You really shouldn't try
to orb anymore, you know?
It could kill you.
Is that what you want?
If that's what I wanted,
you'd already be dead.
All I want is to bring you back.
How did you know I'd be here?
Same reason you knew
I'd be waiting here.
- I mean, this is still our spot, isn't it?
- No.
This is what we hoped it would be.
This is what we were trying to preserve
for our future. Do you remember?
We were naive to think
we could change anything.
- To stop him.
- You don't believe that.
- Or at least you didn't.
- Well, I do now.
What happened to you, Bianca?
How did he turn you back?
That's not important.
What is important is I was interrupted
in stripping you of your powers.
And if I don't finish what I started,
you'll die soon.
Think of it as an infection.
And I'm the only one
with the antidote.
Here or there, I am dead anyway.
No.
He gave me his word
he wouldn't hurt you.
Please, Chris.
Don't make this any harder
than it has to be.
Wait, how old is the little girl?
I don't know. Four, 5?
Chris!
Bianca...
Oh, my God, what is that?
- I don't know.
- Doesn't matter, just heal him.
Why didn't he tell us about that?
Why doesn't he tell us
about a lot of things?
What's the problem?
He's not healing.
Something's draining his powers
and blocking mine, it's like a virus.
A virus named Bianca.
- You think she did this?
- It's gotta be.
But it doesn't explain why she would
come back from the future to kill him.
Well, somebody had to have sent her,
she's a hired gun.
Well, we have to find her to save him,
figure out what she did...
What is it?
Oh, my God. He loves her.
- Loves who? Bianca?
- Yeah.
She broke his heart.
Engagement ring.
Obviously an acrimonious split.
Well, at least we have
something to scry for her now.
You work on the vanquishing potion
in case she's not in the mood to help.
Bianca.
Welcome to
the Halliwell Memorial Museum.
A tribute to magic and, of course,
the Charmed Ones.
Please remember there is no
digi-capturing, no holographing
and most certainly no magic allowed
while inside the museum.
That's a big one.
Don't worry about those probes, folks,
they're merely scanning for witches.
As we pass through the foyer, note the
family portraits hanging on the walls
which date all the way back
to the witch trials.
Nicely done.
Around you, you'll notice just a few
of the many mythological creatures
the legendary sisters transformed into
in their demon-fighting heyday.
The Charmed Ones were responsible
for over 1,000 demon vanquishes
before they were finally
vanquished themselves.
Now, the time is 25 years ago.
Imagine yourself standing here
on this very floor
when the Charmed Ones
were reborn.
Okay, what was that?
I think that means
you're supposed to be here.
Scares them every time.
Let's go to the kitchen where many
of the sisters' potions were brewed,
some of which are available
for purchase in the gift shop.
Of course, the attic was
the preferred spot for potion-making,
principally because that's where they
kept the famed Book of Shadows,
which is where we're headed next.
A little background on the manor itself.
It was actually destroyed...
- Hey, you two, move along.
- Wait for it.
Are you deaf? I sa...
Come on.
We should be safe here
until the museum closes.
Then we'll go get the Book.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
It's just sometimes I forget
who you really are.
Hey.
Come here.
You mean how I used to be, Chris.
Before I met you.
So, what do we do now?
We say goodbye.
Who are you
and what do you want?
Where's the grimoire?
One more time. Who are you?
Who do you think I am...
...Mother?
- Bianca?
In the flesh.
Now, where's the grimoire?
I have to get the Charmed Ones
off my tail fast. I need a spell to do it.
I don't understand,
how is this possible?
Look, I don't have time
for reunions, okay?
And I won't make the same mistake
a thousand other demons have.
Now, where's the damn book?
Thanks.
- Where is the inhibition spell?
- How is that gonna help?
I know the Charmed Ones,
I studied their history.
This is when they want
separate lives.
If I release certain inhibitions,
I can get them to pursue them.
The spell won't last long.
It just has to distract them
so I can get what I came for.
Got it.
Thanks.
Wait.
Do you have to leave so soon?
Can't I help?
Yeah.
Someday, when I ask you
what it feels like to kill,
don't lie to me.
Don't tell me you don't feel a thing.
Hang in there, buddy.
We found Bianca,
she's at her mother's.
- Little Bianca?
- No, the one we want.
Here. Something for Chris
to remember her by, or not.
Got the vanquishing potion,
so after we orb over there, I'm gonna...
- You're gonna what?
- I'm gonna move into Richard's house.
- Are you? Good for you.
- That's a great idea.
And I think I'm gonna go check out
what's going on in Hong Kong.
- Cool.
- Hang on a second.
This isn't you guys.
You must be under some kind of spell.
You have to fight this.
- How can you fight your heart?
- Or your hormones?
Yeah.
Will you drop me off
on the way to Richard's?
- I would love to.
- Paige, Phoebe, listen to me.
Wait.
What do I tell them?
Don't tell them anything.
Just stick to your cover story. The less
they know about the future, the better.
- What if they find out who I really am?
- They won't.
Not as long as you can
pass yourself off as their whitelighter.
You're sure I won't lose my powers
when I go?
Not with this spell,
that's why we need it.
But just remember, protect baby Wyatt
and you protect the Charmed Ones.
Keep them alive for our future.
Great. No pressure there.
Chris, you know you're
the only one who can do this.
You're the only one
who can save us.
If I make it back.
Baby, you have to make it back...
...if you wanna marry me.
You really know how
to motivate a guy.
- Sure you can summon the real Book?
- Yeah.
- Away from him?
But we won't have much time
once it gets here.
His demons will be all over us.
We won't need much time.
Just long enough
to send you back to them.
Hurry.
Before he finds us.
Paige?
Phoebe, get back here right now.
That's an order.
Wyatt's sleeping
and the monitor is in the kitchen.
Okay, Piper, but you can't go.
What about Chris?
Wish me luck.
Come on. We're going home.
- Hey, hold it.
- Why?
Because I just wanna make sure
that you're sure about this.
What's the matter?
Am I not acting sure?
Yeah, it's just that, well, you've been
a little reluctant until now.
And I guess I'm just curious,
why the change?
Who knows? Who cares?
All I know is I want...
Oh, my God.
What? Are you out of your mind?
What are you, a peeping Elder now?
What's going on?
What am I doing here?
What are you doing here?
Counteracting a spell
that Bianca apparently cast on you.
- What kind of spell?
- One that lowers your inhibitions.
- Oh, boy.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So did she get Chris?
Yeah, and I'm hoping
if we can break the spell
on Phoebe and Paige,
we might be able to get Chris back.
Right, okay, so let's go.
You need to turn around,
because you don't get to see anymore.
Hi, how's it going?
- What are you doing here?
- Moving you back home. Hit her.
No time to explain. Come on. We gotta
get Phoebe or we'll never get Chris.
Just let me finish what I started.
You'll feel better soon, I promise.
That's it.
Easy does it.
Slow breaths.
- What did you do to me?
- I just saved your life.
By taking away my powers?
How are you gonna
bring me back anyway?
That spell's a one-way door.
It only goes backwards in time.
He created a new spell
because of you.
- One that works both ways.
- I'm touched.
You should be. He's gone to
a lot of trouble to get you back.
Yeah, I see that.
You know, you don't have
to believe me, Chris,
but this really is for the best.
Oh, really? How's that?
Because this is
your only chance to live.
If I fail, he'll just keep sending
more assassins back
and all they'll have
to bring home is a body.
Doesn't matter.
There's nothing left in the future
anymore anyway.
It's time.
I don't wanna go.
I don't wanna leave you.
Here.
This will remind you
why we're doing this.
And what's waiting for you here.
Just make sure you take care
of the guards, okay?
Then get out of here.
Because if he finds you,
if he knows you betrayed him,
he'll kill you.
Don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
"I call upon the ancient power
To help us in this darkest hour
Let the Book return to this place
Claim refuge in its rightful space"
- It worked.
- The spell, find the spell.
"Hear these words, hear the rhyme
Heed the hope within my mind
Send me back to where I'll find
What I wish, in place and time"
Bianca!
Go! Go!
You really expect me to
jump into this thing like before?
Not without a fight, no.
How can you be so cold?
How can you stand and pretend like we
never meant anything to each other?
I don't have a choice.
Bianca, please don't do this.
Don't give up on everything
that we fought for.
I'm not.
I'm just hoping
we can find another way.
Ready?
Hey, future girl!
- You were saying?
- Wow, she is good.
I can kill her in half the time
it takes you to think about it.
We still have enough potion
to vanquish you.
Maybe, but then you really will have
to hope the power of two will do.
Won't you, Paige?
Oh, you'd be surprised
what's in the history books.
Now put the vials down slowly.
Bianca, don't. Let her go
and I promise I'll go with you.
Chris, what are you doing?
If you kill her, there won't be a future
for us to go back to and you know it.
- What are you talking about?
- You'll see if you live long enough.
Piper, freeze them.
Okay, I get why she didn't freeze,
but why didn't he freeze?
- Unless he's a...
- I'm a witch too?
That's right.
Part witch, part whitelighter.
Just like you, Paige.
- You lied to us?
- I had to.
It was the only way
I could get you to trust me.
Trust you?
Never mind,
it doesn't matter anyway.
So that's it, you're just gonna leave?
I don't have a choice.
She stripped my powers.
Leo is gonna have to fix
that floorboard without me.
Let's go.
Welcome home, Chris.
Hello, Wyatt.
There's gotta be a spell
in here somewhere.
To take us to the future?
I don't think so.
Well, Bianca's a witch, she could do it,
how could she do it?
We don't know how.
How did we do it five years ago?
The Elders made
that happen, remember?
Well, you're an Elder,
make it happen.
- That was a unique situation.
- This isn't?
I don't like this either.
Don't you think I wanna save him?
I don't know if I wanna save him
or kick his ass.
That still doesn't change
all the good he's done.
You're singing a different tune.
You've come a long way, baby.
Okay, despite all his secrets,
I still believe that he came back
to protect Wyatt and that is enough
for me to wanna save him.
The question is how?
- Leo.
- What?
Fix the floorboard.
Maybe he was trying
to tell us something.
- Who? What?
- Maybe.
Maybe that's where Bianca was
taking him. To the attic in the future.
But that would still be there
in the future, wouldn't it?
Yeah, unless we fixed it.
Or used it to send him something,
something that he needed.
- Like what?
- His powers.
They're no threat to me.
Et tu, Chris?
Of all the people to betray me...
I didn't go back to betray you, Wyatt.
I went back to save you.
Save me? From what?
From whatever evil it was
that turned you.
That's always been
your problem, Chris.
Stuck in the old
good-versus-evil morass.
I'm so past that.
It's all about power,
it's as simple as that.
And whoever has
the most power wins, is that it?
That's it.
That's why I keep
this museum intact.
To remind everyone the power
from which I was born,
and that which I possess.
Too bad the rest of the city isn't faring
as well as your shrine here.
You know, if anyone else tried what
you tried, I'd kill them on the spot.
But you...
I've forgiven Bianca,
I can forgive you too.
If you promise
never to cross me again.
You know me better than that.
You said you could talk
some sense into him.
Leave her out of this.
Pardon me?
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- I'm trying, I'm trying.
There you go.
Okay, put it back.
You promised you wouldn't hurt him!
And you promised you'd turn him.
Just like I turned you,
or at least I thought I had.
Chris, please.
I didn't bring you here to die.
Don't worry, I know what I'm doing.
I think.
Have you lost your mind?
I don't need you.
Whatever you're gonna do,
do it fast.
I can't hold him for long.
"Power of witches, rise
Come to me from across the skies
Return my magic, give me back
All that was taken from the attack"
No!
Bianca. Bianca.
No. No. No.
Haven't we been here before?
Maybe we will be again.
Maybe.
You can finish what we started.
Hurry.
Take the spell
so he can't send anyone else.
Go.
"Hear these words, hear the rhyme
Heed the hope within my mind
Send me back to where I'll find
What I wish, in place and time"
No!
- Oh, my God, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Nice spell.
Yeah, but we just put it in there,
like, two seconds ago.
- The way time travel works...
- I don't wanna know,
I already have
a little headache, thanks.
You have some serious explaining
to do, young man.
I know.
Listen, I'm sorry I lied to you,
I really am, but...
No, no buts, it's about time
you tell us the truth. Now.
I can't.
But not because I don't want to.
There's only so much I can tell without
the future being changed too much.
Isn't that your whole point?
To come and change the future?
Yeah, but that was supposed to be
more like a surgical strike.
To save Wyatt.
What about Bianca?
Bianca won't be a threat
to anyone anymore.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
So you still all right
with me hanging around?
Absolutely.
But the next time you're in trouble,
you tell us.
Trust works both ways.
Okay.
If I can't save you,
I swear to God I'll stop you.
- Hey.
What's going on?
Well, I've been thinking.
Does that mean I'm in trouble?
I think it's time we make
some changes around here.
What kind of changes?
Like I think you should move
to Hong Kong with Jason
and you should move in
with Richard.
I never said I wanted that.
You didn't have to,
the spell did that for you. And you too.
Well, we can't leave you alone.
We have to stick together.
No, I know, believe me. I know.
But you can't keep sacrificing
your lives forever.
And neither can I.
Mom did that, Grams did it,
and even Prue.
And look what happened to them.
It's not a legacy I want us to inherit.
What if is doesn't work out,
us going our separate ways?
Well, we'll worry about it then.
You sure about this?
Yeah, I am.