How do we know Zankou's
not here waiting for us?
Magic School is protected from him.
Leo!
Still, now that Zankou's
got the Book of Shadows...
He can't use all of its powers,
not without ours. Leo?
But he could use it to get our powers.
It's been done before.
As long as we're here, we're safe.
- What's wrong?
- How are the boys?
- They're sleeping, why?
- Zankou's got the Book of Shadows.
What? How?
As soon as we figure it out,
we'll let you know.
- He broke us down.
- How does it explain...
Our powers are tied to the Book,
our emotions are tied to our powers.
- By making us vulnerable...
- He made the Book vulnerable too.
He knew us a little better
than we thought.
What is he really after?
What he's always after. Power.
The Nexus.
It's good to be back.
Okay, here you go.
How close are we?
We'd be a lot closer
if we could use our powers to open it.
The Nexus will view that
as a threat, destroy us all.
Remember, it's neither good nor evil.
It's just sheer, unadulterated power,
the kind the Charmed Ones
have been harbouring far too long.
Now it's my turn to play.
What will be your first move?
Once you possess it, I mean.
Oh, I don't know.
I'll have full access to the Book of
Shadows, of course, which means...
...l'll have ultimate power.
I hope I don't get bored.
The Nexus, My Lord.
Step back.
It is done.
Master. What are your orders?
What happened?
The sisters... they cast it
out of me with a spell!
From the Magic School? Lmpossible!
Nothing's impossible there!
- Where are you going?
- The Book of Shadows!
To find a way to stop them!
I think it worked.
- How do you know?
- If he'd already tapped into the Nexus,
he would have broken in by now.
Good thing you remembered that spell.
We can't just keep casting it.
He's gonna figure out a way
around it sooner or later.
We have to get the Book back
before he does.
- Okay, any ideas?
- No, I was hoping you'd have some.
Me? Why me?
Because you're the only one that still
has any confidence around here.
That's just 'cause I'm a good actor.
I hope you can fool the Book.
Unless we get our confidence back,
and fast, it may not let us get it back.
If Zankou gets the Nexus first,
there won't even be a point in trying.
We can't let that happen.
If he succeeds,
everything we've done means nothing,
and I'm not willing to live with that.
- Well, you might not have to.
- Then we go down fighting.
Which brings us back
to how do we stop him?
Okay, let's think about this
for a second.
We know Zankou
as well as he knows us, right?
Yeah, so?
So, what is the one thing that Zankou
wants more than the Nexus?
- Our heads on a platter?
- Exactly.
He hates us. He wants to kill us.
So why don't we give him a reason?
You know, piss him off enough so that
the focus is off the Nexus and onto us.
Could buy us time to get the Book back.
It just might work.
Yeah... unless he kills us first.
You Inspector Sheridan?
Yeah, who are you?
Agent Keyes, Homeland Security.
- You called, didn't you?
- Yes, yes.
I was not expecting you until tomorrow.
Let's just say I was anxious
to hear what you had to say.
All right. What do you know about
what happened to your Agent Brody?
- You tell me.
- He disappeared.
I think I know who knows why.
The same people who know
what happened to three other cops
who were killed or mysteriously
disappeared in the past seven years.
Inspectors Trudeau,
Rodriguez and Davidson.
Then there are the civilian cases,
including one of their sisters,
Prue Halliwell.
That's it?
That's it? Are you kidding?
What, you need more?
Okay.
How about I think they tried
to make me disappear too?
They put me in a coma,
tried to get me to forget what I knew.
Actually, Brody's the one who
put you in the coma, on my orders.
- What?
- They knew you were onto them.
We didn't want you
messing up our investigation.
- How dare you!
- Easy, Inspector.
This is bigger than you think,
much bigger.
Besides, I am here, aren't I?
- With Brody's tranq gun?
- No.
With answers.
The ones you've been looking for.
Okay.
Do you believe in the paranormal,
Inspector?
That there may be forces,
powers that exist beyond our own?
That's what the Halliwells
are involved in.
We want to blow the doors wide open
on that secret of theirs.
What are you looking for?
A reversal spell, to stop them
from keeping me from the Nexus.
Even if you find one, it might not work.
You said yourself that without
full access to the Book, that it...
I know what I said.
Perhaps a potion...
Why not just keep trying
to take in the Nexus? Outlast them.
After all, they can't keep pulling
it out of you, timing it just right.
Sooner or later,
you'll have the power long enough
to break through the protection of the
Magic School. Then you can kill them.
You don't know them like I do.
You can't take them head-on,
it doesn't work.
That's how demons die.
But not this demon. Not this time.
This is no time for personal vendettas.
I think your focus should be
the Nexus, not the witches.
Are you challenging me?
You brought me on as your counsel.
I'm merely acting as such.
If you are displeased, then...
No. No, you served me well,
and will continue to do so.
And to that end, go to the kitchen
and bring me up some mandrake,
henbane and some hemlock root.
- I'm making a potion.
- To do what?
To steal their powers.
There are other ways of gaining
full access to the Book of Shadows.
Wasn't there a confidence spell
in the Book of Shadows?
Yeah, remember we cast it
on that waiter at Quake?
Wow, Quake. That was a long time ago.
Maybe we should cast it on ourselves.
We could use a little confidence.
- But that won't piss off Zankou.
- It might help us get the Book back.
What if we... switched bodies
with him instead?
- Can't, he'd be in Magic School.
- Oh, right.
How about a love spell?
We can make him fall for one of us.
- Sorry, I'm taken.
- Yeah, well, I'm not.
Yeah, but you're not
that desperate. Are you?
Those demons have a way
of keeping you warm at night.
But that's only because
they have fire balls.
"Hear secret thoughts,
stretch the imagination..."
What if we turn you into a banshee again
and turn you loose on him?
Too much screeching,
it's hard on my voice.
Hey, I have an idea.
What if we humiliated him
and turned him into an animal,
like we did that one time
to everyone at P3?
That spell backfired.
Yeah, well, beggars can't be choosers.
Phoebe, Piper! Come here.
I think I got something.
What are they all doing here?
Reinforcements.
- You knew, didn't you?
- Knew about what?
About the Halliwells,
who they really are.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Were you gonna keep your mouth shut
even if I got killed?
- Hey, Inspector, listen...
- You listen to me!
I'm not busting you
because I can't prove that you knew.
I can't believe that you didn't tell me
and let them put me in a coma!
Hey, hold it! I helped find you, okay?
I'm the one who saved you.
You need to come in here
and you need to help us.
- "Us", who's "us"?
- Homeland Security.
They're all over it.
It's a federal case now.
Is something wrong?
No.
Morris, you can't run
from this anymore.
You can't protect them anymore.
Darryl, who is it?
I really don't have a choice.
Then you'd better not warn them
that we're coming or I will bust you!
Was that them?
No, it was... Sheridan.
Is everything okay?
It's not my problem, right?
They're on their own.
Presto!
Hand me one of those vials,
if you would.
How do you know it will work?
I don't. But I assume if it's in
their venerable Book, it should.
But they're hiding in the Magic School.
How are you gonna get close enough
to use it on them?
They're not gonna stay in for long.
It's not their style. As I was saying?
What the hell?
- Now!
- Something wicked in our midst
In our home where he exists
Are you all right?
Well, don't just stand there!
Kill them all!
The Book.
They're after the Book! Stop this!
Reverse the spell from whence I fell
Hurry, get to the Book. Go, go, go!
What happened?
It wouldn't let me take it.
We should have cast a confidence spell.
You're trespassing.
I failed you. Forgive me.
Actually, it was a complete success.
After all, we still have the Book.
And as an added bonus...
...I now have one of their powers.
Does it hurt?
Not any more than usual.
This is getting old.
- You're lucky to get out of there.
- Tell me about it.
He threw something at me,
maybe a potion or something.
- Did it do anything?
- I don't think so.
The magic from your Book
is not available to him yet.
"Yet" being the operative word.
Well, we wanted Zankou to focus on us.
Now, how do we survive that?
- You gotta get the Book back.
- We tried, but it won't let us take it.
Maybe he cast a protection spell on it?
Or maybe the Book
doesn't remember who we are.
Maybe 'cause we don't
remember who we are.
You've gotta remember.
You gotta go back, try again, together.
Leo's right, you have to get the Book
back, if only to destroy the Nexus.
Excuse me?
There's a spell in the Book you've never
used called "How to Banish a Suxen".
- A Suxen?
- Nexus, spelled backwards.
It was put in a long time ago
as a last resort,
in case we lost control of the Nexus,
to keep it from evil.
But if we destroy the Nexus,
good won't have access to it either.
We won't have access to it.
I don't think the Elders think we'll
be around long enough to worry.
Not necessarily.
We're simply taking precautions.
Including, let me guess,
sealing yourselves off from us
in case we fail.
Be well.
Excuse me!
That's what you're leaving us with?
- Now what?
- You can't just give up, that's what.
- Leo...
- Look, I mean it.
Your plan is working.
You got Zankou off the Nexus.
You need to distract him long enough
to get the Book.
He's too powerful.
The hell he is!
You guys are the Charmed Ones!
No one is more powerful.
How many times have you proven that?
You can't just give up.
You have a legacy to carry on,
to pass on to the next generation,
to our boys.
- To your future kids.
- A bit wordy.
Well, you know him with the exposition.
It doesn't mean he's not right.
The question is, what's our next move?
We can't ask the leprechauns
and the trolls for more help.
No, but maybe we could ask some bats.
- Do I need to replace you?
- No. I can still fight.
I just don't know why we have to.
Meaning?
Meaning Zankou has left us
vulnerable to attack for no reason!
- Are you questioning him?
- Aren't you?
You know he should have taken in
the power of the Nexus hours ago.
But instead, he's given the witches an
opening and we've lost demons, friends!
Hold your tongue, Salko.
Or you'll lose more than that.
Send the others away.
They're no longer needed.
You're going after the Nexus?
Yes... but only after I get the
other sisters' powers. I set a trap.
- Was I not clear?
- Perfectly.
Away!
Do you really think they'll leave
the safety of the Magic School?
- I know they will.
- How do you know that?
Now that I have Phoebe's powers,
I know what they'll do next.
They will not humiliate me again.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
I'll get it for you.
SFPD, this is...
- Well?
- The judge denied our request
- for a tap. He wanted more evidence.
- If we had more evidence,
we wouldn't need the tap.
We gotta get in there.
Call the AG. We need to speak
to him. We'll circumvent this.
- You going to claim they're terrorists?
- I'm gonna do whatever it takes.
Then let me go in.
Put the camera on me.
No offence, Inspector,
but I've got better trained agents.
Nobody the sisters know.
They'll let me in, they'll have to.
I'll get you your evidence,
in living colour.
- How?
- I'll provoke them.
Shouldn't be hard.
They hate me already.
If they've got these powers, as you
say, I will make them use them.
I'm not willing to risk it.
Maybe you're not, but I am!
You can do whatever you want with them.
You can expose them, hide them,
dissect them, I don't care.
I just want to be the one to bust them.
Okay, now what?
- We draw out the queen.
- How?
Okay...
Okay, ladies, a little bit
of help here, please.
Bats!
Who are you?
- Stop the attack!
- Then we'll kill all your vampires.
Cease!
What do you want?
Actually, your help.
We have something in common.
Neither one of us wants a certain demon
to take over the Underworld.
I'm listening.
If you help us stop him,
you can keep the Underworld
in disarray, like you like it.
- We'll grant you immunity.
- Immunity?
From us.
We'll never come after your family.
Better, you won't have
to answer to Zankou.
- Interested?
- Very.
Okay. Then follow us.
Fools.
What took you so long?
Where's the queen?
Oh, she betrayed you.
I got to her first.
I knew you were coming,
thanks to your premonition powers.
And now I have yours.
Looking for this?
Why didn't you kill them
when you had the chance?
Because I don't have
all their powers... yet.
Okay, easy, easy. Sit down right here.
A little help down here, please!
A little healing!
They're not coming down.
We're on our own now.
Yeah, two powers down.
Something tells me we're not
getting out of this one, girls.
Sorry.
Why does Zankou keep picking on me?
Why can't he attack one of you two?
Makes you feel better,
I think I'm gonna be next.
He must have gotten the potion
from the Book to steal our powers.
He's two-thirds of the way there,
unless he's got enough to get in here.
He has more access to the Book.
He might figure out a way soon.
We wanted him to come after us.
Looks like we got our wish.
- I should get Wyatt to heal...
- I don't want to traumatise him again.
He's gonna be traumatised soon enough.
I mean, who are we kidding?
We're screwed.
If we're going down,
we are not going down alone.
- We can't think like that.
- Leo, come on, it's over.
He's got our house, he's got our
Book, he's got two of our powers.
The only question is whether or not
we can take him down with us.
I can't believe we're
having this conversation.
Well, believe it.
How do we do it?
We've gotta get that spell
that destroys the Nexus.
And how is that gonna destroy Zankou?
We let the Nexus take in Zankou first.
And then cast the spell,
hit two birds with one stone.
Don't you mean five?
We're gonna have
to be in there to say the spell.
- Can't we say it from here?
- Not and get the timing right, no.
Well, it's been...
nice knowing you ladies.
What was that?
So close.
There must be another way in.
You're wasting valuable time.
You need to take in the Nexus, now.
No, I need to get into Magic School
and get their last power.
Listen to me!
This is a trick!
They're drawing you to them
so you won't go after the Nexus!
Don't you see that? They're playing you!
- You're gonna get us killed.
- I know what I'm doing.
No, you don't.
And I had such high hopes for you.
Do you have picture?
Yeah, we're good. You be careful.
Don't worry.
Okay, hold hands, hold hands.
What are you running from?
Darryl!
Leo? Where did you come from?
How did you get here?
Help from Magic School.
We need to talk.
Listen, Leo, I'm done talking, man.
It's not just about the girls.
It's about Sheridan.
What about Sheridan?
I know she's investigating the girls.
But keep her away from the house.
Something big is gonna go down.
Are they okay?
Leo, what is it?
You're stuck in the middle of this
and for that I'm sorry.
But we need you to keep them
away from the house,
for everybody's sake.
I gotta go.
Take care.
Hey, Leo...
- Sheila, baby...
- No, Darryl, you promised.
Baby, I can't just
leave them high and dry.
Look, there is nothing
more important to me
than you and those kids, nothing!
If we're about building a better future
for our family, I have to help!
Isn't that what they're fighting for?
Please, promise me
this will be the last time?
I promise.
Hey, what the?
- What's going on? Who are you?
- Who are you?
She asked you a question!
Victor. Victor Bennett.
Do you think it's really him?
If it was Zankou,
he would have attacked us by now.
What?
Sorry, Dad, it's the only way
we could be sure.
We didn't want Zankou
to know we were coming.
Zankou? Who is Zankou?
Long story.
It's safe!
Hey.
- What the hell is going on?
- Thank you, sweetie.
Is the guest bedroom that way?
Yeah.
Come on, baby.
Look, Dad, we're running out of time.
And there's no gentle way to break
this to you, so I'm just gonna say it.
We're in some serious trouble.
What kind of trouble?
The kind we can't get out of.
Here is the deed to P3
and the house, already signed.
Bank accounts, power of attorney
and the schedule for the boys.
What? I'm not gonna take that.
Dad, you have to. We need you to.
You're all we have.
We can't explain everything.
You just need to know
this is our only choice. Please!
For them.
I don't understand. Are you saying
I'm never gonna see you again?
No, never say never.
Not in this family.
Hey.
Hey. How'd it go?
As well as can be expected.
You know, we're doing the right thing.
I hope so.
Hey buddy, can I see you
for two seconds?
Come here, come here.
Just two seconds, come here. Listen.
I want you to know that Mommy
will always be close, okay?
I'll always be with you.
Okay, give me a hug.
Quick, quick, quick.
I love you so much.
We have to go, you guys.
Okay.
Be a good boy.
Baby, come here!
Be a good boy for Grandpa, okay?
My sweet baby.
Okay.
Let's get this over with.
I don't think anybody's home.
Get out of there, Inspector.
We'll try again later.
Let me just check the attic.
No! I don't like it. Just turn around.
Look, it'll just take a second.
No, Inspector.
Damn it.
I'm sorry, I was looking for Phoebe.
Who are you?
Get out of there, Inspector.
I'm Inspector Sheridan. Who are you?
How'd you get in here?
Damn it, Sheridan, go! Now!
I... I should be going.
You're not going anywhere.
What are you waiting for?
Go! Go! Go!
No!
What the?
Call FBI, SWAT, Special Forces, Hazmat,
everybody, we're going in.
Go! Go!
We only have one shot. We can't miss.
We gotta get to the Book and convince it
that we believe in ourselves.
- We do, don't we?
- Absolutely.
Just feels kind of strange,
doing it this way.
I wish we'd learned how to do it
earlier. It would have come in handy.
Prue was really protective of it. I'm
just glad she showed Leo how to do it.
So this is Magic School. How quaint.
- What took you so long?
- Patience is a virtue.
I can't begin to tell you how long I've
been looking forward to this moment,
a moment no demon
has ever enjoyed... until now.
Book!
Must we go through this?
Paige, get out of here!
No, not without you two!
Inseparable to the end.
But first things first.
Your power, please.
What's happening?
What?
The astral projecting worked.
Thank you, Prue.
The Book.
Okay, this may be
the last time we have to say this.
I'll hold you to it.
The power of three will set us free
What?
Move, move!
All right, nobody gets in or out,
you got that?
Nobody! I want this place
completely surrounded, over!
- What happened?
- I don't know.
If they come before we get Zankou,
it'll be a blood bath.
Come on, we've gotta find that spell.
I underestimated you.
It won't happen again.
What the hell was that?
It's probably the same thing that got
Sheridan. Everybody, listen up.
On my command, we storm the place.
Everybody in position.
I wouldn't go in just yet if I were you.
You're too late.
You can't take the Nexus.
It's been in me. It knows me now.
I should have done this before.
You can't stop me now.
- No?
- Watch us.
From ancient time this power came
For all to have, but none to reign
Take it now, show no mercy
For this power can no longer be
This is it!
Holy God.
Aren't you glad I told you to wait?
Yeah, this way.
Upstairs, up the stairs. Follow me.
- Follow me upstairs.
- Watch your backs, team leaders.
Nobody goes in any room alone.
Air's good. It's all clear.
- What happened?
- I don't know yet.
See anything?
- Nothing yet.
- Check that out.
My God.
Looks like a bomb went off in here.
House secure, nobody's inside.
Copy that. What do you have?
I have some hydrogen isotopes...
...plasma...
...no uranium.
Damn. Nothing.
Thank God nobody was in here.
Who said nobody was?
Your man said the house was secure.
But the Halliwell sisters were inside.
I saw them myself.
What?
We'd have spotted them if they'd left.
There was no way they got out alive.
There's gotta be another way
out of here.
Oh, dear God, please.
- I gotta get through. Coming through.
- Where do you think you're going?
- It's my house.
- You got ID?
- No.
- You're not getting past.
- It's my wife!
- You're not getting past! Understand?
Yeah.
- What's going on?
- What? I don't know.
Boy, I sure hope nobody died in there.
What?
Do we know each other?
Yeah, I think so.
After all...
...we're married.
What?
It's all part of the plan.
- Plan? What plan?
- Our plan to die.
It's the only way to get our lives back,
our normal lives.
And to stop everybody from
coming after us, including them.
- But...
- No, no buts.
We're free. Nobody knows
we're alive, not even the demons.
They think we died with Zankou.
They were just our astral selves.
Sweetie, we can start all over again.
No more demon fighting, ever again.
- Unless the demons figure it out.
- Which may be never.
- I don't know what to say.
- Just say you're okay with it.
So we can get the next generation
ready, to pick up where we left off.
How do I do it?
You don't, we do.
We'll make you good-looking.
Cute. I can live with that.
Well, all right!
All right.