Previously on "Stargate SG-1".:
Something neither one of us can admit,
given our working relationship...
I didn't leave, because I care about her.
It's time to let go of the things that
prevent you from finding happiness.
You deserve to love someone.
What's his name?
Humming.
Pete. Pete Shanahan.
He's a cop.
Oh, my God.
Maybe I did some good, but nothing I've
done seems to have changed anything.
There is really only one thing
we can ever truly control.
Whether we are good or evil.
I know who you are, Daniel
Jackson, but you know not who I am.
Don't do this.
- Last year, you died.
- I'm dead?
Actually, you ascended to
a higher plane of existence.
He was beamed away
before our eyes.
The human-form replicator
is attempting to probe your mind.
When she is done, she will destroy you.
And when that time comes,
you will be faced with a choice.
A force of rebel Jaffa have managed
to take control of the temple at Dakara.
Have the fleet disengage
their battle with the replicators.
Take it back at all costs.
We have found
the Ancient weapon on Dakara.
- Did Daniel have something to do with it?
- I don't know.
You have failed me.
We've known for some time
that the Jaffa cannot be trusted any more.
The remaining Kull warriors stand an
excellent chance of retaking Dakara, but...
Worse than failure.
Worse than cowardice.
You have betrayed me.
Did you not think
I would know what you have done?
How can you still
underestimate my powers?
Your methods were
ultimately unnecessary.
There was another way
of defeating the replicators.
I will spare your life for the moment,
only so that you may witness
the fruits of your labours.
First, I will retake Dakara.
Then, thanks to the modifications
you've made to the Stargate,
I will destroy every living thing
in this galaxy,
including you,
all at once.
I do not understand. You could have
modified the Stargate yourself.
You have no way of knowing
what is necessary and what is not
in the grand design.
Whose grand design?
Mine.
OK. Yeah. OK.
I'll tell everything I know.
Sorry, sir. I just saw you were with
someone. I didn't wanna interrupt.
- What's up?
- Who was that?
Um, Kerry Johnson.
- CIA.
- I've heard the name.
She headed up the investigation
into Goa'ulds still at large
- after the incident with the Trust.
- Yeah.
- I wanted to talk to you...
- Carter.
- We haven't heard from him in a week.
- Doesn't mean anything.
Chances are he was on board
a replicator ship when it disintegrated.
All we know for sure is that he's missing.
- Sooner or later...
- Forget it! I'm not falling for it this time.
- Falling for it?
- Yeah.
How many times have you thought
he was gone, and then he shows up
in one form or another?
I'm sorry, but we're not having a memorial
service for someone who is not dead.
You hear that? I'm not buying it.
What? He's just waiting for us to say
a bunch of nice things about him.
Next thing you know, he'll come waltzing
through that door, like, right now.
Waltzing.
Now.
So, what can I get for you?
Brothers Bra'tac of Chulak
and Teal'c of the Tauri,
for your enduring courage and vision,
for the strength of will that has
brought us to freedom from the Goa'uld,
a future we have yet to even comprehend
but one that will be determined
by our own unfettered will,
I hereby bestow upon you
the highest honour
any Jaffa can know.
From this day forward,
you shall both be known as blood kin
to all Jaffa.
Brothers.
From this day forward,
no Jaffa shall bow before anyone,
and never again before a false god.
- Hail brother Bra'tac!
- Hail!
- Hail brother Teal'c!
Be proud, Teal'c.
- Today we are free.
- This day is not yet over with.
Then I shall be proud for you,
and of you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Thank you, airman.
So, this is exciting.
- What's the surprise?
- You'll see.
Do I get to go through the Stargate?
What planet are we going to?
- You don't get to go through the Stargate.
- OK. I'm a little disappointed.
Still, full security clearance,
an all-access pass to SGC...
- This must be big.
- Oh, it's big.
Pete Shanahan, Jacob Carter.
Dad, this is Pete.
- Dad.
- Not quite yet.
You have to marry my daughter
before you can call me that.
I was just... I meant...
Stammer, stammer.
It's an honour to meet you, sir. Really.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I didn't want you to be nervous.
Why would I? I wouldn't. I...
- I've been dying to meet you.
- I think it was Sam that was nervous.
- How did not telling me help?
- It didn't.
This is great. You really got
one of those things in your head?
If by "one of those things" you mean
a 2,000-year-old Tok'ra symbiote, yes.
Seriously. Come on.
That has gotta freak you
right out sometimes.
It's weird.
Hey. What do I have to do
to get some more coffee around here?
Find true enlightenment.
- No menus?
- We don't need them here.
Just order what you'd like.
OK, I'll have the truth
with a side order of clarity, please.
The replicator version of Sam
was in your head trying to access
the knowledge buried
in your subconscious,
but you gained control of her instead.
She killed you to stop you.
- That's where I stepped in. How's that?
- Pretty clear.
We aim to please.
Customer comes first, you know.
So I'm ascended again.
Not exactly. Sort of a stop along the way.
You have to make that choice for yourself.
- Waffles.
- Bacon on the side?
- No, I remember this place.
- You should. It came from your mind.
I was brought here after
my parents' funeral. I had waffles.
- Waffles it is.
- Wait.
How do I know this is really you this time?
How do I know this isn't some trick
replicator Sam's playing to stop me from
controlling her?
How deep is the river
if you cannot see the bottom?
Deeper than the coffee in my cup,
I'll tell you that.
Excuse me.
Frank, I need a Noah's boy in a blanket,
two hen fruit on a shingle
with a mystery in the alley,
a warm eve with a mouldy lid,
and two checkerboards, all right?
Hold the pig.
We have dreamed of this day for so long,
fought so hard for it,
and sacrificed so much.
- Now that it is here...
- It is not here, brother.
The balance of power has shifted, Teal'c.
Our victory here at Dakara
has turned the tide.
Jaffa everywhere
are abandoning the old ways,
coming to see the Goa'uld
for the false gods they are.
We are foolish to rejoice in conquest over
the Goa'uld when they are not all dead.
Anubis' claim to be a god is false,
but his powers certainly are not.
It is agreed.
He must be dealt with.
But for once,
there may be greater concerns
than the eradication of all the Goa'uld.
So consumed
were we in attaining freedom
that we did not plan
nearly enough for its aftermath.
The Jaffa have fought with each other
for so long that uniting them as one
may prove as difficult as convincing them
to free themselves from the Goa'uld.
Generations of war and mistrust
will not be healed overnight.
Indeed. If we do not organise quickly,
freedom will become anarchy.
The high priests are proposing
a leadership be assembled.
That is wise.
They wish both of us to sit on the council.
You know that will take you
from the Tauri.
Your purpose in joining them
was to one day free the Jaffa.
That day is now. You must not abandon
your people when we need you most.
Of that I am aware.
The council will preside from our new
home world, where a city is to be erected,
a haven for all those
who have chosen freedom.
Here, on the holy ground of Dakara.
Hey.
- I know you.
- Really?
Yeah. The guy from the paper.
Dr Daniel Jackson.
That's OK. Keep it. I'm done.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
- Are you gonna visit Mark and the kids?
- Tomorrow.
Is everything OK?
I'm just not very hungry.
You've been pretty quiet.
I'm fine.
Dad...
What?
Pete left two hours ago.
You haven't said a word.
- I did so.
- "He seems nice."
I believe that's three words.
- I'm gonna marry him.
- I know.
I just met him.
What do you want me to say?
I know how happy he makes you.
That's all that matters to me.
OK.
- Selmak really liked him.
- Selmak?
Yeah. And he's a great judge of character.
Well, OK.
Look, Sam, I'm tired.
It's been a long day.
I think I'm gonna turn in early.
- Are you sure nothing else is wrong?
- Yeah.
- I'll see you in the morning.
- Good night.
- What?
- Sorry to wake you, sir.
Teal'c's back, and it sounds
like we have a problem.
I knew it.
All right. I'll be there as soon as I can.
Crap.
What was that?
Trouble in Jaffaland.
Gotta go.
I'm sorry.
- You know about this?
- Yes.
- You're not gonna do anything about it?
- You know I can't.
Well, I'm certainly not just gonna
sit here and let this happen.
You can't leave. You're not ascended yet.
You walk through that door,
you're choosing the alternative.
You're saying I'll be dead?
Pretty much.
OK. Ascend me.
That doesn't mean you'll be able to
help your friends. You know the rules.
But once I'm ascended I can take
human form again, like last time.
Technically, yes.
You can't take that paper, you won't have
any of the knowledge you've gained here,
and good luck ever ascending again.
I'm not going to help you a third time.
So I can know Anubis is plotting
to destroy all life in the galaxy,
and all I can do about it is stay here
and contemplate my own enlightenment?
You can eat your waffles.
No syrup?
Hi. How's it going?
I'm, uh, Daniel Jackson.
Sorry to bother you. I just wanted
to know if I could borrow your syrup.
Technically, it's not gonna be borrowing,
cos I'm not gonna give back what I use.
Enjoy your meal.
Hi, guys. How's it going?
- They're not going to talk to you.
- Why not? Who are they?
Others. You're not one of them yet.
You mean Ancients.
- A couple of them.
- What are they doing here?
- Watching.
- Me?
Me too.
I told you before, they're always watching.
You wanted some motor oil?
I wish you had blown that thing up
when you had the chance.
We had to at least be sure that all
the replicators really were eliminated.
And even though we apparently
did get rid of them all in this galaxy,
there may be more elsewhere
that could be a threat again.
So we wanted to try to figure out how the
device worked in case we needed it again.
Great. Well, now the Jaffa have something
that can blow up the entire universe
with the push of a button.
The Jaffa will defend Dakara
with their lives.
You wanna explain to me
why they don't wanna wreck it?
The ruins at Dakara
have become a symbol of freedom.
The Jaffa believe
the device's power helped free them
by destroying the replicators.
They believe controlling this power will
help ensure their freedom in the future.
And get them virtually anything they want.
- The Jaffa would never use it to that end.
- Jack is right.
No one should have
that kind of power at their disposal.
Sorry. I thought I'd turned it off.
So, we're all in agreement?
One way or another, it's gotta go.
Correct?
- Indeed.
- Thank you.
If you suggest we destroy this device
against the wishes of the High Council,
I must point out that would not be
a good first step in relations
between the Tauri
and the newly-formed free Jaffa nation.
Why don't you do it?
They already hate the Tok'ra.
To be honest,
a plan may already be in the works,
but as you know, Selmak and I
aren't fully in the loop any longer.
Mm.
Ahem.
- Yes?
- Sorry to interrupt, sir.
Colonel, there's a call for you.
Apparently it's urgent.
Sorry.
Carter.
We have arranged
a meeting of the Jaffa council.
We hope to strengthen the bond
between previously warring Jaffa
by focusing on our common enemy.
Yeah, I know.
It's not a good time right now.
There are still many Goa'uld
who remain a threat.
I know. I'm sorry.
I don't know.
It could be an hour, it could be all day.
Yeah, I know.
OK. Yeah, me too.
Bye.
- Sorry about that, sir.
- Emergency?
No, no. Just a... a misunderstanding.
Hey, weren't you supposed to meet
Pete at the florist this morning?
No, Dad.
No, I'm sure that's what you said.
For the wedding.
I know.
- Go ahead, Carter. It is your day off.
- It's OK.
Teal'c and Bra'tac are meeting with
the Jaffa. There's nothing to do here.
Go pick flowers.
What?
- More coffee?
- Sure.
- Can you sit a minute?
- OK.
Oh, how am I supposed to put it?
Man, are my dogs tired.
That's good.
- How were your waffles?
- Best I ever had.
Can you tell me why you stopped me from
killing Anubis last time I was ascended?
If I didn't stop you, the Others would have.
They wouldn't have been as nice about it.
They wouldn't have erased my memory
and left me naked?
That was your choice.
OK, maybe not the naked part.
I didn't totally erase your memory
even though I was supposed to.
There. OK. Why is it OK
to break some rules and not others?
You knew I had a problem
following the rules last time.
Why offer me ascension again?
I didn't wanna see you die without
at least giving you a second chance.
Look. I have trouble following the rules.
I'm not really supposed
to help people ascend.
- You're supposed to do it on your own.
- But you do it.
I walk the line. Believe me, I crossed it
a few times and paid for it dearly.
My point is, you just need to be willing
to put your prior human existence
into the proper context.
Sorry. I gotta get back to work.
Coffee, please.
- Chocolate or vanilla?
- I'm sorry. What?
The cake. In case you can't make
the meeting with the caterer.
Oh! I'm sorry.
l-l really do wanna be a part of this.
- I hope so. It's your wedding too.
- I know.
I realise this must be weird for you,
worrying about place settings
when we could be destroyed
by aliens any minute.
A little.
We're not about to be destroyed
by aliens, are we?
No.
Because you seem a bit distracted.
I'm sorry.
- So, did Dad like me?
- Of course. Why wouldn't he?
- Tough guy to read.
- You just have to get to know him.
- How about Selmak?
- Ah. He thought you were very charming.
- For a human.
- Well, generally speaking, that's my type.
Good.
- Did I tell you I have a surprise for you?
- No. What is it?
Tricky.
You'll see.
The council remains unwilling
to destroy the weapon
for fear it will weaken the resolve of the
Jaffa to stand united against the Goa'uld.
You realise we have to consider
that thing a threat to our security.
Indeed.
The council recognises the danger
and has decided to take action
by aggressively seeking out
and killing Anubis.
Once that threat has been eliminated,
they will reassess the decision
to destroy the device.
Well, we don't even know
if Anubis can be killed yet, do we?
We must not suggest
to the Jaffa that he cannot be.
At the very least, we can eliminate
the remainder of the forces of Anubis.
I believe this quest will unite
many of the still-fractured armies
by giving them focus on a common goal.
Got anything to go on?
Many Kull were killed
in battle with the replicators.
Intelligence indicates
Anubis may be marshalling
the remaining Kull warriors on Tartarus.
A pre-emptive strike is being prepared.
It is the point.
- Hey.
Daniel. How's it going?
Do we know each other?
l-l feel like I know you.
Call me Jim. We ran into each other
last time you were ascended.
Ah. Nice to meet you again.
Still haven't made up your mind, huh?
Death or everlasting enlightenment.
Don't really see the choice, myself.
Yeah, of course I don't wanna be dead.
It's just that, uh...
Listen. The reason I came
over here was to ask you...
Why are you talking to me?
Oh, you mean because these other snobs
won't even look at you?
I'm different. Like Oma.
Really? I got the impression
you two don't quite see eye to eye.
What, that little...? Oh, that was nothing.
We both operate somewhat outside
the normal rules and regulations.
Sometimes we disagree on how far
outside we should go, that's all.
- Really.
- Yeah.
As long as these other guys
don't strike me down, I figure I'm OK.
I guess that's what I'm trying to figure out.
I feel like if I agree to ascend, I'm signing
a contract and I don't know what it says.
Obviously, I had a little trouble
with the fine print the last time.
You sure did.
You know about that?
It's all out there.
I just don't see
how I can agree to stand by
and let Anubis destroy
every living thing in an entire galaxy.
I know.
That's a tough one.
Speaking of which,
have you seen the latest?
He's a crafty one.
Really knows the ins and outs of the rules.
I give him three-to-one odds to succeed.
Wanna know the irony of it all?
That device was originally used by the
Ancients to create life in the Milky Way.
Well, recreate it
after the whole plague thing.
No kidding.
Now it all gets undone
with the push of one button,
leaving Anubis to recreate things
all over to his own liking.
There's a waste of a million-odd
years of evolution, huh?
I say someone should really
do something to stop him!
No one will.
Can I get a coffee?
- Can I open them now?
- Almost.
OK. Now.
- What do you think?
- Uh...
Well, uh...
- Speechless, huh?
- Yeah.
Isn't it great?
Remember our first night together?
- You described the house you wanted.
- I can't believe this.
The kitchen isn't yellow, but we can paint.
Come on. I'll show you.
And you're not gonna believe
the back yard. The dog's gonna love it.
Dog?
This is bad.
Yeah. But this pie is great,
and there's nothing to wash it down with.
Can you do anything to stop Anubis?
You said someone should do something.
I did, didn't I?
Well, as far as what can be done,
it's kinda complicated.
Yeah, so Oma tells me.
I don't think she's told you everything.
- What does that mean?
- I'm saying...
- I've already said too much.
- No, you haven't.
In fact, you've hardly said anything at all.
You gave up eternal enlightenment,
all the knowledge
and power of the universe.
- Why do you think you did that?
- To fight for humanity any way I could.
Yes. Very big of you.
You rejected everything Oma offered you,
and now she gives you another chance
based on the goodness of her heart?
Well, that is the point, isn't it?
I mean, she is ascended. She is good.
Sure. Best intentions.
Do you know what happened
between me and Oma?
Why did I choose
to take human form again?
You should ask Oma.
Hi, sir.
Carter.
I'm sorry to bother you at home like this...
- How did you know I was here?
- I saw the smoke.
Oh. Yeah.
Look, is-is this OK?
I mean, I could have called first, but...
No. Yeah. I mean, it's fine.
So, um...
What brings you to this neck of the woods
on such a fine day? My back yard.
Well, actually, I've been sitting
in your driveway for the last ten minutes
trying to work up the nerve
to come and talk to you.
The truth is, I've been trying to work up
the nerve for a lot longer than that.
Oh?
- Pete put a down payment on a house.
- Well, that's great.
It's a beautiful house.
But...?
The-the truth is I'm having
second thoughts about the wedding.
Why?
The thing is, the closer it gets,
the more I get the feeling
that I'm making a big, huge mistake.
Look, Carter, I don't know what...
I'm sorry to bother you with this, but, uh...
there's a very good reason
that I'm bothering you with this,
and if I don't tell you now, I might never...
Jack, I looked everywhere.
I could not find...
- Colonel Carter.
- Hi.
- Ms Johnson.
- Yeah... l-l didn't...
We were just meeting here
in my back yard on this fine day
to discuss the state of affairs.
- Well, this is awkward.
- You think?
Jack didn't want anyone at the SGC
to know about, uh... us.
No, look, I... I'm sorry. This is my fault.
I really... I shouldn't have come by
unannounced like this.
Well, you know,
now that the cat's out of the bag...
You're here. Why don't you just stay?
I'm sure there's enough charred meat
on the grill for all three of us.
No, thank you. I...
It's the, uh, SGC.
Colonel Carter.
What? When?
OK. I'm on my way.
l-l gotta go. It's my dad.
Well, you can't stay here forever,
you know.
Actually, I suppose you could.
I just don't know why you'd want to.
Except for the great service.
Look. Obviously, I don't wanna just die.
I don't suppose there's any other options?
I can't get into it.
What's stopping you from ascending?
I don't know.
Must be something holding you back,
making you doubt yourself.
Maybe it's not me I'm doubting.
Look. Whether you choose to accept
living on a higher plane of existence
has nothing to do with me
or anything that I can or can't tell you.
- It's all up to you.
- There is something you're not telling me.
Did Jim say that?
You shouldn't listen to him.
- Why not?
- Because.
Good answer.
Yes.
Dad?
I'm sorry, kiddo. We both are.
- About what? What's going on?
- I didn't wanna ruin everything like this.
Dad...
It's Selmak. He's dying.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
It's OK. He's OK. He led a pretty full life.
I didn't live with Jolinar long,
but I have some idea what it's like.
Well... this is a little different, Sam.
When a Tok'ra symbiote dies
they can prevent their host from dying,
as Jolinar did with you.
The problem is, that last selfless act
requires a certain amount of energy
and a conscious effort.
What are you saying?
By all rights, Selmak should have
been dead weeks ago.
I wouldn't let him go.
I felt we needed him, that I needed him
to help you stop the replicators.
Dad...
He hung on as long as he could.
Then he slipped into a coma just after
we activated the weapon on Dakara.
You've known all this time since then?
I didn't wanna spoil your wedding.
You know, I thought we could make it.
We?
He's barely alive.
I'm gonna die with him, Sam.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
Doing whatever she does
when she's not here.
- You ask her?
- Yep.
- Wouldn't tell you?
- Nope.
Had to find out for yourself last time, too.
Man, were you pissed.
About what?
Tell me.
What do you know about Anubis?
I know he's half ascended,
whatever that means.
There are many planes of existence
between human existence and ascension.
Basically, the Others
use their collective powers
to keep him from effecting anything
on a grand, cosmic level.
But it's OK for him
to destroy an entire galaxy.
It's OK to do anything he could have done
back when he was a regular old Goa'uld.
I see.
What does this have to do with Oma?
Goa'ulds are bad.
Anubis is as bad as they come.
- And...?
- And...
Ascension requires that somebody
be pure of spirit, good to the very core.
- How does someone like Anubis ascend?
- Now he's getting it.
Oma would never help
somebody like Anubis.
- Not on purpose.
- You're saying he tricked her somehow?
Rule number one.
No lone ascended being
shall help a Lower ascend.
Lowers are what we call
humans and such.
If you deserve to be here, you should
be able to get here on your own.
If there's an exception,
for whatever reason,
a majority vote by the collective
can get you in.
But Oma thinks she knows better,
and she's taken her licks for it.
For the most part,
she's brought good people on board.
But as the old saying goes,
nobody's perfect,
not even us higher beings.
Oma helped Anubis ascend.
Get out.
Get out now.
Well, look at the time. I've gotta go, kid.
Business to attend to.
It was nice talking to you.
A number of the Tok'ra have responded.
They wanna pay their respects.
They can come.
I can't believe there's nothing they can do.
They can remove a Goa'uld.
In the last few years, you've almost
perfected the process of saving a host.
That process instantly kills the symbiote
before it releases toxins.
It's too late for that, Sam.
I'm sorry.
I hate to do this to you,
but I should have been dead
four years ago.
Since then,
I've been all over the galaxy.
I've done things
most men never dream of.
I've heard that before.
I just wanna know you're gonna be happy.
I am.
Don't let rules stand in your way.
What are you talking about?
You joined the air force because of me.
I love my job.
You can still have everything you want.
I do, Dad.
Really.
How's Colonel Carter's father?
- Doesn't look good.
- Sorry to hear that.
Closing the door.
Yeah.
Deeply symbolic.
Really?
I really like you.
We're good together.
Yes.
We are.
But...
You have issues.
It's OK. We all do.
There's just one big one in particular
that I don't think I can love with.
Live with.
I need to get out
before I get more involved.
We can still work together, can't we?
I'd hate to have to ask for reassignment.
This is really important to me.
We agreed this would never affect the job.
- We did.
- Good.
You know, there's just one thing
I don't understand.
Just one?
Is the air force the only thing
keeping you two apart?
Rules and regulations?
Cos if it is, you're making
a very big mistake.
And you know what I should do?
- Retire.
- Again?
You're considered invaluable
to the programme by the Pentagon.
But the president has appointed
a civilian to run the SGC before.
Just a thought.
The time has come for this ancient warrior
to fight one final battle.
I think not, old man.
This victory will present us with new
challenges that will require your wisdom.
What our people will require
is a youthful, vital leadership,
and others are
better suited to provide that.
You are only as old
as you believe yourself to be.
Talk to me in 50 years.
Indeed I will.
So, it's true.
He tricked me.
How? You couldn't tell?
No.
He must have found some old
Ancient research on ascension.
When he came to Kheb,
he knew what he was doing.
When I realised the horrible mistake that I
had made, I tried to undo it but I couldn't.
That's when the Others stepped in.
They only sent him halfway back.
Why not all the way?
- It's complicated.
- Yeah. What isn't around here?
They warned him.
He wasn't allowed to use
any knowledge or power
unless he otherwise
would have gained it as a Goa'uld.
I don't understand.
They let him wreak havoc.
They don't care if he destroys
all life in the galaxy, life they created.
They haven't stopped me
from continuing my work.
I've tried to make up for it,
help when I can.
It's your punishment.
You're forced to watch,
powerless to interfere.
They let Anubis do whatever he wants
just to punish you.
I told you. The galaxy you're from,
the plane of existence
is so small and insignificant
compared to the rest of the universe.
I don't care. It's wrong.
That's what you said last time.
Excuse me.
Isn't it enough already?
I mean, a whole galaxy of innocent people
enslaved and tortured for generations,
now on the verge
of being destroyed for nothing.
For what?
For one mistake a good person made
trying to do a good thing.
The least you could do is listen to me.
That can't be against
the grand highfalutin cosmic rules!
Hey, I'm talking to you!
OK. OK.
Well, I know you can hear me.
Hasn't she suffered enough already?
And certainly enough other people
have suffered to punish her.
- Don't you think you've made your point?
- Daniel, they don't.
I keep breaking the same rule,
helping people ascend.
That's why you're here.
What if you stopped?
Wouldn't undo the problem.
That's why I keep doing what I do.
Anubis can't be killed.
Not by you, not by me.
He is not here. No one is here.
- The defences were automated.
- We have been deceived.
Anubis fed us this intelligence
to lure us here.
Our forces defending Dakara are depleted.
We could not have known, brother.
You were right. The device at Dakara
should have been destroyed at all costs.
You OK?
Actually, I'm fine.
Good, even, strange as that sounds.
I thought I lost him four years ago.
Since then, we've been closer
than we ever were my whole life.
In a way, Selmak gave me the father
I never thought I'd know.
Come here.
Thank you, sir.
For what?
For being here for me.
Always.
I'm ready.
I love you.
- Can I get a coffee?
- Get it yourself.
Don't mind if I do.
Ooh. Hey, Danny boy, you see the paper?
- No. What's it say?
- The trick worked.
Those stupid Jaffa took half their ships
to hunt down Anubis.
Meanwhile, his army was poised
to attack Dakara.
The remaining rebel Jaffa
guarding Dakara are being slaughtered.
It's only a matter of time before
old Anubis gets his hands on the weapon.
I'm sorry.
You sound almost happy about that.
- Who, me?
- Yeah. What do you have against Oma?
- Daniel...
- No. I wanna know.
I mean, you're not just watching.
You're coming in here to rub it in.
Why are you taking pleasure
in her punishment?
Me? I don't have anything against Oma.
I think she's great, don't I?
Hell, she's the one that helped me ascend.
You got it now.
You are Anubis.
Cheers.
I knew from the beginning.
I guess I just thought
when you said yes that...
that you were worth the risk.
Don't say I deserve better.
- It can't get much better than you.
- That's not true.
I wish I could believe
this had to do with your father.
You needed some time to sort things out.
I guess all I can say is
I hope you get what you want.
That's it?
What do you want? You want me
to get down on my knees and beg?
God, no. Of course not.
I just...
I thought you would react differently.
- Bye, Sam.
- Pete...
The rebel fleet guarding Dakara
has fallen to the forces of Anubis.
The remaining rebel ships will not arrive
in time. Anubis now controls the weapon.
We find the biggest damn nuke we can
and we shove it through the gate now.
Anubis will have the gate shielded.
The nuke will not arrive in one piece.
If we dial the Alpha site
we may prevent the weapon
from connecting a wormhole
to either planet.
- It may only buy us the 38 minutes that...
- Go. Go. Just go.
Sergeant, dial the Alpha site now.
- Wait a minute. That's not me.
- What?
I don't know.
Incoming wormhole.
- That won't stop the weapon energy.
- If it is the weapon.
- No iris codes.
- We're too late.
Self-destruct.
That won't destroy the gate. There's only
a remote chance it would disengage a...
Carter! Carter...
You make a great cup of coffee.
Well, gotta go.
There's nothing you can do.
You don't have the power.
But I do.
- You can't kill me either.
- I can fight you.
- Well, you can't win.
- It won't matter.
You won't be able to do anything
but fight me back.
- What are you gonna do?
- I should have done it a long time ago.
Oh, no.
No. No!
No!
- Wormhole disengaged.
- What's going on?
I don't know.
Must be some kind of system malfunction.
- That's impossible.
- Shut it off.
Aborting self-destruct.
The Kull warriors became
disorganised and confused,
as though they no longer
knew what to do.
- They no longer had a master to serve.
- After that, they were easily defeated.
Many Jaffa lost their lives.
Those that survived are united
as never before, and we are in agreement.
The weapon must be destroyed.
Well, that's good.
A new memorial
will be erected in its place,
so that our triumph over the Goa'uld
will never be forgotten.
I still don't quite understand
what happened.
Anubis is about to push the button
that ends life in the galaxy,
and the next minute he's just gone.
Indeed. It is a great mystery.
One can only assume
he was vanquished by some means.
If not, why would he forfeit
the weapon and his army?
- You think?
- I do.
It's the only thing that would explain
the self-destruct not going off.
- Of what do you speak?
- O'Neill believes Daniel is responsible.
Nope. It wasn't me.
Anybody else hear that?
I'm in here.
That's Daniel.
- Don't! Don't come in.
- Ho!
Hey, there.
It's a long story.
- This is great.
- I told you.
Can't believe
we didn't do this years ago.
Yes, well,
let's not dwell.
- There are no fish in this pond, are there?
- Nope.
Nice.
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke
ENHOH