What about the view, Fry?
It really puts things in perspective.
From up here, an entire world
can seem utterly insignificant.
Fear of a 'Bot Planet
Nice seats! We're close enough. . .
. . .to when you hit a player
with a bottle, he's down.
I don't get it. Is blernsball
the same as baseball?
Baseball? God forbid.
Face it, Fry. Baseball was
as boring as mom and apple pie.
-That's why they jazzed it up.
-Boring? Baseball wasn't--
So they finally jazzed it up.
Home run!
Right?
Out!
What happened? Why's the ball
on that spring?
It's tradition, like aluminum
bats and the seventh-inning grope.
I got me a souvenir!
Here you go, kid.
I'd like a jumbo squid log, please.
We don't sell those.
All right. Let me have
one of your young on a roll.
We're out of rolls.
Fine. Just give me something crawling
with parasites.
[GROWLS]
At least hot dogs didn't change.
-Buddies, who wants popcorn?
LEELA: I'll have some!
[POPPING]
Anyone want butter on that?
I'm getting the hang of this.
The blerns are loaded. . .
. . .count's 3 blerns, 2 anti-blerns,
and the blern rule's in effect, right?
Except for the word "blern,"
that's total gibberish.
MAN:
Multi-ball! Multi-ball!
Blern! Blern!
All right! Yes!
Miller's on a pace to hit 70 blerns.
He's good, all right.
But he's no Clem Johnson.
And Johnson played back in the days
before steroids were mandatory.
That sack of skin wouldn't have lasted
one pitch in the old Robot Leagues.
Now, Wireless Joe Jackson,
there was a blern-hitting machine.
Exactly. He was a machine
designed to hit blerns.
Wireless Joe was
a programmable bat on wheels.
And I suppose pitching at 5000
was just a modified howitzer?
Humans are so scared of
robot competition. . .
-. . .you won't let us on the field.
-There's a lot of robots down there.
Yeah. Doing crap work.
They're batboys, ball polishers,
sprinkler systems.
But how many robot managers are there?
-Eleven?
-Zero!
And what a surprise!
Look who's scraping up the filth!
Is it a human child? I wish!
Whoa, dear Lord!
What's wrong?
It's my new pager.
This is Hermes.
A package just came in.
Return to the office immediately.
[GROANING]
Get away, you filthy bird.
Professor? Turn me off, quick!
I'm sorry. What?
See you at the office!
BENDER:
Admit it!
You think robots are just machines
built to make life easier.
Well, aren't they?
I've never made anyone's life easier,
and you know it!
Great news, everyone. You'll be
delivering a package to Chapek 9.
Where humans are killed on sight.
-Why is that great news?
-I'm glad you asked that question.
You see, Chapek 9 was colonized
centuries ago. . .
. . .by a murderous crew
of radical robot separatists.
Just because a robot wants to
kill humans, he's a "radical. "
Hold on. I understand
these robots hate humans.
But how do they feel
about humanoid aliens?
They're not fans.
Bender will have to make the delivery.
I get it.
Make the robot do all the work.
This is the first actual work
you've ever done here.
Well, I'm not doing it!
It's a robot holiday.
Really? Which one?
Only Robanukah. The holiest two weeks
on the robot calendar.
Come on, Bender.
Last month, it was Robomadom.
And before that, Robonza.
-Man, that one was a blast.
-Not just a blast. . .
. . .it was a sacred tribute to my
ancestral prototypes. . .
. . .which took the form
of a drinking contest.
Bender, I respect your diversity
to the extent the law requires.
But you used all your days off
when you had Roberculosis.
All right, I'll go.
But I'll hold a grudge against
every last one of you. . .
. . .for the rest of your lives.
Well then, it's settled.
So long, everyone.
So, this planet is completely
uninhabited?
No. It's inhabited by robots.
Kind of like how a warehouse
is inhabited by boxes.
Okay, Bender. Time to get to work.
Yes, Ms. Leela.
Tote that space barge.
Lift that space bale.
We can't land on the surface,
the robots will kill us.
We'll stay and lower you
with the winch.
Remember, you don't know humans,
you don't work for humans. . .
. . .and above all,
you don't like humans.
I'll try to keep that in mind.
-He seems pretty angry.
-Yeah.
I'd be angry too, if I had to go
to an uninhabited planet.
Let's do something nice for him.
LEELA:
There.
This will show that stupid
robot we care.
[BEEPING]
Bender's done with the delivery,
I'm in trouble. They found out I
work with humans and--
Oh, no!
-My God! We have to rescue him.
-No, they'll kill us.
What will we do?
I don't know.
It's not an easy decision.
If only I had two or three minutes
to think.
To save Bender, we've got to look
and act exactly like robots.
I'm fully operational.
We have to walk and talk
like robots, and maybe. . .
. . .solve differential
equations like robots.
I can dance like a robot.
Will that help?
Fry. First of all, this is serious.
Second of all:
We look stupid. We should've
gotten store-bought costumes.
-But there's no Woolworth's nearby.
GUARD 1 : Halt!
Be you robot or human?
Robot we be.
Just two robots out roboting it up.
Heh?
Administer the test.
Which of the following
would you most prefer:
A: A puppy?
B: A pretty flower from your sweetie?
Or C: A large, properly formatted
data file?
Choose!
[WHISPERING]
-Is the puppy mechanical at all?
-No. It's the bad kind of puppy.
We'll go with the data file.
-Correct.
-The flower would've been acceptable.
GUARD 2:
You may pass.
LEELA: If you see robots,
stay out of their way.
LEELA:
So far, so good.
-Little to the right. Okay.
-Have you seen this robot?
Sorry. Can't help you.
Hey! Watch it!
Don't drop that there!
Oh!
Come on, Fry. Walk like a robot.
-I have to go to the bathroom.
-Robots don't have bathrooms.
Right. Where do they
smoke in high school?
Just go behind those garbage cans.
I'll stand guard.
[UNZIPS PANTS]
[HUMS]
Hurry up, Fry!
Sir? Are you aware you're leaking
coolant at an alarming rate?
-Let me patch you up with hot resin.
-I think the leak's stopping.
Wait. Wait.
Yeah, there we go.
Wait. Yeah.
What sort of robot turns down a free
blast of searing-hot resin?
Uh--
I'm sorry. My friend and I have to
do some mindless, repetitive tasks.
Sounds like a romantic evening.
I won't keep you.
[SNEEZES]
-Get the humanoids.
-Get the intruder.
ROBOT:
Intruder alert.
Quick! Let's duck in here!
ANNOUNCER: We interrupt this sound
file for an announcement:
A nonmetallic being is
in the vicinity of Make-Out Point.
Say, Wendy? Your chassis's scuffed.
Mind if I polish it for you?
Did you hear that?
It sounded like a human.
Relax, Wendy. Humans will never
come to our little town.
It's perfectly safe to
let our guard down.
I will eat and digest you all with
my system of mighty organs!
Behold!
Wow! The 3-D's great!
Mine's not working.
Funny, isn't it?
The human's impervious to our
powerful magnetic fields.
Yet in the end, he succumbed to
a harmless sharpened stick.
-I'm glad the nightmare's over.
-It'll never be over.
Even now, humans lurk in our
playgrounds, breezeways. . .
. . .perhaps even our movie theaters!
FRY:
God help us!
Okay. Keep an eye out for Bender.
What did you think of the movie?
Too much romance,
not enough human killing.
It was a real chick flick.
[FANFARE PLAYS]
What's that?
What do you mean, "What's that?"
It's 5:00.
Time for the daily human hunt.
Stay with the crowd so no one
sees how crummy you look.
-That was uncalled for.
-I'm over here.
I heard a human was draining coolant
behind garbage can 738.
I heard they unscrew our lug nuts at
night and eat them at brunches.
Welcome to a very special human hunt.
We have a guest whose
irrational hatred for humans. . .
. . .makes me look like
a human sympathizer.
[LAUGHING]
A newly-arrived refugee from Earth,
let's hear it for. . .
. . .Bender!
It's him! He's okay!
Death to the humans!
Ah, it's good to hear his voice.
Many said I was too extreme when I
called for. . .
. . .the annihilation of humans. . .
. . .as well as some of the more
cunning monkeys.
After living on Earth, I can tell
you that I am, if anything. . .
. . .too merciful.
[CHEERING]
My God! He's become evil.
I mean, eviler.
Thank you. And if you
enjoyed that diatribe. . .
. . .you'll want to purchase
my spoken-word album.
Just $1 8.95.
Act now, and you'll get this Bender
action figurine.
Bite my shiny metal ass.
Let the hunt begin!
Now, your basic human is between three
and 25 feet tall. . .
. . .and is made of a hairy, oily
goo in a T-shirt.
Do they bite you,
suck your fluid. . .
-. . .and you become human?
-Sure.
-Anything in the trap?
-Nothing.
Nothing.
Humans prefer low-calorie bait.
Well, that makes 1 46,000
unsuccessful hunts in a row.
But I've got a good feeling
about tomorrow.
Wait! What's that?
That's the abandoned
adult-book store.
Nothing there, except a few
shreds of old robot pornography.
Sounds like a breeding ground
for humans. I'll check it out.
Oh, yeah.
You're a bad girl, aren't you?
Psst, Bender!
What? Oh, you!
-What are you doing here?
-Looking for you.
We heard you were arrested
as a human sympathizer.
I was.
They let me go when I said
I killed a billion humans.
Good!
Let's get back to the ship.
-What for?
-We're rescuing you.
-I don't want that.
-Say what?
I love this planet.
I've got wealth, fame. . .
. . .and access to the depths of sleaze
from that.
But we're your friends.
Friends? That activates
my hilarity unit.
I'm a machine.
You're no more my friends. . .
. . .than you are with the toaster,
phonograph or electric chair.
That's not true.
Well, that's how it feels to me.
Bye, Bender. I'll miss you.
Go on. Get out of here
before you get caught.
Bender, good news.
Your album just went gold.
-What the--?
-It's the humans!
Bender, do something!
Got you! You murderous flesh piles!
Your Honor, I intend to demonstrate
beyond 0.5o/o of a doubt. . .
. . .that these humans are guilty
of the crime of being humans.
Come to think of it, I rest my case.
Thank you, prosecutor.
I will now consider the evidence.
Wait a minute.
Won't someone defend us?
Yeah! He may not have a case,
but I am genuinely not a human.
Quiet, human!
He froze up again.
Try control-alt-delete.
-Jiggle the cord.
-Turn him off and on.
-Clean the mouse.
-Call technical support!
Okay, okay, he's back online.
I find the defendants guilty.
No!
Look, one eye! Count them!
One! Not human!
The humans are sentenced to live
as robots live on Earth.
They'll perform tedious calculations
and spot-weld cars. . .
. . .until they become obsolete, and
given to an inner-city school.
Great work, Bender! You've taught us
to hate humans all over again!
Heh-heh. Oh. . . .
[SCREAMING]
[THUDDING]
LEELA: Are you all right?
FRY: Oh, yeah.
-Who are you?
-We are the Robot Elders.
You don't look old.
Thanks. We try to take care of
ourselves.
-What's going on?
-Silence! Bring in Bender!
Make this quick. I'm due
at a mini-mall opening.
Hey! What is this?
Silence! It's time to
kill the humans.
But the judge sentenced us!
Silence! That's just a show
for the public.
We rule this planet.
Handcarved from meteorites by robot
founders over four centuries ago.
Silence! Come forward, Bender.
You'll have the honor of execution.
Silence! I concur.
Here. Use the ceremonial
kill-a-ma-gig.
I'm a little tired right now.
Can I just give them
a savage beating?
No! The elders have spoken.
Show us the killing skills that
made you a media darling.
Do it! Kill them before
they bring down our society!
-Do it!
ALL: Do it! Do it! Do it!
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Oh.
[GASPING]
I can't kill them.
Plenty of humans have mistreated
robots, but not these two.
They're my friends.
Humans are no threat to us.
They're stupid, putrid cowards.
Damn right!
The fact is, humans are completely
harmless.
-We're well aware of that.
-You are?
We use them as scapegoats to distract
the public from their real problems.
Like our crippling lug nut shortage.
And a corrupt government of
robot elders.
That's for sure.
Quiet, Jimmy.
I'm glad that's out in the open.
We'll just let ourselves out.
Silence! You all know too much.
Elders? Execute function control,
shift, kill.
Stop!
Take one more step,
and I'll breathe fire on you!
He'll do it! He's crazy!
Did we make that up?
Gee, I can't remember anymore.
It might be from that stupid movie.
ROBOT ELDER:
The original or the remake?
Hey! They're getting away!
FRY:
So long, suckers!
Hello, suckers.
Hold on.
I forgot to deliver the package.
Lug nuts! Precious lug nuts!
Hooray for the humans!
I can't believe you guys
did this for me.
This is the best Robanukah ever!
We want you to know that we
respect your robot heritage.
Thanks. You know I made Robanukah up
to get out of work, right?
Of course.
That doesn't make it
less meaningful.
In that case, let the dancing begin!
[HEBREW MUSIC PLAYS]
Hey, you guys are good.
How the hell do you do that?