WOMAN:
I hope you don't mind
decaf, Father.
It's all we had
in the cupboard.
A night this cold, I'll
take whatever I can get.
Colleen's upstairs
when you're ready.
Colleen?
Colleen, it's me.
It's all right!
Colleen, it's only me.
I'm here to pray
with you.
F-Father?
Oh, Father,
I'm so sorry.
I-I didn't realize...
It's all right,
my child.
No, no, no, no,
it isn't all right.
You're His emissary,
and I-I tried to hurt you.
I-I need to make it up to you.
I need to make it up to Him.
I can hurt myself!
Please don't, Colleen.
He doesn't want that,
and neither do I.
Michael, Michael
buys them for me.
Mother doesn't know.
She doesn't like me to have candy,
because
she thinks the sugar excites me,
but Michael knows
they make me happy.
He let's me have two a day.
He counts them every day
to make sure that's all I have,
but I've only had one today,
Father,
and I want you
to have the other.
Hail Mary full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for our sinners now
and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace...
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@FADEOUT
sync:FRM@FRM@π€∫£Œ¿
Hey.
Hey
Beds don't float,
do they?
Excuse me?
(sighs)
I mean, in your
experience,
as a rule, beds don't
float in midair, right?
Well, gosh, I would hope
that in the 14 or so years
that we've been together,
that once or twice
between the two of us,
our bed might have
left the ground,
but why do you ask?
It's nothing. It's crazy.
It's... it's stupid.
What are you doing?
I'm working on my rÈsumÈ?
Something you want to tell me?
Mm, yeah. No.
You're gonna think this is nuts,
but I had a dream.
Must be going around.
You want to share?
Mm...
This thing going on
at work.
In the dream?
Uh, no, in real life.
Um, I can't really talk
about it,
but it's a tremendous
opportunity.
And in the dream,
I go to my boss
and I say, "Mr. Canty,
I want this opportunity.
I want to run
this project."
You know what
he says to me?
He says to me, "Well, Joe,"I've just been waiting
for you to ask.
If you want something you got
to stop dragging your feet."
Wow, sounds like a good dream.
Hey.
The only man I know who starts
work earlier than I do.
Yeah, well, ever since
they changed the rules,
let people die 24 hours a day.
Guess that's why they call it
the "graveyard shift."
Ooh, graveyard shift. Very nice.
(chuckles)
So to what do I owe
this pleasure?
Got the call from the coroner
about 2:00 in the morning.
Saw your picture
in his wallet.
Apparently, he was having dinner at
the home of some friends last night,
went up to their study
to make a private call,
slipped and fell
on the stairs,
cracked his skull.
He had already expired by the time
the paramedics got there.
Are you, are you sure it's him?
There's no question.
How long did you guys
know each other?
Armando and I met the first
minute of the first day
of the first grade.
You know what?
I'm, I'm just going to, uh...
Sorry.
ALLISON:
Did you give the kids
breakfast?
I certainly did.
Did you eat?
I certainly did not.
Nervous?
(sing-songy):
You're gonna get it.
You know, the Mars thing?
Your boss is going
to give it to ya.
Who said anything about Mars?
Okay, forget Mars.
Mars, Venus, Jupiter--
whatever it is--
you're gonna get it,
that's all.
Allison Dubois has spoken?
Mm-hmm.
I'll be sure and tell my boss.
Yeah?
Sorry, sir, I know you asked
not to be disturbed.
I just... thought you might need
this for jury selection.
I know you're preparing.
You don't have
to worry.
There's no preparation
going on in here.
I can't hold
a thought in my head.
You can just leave 'em.
Thanks.
Is everything all right?
Ah... I lost an old friend
last night.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. He lived a good life.
Helped a lot of people.
Tripped and fell down
a flight of stairs,
cracked his skull.
When we were kids,
I once saw him walk on his hands
across a movie theater balcony
railing just to impress a girl
that was sitting down below.
Nobody does irony like God.
Armando Aguilar...
Uh, Father Armando Aguilar.
Oh, my God.
No, I know.
Trust me. (chuckles)
When we were growing up,
you would have
never seen it coming,
not in a million years.
Safe-cracker, maybe.
Gigolo,
well, he certainly
had the skill set,
but Catholic priest?
We're back to God and irony.
Happened yesterday evening
at the Fitzpatrick estate.
Fitzpatrick?
Like the Fitzpatrick plaza?
Yeah. Members of our parish.
They must be
devastated.
Oh. They've had a tough time.
Their only child, a grown
daughter took ill last year,
moved back in with them.
And now this.
I'm so sorry.
So if anybody asks,
I'm in here working away.
Absolutely, sir,
working away.
Joe.
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
The Mars project.
Joe, there is no Mars project.
(chuckles)
Of course there isn't.
Uh, but if there were
and if we were contemplating
being involved
in the engineering
of the on-board systems,
I would really like to throw
my hat in the ring
to be considered
the project leader.
You know
how this stuff works, Joe.
We don't call the tune
on these sorts of projects...
if there actually
are these sorts of projects.
My Uncle Sam does.
Well, let your uncle know
that I'm interested.
So let me get this straight.
You're happy because
you have a real shot at a job
that doesn't exist on a project
that your firm isn't doing.
I'm sorry.
I have no comment.
You will never
get it out of me.
You are a cagey one,
Mr. Dubois.
Very hard to read,
highly inscrutable.
Oh, I beg to differ.
You could scrute me
with a little effort.
Scruting is a
definite possibility.
Maybe I should have said
something.
And the point of
telling your boss
that you just saw his
newly-dead friend
in a scene out
of the Exorcist
would have been...?
Okay, obviously, it wasn't
a literal dream.
Obviously, that young woman's
bed didn't really float.
I must have that dream
for some reason,
don't you think?
Hello?
Sorry, honey, I just got
an e-mail from Marcus.
"Dear Joe, I've
just been informed
"that a government polygraph
examiner will make himself
"available at our offices
tomorrow afternoon
"to administer
a test to you
"as part of your
pre-qualification
"for certain programs our
company may participate in
"on the government's
behalf in the near future.
"If for some reason
tomorrow afternoon"does not work for you,
please let me know
so that I..."
Is everything all right?
Yes, actually, I think
everything is very right.
Mars...
Stop that.
Help me.
Give me strength.
What are you doing?
I'm looking
for something.
It's 4:30 in
the morning.
Hey, this is the girl I saw,
the one with the floating bed.
Colleen Fitzpatrick.
She's the one the priest
was praying with the night that he died.
This is a picture
from her wedding in 2003 before she took ill.
Pretty girl.
I wonder if she
can do that thing
where she makes her head
spin all the way around?
What? You told me last
night you thought
that this girl might
believe she had a
demon inside her?
It seems like a perfectly
legitimate question to me.
There are no such thing
as demons.
Said the psychic who
talks to ghosts.
Are there things that exist,
lie beyond this world?
Yes, absolutely.
Demons aren't one of them.
Okay, fine, demons
don't exist.
This girl does.
What's the big deal?
Well, the police are calling
the priest's death an accident.
It didn't look
that way to me.
It looked to me like
Colleen Fitzpatrick might have killed him.
Fitzpatrick?
The department
store Fitzpatricks?
They're members
of Devalos' parish.
The same one the dead
priest worked at?
Mm.
Oh, I wouldn't want
to be them at the
next church picnic.
Sir?
I know you're on your way
into court,
but I was afraid if I didn't
speak with you...
You holding up okay?
I didn't sleep
much last night,
but I guess that's
to be expected.
I tried putting the
time to good use.
I started working on a
eulogy for Father Armando.
Actually, he's the reason
I wanted to speak with you.
Oh?
I'm not certain that your
friend's fall was an accident.
I'm guessing that
I'm not the only one
who didn't sleep
well last night.
You said the Fitzpatrick's
daughter wasn't well?
Colleen. She had some sort
of breakdown last year.
I don't know the specifics,
but I seem to recall
that it was serious enough
for her husband to consider
institutionalizing her.
But Colleen's mother
wouldn't hear of it.
They moved in with her,
and she's been caring
for her ever since.
What does this
have to do with...
Do you know if she's
prone to violence?
Colleen's mother, Helen,
showed up for Mass
a few months ago with
her arm in a sling.
No one actually said it,
but the sense I got
is that it had to do with...
caring for her daughter.
Are you implying...
I think that he was struck
in the head before he fell
down those stairs.
He was hit with something,
I don't know what it was.
Something heavy.
He was your friend.
I just... I think you need
to ask some more questions.
Is your name
Joseph Pritchard Dubois?
Yes, it is.
Are you an employee
of Aerodytech?
Yes, I am.
Have you ever discussed
confidential work matters
with anyone
outside the company?
No, I have not.
Are you married?
Yes, 13 years.
Just a yes or no,
please.
Right. Sorry.
Do you ever work
on company projects while at home?
Sometimes-- yes.
Is there any way
anyone at home
could gain unauthorized access
to company information?
No.
Let's take that one again.
(softly):
Oh. Manuel.
Helen.
I hope you'll forgive
the mess,
but we had a small army
of policemen
pass through her the night
of Father Armando's accident.
MAN:
Helen, have you seen
Colleen's new prescription?
I thought I saw it
in the upstairs bathroom last
night, but now I can't seem...
Oh, sorry.
I didn't realize
you had company.
Oh. Michael, you remember
our old family friend,
District Attorney
Manuel Devalos.
Right. Of course,
from the wedding.
Good to see you again, Michael.
Anyway, I'll keep looking
for those pills upstairs.
Actually, Michael,
if you have a moment.
I'm here on business, business
that involves you and Helen.
Just a few follow-up questions
regarding the statements
you gave the police
the other night.
Would now be a good time?
Well, it was
a little after 9:00,
and we had just finished
our meal, when Father Armando
told me that he had
to make a private call.
And so I told him he
was welcome to use
the study upstairs.
And, uh, I was fixing
a cup of tea,
and Michael
was in the cellar
replacing a bottle of wine
that we hadn't opened.
And there was this
terrible crash from the foyer,
and I raced in
from the kitchen.
(softly):
And... he was at the bottom
of the stairs.
Alone?
There was no third party
in the room?
No one other than you
and Armando?
That's correct.
May I ask where Colleen was
when this was happening?
She was in her
room, sleeping.
The commotion
didn't wake her?
She'd had a very
challenging day.
We'd given her a little
something to help her sleep.
Is something wrong,
Manuel?
I've just come from
the Medical Examiner's office.
I asked them to take a second
look at Armando's injuries.
They now feel that he may have
sustained a blow to the head
before he fell
down your stairs.
I don't understand.
How can they
say one thing one day
and then something completely
different the next?
They also found
a partial fingerprint
in a spot of blood
on the good Father's forehead.
I'm sure you'll both recall
that Colleen was arrested
for erratic driving shortly after she took ill
13 months ago.
We ran the fingerprints
we had on file for her
against the one we found
on Armando,
and I'm sorry to say
it was a perfect match.
ALLISON:
Absolutely.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Devalos?
(sighs)
Colleen Fitzpatrick
did kill Father Armando.
They found the murder weapon
at the top of the stairs on a
table-- it was a wooden bookend.
Ouch.
Her mother and her husband found
her standing over the body.
They knew about it
the whole time.
So what happens now?
Everyone goes to jail?
No. Devalos feels like
the family's suffered enough.
He's not going to charge them
with obstruction.
And if the girl's
found incompetent,
she won't even
stand trial.
Her psych evaluation
is tomorrow.
I hope I did
the right thing.
What are you
talking about?
I don't know,
maybe it's my imagination,
it just... sounded like Devalos
was sadder
now that he knows the truth.
I think he preferred it
when he thought
his friend's death
was a simple accident.
(sighs)
This is one of those moments
I'm not sure that my gift
is such a gift.
I know what you mean.
Can I ask you something?
Are you sure I'm going
to get this thing?
What thing?
What are you talking about?
The promotion?
Yeah, I'm sure.
At least
I think I'm sure. Why?
It's just that
everything was going
fine this morning.
I was doing great, and
then, the polygraph guy
starts asking me
questions about home
and if there was any
way that anyone here
could find out things
that they shouldn't know,
and then I remembered what
happened the other morning.
What happened
the other morning?
You remember--
what you said
when you were getting
out of the shower?
What did I say?
I'm not going to say; I'm
not going to remind you.
That would just
defeat the whole point.
What point?
I don't know what
you're talking about?
You talking about
that joke I made about you going to Mars?
Shh.
What "shh"?
Who could hear us?
Wait a second.
Are you really going
to Mars?
I don't know.
Based on the way today
went, probably not.
Is that what this
is all about?
That I guessed right?
Guess?
You're telling me
that was a guess?
No, it's worse than that.
It wasn't even a guess.
It was a joke.
A joke?
You're kidding.
HELEN:
What was that noise?
(in distance):
Is everyone okay?!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Colleen,
what have you done?
Answer me, Colleen.
What have you done?
Oh, my God.
Father, you're going
to be okay.
We're going
to get you some help.
Michael! Where are you?
We need to call 911.
WOMAN:
Please, Colleen, I know
it's hard, but I need you
to sit and concentrate.
No. N-N-N-N-No. No.
I need you
to tell us
what was going
through your mind
when you hurt
Father Armando.
I didn't hurt Father Armando.
You did, Colleen.
You hurt him very badly,
and you know that.
No, you're wrong.
I didn't do anything.
Are you trying to tell us
that somebody else hurt him?
The demon inside you?
It's okay, Colleen,
you can tell us.
We're your friends.
I can see your words,
you know.
I can see them.
How dark they are,
how twisted.
Like a long, black ribbon.
Please, Colleen, don't.
I know you now.
I know who you are.
The great whore.
The great whore
that sitteth
Colleen, sweetie, you need
upon many waters
to calm down
right now, okay?
with whom the kings
of the earth
have committed fornication.
I know you, whore!
I can see your words.
I can see them all,
whore, I can
see them.
WOMAN:
Colleen has been getting worse
the last few weeks,
more delusional
more violent
during our sessions.
You've been treating
her for how long now?
13 months.
Then she wasn't
under your care prior to her breakdown?
It's my understanding,
Mr. Devalos,
that prior
to her breakdown,
Colleen was a perfectly happy
and healthy woman
with no need whatsoever
for somebody in my line of work.
I'm sorry to say
I never had the pleasure
of meeting that Colleen.
It sounds like she changed
pretty suddenly.
About a year
and a half ago,
Michael came
home from work
and, apparently, she was
hysterical, terrified.
She had called the police
thinking that she had seen
something monstrous
in her house, some
sort of creature.
Demonic creature?
There's always been
a religious theme
to Colleen's
hallucinations--
demons, possession.
I tend to attribute
it to the fact
that she was such
a devout woman
before she took ill.
But you were the one who
diagnosed her, correct?
Undifferentiated
schizophrenia.
Yes, that's true, but
to be perfectly honest,
it's a bit of a catchall
as far as diagnoses go.
I'm sorry.
I don't follow.
It's used
when the patient's symptoms very clearly point
to schizophrenia,
but are so clouded
that classifying the type
of disorder is very difficult.
If I may ask you,
Dr. Randall,
what's so cloudy about
Colleen's symptoms?
She's prone
to delusional episodes
but has long stretches
of lucidity in between.
True schizophrenia
doesn't work that way.
It's far more
consistent.
I've also given her any number of neuroleptics--
drugs that should treat
the symptoms of schizophrenia--
but none of them seem
to have any effect on her.
I'm sure there's some sort
of explanation for this,
but I haven't
been able to find it
Hey.
You know that project
that we're not doing to do?
The one I can't speak
to you about?
You should just forget about it.
Whoa. Wait a second, Marcus.
Your wife.
She's some type
of consultant, right?
Has something to do
with the government?
She works part time for the
District Attorney's office.
Why?
I don't know, but she's
a red flag for them,
a big red flag.
The polygraph
examiner picked up
some deception when you
were asked about her.
And now, they've
considered her to be,
uh, some sort
of security risk.
That is absurd.
Doesn't matter. There isn't...
such a project.
It's not like you had
something that you lost.
It was never here
for you to have.
Wait, what? Marcus?
This is not the end
of the conversation.
Surely, there must be some
kind of a work-around.
A work-around for a government
security clearance?
I don't think so.
Well, think harder, Marcus.
You know what an asset
I would be to this.
L-Let me take, let me
take the test again.
This is not like something
that you can cram for, Joe.
You're either telling
the truth or you're not.
Of course I'm telling the truth.
Well, I know one expert
who disagrees.
I've worked for this
company for 15 years.
I've never put
them at risk.
This is not
the company talking.
All right, fine,
but there must be a
call that you can make.
Isn't there a string
that you can pull?
Please.
ALLISON:
It's 'cause of me, isn't it?
They can sense that you can sense that
I might be able to...
rifle through your thoughts
if I wanted to?
Hmm... I don't know.
They sense something.
Funny thing is...
I don't know
what this project is.
I know it has something
to do with Mars.
Beyond that...
I know it has something
to do with space.
I know what space
means to you.
I remember
the night we met.
You picked me up
at that bar,
you brought me
back to your place,
showed me your...
telescope.
You showed me your books
on the cosmos.
You showed me your lunch box
from the third grade
with rockets and planets.
And you thought,
"What a nerd."
And I thought...
"I think I have
to sleep with this man.
I think I might have
to marry this man."
And now it's me standing between you
and your other love.
I love you.
And I love you.
HELEN:
Michael, is that you?
Hey, sorry I
missed dinner.
I got pulled into
a late meeting.
Don't give it a second
thought, dear.
I made you a plate
and put it in the fridge.
Oh, thanks.
Was that Father Armando's
car I saw in the driveway?
(phone ringing)
Yes, he's upstairs
visiting Colleen.
Don't you need to get that?
Work.
They can call me on
the landline if they
really need me.
FATHER ARMANDO:
...pray for us sinners now
and at the hour
of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou
among women
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners now
and at the hour
of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou
among women
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, mother of God,
pray for us sinners now
and at the hour
of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary,
full of grace...
Dr. Elizabeth Randall, please.
Thank you.
Hey. Sorry I couldn't answer.
Mother Fitzpatrick was standing
right in front of me.
Yeah, she's got
the priest here again.
Guess she still thinks
the power of prayer is going to make a difference.
Honestly, darling?
I don't know what it's going
to take to get Helen
to put Colleen in a home.
Yeah, well... I miss you, too.
If Helen turns in early,
maybe I'll try to swing
by your place later.
FATHER ARMANDO:
Oh, dear God, no!
Something's up.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Give me strength.
What is it, Father?
Her bed.
It's floating.
Do you see it?
Michael, do you see it?!
Having an affair with
your wife's physician is not against the law.
I mean, it's not nice, but
it's not against the law.
At least I don't
think it is.
How's this?
Does this look honest?
Yes, you look honest,
you look thoroughly honest.
'Cause you are honest.
So be honest and tell me what do
I do about this bed thing?
Do I tell Devalos?
Tell Devalos what?
That in your dream his
friend was having delusions
about free-floating furniture?
I mean, if you tell him that,
he's gonna send you
home for the day.
(sighs)
I, uh... I think it's over.
You know who died,
and you know how
it happened.
You know everything.
Okay, then why do I keep
dreaming about all of it?
(sighs)
That I don't know.
Okay. Look, I know you have
other things on your mind.
I know you think this horse
is already dead
and you can't figure out
why I keep beating it.
No.
Well, yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm
nervous about today.
I'm just starting to think
that I should have forgotten
about the whole thing.
You know,it's not a test test,
it's a lie detector test,
and I failed, and I don't
know what made me think
that I would pass it if I
got a second shot at it.
Okay. Well, if you know that...
What can you do?
You in there and...
tell the truth.
I mean, really,
what else can you do?
You go in there
and you tell them the truth.
And after that,
it's out of your hands.
What?
It's not like I didn't tell
the truth the first time.
Fine. If you say so.
ADMINISTRATOR:
Is your name
Joseph Pritchard Dubois?
Yes.
Have you ever discussed
confidential work matters
with anyone
outside the company?
No, I have not.
Is there any way
anyone at home
could gain
unauthorized access
to company information?
Is there any way
anyone at home
could gain
unauthorized access
to company information?
Yes.
Yeah, I suppose there is.
I'm sorry, did you
just answer
in the affirmative?
Yes. Yes, I did.
You're saying
that there is a way
that someone could gain
unauthorized access
to company information,
but you don't discuss
confidential matters
outside the office?
That's correct.
Is this person
in question your wife?
Yes. Yes, it is.
Is she a computer hacker?
No.
Do you talk in your sleep?
Can she read your mind?
Yes.
As a matter of
fact, she can.
She can read your mind?
That's correct.
She can pluck thoughts
from your head?
Your wife possesses
psychic abilities.
Yes.
So, Mr. Dubois,
you're telling me
that your wife
finishes your sentences
and, um, can often tell
when you're lying,
that sort of thing?
That's correct.
Well, what do you know?
My wife is psychic, too.
Thank you very much.
We're done here.
Did I pass?
Well, why don't you call
your wife and ask her?
Talk to me.
JOE:
You were right.
So I take it the truth
set you free.
It certainly felt a lot better
the second time around.
So now I guess we just
hold our breath.
What for? You got it.
I'm sure of it.
Hmm. From your lips
to Uncle Sam's ear.
You sound like
you're in the car.
I'm playing messenger girl.
Devalos had some papers
that he needed
Dr. Randall to sign
at the institute.
I offered to run them
over there.
Out of the goodness
of your heart?
Oh, out of the badness
of my...
what, I don't know, dirty mind?
I just want to look her
in the eye.
It seems like a dangerous
conflict of interest to me.
I mean, she's sleeping
with that poor woman's husband.
Well, just remember,
it may mean nothing at all.
(sighing):
Yeah. Well, I hope so.
Mrs. Dubois, right?
Oh, y-yes. Hello again,
Mr. Barlow.
I was just dropping these
papers off for Dr. Randall.
The nurse at the front desk
told me I could find her here.
Oh, she had to take a call.
She said she'd be right back.
You're welcome to wait
if you'd like.
ALLISON:
How's she doing adjusting to her
new surroundings?
Uh, it's hard to say.
Dr. Randall prescribed
some new sedatives.
She's been sleeping a lot.
Sorry, again,
about yesterday.
I'm sure that wasn't
an easy thing to watch.
You know what they say--
everything happens for a reason.
As it goes,
I think it's exactly
what the district attorney
needed to see.
Made it easy for him
to recommend that she
be kept here, as opposed
to awaiting trial in prison.
You're right-- everything
happens for a reason.
NURSE:
Mr. Barlow?
I'm afraid I'm going
to have to take these.
Take them?
We have a very
strict policy here regarding outside food.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, but they're not food.
I mean, not technically.
They're candies.
My wife has one
or two every day.
She really
looks forward to them.
I'm sorry,
there can be no exceptions.
No, wait a second.
You're not listening to me.
My wife needs those.
They're a great
comfort to her.
I only had one today, Father.
I want you to have the other.
RANDALL:
Is there a problem here?
NURSE:
I was just explaining
to Mr. Barlow that we don't
allow outside food
under any circumstances.
And I was just explaining to her
that it's very important
that my wife have a piece
of candy to look forward to every day.
I think we can make an exception
just this once, don't you?
But, Dr. Randall...
They're nothing, nurse.
Just little balls
of sugar.
I don't see how
they could do any harm.
You're the doctor, Doctor.
NURSE:
Excuse me.
What if I told you
I have reason to believe
that Colleen Fitzpatrick
isn't sick at all?
I'm sorry--
you think she's faking?
Let's just say I don't believe
that she's crazy,
and I don't believe
she's possessed.
But I need your help to prove it.
Manny.
Test results just came back.
And?
Allison was right.
You want us to go
scoop these monsters up?
Yeah.
I do.
No, Stanley,
you're not listening.
As of today, every account is
supposed to have my name on it.
Yes, even Colleen's trust.
Well, that's what
power of attorney means.
Stanley, I'm going to have
to call you back.
Michael Barlow?
Yes.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Father Armando Aguilar.
You have the right to remain silent.
What?
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
No, this is wrong.
in a court of law.
My wife is the one
who killed Father Armando.
...if you can't afford an attorney,
That was Colleen.
one will be
provided for you.
This is crazy.
Crazy, huh?
It's a good thing I picked up a psychiatrist
on the way over here.
Her name's
Elizabeth Randall.
I think you
two have met.
HELEN:
Lysergic acid?
LSD.
We found significant
amounts of it
in Father Armando's system
after we exhumed him.
We're still running
Colleen's blood work,
but I'm confident we'll
find it in hers as well.
I don't understand, Manuel.
Are you telling me
she isn't sick?
It's our belief that
every last one of the symptoms
she's experienced over the past
13 months-- the hallucinations,
the paranoia,
the violent outbursts--
were all drug-induced.
The stretches
of lucidity between,
the days that she would act
and sound like the old Colleen,
those were just recovery periods
between dosings.
But I've hardly ever left
Colleen's side
this past year.
I never saw Michael
give her a single pill,
a single injection.
It was the candies.
He covered each one
with a liquid form of the drug.
And by making them
her daily treat,
he could count on her
self-medicating.
The only thing he didn't
count on was Colleen
offering Father Armando a candy
during his last visit.
We believe that Michael
killed the good Father
because he knew that once
the effects of the LSD wore off,
Armando would start
asking questions,
probably realize
that Colleen was being dosed.
But all those doctors
I took her to,
all those specialists,
why didn't they ever detect
the drug in her system?
LSD doesn't show up
in most blood screenings.
You have to know
that you're looking for it.
You have to run
a very specific test.
And the fact that Michael's
partner in crime, Dr. Randall,
was Colleen's primary physician
didn't help matters any.
She could always run
interference for Michael,
throw any other doctors off the scent.
And all this... cruelty
just to get around a
prenuptial agreement?
If Colleen had died
or divorced Michael,
he would've ended up
with nothing.
If she were to lose
her mind, however,
be declared incompetent,
he could stay married to her
and still have access
to your family's fortune.
It's gonna be okay,
Helen.
It's gonna be fine.
Colleen's working the drug
out of her system
for the very last time,
and it's my understanding
that once she does,
she's going to make
a full recovery.
You're going to get
your daughter back.
So let me get
this straight.
The reason we get to
stay up an extra half hour
and eat cake is because
Daddy got put in charge
of some really
cool project.
That is correct.
Only you can't tell us
about this really cool project
because it's top secret.
That is also correct.
Can we at least have a hint?
ALLISON:
Okay, on that note,
come on, you little
security risks.
It's time
to hit the hay.
Joe, you got Bridge?
Yes.
Come on, kiddo.
Time for bed.
But I don't want
to go to bed.
I like staying up late.
Really? You got a funny way
of showing it.
Congratulations
again, Daddy.
If you can't get
that ship up to Mars,
nobody can.
welcome to www.1000fr.com