I don't understand.
I thought you said
she was getting better.
She fooled us.
The leukemia fooled us.
For a while it seemed
like she was responding
to the treatment.
Unfortunately, her blood
cell count keeps dropping.
I don't know if her system
can take another
round of chemo.
I'm so sorry.
I'll make it a point
to stop back
when your parents are here.
Thank you.
Wow.
How long was I out?
Just a few minutes.
It's weird
the way you do that.
So sudden.
Hmm.
Mom and Dad went
to grab a bite.
Hey. I almost forgot.
I... I brought you
something.
(gasping):
No!
It's Mr. Snookie!
Where in the hell
did you find him?
Me and Dad tore the garage apart
until we found him.
Hmm. He looks as old
and crappy as I feel.
(light cough)
Yeah, that German shepherd
really did a number on him, huh?
It's okay.
Sorry.
(weakly):
I get so tired.
It's okay.
WOMAN:
You girls decent in there?
Hell, no.
We're Dubois women.
Nothing decent about us.
Was she out the whole time?
30 seconds ago,
she was laughing.
The chemo's just completely
knocked the crap out of her.
Doctor came by.
Said it wasn't really helping.
Did Marie hear?
No.
Ariel...
Do me a favor.
You've got to go outside,
call Bridgette.
Okay? Tell her we need her.
Daddy or I will pick her
up at the airport,
but she needs
to come today.
(sobbing)
Okay? Tonight.
ALLISON:
Shh.
I'm going to miss
her so much.
I don't know if I can
live without her.
Hi. You're there.
This is Allison Dubois.
I was wondering, is there
any way I could possibly
bring in my youngest daughter in
to see the doctor today?
11:00. Thank you.
Bye.
(phone beeps off)
Hey.
Woke up.
Your side of the
bed was empty.
Cold. How long
you been up?
I don't know.
I think Marie's coming down
with something.
I was up with her
half the night.
Is it serious?
I hope not.
I hope I caught it in time.
She seems fine now.
I'm just going
to keep her home
and run her by the doctor.
ALL:
God, grant me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change,
courage to change
the things I can,
and wisdom to know
the difference.
SCANLON:
I just think it's weird,
that's all.
The guy calls me
first thing this morning
to make sure I'm going
to be at the meeting,
then he doesn't show up.
Gary's a recovering addict.
We're all
recovering addicts.
Reliability is not
our strong suit.
He's going to do
what he's going to do.
You're his sponsor,
not his mother.
As long as you're there
when he does calls you.
Long as you're there
when he does show up.
The rest is up to him.
That's Gary's car.
MAN:
Good news.
There's no strep.
No fever.
Her inoculations are up to date.
The truth is...
She looks super.
Okay.
So I'm... I'm a little unclear.
Is this an exam for school?
For day care? For camp?
Is there something
you want me to sign?
I need you to talk
to me about leukemia.
Leukemia?
Are we still talking
about Marie?
Well, ah...
Wh-what would you like to know?
Has she been tired?
She doesn't look tired.
I didn't notic
any swelling
or weight loss.
Allison, leukemia's
a hell of a rabbit
to pull out of your hat.
It would help me to know
where this comes from.
Hi, Jen?
Uh, could you come
in here for a second
and get Marie Dubois?
Yeah, keep an eye
on her for a minute,
so her mom and I can
have a conversation.
No, no, I... I know.
I know how backed up we are.
Thank you.
Okay, baby, Mommy's
gonna come get you
in a minute, okay?
Okay.
Allison, look,
I know you know this,
but, uh...
Leukemia is not something
she's going to catch
on the playground.
You've never mentioned
a family history of it.
It's never
come up in conversation
about the other girls.
Has something happened?
Someone on your husband's side?
I just need to know:
is this the kind of disease
that you can get
in front of it?
Treat it
before it strikes?
Allison, what you're saying
doesn't make any sense.
We don't... we don't
treat people for diseases
before they have them.
Before they have them
there is nothing to treat.
But with leukemia, with
cancer, I mean, in theory...
It's already in there
waiting to happen, right?
I am not an oncologist.
But that's kind
of a simple way of...
What if I had had it?
Or my mother had had it?
Aren't there things
you would be doing?
Tests you would be running
to keep an eye on it
in the children?
But you don't
have it,
and as for your mother...
But if we did?
Allison.
The kind of tests
you're talking about
are... invasive.
Painful. It's not something
you'd want done to a child
unless it was
completely necessary.
And they're expensive.
You know, insurance
won't cover them
unless there's some
credible diagnostic rationale.
You know, forgive
my asking this,
but does Joe know you're here?
Talking to me about this?
I didn't want to alarm him
till I knew more.
Allison, I have to be
honest with you,
this-this... this is
kind of crazy talk.
If this were anybody else, if I didn't know
you as well as I do,
I would be tempted
to pick up the phone
and call Child Services.
All right, so here's
what I'm willing to do.
Let's draw some blood.
Okay? We'll send it
to the lab.
That is the first place
we would see
any indication of disease.
Thank you, Doctor.
SCANLON:
Gary, it's Lee.
Listen, man, you need
to check in with me.
I'm worried about you and I'm
wondering what you're doing.
Call me. Let me know
you're all right.
(whispering):
Are you staying
in here all night?
Sorry. I lost track of time.
I appreciate this,
Earl. Like I said,
apparently, the
roommate's out of town.
I'm just concerned
about my friend.
(knocking)
Gary? Anyone?
Hello?
Allison? It's Dr. Bondi.
I've got Marie's tests back,
and, uh,
I have to tell you
that little girl
is as healthy as a horse.
If there's anything in her blood
that's going to compromise
her health,
modern science can't currently
see it, much less treat it.
Will she be healthy
15 or 20 years from now?
Nobody knows that.
But now that I know
it's an issue for you,
we can test Marie
every time she comes in.
Hi, I'm home.
Allison, any one
of our kids could get hit
by a car tomorrow,
be felled by the flu.
It's how we love them
while they're here.
While we're here.
Well, anyway,
you get the point.
Right now, she's the living
definition of healthy
and right now
is all we can control.
Hey...
I'm home too.
Hey.
All the really big bosses
are away at a seminar,
and I figured there was nothing
I was doing at my desk
that I can't do at home
on my laptop.
Hey, we're teaching Marie how
to play Monkey in the Middle.
She's a very good monkey.
You got cake?
Is it somebody's birthday?
Celebrating just to celebrate.
Cool.
Mmm... yum.
What's the occasion?
You know, one day, you're
feeling kind of down...
the next day the sun's out
and things look...
(dog growling)
Hey, get out of here!
Get out!
(dog growling)
Hey! Hey!
Get out!
Hey, kids! Get away
from that dog!
Let him go, Ariel!
Ariel! Ariel!
Just let the dog have it!
Ariel, get inside!
Doggy hurt Mr. Snookie.
Daddy ran outside and saved you?
Ariel saved Mr. Snookie.
What were you thinking, Ariel?
He could have attacked you.
He could have bitten you.
But he had Mr. Snookie and...
I don't care!
You act like that to save
one of your sisters,
not a teddy bear.
Okay?
Hey...
Are you okay?
Honey, why the long face?
Everybody's doing just fine.
Everybody's fine.
JOE:
Leukemia?
She was 20, maybe 21.
But the doctor said she's fine.
Yes, today. Yes, now.
Okay, then, uh...
wait, I don't understand.
What is there not to understand?
The doctor said she's fine.
And for now, she is.
He didn't say
she would always be fine.
There's no way
he could possibly know that.
But I know that.
Just like I saw Ariel give
Marie that torn-up teddy bear.
No, Allison.
Even though it just happened.
Just got torn up
a few hours ago.
Please listen to yourself.
That teddy bear has nothing
to do with anything.
You're not listening!
That torn-up teddy bear
has everything
to do with everything.
I saw it last night
before it happened,
in the same dream
that I saw
our youngest daughter...
dying.
Ariel
said you and her
went into the garage,
and you found that torn-up
teddy bear,
and she wanted
to give it to Marie,
and that's how I know this
is going to happen, you see?
No, I don't see.
Actually, Allison,
you're not making any sense.
Oh, really?
After all this time,
are you saying
that you don't believe in me?
You don't believe
in the things that I see?
Or the things th I feel?
Of course I'm
not saying that.
I absolutely
believe in you.
I'm not questioning
what you see.
It's your logic
that makes no sense.
I'll prove
it to you.
Joe!
What are you doing?
I'm saving our
daughter's life.
What are you talking about?
(whispers):
I'm gonna go,
and I'm gonna take that bear,
and I'm gonna burn it
in the backyard.
Don't you see?
Look, according to your logic,
if there's no bear in the
garage 20 years from now,
then there's nothing for
Ariel to give to Marie
when she goes
into the hospital,
so maybe she's not
in the hospital,
'cause maybe she's not sick.
(whispers):
You're mocking me.
No!
I am trying to
get you to see
how irrational
and potentially dangerous,
destructive your thinking is.
Look, Allison, hey.
Look, listen,
listen, sweetie,
look, you may be
right about this.
She may be fated to die
before her time,
but what's the point of living
for her and for us,
if her whole life
is spent chasing a tragedy
that we're not sure
is ever really gonna happen,
and which for the
time being we can
do nothing about!
I won't do it!
I'll will take
that bear from her
and I will burn it
in the biggest bonfire
you have ever seen
if it will convince you
to forget about what you saw
for the time being.
Just forget about it
until it
actually happens,
if it actually
happens,
till there's something
that we can do about it.
Do you have any idea
what you're asking of me?!
How hard it would be
for me just to pretend
that everything's fine?!
I don't know if I can!
Wait, wait.
I'm not asking you to pretend.
You're missing the point.
Everything is fine.
That's how life works.
Everything is fine
until it isn't,
and then you deal with it.
Otherwise, there is no life.
There's just waiting to die.
What the hell is Willow Elm?
Huh?
Willow Elm,
what is that?
Some sort of a tree?
Why are you
looking up trees?
No, I wasn't.
What are you doing?
It's a quarter
after 5:00.
Come back to bed.
I can't sleep.
I keep thinking
about this kid.
Met him at my
NA meeting.
Asked me to be
his sponsor.
He OD'd yesterday.
I'm sorry.
I have to call his folks
and tell them.
They're back east in Delaware,
two hours ahead of us.
I want to get them
before they go to work.
I'm figuring 5:30 here,
7:30 there.
I'm dreading it.
I'll sit with you.
I'll help you through it.
Thanks.
DOCTOR:
I'm afraid
all we can really do
at this point is make her
as comfortable as possible.
What about more chemo?
I mean, I know it's...
it's knocking her on her ass.
See, there's a tipping point
with the chemo,
where the cure
is worse than the disease
and we've passed
that point, I'm afraid.
So what do we do?
You gather
your loved ones,
and you say your good-byes.
This is our fault, you know?
I knew it. I told you
we should not have stayed
in that house.
(sobbing):
We should not have stayed
in that house.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Actually, I'm good.
You're right.
None of it means anything
until it's clear
what you can do to stop it.
What?
We're moving.
I don't understand.
What is it exactly
about this house
that is going
to make Marie sick?
Is this about mold?
Is this about radon?
It's not like
we're close to
any power lines.
I don't know.
What difference does it make?
What you need to know
is we need to get our
little girl out of here.
We need to move.
Allison, whoa!
Do you understand
what you're saying: "move"?
It's... it's not that easy.
Finding a new house takes time.
Selling the house that we have
is going to take time.
I don't even know
what this place is worth.
People do it every day.
Yeah, people do it every day,
Allison,
but nobody does it in a day.
"Willow Elm."
What?
Willow Elm's the answer.
Now what you're walking through
is the "Hacienda" model
of Phase 3 here at Willow Elm.
We've got 108 acres here,
over $400 million
in construction...
Bunford Properties'
biggest project to date.
Oh, beautiful kitchen,
beautiful everything.
Thank you.
Obviously, there's all kinds
of upgrades and options available.
Take a look around.
Any of my salespeople
will be happy to answer
any question you might have.
And please, feel free to call me
or e-mail me directly.
It's perfect.
You don't
really know that.
I mean, you can't
possibly know that.
You just spent
20 minutes in a model home.
That hardly constitutes
a thorough evaluation.
It's Willow Elm.
It's perfect.
It's where we're
supposed to be.
Allison...
What?
we don't even know
if we can afford it.
It's a house.
It's not an impulse buy.
It's our child!
I know, I know,
but we have everything
we have worked for
tied up in that house.
Now, wouldn't the
logical thing...
figure out if
No, the logical thing?
The logical thing is this second.
figure out if
The instant you find out
your child is in peril
before we uproot the kids!
you do whatever
you have to save them
as quickly as you can
and you screw
the money!
It makes no sense!
I don't understand!
I don't understand
how you could treat
all of this
as if it isn't real.
We're talking
about our child's life!
No, don't do that!
Don't do what?!
Don't act like
I am sending our child
off to a certain death
just because I want to
stop and take a breath
and see if any of
this makes sense!
Make sense!
Don't do that,
either,
'cause I am here!
I took the morningoff work
I am in this with you!
Someone has to ask
these questions!
Well, you do that, Joe.
You ask those questions.
So I have a question.
Who's going to call
the Realtor?
I don't understand.
What's the mystery?
Kid was a drug addict.
He died of an overdose.
I know that.
Just the same,
I need you to perform
another autopsy.
Just because somebody
wona free one during
the silent auction
at this year's
Police Fundraiser?
I knew this kid.
I called his folks
after we found him.
They made me promise.
The overdose thing--
it just doesn't add up for them.
Wow, parents don't believe
their baby's a junkie.
There's one
I haven't heard before.
No, they knew
their kid had a history,
but he's also a medical student,
very careful, very fastidious.
They just don't believe he
wouldn't know what he was taking
and how much to take.
I see, so the city of Phoenix
is going to pay for an autopsy
to test the quality of a young,
dead addict's medical education.
Please?
If we're getting a new house,
who's gonna live here?
Excellent question.
Oh, I spoke with a Realtor.
She's gonna stop by tomorrow
and take a look,
give us an appraisal.
Uh-huh.
So if me and Marie
are getting our own rooms,
then maybe we should leave
the bunk beds here
for whoever moves in, right?
I mean, they're gonna have
kids, too, right?
I don't think I can do it.
I don't think
I can sell a poisoned house.
Look, truth be told,
I don't want to move.
I don't want to sell
this house.
I mean, I will
if I have to,
but just to play
devil's advocate,
we don't know for sure
that it's poisoned.
I mean, maybe it's not
poisoned yet.
Maybe that's something
that happens in the future.
Are you kidding?
You really think
that takes us off the hook?
Well, I don't
know, Allison.
First you tell me
we got to move
because our daughter's
going to get sick and die,
and then you tell me
that you don't want to move
because you can't
bear the thought
of somebody else
getting sick and dying.
Just tell me which side
you want me to take
in this argument
'cause I can't seem
to find one thatorks.
We cannot afford to move
unless and until
we sell this house.
Do you understand that?
We can't, in good conscience,
sell this house
not to a family
with small children,
not to anyone.
God, I hate this!
I'm sorry.
I don't share your sense
of unlimited responsibility
for absolutely everything
from now until the end of time.
What are you talking about?
When we bought
this house
it was, to the best of our
knowledge and to the knowledge
of the people who sold it to us,
clean.
It may very well be
that it is still clean.
As a homeowner,
I got a responsibility
to make sure
that the house stays clean,
to test it from time to time
to make repairs,
adjustments...
Okay, where are you going
with this?
We'll get the
house tested.
We'll call someone in.
We'll have them test the house
for everything.
We'll do everything we can
to make sure
the house is safe to sell.
I think that's all
that anyone can expect.
I don't know.
Or we stay.
And we never speak
another word about it.
I don't understand.
I heard he died
of a drug overdose.
Really? Is that
what you heard, huh?
I'm just telling you.
There it is, Detective.
Thanks, I'll try
and bring it back
with a full tank of gas.
I have been waiting for days,
Doctor!
Mrs. Dubois, as my staff
has repeatedly explained to you,
hospital hours are for surgeries
and follow-ups.
Office hours are for meetings
and consults.
Now, as soon as I have
some office hours free,
my staff will call you
to set up a meeting.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm on my way to surgery.
I'm sorry. My daughter is dead,
and you killed her!
Would you say
that is more
of a follow-up or would that be
an office visit?
Mrs. Dubois, you are violating
the restraining order.
Fine. Call the police.
I don't want
to call the police.
Honestly, all of this
is unnecessary.
I told you how sorry I am.
I-I explained
that we did everything
that we could.
Well, see,
I don't see it that way!
You were there
from the beginning.
You knew
what was happening!
How many more people are going
to die because of you?!
Mrs. Dubois,
this has to stop.
If you'd like to contact me,
I'm going to insist you do so
through my attorney.
Someone looks unhappy.
Mm, let's review.
As of today, our youngest
daughter has been given
an absolutely clean
bill of health;
our house has also
been given a clean
bill of health;
our real estate broker just
this evening has assured us
that we can almost certainly
get enough for our present home
to begin 30 years
of new debt
on the one in Willow Elm.
Have I skipped
anything?
Left any bad news out?
What if I'm wrong
about everything?
Wow, a moment
of self-doubt.
That's new.
That's different.
I kind of like it.
You're joking. I'm serious.
What if I make us
go through all of this moving,
making new friends,
shaking everything up
when I was already just fine,
and it's all for nothing?
Then we'll just
have to tough it out.
You know, bigger bathrooms,
nicer bedrooms,
modern kitchen.
And if at some point
I can free our daughters
from the torture
that is the community pool,
perhaps we'll find a way
forgive you.
Hmm.
SCANLON:
New house? That's exciting.
Yeah, I got to drop off
all the signed paperwork
at the sales office
in an hour.
I mean, we still have
to sell our old place.
We still have
to get our loan.
Or we could
still fall through.
No, I can see how busy you are.
I appreciate you doing this.
I'm happy to see
whoever you like,
just don't be surprised
if I come up empty.
Now, who's this again?
Gary's roommate.
He's finally
back in town.
I asked him
to come down
see if he could
shed some light.
Nice kid.
Pretty upset.
Apparently,
they were very close.
This is the woman from
the District Attorney's office
I told you about.
She's helping me
with the case.
Allison Dubois,
David Channing.
Hi.
Doctor...
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You just bear an
uncanny resemblance
to a doctor I know,
an oncologist.
Of course, he's
a bit older than you.
He could almost
be your father.
He's not my father.
My father's a postman.
Now, look, David
is a medical student.
Yeah, although I don't think
oncology's in my future.
I don't think I'd enjoy knowing
that everyone who came to see me
most likely
already had
a fatal disease, you know?
But you never know.
Yeah, you never know.
I really have to get
these across town.
Of course.
I just wanted
you guys to meet.
Uh, give me a second
to walk her out.
Nice meeting you.
Talk to me.
What'd you see?
It's nothing.
Nothing that applies
to this case.
What are you talking about?
You saw him,
you turned white as a ghost.
It's nothing.
It's personal.
A really weird coincidence.
I really got to go.
All right,
I appreciate it.
Sorry it was all
for naught.
Are you aware that Gary
had a history with narcotics?
Yeah, we were friends.
I mean, we lived together.
We went to med school together.
Of course, I knew.
I mean, it wasn't something
he bragged about.
Although, I think
he took a lot of pride
in the fact he was able
to put it behind him.
At least he said that he had.
I thought
that he had.
Gary mentioned
you guys met working
in a lab last summer.
Yeah. Lab tech work;
like, petri dish cultures,
things like that.
Do any work with lab rats?
Sure, we did everything
with lab rats.
You personally?
Yeah, that's what
they paid us to do.
You know, a big client comes in
with a... chemical,
something they want to put
in a food dye or something,
and they want to see
if it's safe,
so you-you inject the rats
with it
and then you wait...
and see if they die.
Of course, if they're lucky
enough to live,
we dissect them anyway;
make sure they didn't have
anything wrong with them
on the inside.
It was... it was a fun summer.
Do you remember what chemical
you were testing?
I remember
that it didn't kill the rats.
Now what's all this about
anyway?
We found a jar
with three dead rats in it
in the back of Gary's car.
Wow. That's weird.
That doesn't sound like Gary,
not that I know
what he's like.
I understand.
I just figured
they must have come from the lab
you guys worked at.
I don't know.
I kind of doubt that.
These are industrial clients,
big companies.
They need to be sure
their product's safe;
all the rats
tagged and numbered.
We have to document
everything we do
to each and every one of them.
I mean, it wasn't like you could
bring them home as pets or...
I just figured it out.
You're the guy that
Gary was always talking about.
The, uh, the cop
that was his sponsor.
He liked you.
He trusted you.
I think he would have
wanted you to know that.
Hi.
Mr. Dubois, nice
to see you again.
Well, my husband
and I talked about it.
We decided we'd like
to move forward.
So I want to bring
the application
and our thousand-
dollar deposit.
Fantastic.
Sit down.
We put our house
up on the market,
and my husband's
sitting down
with the mortgage
broker tonight.
Again, I want to emphasize that
for us, speed is of the essence.
We need to move
as quickly as possible.
All right, then.
It sounds serious.
Let me dig out
our construction progress list,
see which houses are closest
to completion,
take you on a little tour.
The Sheldons are closing
on a three-bedroom.
My husband and I just bought a
two-bedroom unit ourselves.
And do you have kids?
Because this is a terrific
school district here.
Mrs. Dubois are you all right?
Can I get you something?
Maybe a glass of water.
Yeah?
I don't know
if you're aware of it,
but you got about 55 "While you were out" slips
taped to your cubicle wall.
I think you ought
to call your husband.
Yeah, I will. I just needed
to be alone for a little bit.
So now wouldn't be a good time
to ask you a question?
Well, I probably just made
the biggest mistake of my life;
put my husband
and my kids through hell,
at the very least lost
a thousand-dollar deposit.
Go ahead. Shoot.
You ever heard
of chlorahydrofromaid?
Why? You want to borrow some?
Turns out Gary worked
as a lab tech last summer.
He and David Channing were involved in a
toxicity study of this chlorahydrofromaid.
Okay.
Apparently, it's some kind
of industrial byproduct.
Anyway, a small legion of rats
gave their lives
to demonstrate
that the stuff's harmless.
Here's the weird part.
The company that commissioned
the lab test
is some outfit called, uh...
"Bunford Properties."
Bunford Properties--
your developer.
Apparently, they found
trace amounts of this
chlorahydrofromaid
in the wells they dug
to supply water to the place.
Oh, my God.
Not to worry, 'cause like
I said, according to the tests
that Gary and his friend
David Channing conducted,
the stuff's completely harmless.
Of course, nobody asked
the three dead rats
I found in Gary's car.
They might feel differently.
Of course.
It was never our old house
that was going
to make Marie sick.
It's Willow Elm.
Willow Elm is the answer.
I was just asking
the wrong question.
Mr. Bunford?
Yes?
Mr. Bunford,
my name is Manuel Devalos.
I'm the District Attorney
for the city of Phoenix.
This is Detective Lee Scanlon
with Phoenix PD.
Do you mind if we ask you
a couple of questions?
About?
Chlorahydrofromaid.
Well, what about it?
It's old news.
Apparently some small quantities
had seeped into the aquifer--
the water supply.
We did some testing.
The quantities and the chemical
itself, for that matter,
pose no threat to anyone.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
Good Lord,
what is that?
Rats.
Yeah, I can see that.
Rats that, according
to the city medical examiner,
suffered from abnormally
low white blood cell counts.
Their platelets
and red blood cells
were destroyed.
They died of leukemia,
leukemia brought on by exposure
to massive doses of chlorahydrofromaid.
Says you.
Thanks for stopping by,
gentlemen.
If you have
any further questions,
feel free to call
my attorney.
Does the name Gary Albright
ring a bell?
What part of "I'm not answering
your questions"
did you not hear?
Mr. Albright was found dead
in his apartment.
We're investigating it
as a possible homicide.
ok.
He was one
of the technicians
that performed
the tests you ordered
That jar was found
among his personal effects.
Gentlemen...
We suspect that these rats died
as a part of the test
that your company ordered
on its water supply.
We think that when
Mr. Albright and his
lab partner David Channg
came to you and told you that
chlorahydrofromaid tested as a carcinogen,
you prevailed on them to go back
and run the tests again.
We're guessing you paid them
to get the results you wanted,
the results you needed
to get permission to build here.
Honestly, I've never met
this Gary.
I wouldn't know him
if I fell over him.
Yeah. Well, we think
Gary had a change of heart.
We think he decided
he couldn't live
with what he'd done.
He decided to come forward
with proof of the cover-up
he perpetrated.
Hey, folks, I'm just
finishing up a tour
with these gentlemen.
If you'll step
inside the model home,
I'll be with you
in a minute.
So what are you saying?
I killed this fellow?
Gentlemen, if you have a problem
with the veracity
of the lab's findings,
then you need
to investigate the lab.
I'm just a guy
who builds and sells houses.
And really,
that's what I need to do.
Thanks, man.
I'll see you next week.
Yeah, same time,
same place?
Yeah.
Hey, Channing,
what you doing?
We need to talk.
Sure, sure.
I'm, I'm happy to talk.
I don't know what
there really is to talk about.
Take it easy.
I'm not here as a cop.
Just think of me
as a concerned friend.
You okay?
Yeah, I am.
I'm fine.
'Cause, uh, when you came
to see me the other day,
I though you looked
kind of anxious.
Then, now you actually look
kind of sick,
you know?
You sick, Channing?
No.
Maybe you need
to get high.
What are you
talking about?
I don't think
it was the job
that brought you and Gary
together last summer.
I think it might have been
something else.
No? You feel good?
Great.
Let's go down
to headquarters
and talk for
a couple hours.
Whoa, Detective, wait.
What are you doing?!
What are you doing?
Assaulting a peace officer,
Channing?
I barely touched you!
You're jonesing harder
than I thought.
You, you said...
you were here as a friend.
I am...
a friend of Gary's.
Okay, okay.
You're right.
I have a problem.
I do,
but I need, I need help,
Detective, you know?
I need real help.
I want to get clean,
you know?
I want to kick it...
and I want to help you try...
try to figure out
whatever really happened
to Gary, I swear.
You just...
just unlock these cuffs.
Let me have just a little taste
to make me right,
and then we can...
you know, I can get right,
and then we can talk.
That's good, Channing.
You sound really sincere.
Let me just, uh...
No, I can't seem
to find that key.
No, I guess I'll have to call
over to headquarters
and get them to send over
another one.
Looks like we could be here
for a while.
You can't do that.
That... it's kidnapping.
How long can you
hold out, do you know?
I bet it's not as long as you think.
Look at you. You're a mess.
Well...
if I tell you
what you want to hear then...?
You'll find that I can be
a very understanding man.
Compassionate, even.
After all,
I've been there myself.
So why'd you kill him?
Hmm? 'Cause he was calling me?
'Cause he was starting
to realize
that taking the money
from Bunford
wasn't going to make up for
all the innocent people that
were going to get sick and die?
All the children...
Take your time.
I'm in no hurry.
Girls, breakfast!
All right,
listen to this.
"Convicted developer
Albert Bunford faces
a total of 245 years
of prison time."
Whoo!
True confessions?
I love this house,
but I was actually starting
to get a little excited
about moving.
Oh, really?
Yeah, something about a bathroom
with two sinks,
a community pool...
Maybe in our next life, huh?
"Our next life." I like that.
You get an extra piece
of French toast.
Yum!
Girls!
It looks like
a Frankenstein bear.
No, it doesn't.
I got some needle and thread
and stitched Mr. Snookie.
JOE:
Look at that
excellent job, Ariel.
He looks good
as new.
He does.
(grunts)
Everything's good as new.
welcome to www.1000fr.com