www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@ÐÜ±¦±¦ Sync:FRM@Uranus
Yeah, I-I'd rather not talk
about how I know
that a plane is going to crash
ten days before it happens.
I'm sorry,
I don't have a location.
I just know that they're
headed towards Las Vegas.
I was just hoping that
we could do something,
reach out to the people who
are going to be on this plane,
stop them
from taking this trip.
The man flying the plane
is named Ken.
I'm sorry, that's
all I have: Ken.
He's middle-aged.
Uh, he's a white man,
he's medium build.
Oh, and there's
a passenger.
Uh, a woman: Amy.
She's younger.
Mid-30s, I'm guessing.
Well, I did call the FAA.
They suggested I call you.
Yes, I realize what the Department
of Homeland Security does.
(mouthing)
Yes, I'm an American citizen.
Hang up.
Yes, that's my phone number.
Yes, that's my address.
Allison, put down the phone.
Hey, I'm not going to tell you
if that's my Social or not.
Department of
Homeland Security?Are you insane?
What would you have me do?
Your boss is going to be here
to pick you up in 20 minutes.
I got up half an hour early
to get the girls to school.
How about you take a break
from getting us put on
the national watch
list and get washed and dressed?
ALLISON:
And then you get to the part of the
conversation where they go,
"And how do you know this?"
And they either say it like they're talking
to Chicken Little or...
(groaning):
Osama bin Allison.
(chuckles)
The 28th?
Heading towards
Las Vegas? Okay.
What do you mean, "Okay"?
Well, I was thinking you could
sit with a sketch artist,
develop a likeness of the
people you saw in the plane.
We could distribute the
sketches around the country--
regional airports, aircraft
maintenance facilities--
say they were "people of
interest" in an investigation.
There's no guarantee anyone
will actually recognize them,
but at least
it's something.
Thank you.
(sighing):
I.D.'s out.
Prison gate's up ahead.
ALLISON:
So what is it we're doing here?
I thought you'd
never ask.
Supposedly, your friend Sonny
Troyer wants to confess to yet another murder.
Sonny Troy is
not my friend.
I've never even
met the man.
Nonetheless, you and I
know it was the information
you gave us that led to
his capture and conviction.
It just seemed prudent
to have you here.
Is there a problem?
I guess not.
You know, I was only able
to tell you what I did
because, for some reason,
Mr. Troyer and I began having the same dreams--
dreams about women--
alone, isolated,
in some kind of trouble.
Women he would then attack
and kill.
He threatened me,
he threatened my family.
It wasn't pleasant.
It's not something
that I'm anxious to repeat.
Allison, the man is
serving three life terms.
There's no reason to believe
he can do you any harm
from behind bars, but
if you're uncomfortable,
I can certainly
handle this myself.
(lock buzzes)
Sonny Troyer.
Mr. Troyer, perhaps you
remember me from your trial.
I'm Manuel Devalos,
the city District Attorney.
You asked for
this meeting.
(inhales)
(laughs quietly)
Sorry, forgive me.
"To sleep,
perchance to dream."
I wouldn't want
to miss anything.
I'm sure you've
had plenty of time to dream in the past
nine months or so.
Suspect you'll
have plenty of time in the months and
years to come.
(laughing):
I hope so.
I'm sorry;
I didn't catch your name.
Allison.
Sorry?
(exhales)
Allison.
Would that be Dubois?
We finally meet.
And how are your dreams,
Allison Dubois?
That's none of
your business.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
I don't get too many visitors,
much less ones with whom
I have so much in common.
Does he know
our little secret?
I still see them--
all those helpless women,
in over their heads,
hoping someone will find them
and rescue them.
That must be very...
frustrating for you.
I can dream.
(clears throat)
Will your attorney be joining us?
I have no legal representation.
After I was given my third
consecutive life sentence,
it all seemed
rather pointless.
Then let's get
on with it.
You have something
to confess and we don't have
a lot of time.
You sound nervous,
Mr. District Attorney.
I can hear it
in your voice.
Born in Arizona,
but when you're anxious,
a little bit of your parents'
native Jalisco kicks in.
Hard consonants, switching
your "I"s and "E"s.
I remember noticing that
during your cross-examination.
You're wasting my time.
Debra Waldman.
Ah...
You remember Debra Waldman.
Been missing... ah...
three years now, right?
Spent her last night on Earth at a border bar a lot
of Mesa Uni students visit for the cheap booze.
She was pretty drunk
when her friends ditched her.
By the time she
wandered into the desert
lost and confused,
filled with fear,
I was already having
dreams about her.
When she passed out,
I was already two-thirds
of the way there.
Okay.
Where's her body?
Raised in Oklahoma?
I've never heard
your voice in person before,
but there it is, diphthongization
of short vowels and all.
Mr. Troyer...
The state of Texas has filed
papers for my extradition.
Seems they found the remains
of a young woman
in a grain silo
outside Aberdeen.
Something about my DNA
being present in several of the pockets
between her teeth and gums.
Those forensic scientists,
those Crime Scene Investigators,
they all have
such lurid imaginations.
(slams chains on table)
Nonetheless,
the state of Texas seems
to actually enjoy executing
fellows like me.
I would prefer to stay here,
in comfortable Arizona,
serve my three life sentences,
and dream.
If you file papers
to block their extradition,
I will provide you
with precise directions
to the location of
Ms. Waldman's remains.
It was nice to finally
make your acquaintance.
Deputy Mayor Lynn
DiNovi, please.
Saure, I'll hold.
Something
bothering you?
It's weird.
When Sonny Troyer was active,
when he was killing,
I dreamt the same
dreams he had.
I never dreamt
of Debbie Waldman.
Of course, that was before
I worked in your office,
before I took
everything that I felt,everything I dreamt
so seriously.
Are you suggesting
he's lying?
To be honest with you,
the bell that's going off
loudest in my head
has to do with the plane crash
ten days from...
Lynn. Manuel.
Hold onto your hat.
Sonny Troyer, the serial killer,
just confessed to
the killing of Debra Waldman,
the co-ed who's been
missing since 2004.
No, he won't tell us
where the body is
until we get Texas to waive his
extradition on another matter,
which is why I'm calling.
I need you to tell the mayor
to call the governor.
I need the governor
to get on the phone with our friends in Texas
(chuckles):
Hey.
If it isn't our favorite
candidate for city council.
To what do I
owe this honor?
It's done.
Excuse me?
Late last night, the
Governor called the Mayor.
Texas is gonna waive their
rights to Sonny Troyer,
at least for
the moment.
At least long enough
for you to see
if there really is a body
where he says there is.
So let me ask you...
Whew!
how sure are you that what this guy's
telling you is the truth?
Are you pretty confident
about this body?
What's he gain
by lying?
If he tells us where to go
and there's no body there,
he's still in prison for
the rest of his life,
and Texas is still free
to take him and fry him.
The mayor might want to leak
something to the press
about an ongoing investigation
into the disappearance of a young college co-ed,
an investigation
spearheaded by His Honor.
You. Me.
Well, that wouldn't
be a bad thing
for someone running for,
say, city council, would it?
Not a bad thing for
a district attorney either.
(knocking on door)
DEVALOS:
Yeah?
Hey.
I got a fistful of messages
here from you.
Are you stalking me?
I've been trying
to get in to see you all day.
It's the 27th.
Okay.
Tomorrow's the day that small
plane is supposed to go down.
I was wondering if you got
any calls from anyone,
off our sketches--
any persons of interest.
Not a one.
Well, maybe that's good news.
Maybe it's gonna happen
on the 28th of another month.
Maybe we can still stop it.
Maybe.
I, uh...
Sorry.
JOE:
It's been over a week, Allison.
You done
everything you can.
Well, that's the thing.
I really haven't been
able to do anything, really.
Well, maybe you're
not supposed to.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Well, I don't know.
I don't subscribe to the
Psychic Friends Network.
But if the modus operandi
you have to buy into
is that there's actually
a plan for all this,
then perhaps this once
you're not part of it.
Perhaps this
particular message,
this particular dream, ended
up in your inbox by mistake.
What are you saying, these
people are supposed to die?
Maybe that's the
plan for them.
Maybe they're
horrible people.
No.
I don't believe that.
(siren blaring)
(fire roaring)
MAN (over P.A.):
All prisoners, step away from the plane!
All prisoners,
step away from the plane!
All prisoners in the yard
will immediately
return to the block.
All prisoners in the yard
will immediately...
Oh, my God. He knows about the plane.
(chuckles):
Hey, early bird.
It's not even 7:00.
Don't you carry
your cell phone?
It's in my office.
I called your house.
Yeah, I've been here
since quarter to 6:00
working in the law library,
putting together the thing for the judge tomorrow.
I know why
Sonny Troyer confessed to killing
Debbie Waldman.
He dreamt about the
same plane crash I did.
Not this again, Allison.
I've already done everything
I possibly can.
It is going to happen.
That plane is gonna crash
into the Arizona State Prison.
This morning, today, 8:19.
Sonny Troyer is gonna
make it his business to be out on the prison
yard when it does.
Think about it:
He dreamt the dream,
he recognized
the location,
he realized that if
he was sent to Texas,
he would miss his
chance at escape,
so he came up with the
whole confession thing.
Has he told you the
location of the body yet?
Today. I'm scheduled to go out
to the prison this afternoon.
He's not even gonna be
there this afternoon.
Please.
We have to call
the prison.
We have to find
the warden.
What do I tell him?
Anything. Anything
that'll keep Sonny Troyer off of that
prison yard till after 8:19.
(line ringing over speakerphone)
ECKLER:
This is Warden Eckler.
Warden Eckler-- I'm
sorry to disturb you at such an early
hour, sir.
This is District Attorney
Manuel Devalos over in Phoenix.
I have you on speakerphone.
Morning, Mr. District Attorney.
Just getting into my office.
How can I...?
Sir, some investigators working
under me have just come into
some highly credible information
about a possible
large-scale escape attempt
at your prison.
Are you serious?
I most certainly am.
To the best of our knowledge,
the plan is set to happen just after
8:00 this morning.
I'm not at liberty to
discuss the particulars,
but it is crucial that you clear
the prison yard immediately
and initiate
an immediate lockdown.
And specifically,
most specifically,
that you isolate
prisoner number 16309,
Sonny Troyer.
A pretty tall order, counselor.
It's already quarter past 7:00
on my watch.
But I think we can
make this happen.
(laughs)
Much appreciated, sir.
Yeah, well, you owe me
a steak dinner next time I'm over your way.
(jet engines roaring)
What the hell?
Hang on a second.
(engines roaring louder)
(explosion,
then alarm sounding)
(dial tone)
Come on...
(speed dialing beeps)
(musical tone)
FEMALE VOICE:
You have reached a number that has been disconnected...
No, wait-- it's only 7:20.
Please check the number
and try your call again.
(musical tone)
TV ANCHORMAN:
And the hunt continues tonight for Sonny Troyer,
the notorious serial killer who escaped from
Arizona State Prison today
after a freakish
private jet crash that killed two.
A statewide manhunt
is currently underway,
with federal marshals
coordinating their efforts
with local authorities,
setting up roadblocks
and monitoring
all airports and...
(TV turns off)
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
That was the FAA.
The pilot was
a Ken Androsky,
and his passenger was
his girlfriend Amy Chandler.
They took off from
a private airstrip
in El Paso;
they didn't file a flight plan.
El Paso, Texas--an hour ahead of us.
There's no way
you could have known.
He knew.
Sonny Troyer knew.
He heard it in their accents.
(knocking)
Hey, I just went through Sonny
Troyer's cell with the dogs.
No luck at all.
Apparently, he doused everything
with rubbing alcohol--
his clothes, the linens,
even his mattress.
Even switched clothes with
one of the other inmates
before he went out to
the yard this morning.
This isn't what you'd
call a spontaneous trip.
You want to see
something else?
DEVALOS:
Scientific Foundations
of ESP,
Psychic Phenomena
in the Real World,
The Uses and Control
of Paranormal Activity.
Looks like he's getting ready
for a test of some kind.
Getting ready
for something.
Why couldn't he just hang out
in the weight room
with all the other lifers?
ALLISON:
You know what?
This marshal on TV, he was
talking about prison breaks
and how they
usually have everyone rounded up
in six hours.
Now where is he hiding?
He's one man, on foot,
wearing an orange jumpsuit.
How hard can that be to find?
(yawns):
I don't know.
But if he
caught a break,
he could be halfway
to Mexico by now.
No.
He's somewhere asleep.
Excuse me?
Think about it.
He's just spent
nine frustrating months
waiting for an opportunity
to do what he does best:
to prey on women in peril.
And to what do we
owe this optimism?
You should have seen the library of books
that they pulled out of his cell.
This is not a man
waiting to retire.
So they close
off the border,
make it impossible
for him to leave.
No-- he's gonna do
what he's built to do,and he's gonna do it
right here in Phoenix...
soon as he can
get some sleep;
close his eyes.
Closing eyes.
Getting rest.
Oh, my goodness.
I think this fellow
may be onto something.
(sighs)
Hey...
That's not funny.
I'm still talking.
(groans)
Hey.
Fine, play dead.
You won't be
playing for long.
(sighs)
(bell dings)
(elevator clanks)
Oh, geez.
Lord...
Please.
Hello...?!
Hello!
Can anyone hear me?!
Help!
Help...!
(gasps)
(groaning):
Allison.
There's a woman--
she's trapped in an elevator,
She's calling for help.
What?
(sighs)
It's those dreams.
The same one that Sonny Troyer's
having, I'm having them again.I have to call Scanlon.
No. Honey...
Even if he's having the same
dreams, which you don't know,
he's a wanted man.
His face is on
every newscast;
every cop in town
is looking for him.
I mean, do you really
think that he's gonna
stick his neck out to kill
this woman in an elevator?
Do you want to take
that chance?
I have to get her out
of there.
But out of where?
Do you know, do you know
where the elevator is
or the building's
address?
(cat meowing)
WOMAN:
Quincy. Quincy.
Get down here, Quincy.
Quincy!
(grunting)
(screaming)
Hello!
Is anyone there?!
(gasping)
There's a girl somewhere.
Her-- she was trying
to get her cat out of the tree.
She just fell.
Okay.
All right. Were there...
Were there any, uh,
like, landmarks
or buildings?
It was the woods.
It was dark.
There were trees.
So it's like a state
park or something?
I don't know.
I just know her damn cat's name is Quincy.
That's all I know.
Hmm. Okay.
Well, wait-- now,
that's good, right?
Because that means that
that's all that he
knows, too, right?
(moans)
(ring tone playing)
Hello?
TROYER:
God... I'm guessing you having as much trouble
sleeping as I am.
One dream after the other.
I guess when it rains
it pours, huh?
How did you get this number?
First that poor woman
in the elevator. Then that girl
with the kitty cat.
Did you find her
as attractive as I did?
She was kind of fetching,
wasn't she?
Now there's a word you don't
hear too much anymore--
It's him.
"Fetching."
Call Scanlon.
Anyway, none of that is why I really called.
I really called to talk
about our situation.
What are you talking about?
"Our situation"?
Well, I mean... we're kind of at a standoff here,
don't you think?
I have a dream.
You have a dream.
It's gonna make it
really hard for me to do the things that I have to do.
Not to mention cops everywhere,
my mug shot on the TV.
I had to pay a homeless guy $25 bucks to buy me
this cell phone.
I just don't think
we can go on this way.
Hey, did you have the dream
about that blonde mom
boo-hooing to her husband
because she just couldn't
figure out her dreams?
Did you have that one, too,
or was that just me?
I don't know where
the elevator lady is...or the cat girl.
But that blonde mom?
I've been to her house.
I don't know what else
to suggest.
He does know where you live.
I mean, uh...
I could move you and your family
to a hotel, but...
that presents all sorts
of other problems.
I really do think
the best solution is just to hunker down
right here.
We'll keep a visible police
presence outside your home.
Wait a second.
I got work.
The girls have school.
Work? How're you
gonna go to work?
I can barely keep
my eyes open.
It's 5:40 in the morning,
we've been up since 2:00.
How are you going
to go to work?
I don't really have
a choice, Allison.
I don't think work is a problem.
With all due respect,
you're not really our killer's type.
But the girls,
Allison--
I would just feel better
if they were all in one place.
(elevator bell dings)
Good morning.
I beg to differ.
I got a call at
4:00 this morning
from a reporter on
the Arizona Observer.
This reporter claims you
actually phoned officials
at Arizona State Prison to warn
them about that jet crash 90 seconds before it happened.
Before the plane crashed?
That, uh... doesn't
make any sense.
I don't know-- a plane
falls from the sky,
I'm sure there's an enormous
amount of panic, confusion...
Why was your office circulating sketches
of "persons of interest"
to airports and aircraft
maintenance facilities a week
before the crash--
sketches that look
exactly like the victims?
I'm sorry.
I can't help but think
that someone is confusing
two separate investigations.
If we coincidentally
sent out sketches
that happened to look like
the two victims of the crash...
Manuel... based on
our conversation,
my boss, your boss,
the mayor...
called our governor.
Our governor called Texas.
Now reporters are calling me.
I will need answers.
Do you have any idea
the blame storm that's
going to rain down on all of us
if
there's reason to believe we knew, but
didn't do everything we could
to prevent the escape
of a serial killer?
Once we've captured
Mr. Troyer, and we will,once he's brought to justice,
I'm sure all these questions will be answered
to everyone's satisfaction.
I hope you're right.
(phone ringing)
Oh... Ariel?Honey, can you,
uh, get the phone and mute the TV?
(TV mutes)
Thanks. Hello?
SCANLON:
Get any sleep yet?
You're joking, right?
Do you think any of the cops outside would like
to do a little babysitting?
Yeah, I don't think
our boy Troyer got all that much rest either.
I'm here waiting
for the coroner to come help clean up the mess
he made last night.
What?!
Was it a nurse in an elevator?
Or was it a girl in the woods?
A woman in a Dumpster.
Seems like she got in a fight
with her boyfriend
while they were driving
to Flagstaff.
He left her to calm down
at a rest stop here on the Intestate.
He says that was around
4:00 in the morning.
Ring a bell?
No, how could it?
I've been awake
since Troyer called.
And he knew I would be.
Excuse me?
Damn, he's smart.
He wasn't really threatening me.
He was frightening me.
He wanted to be sure
that I would stay awake,
to be sure that I couldn't
dream his dreams.
WOMAN:
Hey roomie, it's me.
Waiting for some stuff
to print out. What are you doing?
I know. It's all over the news.
I wish they'd just catch
the son of a bitch already.
You're damn right, it's scary.
Look, just pour yourself one of your Bloody Marys
and get to bed.
You'll forget
he's even out there.
No vodka?!
Tell you what:
I'll call the liquor store
and have them deliver,
but by the time I get home,
you better have one
mixed for me, too.
(laughing)
Night.
(auto-dial beeping)
Hello, Christopher's Liquors?
Yeah, order for delivery.
Claire Williams,
1701 Pike's Way.
(door closing)
(clattering in distance)
Detective Lee Scanlon please.
There's Sleeping Beauty.
Hey, Mom,
I ordered pizza.
What time is it?
Um, it's a little after 7:00.
Have you looked out the window?
There's, like, a brigade
of cops out there.
Our neighbor's yelling
at them 'cause there's
nowhere to park.
Wait... Lee?
Hey, I had another dream.
There's a woman.
Her name is Claire Williams.
She's stuck on the roof of the Phoenix East
buding downtown.
She locked herself out
and she feels trapped and vulnerable.
Phoenix East. Got it.
(helicopter whirring)
OFFICER (P.A.):
Claire Williams!
This is the Phoenix
Metro Police.
Move away from the door.
(crashing)
(screams)
Okay, look-- I know we're not
supposed to smoke on the roof.
I know we're not supposed
to smoke on the roof.
Don't shoot me.
Don't shoot me
SCANLON:
Her name's Claire Williams.
She's a statistical
analyst in data
reconfiguration--
whatever the hell that is.
CLAIRE:
Detective Scanlon?
Yes, Ms. Williams?
Hi.
I just wanted
to thank you.
And... well, would
it be possible for me to get a ride home?
My roommate's not
answering the phone.
I can't figure it.
I know she's home.
I just talked to
her an hour ago.
Yeah, I'll have
an officer run you home.
What's your address?
1701 Pike's Way.
How did you know that?
Your roommate...
She was alone and she was
afraid, wasn't she?
OFFICER:
Clear!
OFFICER 2:
Detective!
We're bored.
Yeah.
We want to go out.
We're sick of being stuck
in the house.
Yeah.
ALLISON:
e, we have a problem.
I'm looking at
a potential mutiny here.
It's Saturday and the girls
are going stir-crazy.
Joe wants to take them up to his sister in Flagstaff
for the weekend.
I think it's a good idea.
Flagstaff, huh?
I'll stay here
on Dream Patrol.
The house is surrounded
by police;
I feel completely safe.
The girls are just
at the end of their rope.
Okay. I'll have one of my guys
follow them up there.
I'll give the Flagstaff PD
a shout,make sure
they're on alert as well.
I'll call you like a
hured, 150 times a day.
You call me
as much as you like.
Okay.
You got it?
(dog barking in distance)
Bridge, honey?
Daddy wants to go!
BRIDGETTE:
I'm looking
for something!
She's looking for her
baseball bat and batting helmet
in case she has to beat up
the serial killer guy.
Honey, you don't
need that!
BRIDGETTE:
Yes, I do!
Hurry up and
catch this guy, Mom,
so we can
come back home.
I'll try.
(smooching)
Bridgette!
(indistinct police radio
communication in distance)
(yawning)
TV REPORTER:
...hospital for
sick children.
Tracy Hooper was given
the liver
of a nine-year-old
accident victim,
in a four-hour operation.
Hooper is in critical
but stable condition,
normal after
such an operation.
Her condition will be
monitored for 72 hours
to see if there's any sign
of organ rejection.
Shoot me and
I'll never forgive you.
(sighs)
Are you crazy?
Are you trying
to get yourself killed?
How did you get
in here?
You left me a key.
Remember?
The night you broke it off?
Left me sitting in
that restaurant...
I don't want to talk about this.
Not tonight. Not now.
I said things,
you said things, but this is not the time.
There's a maniac out there,
killing women,
making an ass out of me.
You wanna spend the night,
that's fine.
But I have no interest
in talking.
Put your ego back in your pants.
I have no interest in staying.
I'm here to get some
questions answered.
I just said...
Not about us, about why a woman
who works part-time
for the District Attorney's
Office is being given 24-hour police protection.
I'm talking about
Allison Dubois.
Okay.
That's your answer?
"Okay?"
Are you aware of that the
message Sonny Troyer wrote
in blood last night:
"Wrong Roommate Allison"?
Yeah.
I was there.
What's the connection between
this woman and Sonny Troyer?
I am not at liberty
to discuss this with you.
Let me paint a
picture for you.
There's a journalist that
calls me four times a day.
She thinks the District
Attorney's Office
somehow knew that Sonny Troyer was going
to escape from that penitentiary ahead of time.
I'm starting to
believe her.
And you can bet
I'm not the only
one she's calling.
This thing is getting ready to
blow up in everybody's face.
The DA, me, you.
Lynn, listen to me.
Leave... this... be.
We're going
to catch this guy.
It'll make all
the questions go away. It always does.
No. Lee...
Tell me what's going on.
Let me help you.
I would tell you...
...but the truth is
you'd never believe it.
Hell, there are days
I don't even believe it.
(engine revving)
(tires squealing)
(sighs)
(keypad beeping)
Joe, it's me.
Hi.
Is something wrong?
It's the middle of the night.
I'm watching out the window;
it looks like all the
police cars are leaving.
There's only one left...
and now he's gone.
Hang up. Call Scanlon. Maybe it's good news.
Maybe they caught the guy.
(line ringing)
(gasping):
Lee.
Yeah. Who am I talking to?
Lee! It's me. It's Allison.
They took all the police away.
What is going on?
I'm here all by myself.
Damn it--
she promised me she wouldn't do anything until the morning.
What are you talking about?
That Deputy Mayor.
She was asking a lot
of questions.
I wouldn't tell her
what she wanted to know.
She was threatening
to pull the plug on everything
but I thought for sure she was
gonna give me till the morning.
I'll be right there.I'm coming right over.
yeah Hey.
There's, uh, been a mix up.
They took the police cars away,
but it's okay 'cause
Scanlon's coming over.
He's going to be here
in 20 minutes.
All right, I'm waking the kids,
we're coming home.
No, don't do that.
Honestly. You're hours away. He'll be here in a few minutes.
I don't care.
No, please don't.
Please, I don't...I'm upset and frightened enough.
That'll just make me feel worse.
Joe? Joe?
Lee!
My power went down.
My phones are out.
Damn it.
Allison, calm down.
Calm down.
There's a pretty strong wind
off the desert.
It may have just...
I'm scared.
I know.
I'm still maybe ten,
12 minutes away.
Just hang tight.
Double-check your windows
and doors and by the time you're done,
I'll be there.
I had a dream.
(screams)
And you were in it.
(pounding on door) Electric company!
Heard you might be having a problem!
Allison, be a dear
and open the door.
We don't want to
disturb the neighbors.
Lee! He's here!
Allison, I'm still
ten minutes away.
Ten minutes!
You were ten minutes away
ten minutes ago!
I'm doing 90.
(screams)
He's trying to smash his way in!
Lee?
Are you there?
(pounding on glass)
Lee?
(gunfire)
(sighs)
You okay?
Oh...
(distant siren wailing)
SCANLON:
I'm sorry.
We're sorry.
That whole thing hinged
on you not knowing.
You had to be alone; feel
vulnerable, terrified.
I get it.
DINOVI:
The police never
really left.
You were really never
in any danger.
So, I bet you're full
of questions.
Nothing that can't wait.
I'm going to go home.
Let you two talk.
Go ahead,
go say good-bye to her.
Hey...
Thank you.
I don't think I would have
gotten to this on my own.
You're welcome.
So how about my key?
You want it back?
Nah. It's okay.
I'll change the lock.
No, you won't.
If you ever pull anything
like that again...
Are you kidding?
This is my new technique
for solving murder sprees.
Scare the wits out
of Allison Dubois
and then, uh, bring
in the firing squad.
Can't argue
with success.
How dead is he?
Real dead.
Very dead.
You should sleep
just fine.
Just because he's dead?
No, it doesn't work
that way.
welcome to www.1000fr.com