???????
a series of questions we answer
through the choices we make.
Sometimes they work against us.
Most of the times, it isn't the
choice itself that's stressful,
but rather the consequence
of the choice,
a result we couldn't foresee...
or didn't quite imagine.
But what if
when we made our choices...
...having realized
we made the wrong ones,
there was some way to go back,
some way to invoke
a kind of big do-over.
You know what I mean?
Wouldn't that be great?
Wouldn't that just be the best?
You okay?
Everything all right?
Mm-hmm.
I'm fine; I just had a dream.
What are you doing?
You know what
I'm doing.
Well, I don't feel like
doing that right now.
That's okay, I'll
do all the work.
(chuckling):
That...
that is not the
look of love.
What's your problem?
What are you
talking about?
I don't have a
problem, I just...
I just figured
that you're up
and I'm up...
I know.
It's been a while.
Well, I'm not going
to forget how to do it.
It's just I'm tired,
honey, I'm cranky.
Yeah...
Tomorrow,
I promise tomorrow.
Yeah, you say that, but
it's a vicious cycle.
Let me explain
something to you.
Sex isn't just sex.
Sex is good for you,
'cause sex releases
endorphins.
And endorphins
make you happy.
Mmm.
Yes. I know that, I do.
And I fully plan on
being happy tomorrow,
whether I feel like it
or not.
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:FRM@FadeOut
Sync:FRM@Navel
Girls, breakfast is ready!
Where is your sister?
Ariel says she's not going
to school today.
Why not?
I don't know; ask her.
Ariel? I need to speak with you!
I'm here, I'm
here, I'm here...
but I'm not going
to school today.
Oh, really?
You can't make me go.
Oh, yeah, I can;
I'm your mother.
They gave me permission
at the hospital when I had you.
Mom, I have to stay home,
or Amy Amson
is going to beat me up.
Wait a second-- who's Amy Amson?
She's this girl
in my biology class.
Somebody passed her
this note by mistake,
and I guess the boys wrote it.
Um, it's a list of who's hot
and who's not,
and according to them, I'm hot,
and according to them,
she's not.
So Hannah says she says that
she's going to mess my face up
today before Biology,
so I'm not hot anymore.
Somebody thinks you're hot?
I thought you had to be smart
to get into eighth grade.
And you actually think
this is going to happen?
If you stay home today,
what do you do tomorrow?
(chuckling):
Tomorrow's Saturday.
No, you know what
I'm talking about.
You know what this is?
This is a vicious cycle,
that's what it is.
And you know what
we have to do?
You have to go to school.
You have to show this girl
that you are not
going to be intimidated,
and I can almost guarantee you,
nothing is going to happen.
Did I hear someone mention
a vicious cycle?
There's a lot of that
going around lately.
Daddy, please,
I have to stay home.
This is really a matter
of life and death.
(sighs)
Sounds like it's going
to be a rough morning.
Bet you wish you
had some endorphins
right about now.
I'm sorry, Ariel, staying home
is not the answer.
I've got an important
arraignment at work today,
and you can't stay here
by yourself.
BRIDGETTE:
What's an arraignment?
Okay, fine, but
you are responsible
for whatever
happens to me.
If I die...
You're not
going to die.
Nothing's going to happen.
What's an arraignment?
We'll see.
Will somebody please tell me
what an arraignment is?!
I believe our middle child
has a question for you.
An arraignment.
An arraignment is what happens
when someone is being accused
of a crime.
Before there's a trial
or anything,
they go down to court...
(phone rings)
and the court tells them
what they're being accused of,
and they tell the court
if they believe they're innocent
or guilty.
JOE:
Hello?
But why would anybody
say they're guilty?
Who's calling?
Well, that's a very
good question.
They want to speak
to a Mrs. Dubois.
They won't take "no"
for an answer...
Hello?
No.
I'm not interested in having
my carpets and drapes cleaned.
No.
I don't want a free
in-home estimate.
No, you don't have to call back
in three months
for a follow-up.
Thank you.
Oops.
Oh, great.
This is turning out to be
a wonderful day.
Don't blame me.
I offered, you passed.
Sorry to bother you.
I was going over
these crime scene photos
from the Krieger case.
I think I may
have found something.
Why are you showing me this?
Well, just... I think Krieger
may have had some help.
I don't think he killed
these people by himself.
Well, that's all well
and good, Allison,
but we're not even sure
we're going to trial
on the Krieger case yet.
It's only being arraigned
this afternoon...
I know, I just thought...
The truth is,
I have a hunch this one
won't even make it to court.
The defense lawyer
has already pushed
the arraignment
date four times,
which makes me think they're
having second thoughts.
I think they're going to
come in this afternoon,
simply plead guilty
and make a deal.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Mrs. Dubois.
This is Nurse Dunbar down
at Central Middle School?
I've got Ariel here,
and she's telling me
she's feeling pretty ill.
What was I going to do, Joe?
She obviously didn't want
to be there.
She was obviously scared
out of her mind.
So I told the nurse I'd be there
in, like, 45 minutes.
I don't know.
It's like 12:30 now.
I just figured
I'd try to rush her home,
and get back...
BRIDGETTE:
Daddy, I think
I see her eyes moving.
Darling? Hey.
Hey.
Are you awake?
Do you see us?
Hey, you got a lot of
drugs in you, baby.
Your-your face is
all stitched up,
so they don't
want you to speak.
You just blink once if
you know we're here, okay?
Mommy, this is all my fault.
If I hadn't gone
to the nurse's office,
this would have never happened.
Sweetie, sweetie,
sweetie.
(sobbing)
Ariel, honey.
No, no, no,
sweetie, sweetie.
We talked about this,
we talked about this.
You know that's
not true, okay?
not true.
Your mom is
going to be fine.
She's going
to be okay.
Sweetie, I
need you to go
to the vending machines
in the cafeteria. Okay?
You need to take your
sister down there.
I need to talk to Mommy
for a second, okay?
Go on.
Go with your sister.
Mommy, I'm so sorry.
Hey.
Everyone's calling
to make sure you're okay--
everyone from work
and your brother,
the district attorney.
He wanted me to tell you
that the arraignment went fine,
by the way.
I don't know what you remember.
I don't know what you know.
(sighing):
Um...
This asshole went
right through the light,
He just went right through it.
Like 40 miles an hour.
Maybe he was high or something.
I don't know.
Nobody's telling me anything.
I do know--
here's the good news.
Here's the cosmic joke
in all this.
There was a body
in the trunk of his car.
A body.
And a blue duffle bag
filled with ammo
and an automatic weapon,
and blueprints for some
building downtown, so...
I mean,
we're all reasonably sure
that he wasn't rushing
to church, you know?
That's my wife,
always out there
stopping the bad guys,
even when she...
(chuckling):
even when doesn't know
that she's doing it.
Here's the thing.
You got hurt really bad.
Nothing that can't be fixed
with time and with therapy.
Okay, this is ridiculous,
'cause they told me
not to say anything.
Not until you
were fully conscious
and they had weaned you
off the drugs.
I guess they're right...
I guess they're right.
Just know that...
that, you know,
we're going to...
we're going to get you
everything you need.
Whatever it is,
whatever it costs.
I love you, baby.
I love you.
Nurse.
Nurse!
I have to go to the bathroom.
Is that the bathroom?
I have to go to the bathroom,
but I can't feel my legs.
Let me get
some help.
No, no, no,
we don't need any help.
You and I can do it.
My legs are asleep.
(screaming):
Oh, my God!
Uh...
Where are my legs?!
You okay?
Oh, man.
I had the most
horrible nightmare.
I dreamt I totaled our car.
I lost both my legs.
It was so vivid.
Cool.
The kids don't get up
for another ten minutes.
Oh, man.
I so believed
what I was dreaming.
I'm so relieved.
I feel like I...
I got the ultimate do-over,
like the universe gave me
a get-out-of-jail-free card.
Um, well, did you
use that card yet?
Because I was
thinking that,
if you're still in jail, I could
really go for a conjugal visit.
Come on.
Don't look at
me that way.
Let me explain
something to you.
Sex isn't just sex.
Sex is good for you.
Sex releases
endorphins.
And endorphins
make you happy.
And right now, you look
like you could use
a little happiness.
I sure know I could.
Girls, breakfast!
Mommy, can't I
have oatmeal?
Not this morning.
We're behind schedule,
this is faster.
Tread gently with
Mommy, Bridge.
The woman's in dire need
of some endorphins.
Hmm?
ALLISON:
Where's Ariel?
We got to get move on.
I got to get to work.
Got an arraignment today.
What's an arraignment?
Ariel!
Where's your sister?
Why is she not here?
Ariel says she doesn't
want to go to school today.
What's an arraignment?
Why do you want to know
what an arraignment is?
You're only eight.
I don't know.
ARIEL:
I'm here, I'm here,
I'm here.
But I'm not
going to school.
Is this about Amy Amson?
You're on the hot list,
she's not on the hot list?
That's so unfair
you can do that.
That is so cool
that you can do that.
What's everybody talking about?
What's she doing?
You want me to get that?
Hello?
May I ask who's calling?
ARIEL:
Mom, this isn't funny.
It's really important
that I stay home.
They want to talk
to a Mrs. Allison Dubois,
and they won't say
what it's about.
Hello?
MAN:
Mrs. Dubois, this is
All Right Carpet
Cleaning Service.
I'm calling to offer you
a special half-off...
ARIEL:
Bridget!
Oops.
This is the same exact day.
Is that a yes?
JOE:
Ariel, here, take this.
Because for $19.95 an hour,
we can send a team
of professionals
to your house
to clean your carpets...
Here.
I dreamt this.
I dreamt this whole morning.
Everything-- the juice,
the phone call,
Ariel wanting to stay
home from school.
Uh, okay. So?
Everything.
It's as if I lived
this day already.
And I'm gonna get in a horrible
car accident in a little while.
You're what?
No, wait, wait.
I had that dream for a reason.
I can stop this from happening.
Hello.
Good morning, yeah.
Is Detective Lee Scanlon in yet?
Can I leave him a message?
My name's Allison Dubois.
Can you tell him
to meet me at the corner
of Mesa and Pueblo at 12:30?
Tell him
to look out for me.
I'll be taking a cab.
Mom, can I please
stay home from school?
No. No, you cannot.
And don't you dare
go to the nurse's office
and make me come and get you.
You will be grounded
the rest of eighth grade.
Endorphins.
Just so you know,
I was supposed to
have lunch with a certain
someone who works for the Mayor.
You may have to vouch for me
at a later date.
Consider yourself vouched.
Now, what is it
we're looking for?
In about one minute, a
man's gonna go through
this traffic signal.
There'll be a dead man
in the trunk of his car,
along with about 100 rounds
of ammo, automatic weapon,
not to mention blueprints
to a building downtown.
If I'd driven
myself here today,
I believe that he would've been
fated to run through the light
and hit me with his car.
But since I got
here early by cab,
my hope is that he will
go through the light
without incident, you will
arrest him and prevent him
from whatever awful thing he
was bound and determined to do.
You with me?
And you know this
because...?
Because of the wonderful
things she does.
That traffic light
right there?
That light there.
Black sedan.
Like that one.
Oh, boy, I get to use my siren.
Wait here.
Well, this is
embarrassing.
I ran a red light
back there, didn't I?
You certainly did.
Your Honor.
I don't understand.
I don't know
what to tell you.
It's pretty
cut and dried.
I just pulled over a
Federal Court Judge.
A Federal Court Judge.
The Honorable
James T. Whitman.
Nice fellow,
crappy golfer.
What about his trunk?
I didn't see you
look in his trunk.
That's 'cause I didn't
look in his trunk, Allison.
He's a Federal
Court Judge.
What part of Federal Court
Judge don't you understand?
I'm not about to ask that
man to open his trunk
when I have no
probable cause.
The last time
I checked,
your dreams do not
constitute probable cause.
You want some lunch?
I'll buy you lunch.
Hello?
This is Nurse Dunbar
down at Central Middle School.
I've got Ariel here,
and, please
don't be alarmed,
but another child
here at the school
has apparently given
Ariel a black eye.
A black eye?
We've got some ice on it,
and I'm sure
in an hour or so
she'll be fine
to return to class.
Oh, my God,
this is horrible.
Is she okay?
Can I talk to her?
Um, actually, um, she's laying
down at the moment, Mrs. Dubois.
MAN (over radio):
All units in the vicinity...
I want to come pick her up.
Tell her I'll be right there.
Thank you.
...reporting a possible
hostage situation
at the Florenzo Ristorante.
I'm afraid you're not
going anywhere soon.
I was in the
neighborhood,
I heard you guys
were up to no good.
JACKSON:
Well, somebody's
up to no good.
About 35 minutes ago,
911 got a call from inside
the restaurant about a robbery.
When the first
responding officer arrived,
the perpetrator
was still inside.
He's holed up in there
with 57 hostages.
How many?
I've got sharpshooters on
all the surrounding rooftops.
And the hostage negotiator
just got off the phone.
What's he want?
What's he asking for?
That's the fun part.
He wants nothing.
He's made no real demands.
Just wants us to wait out here
till 5:00 p.m.
Then he'll release the hostages
and give back the money.
That makes no sense.
Tell me about it.
Excuse me, Captain Jackson,
could you follow me?
Lee.
Take a look at that.
Is that who I think it is?
Man, this guy's really
pushing his luck.
A handicapped spot.
I'm not imagining
it, right?
That's that
judge's car.
Well, I guess today
is not his lucky day.
I don't know
what to do.
I dreamt about
that car.
Now that that car's here, I'd
kind of like to stay if I could.
Let me go call
my husband.
MAN (over radio):
Central Command,
this is Watchtower. Over.
I'm on the northeast corner
of the roof of
the adjacent building.
From my vantage point, sir,
it appears someone is attempting
to make their way out of the
rear entrance of the restaurant.
It's a glass door,
and I keep seeing them
approach it and then hesitate.
To be honest, sir,
I don't know if I'm looking
at a hostage
or the hostage taker.
Can you describe him?
Male, approximately
six-feet-tall,
shirt and tie,
looks like he's got a mask on,
carrying some kind of
blue gym bag.
Judge Whitman.
In my dream,
there was a blue gym bag
in the trunk of the car,
along with the body,
along with the ammo,
along with
an automatic weapon.
Sir, I stopped
a suspicious-looking person
matching that description
earlier today.
He comes through the door
and gives you any reason
to believe he's anything
other than a hostage,
shoot to immobilize.
MAN (over radio):
Here he comes.
He's out.
He's got a weapon.
I'm taking my shot.
He's down.
Repeat. Man is down.
He's just outside the rear
of the building.
Sir.
I need you to
release your weapon.
It's taped to him
or something.
We shot the wrong guy.
His-his gun jammed.
It jammed.
Judge Whitman...
He taped this
gun to his hand, he...
gave him that bag,
he pushed him out the back door.
So he could leave out the front
with the rest of the hostages.
Do you need help
deciding what to wear?
It's clean.
It's absolutely clean.
What day is today?
Mmm. Friday.
Thank God.
Wait...
I feel a hackneyed phrase
coming on.
It passed.
Okay, but why would a
federal judge do that?
Rob a restaurant?
Hold hostages?
I don't know.
He's not doing it for the money.
He sends the money out
with one of the hostages.
Assuming any of this is real.
Assuming any of this
is actually going
to happen, I mean...
it was just a dream.
What?
No, just... I love
that you said that.
I mean, normally I'd
be the one to say that.
Yeah.
Well, it just occurred to me
when I woke up,
when I realized that my jacket
wasn't covered with blood.
None of what I had dreamt
had happened.
I felt relief.
I still feel relief.
Excellent.
Relief is good.
You know,
it's hard to explain it.
Every time I dream the dream,
there are certain cues.
There are certain things
that happen at the start.
But this morning...
the fact that
the kids aren't up,
the fact that we're up early.
This is different.
Gee, we are up kind of early.
Hey, here's a crazy idea.
How about we go back
to bed and not sleep.
Hmm?
Was that a "no"?
Yeah.
No.
But it's not why you think...
I just...
I don't want
to have this conversation.
Cool. Kill the
conversation.
I'll race you
to the bedroom.
No.
Change the conversation.
I don't want to have it.
Wait a second...
which "it" don't
you want to have?
Either "it."
I don't want to have
the conversation.
I don't want to have sex.
Allison,
let me explain
something to you.
Sex isn't just sex.
Sex is good for you.
Sex releases
endorphins.
(moans)
And endorphins, they
make you happy.
And right now,
you look like you could
use a little happiness.
I sure know
I could.
Oh, my God.
Guess what?
Ariel doesn't want
to go to school today.
How... ?
You want to know what
an arraignment is?
Huh?
Well, trust me, you will.
Ariel, let's go.
Let's get the show
on the road.
Mom...
I know all about it.
You're hot. She's not.
But you're not staying home from
school because of some bully.
The girl's got you completely
intimidated and that's crazy.
You know what you have to do?
Intimidate her.
That's right, you have
to go to school
with a little less of
that "I'm pretty,
I'm smart, I'm
well-behaved" thing
and get yourself
a little bit of
badass!
Mom!
Allison?
You know what
I'm saying.
Don't pretend you don't know
what I'm saying. Badass,
badass, badass.
You got to get yourself
a little attitude,
Ariel Dubois,
and you got to give it
to that girl.
Joe, back me up here.
Your father and I
do not want you to spend
your whole life afraid
some girl's going
to hit you.
that you are going to hit her.
JOE:
Hey.
Are you okay?
Do you follow what I'm saying?
Attitude.
I'm trying to
teach this girl
something here.
(telephone rings)
Here, look, follow.
Watch this, okay.
No!
No, no, no.
No, you listen to me
you scum sucking,
bottom-feeding,
hide-behind-a-telephone-headset
piece of garbage.
you ever call my house
again during breakfast,
I will personally come to
your carpet cleaning company,
I will find you and
I will hurt you.
And when I'm
finished with you,
nothing and no one
will ever be able to
to get your stain out.
Okay, you get the gist?
All right.
Everybody ready for work?
I have an arraignment
to get ready for.
What's an arraign...?
Too late.
ALLISON:
I know it's
kind of hard to follow.
No, I... I think
I follow you.
You want us to arrest
a federal judge
for a crime he
hasn't committed. Yet.
Look, maybe there's some other
way I haven't thought of yet.
I'm just worried if we
don't do something come 1:00,
you're going to get a 911 call
from inside
the Florenzo Ristorante.
Once that happens,
it's already too late.
Allison...
look at it from my side.
You have been wrong
from time to time.
Besides what is it
we're supposed
to arrest him for
if he hasn't done
anything yet?
I don't know.
All I know is,
this is the third time
I have lived
this same day.
Twice now, I have
tried to stop this man.
Both times I failed, people
have been hurt or killed.
You almost had him yesterday.
Excuse me?
You found out he was a judge,
you wouldn't check his trunk.
If you had, you would have
found a dead body in it.
What?
I have absolutely
no recollection
of any of this.
Because it
hasn't happened yet.
Wait a second,
I have an idea,
it might even be legal.
Why don't you and Allison
walk down to the
judge's chambers right now.
Explain to him that a car,
matching the description
of his honor's,
appears to have been used
in the commission of a crime
you're investigating.
Ask the judge
if he wouldn't kindly
allow you to confirm
that the car is still
parked where he left it.
And if he would consent
to letting you take
a peek in his trunk.
If the car is still there,
there's nothing in the trunk,
no harm, no foul.
I don't know.
He's a judge.
It's almost lunch.
Don't worry.
I'll call her.
She'll understand. Thanks.
Morning.
My name is Lee Scanlon.
I telephoned about
five minutes ago.
Spoke with an aide,
asked if there was any way
I can get a look
at his honor's car
as part of a criminal
investigation we're conducting.
I was told
to speak to you.
That you would know
where it was parked.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to need a minute.
I'm going to have
to check with his honor.
Nobody told me about this.
Who's that?
SECRETARY:
Well, that's Judge Whitman.
Are you sure?
I've worked for the man
for 26 years.
I think I know
what he looks like.
Allison?
Doesn't
make sense.
What's going on?
The person I saw yesterday
was a different Judge Whitman.
Trust me.
There are
no other Judge Whitmans.
Don't feel bad, this
is a good thing.
At least we know our federal
court system isn't run
by a bunch of gun-
wielding maniacs.
Besides, now I can
still make my lunch.
No, you can't.
I cancelled for you,
before we came.
Okay.
You hungry?
Sure.
Hello?
Mrs. Dubois,
this is Nurse Dunbar
down at Central
Middle School.
I've got Ariel here and...
ALLISON:
Yes?
Mrs. Dubois?
This is Principal Phillips.
I'm here with your daughter,
Ariel, and I'm
afraid we've have
ourselves a very
serious situation here.
Oh my goodness,
is she alright?
Oh, she's fine,
but apparently ????????
Now we consider that a very
serious matter, Mrs. Dubois.
I mean this is something
that's going to go
on her permanent record.
Oh, my God.
I mean, frankly, Mrs.
Dubois, I've never seen
this kind of behavior,
this kind of attitude
from Ariel before.
Wherever it came from,
we need to nip it in the bud.
Yes.
Thank you.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
No, it's Ariel.
It's a school thing.
She's such a good kid.
So I guess you've
been here before.
What's good?
What time do you have?
Uh, 1:16.
I don't get it.
Yesterday you said that
the police got a phone call
at 1:00 p.m. about a robbery.
I never talked
to you yesterday, Allison.
That yesterday never happened.
That yesterday was a dream.
WAITER:
Hi, my name is David.
I'll be your, uh, your server.
Would you guys like
to hear today's specials?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, we, uh,
MAN:
Can you check in
with the maitre d'
and see if there's been a call
from Judge Whitman?
He should of been here
15 minutes ago.
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
I'm not a big fan
of the goat cheese.
You know, you go right ahead.
No, the man at that table
just mentioned Judge Whitman.
I wasn't wrong, there
is a connection.
Should I give you guys a minute?
Yeah.
Look around, Allison.
This restaurant
is not being robbed.
MASKED MAN:
Everyone stay still.
This is a robbery.
If you move, you die.
Everyone out of the bar,
everyone out of
the kitchen now,
move it, move it.
You hear that?
That was fast.
(distant sirens wailing)
It's almost as if
someone phoned it in
before it even happened.
Quiet!
Now I want everyone
to put on a mask and get down
on the ground... now.
Move, move, move.
Down on the ground now.
Everyone out of the kitchen.
Out here.
What you got
in there, fella?
My asthma medication.
Well, you look fine to me.
Both hands in the air.
And they better be empty.
All right, stand up.
Slowly.
Open the jacket.
Well...
that's some serious asthma
you got, huh?
Here's what
we're going to do.
You're going to take
off the holster
and put it on the table,
and then you are going to
back away from the table.
Do you understand me?
Anytime.
Lee, don't.
His gun doesn't work.
Remove that holster now
or I will pull this trigger.
Lee, don't.
The gun's going to jam,
trust me.
You were right, his gun did jam.
Who is he?
Michael Williams.
Bulletproof vest.
Joe? Joe, honey, wake up,
I've got to ask you something.
What's the matter?
What's going on?
What day is today?
Hmm?
You hate me,
don't you?
I mean, deep
down inside,
there's gotta be
like an anger thing.
Otherwise, why would a
person wake a person?
Is it Friday?
Yes, it's Friday.
(sighs):
Oh, thank God.
Wait.
BOTH:
I feel a hackneyed phrase
coming on.
Wait. It passed.
Why would he want a
hostage situation?
No, no, I'm not buying it.
He releases all the
hostages at 5:00 p.m.
Well, maybe he's just
trying to get people
out of work
for the afternoon.
Maybe I should bring
my engineering team
to lunch there.
Ah, yeah, well,
good luck.
That place was packed.
Scanlon and I could
hardly get a table.
I don't think they
could accommodate...
I almost forgot.
At the restaurant,
there was this table,
seemed like 20 people.
And one of them asked e waiter
about Judge Whitman.
But I thought you said that
the gunman wasn't Judge Whitman.
It was some guy named Williams.
Right. But he told Scanlon
he was Judge Whitman
when we pulled him over.
An he was driving
Judge Whitman's car.
So what are you saying?
Remember you told me
there was a dead body
in the trunk of that car?
No. When was that?
Today. In the hospital.
A couple of hours from now.
Never mind. I remember.
I think this guy Williams might
have killed Judge Whitman.
I think he might have
killed Judge Whitman
and stuffed Whitman in
the trunk of his own car.
Okay. Why?
That I don't know.
Florenzo Ristorante.
This is David.
Hi. Um, I'm supposed to attend
a lunch at your restaurant today
and for the life of me
I can't remember
what time the reservation
is for.
Well, what name
is the reservation under?
I don't know.
Uh, it's a big party.
Maybe 20 people.
Judge Whitman's party?
Yes.
Yeah, we got you down here
for 12:45.
Uh, great.
It wouldn't happen to say there
who else might be attending,
would it?
No, I'm sorry, ma'am.
All I know is we were told
to be seen and not heard.
Something about every judge in
the county being at that table
???????
Really?
Uh, thank you so much
for your help.
Every judge in the county is
going to be at that restaurant.
I have to go see Devalos.
Can you take the
kids to school?
Yeah, of course I can,
um, but wait a second.
I need to talk to you
about something.
Endorphins?
As a matter of fact.
Heard you can get them
from running, which is
what I got to do.
Girls, Daddy is going to be
driving you this morning.
Mom...
Ariel, I want you to stay
home from school today.
What?
Bridgette,
an arraignment is when someone
pleads innocent or guilty.
(phone ringing)
BRIDGETTE:
Are you talking to me?
Marie, say hi to the nice man.
Bye, girls,
see you tonight.
MAN (on phone):
Hello? This is All Right
carpet cleaning service. Hello?
Can I ask you a question?
Don't ask me
how I know this,
but a man is going to hold every
judge in the county hostage
from 1:00 to 5:00 p.m. today.
Okay.
What changes?
What does that effect?
How does that
make the world different?
Well, I don't know.
I suppose if the court
doesn't have a judge
to preside over its cases
on a given day,
then the court proceedings
don't happen on that day.
What could be gained by that?
Nothing.
Everything would just be
rescheduled until the next day.
Unless...
What?
Unless somehow the proceedings
are time sensitive.
What do you mean?
Like my arraignment this
afternoon, for instance.
What about that arraignment
makes it time sensitive?
Normally it's no big deal.
But the law mandates that
a defendant's arraignment
be held within ten days of
the person's indictment.
But as it happens, in
this particular case,
the defense attorney
has worked very hard
to get that arraignment
date pushed back
until the final day of the ten
day window, which is today.
What if that arraignment
doesn't happen today?
The defendant's due process
is violated-- he's released.
That's why
this is all happening.
That's why "what"
is all happening?
This hostage thing
you mentioned?
Where is this coming from?
I had a dream-- well, I had
three dreams actually.
Allison, you're losing me.
What makes you think that
your dream hostage taker
has a connection with
the Krieger arraignment?
I don't know.
His name is Michael Williams.
That's really
about all I can tell you.
Michael Williams?
Krieger has a wife.
Her maiden name
is Williams.
She has a brother named Michael.
The very first dream,
I came to talk to you about
a second shooter in that case.
And what did I do?
You shooed me
out of the room.
Not this time.
Get me Detective
Scanlon please.
Everyone stay still!
This is a robbery!
You move, you die!
I want everyone out of the bar!
Everyone out of the...!
SCANLON:
Boys...
He's wearing a bulletproof
vest-- aim for his head.
Michael Williams...
you're under arrest.
Drop the gun, put your
hands over your head.
Okay.
Hey. Are you okay?
Hmm? Everything
all right?
I don't know,
I think so.
You wouldn't happen to know
what day it is, would you?
It's Saturday, darling.
Why do you ask?
I don't know.
It was a pretty
amazing week.
I packed a lot
into last week.
Packed a real lot
into yesterday.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm...
Guess I'm kinda... sad,
kinda let down.
Kinda depressed.
After all
that excitement, I mean.
You don't say.
Any thoughts?
Any suggestions?
I don't know.
You could do
something physical.
That always helps.
Creates endorphins,
elevates the mood.
Hm, endorphins, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Physical, huh?
Mm, yeah, you know,
running. Running's good.
Anything else?
Mm, let me think.
What are you doing?
I'm thinking.
Well, think about this--
you have about ten seconds
to peel off those shorts
and get over here
and spread a little happiness
before the kids
start getting up.
Wow. Someone's
in a crabby mood.
No, let me explain
something to you.
Sex isn't just sex.
Sex is good for you.
Sex releases endorphins.
Endorphins make you happy.
No, I know.
Well then,
come over here.
All right. Fine.
But I warned you.
You warned me.
You made your choice.
(laughs):
l made my choice.
I just hope you
can live with it,
'cause there's
no going back.
Vicious cycle.
Got it.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com