?i have to get out
?i'm turning to a reason????
?hey lover
?he suppose to followe me out
In a minute.
I was thinking of actually
getting some showering
done in here first.
ANNOUNCER:
In February, 1996,
the police in Portland, Oregon
were no closer to finding
the so-called Suitcase Killer
than they had been
11 months earlier
when the first of his
six victims was found--
dismembered and stuffed
inside a suitcase.
They sought the assistance
of FBI criminal profiler
Edward Cooper.
Cooper's insights
led the police
to a failed dental student
named Richard Gomez.
A search of Gomez's apartment
yielded the bloody handsaw
that he used to dismember
his victims...
(man whistling tune)
During Gomez's trial...
You better hurry up.
a bureaucratic error
compromised the prosecution.
I'm getting pretty into this
show, you might lose me.
The bloody handsaw
was misplaced.
Civic employees scoured
the evidence storage room
but they were never able
to locate it.
Richard Gomez was acquitted.
Richard Gomez murdered
those young women.
There's no doubt about that.
Seeing him walk free...
I'm not sure I can describe what
that feels like.
To this day,
no one knows the present
whereabouts of Richard Gomez.
The serial killer
who scoffed at the law.
(man whistling
"Strangers in the Night" )
Why'd you shut it off?
I was watching that.
(screaming)
(Joe whistling
"Strangers in the Night")
(shower running)
Hey, songbird, you think you
could keep the whistling down?
I'm trying to have
a nightmare in here.
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:FRM@ID
Sync:WWWKWOK
Mommy, the syrup's cold.
That's okay,
the waffles are hot.
Eat them both at the same time,
you got warm.
Guys, when you're done, bring
all your dishes to the sink.
ARIEL:
Hey, what's Marie doing?
There's nothing
on that channel.
Give me the remote.
No, Marie likes it.
And why can't she get
to pick sometimes?
She also like smearing
jelly all over her face,
but that doesn't mean
we should let her.
So give me
the remote.
JOE: You know what,
give me the remote.
It's morning, it's breakfast,
it's way too early
to be fighting over television.
It's way too early
for television period.
Right, Mommy?
Um, why aren't you guys
watching TV?
Daddy said no.
Hey, let Marie pick
for a change.
Turn it up.
I had a dream about
this guy last night.
Oh, yeah?
What's he got that I don't?
As an amazing reputation
as a criminal profiler
for one thing.
I read this book in college
for a criminology course.
Hmm...
And the dream?
It was about an old
case of his from years ago--
Richard  Gomez.
And the girl, the victim,
her picture's
no where in here.
She doesn't look anything like
any of the people in here.
Sorry. (chuckles)
That's okay.
I think I just decided
to become a vegetarian.
(phone rings)
Allison Dubois.
I'm sorry, you've reached
the wrong extension.
Sure, I can transfer you.
Actually, I can
see from here
the District Attorney's
not in his office.
I believe he's in a conference.
DEVALOS:
Yes.
Sorry to interrupt... sir.
Allison, what?
Sorry to interrupt, sir.
I have a message for you.
He said it was important.
He's only going to be there
another half hour.
Uh-huh.
Um, oh, forgive me, I'm sorry.
Allison Dubois,
this is Special...
ALLISON:
Edward Cooper of the FBI.
I'm very familiar
with your work, sir.
It's an honor
to meet you.
And what is it you do
for the District Attorney
that makes you so familiar
with my work?
Uh, Allison was studying
law and criminology
when she came to work for us,
and while she doesn't
actually have a law degree,
she's proven to be a very
effective resource when
it comes to jury selection.
Pretty good with crime
scene analysis as well.
I see.
Jury selection, huh?
Yeah.
Well, you must be a good judge
of human nature.
Keen sense of intuition?
You might like to join us.
Actually, I need
to return this call
and go over a few things
with Allison myself.
Maybe  we can reconvene
back here in say ten minutes?
Edward Cooper!
Oh, my God!
Yes.
That's so strange-- I had
a dream about him last night.
As you probably figured
out by now,
Agent Cooper and his staff
are going to be using
the conference room
as their temporary
base of operations.
They're in town on a case.
But to be honest
with you,
I was sort of hoping
that you wouldn't
run into each other.
Why?
I don't know. The man
makes me very nervous.
Anyway, I know I don't
really need to tell you this,
but we need to be especially
discrete about what it is
you really do here,
and how you do it.
Hey, as long as I can
sit in the room.
As you all know, three days ago
a jogger found the body
of Diane Colquitt
on a path in Boyce Park
here in Phoenix.
Diane was a
16-year-old prostitute.
Appears that someone
picked her up,
drove her to the park,
and  then strangled her
with own underwear.
Every detail of Diane's killing
matches a series
of murders the Bureau and I
are investigating
up in Columbus, Ohio.
Four young girls dead,
all of them prostitutes,
all of them strangled
with their own undergarments.
All of them found
hands bound behind their back
with a sailor's hitch knot.
Every girl dumped facedown
on a jogging path.
When was the last killing
in Ohio?
Little over ten weeks ago.
So you're thinking
that your killer migrated
from the Midwest to here?
Killers aren't immune
to the cold.
They've been known to travel
south for the winter.
This is a very preliminary
psychological profile
of the killer.
It appears that he is threatened
by women.
Based on the forensic
evidence recovered
from the four Ohio victims,
we believe that he prefers
to have sex with his victims
only after they're dead.
Has he left any bodily fluids
behind?
Any DNA to work from?
No.
He's methodical about cleaning
up after himself.
Extraordinarily thorough,
which makes me suspect
he's had a lot of practice
doing what he does.
I have an appointment with the
coroner to personally examine
Diane Colquitt's remains.
My team and I will be there
at 3:00.
Anyone from this office
that would care to join us,
please do so.
JOE:
I'm sorry to stick you
with babysitting duty, honey.
Mommy called me
at the last minute
to pick you guys up.
I got to get back to work.
We'll be okay, Daddy.
Bridgette and I have homework
and Marie can just sit
with us and
watch television.
Police, fire, doctor--
all the numbers you need
are on the fridge.
Look, it's your favorite show.
You have my cell phone,
you have Mommy's cell phone.
One of us will be home by 5:30
at the absolute latest.
Daddy, I've got it
under control.
Okay, we've got to find
something better
for her to watch than this.
Back, back, back, back, back.
Huh, what's wrong, sweetie?
She likes the other one.
There's nothing on
the other channel.
Back, back, back,
back, back.
Told you.
WOMAN:
As you indicated on the phone,
the victim had been fairly
well cleaned up by her attacker,
but we did pull this
off her underwear.
It's dog hair.
Looks to me like something
from the terrier family.
COOPER:
Her fingernails
have been cut.
Someone wanted to be sure
that we didn't find
any DNA
under them.
This bruise on
her shoulder
is probably from
the killer's knee.
Perhaps forensics
could analyze it...
(man whistling
"Strangers in the Night")
...what the killer was wearing
on the lower half of his body--
denims, chinos...
Excuse me.
I was just wondering...
when you said earlier
we were dealing with an
experienced perpetrator--
someone who was good
at what he did,
who clearly had a lot of...
practice,
I wonder if anyone had
considered the possibility
that the man who did this,
the man we're looking for,
might be Richard Gomez.
(clearing throat)
Richard Gomez...
No, we had not considered
Richard Gomez.
Frankly, to the best
of my knowledge,
Richard Gomez has been inactive
for more than ten years.
Any particular reason
you bring his name up?
Just, uh, a hunch.
Instinct.
A hunch.
You know what I call a hunch
made without a scientific basis?
You know what I call
an instinct
uninformed by either experience
or intellect?
I call it a distraction.
I call it a waste of time.
Forensics also might be able
to speculate as to
the perpetrator's weight
based on the depth
of the bruise.
Correct me if I'm wrong...
Happily.
Gomez is still at large,
is he not?
How can you be so sure
this is not his work?
What would prevent him
from killing and raping
these women in Ohio?
Seems to me if he's
still out there...
Mrs. Dubois...
you indicated that you were
familiar with my work.
If that's truly the case,
then you know
that Richard Gomez
was a dominance killer.
He used his charm
and good looks
to convince women to go back
to his home
or a motel room--
somewhere private,
where he would violate them,
torture them
and keep them alive while he
sawed them into little pieces.
He was a passionate
sadist.
He took pleasure in their pain.
This killer--
the Lincoln Park killer,
he strikes from behind.
It's more of a blitzkrieg
style of attack.
It's the mark of a timid
personality, a coward.
These two men might as well
speak different languages.
Now, any other dormant
serial killers
that you're curious about?
Any other hunches,
any other random instincts?
?perhaps we can continue to the important working hand?
,
It was so mortifying.
(water running)
He was so cutting.
He was so convinced
of his own infallibility,
he wouldn't even
consider the possibility.
Mmm... yeah. I think you need
to cut the guy a little slack.
He's been catching killers
for what, 30 years?
Now, you spent a
couple hours with the guy,
and all of a sudden
you're bringing up
his most famous setback.
He's bound to get
a little testy.
What does he have
to get testy about?
Agent Cooper led the police
right to Richard Gomez.
He did his job.
It's not his fault
somebody lost the evidence.
You're right, but maybe Cooper
doesn't see it that way.
Catching these people is pretty
much a crusade for him, right?
So when one of
them slips away,
I doubt he spends much
time consoling himself
with the idea that he is
not personally to blame.
Well, that doesn't give him the
right to make a fool out of me.
Are you using this
arm for anything?
GOMEZ:
Why'd you shut it off?
I was watching that.
(screaming)
(strained screaming)
(pained yells)
(Gomez grunts, Allison gasps)
(knocking)
Y up.
Sorry to bother you.
I need your help.
What does this mean?
Dioner Mapache--
it's a name.
It's a man's name.
Uh... first name Dioner,
last name Mapache.
Why do you ask?
Actually, I think
it's a business,
like a bar or restaurant,
the kind of business that
advertises on hotel ashtrays.
Wherever this business is,
I think it's located
nearby the hotel
where... Richard Gomez
killed Diane Colquitt.
( sighs)
Close my office door, Allison.
(door closes)
What are you doing?
Just what I always do.
But I believe
Agent Cooper
made it perfectly clear
that he's not interested
in any leads involving
Richard Gomez.
That he feels very strongly
that Richard Gomez
had nothing to do
with this woman's death.
Well, he's wrong.
Allison...
(sighs)
All right.
All right. Let me...
see if I can try and get
Detective Scanlon
to discretely
run this down, find out
if there is such a place
and where it might be,
but do me a favor-- stay away
from the conference room.
Keep out of
Cooper's way.
Let's let him think that you've
moved on to something else.
Let's let him think
that you're doing other things.
Huh.
Okay.
The government
wants the chassis
to be made
with light polymer.
They also want it
to hold six cameras,
but if you put six cameras
on it, the light polymer
won't stand up
to atmospheric pressure
which means we've got...
Nothing.
(head thumping)
Are we taking a break?
I think we're
taking a break.
Deep breaths, Aaron.
Pretend we're not days
away from our deadline.
Think happy thoughts.
Can you think happy
thoughts for me?
What are you
thinking about?
A.J. just turned three.
There you go.
My youngest just
turned three, too.
And now you say
something back.
Pretty soon we're
having small talk.
That's how a break works.
A.J. likes to
eat Play-Doh.
Congratulations.
You must be very proud.
Marie sits in front
of the TV and watches static.
I think she'd do it
for hours at a time
if we'd let her.
What?
Nothing.
It's...
It's none of my business.
I'm sure
it's nothing.
You can't just say that.
What's nothing?
You say your daughter
just stares
at a blank channel for hours?
Well, like I said,
it's probably nothing,
and I certainly don't mean
to alarm you, but...
my brother has
an autistic son.
That sounds like the kind
of thing he used to do.
It doesn't necessarily
mean anything.
It's... It's
probably nothing.
Yeah.
(elevator bell dings)
Bad hunch, huh?
His name is Warren Bell.
He was in your
local registry
of sex offenders.
One of my people
remembered his face.
Back in Columbus, we questioned
him about the murders.
We just... couldn't find
any evidence to tie
him to the crime.
And now he's
here in Phoenix?
Well, he's a
sex offender.
He's obligated to register
whenever he moves
into a new community.
I asked them to bring
him in for questioning.
Sure you wouldn't
like to stick around?
You might find
it fascinating.
Me? You think so?
I don't know.
I think I probably lack the
experience and the intellect
to really appreciate whatever
it is you're gonna do or say.
Besides, I wouldn't want
to be a distraction.
I wouldn't want
to waste your time.
Want to know who
Dioner Mapache is?
You found it already?
It's kind of an
interesting story.
Turns out he was a general
in the Mexican army,
killed by his own men
the night before a battle.
Given his less-than-
inspiring history,
I guess it isn't a surprise
there's only one
restaurant anywhere
that's named after him.
It's in Mexico,
half a block away from
the El Coyote motel.
Would this be the
scene of the crime?
Yeah.
This is the place
I saw in my dream.
I called the motel,
asked them if they'd had
any suspicious activity
there lately, if anyone
matching Richard Gomez's
description had checked in.
Turns out there was someone
matching Gomez's description.
You're kidding.
I knew it.
We gotta tell Cooper.
I can't wait to see the look
on that egomaniac's face.
Nine years ago.
1997.
He checked in
under a false name,
he wasn't carrying a wallet.
They had no way
to establish his identity.
What are you talking about,
no way to establish his...?
I'm trying to tell you
that there was a murder
at the El Coyote motel in 1997,
only Richard Gomez wasn't
the killer, he was the victim.
Looks like robbers tied Gomez
to a chair while they
ransacked the place.
They took what they wanted,
then put two bullets in him.
Cops thought it might
have been drug-related.
I don't know what
to tell you, Allison.
I mean, unless he's unusually
spry for a rotting corpse,
I think it's fairly safe to say
that Richard Gomez
?it is not the leading part killer
Joe?
Where are the girls?
Homework.
Okay.
And what are you doing?
I'm watching our daughter
watch her favorite channel.
Yeah, I know
what you're thinking.
What channel?
That's what
I thought, too,
that she just likes to
watch nothing, static,
but I was wrong.
She just likes to watch
this particular channel.
Channel 282.
You want to know what happens
when I try to change the channel
to another channel
that just has static on it?
She starts to cry.
Want me to show you?
No, I don't need you to prove
you can make our daughter cry.
Why are you doing this?
I'm trying to learn.
I'm trying to understand.
Watch this.
Hey, sweetie, what are
you watching on the TV?
Funny man.
Funny man?
What is the funny man doing?
Talk to me.
Talking to her.
All right, babe, come on.
It's time to brush
your teeth.
I'll meet you in there
in a minute, cupcake.
Go on.
All right, once again,
what are you doing?
What am I doing?
Are you okay with this?
This doesn't bother you?
You're not in
the least bit curious
what the funny man might
be saying to her?
What he might be showing her?
She's three.
Exactly.
What does that mean?
It means it's not normal.
She has an
imagination.
Maybe.
Or maybe it's something else.
I'd like to have her tested.
Tested for what?
I don't know.
Autism.
She does not
have autism.
How do you know?
You don't know.
I know. I know my baby.
I know my daughter.
Oh, yeah? Well, do you know
what she's seeing on that TV?
No. And I don't
think it matters.
Well, I do.
I mean, you see things
that aren't there sometimes,
and, most of the time,
they're not pretty to look at.
They're not
the kind of things
that you'd want
a three-year-old to see.
Okay, I'm just trying
to understand this.
Are you hoping she doesn't
have autism or that she does?
Okay. I'm done
having this conversation.
Oh, that's
a great answer.
I'll be in the shower.
You know, if it
bothers you so much,
maybe you should
just read to her
instead of sitting her
in front of the TV.
(door closes)
COOPER:
August 22, 1996.
Excuse me?
That's the day that
Richard Gomez was acquitted.
I mark the anniversary
in my calendar every year.
My wife has learned
to avoid me on that date.
She says that I'm
a world-class brooder.
But now,
because of you,
August 22 is freed up for
more productive pursuits.
Thank you,
Mrs. Dubois.
A lot of people will
sleep easier tonight
because they know that
Richard Gomez is dead.
I accused you of
wasting my time,
of being a distraction.
I stand corrected.
You have
terrific instincts.
I wish I had
been wise enough
to understand
what they were
trying to tell me.
Thank you.
Although, to be honest,
I really wish
they would steer me
towards
the Lincoln Park Killer.
Well, might
not be too late
for you to pitch in.
We couldn't locate
Warren Bell yesterday.
He finally showed up at
his apartment this morning.
They're bringing
him in now.
I'm headed over
to interview him.
Appreciate it
if you'd sit in
and give me the benefit
of your expertise.
I already told your men
back at my apartment.
I was home watching TV
the night that girl died.
Can anyone
confirm that?
No. I was alone
the whole time.
Nobody called?
Nobody came by?
COOPER:
You watch a lot of TV, Warren.
I remember, when we met
back in Columbus,
you said you were watching TV
on the nights the women
there were killed, too.
I live by myself.
TV helps fill up the quiet.
You up and
leave Columbus,
the murders there stop,
you land in Phoenix,
lo and behold,
girls start dying.
I'm sure I'm not
the only person
to move from Ohio to Arizona
in the past couple months.
I got a job here.
I registered my whereabouts.
I'm allowed to move.
You work as
an apartment manager.
Am I remembering that right?
Are you a dog owner,
Warren?
No, I'm not.
Are you sure?
You seem
a little uncertain.
Can't smoke in here, Warren.
It's okay, sweetie.
It's okay.
(dog whimpering)
(sizzling, dog yipes)
Excuse me.
You all right?
Thanks. I will be.
I'm sorry I left the room.
I found it hard
to be so close to that man.
You have a hunch about him,
do you?
He keeps a dog
chained up somewhere.
It looks like a garage.
He doesn't feed it.
It's barely alive.
He tortures it
with a burning cigarette.
I've worked a couple
of missing children cases.
Met people like you before.
You see things, don't you?
That must be quite a burden.
A long time ago,
at the start of my career,
I made a choice.
I dedicated myself
to getting inside
the minds of killers.
To... going to worlds
where other people wouldn't,
or couldn't.
It's rarely been pleasant.
And it's changed me.
But it was still my choice.
You, Mrs. Dubois...
you go into
the heads of murderers
whether you want to or not.
I admire you.
But I sure don't envy you.
That one.
Wise choice, my dear.
See, she picked the one
with monsters and mayhem.
She takes after
her mother.
That's my girl.
(telephone rings)
Oh.
And here we go.
Hello?
Allison,
it's Manuel Devalos.
I'm sorry to bother you at home,
but I thought you'd like to know
that the police have executed
a search warrant
on Warren Bell's apartment.
Did they find anything
that linked him to the murders?
Not inside the apartment.
But in a garage
that he had access to,
we did find a grey
wire-haired terrier.
My God, was he still alive?
Barely. We took a sample
of its hair.
Preliminary DNA tests indicate
that it's a match
for the hair we found
on Diane Colquitt's body.
We've placed Warren Bell
under arrest.
That's great news, sir.
Agent Cooper wanted me
to call you and to tell you,
and to send his thanks.
Allison? What does he know?
Oh, I don't think
he "knows" anything.
There's no denying he certainly
has strong instincts.
Mmm. Well, I guess I'll see you
in the morning.
See you in the morning.
(humming)
You look happy.
(man singing in Spanish)
What now?
A leg or a breast?
(door opens)
Hello?
You.
How did-how did you find me?
Wasn't easy.
(gasps)
(sighs)
No wonder Cooper
was absolutely certain
that Richard Gomez wasn't
the Lincoln Park Killer.
I can't believe
I'm saying this...
it's not hard
to understand.
Imagine that you're him.
You catch this guy,
you do everything you need to
to be sure that he gets
the death penalty.
And then... they set him free.
He likes to kill, you know
he's going to do it again.
You track him down.
You rectify the situation.
So if you understand it,
what are we doing
here in our kitchen
at 3:00 in the morning
talking about it?
I just don't understand what
I'm supposed to do about it.
Am I supposed to speak out?
Ruin the life, the career,
of a good man
just because he couldn't live
with the idea
of Richard Gomez getting away
with murder?
Six murders?
Even if I wanted to tell
the world what Cooper had done,
it all happened nine years ago.
I doubt I could prove anything.
You know what?
This is easy.
Don't do anything.
I'm completely
serious, Al.
I mean besides, it's not
like you're absolutely certain
that Cooper did it.
He shot him once in the head.
He shot him once in the stomach.
I saw it, Joe.
I know.
But you also saw Richard Gomez
kill Diane Colquitt
in that very
same room,
and we both know
that didn't happen.
My point is, your wires have
been a little crossed lately.
And unless you're absolutely
certain that it's true,
you can't a accuse a man
of murder.
And even if you
were certain...
I don't sense that you want
to accuse this particular man
of this particular murder,
and I don't blame you.
(inaudible shouting)
(door slams)
(heavy sigh)
Thanks.
I'm negotiating a deal
with Warren Bell's attorney.
Agent Cooper doesn't like it.
What kind of deal?
We're offering to take
the death penalty off the table
in exchange for a full
confession to all the murders.
I've got a few pieces
of dog hair--
it's not much to stand on
when you're asking a jury
to sentence a man to death.
Given the paucity
of corroborating evidence,
I felt the full confession
was the best way to end this--
take Bell off the street
for the rest of his life
and bring closure
to the victims' families.
I've spoken with the authorities
in Ohio-- they agree with me.
Obviously, Agent Cooper
is advocating strongly
for the pursuit
of the death penalty.
I don't sense that he's
big on compromise.
Noticed that, did you?
Okay, well, it's clear what we
got to do-- we got to tell him
that the satellite
can only carry one camera.
AARON:
Joe, this is a government
contract-- you sure you want
to tell them
we can't meet their specs?
No, I want to tell them that
their specs are fanciful,
a creation of pure whimsy
on a par with the works
of Lewis Carroll.
MARIE:
Airplane!
But I can't do that,
so I'm just gonna tell them
that the satellite
can only carry one camera.
Airplane. Airplane.
Can you hold
on a sec?
Hey, Bridgette, did you
turn on the TV for your sister?
BRIDGETTE:
She asked me to, Daddy.
It's no problem.
I was just asking
Airplane!
if we should...
Hey, Aaron, did your son
just say "airplane"?
Uh, yeah. He's watching TV.
He is?
He wouldn't happen
to be running around
the room
with his arms spread out
like a couple of wings,
would he?
He is, actually. Why?
Can you tell me
what he's watching?
Otis the Octopus--
it's that show where the big guy
in the fuzzy suit
makes him do jumping jacks...
Sorry, what channel
is he watching?
Nugget. You know,
the kid's channel.
I'm glad he likes it--
it costs me $10.99 a month.
So it's a premium station.
Is that channel 282?
I don't know, Joe.
We're kind of
on a deadline here.
Why are you so curious
about Nugget TV?
C-Can you please tell me
if that is Channel 282?
Okay.
(cartoon music playing)
Yeah, it's channel 282.
You happy?
ALLISON:
Hi. I'm home.
I came bearing pizza!
Actually, I think I am.
Listen, Aaron, I'm gonna
have to call you back.
Hey. What's up?
Hi.
Hey.
I have good news,
and I have bad news.
(groans):
What are you talking about?
What's the good news?
Uh, I don't believe that
our daughter has autism.
In fact, I don't believe it'll
actually be necessary for her
to see a doctor at all.
Well, that is good news.
And the bad news?
I think she might
be a felon.
Excuse me?
I think she's
stealing cable.
(door creaks softly)
(light switch clicks)
(phone rings)
Hello?
It's Edward Cooper.
Sorry to wake you, Mrs. Dubois.
The district attorney
gave me your number.
We both felt that you'd want
to hear about it right away.
Hear about what?
You might want
to turn on your TV.
I don't know what to tell you.
God bless America.
Last night my attorney
was advising me to take a deal
so that I could avoid going
on trial for my life.
Then, at 5:00 this morning,
a prison guard
is shaking me awake
and telling me I can go free.
I don't understand.
COOPER:
Well, as I understand it,
Bell's lawyer asked
the prosecution to produce
the evidence against his client.
According to the law, they're
entitled to a second DNA test
at a lab of their choice.
Apparently, when they went
to the evidence room
to retrieve the dog hair...
it was gone.
No one can find it.
This is unbelievable.
Do they have any idea
what might have happened to it?
Not really.
The district attorney thinks
one of the clerks
must've screwed up.
(sighs):
What do you think?
I don't know.
I don't know what to think.
However it happened,
the evidence is gone,
and without it,
there's no way to prove
that Warren Bell was
the Lincoln Park Killer.
He's a free man.
BELL:
Of course, this is
an enormous relief
for me and my family,
and to anyone who wants to see
the real Lincoln Park Killer
brought to justice.
Like I said, God bless America.
ALLISON:
It must have been hard
to get rid of.
The handsaw--
the one Richard Gomez used
to cut his victims
into little pieces.
I've been thinking about it--
it's kind of bulky.
An awkward shape.
It must have been hard for you
to get rid of.
Unlike, say,
a few strands of dog hair.
It sounds like you're accusing
me of something, Mrs. Dubois.
I am. I am,
because I know.
I know what you did.
I know you got rid of the
evidence against Richard Gomez.
I know you tracked him
to Mexico.
I know you put
two bullets into him.
That's a colorful theory.
I'm guessing you
can't prove any of it,
or I'd be talking
to the police
and not a... consultant.
(wry chuckle)
I am not gonna tell anyone
about what you did to Gomez.
I can carry around
that knowledge
and live just fine.
But knowing what
you are going to do,
that I don't think
I can live with.
I can't just step aside
and let that happen.
So before you go through
with what you're planning,
before you kill Warren Bell,
you need to know
that I am on to you.
I know what's coming.
And I will find a way
to expose you.
(exhales)
You really are an extraordinary
woman, Mrs. Dubois.
I can see why the
district attorney values
your services so highly.
As far as Warren Bell
is concerned, my guess is
that... he'll keep his
nose clean for a while.
He knows he's in the
spotlight right now.
But someday...
someday not too
far from now,
the sickness that
lives inside him
will make its way
back to the surface.
He'll kill again.
He won't be able
not to kill again.
Unless something
happens to him.
Unless the universe
intervenes.
Maybe he'll wrap his car
around a telephone pole.
Maybe he'll die in an
accident in his apartment.
Who knows, maybe he'll
just... disappear.
That happens
sometimes, too.
My guess is, if something
like that does come to pass...
you'll think about
Diane Colquitt,
lying in a park with her panties
wrapped around her neck.
You'll think about all
those dead girls in Ohio.
Or maybe you'll
even think about
that poor dog down
in the garage.
And who knows
what you'll do.
I know we only just met
each other, Mrs. Dubois...
...but I think we both
know that your choice...
(sighs) won't be as easy as you
imagine it's going to be.
Call it a hunch.
An instinct.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com