When I was little,
our next door neighbour Mrs Walters,
used to bring me
her daughter old clothes.
I never wanted to wear them.
It wasn't that I didn't
like the clothes,
it was the way they made me feel,
whenever I put them on.
Later,
I found out that when Mrs. Walter's
little girl would misbehave,
she would lock her,
in a dark closet.
Then there was a time I was about
to sit down and watch television.
And suddenly got
the distinct impression,
that things between my babysitter
and her latest boyfriend had...
moved to the next level.
My point being,
that sometimes the energy from an event
can hang around a particular object
long the event is over.
Almost... like an emprint.
And people like me,
people who are sensitive,
it's almost as if we can read
the energy,
and know what happened.
Like the time Boby Page
taught me to shoot with his dad's rifle.
Not knowing
his dad has just used it
to put down their old Retreiver Buck.
Yeah,
that was a particularly bad energy.
And it isn't just energy
of other people's things.
Other people's behavior,
that comes floating back to me at times.
What?! What?
What is it?!
The trick, I learned,
is to try to figure out why,
the object is sharing
that energy with you.
What the message might be.
And then,
hopefully,
behave accordingly.
You okay?
It's 03:15 in the morning.
It's never God's plan for people
to be up at 3:15 in the morning.
I'm sorry.
I want to clean up the blood and
open the road before the morning rush.
I knew you'd want to see it all
before they carted it away.
You sure she wasn't drunk?
She was heading east around 11:20.
Light trafic, looks like
she was going between 20 and 30.
One in the head, two in the chest.
I don't think she even
knew what hit her.
Somebody shoot her
from a passing car?
I guess someone was up
on that walkway, there.
What do you mean?
That's half a football field away.
You're saying we have a...
...highway sniper
and nobody saw him?
So, how old are you Daddy?
I'm old, kiddo.
I'm really old.
No your not.
Mommy, I don't understand.
Why can't Daddy open
his birthday presents now?
'Cause that's not how we do it.
We don't offer birthday presents
in the morning.
We do on Christmass.
Yeah, this isn't Christmass,
this is Daddy's birthday.
Have you ever seen anyone
put a birthday candle
in a ball of breakfeast cereals?
No. You want to know why?
'Cause we don't open birthday presents
in the morning.
Let me let you in
a little secret, Bridge.
I think it's really 'cause Mommy
likes to procrastinate.
Really?
What's that?
When someone puts on doing things
that they really need to do.
P recisely.
I think the real reason
I can't open my presents,
Is because Mommy has not actually
gone around and getting me one yet.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Good morning.
- Hi, uh...
Do you have the add
that ran this morning's paper?
Oh, sure.
Anything I can help you with in there?
I'm interested in this.
It's a great machine,
would you like to see one?
- Sure.
- Yep.
It says to ask about pricing.
1099.
1100 dollars.
And believe it or not,
our competitors have 'em for 3049.
Not which you had budgeted..
What were you
looking to spend?
Half of that, or less.
This...
is a 1200 $ camera too, but....
far superior
to the one you wanted to buy.
It comes specially equiped
with a 12:1 zoom lens,
that's like having a...
video camera on the end of a telescope.
It's excellent in low-light situations,
this is the...
Rolls-Royce of video cameras.
I let you have it for 500 dollars.
Okay, why would you do that?
Everyone of these that I sell,
comes right back to the store.
It's an excellent
piece of gear, it's just...
too damn complicated for your
average point-'n-shoot customer.
And nobody wants to read the
operating manual anymore, you know?
We were just gonna sent it back
to the manufacturer, and...
frankly I would much rather
sell it to you,
hopefully make a new customer,
and saves money on shipping.
Let me run to the back,
take a battery, a blank DVD
and let you play.
Hello...
Wow, face the camera, sweetie.
Yeah... thank you.
So...
Roll over.
Come on, you want to.
You want to do it.
You wanna roll over.
- Thank you...
- Hey you!
Camera guy, I'm talking to you.
What's you do here camera guy?
What do y-- W-what do you mean?
What do I mean?
What do you think I mean?
I mean, I've been coming to this park
for 3 days in a row,
and for 3 days in a row I've seen
you trying to take pictures of me.
I don't like it.
Okay, so what?
Now you have nothing to say?
What's your name?
I'm thinking your name must be Dick.
Do you mind if I call you Dick?
Dick.
Big, brave guy, with a camera.
Go ahead, Dick
Tilt  down.
I know you want to.
Tilt... down,
Dick
Allright, that's enough.
Now,
You got what you needed?
- I'm out of here.
- Oh, Miss!
Wait Miss, don't go!
Ready to play?
How does it feel to you?
It's small, light, it's terrific, right?
Just wait till I put this battery in,
power it up, so you'd see
what it really can do.
Ok but I think there might
already be one in there.
No, actually it's impossible,
you can't put the DVD in
until you put the battery in.
And I just put the battery in,
Go ahead.
I'll take it.
Cathy come on, I haven't got all day
Get in there.
I'm using up the battery!
I can't keep photographing an empty bed.
Cathy.
Get in there!
No.
Get in there, I'm using up the battery!
Oh, you are so
predictable at this video thing.
And what does that mean?
What do you think it means? It means...
It's just good for you
to be predictable.
You are completely predictable.
Does that mean...
that you don't love me anymore?
It means...
that I'd better be the only one
that you videotape.
From now and 'til the end of time.
That's what I mean, camera guy.
And what else?
It means...
Cathy loves Travis.
-Louder.
- Cathy loves Travis.
Tell it louder!
Allison?
You're busy?
Just a birthday present for Joe.
Just wrapping in.
Well, we're all summoned
to the conference room,
I know not why.
Maggie played cards at the club.
Every Wednesday night, 8:45.
Game ended at 11, It had to.
That's when they closed the room.
She was always home by 11:25
On 30, I call her cell phone.
It goes straight to voice mail,
I thought - "okay,
she forgot to put
the damn thing on."
By quarter to 12,
I start to get anxious.
So I call the other girls--
Camille, Lorraine, Rhonda.
They're all home.
I don't know
what
else to do, so I keep
calling the cell phone.
And then
I call the police.
No help.
No offense.
So...
tried her cell again.
And this time,
I got
an EMS guy who answered.
I met Mr. Caffey
when
he came in this morning
to identify his wife.
I assured him
that we're doing
everything we can
to find
this animal.
We all drive the same streets.
Our loved ones
all drive the same streets.
Oh, how do I smell?
Like the cool mist of the ocean.
Hmm, just like the box says.
Thank you, honey.
- Happy birthday, Daddy.
- Thank you, sweetie.
Open mine!
Wow, is this for me?
- Is it a car?
- No, and you did that joke last year.
He does that joke every year.
That's how we know he's a year older.
It's beautiful.
- I made it.
- You're kidding.
Do you know what it is?
Yes I do, but I'm not going to tell you.
She thinks it's an ashtray.
That is so otherworldly.
This is so what I was hoping for.
You don't even smoke.
And I never will,
but I can still appreciate
a beautifully made ashtray.
Thank you, honey.
I am going to put this
on my desk at work,
right next to the one
you gave me last year.
Here's a little something
from me and Marie.
Also not a car.
You shouldn't have.
Oh, my.
Oh, come on.
Oh, wow, look at this.
Awesome!
Now this is even better than
the one that I showed you in the paper.
Wow, this one has all
the bells and whistles.
Don't look at me.
Marie picked it out.
Whoa. I can't even imagine
how much this cost.
So which of the girls
isn't going to college?
Where is...?
Well, that's it.
There's no bonus gift.
I'm not looking for a bonus gift.
You outdid yourself.
And you, too!
Oh, how did you know?
No, I just thought
that maybe they included
a blank DVD for you to record on.
you're kidding?
There's nothing to record on in there?
- I didn't even think to ask.
- That doesn't matter.
I can wait to record
something till tomorrow.
This is clearly an amazing camera.
I got me some amazing cologne
and an amazing ashtray.
And an amazing little
raspberry right here.
Sorry about the DVDs.
I'll grab some tomorrow.
It was a great birthday.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'm so glad you thought so.
I was worried you would think
I didn't put enough thought into it.
I always think,
"This year I'll be different.
"This year I'll whisk him off his feet,
"take him to the pyramids,
"buy him box seats
"for some great sports
team or something.
Make him a gourmet meal."
And then
I run around the day of
getting your present,
making you a cake from a mix...
worrying
that you'll think I don't care.
I was driving home tonight,
the sun had already set,
and every building that I passed,
every bridge
every water tower,
I was thinking,
"Is he there?"
And  you could just feel that
every person
and every car around me,
they were thinking the same thing:
"Is he out there?
Is he thinking about
shooting at my car?"
At me.
Doesn't he know it's my birthday?
Doesn't he know I have to get home
so Bridgette can give me her ashtray?
Come on, baby,
get up there.
No, Travis,
I don't want to.
Come on. It's just
you and me here.
I want to see you
on camera.
It's  too embarrassing.
I don't want anyone
to see this online.
Kathy,
don't you
trust me, baby?
If you really love me,
you'll do this for me.
Travis,
I don't want to do this, okay?
Can you just get in there
so I have something to focus on?
I've never used this
tripod thing before.
Travis, did you hear me?
I don't want to do this,
okay?
I mean,
I'll do this, I'll do anything,
but I don't want you to tape it, 'right?
I'm not asking you to do anything
that I'm not gonna do.
No,
you shouldn't tape it, okay?
Not tonight.
Why?
It's gonna be fun.
Listen, nobody's gonna see it.
I mean, you're beautiful, but...
you're not famous.
I mean, no offense,
but you ain't exactly Paris Hilton,
I'm not Colin Farrell.
Now give me something to focus on.
What the hell is that?
I told you I didn't want to tape it.
What are you showing me?
He knows something's up.
Last night, he came home,
said he couldn't
reach me for hours.
He beat the living crap out of me.
No, don't.
I told him I got a call, you know,
to do temp work at the V.A. Hospital,
but he didn't believe me.
He said he could...
smell you on me.
Not you, but someone.
Said the next time
he'd kill me.
Do it with drugs.
No one would ever know.
Sometimes I lie in bed at night,
I lie next to him and I think about...
what my life would be like
if he were gone...
if he were dead.
Is it something you want?
I can't let him hurt
you anymore, Kathy.
Shouldn't you maybe shut off the tape?
Kathy and Travis.
Any particular Kathy and Travis?
I just know,
at least I strongly suspect
they're going to attempt
to kill her husband.
He's a doctor, there must be
some way to research
doctors with wives named "Kathy."
- I'm pretty sure they're from this area.
- Why's that?
I bought my husband a video camera
for his birthday from Archibald's.
Before there were batteries in it,
before there was anything to record on,
I started to see videos
of this couple on the viewfinder screen.
Kathy and Travis?
I think perhaps they owned
the camera before I did.
I think the camera
remembers what it saw
and it's showing it to me so we could
stop this thing from happening.
It's showing you all this,
but it's not giving you last names.
but it's not telling you
where or when this killing
might take place.
Allison, maybe you haven't noticed,
but the city's come to a standstill.
We're in the middle
of a bona fide crisis.
Give me a name,
first and last.
Better yet, buy a camera
that has videos of this madman
who's using our streets
for target practice.
That would be truly helpful.
He loved it, right?
Someone owned this camera
before I did, didn't they?
You told me people were
bringing them back to the store,
but you never explained
that someone actually used
this specific camera
you sold me before I bought it.
- Well, I don't know that to be true.
- Well, I do.
I need the name
of the previous owner.
Ma'am, I can assure you
if by some chance
someone purchased the camera
before you and returned it to the store,
it passed the most
rigorous of inspections
before being
returned to inventory.
It's completely covered
by manufacturer's warranty.
I don't care about
the manufacturer's warranty.
I just need the name of the
person who owned it before me.
Furthermore, as I offered
at time of purchase,
I'd be happy to take the machine back,
swap it out for an easier-to-use model.
His first name was Travis.
He had brown hair.
Ma'am,
I'm not saying that someone else
did buy your camera before you, but--
if they did,
I still couldn'ttell you their name.
I'm with the District Attorney's office.
That's all well and good, but...
You're gonna need
to speak to a manager.
I mean, do you have
a warrant or something?
Did he not bring it back?
Did a girl bring it back?
Kathy-- brown hair, pretty?
I don't get it.
Are you not happy with the camera?
I need some recordable DVDs.
Basically what the Mayor,
and the City Attorney
want you to weigh in on
Is if we assign
a disproportionate share
of police to monitor the neighborhoods
where the wealthy people live--
what's our exposure if our sniper friend
shoots someone in a poor neighborhood
and their family
decides to sue the city.
Want to hear a scary thought?
Which is also a great thought?
- What if he never shoots again?
- What's scary about that?
Between you and me?
If he doesn't make
another try I don't think
there's a lot of hope
we're ever going to catch him.
The evidence he left behind
the other night
isn't leading us anywhere.
On the other hand,
I suppose I'd rather have
one unsolved murder than two
or three or four or five.
Hell, I'd rather have
one unsolved murder
then two or three solved ones.
I just invited Sean Caffey back
down here for a little conversation.
Thought you might want to listen in
from the other side of the glass...
You're having a conversation
with him in the interrogation room?
That's a hell of a way to treat a widower
two days after his wife is shot to death.
Maybe.
Apparently there was trouble in the marriage,
but there was also a solid prenup in place.
In the event of divorce,
Sean would get nothing.
How much is she worth to him dead?
Between the inheritance and
insurance pay outs, about 30 millions.
So he bought himself
a long-range rifle,
got up on that pedestrian bridge
and, boy, talk about a lucky shot.
He's rich.
They hire people to do
their dirty work.
Sounds improbable, but...
not impossible.
And as it happens
we're suffering from...
an acute shortage of leads
in this particular case, so yeah,
sure.
I'll come with you.
- I'll pass.
- It's okay.
You weren't invited.
Just an errand.
Now that you're back,
want to be my date for an interrogation?
I suppose.
Where did you get these?
Your wife hired a private detective.
Were you aware that she was
contemplating divorce?
These photos are over a year old.
Maggie and I were working things out.
I don't understand.
How is this relevant to anything?
Shouldn't you be out there
looking for a man with a gun?
I don't know, we're not sure
who we should be looking for.
That's why we're having
this conversation.
- Should I be calling my lawyer?
- You have a lawyer?
Of your own?
Because your late wife's family
made it very clear to me
the family attorney had no interest in
helping you with this particular matter.
What do you make of him?
I feel really stupid, really useless.
It's as if I'm not even
tuned in to the same channel.
Everything I see in my head
has to do with those two kids
I told you about this morning.
And their plan to kill her husband.
So talk to me about being a player.
How does that work?
I mean,
you marry a really wealthy woman,
she makes you sign a prenup,
and then what is it?
You just can't be faithful?
Because from a monetary standpoint,
it makes no sense.
You're really playing with fire.
Unless of course,
you can make absolutely certain
that she won't divorce you,
can't divorce you,
isn't alive to divorce you.
I loved my wife.
Where were you between 11 and 11:45
on the night your wife was slain?
I've made no secret of where I was.
I was at home,
trying to contact her.
Then why didn't you
use the home phone?
Why'd you keep
calling her from your cell phone?
Because I was lazy.
Because I had her mobile number
programmed into my cell.
Because if I use the regular
phones at home I had to dial it,
but if I used my cell phone
I just had to press one button.
Do you think I don't know
how bad this sounds?
The answer to all
your questions is "yes."
Yes, I do think you
know how bad this sounds,
yes you do need a lawyer
And yes,
I know you didn't ask,
but I do believe you're going to be
spending the night with us, Mr. Caffey.
I wonder who lives in here.
Daddy.
I'm making a documentary
on the nocturnal habits
of eighth graders.
Explain to our viewers at home
what it is you're doing right now.
I'm doing geometry.
And it's stupid.
This is fascinating.
I know I'm riveted.
My name is Bridgette Dubois
and I shall now
dance with a spoon
on my...
on my nose.
Goaway!
- Honey...
- Goaway!
Honey, smile.
This is Daddy's birthday present
- and I need you to smile...
- Goaway!
I think she wants you to go away.
I bet you can't guess
who the only two people
in this family are
who haven't been
captured on DVD yet?
Let me think about it.
Time's up.
What was that question again?
Um, I... Are you forgetting
that yesterday was my birthday?
Exactly.
So ask me again in 365 days.
Hmm. Sorry, fella.
I guess your work here
for tonight is through.
I'm going to go
lock the door.
And then I'm going
to go brush my teeth.
No.
Don't waste your time.
I told you nothing's going to happen.
Hardy-har, har, har.
So what am I looking for?
A Mercedes.
It'll be coming towards you.
It's 11 after 11,
so it should be any minute now.
He plays cards
every Wednesday at his club.
They close the place at 11:00.
There's one.
I'm pretty sure there's one.
Yeah. That's it.
- I can tell from here.
- You sure?
I'm absolutely sure.
That's him.
Bang.
Too bad this camera
doesn't have bullets.
- That was a joke.
- I know.
- Next week.
-I know.
So....
you're telling me you believe
these two lovers
- you've been talking about-
- Kathy and Travis.
...were trying to kill
Kathy's husband,
but shot Sean Caffey's
wife by mistake?
Well, it would certainly
simplify things if it were true.
What do you mean?
I mean, what a relief if we're no longer
dealing with a homicidal maniac
who's bent on shooting
people at random,
but rather a single
act of passion.
Of course, you don't know Kathy
and Travis' last name.
So it's not like we can track
these people down, check this story out.
Well, that's the thing--
when I saw them
rehearsing to kill this man,
the wife, Kathy, kept talking
about this card game.
How it had to end at 11:00.
Sounded like the same card game
at the same club that
Sean Caffey was talking about.
- What's your point?
- Am I being naive, or...
isn't it as simple as going to this club
and asking them if they have a member
named Kathy
who's married to a doctor?
Anything to help solve
Mrs. Caffey's murder.
Everyone around
here's devastated,
as you can imagine.
We're actually interested in talking
to some people we think may have
important information
about the killing.
People we believe to be
members of the club here.
They're a couple.
The husband's a doctor.
Drives a car very similar
to the one Mrs. Caffey drove--
expensive black sedan.
A lot of the gentlemen here
drive expensive black sedans.
And any number of our
members are physicians.
Can you tell me anything
else about him?
He plays cards here
on wednesdays at the club.
His wife is named Kathy.
She has brown hair, maybe 25.
Mrs. Dubois,
I have been at this club
for almost  25 years.
I know every member personally.
And the only female
member named Kathy
is a 63-year-old divorcee.
Okay, so much for Kathy.
Would it be possible to
get our hands on a list
of the gentlemen who played
cards here last wednesday?
Maybe the Wednesday
before that as well?
I'm sorry,
but there is no list.
Wednesday is ladies only.
Has been for as long as
I've been here.
If there's nothing else for the moment,
we have a lunch on,
I really need to look in on.
Of course.
We appreciate your help.
If you need me,
I'll be in the clubhouse.
What brand was that camera?
I wanna make sure I don't get one of those.
I'm sorry.
We should head back to the ranch.
That's Kathy.
What'd you say?
Excuse me, Miss.
Waitress...
Sorry, were you calling me?
What can I get for you?
Something to eat, something to drink?
Diana.
Do I know you?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
It's just from over there
you look so familiar.
Been here almost
a year and a half, so...
Are you a member
or a guest, or...?
A guest, a visitor.
Oh.
It's weird.
Has that ever happened to you?
No, I'm certain we've met.
But your name wasn't Diana.
I think you were
with your husband.
Okay, if you say so.
Only thing is,
I'm single. So...
Are you sure I can't
get you anything?
No, I'm fine, thanks.
Okay, well, call if you need me.
Okay.
Who's that?
What'd you have to say?
Her?
Nothing, nobody.
Sorry I'm late.
Saved you some Chinese.
Wow,
Wow, someone had a bad day.
I wasted half a day
at the golf course
for no reason at all.
Questioned someone I had
no business questioning.
By the time I got back to the office,
there were all these
meetings about a sniper
who seems to have
gone on vacation
I want to take that thing back.
What thing?
What are you talking about?
Girls.
Are you through with that?
What's going on?
The camera, I want to take it back.
I'll get you a different one,
but I want to take this one back.
Why? I like it.
Yeah, well, for what
it's worth, I like it, too.
Is something the matter
with it, Mommy?
Yeah, I think so.
The guy who sold it to me
gave me a huge discount on it.
Every night since I gave it to you
I watch you turn it off.
Then I come out here in the middle of
the night, it's turned itself back on.
I'm worried it's going
to catch fire or something.
What?!
I'll get another one
a different one...
I promise.
Tomorrow. I promise.
I don't want to hear a peep.
You're going back.
- You okay?
- Do you hear that?
No, I don't hear anything.
Go back to sleep.
Doesn't anyone hear that but me?
It's open.
Can you turn
that thing off, honey?
I'd really rather not.
The first time I saw you
it was through this thing.
I have a fond
memory of that.
And I have a...
hunch we're gonna be
needing some memories.
So I'll just keep pointing this
memory-maker at you if you don't mind.
What are you talking about?
We're together forever, baby.
You think so?
WeWe shot the wrong car.
We shot the wrong person.
You saw the news?
How could I miss the news?
It's everywhere.
We shot a woman, Kathy!
Some woman driving home!
Okay. So next time
we'll kill the right person.
What? Next time?
Kathy, I don't know if I have
a next time in me.
I mean, if we're lucky
to get away with this,
I don't know if I want to
tempt fate with a "next time."
Well, what's the alternative?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
We can't run away together--
you're still married.
You're not gonna get the money.
You tell me.
What do you think we should do?
Well, I don't think you should
sit there crying like a baby.
Listen to yourself.
You sound like you want
to commit suicide or something.
Suicide?
Seems to be working fine.
No... I'm sure it is.
It's just, um...
my boyfriend gave it to me
and... I'm just
not a memory person</i
I'm really about
the here and the now.
So, here's the receipt.
Any chance I can get cash?
Hello.
Sorry to wake you at this hour
but I thought you'd want to know
you were partially right.
Right about what?
Guy's name was Travis.
What are you talking about?
Whose name was Travis?
Travis McQueen, 24 years old.
He's an Army sharpshooter.
Mustered out of the service
5 months ago.
Couple of uniforms
responded to an odd smell
coming from
an apartment downtown.
Found a high-powered rifle
with a night scope.
not to mention a dead body.
Young guy. I'm guessing he's been
sitting here almost three days.
Looks like a suicide.
Of course it does.
Sorry.
I'm not sure if this
is where I'm supposed to be.
Diana.
Diana Marvin.
I have a strong feeling this is exactly
where you're supposed to be.
Hi.
Diana.
Of course I know who he is.
He's been a member of the club
I work at since I've been there.
Not to mention he's been all over
the papers and the news.
I know you arrested him,
which is absurd.
I feel so terrible for him.
You know, what
happened to his life.
It's just...
I know there's a
news blackout, but...
are you folks any closer to catching
the person who's actually responsible?
We certainly think so.
That's good.
If you don't mind my asking,
just how well did you know him?
We're getting awfully
personal here.
I'm happy to help
with your investigation,
You know, if Sean
needs a character witness,
I'm only too happy
to help, but...
Sean indicated that the two of you
were deeply involved for some months.
Is... is that against the law?
Is that why I'm here?
Do you mind if I ask...
Who ended the affair?
No one ended anything.
Sean Caffey is a married man.
The reality of the situation
became obvious to both of us.
So you knew he wasn't about
to divorce his wife for you.
He didn't offer.
I certainly never asked.
Do you mind if I ask
where you're going with this?
Are you aware That Mr. Caffey
was bound to a prenuptial agreement
that for all intents and purposes
would leave him penniless if
his marriage ended in divorce?
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Penniless as a divorce
but extraordinarily wealthy
as a widower.
Well, it's...
flattering to assume your lover
might do anything to be with you.
That you could
stir that kind of...
passion, in another person.
Sean is many things,
but he is not a murderer.
Not even with help?
No.
Not Sean.
Not ever.
I believe you.
Thank goodness.
I do, too.
I don't think he had
anything to do with it.
I don't think he knew
anything about it.
I'm sure he didn't.
Do you know a man
named Travis McQueen?
Did you say "Travis"?
I don't know anyone
by the name of Travis, no.
He was a sharpshooter in the Army.
Been out about six months now.
He liked to hang around in the park,
take long-lens pictures of pretty girls,
chat them up,
talk about his adventures
as a sniper in Iraq.
No, I'm sorry.
How about Kathy?
Kathy...
just Kathy?
Do she have a last name?
I'm sure she does.
All I know is she
was Travis's girlfriend.
or, at least,
she pretended to be.
No, sorry.
Don't know a Travis,
don't know a Kathy.
And are you prepared
to swear to that?
In a court of law?
Excuse me?
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you in a court of law.
- You have the right to counsel.
- Hold on.
I just told you--
whoever this person is,
whoever his girlfriend is,
however they were involved,
I don't know them.
Why don't you bring
Allison's friend in here?
Yeah.
This will just take a second.
This is the lady, right?
Hi, Kathy.
And you're prepared
to testify to that in a court of law?
Yeah, sure.
That's her. Kathy.
She came in and exchanged
a video camera for store credit.
How's that flash screen
working out for you?
And the proof of purchase
was this receipt,
charged to the credit
card of Travis McQueen?
That's the receipt.
You want to hear
something funny?
It may well be that the
camera you returned...
...is the one I sold her.
Go figure.
Transcript FRM/Framand Synchro : Framand
www.forom.com