The Fourth Great
and Bountiful Human Empire.
Every fact beams out from here.
That's what I call power. 600
channels coming out of Satellite
Five, broadcasting everywhere.
This technology's wrong.
Trouble? Oh, yeah.
This is not the Fourth Great
and Bountiful Human Empire.
Humans are allowed to live here
by kind permission of my client.
Who controls Satellite Five?
The Mighty Jagrafess of the
Holy Hadrojassic Maxarodenfoe.
You mean that thing's in
charge of Satellite Five?
Once you go to Floor
500, you never come back.
You'll have to stay and explain
it, no-one's gonna believe me.
Oh, they might start
believing a lot of things now.
The human race should accelerate.
All back to normal.
What is it? What's happening?
Oh, my God!
I don't believe it, why
did they put you in there?
They never said you were coming!
What happened? I was. . .
Careful now, oh. . .
Oh, mind yourself!
Oh, that's the transmat,
it scrambles your head.
I was sick for days.
You all right?
So. . .what's your name,
then, sweetheart?
The Doctor, I think, I was. . .
I don't know what happened!
You got chosen.
Chosen for what?
You're a housemate! You're in
the house! Isn't that brilliant?
That's not fair, we've got
eviction in five minutes!
I've been here for all nine weeks,
I've followed the rules,
I haven't had a single warning,
and he comes swanning in!
If they keep changing the rules,
I'm gonna protest, I am.
I'm gonna paint the walls.
'Would the Doctor please
come to the Diary Room?'
You are live on Channel 44, 000.
Please do not swear.
You have GOT to be kidding.
Oh. . .
Ah. . .
What happened? It's all right.
It's the transmat.
It does your head in,
you get a bit of amnesia.
What's your name?
Rose. But. . .where's the Doctor?
Just remember,
do what the android says.
Don't provoke it.
The android's word is law.
What do you mean, android?
Like a robot?
Positions, everyone, thank you!
Come on, hurry up!
The contestants are in place,
the cameras. . . Oh, steady!
I was travelling,
with the Doctor and a
man called Captain Jack?
The Doctor wouldn't just leave me.
That's enough chat!
Positions! Final call. Good luck.
But I'm not supposed to be here.
It says Rose on the podium.
Come on.
Hold on. . .
I must be going mad.
It can't be, this looks like. . .
Android activated!
Oh, my God, the android. . .
The An. . .droid.
Welcome. . .to the Weakest Link!
WEAKEST LINKJINGLE
Here we go again.
We've got our work cut out for us.
I don't know, he's sort of
handsome. Good lantern jaw.
Lantern jaws are so last year.
Sorry. . . Nice to meet you,
ladies, but where exactly am I?
We're giving you
a brand new image.
Hold on, I was with the Doctor. . .
Why, is there something
wrong with what I'm wearing?
It's all very 20th century,
where did you get that denim?
A little place in Cardiff,
it was called. . .the Top Shop.
Ah, design classic!
We're gonna have to
find you some new colours,
maybe get rid of that Oklahoma
farm boy thing you've got going.
Just stand still and let the
defabricator work its magic.
What's a defabricator?
OK, defabricator. Does
exactly what it says on the tin.
Am I naked in front of
millions of viewers?
Absolutely!
Ladies. . .your viewing
figures just went up.
I can't open it. It's got a deadlock
seal, ever since Big Brother
504 when they all walked out.
You must remember that.
What about this?
Oh, that's exoglass, you'd need a
nuclear bomb to get through.
Don't tempt me.
I know you're not supposed to
talk about the outside world,
but you must've been watching.
Do people like me? Lynda, Lynda
with a Y, not Linda with an I,
she got forcibly evicted cos she
damaged a camera. Am I popular?
I don't remember.
Oh, but does that mean I'm nothing?
Some people get this far
just cos they're insignificant.
Doesn't anybody notice me?
No, you're nice, you're. . .sweet.
Everybody thinks you're sweet. Oh,
is that right? Is that what I am?
No-one's ever told me that before.
Am I sweet? Really?
Yeah, dead sweet.
Thank you.
It's a wall. Isn't there
supposed to be a garden out there?
Don't be daft, no-one's got a
garden any more! Who's got a garden?
Don't tell me you've got a garden!
No, I've just got the Tardis.
I remember.
That's the amnesia! So what
happened, where did they get you?
We'd just left
Raxacoricofallapatorius and then we
went to Kyoto, that's right,
Japan in 1336, and we only
just escaped. We were together
and we were laughing and then. . .
there was this light,
this white light
coming through the walls, and then. . .
I woke up here.
Yeah, that's the transmat beam,
that's how they pick the housemates.
Oh, Lynda with a Y. . .
Sweet little Lynda.
It's worse than that.
I'm not just some passing traveller.
No stupid little transmat
gets inside my ship.
That beam was 15 million
times more powerful, which
means. . .this isn't just a game.
There's something else going on.
Well, here's the latest update
from the Big Brother house.
I'm getting out,
I'm gonna find my friends. . .
and then I'm gonna find you.
Need a word. Hold on.
Let me finish this. 19, 18. . .
17, 16, 15. . .
Thank you, people, transmitting in. . .
12, 11, 10. . .
But I need to find the Doctor.
Just shut up and play the game!
All right, then. . .what the hell?
I'm gonna play to win!
And. . .cue.
Let's play the Weakest Link!
Start the clock. Agorax,
the name of which basic foodstuff
is an anagram of the word "beard"?
Bread. Correct.
Fitch, in the Pantraffic Calendar,
which month comes after Hoob?
Is it. . .Clavadoe?
No, Pandoff. Rose, in maths,
what is 258 minus 158? 100.
Correct. Rodrick. Bank!
Which letter of the alphabet
appears in the word "dangle"
but not in the word "gland"?
E. Correct.
Colleen, in social security, what
Correct. Broff, the Great Cobalt
Pyramid is built on the remains of
which famous old Earth institute?
Touchdown. No, Torchwood.
Agorax, in language, all five
examples of which type of letter
appear in the word facetious?
Vowels.
Correct.
Fitch, in biology, which blood
cells contain iron - red or white?
Erm. . .
White. No, red.
Rose, in the holovid
series Jupiter Rising,
the Grexnik is married to whom?
How should I know?
Why is she laughing?
Rodrick, in maths. . .
Oh, my God, I think she knows.
And I've got a housemate
who appeared out of nowhere.
I told you.
It's like the game's running itself.
It's the buccaneer look - a
little a dash of pirate and just a
tweak of President Schwarzenegger.
I'm not sure about the vest, what
about a bit of colour to lift it?
Absolutely not,
never wear black with colour.
Now, let's talk jackets.
I kinda like the first one.
No, that's a bit too
much Hell's Angel,
I think I like the shorter one.
Look, waist-length, nice
and slimming, shows off the bum.
Works for me. Once we've got an
outfit, we can look at the face.
Ever thought about cosmetic
surgery?
I've considered it. A little
lift around the eyes, tighten up
the jaw line. What do you think?
Oh, let's have
a bit more ambition!
Let's do something. . .cutting edge.
So, Rose, what do you actually do?
I just travel about a bit,
a bit of a. . .tourist, I suppose.
Another way of saying unemployed?
No.
Have you got a job?
Well, not really, no, but. . .
Then you ARE unemployed, and yet
you've still got enough money
to buy peroxide. Why Fitch?
I think she got a few of
the questions wrong, that's all.
And you'd know all about that.
Well, yeah, but I can't vote for
myself, so it had to be Fitch.
I'm sorry, that's the game,
that's how it works.
I had to vote for someone.
Let me try again, it was the lights
and everything, I couldn't think.
In fact, with three answers wrong,
Broff was the weakest link in that
round, but it's votes that count.
I'm sorry, please. . .
Oh, God, help me!
Fitch, you are the weakest link.
Goodbye.
And we've gone to the adverts,
back in three minutes!
What was that? What just happened?
She was the weakest link,
she gets disintegrated.
Blasted into atoms.
But I voted for her!
Oh, my God, this is sick!
All of you, you're just sick!
I'm not playing this!
I'm not playing!
I. . .I can't do it!
Oh, please, somebody let me out!
You are the weakest link.
Goodbye.
Don't try to escape.
It's play. . .or die.
Doctor,
they said all housemates must gather
on the sofa, you've got to.
I'm busy getting out, thanks.
But if you don't obey, then
all the housemates get punished.
Well, maybe I'll be voted out, then.
How stupid are you? You've only
just joined, you're not eligible.
Don't try anything clever
or we all get it in the neck.
Big Brother house,
this is Davina-droid.
Crosbie, Lynda and Strood,
you have all been nominated
for eviction.
And the eighth person to be
evicted from the Big Brother house
is. . .
Crosbie!
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It should've been me,
that's not fair. Oh, Crosbie. . .
Crosbie, you have ten
seconds to make your farewells
and then we're gonna get you.
I won't forget you!
I'm sorry I stole your soap.
I don't mind, honestly!
Thanks for the food, you were
a smashing cook, bless you.
Crosbie, please leave
the Big Brother house.
Bye, then. Bye, Lynda.
Bye. . .
I don't believe it, poor Crosbie.
It's only a game show!
She'll make a fortune on the outside.
Sell her story,
release a record, fitness video,
all of that, she'll be laughing.
What do you mean, on the outside?
Here we go.
Well, what are they waiting for?
Why don't they just let her go?
Stop it, it's not funny!
Eviction in five, four,
three, two, one!
What was that?
Disintegrator beam.
She's been evicted.
>From life.
No-one programmed the transmat,
no-one selected the new contestants.
It is exactly like those stories.
Oh, don't start that again.
I think you need to
take a session off.
I would, if you'd take it with me.
And don't start that again either.
Though the rumours go back decades,
saying that something's been
hidden up here
underneath the transmissions.
But the controller would know.
She watches everything.
Maybe she just can't see it.
You've got to allow for human error.
Well, that's your problem, then.
I don't think she's been human
for years.
18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, transmit.
Are you insane?
You just step right into the
disintegrator? Is it that important,
getting your face on the telly?
Is it worth dying for? !
We haven't got a choice!
But I thought you had to apply.
Don't be so stupid, that's how
they played it centuries back.
You get chosen whether
you like it or not.
Everyone on Earth is a potential
contestant, the transmat beam
picks you out at random.
It's non-stop, there are 60
Big Brother Houses running at once.
How many, 60?! They've had to
cut back, it's not what it was.
It's a charnel house!
What about the winners, what do they
get? They get to live. Is that it? !
Well, isn't that enough?
Rose is out there. She got caught
in the transmat, she's a contestant.
Time I got out.
That other contestant, Linda with an
I, she was forcibly evicted for what?
Damage to property. What, like this?
No, I'm just not getting this,
it's just too. . .safe, too decent.
And you'd never keep it clean.
Stage two ready and waiting.
Bring it on, girls.
Now it's time for the face-off!
Does that mean I get
to compete with someone else?
No, like I said, face. . .off.
I think you'd look good
with a dog's head.
Or maybe no head at all,
that would be so outrageous.
And we could stitch your legs
to the middle of your chest.
Nothing is too extreme,
it's to die for!
Now hold on, ladies, I don't want
to have to shoot either one of you.
But you're unarmed.
You're naked!
But that's a Compact Laser Deluxe!
Where were you hiding that?
You really don't want to know.
Give me that accessory!
You are the weakest link, goodbye!
Going to the break,
two minutes on the clock.
Just a reminder, we've got solar
flare activity coming up in ten.
Colleen was clever, she banked all
the money, why'd you you vote
for her?
Cos I want to keep you in!
You're stupid, you don't even know
the Princess Vossaheen's surname.
When it comes to the final,
I want to be up against you.
So that you get disintegrated and I
get a load of credits, courtesy of
the Bad Wolf Corporation.
What do you mean? Who's Bad Wolf?
They're in charge.
They run the Game Station.
Why are they called Bad Wolf?
I dunno, it's just a name.
It's like an old Earth
nursery rhyme, what does it matter?
I keep hearing those words
everywhere we go, Bad Wolf. . .
The things you've seen. . .
The darkness!
The big bad wolf.
Attention, all personnel, Bad Wolf
One descending. Blaidd Drwg. . .
What does it mean? Bad Wolf.
Different times, different places,
like it's written all over the
universe. What are you on about?
If the Bad Wolf are in charge
of the quiz, then. . .
maybe I'm not here by mistake.
Someone's been planning this.
The Doctor, you've broken the
house rules, Big Brother has
no choice but to evict you.
You have ten seconds
to make your farewells,
and then we're gonna get you.
Come on, then, open up! You're mad,
it's like you want to die!
I reckon he's a plant, he was
only brought in to stir things up.
The Doctor, please
leave the Big Brother house.
Come on, then! Disintegrate me!
Come on, what are you waiting for?
He's mad, he's bonkers.
I told you to keep an eye on him,
not kill him.
He damaged the property,
it's an automatic process.
Eviction in five, four. . .
three, two. . .
one!
Ha-ha, I knew it! Do you see?
Someone brought me into this game.
If they wanted me dead, they could've
transmatted me into a volcano.
What did you do? Nothing,
it's like. . .some sort of override.
Maybe the security
isn't as tight this end.
Are you following this?
I'm getting out!
Come with me.
We're not allowed!
Stay in there, you've got a 50/50
chance of disintegration.
Stay with me, I promise
I'll get you out alive, come on!
No, I can't. . .I can't.
Lynda, you're sweet.
>From what I've seen of your world,
do you think anybody votes for sweet?
Hold on. . .I've been here before.
This is Satellite Five.
No guards. That makes a change.
You'd think a big business like
Satellite Five
would be armed to the teeth.
No-one's called it Satellite Five in
ages. It's the Game Station now.
It hasn't been Satellite Five
in about 100 years.
100 years exactly.
It's the year 200100.
I was here before, Floor 139.
The satellite was broadcasting
news channels back then.
I had a bit of trouble upstairs,
nothing too serious.
Easy, gave 'em a hand,
home in time for tea.
100 years ago?
What, you were here 100 years ago?
Yep.
You're looking good on it.
I moisturise.
Funny sort of readings.
All kinds of energy.
The place is humming. It's weird.
This goes way beyond
normal transmissions.
What would they need all
that power for? I don't know,
I think we're the first ever
contestants to get outside.
I had two friends with me,
they must've got caught in the
same transmat, where would they be?
They could have been allocated
anywhere, there's 100
different games.
Like what? Well,
there's ten floors of Big Brother,
there's a different house
behind each door,
and beyond that there's all sorts of
shows, it's non-stop.
There's, em. . .Call My Bluff
with real guns,
Countdown where you've got 30
seconds to stop the bomb going off.
Ground Force, which is a nasty one,
you get turned into compost.
Erm. . .Wipeout,
speaks for itself, oh, and
Stars In Their Eyes, literally,
stars in their eyes -
if you don't sing, you get blinded.
And you watch this stuff?
Everyone does. How come you don't?
I never paid for my licence.
Oh, my God,
you get executed for that!
Let 'em try.
You keep saying things
that don't make sense.
Who are you, though, Doctor, really?
It doesn't matter.
Well, it does to me.
I've just put my life in your hands.
I'm a traveller wandering past.
Believe it or not,
all I'm after is a quiet life.
So. . .if we get out of here,
what are you gonna do,
just. . .wander off again?
Fast as I can.
Cos, em. . .I could come with ya.
Maybe you could.
I wouldn't get in the way.
I wouldn't mind if you did.
Not a bad idea, Lynda with a Y.
But first of all we've gotta
concentrate on the getting out,
and to do that, you've got to know
your enemy. Who's controlling it?
Who's in charge of the satellite now?
Hold on. . .
Your lords and masters.
OK, you win, the
Controller's got to handle this.
Archive makes a record of
all transmat activities.
Find out how he got on board.
Archive Six.
Controller. . .
we have a problem.
Continue working.
We have a security problem.
I'm sorry, but I can't. We have
contestants outside the games,
but the alarms haven't gone off.
No security, the games continue.
We can't just let them wander.
They are no-one.
I'm sorry, I was just, erm. . .
Archive Six is out of bounds.
But I need to check the transmat log.
No-one may enter Archive Six.
Return to work.
Inform all staff,
solar flares in delta point seven.
19, 20. . .
Compatible systems. . .
Just align the wave signature. . .
That-a-boy! Got myself a gun!
Well, ladies, the pleasure was
all mine, which is the only
thing that matters in the end.
Two hearts, that's him.
Which floor?
Blimey!
I've never seen it for real before,
not from orbit.
Planet Earth!
What's happened to it?
It's always been like that,
ever since I was born. See there?
That's
the Great Atlantic Smog Storm.
We get newsflashes, telling us
when it's safe to breathe outside.
So the population just sits there.
Half the world's too fat, half's too
thin, and you lot just watch telly.
10, 000 channels,
all beaming down from here.
The human race! Brainless sheep,
being fed on a diet of. . .
Mind you, have they still got
that programme where three
people live with a bear?
Oh, Bear With Me, I love that one!
And me. The celebrity edition
where the bear got in the bath. . .
But it's all gone wrong,
I mean, history's gone wrong, again!
This should be the Fourth Great and
Bountiful Human Empire.
I don't understand.
Last time I was here I put it right.
No, but that's when it first went
wrong, 100 years ago, like you said.
All the news channels,
they just shut down overnight.
But that was me. I did that.
There was nothing left in their
place, no information.
The whole planet froze.
The government, the economy, they
collapsed. That was the start of it,
100 years of hell.
Oh, my. . .
I made this world.
That leaves Rose and Rodrick,
you're going head-to-head.
Let's play. . .the Weakest Link!
That's the end of tactical voting.
You're on your own now.
Hey, handsome, good to see you.
Any sign of Rose?
Can't you track her down?
She must be still inside the games,
all the rooms are shielded.
If I can get inside this computer.
She's got to be here somewhere.
Hurry, these games
don't have a happy ending.
You think I don't know that? !
There you go. Patch that in,
it's programmed to find her.
Thanks. Hey, there. Hello!
Captain Jack Harkness. Lynda Moss.
Nice to meet you, Lynda Moss.
Do you mind flirting outside?
I was just saying hello!
For you, that's flirting.
I'm not complaining. Muchas gracias.
Not compatible! This stupid
system doesn't make sense!
This place should be a basic
broadcaster, but the systems
are twice as complicated.
It's more than TV, this station's
transmitting something else.
Like what?
I don't know. This whole
Bad Wolf thing's tied up with me.
Someone's manipulating my entire
life, it's some sort of trap,
and Rose is stuck inside it.
Rose, in geography,
the Grand Central Ravine is named
after which ancient British city?
Is it York? No, the correct
answer is Sheffield.
Found her! Floor 407. Oh, my God,
she's with the Anne-droid,
get her out of there!
Rodrick, in literature, the
author of Lucky was Jackie who?
Stewart.
No, the correct answer is Collins.
Rose, the oldest inhabitant
of the Isop Galaxy
is the face of what? Boe!
The Face of Boe!
That is the correct answer.
Come on! Come on!
Rodrick, in history who was the
president of the Red Velvets?
Hoshbin Frane.
That is correct.
Rose, food, the dish gaffabeque
originated on which planet?
Em. . .is it. . . ?
Mars?
No, the correct answer is Lucifer.
Rodrick, which measurement
of length is said
to have been defined
by the Emperor Jate
as the distance from his nose
to his fingertip?
Would that be a goffle?
No, the correct answer is a paab.
Rose, in fashion, Stella Pok Baint
is famous for what?
Shoes.
No. The correct answer is hats.
Rodrick. . .
Game Room Six, which one is it?
Over here!
San Hazeldine.
No, the correct answer
is San Chen.
Let me blast it open.
You can't, it's a vital combination.
Rose, in history, which Icelandic
city hosted Murder Spree 20?
Reykjavik?
No, the correct answer
is Pola Ventura.
Oh, my God! I've done it!
You've lost!
Cone on, come on, come on!
Rodrick. . . I'm not mean to be
here. . .you ARE the strongest
link.
I need to find the Doctor,
he's gotta be here somewhere!
He wouldn't just leave me!
Thank you so much. This game is
illegal, I'm telling you to stop!
Rose! Stop this game!
I order you to stop this game!
You are the weakest link. . . .
Look out for the Anne-droid,
it's armed!
A-a-a-a-ah!
What the hell did you do to her?
I'm calling security,
you have no permission to be here.
Deactivate the Anne-droid.
You killed her and all
you're worried about money? !
Back off, mister! Back off!
Control, I'm overriding your
commands, I need security,
and I need it here right now!
It's that lot. . .
Leave him alone!
Sir, put down the gun
or I'll have to shoot.
You killed her! Your stupid
freaking game show killed her!
Sir, I'm arresting you under Private
Legislation 16 of the Game Station
Syndicate. . .
HIS VOICE FADES OUT
Can you tell us the
purpose of this device, sir?
Can you tell us how you got
on board?
Just leave him alone.
I'm asking him.
Sir? Can you tell us who you are?
You will be taken from this
place to the lunar penal colony,
to be held without trial.
You may not appeal
against this sentence.
Is that understood?
Let's do it.
Oh, my God, now we're in trouble.
Floor 500.
ALARM SOUNDS
Clear the floor!
He's on his way up here. . .
with a gun!
This is an emergency,
close down the lift.
All staff are reminded that
solar flares commence. . .
Never mind solar flares,
he's gonna kill you!
OK, move away from the desk.
Nobody try anything clever.
Everybody clear, stand to the side
and stay there.
Who's in charge of this place?
19, 20. . .
This satellite's more than
a game station. 79, 80. . .
Who killed Rose Tyler?
All staff are reminded. . .
I want an answer!
She can't reply. Don't shoot!
Oh, don't be so thick,
like I was ever gonna shoot.
Captain, we've got more guards on the
way up, secure the exits. Yes, sir!
What were you saying?
But. . .I've got your gun. OK, so
shoot me. Why can't she answer?
She's, erm. . . Can I put this down?
If you want, just hurry up. Thanks.
Sorry, erm. . .
The Controller is linked into
the transmissions, the entire
output goes through her brain.
You're not a member of staff, so she
doesn't recognise your existence.
What's her name?
I don't know. She was installed
when she was five years old, that's
the only life she's ever known.
Doors sealed, we're safe for about
ten minutes. Keep an eye on 'em.
That stuff about something going on
with the Game Station,
I think you're right.
I've kept a log, unauthorised
transmats, encrypted signals.
It's been going on for years.
Show me.
You're not allowed in there,
Archive Six is out of bounds.
Do I look like an
out-of-bounds sort of guy?
What the hell. . . ?
Solar flare activity in delta. . .
If you're not holding us hostage,
let us out, the staff are terrified!
That's the same staff who
execute hundreds of contestants?
We're just doing our jobs.
With that sentence you
just lost the right to even
talk to me, now back off!
That's just the solar flares.
They interfere with the
broadcast signal, so this place
automatically powers down.
Planet Earth gets a few repeats.
It's all quite normal. Doctor. . .
Doctor? Whatever it is,
you can wait. I think she wants you.
Doctor. . . Doctor. . .
Where's the Doctor? I'm here.
I can't see, blind. . .
So blind, all my life blind.
All I can see is numbers,
but I saw you. What do you want?
Solar flares hiding me,
they can't hear me.
My masters listen, but they can't
hear me now, the sun,
the sun is so bright.
Who are your masters?
They wired my head,
the name is forbidden.
They control my thoughts,
my masters, I had to be careful.
They monitor transmission.
but they don't watch the programmes.
I could hide you inside the games.
My friend died inside your games.
It doesn't matter.
Don't you dare tell me that!
They've been hiding, my masters,
hiding in the dark space,
watching and shaping the Earth,
so. . .so. . .so many years.
Always been there, guiding humanity,
hundreds and hundreds of years.
Who are they? They wait and plan
and grow in numbers,
they're strong now,
so strong, my masters. Who are they?
But speak of you.
My masters, they fear the Doctor.
Tell me! Who are they?
When's the next solar flare?
Two years' time.
Fat lot of good that is!
Found the Tardis.
We're not leaving now.
No, but the Tardis worked it out.
You'll wanna watch this.
Lynda, could you stand
over there for me, please?
I just wanna go home.
It'll only take a second,
could you stand in that spot?
Quick as you can!
Everybody watching?
OK, three, two, one.
But you killed her! Oh, do you think?
What the hell was that? It's a
transmat beam, not a disintegrator,
a secondary transmat system.
People don't get killed in the
games, they get transported
across Space.
Doctor, Rose is still alive!
No, it can't be.
I saw you die!
She's out there somewhere! Doctor!
Coordinates 5.6.1.
Don't, the solar flare's gone,
they'll hear you!
No, my masters, no, I defy you!
Sigma 7. . . A-a-a-ah! They took her.
Oh, my masters. . .
you can kill me. . .
for I have brought your destruction.
Look, use that. It might contain
the final numbers,
I kept a log of all the unscheduled
transmissions. Nice. . .Thanks.
Captain Jack Harkness, by the way.
I'm Davitch Pavale.
Nice to meet you, Davitch Pavale.
There's a time and a place.
Are you saying that this whole
set-up's been a disguise all along?
Going way back, installing the
Jagrafess 100 years ago.
Someone's been playing a long game,
controlling the human race from
behind the scenes for generations.
Click on this.
The transmat delivers to that point,
right on the edge of the solar
system. But there's nothing there.
It looks like nothing because that's
what this satellite does.
Underneath the transmission
there's another signal. Doing what?
Hiding whatever's out there.
Hiding it from sonar, radar, scanner.
There's something's sitting
right on top of Planet Earth,
but it's completely invisible.
If I cancel the signal. . .
That's impossible.
I know those ships.
They were destroyed.
Obviously, they survived.
Who did? Who are they?
200 ships.
More than 2, 000 on board each one.
That's just about
half a million of them.
Half a million what?
Daleks.
Alert! Alert! We are detected!
It is the Doctor!
He has located us!
Open communications channel!
The female will stand! Stand!
I will talk to the Doctor.
Oh, will you? That's nice, hello!
The Dalek stratagem
nears completion.
The fleet is almost ready.
You will not intervene.
Oh, really? Why's that, then?
We have your associate.
You will obey or she
will be exterminated.
No.
Explain yourself.
I said "no".
What is the meaning
of this negative?
It means no.
But she will be destroyed!
No. . .cos this is what I'M gonna do.
I'm gonna rescue her, I'm gonna save
Rose Tyler from the middle of the
Dalek fleet,
and then I'm gonna save the Earth,
and then just to finish off,
I'm gonna wipe every last
stinking Dalek out of the sky!
But you have no weapons,
no defences, no plan!
Yeah. . .
and doesn't that scare you to death?
Rose? Yes, Doctor?
I'm coming to get you.
The Doctor is initiating hostile action!
The statagem must advance!
Begin the invasion of Earth!
The Doctor will be exterminated!
Exterminate! Exterminate!
Exterminate!
Launch missiles, exterminate.
We've got incoming! This is it,
ladies and gentlemen, we are at war.
There's an army
about to invade this station.
Defences have gone off-line.
I'm dead or about to die any
second with no chance of escape.
They interfere with the
broadcast signal, so this place
automatically powers down.
How did you survive the Time War?
They survived through me!
Subtitles by BBC Broadcast - 2005
DVB-SRT Conversion by reirei.