Why are we chasing it? It's mauve
and dangerous and about 30 seconds
from London.
Excuse me, there's this thing
I need to find, would've fallen
from the sky. . .
Nancy, the thing I'm looking for,
you know what I'm talking about,
don't you?
A-a-ah!
I've got you, you're fine. Hello.
Hello. Jack Harkness,
I've heard all about you.
It's 1941,
the height of the London Blitz and
something else has fallen on London.
He said it was a warship, he stole
it, parked it somewhere out there,
somewhere a bomb's going to fall
on it unless we make him an offer.
It's a con.
I was conning you, that's
what I am, I'm a con man.
There's something chasing
you and the other kids.
Mummy, mummy.
You mustn't let him touch you.
What happens if he touches me?
It makes you like him.
Right, everybody out, across the
back garden and under the fence.
Now, go, move!
You'll find them everywhere, in every
bed in every ward, hundreds of them.
They've all got the same injuries,
scarring on the back of the hand
and the gas mask seems to be fused
to the flesh.
What was the cause of death?
They're not dead!
Are you my Mummy? It's me Nancy!
Don't let 'em touch you.
What happens if they touch us?
You're looking at it!
ROBOTIC VOICES: Mummy!
Go to your room!
I mean it. I'm very, very angry
with you. I'm very, very cross.
GO. . .TO. . .YOUR. . .ROOM!
I'm really glad that worked.
Those would have been
terrible last words.
Jamie. . .
Why are they all wearing gas masks?
They're not.
Those masks are flesh and bone.
How was your con supposed to work?
Simple enough, really.
Find some harmless piece of space
junk, let the nearest Time Agent
track it back to Earth, convince
him it's valuable, and name a price.
When he's put 50% up-front, oops,
a German bomb falls on it,
destroys it forever.
He never gets to see what he's
paid for, never knows he's been had.
I buy him a drink with his own
money and we discuss dumb luck.
The perfect, self-cleaning con.
Yeah. Perfect. The London Blitz
is great for self-cleaners.
Pompeii's nice if you want to
make a vacation of it, though.
But you've got to set
your alarm for Volcano Day.
Getting a hint of disapproval.
Take a look around the room.
This is what your piece of harmless
space junk did.
It was a burnt-out
medical transporter, it was empty.
Rose!
Are we getting out of here?
We're going upstairs.
I programmed the flight computer so
it wouldn't land on anything living.
I harmed no-one!
I don't know what's happening,
but I had nothing to do with it.
I'll tell you what's happening.
You forgot to set your alarm clock.
It's Volcano Day!
AIR-RAID SIREN
What's that?
The all clear.
I wish.
Ah!
I thought you were Jamie.
Mum, Dad! Ruddy kids!
Get off of me!
Get your hands off me!
Oi, you, get in, get in!
Get her in there! She's nicked.
Mr Spock? Doctor.
You got a blaster?
Sure.
The night your space junk
landed, someone was hurt.
This is where they were taken.
What happened?
Let's find out. Get it open.
What's wrong with your
sonic screwdriver? Nothing.
Sonic blaster, 51st century.
Weapon factories of Villengard.
You've been to the factories? Once.
They're gone now. Main reactor
went critical - vaporised the lot.
Like I said, once.
There's a banana grove there now.
I like bananas. Bananas are good.
Nice blast pattern.
Digital. Squareness gun. Yeah.
I like it.
What do you think?
Something got out of here.
Yeah. And?
Something powerful.
Angry.
Powerful and angry.
A child?
I suppose this explains "mummy"?
How could a child do this?
TAPE PLAYS:
'Do you know where you are?
Are you my mummy?
'Are you aware of what's around you?
'Can you. . .see?
'Are you my mummy?
'What do you want?
Do you know what. . . ?
'I want my mummy!
'Are you my mummy?
I want my mummy.
'Mummy? Mummy?'
Doctor, I've heard this voice
before.
Me too. 'Mummy?'
Always, " Are you my mummy?"
Like he doesn't know. 'Mummy.'
Why doesn't he know?
'Are you there, Mummy?
'Mummy!'
The police are on their way.
I pay for the food on this table.
The sweat on my brow, that food is.
The sweat on my brow!
Anything else you'd like?
I've got a whole house here.
Anything else you'd like
to help yourself to?
Yeah.
I'd like some wire-cutters, please.
Something that can cut through
barbed wire. Oh, and a torch.
Don't look like that, Mr Lloyd. . .
I know you got
plenty of tools in 'ere, I've
been watching this house for ages.
And I'd like another look
round your kitchen cupboards.
I was in an 'urry the first time.
The food on this table. . .
.is an awful lot of food,
isn't it, Mr Lloyd?
A lot more than on
anyone else's table.
Half this street thinks your missus
must be messing about with
Mr Haverstock, the butcher.
But she's not, is she?
You are.
Wire-cutters. Torch.
Food. And I'd like to use your
bathroom before I leave, please.
Oh, look!
There's the sweat on your brow!
'Mummy? Please, Mummy? Mummy?'
Doctor?
Can you sense it? Sense what?
Coming out of the walls.
Can you feel it? 'Mummy?'
Funny little human brains! How do
you get around in those things?
When he's stressed, he likes to
insult species. I'm thinking!
Cuts himself shaving,
he does half an hour on life-forms
he's cleverer than.
There are these children.
Living rough, round the bomb sites.
They come out during air raids
looking for food. 'Mummy, please?'
Suppose they were there when this
thing, whatever it was, landed.
It was a med-ship, it was harmless!
You keep saying harmless.
Suppose one of them was affected,
altered. Altered how?
'I'm here!' It's afraid,
terribly afraid. And powerful. . .
it doesn't know it yet.
But it will do.
It's got the power of a god
and I just sent it to its room!
Doctor. . . 'I'm here!
'Can't you see me?'
What's that noise?
End of the tape.
It ran out about 30 seconds ago.
I sent it to its room.
This is its room!
'Are you my mummy?
'Mummy?' Doctor?
OK, on my signal,
make for the door. . . 'Mummy?' Now!
'Mummy?'
Go, now, don't drop the banana!
Why not? Good source of potassium!
Gimme that!
'Mummy?'
Digital rewind.
Nice switch.
It's from the groves of Villengard -
thought it was appropriate.
There's really a banana grove in the
heart in Villengard? And you did
that? Bananas are good.
Doctor!
Come on!
ROBOTIC VOICES: Mummy!
It's keeping us here till it can get
at us! It's controlling them?
It is them.
It's every living
thing in this hospital.
OK. This can function as a sonic
blaster, a sonic cannon and it's a
triple-enfolded sonic disruptor.
Doc, what you got?
I've got a sonic, uh,. . . Never mind.
What? It's sonic,
OK, let's leave it at that.
Disruptor, cannon, what? It's sonic,
totally sonic, I am sonic-ed up!
A sonic what? Screwdriver!
Going down!
Doctor, are you OK?
Could've used a warning.
Oh, the gratitude!
Who has a sonic screwdriver?
I do! Lights?
Who looks at a screwdriver and
thinks, "Ooh-hoo this could be a
little more sonic?"
There's gotta be a light switch.
Never had a long night? Never
had a lot of cabinets to put up?
Mummy!
Door! Mummy? Mummy? Mummy?
Damn it! Mummy?
It's the special features, they
drain the battery. The battery?!
It's so lame!
I was going to send for another one.
But somebody's gotta
blow up the factory.
I know. First day I met him, he blew
my job up. That's
how he communicates.
OK, that door should hold it
for a bit. The door?
The wall didn't stop it!
It's got to find us first! Come on.
Assets!
Well, I've got a banana and in a
pinch you could put up some shelves.
Window? Barred. Sheer drop outside,
seven storeys. And no other exits.
Well, the assets conversation
went in a flash, didn't it?
So where'd you pick
this one up, then? Doctor!
She was hanging from a barrage
balloon, I had an invisible space
ship. . . I never stood a chance.
OK! One. . .
we've gotta get out of here.
Two. . .we can't get out of here.
Have I missed anything?
Yeah.
Jack just disappeared.
Thought as much. What are all
of you doing 'ere? Different
house every night, I told ya!
We thought you were dead
or you'd run off. I didn't.
I knew you'd come back for us.
Found that old thing in the junk.
Thinks he's can write now.
Writing a letter to me dad.
You don't even know
where your dad is.
And how you gonna send it?
I dunno, stick it in an envelope.
You can't even read or write.
I don't need to, I've got a machine!
Will you stop making that noise? !
I'm sorry, Jim.
On you go, you write a letter
to your dad if you want to.
I know we should've went somewhere
else, but we need you, see,
for the thinking.
What if I wasn't 'ere?
What if one night
I didn't come back for ya?
There's a war on, people go out.
They don't always come back.
It happens. What would you do then?
They're wire cutters.
I need you to think about that.
Someone's gotta look after this lot.
Why?
You going somewhere? . .The bomb site.
The one at the railway station.
Why? The Child.
That's where he was killed. That's
where it all started. And I'm gonna
find out how.
He'll get you. And then he'll come
for us. He always comes for us! No.
Ernie, he doesn't.
He always comes after me.
There are things I haven't told ya.
Things I can't tell ya.
As long as you're with me,
you're in danger. Even right now,
you're in danger because of me.
You're the one that keeps us safe.
You think so, Ernie?
Then answer this.
Jim is sitting there
right next to ya. . .
.so who's typing?
Is he coming?
Ernie, as long as you're with me. . .
he's always coming.
Plenty of greens.
And chew your food!
OK, so he vanished into thin air.
Why is it always the great-looking
ones who do that? ! I'm making
an effort not to be insulted.
I mean. . . men.
OK, thanks, that really helped.
Rose? Doctor? Can you hear me?
Back on my ship. . .
used the emergency teleport.
Sorry I couldn't take you,
it's security-keyed
to my molecular structure.
I'm working on it.
How are you speaking to us?
Om-Com - I can call anything
with a speaker grill.
Now there's a coincidence! What is?
The Child can Om-Com too. It can?
Anything with a speaker grill.
Even the TARDIS phone. What,
you mean the Child can phone us?
'And I can hear you. Coming
to find you. Coming to find you!'
Doctor, can you hear that?
Loud and clear. I'll try to block
out the signal. Least I can do.
'Coming to find you, Mummy.'
Remember this one, Rose?
MUSIC: "Moonlight Serenade"
by Glenn Miller
Our song.
MUSIC PLAYS
What you doing?
Trying to set up a resonation
pattern in the concrete,
loosen the bars.
You don't think he's coming back,
do ya? Wouldn't bet my life.
Why don't you trust him? Why do you?
Saved my life. Bloke-wise,
that's up there with flossing.
I trust him cos he's like you.
Except with dating and dancing.
What?
You just assume I'm. . . What?
You just assume I don't. . .dance.
What? Are you telling me you do. . .
dance? 900 years old, me.
I've been around. I think you can
assume at some point I've danced.
You? ! Problem?
Doesn't the universe implode
or something if you dance?
Well, I've got the moves
but I wouldn't wanna boast.
SHE TURNS MUSIC UP
You've got the moves?
Show me your moves!
Rose, I'm,
I'm trying to resonate concrete.
Jack'll be back. He'll get us out.
So come on. The world doesn't
end cos the Doctor dances.
Barrage balloon? What?
You were hanging from a
barrage balloon. Oh, yeah.
About two minutes after you left me.
Thousands of feet above London.
Middle of a German air raid,
Union Jack all over my chest!
I've travelled with a lot of people,
but you're setting new records for
jeopardy friendly.
Is this you dancing?
Cos I've got notes.
Hanging from a rope.
Thousands of feet above London.
Not a cut, not a bruise.
Yeah, I know.
Captain Jack fixed me up.
We're calling him Captain Jack now?
Well, his name's Jack,
and he's a captain.
He's not really a captain, Rose!
You know what I think?
I think you're
experiencing captain envy.
You will find your feet at
the end of your legs.
You may care to move 'em. If ever he
was a captain he's been defrocked.
Yeah? Shame I missed that.
Actually I quit.
Nobody takes my frock.
Most people notice when
they've been teleported.
You guys are so sweet.
Sorry about the delay.
Had to take the nav-com off-line to
override the teleport security.
You can spend ten minutes overriding
your own protocols? Maybe you
should remember whose ship it is!
Oh, I do. She was gorgeous.
Like I told her. . .
be back in five minutes.
This is a Chula ship. Yeah,
just like that medical transporter.
Only this one IS dangerous.
They're what fixed up my hands up.
Jack called them, um. . . Nanobots?
Nanogenes? Nanogenes, yeah.
Subatomic robots. There's millions
of them in here.
See? Burned my hand on the console
when we landed.
All better now. They activate when
the bulkhead's sealed,
check you out for damage,
fix any physical flaws.
Take us to the crash site.
I need to see your space junk.
Soon as I get the
nav-com back on line.
Make yourselves comfortable.
Carry on with whatever it was
you were. . .doing.
We were talking about dancing.
It didn't look like talking.
Didn't feel like dancing.
Halt! Don't move!
So you used to be a Time Agent,
and now you're trying to con 'em?
If it makes me sound any better,
it's not for the money. For what?
Woke up one morning
when I was still working for them,
found they'd stolen two years of
my memories. I'd like them back.
They stole your memories?
Two years of my life.
No idea what I did.
Your friend over there doesn't
trust me and for all I know,
he's right not to.
OK! We're good to go!
The crash site?
As you were. You feeling any better?
Just a touch, sir.
Chain her up where Jenkins
can keep an eye on her.
No! Not in here! Not with him.
You shouldn't have broken in here
if you didn't want to stay.
You don't understand! Not with him!
This is a restricted area, Miss.
You can sit here for a bit,
we're going to have
to ask you a few questions.
Found these, sir.
Very professional.
A little bit too professional.
Didn't just drop in by accident,
then. My little brother died here.
I wanted to find out
what killed him.
Take the men, check the
fence for any other breaches.
And search the area,
she may not have come here alone.
Yes, sir! Please.
Listen, you can't leave me here.
Watch her, Jenkins! Yes, Mummy.
Jenkins? Sorry.
Sir, I don't know what's
the matter with me.
Look, lock me up, fine, but not
here. Please, anywhere but here!
You'll be all right, Miss,
I'm just a little. . .
just a little. . .just a little. . .
What's the matter with you?
Please. Let me go.
Why would I do that? Cos you've
got a scar on the back of your hand.
Oh, yes,
but what's that got to do with
anything?
And you feel like you're gonna
be sick. Like something's
forcing its way up your throat.
I know because I've seen it before.
What's happening to me? In a
minute you won't be you any more.
You won't even remember you.
And unless you let me go, it's
going to happen to me too. Please!
What are you talking about? What's
your mother's name? Matilda.
You got a wife? Yes. Wife's name?
You got kids?
What's your name?
Please.
Let me go. It's too late for you.
I'm sorry. But please let me go.
What do you m. . . ?
M-m-m-mumm-y.
Mumme-e-e-e!
Well, there it is!
Hey, they've got Algy on duty.
Must be important.
We've gotta get past.
Are the words "distract the guard"
heading in my general direction?
I don't think that'd
be such a good idea.
Don't worry, I can handle it.
I've got to know Algy quite well,
since I've been in town. Trust me,
you're not his type.
I'll distract him.
Don't wait up!
Relax! He's a 51st-century guy.
He's just a bit more flexible
when it comes to dancing.
How flexible?
By his time, you lot are
spread out across half the galaxy.
Meaning?
So many species, so little time.
That's what we do when we get out
there? That's our mission?
We seek new life and. . .and. . .
Dance!
Hey, tiger. How's it hanging?
Mummy?
Algy, old sport, it's me.
Mummy?!
It's me, Jack!
Jack?
Are you my. . . mummy?
Stay back! You men, stay away!
The effect's becoming airborne,
accelerating.
What's keeping us safe? Nothing.
Ah, here they come again.
All we need!
Didn't you say a bomb
was gonna land here?
Never mind about that.
If the contaminant's airborne now,
there's hours left. Till what?
Till nothing! Forever!
For the entire human race.
And can anyone else hear singing?
# Rock-a-bye baby on the tree tops
# When the wind blows
the cradle will rock
# When the bow breaks the cradle
will fall
# Down will come baby
cradle and all. . . #
DOOR OPENS
HE MOUTHS
# Rock-a-bye baby. . .on the tree tops
# When the wind blows
the cradle will rock. #
You see? Just an ambulance!
That's an ambulance?
It's hard to explain, it's. . .
it's from another world.
They've been trying to get in.
Of course they have. They think
they've got their hands on Hitler's
secret weapon.
What are you doing? When you see
this thing is empty you'll know
I had nothing to do with it.
Oh!
Didn't happen last time.
It hadn't crashed last time.
There'll be emergency protocols.
Doctor, what is that?
Mummy.
Doctor!
Captain, secure those gates. Why?
Just do it!
Nancy, how did you get in here?
Cut the wire.
Show Rose. Setting 2428-D.
What? Re-attaches barbed wire. Go!
Who are you? Who are any of you?
Never believe me if I told ya.
You just told me that was an
ambulance from another world.
People are running round with gas
mask heads calling for their
mummies, the sky's full of bombs.
Tell me, do you think there's
anything left I couldn't believe?
We're time travellers
from the future. Mad, you are!
We have a time travel machine.
Seriously. It's not that.
All right, you got a time
travel machine, I'll believe ya.
Believe anything, me.
.But what future?
Nancy, this isn't the end.
I know how it looks, it's not the
end of the world or anything.
How can you say that?
Look at it. Listen to me.
I was born in this city. I'm from
here. In like 50 years time.
>From here? I'm a Londoner.
>From your future.
But. . .but you're not. . . What?
.German.
Nancy, the Germans don't come here.
They don't win.
Don't tell anyone I told you so.
But you know what? You win.
We win?
Come on!
It's empty. Look at it.
What do you expect
in a Chula Medical Transporter?
Bandages? Cough drops?
Rose? I dunno.
Yes, you do.
Nanogenes! It wasn't empty, Captain.
There was enough nanogenes
in there to rebuild a species.
Oh, God. Getting it now, are we?
When the ship crashes,
the nanogenes escape.
Billions upon billions of them.
Ready to fix all the cuts and
bruises in the whole world.
But what they find
first is a dead child.
Probably killed earlier that night.
And wearing a gas mask.
And they brought him back to life?
They can do that? What's life?
Life's easy. A quirk of matter.
Nature's way of keeping meat fresh.
Nothing to a nanogene.
One problem though.
These nanogenes, they're not like
the ones on your ship. This lot have
never seen a human being before.
Don't know what a human
being's supposed to look like.
All they've got to go on
is one little body,
and there's not a lot left.
But they carry right on,
they do what they're programmed
to do - they patch it up.
Can't tell what's gas mask and
what's skull but they do their best.
Then off they fly, off they go,
work to be done!
Cos you see, now they think they
know what people should look like.
And it's time to fix all the rest.
And they won't ever stop.
They won't ever, ever stop.
The entire human race is gonna be
torn down and rebuilt in the form
of one terrified child,
looking for its mother.
And nothing in the world
can stop it! I didn't know.
BOMBS DROP IN THE DISTANCE
Mummy, Mummy, Mummy, Mummy.
Rose!
It's bringing the gas-mask people
here.
The ship thinks it's under attack.
It's calling the troops.
Standard protocol. But the gas-mask
people aren't troops!
They are now.
This is a battlefield ambulance.
The nanogenes don't just fix you up,
they get you ready for the front
line. Equip you, programme you. . .
That's why the Child's so strong?
Why it could do that phoning thing?
It's a fully-equipped
Chula Warrior, yes.
All that weapons tech in the hands
of an hysterical four-year-old,
looking for his Mummy
and now there's an army of them.
ALL: Mummy!
Why don't they attack?
Good little soldiers.
Waiting for their commander.
The Child!
Jamie. What?
Not the Child, Jamie.
So how long until the bomb falls?
Any second.
What's the matter, Captain?
Bit close to the volcano for you?
He's just a little boy. I know.
He's just a little boy who
wants his Mummy. I know.
There isn't a little boy born
who wouldn't tear the world apart
to save his Mummy.
And this little boy can.
So what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
It's my fault.
No. It is. It's all my fault.
How can it be your. . . ? ALL: Mummy!
Nancy, what age are you?
20, 21? Older than you look, yes?
Doctor, that bomb. . .
we've got seconds!
You can teleport us out.
Not you guys. The nav-com's back
on line, gonna take too long
to override the protocols.
So it's Volcano Day.
Do what you've got to do! Jack?
How old were you five years ago,
15? 16?
Old enough to give birth anyway.
He's not your brother, is he?
Teenage single mother in 1941.
So you hid. You lied.
You even lied to him.
Are you my mummy?
He's gonna keep asking, Nancy.
He's never gonna stop. Tell him.
Nancy, the future of the
human race is in your hands.
Trust me and tell him.
Are you my mummy?
Yes. Yes, I am your mummy.
Mummy? I'm here!
Are you my mummy?
I'm here. Are you my mummy? Yes.
He doesn't understand,
there's not enough of him left.
I am your mummy.
I will always be your mummy.
I'm so sorry.
I am so, so sorry.
What's happening?
Doctor, it's changing her, we've. . .
Ssh!
Come on, please!
Come on, you clever little
nanogenes. Figure it out!
The mother, she's the mother.
It's gotta be enough information.
Figure it out! What's happening?!
See?
Recognising the same DNA!
Oh, come on!
Gimme a day like this!
Gimme this one!
Ha-ha, ha-ha!
Welcome back! 20 years to
pop music, you're gonna love it.
What happened?
The nanogenes recognised
the superior information.
The parent DNA. They didn't change
you, because you changed them.
Ha-ha!
Mother knows best. Jamie. . .
Doctor, that bomb. . .
Taken care of it. How? Psychology.
BOMB WHISTLES
Doctor! Good lad. The
bomb's already commenced detonation.
I've put it in stasis,
but it won't last long!
Change of plan! Don't need the bomb.
Can you get rid of it,
safely as you can?
Rose? Yeah? Goodbye!
By the way. . .loved the t-shirt!
What are you doing? Software patch.
Gonna email the upgrade.
You want moves, Rose.
I'll give you moves!
Everybody lives, Rose.
Just this once!
Everybody lives!
Dr Constantine,
who never left his patients.
Back on your feet, constant doctor.
World doesn't want to get
by without you just yet
and I don't blame it one bit.
These are your patients.
All better now.
Yes. Yes, so it seems.
They also seem to be standing around
in a disused railway station.
Is there any particular reason for
that? Yeah, well, cutbacks.
Whatever was wrong with
them in the past you're probably
gonna find that they're cured.
Just tell 'em what a
great doctor you are,
don't make a big thing of it. OK?
Dr Constantine.
Mrs Harcourt,
how much better you're looking!
My leg's grown back!
When I come to the hospital,
I had one leg!
Well, there is a war on,
is it possible you miscounted?
Right, you lot, lots to do.
Beat the Germans, save the world,
don't forget the welfare state!
Setting this to self destruct
soon as everybody's clear.
History says there
was an explosion here.
Who am I to argue with history?
Usually the first in line.
The nanogenes will clean up their
mess and switch themselves off
cos I just told them to.
Nancy and Jamie will go to
Dr Constantine for help. . .ditto.
All in all, all things considered,
fantastic!
Look at you, beaming like you're
Father Christmas! Who says I'm not?
Red bicycle when you were 12. What?
Ands everybody lives, Rose.
Everybody lives.
I need more days like this!
Doctor. . .
Go on, ask me anything. I'm on fire.
What about Jack?
.Why did he say goodbye?
OK, computer. . .
how long can we keep
the bomb in stasis?
ROBOTIC VOICE: 'Stasis decaying at
90% cycle.
'Detonation in three minutes.'
Can we jettison it?
'Any attempt to jettison the
device will precipitate detonation.
'100% probability.'
We could stick it in an escape pod?
'There is no escape pod on board.'
OK, see the flaw in that.
I'll get in the escape pod.
'There is no escape pod on board.'
Did you check everywhere?
'Affirmative.'
UNDER THE SINK? 'Affirmative.'
OK.
Out of 100, exactly how dead am I?
'Termination of Captain Jack
Harkness in under two minutes,
100% probability.'
Lovely, thanks.
Good to know the numbers.
'You're welcome.' OK, then!
Think we'd better initiate
emergency protocol 417.
'Affirmative.'
Ooh, a little too much vermouth.
See if I come here again.
Funny thing. . .
Last time I was sentenced to death,
I ordered four hyper-vodkas
for my breakfast.
All a bit of a blur after that.
Woke up in bed with
both my executioners.
Mmm, lovely couple.
They stayed in touch.
Can't say that about
most executioners.
Anyway. . .
Thanks for everything, computer. . .
it's been great.
MUSIC PLAYS
Well, hurry up, then!
OK. . .And turn.
OK, try and spin me again. But this
time don't get my arm up my back!
No extra points for a half-nelson.
I'm sure I used to know this stuff.
Close the door, will you?
Your ship's about to blow up,
there's gonna be a draft.
Welcome to the TARDIS.
Much bigger on the inside.
You'd better be.
I think what the Doctor is
trying to say is. . .you may cut in.
Rose!
I've just remembered!
What?
MUSIC:
"In The Mood" by Glenn Miller
I can dance! I can dance!
Actually, Doctor, I thought
Jack might like this dance.
I'm sure he would, Rose, I'm
absolutely certain. . .but who with?
ROSE SNIGGERS
Whoo! . .Ooh!
And I was having such a nice day.
According to intelligence,
the target is the last surviving
member of the Slitheen family,
a criminal sect from the planet
Rexicoricophalvitorius,
masquerading as a human being
zipped inside a skin-suit.
This nuclear power station right
in the heart of Cardiff city
will bring jobs for all.
This nuclear power station right
in the heart of Cardiff city
will bring jobs for all.
And it just so happens to
be right on top of the rift.
If this power station went into
melt-down the entire planet would go
schloop.
Ah, Go on, then, run!
It's the rift, the rift's opening.
The whole city's gonna disappear!
Time and space are ripping apart.
It's gonna rip open the planet!
Subtitles by Kate Spence
BBC Broadcast 2005
DVB-SRT Conversion by reirei.