That I could live with.
I've kept you out of the mix.
I'm in this so deep, and I don't
know how to get myself out.
You're talking
to the right guy.
Hanging with shane
is gonna push our heads under.
We need shane right now.
You know what's at stake
here for me.
Shane's Armenian friends
can get to our families
anytime they want.
Shane?
Lem, I'm sorry!
And the way he died...
shit.
And he never turned on us!
You killed him
because you were scared.
He was strong,
and you were a coward!
All I was doing was following
your game plan, coach!
You don't get to do
what you did for free.
You're gonna pay that Bill.
It's the third time
this month.
If our chip's too close to
the place, the thing goes off.
I got the back.
D-d-don't shoot.
Sir, you all right?
Where are your clothes?
Just stay where you are.
Stay where you are.
You got a moment?
I just put a call in to
one of my contacts at justice.
Regarding what?
It's time to end this
and turn over
the blackmail box to them.
And I'm giving you the opportunity
to come with when I do it
so we can share the credit.
I want Pezuela in jail,
and not for 30 days
on some pissant charge
his lawyer can plead down
to a fine.
Hey, I'm the one still washing
Robert Martin's blood out of my suit.
So this off-the-books
investigation is done.
What about Olivia?
If you turn over
that box now,
you're throwing a good woman
and her career under the bus.
She got herself
into that jam.
All she did
was to get arm-twisted
into helping a couple
of illegals cross the border.
She doesn't even deal
with Pezuela directly.
She got blackmailed into
committing an illegal act.
She's the only link
we know about for sure,
so if she's got to get dragged
down to bust Pezuela, so be it.
Iook...
Pezuela uses a guy named rios
to do his dirty work.
Now, if I can catch
rios red-handed...
and make him give us
Pezuela...
but if you can do that,
so can the feds.
I'm on the inside.
I'm the only one now
who can get Pezuela to trip up.
You've had your chance.
Just give me one more day.
If I can't pull this off...
we can both walk into
your buddy's office
the day after tomorrow.
All right, you get 36 hours.
But that box
is getting turned in
whether you sting rios
or not.
He had blood on his hands
and chest.
No visible lacerations or cuts,
though.
What happened to his clothes?
He was naked
when we found him.
Seemed scared.
He thinks he hurt somebody
but can't remember anything.
Trying to get someone to come
down, run a test, psych exam.
This time of night,
good luck.
You guys want him
when we're through?
Steve?
I'm a little busy here.
Any naked girls show up, though,
you give me a holler?
If psych doesn't want him, I'll
take him in the morning. Okay.
The last time
we were here...
shane stood
right next to us.
He watched as I vowed to get
the guy who killed Lem.
All this time has passed,
and I still haven't made good
on my promise.
Why are we here?
Aceveda's taking the box
to justice day after tomorrow.
We're gonna lose
a lot of leverage with Rezian
when he finds out that box
is out of play.
What do we do?
I've been standing here
for the last two hours
trying to figure that out.
I think I've come up with a way
to dig us out of our hole.
Which one?
All of 'em.
I got a plan that's gonna get rid
of our Armenian problem for good...
take care of Pezuela in a way
that secures my badge
and that'll give Lem
the justice he deserves.
You were right.
We can't just wait around
until shane makes a mistake
that's gonna drown us.
As long as he's around, we'll
never breathe free air again.
Wait a second.
If we go through with what you're
talking about, there's no turning back.
Never thought I'd have to
convince you. You don't.
But doing this, in a rush,
to meet some deadline?
We're bound to make
a mistake.
Iook, it's time we made good
on our vow.
We owe it to Lem.
What's the plan?
What I'm thinking about
won't ever lead back to us.
Where you guys been?
We've been talking.
I may have let
the rough patch between us
make me a little hardheaded
about the blackmail box.
I told Vic about that
conversation that we had.
As soon as that thing
is back in Pezuela's hands,
Rezian's eternally grateful...
we can move past all this.
The problem is
Pezuela is not gonna want to pay
for something
he considers his.
But Rezian might.
Our third and final wish
to the armenians.
And considering all the hell
we've been through,
might as well earn
a little scratch for it.
Call Rezian.
Tell him the owner of the box is
willing to sell it for a price.
Okay.
We get a couple of cholos to
play the role of our sellers.
I'd say we could milk
at least 100 grand out of this.
I'll find the cholos.
You get us some face time
with Rezian this morning.
We got to agree to terms
before we make the delivery.
Yeah, sure.
I got to tell you,
it's gonna feel real good
to move past this.
I already feel like there's
this weight...
oh, I'm sorry.
Am I interrupting something?
Look what crawled in.
Tavon.
How you doing?
I, uh...
I'm pretty good.
Just got off disability
a few weeks ago.
Still have some physical therapy
to do, though.
That's great, man.
Yeah, they got your boy
working Hollywood now.
Hollywood?
Blow jobs for b-listers.
Sounds like
good therapy to me.
It's not so bad.
It's, uh...
hey, Julien.
Oh, you went out and found
yourself another brother?
They letting you ride
in the front of the bus yet?
Sorry.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter.
Listen, Julien, these guys,
they might be tight,
but they're not unbreakable.
Listen,
my sympathies about Lem.
Uh, thanks.
What brings you
to the Barn?
Oh, I actually came to talk
to that guy.
Uh, you got a minute
to run upstairs
and chat
with your captain?
Yeah.
What about?
Gary barba.
Hope he fell
into a meat grinder.
Actually, he popped back up
on the grid,
and he landed
right in my lap.
Sure, yeah.
Let's go.
I'll, uh...
I'll catch you guys later.
Yeah, see you later.
Who's Gary barba?
A blast from shane's past.
Don't worry.
He won't slow us down.
I liked barba for a rape
back when Vic and I
were working vice.
We couldn't get enough
to bring him in.
Piece of shit goes off and
kills his family a week later.
Only survivor was his
10-year-old daughter, camille.
And he's been a fugitive
ever since.
I mean, completely off the radar
for six years,
until this week,
when he reached out to camille.
No shit.
Yeah, her foster family
lives in Hollywood.
They contacted us
two days ago.
How's cammy doing?
She's in bad shape.
I mean, he's been
calling her every day.
At first, he wasn't even
talking, just... breathing.
And now he's trying to get her
to meet face-to-face.
Camille told me
that she was close to you.
I stayed with her
in protective custody
while we were trying to track
down her... asshole of a dad.
Camille isn't comfortable with
going face-to-face with her old man,
even with a battalion
of undercovers around her.
She said she'd only do it
if shane was there with her.
Can Ronnie spare you?
For this?
Yeah.
You know what?
I got to wrap up
a few things here first.
I'll, um...
I'll met you there?
Yeah, listen, before we get into
all this...
I just really want
to apologize to you...
for hitting Mara that night.
Iook, what happened in the past
is exactly that.
I've moved on.
And so has my wife.
I really am sorry.
Okay.
Anything interesting?
Barba's back.
We got a chance to take
him today. I'm gonna assist.
We got that other thing today. I know.
I'll set it up, but then I'm
gonna have to go back and forth.
I need you to appreciate the seriousness
of what we're trying to do here.
I do.
But barba is here today.
Tavon say anything else?
No.
No, he still thinks he
smacked Mara around. Good.
Got enough problems
as it is.
What's the daily word
from the streets?
More like a whisper.
Nothing worth repeating.
Nothing on the armenians?
Let me decide that.
I might have heard
something.
But I'd rather not
tell you about it.
'Cause I'm afraid of what
you'd do with the information.
I don't pay you
to be afraid.
You don't pay me enough
to stand by
while you assassinate
city officials, either.
It made my point.
Yeah.
And it scared the real Armenian
targets right into hiding.
And do you know
where they are?
Look, I need to be sure
there will be no more
civilian casualties.
I already made my point.
All right, the word is
the Armenian board of directors
is meeting,
all of them, in one spot.
Where and when?
Tonight.
I'll have
all the details soon.
Coordinate with rios.
Give him the details.
If you're gonna go through
with this,
it's gonna burn hot and bright
for a long time.
Now, it might be best if
your boys get lost afterwards.
Real lost.
Why would he come back now?
Baby, your old man
is a bad penny.
He was bound to show up
sooner or later.
The important thing
is I am here,
and I am not going anywhere
until you're safe
and he's under arrest.
Shane and I will be listening
the whole call.
Okay? And he can guide you
through any bumps.
You ready for when he calls?
I'm ready.
Are you?
Look, you don't want him
out there,
never knowing
when he's gonna show up again.
And trust me, cammy,
you are better off
dealing with trouble now
than looking over your shoulder
for the rest of your life.
Okay?
Oh, God.
Jesus, I've been calling you
all morning.
I practically beat in
the front door.
I thought you were supposed
to be at the hospital.
I took a personal day.
Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah.
What's going on?
We were supposed to meet,
remember?
To talk about counseling
for cass.
Can we do it tomorrow?
You've been bitching to me
about being more involved.
Now you want to do it
tomorrow?
I just...
are you... let me look at you.
Are you on something?
God damn it, you're high.
I couldn't sleep last night.
I had these pills.
What kind of pills?
The kind
that help you sleep.
Well, looking at your eyes,
they look like downs.
Do you have any idea how
addictive those things are?
Between shane kidnapping us and
your ex-cop buddy guarding us,
I haven't had
a lot of rest lately.
Our three children
are living in this house
under your supervision.
If you have to pop downs
in order to handle
what's happening,
maybe we should figure out
a different plan.
That's just great.
Let that be the last thing
you say before you leave.
Our daughter's falling apart,
and you're snoring the day away?
I can't remember anything
after 11:00 last night.
Where were you then?
Watching the news at home.
I must have fallen asleep.
I sleepwalk.
Really?
You ever woken up
in strange places before?
Most of the time,
I come to in my house.
Garage or the kitchen.
Most of the time?
Once, I woke up
at a convenience store.
I was arrested
for public indecency.
I was naked then, too.
How does your...
girlfriend feel
about you running
all over town naked?
I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm married.
Well, been separated
six months.
Do any drugs last night?
Have anything to drink?
No, I'm recovering.
Any idea
who you might have hurt?
I was sleepwalking.
You ever see a doctor
about this problem?
I know how it sounds.
I'm just scared I hurt someone.
I want to make sure
they're all right.
Officer Hanlon took a sample
of the blood that's on you.
As soon as we get a type,
we can match it against
any reported assaults,
murder victims in the area.
Was somebody murdered?
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
What happened to your wrists?
Um... sometimes
I tie myself up at night.
Stop myself from leaving.
Okay.
This isn't the first time he's
been caught waving his willy.
Yeah, he told me.
Iooks like unis responded
to a 911 call
from his wife six months ago,
right around the time Jeff said
they were separated.
Could be our victim.
Let's track her down,
find out.
How's that tavon thing
coming along?
Stopped by
to check on camille.
She looks great, man.
Ought to see her.
She's really grown up
in the last few years.
Really likes her new family,
too.
Hey, you got a lockdown
on this old man yet?
'Cause we got to tell Rezian
what time this thing's happening.
Iooks like barba wants
the meeting in the park.
This is gonna be
this afternoon.
Got to tell you,
it's gonna feel really good
righting that wrong.
Let's go get paid.
Okay.
Open up, you shitheads!
Come on, open this door.
Goddamn.
Smells like dog's ass
in here.
You boys forget to slap on
some deodorant?
Till my people
stop getting slaughtered,
I'll be interested in survival,
not luxury.
You said you have the box?
I don't.
But I found out who does.
Someone
in the mexi organization
has been pulling a fast one
on his bosses,
pointing the finger at you
while he plays God
with his little box of intel.
And now that the heat's
getting too high,
he wants to offload the box
once and for all.
Asking price is $100,000.
As far as I'm concerned,
that's cheap.
You're gonna make 10 times that
in blackmail alone.
Or sell it back to the mexis
for twice as much...
and end this war.
This sounds like
a Mexican problem.
Let their gang handle it
internally.
The Mexicans think
you still have it,
so it's gonna stay
your problem.
And eventually, you're
gonna run out of lamb kabobs,
have to poke your head out.
Now, hopefully you won't catch
a bullet anywhere it hurts.
Forget it.
I'll have no problem
getting another buyer.
Can I see this box?
9:00 tonight.
That is, if you can
get the cash that soon.
The money is not a problem.
Good.
The sellers want to bring
a full crew,
guarantee their protection.
Then I want a full crew, as well. Fine.
You bring your three lieutenants
with you, no weapons.
I'll screen the Mexicans,
make sure no one has
an itchy trigger finger.
Absolutely not.
You're asking me to expose
myself and my men
while there's a target
on our heads?
I'll be there with you,
armed.
Anything looks out of place,
I'll pull the plug.
Can't get a better guarantee
than that.
Here you go.
Thanks.
What's this?
Composite sketches
of the Robert Martin shooters.
Mayor wants them hung
in every precinct.
Help yourself.
A man attacks you
in the line of duty,
and this is the first time
I'm hearing about it?
Army surplus room
was supposed to be cleared.
I didn't want to get
another officer in trouble.
You understand if you had
stepped forward sooner...
I spent hours looking through
mug shots on my own time.
This guy wasn't
in any of them.
I mean,
this is the first time
I've even come across his face
since that night.
New intel which makes
the Robert Martin shooters
the same
as our body draggers.
I need the strike team
to look into where they are.
Any gangs you can roust.
I know where shane is.
Where's Vic?
He's on his way here now.
From doing what?
He's running down a lead.
On what?
On this ongoing
Mexican/Armenian shit.
The shit is what
you're trying to feed me.
I put you in charge
of the strike team
so that I can have somebody
who could be held accountable.
Captain, he's running down
a lead.
If I wanted to be lied to daily,
I would have left him in charge.
Now, the truth is that he is
running around out there
doing God knows what
while you are content
to sit back and
cover his ass repeatedly!
Now, I've told you
time and time again,
so a reprimand
goes in your jacket.
One more,
you lose the team,
plus your job,
if I can manage it.
You understand?
Yeah.
I am prepared to make it through
putting up with Vic's bullshit
till the hearing.
The question is, who's gonna be
left after he's gone?
Hey.
Where you off to?
Somebody connected a few dots.
Claudette knows
that the Martin shooters
are the same guys
who did the body draggings.
She connected them
to rios yet?
No.
What happened with Rezian?
He's in.
Shane even offered to ride
the deal from the Armenian side.
I didn't even have to
suggest it to him.
I think he's already spent
his share of the 100 g's.
Holy shit.
This is gonna work,
isn't it?
Blood tests on the naked guy
came back.
Can you believe this?
My lawyer says my disability
case is hanging by a thread.
I'm lucky to get payment
for days missed.
Um, sorry?
Where we at
on Mr. Basada?
Blood on his hands and chest
came back ab-negative,
as in not his,
but get this.
The wife's 911 call was because
he was choking her in her sleep.
Claims he doesn't remember
doing it.
Because he was sleep-killing.
I think the parasomnia claim
is bullshit.
He lied to cover up what he did,
just like he lied to the ex-wife.
We don't find the victim,
he just comes off
as paranoid.
We do, he's already established
his defense.
That Lloyd kid burned you,
gets away with shooting
a school buddy,
you start taking out everybody
who walks through that door?
Quit projecting on this guy.
Uh, I would hardly say
Lloyd burned me.
And haven't you got a lawsuit
to lose?
Sounds like it's time to have
another talk with Mr. Basada.
I'd love to, but I got a legal
catastrophe on my hands here.
Dutch boy's gonna have to
screw this one up without me.
I guess I'm on my own?
I could use the diversion.
You okay?
What's wrong?
I just got a call
from rios.
He says he needs safe passage
out of the country
for himself and two others
late tonight.
Something big
must be going down today.
I haven't heard any lip-flapping
on the street.
I've been thinking
of turning myself in.
Deal with this the way that
I should've from the beginning.
You've done nothing
but try to protect your brother.
Don't worry.
I will keep you clear of this.
This is my litter box.
I'm not worried
about myself.
But why is it that people
like Pezuela walk around free
while you're
falling on your sword?
Because I don't have
any other options right now.
Because I did wrong.
You always have
other options.
Let's say you were gonna help
these guys with this task.
I'm not.
I'm just trying to figure out
a way to string them along,
buy us some time.
Time to do what?
If we can deliver rios
on something solid,
we can get him
to turn on Pezuela.
Whatever
they're planning today
sounds like
a perfect opportunity.
And if we don't figure out
what they're up to in time?
Vic, I can't have any more blood
on my hands.
We'll never let it come
to that.
Now, just call rios,
tell him that you're trying
to get his paperwork together.
Meanwhile, I'll find out
why he's in such a rush
to leave, okay?
Yeah.
I'm gonna take care of you
on this.
Señor rios.
You give lube jobs
dressed like that?
You have information
for me?
Witnesses made two of your boys
for the Robert Martin killing.
Same two guys who dragged
a couple of Salvadorans around
like tin cans on a limo.
Are these the same two guys
you plan on using
for our thing tonight?
Half the force is already
out looking for them.
Make sure
they can't be found.
They won't be.
How's your exit strategy
coming along?
How are your boys
skipping town?
That's not your concern.
With my badge on the line
and Pezuela about to be
my only paycheck,
you bet your ass
it's my concern.
Call has been made.
I'm not gonna do this dance
after every question.
How is it being handled?
I received confirmation that our
new identification is being drafted.
Satisfied?
Be at the armo junkyard on
bradwell, little after 9:00.
Everyone will be there?
Everyone that counts.
You put one of them
in the ground...
you better make sure
you put them all there.
Anyone having better luck
than me finding these assholes?
South side door-to-door got me
nothing but blank stares.
Byz lats
are in the dark, too.
How'd the takedown go?
Asshole dad sent something
and almost canceled.
So I'm gonna have to push that
other thing a little bit later.
Uh, show me which locations
we have left to hit.
I don't think this other thing
can wait until later.
Why not?
You know the cholos, right?
Just tell them
to push an hour.
What if Rezian gets cold feet
because of these changes?
It's a couple of hours, man.
Which is it?
One hour or a couple of hours?
All right, fine.
I'll make sure
our Mexican proxies know
the meeting has been pushed,
but make sure you and the armos
are there on time, okay?
I wouldn't miss this
for the world.
Okay.
I was grabbing sophia,
not choking her.
I was asleep when I did it.
That's not what you told
your wife.
In fact, you told her you didn't
remember what you did.
I didn't know what was happening
at the time.
I was embarrassed.
Let's, uh... talk about your trip
to the convenience store
a month earlier.
I was asleep then, too.
I was. I swear.
I have a disorder.
It's called parasomnia,
Jeff.
And if you'd really had a problem
this severe these past six months,
I think you'd know what
the proper name for it was.
I wasn't really diagnosed.
And yet it's your excuse
for everything,
and yet you won't see
a doctor about it.
You're a recovering alcoholic,
Jeff.
You'd hurt someone
while drunk last night
and still be
accountable for it.
It doesn't mean
that it isn't true.
It doesn't.
You want to know
what I think?
I think the demise
of your marriage
was making you
feel powerless.
Being naked in public was a way
to get that power back.
In truth, you like making people
experience discomfort.
Most exhibitionists do.
That's the rush.
Until it doesn't work anymore.
You amp it up.
Attack someone.
I think you probably
got into some kinky sex.
That would account for
the rope burns on your wrist.
Only last night, things went
a little too far.
She got scared.
So you silenced her.
Unburden yourself, Jeff.
You did a bad thing.
Don't make it worse
by lying about it.
I'm not lying.
Just tell us
who the victim is.
I never...
I never meant to hurt
anybody.
I swear,
I'm not a bad person.
Why don't you leave Mr. Basada
and me alone for a moment, Dutch?
I ran rios
through the database at I.c.E.
Yeah, there's nothing.
There was nothing.
But today, I ran him again,
and he was flagged.
They put him
on a federal watch list.
Bank accounts, travel,
and surveillance.
What kind of surveillance?
Camera cops documenting his
whereabouts and contacts, 24/7.
Audio, too?
I don't know.
Vic, if he gets grabbed,
I'll be the first name
out of his mouth.
I need to turn myself in now
while I still have some control.
Turning yourself in might clear
your conscience for a few hours,
but it's not gonna stop
what rios has planned.
And if he thinks
you're a burden,
he's gonna disappear
for good.
I can arrange a meet
to give him the fake ids
and arrest him there.
That way, I can turn myself in
with him.
You still could get him
red-handed, get you out clean.
What's done is done, Vic.
I'll never be clean of this.
Feds are running visual
surveillance on rios.
Could be audio, too.
Shit.
Photos
of me and rios chatting
on the same day
this thing goes down?
It's gonna be hard
to deny involvement
when we arrest him
for the armo hit.
Do we call it off?
If letting rios and his shooters
slip through the cracks
means my family being safe,
that's worth
going through with it.
It might delay us
getting Pezuela,
but at least we get Rezian
and his crew members
who knew about me
and the money train.
And shane, finally.
I'll call you.
Who told you this?
Believe me, it's solid.
With the feds watching rios,
he's of no use to us.
Find a way
to get a message to him.
Tell him to stay clear
of that junkyard, too.
I'll have his men
do the job without him.
We have to assume that whatever exit
rios has planned was compromised.
Got to find another way
to get these guys out.
Understood.
You said earlier that you were
embarrassed to tell your wife
that you were asleep
when you tried choking her.
Why?
It's hard to explain.
Try me.
Well, it's disgusting.
That I did that
in my sleep...
shows those feelings
actually exist some...
somewhere in me.
It must be difficult.
That moment when you awoke...
and she said what you did
while subconscious,
I'm guessing that's a lot of
shame with that loss of control.
Must be tiring, too,
having to defend your actions
no matter how unacceptable
it may seem to other people.
I thou...
thought about hurting sophia.
I wanted
to make her pay for...
for trying to take
my daughter away.
That's understandable.
I know you must love
your daughter a great deal.
Who thinks that about...
about the mother
of their own child?
I thought about
other things, too.
I don't know why.
My brain just goes places.
Like where?
Remember that... story
about the football player
in the news last year?
He got in trouble
for dog fighting.
Put the female dogs in a box
to keep them trapped
so the male dogs could
have sex with them for breeding.
They called it
the rape stand.
I don't know why,
but I...
I couldn't stop thinking
about that.
I started to wonder
whether I could build
one of those for women.
I even made some sketches.
What normal person
would do that?
We can figure this out,
Jeff.
And...
whatever you have to tell me,
the faster we can resolve this,
can maybe even save whoever
you attacked last night.
I get these flashes.
Blond hair and... young,
I think.
I see her screaming.
I think
I wanted to kill her.
You're doing fine, cammy,
just fine.
You got six cops
protecting you.
I'm scared, shane.
Iook, you're not scared, baby.
You're brave.
Okay, this is almost over.
What time is it?
He's not due
for another 10 minutes,
but let's keep the chitchat down
in case he's early.
You're good with her.
Hey, look,
I was wondering...
would you tell me
what happened that night?
I thought Lem told you.
He did.
It's just...
I-I've been replaying it
all in my mind all this time,
what I can remember,
at least,
and I just can't understand how
I'd do something like that.
We got a 16-year-old girl out
there who's scared to death.
Maybe this isn't the right time
for this, you know?
Picked a bad day
to come out of hiding.
I need to tell her
I'm sorry.
Yeah, that should make it
all better, right?
You killed her mom,
two brothers.
You almost killed her.
Promise me you'll tell her
I'm sorry.
Please.
I'm sure she knows I mean it.
You know what, buddy?
Sometimes it's too late
to apologize,
no matter how much
you mean it.
Now, do the right thing, Gary.
Confess to all of it.
Maybe I'll tell camille
you did that.
Nice collar.
Yeah, old-style strike team,
right?
Yeah, a long time coming.
I need a minute.
Okay.
Good job.
Yeah, thanks.
Need that guy's booking slip.
His lawyer called.
Rezian get the money?
As far as I know.
Okay, just... get there early
and make sure he stays calm.
I know what to do.
I just want to make sure that
we don't miss out on a payday.
That's all.
You won't, man.
Okay?
Listen, I was wondering
if you'd be cool
with me stopping by
this weekend.
I'd really like
to apologize to Mara.
That's not necessary.
I'll pass it along.
Iook, shane, I'd really, really
like to talk to her in person.
I need to try to make some peace
with myself over all this.
Iook, I appreciate it, tavon,
really.
I just don't think that Mara
will be too comfortable with it,
man, honestly.
Yeah, sure.
Sure, I understand.
I mean, hey.
After all, she might not have
her iron ready this time, right?
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It's like I said, man.
I've been thinking about that
night for a long time now.
And I...
I could remember
almost everything...
everything
except for hitting Mara.
You want to know why I can't
remember that one thing, shane?
Because it didn't happen.
Did it?
You must've gone through that
windshield harder than you thought.
You lied to me!
And then your ass used Lem
to cover it up
so you wouldn't get
in trouble.
And I'm guessing it wasn't
the first time
that you had these guys
cover your ass.
What's wrong?
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Ain't got nobody here
to get your back.
But now I know
who you really are.
And so do you.
Hey.
Thought you were headed
to the junkyard.
I am.
I, uh...
I just forgot something.
Iook, you know what?
Um...
maybe I've been
looking at this thing
from my side
this whole time.
Maybe you guys
would be better off...
you know,
with a fresh start.
Without me around.
It's just that, uh...
I don't know
that we'll ever be able to put
all this shit behind us, man.
Really.
So, when this is done,
and your family's safe...
if you want me
to transfer out, I will.
You do what you need to do,
but...
Ronnie and me,
we got no ax to grind.
Okay.
Okay, I'll, uh...
I'll see you
on the other side.
Can you believe the balls
on that guy?
Hey, superstar.
How's the canvassing going?
No one's seen these shooters
or even heard of these guys.
Splitting up
has gotten us nowhere.
The three of us should
roll together as a team.
See if we can shake things up
that way.
I wouldn't mind coming.
I'll see you there.
Hey, give me a minute?
You come to raid
the evidence locker?
Here.
I've only been taking them
for a week.
I just wanted
some peace of mind.
I'm exhausted, Vic.
And I know I am not doing
the best job
of handling all of this,
but it's the best
that I can do.
Those kids
mean everything to me,
and I don't care how many times
Cassidy screws up.
I will never give up on her.
Never.
So, please...
don't try to take them
away from me, please.
Corrine, I'm not gonna try
and take the kids from you.
How could you even
think that?
We need to figure out
a new plan?
I know you, Vic.
I don't have the energy
to raise these kids
while I'm fighting you, too.
I'm begging you.
You think my first move would be
to rip the kids from you?
That's who you think I am?
We both know who you are.
Just please don't dodo it.
Victim is Fiona perski, 34.
Was found in a dumpster.
How far away
from where we found our guy?
A few miles.
He walked all the way without
anyone seeing his bare ass?
No, it just means
he knew what he was doing.
Drove away from the scene,
got undressed to sell his story.
Stabbed five times.
We're running some tests
on the blood.
But if you recognize her
as the woman you remember,
you'd be doing yourself a favor
by admitting it now.
Jeff, do you remember
what you did to her?
I'd like to call a lawyer,
please.
We got to stall
about five more minutes.
We got to pull shane
out of there, man.
What?
I can't do this.
Vic, it's done.
It's all set up.
We're never gonna get another
chance this clean.
I don't care!
It's not too late.
We still have a choice.
Do you think
that shane gave Lem a choice?
I'm not shane.
Don't answer that.
This'll just take a second.
Hello?
Hey, baby.
Can you do me a favor?
Now's not the best time.
Can I call you back later?
I just need you to stop by
the pharmacy
and pick up Jackson's prescription
on the way home tonight.
Yeah, sure, honey.
I got to go.
I'm getting another call, okay?
Okay. Bye.
I said no phones,
no distractions.
Give it to him
or we're leaving.
I see any calls to Armenia,
I'm coming after you.
Hey, there, it's shane.
Leave a message.
Something's wrong.
Shane should be answering
his phone.
Hey, Ronnie, didn't, uh...
didn't shane tell you
he was gonna be seeing
the armenians today?
Yeah, I think so.
Did he say where?
No. No idea.
Maybe we should roll by
little Armenia anyway,
see if we get lucky.
Captain was pretty clear
about wanting us to stay on task
with the shooters.
Shane should be
answering his phone.
Plenty of reasons
he might not be.
We're looking out
for one of our own.
I'm not gonna sit back
while a team member falls
off the map in a red zone.
This is taking too long.
You trust this seller
of yours?
If Vic says it's solid,
it's solid.
Trust me. We want this over
as much as you do.
You know what?
I'll take a look around.
He's still not answering.
Can we pick up the pace
a little bit?
One tango 13...
shots fired in the area
of 5959 bradwell avenue.
Isn't the armo junkyard
right around there?
No further.
Code 2.
Anyone else?
We just got here.
Shane.
Sorry, I'm late.
I, uh... forgot to sign
tavon's arrest report.
Had to... stop by Hollywood.
No problem.
I'm just glad you're here.
Where the hell did you get
those Mexicans, man?
I almost got
my dick shot off.
I just got some late intel.
I tried to call you.
Yeah, Rezian
took my cellphone.
Jesus Christ, shane.
Thank God.
Yeah, no shit.
I'm still shaking.
I don't see any money.
Iooks like our Armenian
problem's solved, though.
At least your family's safe.
Found a victim
for our naked guy.
We already got her.
Captain's working on
a confession now.
No, the mission cross
just called.
Says they have a blood match
for a girl.
Says she had a run-in
with a naked man
after leaving a bar
late last night.
I had
a few too many maitais.
I felt sick,
and my friend took me outside
to get some fresh air.
But I tripped on the curb,
and I smacked my head
into a fire hydrant.
Suddenly, he just came
running up to us.
Did he say anything to you?
He just stood over me.
He kept grabbing on my arms
to pull me up.
He was, like, naked.
So, I mean,
he was a freak.
I just shoved him off me,
and I ran back to the bar.
Did he try to assault you at all
or act inappropriately?
No.
He just gave me the creeps.
Officer!
Help me open this door,
please.
Oh, shit.
Call an ambulance!
Vic.
Didn't want to wake you.
You didn't.
What's wrong?
I just wanted to come by
and tell you, uh...
you're safe now.
I, uh... I let Carlson go.
It's all over.
It's just you and the kids.
Nothing to worry about.
Really?
Get some sleep, Corrine.
You've earned it.
So the city is countersuing
against my pursuing
legal recourse
for getting hurt
on the job.
Negligent lawsuit
or some bullshit.
And then my bitch-dyke lawyer
won't take the case
without a retainer,
but I can't afford the retainer
without winning the case.
Nice legal system, huh?
You gonna eat that?
You know, Steve,
someone died here tonight.
Yeah, well,
the guy sounded like a nut job.
Maybe, but I missed it.
I couldn't close Lloyd,
either.
Having a bad month.
Happens to the best of us.
I did my best work when
Claudette was my partner...
because she challenged
my assumptions.
Forced me
to prove my theories.
For better or worse,
you are my partner now.
And I need the help.
Okay?
Yeah.
Sure.
Hey.
You okay?
Someone
should call the wife.
Tina put in a call.
Maybe we should, uh...
talk about what happened.
I'm going home, Dutch.
Where you been?
I been looking for a place
to hide $100,000
where Vic won't find it.
$100,000?
My God.
Where'd it come from?
It's a consolation prize.
For what?
Vic and Ronnie
tried to kill me tonight.
What?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Yeah, they set me up.
It's sheer luck
I'm even alive right now.
And, you know...
you know
what the worst part is?
Is they think I'm too stupid
to even realize it.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com