Previously on "the shield"...
Guillermo Beltran...
the Guerrero drug cartel
head of security.
You heard Vic turned in
his badge yesterday?
That leaves me to be
your most important instrument
in the Guerrero cartel
investigation.
We're not sure you're valuable
to this investigation.
Just give me some time to get
cozied up to this Beltran guy.
You want to prove yourself
to me?
I never want to see
Pezuela again.
Beltran sent me
to kill you.
Lucky for you,
I work for Olivia Murray.
I'm gonna need you
to give me back her file
before I can bring you in.
We have to convince Beltran
that I took out Pezuela.
A colleague of yours
committed suicide tonight.
That means there'll be a hole
in your organization.
Where do I submit
an application?
Shane Vendrell hired you
to kill Gardocki?
Why does Vendrell
want you dead?
Vic thinks that Shane was
waiting at his place last night.
There's a reward waiting
for anyone who can deliver him.
Your cop buddy's paying 10 g's
for your head, ese.
You got almost 100 grand
in there.
That's more than enough
to keep walking.
As punishment for the
shit you tried to pull today,
there is a written confession
of one of your many sins
on its way to the Barn,
addressed to claduette Wyms.
Since you caused us
to lose all of our cash today,
you're gonna replace it.
We got to figure out a way
to put a hundred grand
- in Shane's hands by tomorrow afternoon.
- I'm gonna run.
Give me one last shot.
If I fail,
we'll both run.
Mara,
this is Claudette Wyms.
All I want from this
is Vic Mackey.
Corrine's working
with the police.
Think Mara
changed her mind?
Does anyone want
any coffee?
Uh, thanks, but no.
Hello.
Put on Claudette.
She wants to talk to you.
I'm glad you called.
My husband's given Vic
a 5:00 deadline
to come up with $100,000.
Okay.
Corrine is supposed to hand
the money to Shane
by the fountain
in Hollenbeck park.
I appreciate you
working with us.
Promise Shane won't
get hurt.
I promise.
'Cause I know how some suspects
wind up dead getting booked.
You are going to make sure
that every cop in that park
understands that Shane
going after Vic and Ronnie
was self-defense.
So, he'll cooperate
with us?
I can get him to cooperate.
But he's gonna have to
get something in exchange.
I'll do everything I can.
That's not good enough.
You need to guarantee
that he'll get a light sentence.
Otherwise, I will blow this
whole thing out of the water!
I will work it out
with the D.A.
Just make sure
he's treated okay.
That's beautiful.
That was beautiful, baby.
We just walked Vic and a bag
of dirty money into a bust.
We never have to worry
about that prick coming after us
ever again.
The only problem
with getting Vic arrested
is that we lose any leverage
to negotiate a deal
if we ever get caught.
Well, that's why we absolutely
can't get caught,
'cause I'm not going
to prison.
And I'm sure as hell not
gonna let you end up there.
When Vic makes contact
with you,
you're hearing all this
for the first time.
You go along with it
reluctantly.
Don't sign on too easily.
Believe me,
having a problem with all this
won't be a stretch.
I don't want you wired
for your initial meet.
Vic's a master
at smelling a setup.
But when he hands over
that money,
we'll be recording it.
How does Vic not figure out
that I set him up?
We'll play as if he's been
under surveillance for a while.
We'll go
through the motions
of arresting you
to sell your cover.
I don't like this.
I mean, what if Vic finds out or
something goes wrong with Shane?
We will take
every precaution.
You came to us
to get Vic out of your life,
to close the book on him
forever.
Let's do that.
How does somebody
get witness protection?
You'll have to testify.
That's not gonna happen.
Like I said,
Vic can never find out
that I helped put him in prison.
It's his own doing.
Then why do I still feel ashamed
about this?
Little overdressed
for your paper route.
Pezuela's grieving widow.
Obit mourns "an international
business guru's tragic suicide."
His shrink should be sued
for not recognizing
the seven warning signs.
Only Pezuela wasn't
suicidal.
Oh, it just goes
to show you...
you never really know what's
going on inside someone's head.
Suicide my ass.
Beltran had him whacked.
The only question is whether
or not he used you to do it.
Hey, whoa, you're giving me
a hell of a lot
of credit there, Dave.
Olivia's not returning
any of my phone calls.
Now you drop a body
in the middle of my campaign?
Well, you were the last one seen
mud wrestling with Pezuela.
You're not screwing up
my investigation
and costing me the mayor's job
with one last scandal, Vic.
Nice to know that justice is
still your number-one priority.
Hello.
Corrine, I need to see you
A.S.A.P. It's important.
I'm on my way to work, Vic.
What's up?
It's not something I can
get into over the phone.
Can you take
a personal day?
What's wrong, Vic?
Meet me by the fountain
in Hollenbeck park.
How soon can you be there?
Vic, this is crazy.
It's gonna be fine.
Just meet me here
at 5:00.
And you're gonna give me
a bagful of money
to give to the guy
who tried to kill you.
So Shane can take his wife
and his kid
and this whole Vendrell
shitstorm out of the country.
What if he tries
to hurt me?
He saved you once
from the armenians.
It's me he wants to hurt,
not you.
Maybe we shouldn't
do this, Vic.
When Shane calls,
tell him he's on his own
or blame it on me.
I...
I just need you to do
this one last favor for me.
You certainly
caught yourself a break...
Pezuela's narrow-mindedness
being cremated
along with the rest
of him.
Narrow-minded how?
I can understand him
being down with la raza,
but 40% of the drug trade
in this city
is black-owned
and -operated.
Never could
get that prick interested
in affirmative action.
Our experience with the blacks
in phoenix, San diego
has never been good.
Well, that's because
you don't have a trade rep
fluent in the culture,
and that's costing you
market share.
You would be
an upgrade, huh?
A white cop
who's made a career
cracking the heads
of low-level gangbangers.
You would be surprised
at how much sense
I've knocked into some
of those heads over the years.
If I was interested...
well, then,
I'd set up a meet and greet
with you and the black board
of directors,
offer to become
their exclusive supplier
below current
wholesale cost.
Year or two,
you'd have a monopoly.
I don't meet and greet.
Sure, want to minimize your
exposure to law enforcement.
I'd be happy to take
the meeting, negotiate terms.
I would need
a substantial security deposit
from the blacks
as a show of good faith.
Of course.
What you need, Mackey?
Well, back in the day,
we had an understanding.
We did?
I don't recall that far back.
Just two dinosaurs
sitting down now.
I need to arrange a meet
with your board of directors.
I got
a business opportunity.
Business? What do you know
about our business?
You and your five-o crew
only swarm on the street level.
Thought it was about time
I started using
my entrepreneurial skills...
go to work
for the other side.
Mm-hmm, so, you come to me
and the board with this
'cause Vic Mackey is all about
the black man rising?
I don't give a shit
about the black man.
I'm just looking to earn.
I'm guessing that's
the first honest thing
you've said in a month.
I'm gonna need to think on this
for a minute.
Beltran's still
taking my temperature,
but he'll come around.
The goal is getting him
to trust you to the point
where you have access
to the cartel's inner workings.
Has he mentioned
any illegal dealings yet?
He's still
playing it quiet.
Pezuela
give you anything?
Besides attitude?
He's an uncooperative shithead.
No worries...
only a matter of time
before I know everything
he knows and more.
I hope that includes
what he did with
the blackmail box and my file.
I turned his world upside down
looking for it,
and still no luck.
Good news is,
with Pezuela in custody,
he can't get to it
to use it against you.
It doesn't mean
somebody else won't.
Iook, I got two jobs...
gathering enough intel
against Beltran and the cartel
to deliver I.C.E.
Their biggest bust to date
and cover your ass
by finding that file.
I intend to come through
on both.
Yeah.
Meet is on.
72 pine bluff, inglewood.
2:00 P.M.
That was quick.
What you think, man?
Men's jail is headquarters,
baby.
Something you need?
This new guy handing out
the mail must be dyslexic.
They keep
mixing up our mail.
When's Danny coming back?
Unis responded
to a shooting.
Victim pronounced
at the scene.
Steve!
Need you, too!
Kid's name
is Cardell Rhodes,
gunned down
outside his house.
Cardell Rhodes?
The football player?
You know him?
Yeah, coached him in
pop Warner. I'm sorry.
I need you and Steve
to get on over there.
But I thought I was still supposed
to be riding a desk? Well, not today.
I've got everyone available
sweeping the streets
ahead
of the presidential motorcade.
Stash houses, dealers,
hookers, the whole nine.
Well, much as I want out
of my forced detention,
Julien's history with the kid
gives him a leg up here.
You're right.
Go with Ronnie.
What's up?
Uh, never mind.
There was another victim,
minor injuries...
he was treated
at the scene.
I'm going back
to my crosswords.
I'll meet you outside.
Hey, Steve. Steve.
I need you to do me a solid.
I took a bedroom tumble
with a woman on the force.
She found out she's not the only
teeter-totter on the playground,
got pissed,
now she's trying
to jam me up with Claudette.
This chick wrote a letter
to Claudette
laying the whole thing out.
Should stand out as personal.
I've been trying
to intercept it,
but now I got to work this case
with Julien.
You know, Ron, you and me,
we've had our friction.
But in a world
of crazy coozes,
trust me,
I got your back.
That poison pantygram
won't hit Claudette's desk.
Thanks, man.
First mail delivery came in...
nothing.
Shit.
Might not come until
this afternoon, maybe tomorrow.
Or maybe not at all. He could
just be screwing with us.
Ah, we can't
take that chance.
Good news is,
you're trapped at the Barn.
Was. Claudette just put me
on a 187 with Julien.
You can't bail?
Believe me, I tried.
How's that other thing
going?
One minute.
I think I see a play
with the cartel.
More on that later.
That sounds kind of iffy.
I don't do "if."
I'm only about "when."
Hey, wake up.
All right, I put something
over here for safekeeping.
You all know
what I'm talking about.
Now, where the hell is it?
Huh?
You think your quality
of life sucks now?
You wait till I get done
with you.
Now, where's my gun?
Huh?
Hey, dog's ass!
I got to talk to you.
Think pink
while you can, hero.
You die now amongst the
righteous and the urine savior.
It's not loaded, pigpen.
I've arranged
the trade summit...
all the Senior management.
Just need to know
how much weight you can provide.
It's a tempting opportunity
to eliminate the competition
in one fell swoop.
Absorbing them into
your corporate structure
means less waves,
more profit.
Pezuela was here for how long
and he never moved
past the byz lat level?
Pezuela.
Pezuela
was a waste of clothes.
But he did manage
to renovate this place
and build a few others
to store our product...
over budget
and behind schedule.
You're gonna fill
this whole place with drugs?
The blacks...
they understand the terms?
They will.
Disagreeable people.
Well, they've gone through
some shit over the years.
I'm gonna be walking
into an adversarial situation.
You got a few guys
I can borrow?
You forget, huh?
My background
is professional military.
Cardell and I are talking,
he dives on top of me,
pulls me down.
Then I hear gunshots.
Kid saved my life.
How'd you know Cardell?
I'm out here
on a recruiting trip.
Cardell was my prize get...
had him all but committed.
He was on his way to a heisman,
had a special talent.
Yeah, his field vision
was one of a kind.
That kid had eyes
in the back of his head.
I coached him
a while back.
You guys vet these kids
pretty thoroughly.
Any problems
in his personal life?
Enemies?
Look around.
Shit you have to put up with
to get a bcs bid...
take a banger to brunch.
- Rhodes was affiliated?
- No way.
I had to get permission
from the shot caller
just to get a sit-down
with the kid.
I'll talk to his mother.
He was a child of God.
But I don't
have to tell you that.
You knew my baby.
Do you have any idea
who might have done this?
Why would
anyone want to hurt my baby?
No!
Hard to understand
why the good lord
would let something
like this happen.
I see it every day,
all day.
Tests my faith,
believe me.
Mister,
faith is all we got.
I lost my son
last year, too.
He was killed
in a drive-by.
Sorry to hear that.
So, they're saying
that all this happened
because Cardell was
running around with a gang.
You think that's what
this is about?
No.
Here's my card.
If you hear anything,
give me a call.
Recruiter says Cardell
was repping acorn park.
How in the hell does he know
what goes on around here?
Well, you heard him.
He had to have a sit-down with
o.g. S just to talk to Cardell.
That wasn't Cardell.
I knew him.
I get your history
with the kid,
but we got to look
at everything.
That kid was the closest
thing to a hero
this neighborhood ever had.
And nothing would make me
happier than to be proved wrong.
Let's chat
with the warring factions.
You get with acorn park,
and I'll discourse
with spook street.
You're using
the I.C.E. Sting on Beltran
to scam 100 grand
off of Beenie Spears' guys?
Hail Mary,
but I don't know how else
to come up with the money
to buy off Shane,
given the time frame.
Playing both sides like this
is crazy dangerous.
How long before Beltran
or the board
figure out
they're getting jacked
and this thing goes nuclear?
I only need to keep it together
a couple of days...
enough time
to get Shane ghost,
walk Beltran into a jackpot
so I.C.E. Can take him down
in exchange for giving us
an overall deal and immunity.
Jesus.
I got Billings
back at the Barn
intercepting Shane's letter...
nut-job plan.
The wheels are coming off
the whole goddamn thing.
I'm on the way
to this fund-raiser.
I could really use some backup
that speaks inglés.
Can't. Claudette's got me
hip-deep in some shit.
Okay, no worries.
God damn it.
You know, you don't have to be
on the stakeout
if you're not feeling
up to it.
If you have
to take me there
on a damn stretcher
with I.V. S running,
I'll be there to take down
Vic Mackey and Shane Vendrell.
You need help
finding something?
I'm looking for my medicine.
It was here a minute ago.
Um, is this it?
Take it easy.
How's Vic
gonna get the money?
Somebody could get hurt
or worse.
You wanted me?
Vic been in communication
with Ronnie at all today?
Ronnie's gotten a couple
of calls. Don't know who.
We're moving on intel
that we're pretty convinced
will give us Shane Vendrell.
We have reason to believe
we're gonna be making
another arrest...
Vic Mackey
for aiding and abetting.
If you're free
of the other case,
I'd like you involved.
I'll make myself available.
Just let me know when.
I just want to give you
a heads-up
so that you could
mentally prepare yourself
to throw bracelets
on your former colleagues.
Also, Ronnie and Vic
might be planning something.
We don't know what.
They were your teammates.
It's pick-a-side time.
If I get wind of anything,
you'll be the first to know.
Good. I'm also borrowing backup
from rampart.
I'd like you to take point.
Is any of this
gonna be a problem?
Not at all.
Changing suppliers
benefits us how?
Lower cost,
unlimited supply,
highest-quality product
on the market.
We've been
with the same wholesaler
since before
you had a cowlick.
This meth came
from pure Mexican ephedra,
cooked up
in a state-of-the-art laboratory
by a team
of PhD chemists.
Clean
as a virgin's whistle hole.
And a lot cheaper than the shit
that you're getting.
You sure you want an undercut
on your price on the street?
We pass.
But you haven't even, uh,
sampled the blow.
We got love for Beenie.
Only took this meeting
as a courtesy to him.
We got too much history
with our connect
to just go astray
for some cop...
a peckerwood cop at that.
I lay out a proposal
with enormous financial upside
to you people
and you just dismiss it
out of hand?
Why don't you take a look
outside that window?
That's what's in your future.
I asked my boss
for a little backup today.
That's what he sent.
Your spik boss wants
to throw down, bring it.
'Cause I see two trucks eight
deep with Mexican gardeners.
They hear a shot out there,
there'll be an rpg
in this living room
before I hit the floor.
Put that shit away.
Let me tell you
about the landscaping job
those gardeners did.
In rosarito beach, Mexico,
last year,
them and a convoy of amigos
rolled up on a police station,
murdered everyone inside.
47 people...
cops, dispatchers, janitors.
That was my, uh, spik boss' plan
for gaining market share
in the area.
Now, if they're willing to do
that to their own countrymen,
imagine what
they're willing to do
to a handful of, uh,
stubborn soul brothers.
And you think I'm a peckerwood.
This ain't no proposal.
This is a gank and grab.
I'm just trying
to increase the peace
and promote racial harmony
through economic opportunity.
Buy-in's 200 large.
I can wait if you need
to run to the atm.
Jefe.
Wrong way.
Señor Beltran's
in the other direction.
I'll catch up to you.
I got an errand to run.
No, jefe.
Our instructions are
to be your seguridad.
We got to get the money back
to Beltran right now.
He's waiting.
Oh, shit.
Uh, I'm gonna need
some gas...
gasolina.
Yeah?
Code red...
third and alvarado.
Gas station, men's room,
trash can... there's a package.
You know what to do.
Highest priority.
Oh, you get your ass over here
as fast as you can,
and I mean soon.
All right, sweetheart,
daddy has to work late.
I'll see you later, okay?
Love you.
Kids are terrific, huh?
You got any?
Sí. Cinco.
Vanbro!
Yo, docki, my man.
What's good?
What's up, black?
Hey, I heard what happened
to the strike team, man.
I guess you must be
the last cat standing.
Upright and breathing.
You signify your own path,
you won't get caught up
in other folks' bullshit
and tribulation.
That's how I do.
And look at me, standing strong
and doing the damn thing.
But, vanbro, what is up with this? Huh?
You used to have talent.
Hey, that's nonrepresentational
art right there.
It worked for basquiat.
It'll work for vanbro.
Take it. Nah, nah. We
just want information.
Suit yourself.
What do you hear about
the Cardell Rhodes shooting?
Rumor going around
the cats making book
got pissed at youngblood
for point-shaving against dorsey
the other night.
Cardell was involved
in gambling?
I mean, I wouldn't want to
speculate on that for certain,
but little man
with all that speed
stepping out of bounds
with all kinds of daylight
numerous times?
I mean, you got to wonder
about the spread.
Where did you hear this?
Fourth-hand knowledge.
Don't really have
any specific names.
You might want to check
with my man deuce
down there on bronson,
next to the laundromat.
Appreciate it, though, you keep
vanbro name out your mouth.
Stay black.
Detective Billings.
Anything yet, Steve?
Oh, shit. Right.
Uh, let me look.
Deuce says
it wasn't point-shaving.
Cardell's been playing it smart
all season...
stepping out of bounds
to avoid cheap shots,
saving his knees
for the next level.
All the bookies making the line
knew that.
They factored that
into the spread.
No, no mail yet.
Just keep an eye out,
okay?
Let's head back to the Barn
and regroup.
No, hey, I want to talk
to that recruiter again
as soon as he gets back
from scouting that kid
down in San diego.
Polk's a victim, not a suspect. Exactly.
Maybe he was the target.
That's worth
a conversation.
I got to go get
a prescription filled.
I'll meet you
back there, okay?
Hey, yo, my man!
Hey, man, you goddamn deaf,
homey?
What are you looking
to get into, gabacho?
None of that goddamn
stepped-on shit.
I ain't
seen you around before.
Yeah, well,
I'm changing slangers, man.
I'm looking to bring my business
to you.
You want to get paid
or what, man?
'Cause I'm looking
to get low.
Let me see
what I'm working with.
I'm gonna hold a dub, cuz.
You ain't no cop!
You need to work
on your street skills.
Now, you're gonna walk me into
that stash house off normandie.
I ain't doing shit for you.
I'm 16.
Take me in,
and we'll call my moms.
I don't have her number.
Hey, bro, why you tripping?
Aah!
I can do this shit all day.
So, what's it gonna be?
You doing what I tell you
or blood coming out your ears?
How much firepower inside?
Enough to shred
your bony, white ass.
How much cash?
Huh?
8 to 10.
Had a good couple of days.
All right,
let's get this done.
What the hell happened?
Beats the shit out of me.
It was up and slanging
two hours ago.
You ain't a cop.
I was right.
Yeah,
you're a goddamn genius.
We got a runner!
Hey, freeze!
Police!
100 grand...
earnest money.
Don't smoke, don't drink.
A man of few vices.
For me,
it blurs the edge.
The edge is where we live...
all of us, all the time.
People try to convince
themselves otherwise,
it's just an exercise
in self-deception.
A philosopher.
Former cop.
Same deal, less horseshit.
Things come easy
for you, huh?
Are you one of these
"hard work
is its own reward" guys?
I had grandparents
like that.
They died miserable
and broke.
You've accomplished a lot
in a very short time.
You need to understand
something Pezuela never did...
you got an action hero
on your payroll.
Okay.
She's in position.
I've got a visual.
Tell me she's gonna get through
this without cracking on us.
I'd feel better if we could
communicate with her.
The wire's risky enough.
I don't want Mackey
sniffing anything.
Ronnie's here.
Vic's not with him.
It's Gardocki.
What's he doing...
recon for Vic?
Julien, you have a visual
on Mackey?
Negative.
Where's Vic?
This is for you.
Well, Vic was supposed
to be here. Is he all right?
He's fine.
Something came up.
Come on, Corrine,
get him talking.
Is that what I'm supposed
to give Shane? Good girl.
I got to go.
Thanks, Corrine.
Ronnie as his goddamn
errand boy.
Mackey's a no-show.
On my signal, prepare
to apprehend Gardocki.
No, no,
Mackey might be watching.
You hold your positions
until you've got a visual
on the primary.
We've got Ronnie
dead to rights.
We've got Gardocki on tape.
We can file on him later.
We haven't got
the real bastard yet.
Stand down.
Do not engage the target.
Shane's an hour late.
This doesn't feel right.
Maybe Mara got cold feet,
spilled to Shane.
Claudette,
they're not coming.
What if Vic figured out
that I was working with you?
That's why he sent Ronnie.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, she's losing it.
Why didn't you give me something
so I could hear you?
Somebody talk to me!
Okay, call it.
Yeah.
All units, abort.
10-4. copy that.
God damn it!
So, now what?
Bottom line...
we got to hunker down
while they sweat the streets
on account
of the president coming.
You know, the real danger
is that they know you think
like a cop,
so they're expecting you
to hit certain targets.
But they don't know
how I think.
If you've got an idea on how
we can score some cash, baby,
lay it on me.
The safe
at the real-estate company.
Come on.
No, there's a lockbox where
the coordinator keeps checks
before they send them
to escrow.
Mara, if I can't
knock over a stash house,
what makes you think
we're gonna walk into a bank
and cash a bunch
of stolen checks
made out to a goddamn
escrow company? Shh.
They also keep the checks
for apartment rentals...
first, last, security deposit. So?
So, most of the time,
they're cashier's checks.
Folks in the hood
don't have checking accounts.
Well, I can pass
a cashier's check, no problem.
But I don't know
about cracking in no safe.
No, no,
I have the combination.
I've been filling in
for the assistant manager
out on maternity leave.
So, I'll go in,
grab the checks, and go.
Hmm?
No, it's too dangerous.
The only people that'll be there
are the cleaning crew.
You don't think they know you're a
fugitive already? And they know me.
They're illiterate,
and they don't speak english.
I'll go in.
I don't want the mother
of this little girl
in harm's way any more
than she already is.
Ha!
For a guy in a close race,
you'd think you'd have
more pressing matters
than to stalk me
for my vote.
I've been looking
into the circumstances
surrounding Pezuela's
"suicide."
And here I thought
you'd miss the prick.
Interesting fact surfaced when
I reached out to my contacts
at the coroner's office.
Cruz Pezuela ate a bullet
less than 24 hours ago,
yet his body
is already back in Mexico.
Why waste time
taking out the garbage?
A suicide in L.A. County,
the coroner's required
to perform an autopsy.
But he never
had the chance.
That's because
Pezuela isn't dead,
is he?
I got someplace to be.
We can debate the eternal
qualities of the soul
at another time.
Is Pezuela testifying?
What's he saying about me?
I played my cards.
You played yours.
I took the pot.
I win.
Now step away from the table.
Game over.
No, I still have
one more card to play.
I will go
straight to Beltran
and tell him that Pezuela
is alive and testifying.
I will wreck
this investigation
before I let you and Olivia
cut me out.
What makes you
more afraid...
being denied your legacy
as the great Brown informer
or it coming out
that your campaign is financed
with dope money?
We have a common cause.
Are you asking me
to be your friend?
I'm asking that we both
respect the other's end game.
Hey, how goes it?
Fine.
Claudette had you out
on something?
Checking a lead.
Something on Shane?
Um, turned out
to be nothing.
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Um, Polk's back from San diego.
I'm gonna go see him.
You got that covered?
Yep.
Great.
What about drugs?
Our intel says
the cartel's a major supplier
across the southwest.
Beltran never mentioned
any drugs.
This guy's all about banks.
The scale of this thing...
the infrastructure,
transportation, security...
looks like they're planning
to wash half the Mexican gnp.
Chaffe wants to find a way
to embed a couple
of our agents with you.
It's time for me to pull my guy
Ronnie Gardocki into this thing.
We'd rather use someone
from our end.
This isn't the time to play
"getting to know you."
Ronnie and I
have a short hand.
Also, I need Beltran to feel
like he's got reach
into the local
police department.
Vic, I can't say yes
to that.
That's the way
it's got to be!
Meanwhile, this is yours.
Pezuela's blackmail file
on you.
I just found it.
If I'm honest...
I was tempted
to hold onto it...
pull an Aceveda,
use it to squeeze you.
Thank you.
I just gave away any leverage
I ever had on you.
Now I'm out of a job,
and I'm cozying up
to the most dangerous man
in the Mexican cartel.
And even if I fool Beltran
long enough to stay alive,
I've got no future
I can plan on past tomorrow.
I need a place to land.
Can I count on you for that?
Excuse me, mi amigo.
Hey, uh, mi amigo?
¿qué?
¿sí?
Buenas noches.
Let's go... in the back.
Silencio.
Silencio. Silencio.
Shh. Be quiet. Be quiet.
In the back. In the back.
Silencio.
Hey, come on. Let's go.
Let's go, right there.
Shh! Be quiet!
Shh!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
Silencio!
On the floor, damn it!
On the floor!
Hit the deck, damn it,
right now. Down.
Down.
Abajo. Abajo.
God!
All right.
Right 32, left...
hey, shut up!
I'm trying to think here!
...27, right 60.
Ahh.
Okay.
32 left, 27 right, 60.
Shit.
Okay, all right.
Anyone moves, um, muerto.
Muerto.
Mara, come on.
I got...
bring him.
Just bring him. Come on.
Let's go! God!
Hurry up!
God.
What?
That goddamn safe.
Okay, I dialed right 32,
left 27, right 16.
You have to pass 27 twice,
remember?
Stop on it the third time
and then right to 16.
I don't know
what that means.
Oh, God.
Here. Take him.
Um, hey.
Hey, Jackson,
be still, buddy.
Can you just
be still, okay?
Dámelo, por favor.
What?
Dámelo.
Hey.
Okay, I got it.
Gracias.
De nada.
So?
How'd we do?
$5,000, give or take.
That'll work.
Shane didn't show up
today?
What happened?
I was worried.
Job interview came up
at the last minute.
I had no choice.
Job interview?
Yeah, a position opened up
with the feds.
I really have a shot...
good benefits.
Obviously,
we're gonna need it.
Corrine, I am so sorry
I left you on the hook today.
I did not want
to do that to you.
We sure as hell would have heard
if Shane got popped.
Anything happen at the park
that might have spooked him?
No, just me
and the crackheads.
Listen, please just get this
out of here, okay?
It makes me nervous.
Keep it.
Shane might call back.
And if he doesn't,
use it for the kids.
Where did this money
come from?
All that matters now
is it's in good hands.
Please tell me
when this is gonna be over.
Soon.
Hi, dad.
Hey, kid.
How are you?
Cassidy, you need
to get to bed.
You have an early morning
tomorrow.
I just want to show dad
my math test.
I got a 98%.
You got a 98%.
That's great, kid.
You're really pulling it
together, aren't you?
Thanks. I'm trying.
Vic.
What?
She earned it.
Okay, dad.
Iove you.
Iove you, too.
I'll fax you a list of
all the I.a. Kids we've met with
as soon as I get back
to dallas.
That could be helpful.
Just know that, usually,
a sit-down for me
involves a coach,
overprotective mother,
sometimes
a family minister.
With Rhodes,
I had a meet-cute
with some inked-out thug
in baggy clothes and a grill.
Got me wondering
if offering him a scholarship
was even a good idea.
For all we know, that thug
could have been there
as a show of respect
to Cardell...
make sure he wasn't
taken advantage of.
By who? Me?
I walk into a place like this,
I'm Mr. Opportunity...
money, education,
chance to get out
of a shitty environment.
That cuts both ways.
In your job, you destroy more
dreams than you make come true.
That earns you
some enemies.
Tell me about it.
Last year, I had a mother come
after me with a baseball Bat
after we took a pass
on her kid.
Same block as Cardell.
How random's that?
Thanks for bringing verna
down here.
I didn't want her
coming down here by herself,
picking up
her boy's things.
Did they find
who did this?
Um, not yet.
Never found the gang member
that murdered your son
last year, either.
No, they didn't.
You were at home at the time
of today's shooting?
I was there watching my stories
on television.
Did you hear shots?
No, I, uh...
I heard the siren, though.
And then my neighbor came
knocking on the door.
If you care
about your friend,
you'll help me
solve this case...
save verna a lot of pain.
All you got to do is
tell the truth. Of course.
You knew darren Polk was
in that truck,
didn't you?
He the same man
that recruited your son?
He promised dion a scholarship,
a car, money...
all kinds of things.
And then it just, what?
All falls through?
Your son was shot and killed
a little while after that.
Six months. Shot my baby
in the head at a bus stop.
Mia, as a mother
who has lost a child,
tell me that you didn't know
he was in that truck.
With them dark windows...
...I didn't...
I didn't see Cardell.
And that's the truth.
That man...
he destroyed my boy.
And now he's lying
in the dirt
when he should be running
for touchdowns.
Shit.
Hey, I was just about
to go upstairs and take...
did you get it?
Called I.A.D., got the paperwork
started on Gardocki.
We'll be ready to hit him
with an indictment
when the time comes.
That's fine.
Why don't you go home?
Because I've got work
to do.
I, uh, talked to Danny.
Now that Vic's not
around here anymore,
I think she's ready
to come back...
help you take care
of things again.
Seeing the bottom of my inbox
is not a priority.
We'll get Vic.
At the moment,
I'm a little bit more concerned
about you.
You know, we can't
expect justice out there
when we don't demand it
in our own house.
Okay, so,
now you're taking on
the problems
of the whole world?
Everything's not
under your control.
You don't like the way
I'm handling this case,
you can always leave.
Olivia smelled Beltran's musk
on me... made her wet.
We deliver,
I.C.E. Is gonna take care
of both of us, I know it.
If we close the deal
before Shane gets caught.
He and Mara just
have to stay invisible
for another day or two.
What do you think of Shane
taking a pass on that bag
of free money?
He was just
giving us busywork...
keeping it so we couldn't
look for him.
Jesus,
this is cutting it close.
Hey.
A little ulcer
never hurt anyone.
Say hello
to my friend Ronnie Gardocki.
Mucho gusto.
He speaks highly of your
character and your abilities.
He taught me
everything I know.
Boo-Ray.
It's been a minute.
How's the family doing?
My peoples
is doing good.
Glad to hear it.
Iook, uh, I need your help
on a little business matter.
I'm tapped out.
Come back another time.
Oh, look, man, come on, you know
these are as good as cash.
All the favors I did for you...
looking the other way
while you ran your little
weed operation out the back.
Come on.
You owe me, homey.
I will make it up to you.
You got yourself
in a spot.
Yeah, don't believe
everything you hear.
This is 2 grand light.
50 cents on the dollar.
That's a pretty steep vig.
Iook, it's unacceptable.
Give me 75 cents,
and we'll call it even.
I got enough trouble.
I got a kid. You know,
I got another one on the way.
Walk away, white man,
or I dial 911.
Put the phone down.
You're not a snitch, man.
Giving up a killer cop
ain't snitching in my hood.
It's the best I could do.
Anyway, it's a down payment
on us getting out of here.
I thought you said
this guy was your friend...
that he owed you big-time.
Baby, come here.
Moving forward,
I guess we both need
to embrace the reality
that neither one of us
has a friend in the world...
...except each other.
Transcript by www.1000fr.com