Previously on The Shield...
We'll order some chinese food.
Got a great bottle of wine
I've been waiting to open.
Is this a date?
Do you want it to be?
Looks like Moses finally made it
to the land of milk
and underage honey.
Lem, I'm sorry.
But I had to, right?
We're gonna find out who did this.
And we're gonna kill him.
Maybe he didn't do it, man.
- If it wasn't Guardo, who else was it?
- Look at him, man.
If he had a name, don't you think
he would've told us by now?
Just means he was acting alone.
- Who's jacket?
- This is Captain Hyatt.
He used to be a rising star at INS.
He's ours starting next week.
You're not adding anybody to my team
that I don't have approval of.
He's not your addition,
he's your replacement.
Come on, boys. Let's go.
- Don't shoot.
- Hold your fire!
It wasn't me. They got guns in there.
- All right, give me the cliff notes.
- No read on how many inside.
Can't get a visual. No one's talking.
Any shots fired since you got here?
Couple. Sounded semi-automatic.
Vic, Kevin Hyatt, your replacement.
Hey.
Looks like I found the fun.
Gang shoot-out.
Couple of shots fired.
Called 10 minutes ago.
Stay down.
Both of you.
Go, go, go.
Uh, did he just give me a timeout?
Hey!
Let me see your hands!
Now, asshole!
- Shit.
- Jesus christ.
One of them niners shot us up
then took off.
- Aah...
- Put some pressure on that, sweetheart, ok?
Hey! Get your hands on your head!
Right now.
Get your hands on your head!
I can't, man. I can't move.
Hey.
I was getting splinters in my ass
sitting on the bench.
Figured I'd chip in.
Ash!
This one's not colored up.
Keep him away from the one niners.
I got it.
C'mon, he had Lem's gun.
It was in my trunk.
Probably just pulled it out.
Tossing you out is bullshit
Doin'it for some cop in diapers.
Probably squash this.
How about some official introductions.
This is a little out of hands right now.
Shane Vendrell, Ronnie Gardocki,
this is Kevin Hyatt.
- How's it going?
- I'll take that.
Listen, I heard about your boy.
Lemansky.
I lost a partner on the border 3 years ago.
It's a bitch of a thing, and I'm sorry.
Lem was more than a partner.
Well, of course he was.
- Listen, ride with me.
- You got it.
I'll give you a rundown on the one niners
on the way to the Barn.
I reassigned units to enforce
the one niner injunction.
That should keep things to a low boil
until we know what we're dealing with.
Having Hyatt around here
might be a good thing for you.
Give you a chance to show
you can play well with others.
It's a little late in the game
for me to win miss congeniality.
What do you think?
**** of the biz lads heard that
the one niners were having a square dance.
Decided to crash.
Hot shot hero learned street gang names
on his ride in. Likes to show off.
I was about to tell Vic
that you're gonna bring in your own guys
eventually expanding the team.
What about Shane and Ronnie?
Let's keep them on.
I'd like two teams here under
Hyatt's supervision.
There's not a lot of people
who can do this job.
I know.
That's why I set up an appeals panel
to review your retirement.
They meet in two weeks.
If the panel's convinced
that we need you...
Acevedo will never support that.
He's got a lot riding on the barn.
And if you're not in charge,
he'll feel more comfortable.
But if you want me to make that case,
you have to show me
you can make it work.
Listen, I gotta deal with this.
And I'll make it work.
I gotta say, I'm a little confused.
I lied to Mackey.
In 3 weeks, he's gone. Period.
But if he knows that, he'll start working
some angle. Looking for loopholes.
I'm trying to keep him
on his best behavior.
Especially for your sake.
Well, it's kind of cold.
- What do you know about Vic?
- Rumours mostly.
I know he's made an assload of arrests.
And I know that two guys on his team
got dead in the last 3 years.
Another went head-first
through a windshield.
So if I'm banging down doors, I better
make sure Mackey's where I can see him.
You'll be just fine as long as
he doesn't have a problem with you.
Now I've taken care of that.
Have a seat.
How about I start putting my
own team together now?
Swing the numbers my way a little.
We do have good cops around here.
I'll think on it.
- Everything ok?
- I'm fine.
No, no, no. Stay.
Maybe you should all hear this.
I feel really stupid for saying
this out loud, and
normally, I don't even believe in this stuff,
but I woke up this morning,
and i felt like I was given a message.
What are you talking about?
I had this dream last night.
And we were all there
in our old backyard
having a barbecue,
only it wasn't our old yard, you know,
it was this beautiful place
by this precipice.
And Lem was there.
And he was wearing his usual jeans,
but he had on this pinstripe shirt,
and his hair was shorter,
and he was younger
like when I first met him.
He was wrestling with one of you guys.
I don't remember which,
but then he wanted
burgers for you guys.
Really well done, no pink.
The thing is,
when I turned to give him the burgers,
he got really mad,
and he said I made them all wrong.
I'd never seen him like that.
He was shouting.
And then you came over to him,
and you said,
it's all right. You'd learned to eat
your burgers like that.
Then he got really calm.
And he said...
Ok.
It's all gonna be ok.
And then he stepped off the cliff,
and he didn't go up or down,
he just disappeared
into this, like, haze.
I know this sounds crazy,
but I think it was Lem.
I think he wanted me
to tell you this story.
Maybe it means that everything
is going to be ok.
Right?
Transcript: SW
[www.subway.com]
Synchro: Pasbel, ::emicad::, Javawarrior2003
:: Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]
let it go, man. It's just a dream.
Corrine knows we've all been hurting lately.
Thought it would give us some confidence.
Just go with it.
He didn't disappear up in the sky.
He disappeared sideways.
How is that comforting?
He lost friends today.
You lead with that. Don't show sympathy.
Gang bangers see weakness,
they tighten up.
- I've done gang work before.
- Well, this isn't the valley
or the rio grande.
This is the majors.
Listen, you're not ready for this.
I know immigration isn't a cakewalk...
I saw shit on that border you can't imagine.
4 years worth.
I understand.
But all those mexis, too smart
to get picked up, we got them.
Plus black gangs, russian mob,
salvadorans,
asians, armenians and more,
all in the same square mile.
What do you want me to say?
You're right.
So, you know, get me ready.
All your dead buddies
were in the same one niner rack as you.
Altered just like yours.
You starting up a new faction?
Either you found a new set,
or you're trying to jump out.
Both are punishable by death.
My guess is you wanted to get out.
In which case, you're not a bad guy.
But I'm looking at you now, man,
with your locked jaw,
your pissed off stare.
- And I'm a black man, and you're a cop.
- So picture me with a puppy.
Give you that warm, fuzzy feeling.
Look, man.
Banging ain't my life no more.
I've been straight for 4 months.
Then explain the .22 you were carrying
when we popped you.
It's a little thing we call
self defense, man.
If you're so squeaky, why were you and
your boys meeting up with the one niners?
I need to know about Vontez, man.
If he got out.
Les autres victimes portaient
were wearing one niner colors.
Now start talking.
So Vontez is the leader of the revolution.
And Vontez say, oppressors are oppressors.
It don't matter if you black,
or you white. And you already know
how much one niner soldiers make.
Hustling all day, all night.
They all might as well be just
flipping burgers.
That's oppression.
Breaking ties with the one niners
over drug money ain't exactly noble.
We quit selling.
That's why we quit paying.
Banging doesn't come with an out clause.
So what was your escape plan
for getting out alive?
Just a bunch of boys from the block.
We all jumped out together.
Safety in numbers.
How many?
It was about 7.
I mean the meeting was supposed
to be us settling up
with them making sure
everything was solid.
Why the guns?
We ain't stupid, man.
Anyway...
Niners, they shot first.
And the revolution begins.
Stop it! Stop it!
You with me?
Yeah.
1-Baker-23, code 6.
Hands up!
Get your hands up!
What do you want? What do you want?
I do nothing! I do nothing!
Are you all right, hey.
1-Baker-23.
- I need a paramedic for an assault victim.
- Hey!
I was watching that.
- Hey, get a life, asshole.
- Got one, officer.
Vontez Carter.
He's a low level one niner.
I sent him to Corcoran about a year ago
for dealing and possession.
This kid, he's more of a thinker
than a slider.
He spent his 8 months reading Malcolm X,
Huey Newton.
As soon as he was released,
he started pulling his buddies out.
They stayed under the radar
- till they stopped paying taxes.
- That meet this morning was a set up.
Get the rebels in one place.
Take them all out at once.
Look, these kids are trying to
get their lives straight.
Make up for their mistakes.
- How many of these revolutionaries are there?
- Minus the two that are dead
and the one in interrogation,
four. All in the wind.
With a hundred or so one niners
after their heads.
Got a plan?
Find Vontez and his boys,
get them off the streets for starters.
Yeah? Thanks for weighing in.
First thing we gotta do
is have a sit down with Moses.
He's the head of the one niners.
See if we can't convince him to back off.
We can introduce him to the new guy
while we're at it.
Meantime, let's get the ball rolling
and find these kids.
Keep me informed.
Shane's still a bit raw about Lem.
It's nothing personal.
- Hits everybody different.
- Yeah.
- How are you doing?
- I've been better lately.
50 bucks says Mackey and the new guy
get into it by the end of the day.
No, thanks.
Lowe and Sofer interrupted
a rape in progress.
The victim's Graciela Sanchez.
She's in the system.
She ran away from her fourth
foster home 2 months ago.
She's at mission cross.
I love the smell of underage
sexual assault in the morning.
I didn't mean that the way it came out.
Julien and Danny are riding together?
For the moment. The suspect's been
apprehended at the scene.
- What about Tina, she out sick?
- No. She transferred out.
Finally make your move?
Scare Hanlon and her
bikini briefs out the door.
He say cops would be coming.
Come on.
We're all out back.
all the shit we cleaned up for Moses,
we shouldn't be talking to this asshole
in front of Hyatt.
You think he's gonna admit to killing kern?
For christ sakes, hold it together.
And good. 'cause I got a shot
at keeping my job.
There's an appeals hearing forming.
I'll fill you in later,
but for now, help me be helpful.
Mackey's lackeys.
We're almost done, but I got a minute.
And who's this?
Detective Hyatt.
But you can call me detective Hyatt.
You're gonna be seeing a lot of him.
Let me save you time asking.
I gots none for you.
Low low shit ain't my concern.
You boys set up a shooting gallery
at a chicken shack.
If one of my lieutenants is having problems
with his quadrant, he solves it.
I got zero knowledge.
Might be good for you to let Vontez
and his boys go their own way.
I mean, what's 7 soldiers
in an army full of assholes?
You fall for that Vontez
the revolutionary shit?
Just a scam to take
more cut for himself.
Hey, you got an eye cramp?
Thought we told you to stay away
from the tweener pussy.
You be having a good day now.
Graciela's tox report
came back with extremely high levels of
ghb. She was practically in a coma
when we got her.
Date rape drugs.
21st century chivalry in action.
Yeah, we've gotten lazy as a society.
I'd write a song if you slip a girl a mickey.
Anyway, her rape kit reads from a to z.
In addition to fresh vaginal tearing,
she showed signs of significant anal trauma.
There's something else.
Jesus.
Before he raped her?
Appears to be one or two days old.
What do you think it means?
There's no point in lying, mehud.
Two police officers
caught you raping her.
- I screw her, but I no rape her.
- What does "go home" mean?
So what happened?
You get a hard on,
you slip her a roofie at some club,
huh?
You give drugs, she go sleep?
I find her. She look like hooker.
I say, give 20 bucks for quick bang.
She nodded ok.
Either way, at some point,
she became unconscious.
- What? I'm supposed to stop?
- Yeah!
Why do you want her to go home?
I give her 20 bucks in her pocket.
Look and see.
- He didn't do it.
- What?
- He didn't cut her up.
- Great.
Vontez framed this himself.
Said it reminds him of where he's been
and don't want to go again.
Let us get your son somewhere safe.
He's better off on his own.
- Hey, hey. Vic.
- Shit.
Get inside. Keep your head down.
What's up?
What's up, man?
Get out of here, assholes.
Niners been driving by here
every 5 minutes all day acting tough.
My boy's gotta hide from them and you
just the same.
Tell us where your son is.
Vontez can't do this on his own.
Oh, he won't have to.
See a lot of people think my boy
is a hero.
Look, please...
If you want your son to be a live hero,
not a dead martyr, have him call me.
I just want to talk.
If I'd have known
I was gonna see you today,
I would've worn that little top you like.
Thought you were gonna stop
seeing that asshole.
I know.
It's just hard to find the moment.
Well, then try harder.
I don't want him touching you.
Ok, baby.
What do you want?
You.
But I need Moses' lieutenant
who's cracking down on Vontez.
Lieutenant's Angelo Owens.
But he's just doing this
'cause Moses came down on him.
I mean, them boys,
they been friends
they whole lives.
Where's Angelo?
Blue house on Warnol.
By the gas station.
Look, don't get me
in trouble with the niners.
Ain't nobody messing with you, tilly.
They're the ones in trouble, ok?
End it with Moses. Today.
I need you to do that.
For me.
Ok?
One niners are all clamped down.
I want to settle this in-house.
What about the families?
Somebody knows where these kids are.
The niners have got them too scared to talk,
or they don't know where they are.
I want to send a message.
Somebody wants out of a gang,
we're here to protect them.
Find Vontez and his friends.
Anything you need to bring them in safe,
you got it.
Hey, man, where's Shane?
Said he had some C.I.
Somebody from when he was in vice.
Shane was in Vice?
That explains a lot.
Vice guys are pretty intense.
Just picture Shane with a puppy.
It'll give you that warm, fuzzy feeling.
That's Hyatt's interrogation technique.
No shit.
What, are you trying to get answers
or pussy?
Whatever it takes, right?
Glad to see everybody's having fun.
Of course, Lem's still dead.
Anyone else give a shit about that?
- Hey, we...
- Shut up, man. You don't belong here.
In this room.
2 minutes of breathing your air,
I could tell you're not
half the man or cop Lem was.
I got thick skin, man,
but you're starting to chafe.
You guys just act like
everything's fine, man.
Like shit just moves on, right?
It does.
Yeah?
Not for me.
I actually give a shit that he's gone.
Uh, lieutenant's Angelo Owens.
He's got a location over on Warnol.
Good. Thanks.
My C.I. says Angelo set up the shootings,
but Moses didn't give him much choice.
I just, I didn't want him back.
And what's with that guy, man.
I mean, he's not Lem, you know.
This is what's real, all right.
You keep this up, I'm not the only one
around here that's not gonna have a job.
You.
Maybe Ronnie, too.
You know Lem wouldn't want that.
In a couple of weeks,
this appeals panel
is deciding
whether to send me packing or not.
I'm gonna need this Hyatt on my side.
If he says he needs me, I got a shot.
Yeah, I hear that.
What happened with Lem...
Slate's clean.
We made that right.
Right?
You think killing Guardo
- made any difference, man, Lem's dead.
- Oh, jesus.
Corinne said he's pissed.
- She said she's never seen him like that.
- Stop.
I can't deal with a goddamn dream right now.
Look, just find this lieutenant.
Let's save who we can save today.
Mackey.
Hey. You wanted me to call.
- Vontez, where are you?
- Don't matter.
I gotta handle this.
Look, man, let me put you
into protective custody.
Moses even knows I talked to the cops.
Niners ain't going back to the table.
Moses wants you dead. Where are you?
Do you read Dubois?
Do I... No.
He wrote about the path
of honor and humanity.
I die,
I still got that.
More than most people got.
- Just wanted to tell you stop looking.
- Vontez.
- Don't feel like being found.
- Come on, man. Vontez.
Shit!
So the site's coming along.
You're making quick time.
Thanks to the support from the
housing commission.
A few more, gracias,
construction hurdles.
It's an easy sell.
It's a worthwhile project.
Noticed something else
you've been selling.
A cleaner, kinder Farmington P.D.
There was a bad apple.
He got deep, he got himself killed,
police committee wants
the community to know
that the rest of the players
are still here to protect them.
It's tough to buy
when you've got 12 dead mexicans
slaughtered in that house in san marcos.
And no arrests.
Those murders were handed off to
robbery/homicide. Farmington's out of it.
RHD doesn't give a shit about
a dozen illegals.
They did, this thing
would be solved already.
I'll make some calls.
See if I can light a fire.
Couple of the guys
from the crew came to me.
Said they've heard rumors that
a salvadoran gang called
"Larasa Juanaca" was responsible.
I'll pass it along.
If the Farmington p.d.
Were to crack this case,
it would go along toward
allaying your constituents
belief that police don't care.
It would reflect well on you.
You should've been a politician, Cruz.
I leave that to the experts.
You remember that runaway came in
6 months ago? Claimed she'd been kidnapped?
- Rings a bell.
- I dug up her taped statement.
- Oops.
- Sorry.
It's ok, I...
I thought I'd have some privacy in here.
you can use my office anytime.
Sure.
Princess Gaines. Ran away.
Came back a month later
mom found blood on her pants,
asked about it, princess said
she was abducted, anally assaulted,
and held captive for two weeks.
he was white.
Or latin.
Yeah, he was a latin dude.
Can you tell us anything else?
Not too much.
Had me drugged or something.
Or something?
So the last thing she remembered
was begging outside of a burger place.
Next thing she knew, she woke up in a
strange room, man was holding her prisoner.
It would really help us.
Any little detail.
He kept saying, "go home now. Go home."
And then this man just... let you go?
I'm here ain't i?
One morning, i just wake up in the street.
- What'd you do then?
- Did what he said.
Went home.
- We didn't believe her.
- Yeah.
She didn't take a rape kit.
Toxic screen came back negative.
Case didn't add up.
So this guy targets runaways.
Uses GHB
to keep them out of it just long
enough to do what he pleases.
While telling them to go home.
Like good little girls.
So graciela got double pumped.
This creep does her in the rear,
and left the vaginal cavity
intact for mehud to spill
his load in the alley.
The cutting's an escalation.
- He'll go further next time.
- I'll call the mom.
Bring princess in.
So your lieutenant set up a slaughter house
this morning without any
encouragement from you.
The streets|are full of liars.
Ain't my fault somebody
says i got fingers in this.
You're a two striker.
All i need is one good bust.
You gonna plant some shit on me?
You wouldn't do that, right, Mackey?
Leave me out of options.
We stay on you, we'll get you
fair and square.
Might take a couple of months.
But you can bank on it.
Shoot.
Hey, fellas.
What say we trade some names.
You two, come here.
Vontez is the one caused me problems.
He dies.
The other ones... I'll pull the order
as soon as vontez is cold.
That's what i'm offering.
Now what do i get for my generosity?
What do you want?
Back off my boys.
I don't want to see no popo for 6 months.
2 months. Me and my guys stay away.
I don't control the black and whites.
You control them on me?
But you pull the order on the other three
right now.
- Lover's quarrel?
- Moses had a proposal.
Sacrifice vontez, the other three stay safe.
So what's stopping us hauling his ass in
on conspiracy charges right now?
I took the deal.
At least, that's what he thinks.
I teach you all my tricks
on the first day,
what are we gonna do tomorrow?
You're looking for princess gaines.
16.
According to her mother,
she ran away for a second time
couple of months ago.
Start with runaway row.
Shelters, fast food places, huh?
Thank you.
Um, i'm sorry about, um...
Busting in on you.
I know it's all perfectly natural.
Don't worry, i'll keep them
locked down from now on.
Wow. They put hanlon on a poster.
Oh, great.
She gets to be miss farmington, huh?
And i'm stuck with her p1 duties.
Let's ride.
Take one home tonight. Do it in private.
Right now we got the
files of every latin sex offender
in a 10-mile radius to go through.
Where'd this come from?
Captain told me to put them up.
Well, yeah, but where did it come from?
Do i look omniscient?
Hey, what's the deal with the poster?
The all new faceless cop fighting bogus O.T.
She's out, tina's in.
Posters, public appearances,
the whole bit. She's citywide.
But tina wanted to be a detective.
This is straight from the chief's office. She was picked
from the P.R. Photos  they shot the other day.
Ok, thanks. We'll be right down there.
Dutchman, graciela's awake. We got a sketch.
One baker, 23 roger.
Do you have a description of the vehicle?
- Do you copy?
- Shit.
Can't afford a babysitter that speaks english.
- One baker 23.
- We're approaching at 12th and effie.
- Roger that.
Vontez was your friend. Your soldier.
Him, marlon, jayson, they're all still
out there trying to escape your hit.
Fine way to treat your friends, lieutenant.
What do you do on birthdays?
I don't want to.
Make the call, angelo.
Put an end to this right now.
I didn't push the button.
I can't unpush it.
Moses is laying all of this on you, man.
So why don't you tell me something different.
Give me moses. We can work out a deal.
Cop says deal, you go to jail.
Call off the hit.
You can still make this right.
I do what you want,
i'm a dead man, and my family, too.
Life is just the way life is.
- Who is it? Is it vontez?
- Daniel billup.
- You're sure?
- Positive.
Goddamn.
I guess moses wasn't planning
on keeping his end of the deal either, huh?
I guess not.
One down, three to go.
Hey, step back. Sir, step back.
- Move it. Come on.
- I don't want to see this shit like this, man, damn.
Daniel was on a peace mission.
- Vontez sent him back to the table.
- Yeah.
Someone sure shoved the peace pipe
right back up his ass.
- I don't want to go over there.
- No, man, that's my nigger!
Damn!
Damn, man!
Give him to me. Hey, ray.
You see this?
That's what's gonna happen to the rest of your friends
if you don't help me find out where they're holed up.
One niners took his cell phone.
Any call daniel made, they're gonna know
about it.
Only a matter of time
before some one niner
finds that person.
My man vontez can defend himself, man.
He might be a revolutionary,
but he ain't bulletproof.
We find him, or the one niners leave
the rest of their bodies for us to find, ray.
How many funerals you want to go to?
Bag him.
Look at me. Ray.
You've done a lot of bad things, ray.
Sold drugs, stole money. Murdered.
You do this one last
good thing for your friends.
Vontez would've called
his cousin akil, man.
He'll know where they at.
All right. Take him.
Let's find this akil.
Police! Open up!
Oh, the hell with it.
Hands on your head! Don't move!
Hands on your head!
Sending your cousin on a little trip?
Where's vontez?
The mask was red.
Anything else you remember?
Maybe he took you somewhere?
You remember something about his hands?
He have an accent?
Detective wagenbach.
Nurses say she needs a gentle touch.
You're the gentle touch, i suppose?
- I happen to be a wonderful father.
- Two weekends a month.
I'll be outside.
Sometimes i think humans need
a subspecies to categorize these bastards.
Hey, i saw vic this morning.
He's doing better.
I, uh, i hear he's handling the situation
with his replacement well.
- What, they filled lem's spot?
- Vic's replacement.
Some guy named hiatt. He's taking
over the strike team when vic retires.
That's not for years.
Department's pushing him out at his 15 mark.
It's in, like, a month.
So, how's hiatt working out?
He's nothing like vic. I love him.
The dead mexicans dutch found.
They were killed with a machete?
Several machetes.
Based on the number of body parts.
I got word today from a community back channel
that a salvadoran gang did the job.
You heard of larasa juanaca?
I didn't realize they'd come this far north.
It could be the murders,
or the juanaca's response to the influx
from the prison closures in mexico.
Salvadorans putting out the unwelcome mat
for the mexican competitors.
It occurred to me that hiatt's background
in ins makes him the perfect candidate
- to get to the bottom of it.
- Maybe.
If he was at robbery homicide.
It's there's.
I had the case transferred back to the barn.
You said you weren't gonna pull any strings.
Come on, handled correctly,
this could be the big p.r. Win we need.
Or a crime stat's nightmare
that shuts this door forever.
You solve this, that's a dozen murders
in the win column.
It just might be enough
to put your quarterly stats over the top.
Keep these doors open.
Man, this wire shit, this is straight up
dirty snitch, man.
Blame akil.
He'd given us the info we need,
we'd be off saving your friends by now.
He's set.
Once akil gives you the location where
vontez is hiding, give the signal.
Don't make it obvious though.
He gets suspicious, we're shit out of luck.
- Got a sec?
- Sure.
A possible man for your team.
Take a look at his jacket, see what you think.
Will do.
You know, mackey played moses today.
He let him think he was making a deal.
Vontez dies, the others go free.
It's a smart strategy.
It didn't work,
but it got me thinking.
So far, it seems
that
mackey's usually spinning
three different wheels at once.
Creating the perception that he's willing
to cut a deal. Go off the grid. It's a way in.
Maybe this reputation
has more to do with that perception
than with reality.
Vic is showing you his good side
because it's in his best interest.
Ne soyez pas dupe.
Don't be fooled.
Man, can you get up off me?
Let's see how you sit.
Hey, man. I can walk by myself, man.
Et tu sais t'asseoir ?
Anyway, the poster looks great.
Give me a call, if you want.
Hey. Worked up a profile on our guy.
Single dad, probably had a daughter
disappeared or died prematurely.
Thinks he's teaching his
victims a lesson. Go home.
Good advice. If it
didn't involve kidnapping,
rape, and torture.
Profiling's overrated. Shoe
leather is what cracks cases.
Come on. You just like making
stories up in your head.
Kind of like the one about you and tina.
Fact is, you don't have a shot. Looks
department alone you're a total mismatch.
What, you're such an adonis?
I know the kind of lady
who's attracted to me,
and it ain't tina.
Helping her improve her
skills had nothing to do
- with any interest in her.
- Right.
She happens to have talent.
Even if others don't see it yet.
Face it. You took advantage
of her vulnerability. Just
like our mystery psycho.
Except your drug of choice was power
and the false hope
of career advancement.
That's ridiculous.
You have a reputation, holland.
Chasing mulies, mackey's ex.
Wives of murder victims. I
think a profiler would call that
a pattern of shitting where you eat.
I happen to be devoted to my job. I don't
exactly have time to hit the bar scene.
I want to ask tina out, i will.
You let me know how that goes.
Ramos found princess
gaines. He's bringing her in.
Thanks, paula.
Mom's on her way, too.
Here he's at it again.
Congratulations on getting
another girl ass raped.
I'm sorry we didn't believe you.
At the time you came in, we just
couldn't corroborate your story.
- But that may have changed.
- Ain't no never mind to me.
I cried my tears all out.
I whipped this girl
based on you telling me
she lied.
- And now you're telling me she didn't?
- There's another girl.
Certain details in her story
match what princess
said happened to her.
I told her to go to the
police. Tell them what happened.
I said, the police would help.
We are so sorry, mrs. Gaines. We just
didn't have enough evidence at the time.
Well, that beating i gave
her is on your two heads.
Just ask her what she knows.
I want my daughter home.
Do you rember
any details since we talked to you last?
Wish i didn't.
Anything you can tell us?
What he looked like,
where he held you?
It was a girl's room
only from a long time ago.
How so?
Posters on the wall were all whack.
White boys in these gay poses.
One of them was called,
like, 65 degrees or something.
98 degrees.
Took my oldest to the concert.
Do you recognize this man?
I know it's not much of a sketch.
Those are his eyes.
Ray's got akil chatting.
Shouldn't be long before
we learn vontez' whereabouts.
Little light reading?
Package just came in.
"not looking forward to the 8x10
cell, "fighting for the top bunk...
"but i figure the least i can do
"is come out smarter than i went in.
"send these to me wherever i land.
I'll miss you. Lem."
he ordered these online the night
before he went on the run.
Art, sports, history,
stephen king. Look at this.
"birds of america."
"dreams and what they mean."
so what do you want
to do with these books?
Vontez is a big reader, right?
Well, we're gonna find him.
And the other two.
We're gonna send them
someplace peaceful. Safe.
We're gonna give the books to him.
Corinne.
Yeah, where are you?
What are you doing out there?
All right. I'm on the way out.
Give me a minute.
- You could've come inside.
- I've only got a half hour break
and i don't want everyone in
there to know our business.
Except i guess they already
hear everything first anyway.
The so-called retirement. Oh, shit.
- Look, i was gonna...
- What,
were you gonna send me
a postcard from florida?
I just spoke to the captain. It's
probably not even gonna happen.
What if it does?
I mean, are you figuring
things out, making plans?
Or do you think your check is just
gonna magically appear in my mail?
I'll work it out. I've
always taken care of the kids.
Yeah, i know.
And i see what it costs you.
I don't want that anymore, vic.
I don't want me or them responsible
for all the things you do.
- It's all in the past.
- I hope so.
We've lost enough.
Hey, wire worked. We got a location.
Vontez is holed up with the other two.
I'm not gonna lose my job. I promise.
God, the amount of time i
spend attached to that machine.
I hope this is enough to
get me through tomorrow.
What?
Nothing.
You think i should've
taken my full 6 weeks, huh?
- Be there to feed lee myself.
- I wasn't thinking that.
Come on, julien, you had 9 months
to lay your judgments on me.
I'm not saying anything.
I'm sorry. I'm just so tired.
It beats riding with tina.
I'm gonna get my groove back, i promise.
- Good night.
- Good night, captain.
Everything all right?
Sleep deprivation.
Hiatt's decided to add another
member to the strike team.
I suggested you. Say yes.
- Working with vic?
- Hiatt will be taking over.
It's an opportunity. More money,
more prestige. Making a difference.
Those guys will never accept me.
They won't have a choice. It may
still be called the strike team,
but it's a different animal.
No more bullshit antics.
You can handle this, julien. Say yes.
All right.
Thank you, captain.
New life starts tomorrow. Good luck.
Vontez!
It's vic mackey. I just want to talk.
He's back here!
He's hurt. He was shot this morning.
Clear!
Holy shit.
Vontez. What happened?
He was shot this morning at the
restaurant. You gotta help him.
And you just let him bleed?
He wouldn't let us get help.
He said moses would find us.
He wouldn't even let me tell his cousin.
Niners will come.
Shit, he's going into shock.
Vontez, open your eyes. Wake up, man.
He bleeds out, moses
lets the other two live.
All three of them live.
- Keep your eyes open. Stay with me.
- Need an ambulance
9246 Norton.
Come on, open your
eyes. Stay awake, man.
Shit! Come on. Grab his legs.
- He just called an ambulance.
- Grab his legs, goddammit!
He stays here, he's gone.
Take it easy, buddy. We're
gonna get you to a hospital.
You're gonna be fine. You hear me?
Get these guys to the barn. Let's go!
Stay awake. You hear
me, stay awake, kid.
Hey! Hey, keep your eyes open.
- Stay awake.
- Come on, buddy. Come on!
Your mom wants you to come home, man.
She wants you to stay alive for her, right?
For the revolution.
Shit.
You're not gonna die on me.
I'm not gonna let you die.
We're almost there. You'll be fine.
We need a doctor here!
- A doctor, goddammit!
- Move!
Get out of the way!
Gunshot. He's bad. He needs help.
I'll page a doctor.
Ah, shit.
Corrine. Corrine!
Corrine, i need you.
Lem, in your dream, was there blood?
Your dream was...
In your dream, did lem...
What is it? What's going on?
We're cops. Leave him alone, all right?