- Syd, you can't blame yourself.
- Sure I can.
- Well, don't. She was playing you.
- Maybe she was.
- What were you supposed to do?
- I could have listened.
- She offered to help Will and I said no.
- You talk about her as if you can trust her.
Which we know we can't.
So maybe we could have played her.
If you keep second-guessing yourself,
you're gonna drive yourself crazy.
I keep checking my voicemail,
just hoping Will's called,
told us where he is.
So Carrie and I went out.
It was great. We got sushi. When we got
there, the guy behind the counter,
they were like "Hey". You know,
when we got there. Like they knew us.
- They do that at a lot of sushi places.
- Really?
Anyway, it was great.
We had a fantastic meal and...
- So what's the problem?
- Post-fish, when I went to drop her off...
This is traditionally, classically the time
where I would - or a man would - kiss her,
and, well, I just started sweating.
- How bad?
- Bad. Weird bad. Freak-show bad.
- Did she notice?
- It was like I'd just got out of a lap pool.
- OK, you need help.
- Yeah. With the ladies.
The thing is, it's sort of a catch-22.
- Go ahead. Keep going, I'm listening.
- To feel comfortable around a woman,
you have to have experience. And to have
experience, you have to not be you.
I was almost killed last year and the
doctors didn't think I was gonna make it.
And the thing that I learned
from that experience... Thanks.
Syd. Excuse me. We're receiving intel
on a local top-secret server
- from a source outside the building.
- Who's sending the signal?
Your mother.
- We just got an upload.
- I just left you a message.
It's the DNA string
of the person who was doubled.
Mr Kendall, I'm gonna ask that
as soon as Will Tippin is located,
we bring him in to compare this
to his DNA.
We're verifying the data now, sir,
but it looks legit. Legitimate.
Yeah, I know what "legit" means.
What else do they know?
Did Sydney tell you what the CIA knows?
Or Jack?
I didn't say Jack was involved.
Of course you did. You said in the car,
you mentioned his name.
God, I'm losing my mind.
The CIA doesn't know anything.
That's the problem.
Doesn't make any sense, does it?
The entire CIA,
and they've no idea who the double is.
It just shows you how wrong they can be.
And now they think I'm a killer.
Which I am, by the way.
I've killed people.
People who were trying to kill you.
So what? Does that make it easy? Or...
Francie, I ended someone's life.
Two people's lives.
I'm a killer.
I shouldn't be yelling this.
You're warm.
Hold it.
Hands where I can see 'em.
Yeah, it's him. It's Tippin.
- So tell me.
- We received a file.
A DNA string
of the person who was doubled.
- And?
- Your DNA didn't match.
And there was no Provacillium
in your blood. You've been cleared.
- Thank God for you.
- You're OK.
- What about Francie?
- Francie's been questioned.
- She's at home. She's fine.
- Thank you.
- What I said about not trusting you...
- No, don't worry about it.
I was scared to death.
I didn't mean any of those things.
You know that.
I trust you more than I trust anyone.
I'm sorry about the cell. They're gonna
need you to stay here for a while.
- They've got a lot of questions.
- OK.
And a therapist is gonna work with you
to try to reverse your memory conditioning.
That file, the DNA string.
Was there a name attached to it?
- There was, but we don't have any leads.
- What was the name?
AG Doren.
I'm just so relieved for him.
It's like I can breathe again.
You know where it's fun to breathe?
Santa Barbara. You ever been?
Yeah, I love it. The zoo?
That giraffe with the crooked neck?
No, I mean the beach,
the Biltmore, the food.
- La Super Rica. You ever been there?
- No.
- OK, we're going this weekend.
- Yeah, come on. As if we can go.
There'll be some emergency, some...
See?
Yours.
Yeah? Yeah, practice is over. Why?
No, that wasn't gonna be me.
What do you mean, Markey's sick?
How sick? Weiss, come on, man.
OK, OK. OK. Goodbye.
- I have to go in.
- I'm gonna practise so I can kick your ass.
Really? Don't forget about Santa Barbara.
Yeah, some day.
You received my intel.
Your friend was cleared.
I told you I'd want a favour.
This is it.
266 Kronastrasse, in Zurich.
I've just given you the address
of Sloane's warehouse,
where he's hiding the Rambaldi artefacts.
- That's not why you're here.
- Yes.
It's the only reason.
- I know you're lying, but I don't know why.
- Sydney, I'm here to help you.
Stop being as stubborn as I am.
I knew from the beginning I'd turn myself
in, that I would betray the CIA.
But not you.
I had to be careful.
I needed you to trust me.
But I also couldn't tell you my plan.
Sloane had 23 Rambaldi artefacts.
The CIA had 24.
In order to assemble the device,
they all had to be brought together.
Those are the pieces
in Sloane's warehouse.
You stole Rambaldi pieces
from the US government?
Yes.
By winning your trust, the CIA's trust.
And then, as planned,
I had a proposal to deliver to Sloane.
A proposal that we work together
to take down the Alliance
and raid the CIA all at once.
I came up with a scenario where the CIA
needed to let me use their computers.
I used the opportunity
to learn where the US government
kept its stash of Rambaldi artefacts.
They were being held
at a secret NSA lab in Nevada.
One month later
Sloane had a team raid the lab.
- I never heard of an NSA raid.
- Of course not.
When the time came for my escape,
it was painful.
Because my love for you, for your father,
was not a contrivance.
Suddenly you want us
to have Sloane's artefacts?
Sydney, I know our relationship
is complicated.
But I'm your mother, and I have to believe
that'd be the case under any circumstance.
- Go to Zurich.
- You're insane.
One more thing I need to do...
And I'm sorry for this, too.
- Provacillium to the rescue.
- Thanks. The fevers were getting bad.
So what are we doing with Tippin?
Nothing. For the moment.
Then when am I getting extracted?
I don't know what new evidence
the CIA has, but it's gonna lead to me.
Not necessarily.
If you disappear now,
you'll be a suspect for sure.
What is it?
Allison...
we can't reverse the process.
Markovic's lab was destroyed.
But we're doing everything we can
to retrieve the lost data,
and I'm hopeful that we will find a way
to reverse the procedure.
- I may have to stay this way?
- No. No, we'll get you back.
Look at me.
We'll get you back.
You don't fancy him, do you?
Tippin?
Don't be stupid.
And it didn't occur to you, Mr Brandon,
that a raid on an NSA...
I'm not at liberty
to discuss the details of the Nevada raid.
And I'm not at liberty
to respect the way that you do business.
How many Rambaldi pieces were stolen?
24?
- That's what my mother said.
- I can confirm that number.
And we have to find out about this breach
from Irina Derevko?
The question is,
what is the prudent next step?
She's lying. She has to be.
It's a setup.
Then why show up in person?
It's a big risk.
From what I know of Derevko,
she's loyal to only one person. Herself.
Dixon's right, obviously. I don't know,
maybe this is a valid play for Sloane.
Maybe, but why would
she need us to play it?
Guilt? Her motives may be insidious,
her methods loathsome,
but she is not unfeeling.
I say we send a team.
Proceed with caution, but proceed.
We'll prep to have whatever we find at the
Zurich warehouse brought to the States.
A neutral location.
I propose Evans naval base in Ventura.
- I'll call my director.
- Yeah, you do that.
Sloane may have most of the pieces
to assemble this Rambaldi device,
- but I don't think he has them all.
- The Di Regno heart.
- If the NSA has still got it.
- All right, that's enough of your crap.
Jack, you go along with the NSA here,
transfer the heart to the naval base.
And let Marshall know
that he's going to Zurich, too.
I want him to confirm what we've got,
or not, ASAP.
Weiss, I need you to tell Tippin
we're done with him.
- Escort him to the safe house.
- Yes, sir.
Marshall, we're sending you to Zurich.
It's a research mission.
We believe we may have gained access
to Sloane's Rambaldi artefacts.
Wow, that's fantastic. I mean...
You know who should really go with us
on this mission? Carrie. Miss Bowman.
Because she's NSA,
she works under Brandon,
and she's... would be very helpful.
In the field.
- In the field.
- Please?
- Miss Bowman.
- Yes, sir?
You're going to Zurich.
Plane leaves in an hour.
Mr Tippin, I'm Agent Weiss.
We're all through here. I'm supposed to
take you to where you'll be staying.
Is there a computer I can use here?
The name on this DNA file - AG Doren -
I know that from somewhere.
- I just wanna check it out.
- Sure.
- Thanks. I'm Will.
- Weiss.
- Eric Weiss.
- Like Houdini.
Yeah. Yeah, actually he was
a great-great-uncle of mine.
Get outta here. Really?
Can you do magic tricks?
OK, check this out.
OK? You ready?
- AG Doren doesn't ring a bell?
- No, still doesn't.
Can I access my Trade Roads
while we're here?
Yeah. What's your password?
"Sydney".
- Thanks.
- I considered becoming a magician.
Then I thought to myself
"What the hell am I thinking?"
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- What is that? What's that list?
- Project Christmas.
It's a CIA black-ops programme
from the '70s.
Trained kids as sleeper agents
to be used as future spies.
- What?
- It's a summer camp. There were 20 kids.
Allison Doren was supposed to have died
in a car accident.
This is Kendall.
We've got the Di Regno heart. We're en
route to the naval base. ETA three hours.
Roger that.
OK, we're free of explosives.
You can move in.
- This could be real.
- Let's get Marshall in here.
How's it looking?
I don't know, sir. It's not consistent with
any of the Rambaldi artefacts I've seen.
- I was thinking the same thing.
- Well, then what the hell is it?
Looks like a waffle iron.
It's a setup.
- There's nothing here.
- Give me Jack Bristow.
Drop the weapon or you're dead.
Irina Derevko has struck again.
Based on her intel, we sent in
some of our finest-trained agents,
we took control of a storage facility,
and with the help of a bomb squad
we are now in control
of two dozen rusted kitchen appliances.
Simultaneously an enemy team ambushed
our caravan, they killed two of our men.
And along with the Di Regno heart
Jack Bristow is missing.
- What's our next move?
- We scour every source of intel.
Anything halfway concrete, we move on it.
He had so many brilliant creations.
Rambaldi.
But there was one in particular,
a machine.
He called it Il Dire - The Telling.
The construction consists of 47 pieces.
Classic Rambaldi.
As you know, it took me a long time.
Longer than I thought.
But I've acquired them all.
Including the Di Regno heart.
With your help.
They're in the next room, Jack.
I have a team assembling Il Dire right now.
They say it shouldn't be more than a day.
And then what?
I've seen things, recently.
I've seen what's possible.
There's a change coming, Jack.
Something even I couldn't imagine.
I used to feel sorry for you.
Couldn't you sense it?
That you'd been abandoned.
Left for dead. Disgraced.
I pitied you.
That you needed Rambaldi
to fill the void in your life.
It was like a religion for you.
I didn't expect you to understand.
Then why keep me alive?
Because we're friends, Jack.
- Vous m'appelez d'urgence tout de suite.
- Wann würde die Nachricht anfangen?
Any anomalies?
Were you close to him? Brandon?
I hated him. Which is why I feel so bad,
if that makes any sense.
I'm sorry.
You're sweet.
I see.
No, actually, that helps a lot.
I'm so sor... I'm sorry.
- What's up?
- This is AG Doren.
Allison Doren.
I just talked with her parents, told 'em I was
with NTSB, asked about the accident.
- And?
- It was a bus crash and there was a fire.
But at the time the coroner told them
that their daughter's burns were severe.
- So they never identified the body.
- No.
- Hello.
- I didn't know Sloane would switch crates.
- I promise that.
- Where the hell are you?
He must have known I was going to
double-cross him. Somehow he knew.
- I am gonna find you. I don't care...
- I don't know where Sloane is. Sark does.
It doesn't have to be you,
just make sure someone from the CIA
goes to Välsmakande.
Välsmakande. It's a club in Stockholm.
Sark's gonna be there
at ten o'clock tomorrow night.
How stupid are you
to think I would ever believe you again?
Ultimately, you do whatever you want.
That's what free will is all about.
I've got nothing. You?
We're going to Sweden.
Everyone's blonde.
Keep thinking I see him.
Sark's not here.
As expected.
Your dad's gonna be OK.
I know.
So when this is over,
how do we go on vacation?
- Well, I was thinking about this.
- Yeah?
And I was thinking that we have to stop
talking about it and just book the hotel.
- Just do it.
- Right. We have to think more positively.
- I mean, we're going to Santa Barbara.
- We're going. We're just going.
There he is.
- I don't get it.
- What?
My mother. Nothing. Let's move.
- Freeze.
See, when I have a gun trained on you
I don't just pull the trigger.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Where the hell is my father?
Not a problem.
My loyalties are flexible.
Sloane and your father are in Mexico City.
- Base camp, we're at sub-level two.
- Copy that, Mountaineer.
They're in the basement.
Now what?
The alarm system for Sloane's floor
is located 20 yards down on the north wall.
A grey box with a yellow stripe.
The deactivation code is 1 -1 -5-6-6.
If this intel turns out to be wrong, I will
personally escort you to Camp Harris,
and I won't leave
until you're dead and buried.
Then I certainly hope
Mr Sloane hasn't changed the code.
Mountaineer, there's a grey control box
with a yellow stripe
20 yards down on the north wall.
You will enter 1 -1 -5-6-6.
Alpha team,
we've neutralised the central alarm.
- You're go to enter the building.
- Move. Move.
Jack, it's been assembled.
Sir, there's a tactical team
heading up the stairs.
Pack everything and go. Go.
We'll see each other again, Jack.
Jack.
Tell Agent Bristow I've got her father.
- Equipment's being loaded on the truck?
- Yes, sir.
Go.
- Go after Sloane.
- You get Sloane.
Freeze.
I've shot you before.
I will do it again.
Keep your hands in the air.
- I'm on the roof. I've got Derevko.
- Roger that.
Get off the ledge.
- I'll tell you what you need to know.
- Get off the ledge, now.
Sloane believes he's been chosen
to realise the word of Rambaldi.
But you, too, have been chosen.
- If you think I'm bluffing...
- It's you in the prophecy, Sydney. Not me.
Only you can stop him.
Good luck, sweetheart.
Get down. Now.
I love you.
She jumped.
- Any available agents, get to street level.
- I'm on my way.
She just climbed into a floor
in the middle of the building.
- Which floor?
- I have no idea. 18th, maybe 19th.
I can't tell from here.
Sir, it's been almost two hours.
Home Base, we just found an
elevator shaft pried open on the 19th floor.
We think Derevko's left the building.
Sir, you're not supposed to throw these
like that. You'll break 'em.
- Hey.
- Any news?
- No.
Just trying to figure it all out.
You're the best.
I gotta get an aspirin.
I'll be right back.
You've reached Sydney's cellphone.
Leave a message after the beep.
Sydney, it's me. Listen.
This is gonna sound insane, but...
I just found Provacillium in the bathroom,
and I think that... I think that...
OK, just think about it.
I think that the double is Franc...
Fran?
It was always you?
Allison?
It sucks it turned out this way.
That's it. Get on the ground.
Get on the ground.
Sloane's got the device.
And my mother, she...
Another day.
- So I did it.
- Did what?
- Booked the hotel.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
- You didn't? Santa Barbara?
Three nights, starting tonight. Probably
the greatest phone call I ever made.
- You're a genius.
- Thank you.
So after the debrief
I'll come pick you up.
OK.
Hey.
Hi.
- You OK?
- Relatively speaking.
You?
Tired.
What's up?
- I am so burnt.
- I understand.
You have two messages.
- Where's Will?
- I don't know.
Hi, Miss Bristow, it's Marybeth
from Director Kendall's office.
- I've got him for you, so give us a call.
- Will said he had something to do.
Sydney, it's me. Listen.
This is gonna sound insane, but...
I just found Provacillium in the bathroom,
and I think that... I think that...
OK, just think about it.
I think that the double is Franc...
End of messages.
Want some?
Sure.
I just have to change out of these clothes.
I just remembered.
Francie doesn't like coffee ice cream.
No, she doesn't.
Drop the gun.
Drop it.
Dispatch.
This is Officer 2300844 calling for
connection. Confirmation: looking glass.
Stand by.
- This is Kendall.
- I just woke up in Hong Kong.
I don't know how long I've been here
or how I got here.
Hello?
Get to our safe house in Tsim Sha Tsui
as quickly as possible.
- You remember how to get there?
- Of course I do.
I'll make sure they're expecting you.
OK.
Have they said...
Have they said anything about how
I got here? Do you know any possible...?
They've asked you to wait for information,
until your contact arrives.
- They doubled Francie.
- I know.
What happened to Will? To Francie?
Are they dead?
Will's OK.
What? How?
You...
Sit down.
Vaughn?
We thought you were dead.
They asked me to come back,
to... to explain.
Come back from what?
What are you talking about?
Vaughn.
Why are you wearing that ring?
Syd...
since that night...
you were missing.
You've been missing for almost two years.