OK, I'm in.
Agent Bristow works undercover
with her father, Jack Bristow,
also a double agent with CIA.
Get down.
I guess we'll just have
to learn to trust each other.
Bristow's CIA contact: Michael Vaughn.
My guardian angel.
Her current assignment:
to infiltrate and destroy SD-6,
a secret organisation
dealing in espionage, extortion,
weapon sales, posing as the CIA.
SD-6 has made over $400 million
in arms sales alone.
The sanctity of this agency requires
the sacrifice of some personal freedoms.
This is not about cutting off an arm of the
monster. This is about killing the monster.
Bristow's mother:
formerly Russian intelligence,
recently turned herself in to the CIA.
Mom?
Intel indicates she may still be
an enemy of the United States.
The true loyalty of Agent Bristow's
mother remains unknown.
Previously on Alias:
I want your help to persuade Sydney
not to interact with her mother.
Why?
Because Irina Derevko is an
opportunistic sociopath, who will use
whatever inroads she can make
with my daughter to get what she wants.
Well, I'm sorry, but I am not in the habit of
helping a father manipulate his daughter,
no matter how good his intentions may be.
Sark is looking for a music box designed
by Rambaldi. The box plays a unique tune.
Encoded within the tune
there's an equation.
- For what?
- Zero point energy.
Watch your step. If you fall through the ice,
it'll freeze over in four seconds.
Cooper. Reading four, four tangos.
They're heading for the entrance.
Novak, they're under the ice.
- Sydney, do you copy?
- I read you, Dixon. What's wrong?
Get out of there. Sark's here.
Sydney.
Hi.
The music box that you were sent
to retrieve, Mr Sark got away with it?
Yes.
But after 500 years buried in the Siberian
ice, the music box was corroded.
It practically fell apart in my hands.
It's odd.
- What's that?
- Milo Rambaldi.
He's done this before, many times.
Hiding information inside works of art:
the clock, the sculpture.
Hm?
But this time he chose to bury
one of his most important innovations,
the formula for zero point energy,
inside a music box.
You're talking about an inventor
who lived 500 years ago.
Anything regarding Milo Rambaldi
seems odd to me.
Well, what's unusual isn't how he hid
the information, Sydney - it's where.
Why would Milo Rambaldi
go to the unimaginable length
of having catacombs built in Siberia,
only to leave his music box
exposed to corrosive elements?
Another Rambaldi mystery.
So, do you think Sloane suspects you?
That I used the inhaler to corrode
the music box? No, I don't think so.
Sloane made sure I knew how relieved
he was that I made it back safely.
I went home and took a shower
and came here.
Good. By the way, you should know,
Siberia was a complete success.
When you activated the music box,
we recorded it. It's at Langley for analysis.
- So we got the intel and Sloane didn't.
- Neither did Sark.
What?
The information my mother gave us
helped us again. That's all.
You know, you can talk
to me about your mother.
I know that doing that is
harder for you than you make it seem.
- Well, it's my job.
- Vaughn, she killed your father.
- Yes. Thank you.
- You don't have to pretend with me.
- And you don't have to withhold.
- All I'm saying is that it's unfair.
Maybe so, but I certainly didn't
join the CIA looking for fairness.
After everything she's done to you,
are those things you could ever forgive?
I don't know.
Yeah, well, your father
doesn't share that ambiguity.
He's meeting with
Assistant Director Kendall right now,
and he is lobbying to have
your mother taken away.
As long as she's helping us in the war
against SD-6 and the Alliance, she stays.
- Did you even read my report?
- Yes, of course.
Well, why are you completely
disregarding what I wrote?
- Great job in Siberia, Agent Bristow.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
I agree with what you wrote,
that on more than one occasion,
your mother has provided
crucial intelligence to the CIA
to the detriment of SD-6.
And it would even appear that her actions
have kept you out of harm's way.
- Dad, that's a fact.
- There's another fact.
Nothing that woman says or does
can be taken at face value.
Her motivations are strictly her own.
Now that your dealings with your mother
have taken on an emotional component,
- I'm concerned.
- Don't be.
I'm more professional than that.
Every one of our discussions
has been specific and mission related.
You told her about your school play.
- You heard me tell her I was a turkey?
- Yes.
You were watching me.
Dad, I have enough spying
in my life to worry about...
What I've been watching is you making the
same mistakes with that woman that I did.
Sydney, she's someone
you've idealised for almost 20 years.
You didn't learn about her history
with the KGB until recently.
- What does that matter?
- That you've wanted a mother -
your mother - all your life.
And now here she is.
Dad...
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm not that naive.
I'm sure that's something
we both hope is true.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah.
Several nights ago,
I received a phone call at my home.
There was no one at the other end,
just some high-pitched static.
But something about the call
left me unsettled.
- Did security section run a trace?
- Yeah.
The call originated in Sonoma, California -
the Barranca bed and breakfast inn.
Emily and I spent some time there.
It was...
It was our favourite getaway.
Simple. It was a wrong number.
I'm not so sure.
I don't understand what you're suggesting.
I'm suggesting that someone
may be trying to leave me unsettled.
I would like you to send
someone to Sonoma, Jack.
I need to know who made that call.
- Sure. I'll get security section...
- Jack.
I don't want this to get back to the Alliance.
They can't know that I'm taking measures.
- I understand.
- Good.
I'll send Dixon.
Jack, there's something else.
After Sark recovered
Rambaldi's music box,
we tracked him to a safe house
in the Falkland Islands.
We sent in a team.
And did we retrieve it?
Yes. It was destroyed with age,
as Sydney said. Worthless.
But we found something else.
- He was not 80 years old.
- At least.
Syd, I'm serious.
I expect, like, a delivery guy
to be totally buffed out.
I mean, he sounded hot on the phone.
- Was he a cute 80?
- Shut up.
Hey, Francie, there's a woman
on the phone from the health department.
Ooh, I'm getting graded today.
How's it going?
OK.
How's your mom?
How are you?
I got four weeks left of community service,
then I'm done.
Hey...
You remember last week, when I
cooperated, let the CIA hypnotise me?
- Yeah.
- What happened with that?
Was I helpful at all?
I'm only asking because about five minutes
ago I was doing pretty well as a reporter,
and now I'm just...
I'm a dishwasher living in denial.
That's all.
- The information you provided was huge.
- Huge? Really?
Because of you,
the CIA scored a real victory.
I should have told you that before.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, don't worry about it.
That's so good to know.
- Good guys or bad guys?
- Neither.
My father.
- Everything OK?
- I talked with Sloane this morning.
He sent a team after Sark.
He wanted to recover the music box.
- I told him it was ruined.
- Yes, but he wanted it anyway.
He tracked down Sark
to a location in the Falklands.
Sark fought back. He got away.
They did, however, find a man at that
location. He was being held, tortured.
His name is Claus Richter. Three
weeks ago Richter was in Barcelona.
- When I was there.
- Yes, along with your mother.
The operations manual of the organisation
your mother used to run, the Bible,
anyone who gets their hands on that book
will gain access to all the contacts,
technology and weaponry
they amassed over the last ten years.
Sloane believes your mother
gave the manual to Richter,
that he was the man
who hid the book.
- Do you think that's true?
- I know it is.
They brought Richter into an SD-6
holding cell, and I interrogated him.
Before being brought into SD-6,
Richter was screened for
every type of possible infection:
Ebola, HIV, retroviruses.
They didn't find a thing,
yet this man was clearly dying.
Med-Tech believes he may have been
suffering from an allergic reaction
to something Sark used on him.
Apparently, the first sign of illness
was bleeding from the fingernails.
Sloane wanted me to torture him,
but that man was tortured as it was.
So I gave him morphine.
Irina Derevko gave you
the operations manual for her syndicate.
I would like you to tell me
where you've hidden it.
Derevko is a great woman.
Morphine's not bad either.
Let me be clear. I've only given you
enough to last five minutes.
Cooperate and get all you want.
Resist, and you get none.
Where did you hide that manual?
The location was too remote to describe.
It turns out Richter had designed a map
to lead your mother back
to the book's location.
- So where is the map?
- Inside a first edition of War and Peace
located at the technical services library
at FAPSI headquarters in Moscow.
FAPSI headquarters.
Sloane is preparing to send you
to Moscow to retrieve Richter's map.
I've had the CIA fabricate a bogus map.
You go to Moscow, retrieve the real one,
which you'll return to the CIA.
You'll give SD-6 this map, which will lead
them to the middle of the Sunken Forest.
Why have you come to me like this,
before my SD-6 briefing?
You giving me the CIA countermission
instead of Vaughn?
- Because this is the best way to respond...
- No, I know what this is.
You don't want me to take this to Mom.
There's no benefit in seeing her.
You have all the information you need.
We don't know that.
Sydney, we've been doing this long
enough to know that our system works.
The system was stagnant until Mom
turned herself in. Dad, we've covered this.
We've both been betrayed by this woman.
The difference between you and me is that
I'm willing to squeeze her for everything
she's got to take down the enemy.
Anything to get me the hell out of this life
as soon as possible. Anything.
- I'm Will, and I'm an addict.
- Hi, Will.
I never thought about my reputation
until I lost it.
It all happened very publicly, so people
actually look at me at the market and stuff.
"Oh, hey, there's the drug addict
from the newspaper."
Well, actually, there has been one
happy by-product from all this.
I have a good friend, who, it turns out,
I, uh, I didn't know at all before.
And now she and I can talk
in a way that we never did before.
And, uh...
And I don't think I would
trade that for anything.
- Same thing happened to me.
- What?
I learnt who my true friends were
when everyone found out about my habit.
- Um, Rebecca Martinez.
- Hey, I'm Will.
I know who you are, Will Tippin.
I read your articles.
The reporter with the big imagination who
fell in love with the heroin chic lifestyle.
- Yeah, yeah, that's me.
- But my theory?
I don't think you ever
really were a drug addict.
Why would you say that?
I believe what you wrote
about SD-6 was true.
I think you got too close to
some kind of secret conspiracy
and they had to shut you down.
They probably came after you,
told you not to talk.
I mean, they couldn't kill you, could they?
No, that would expose them.
So they threatened you and then,
to ruin your rep, they shot you up.
No, no.
I made up all that stuff about SD-6.
That was me.
That was me being an idiot.
- What?
- I just... Sorry, I'm...
I'm sort of a conspiracy theorist.
I have a web page: conspiracychick. com.
I wanna prove your story
about SD-6 was real.
Claus Richter is in SD-6 custody.
I'm aware that you refuse
to give the CIA details
about this operations manual
that you had Richter hide away.
And I understand why.
The knowledge contained in that manual
is your only leverage.
But now, having spoken with Richter,
SD-6 is after it.
Richter was found
in the custody of Mr Sark.
We don't know what Sark knows. He might
already have the map in his possession.
I'm here because SD-6
is sending me to Moscow.
I'm going to retrieve the map
at FAPSI headquarters.
So if you want to help the CIA,
as you claim to,
you'll give us any information you have that
will facilitate the recovery of Richter's map.
When I turned myself over to CIA,
a pair of earrings were taken from me.
They have sentimental value.
I'd like them back.
I'll see what I can do.
Then, in good faith, tell me how
you plan on breaking into the library.
She went to see her mother.
I tried... I tried to stop her.
I made it clear.
Made what clear?
Trusting her mother -
she's playing with fire.
- We've had this discussion.
- There is no one else to do this job.
- Sydney went to see her mother?
- Yes, she's there now.
Looking for help.
The east wing stairwell is an option.
I can see why SD-6 chose that route.
But there's a better way
to get to the sixth-floor library.
Write this down.
Once you're inside the building, don't take
the main stairs. You just look to your left...
No one wants a happy ending to this story
more than I do, but I know this woman.
I know her charms.
I know her tricks.
The way she presents herself, she disarms
you. Some people have that talent.
Compared to all of them,
Irina Derevko is extraordinary.
Is there any chance that
all she wants is forgiveness?
No.
Be specific about your concerns.
I don't know what it is Derevko wants.
Maybe something within the CIA,
maybe to recruit Sydney to her side.
I can tell you, I know this:
Derevko is using this agency
and my daughter
to get whatever it is that she wants,
and everywhere I look, people are
complacent and cooperative, listening to...
listening to a woman
who killed operatives of the CIA,
who destroyed countless lives.
Yours.
We'll take your suggestions
into consideration.
Be careful.
You asked me what I was afraid of.
I can tell you. It's obvious.
I'm afraid of losing my daughter.
Hey.
So, I heard your father came to see you,
and he tried to preempt my involvement.
He was just trying to keep me
away from my mother.
I know.
She actually had some intel
for this mission that could help.
Good.
Listen, as far as your mother's concerned,
it's ridiculous for you to worry about me.
I'm fine.
What she did to my father, I can handle.
But when I heard what your father did,
coming to see you like that, I...
I realised how insane this must be for him.
Having your mother back in his life.
Which only concerned me
because that means
he's not making it any easier for you.
So, before you leave for Moscow,
I just wanted to say that
you might feel alone in all this,
like you don't have an ally.
I'm your ally.
Never question that.
Miss Bristow, your plane's standing by.
I'll see you when I get back.
OK, these medals that you won?
Well, you didn't really win them
and they're not really medals. This one
right here is the Order of Bravery, right?
Not a medal, right?
No, it's an electronic skeleton key.
It'll get you access to the sixth floor.
This one, the Order of Zhukov, first class.
This'll get you into the technical library.
Now, this one is the Order of Merit.
It'll get you into the ASRS.
- What's ASRS?
- Oh, yeah.
The majority of the books are kept in
a secure area underneath the building.
Now, in order to get them, you're going
to need to get to the selection terminal.
What you'll do is you'll type in
the name of the book that you want,
then there's going to be
this automatic crane thing
that retrieves the book that you requested,
and then deposits it
over on the sixth floor, OK?
Now, just make sure that
you don't remove the metal
until after you've logged out the system,
or you'll probably set off the alarm, OK?
Ow.
Actually felt quite good.
Whatever Arvin Sloane pays you,
it can't be enough.
Would you consider coming to work for me
if it meant I'd let you walk out of here?
I believe if you took the time
to hear a comprehensive offer,
you might actually say yes.
You're cute, but I'll pass.
- Go ahead.
- It's me.
I am trapped in the technical services
building. I need a way out.
My mother said something about
secret passages. Get her on the phone.
Sydney's trapped in the FAPSI building
in Moscow. She needs a way out - now.
- Where is she exactly?
- Where are you exactly?
- An office on the seventh floor.
- Whose office?
- General Vitali Simonov.
Ask her if there's an abstract painting
behind the desk.
Is there an abstract painting
behind the desk?
Yes, yes, yes.
Behind it there's an activation switch
for a private security door.
- What time does this place open?
- Not for another hour.
I'm out and I've got the map.
Copy, Freelancer.
See you at home.
How do you say thank you
to the woman who killed your father?
You don't.
- Sark asked you to come work with him?
- Like it wasn't even a question.
Like it was a done deal.
Sark is like the good-looking guy
in high school
who knows how cute he is
and won't take no for an answer.
Any suspicious reactions
to the map you gave SD-6?
- No, they're analysing it now.
- Good.
We have a CIA tech
trying to decode the real map.
I know they're having trouble with it.
Do you think Richter used
a cipher text only they could read?
Maybe.
Your mother might be
able to help us with this.
If you're asking me to go see her again,
she did have a request.
They've been checked
for hidden compartments,
transmitters, passive sensors.
Every sharp edge has been dulled.
I was 21 years old when I was given these.
At graduation from the academy,
my mother,
your grandmother,
put these in my hands.
I cried.
She said "Sweetheart, wear them well."
You would have liked her,
had things been different.
We need you to decode the map.
I have a request.
Sure.
Mr Sloane is concerned about a phone call
he received at home last Thursday night.
The call was traced to the Barranca
bed and breakfast in Sonoma, California.
He's asked me
to send someone to Sonoma,
find out who was staying there,
who might have made the call.
- Whatever information you can get.
- Sounds easy enough.
No one's to know about this.
Understood.
Madagascar, close to Sambava.
Latitude: minus 14 degrees, 26 minutes.
Longitude: 49 degrees,
57 minutes and 20 seconds.
She says the building is clean. There are
no explosives or anti-intrusion systems.
- We obviously can't trust this information.
- Dad, come on.
If she wanted me dead, she could have
left me stuck at FAPSI headquarters.
Your mother knows that
the only leverage she has
is the information about her agency.
As soon as we get that manual,
she's got nothing.
Unless she wants to prove herself.
That's the kind of hopeful thinking
that will get you killed.
- I'm going in.
- No, you're not.
Irina Derevko's proved her value...
Do not talk to me about
that woman's value.
Of all people, you should know better.
We're sending you to Madagascar
to retrieve the Bible.
You two, prepare to leave tonight.
I want you to deal with Sydney's cover
at SD-6. Let's move it.
The team will be in Madagascar
in 12 hours.
I'll need you to have
everything in place by then.
On that time frame,
I'll have to parachute in.
Jack, I owe you.
But why 30lb of Semtex?
I could do the same job with 5lb of C-4.
I need you to make sure that if anyone
enters that building, no one will survive.
God grant us the serenity
to accept the things we cannot change,
courage to change the things we can,
and wisdom to know the difference.
Don't forget, next meeting
Patty's bringing the doughnuts.
Hey. I had a thought.
You and I could do this together.
Do what together?
You could tell me what to do.
Who to contact, what to write.
I can publish it all on my web page,
totally anonymous.
- Rebecca...
- And we could hang out.
Which could be kinda nice.
Do you like frozen yoghurt?
I already told you that the whole thing
about SD-6, it was all fictional.
Will, come on.
Now, why would anyone,
especially you, make up a story like that?
OK, just tell me this.
Did they do this to you?
A friend of mine, her fiancé was killed.
The police, they thought
it was just a random shooting,
that some guy had
broken into his apartment.
And I was worried about her.
I decided to play hero.
I was gonna find out who killed him,
and after that I was gonna...
I don't know, maybe, uh...
maybe our relationship would be different.
But the more that I looked into it,
the less I found.
Then I had to make it up,
because to me it was more important
not to let her down
than it was for me
to just be honest with her.
So, you wanna look into SD-6?
Hey. Good luck.
Will Tippin shouldn't be a problem.
I gave him a number of opportunities,
all recorded on audio files,
to restart his SD-6 investigation.
Tippin never took the bait.
- Security section's seen that?
- Yes.
And they're classifying Tippin
as a nonthreat.
Good.
- Did you talk to the desk clerk?
- Yes, I did, sir.
The Barranca Inn has no way of linking
a back-trace for an outside line
to an individual room, so we don't know
which room it was that called your home.
But we do know who was
staying at the inn that night.
Is that your wife's signature?
Freelancer has reached the target
and is heading toward position.
We have you on-screen, Freelancer.
There's the house.
Freelancer's going in.
We're at the door.
Can you switch from the real-time
SAT radar scan to infrared?
Switching to infrared.
- Sydney, hold your entry.
- What is it, Dad?
The building is wired to explode.
See how these areas don't give off
the same amount of heat
as the surrounding structure?
- That's because they're not made of wood.
- What are they made of?
Sydney, I need you to take a look
under the house. Is there a crawlspace?
She lied to me.
Sydney, come on.
We're pulling back.
If she was counting on my trust,
that I would just walk in there
and set off the explosives,
then why did she help us get this far?
There are enough explosives in there
to blow this entire place,
operation manual included.
Your mother was using us
to destroy it for her.
Secure the perimeter until...
Your efficient reconnaissance work
saved us the trouble of using our GPS.
Thank you.
Go inside and recover
the operations manual.
You escaped technical directorate
after lockdown.
Clearly you had no trouble
decoding the map.
I'm surprised Claus Richter was
so willing to reveal his secrets.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd guess you had another source.
Sydney. Sydney.
Where's Sark?
They're gone.
Sydney, are you OK?
We're OK, Dad.
We're coming home.
This is Assistant Director Kendall. I want
Irina Derevko removed from this facility.
I want her transferred to Camp Harris
for unrestricted interrogation.
She'll be gone within the hour.
You were right about her, Jack.
You were right.
If I build a wall a hundred feet tall
Would that keep you in?
If I shackled your feet
so you couldn't leave
Would you try and run?
I thought there might have been
a chance to believe...
to believe that she had no hidden agenda.
Everything you said was right.
And I was so stupid.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry that I doubted you.