~~["Misty” On P.A.]
** [ Humming ]
** [ Continues Humming ]
Let's get this show
on the road.
Federal agents !
Get down !
[ Chuckling ]
Turn this thing off.
- You're Pusher, I presume.
- You must be Frank Burst.
You know, I gotta tell you.
You got the greatest name.
Agent Collins, read him his rights
and let's get him out of here.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
- Think you’re gonna hold me ?
- I want him in a waist chain
and leg irons.
I want him in a car with a cage.
Loudoun County unit whatever.
I'll ride shotgun.
You know, it'd really help me out
if you gave us your name.
Pusher is good enough.
You know, Deputy,
I just gotta say...
that your uniform is really
the most soothing shade of blue.
I'm not kidding you.
I notice those things. It's a sky blue.
Very calming.
Very tranquil.
I think the word for that particular
shade is "cerulean, "actually.
Cerulean blue.
- Okay, we get it.
It's a nice shade of blue.
- Cerulean blue.
Cerulean makes me
think of a breeze,
a gentle breeze.
- Hey, Mr. Blackwell, put a sock in it.
- Cerulean is a gentle breeze.
Cerulean, a gentle breeze.
- [Horn Blaring]
- Stop !
[Burst] When the truck hit us
I was knocked unconscious.
Deputy Scott Kerber
was mortally injured.
Before he succumbed, he managed
to pull himself out of the car,
dig his keys
out of his pocket,
and his last breath was spent
unlocking my prisoner...
who, despite his own injuries,
managed to escape on foot.
He calls himself Pusher.
- What's his story ?
- He cold-called me about a month ago.
He confessed to a series
of contract killings going back
over the course of two years.
- He wanted to turn himself in ?
- No.
It was a game.
He was bragging.
See, the thing about these murders
is nobody considers them murders.
They went down
in the books as suicides.
- So you think he was just a crank ?
- No.
He knows too much
about each case,
too many details that were
only in the police reports.
What connection did this
dead deputy have with him ?
None, as far as I can tell.
Kerber was a good cop.
Then why did he free him ?
Pusher kept rambling
about cerulean blue--
kept saying how it reminded him
of a breeze or something.
"Cerulean blue
is like a gentle breeze."
Over and over.
And then Kerber pulled
into the truck and blammo.
So you think that Pusher
somehow talked him into doing this ?
- He willed him into doing that ?
- Willed him ? How ?
No kidding.
How ?
You’re guess is as good as mine
on this one.
See, Pusher
likes to leave clues.
- " Ronin."
- Ronin.
It's a samurai
without a master.
- What, you never saw Yojimbo ?
- Still, what does it mean ?
It means I bet I know ten to one
what this guy's got stacked
on the back of his toilet.
- Agents, here's volume ten.
- Oh, thanks.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help noticing.
I was in Georgetown
this weekend.
A guy knocked me down
and stole my purse.
- They get him ?
- Do they ever?
No offense.
Excuse me.
Mulder, I'm still not sure
what we're looking for.
- Samurais without masters
have to advertise.
- Yes, but advertise for what ?
I mean, how--
How did this Pusher...
convince an otherwise honest
deputy sheriff to free him ?
I mean, I'm sure
you have a theory.
Suggestion
is a powerful force.
The science of hypnosis is predicated
on it as are most TV commercials.
I mean, they're designed
to plant thoughts in your head.
Inducing someone to buy hair color
is a little different...
than inducing them to drive
in front of a speeding truck.
But the mechanism of suggestion
is the same. It’s just a lot
more powerful in this case.
I mean, this guy
calls himself Pusher.
Can't we take that to mean that he
pushes his will onto other people ?
Well, even if he could
push his will,
why would he cause an accident
when he himself was in the car ?
Maybe he really
didn't want to go to jail.
Look at this.
"I solve problems. O.S.U."
Ohio State University ?
No. It's a northern
Virginia area code.
I've seen this add in all these
magazines dating back to April, 1 994.
The time span of the murders.
O.S.U.
O.S.
U.
Osu. It's a Japanese word.
It means, "to push."
I say we run down
those telephone numbers.
[ Ringing ]
[ Continues Ringing ]
[ Phone Beeps ]
Hey, I think
you drooled on me.
Sorry.
What time is it ?
Twenty to 3:00.
No luck,
I take it.
No. Nothing here,
nothing at the other two pay phones.
I checked in with Burst. He's beginning
to think it's a wild-goose chase.
[Pay Phone Ringing]
[ Continues Ringing ]
- Hello ?
- Are you two just gonna
sit there all night ?
Don't bother hunting around for me.
I'm far away.
- Although I was watching you
up until about an hour ago.
- They're on the trace.
You and your pretty partner
seem awfully close.
- Do you work well together ?
- Who is this ?
- What's your name ?
- Sorry, G-man. It's not that easy.
You have to follow my little
bread crumb trail. Prove your worth.
So far,
you're doing all right.
Why do I have
to prove my worth to you ?
You think this is a game ?
What, do you want
to be found ?
- All right.
Where's my next bread crumb ?
- Right in front of you.
- Let your fingers
do the walking, G-man.
- [ Dial Tone ]
Okay.
Not a complete trace.
They think he was using
a digital scrambler.
Let your fingers
do the walking.
Phone book.
You know, what if Pusher
was the last person to use this phone ?
- Can you redial
on these kind of phones ?
- Hang on a second.
- [ Man On Phone, indistinct ]
- Yeah, it's me again.
- We want the last number
dialed out from this location.
- Okay.
-Just ring it on through.
- Give me a second.
- Okay.
- [ Phone Beeps ]
[ Rings Twice ]
[ Woman ]
Hi. You've reached Teetotalers
Golf Driving Range and Pro Shop.
Our hours of operation are 7:00 a.m.
to midnight Monday through Saturday...
and 7:00 a.m.
to 1 0:00 p.m. on Sunday.
So he's a killer and a golfer.
Rings a bell, huh ?
Let's go, G-woman.
Oh, yeah.
Strong shot.
Good shot.
Whoo-hoo !
All right, gentlemen, I'm using
this here non-sanctioned ball.
It's got a core of uranium--
or some damn thing. I don't know what.
It gets up there
like Sputnik.
Yeah.
About time.
Konnichiwa, gentlemen.
I was never here.
- Police ! Get down !
- Whoa. Okay.
- Get down !
- Okay. Okay. Relax.
Relax.
Let me see your face.
Take it easy.
Come on.
That's right.
Hey, Collins.
Listen.
I need you
to do something for me.
Will you do something
for me ?
[Man Sobbing]
Mulder.
- Collins ?
- [ Sobbing ]
What the hell ?
Collins, what the hell
are you doing ?
Collins, let it go.
Stop me !
[Burst]
Collins !
- Put that down.
- [ Grunting ]
[ Screaming ]
Light up. Light up.
- Come in. This is Burst.
Get a burn unit over here.
- Light up. Light up.
- Yeah, Collins is down.
Bad. Yeah, real bad.
- Light up. Light up.
- I don't know what happened.
Get over here !
- Light up. Light up.
- [Horn Blaring, Distant]
- Yeah, get somebody over here. Now !
Collins, it's all right.
It's all right. Take it easy.
[ Horn Continues Blaring ]
- Federal agent !
- Light up. Light up. Light--
Light up.
[Sighs]
Bet you five bucks
I get off.
[Man] Rise and state your name
and address for the court.
Robert Patrick Modell,
3083 Roseneath Avenue,
apartment nine.
Alexandria, Virginia.
Agent Mulder, does the F.B.I.
believe that this defendant...
is responsible
for 1 4 murders ?
That is correct,
Your Honor.
Well, in each of the cases,
the coroner's office ruled suicide.
We believe that they
were indeed murders, Your Honor.
You believe ?
- But do you have any evidence ?
- We have the defendant on audiotape...
confessing to the murders
on several separate occasions--
he clearly identifies
them as such.
Furthermore, the defendant
knows crime scene details...
that were only available
to the police.
Your Honor, one of these
so-called murder victims threw
herself under a commuter train.
This was a crowded platform.
A hundred witnesses. Nobody pushed her.
No one was
within30 feet of her.
- But your client was present.
- Which is how he knew your
crime scene details.
- Make your point, Agent Mulder.
- I believe that these people died...
because it was the defendant's
express will that they do so.
- His will ?
- This man admitted to being
a killer for hire.
I believe he has a unique suggestive
ability which makes for the perfect M.O.
He is able to talk his victims
into injuring themselves.
- I can't believe this.
- Do you want to run that by me
one more time, Agent Mulder?
Yesterday a federal
law enforcement officer...
was induced to self-immolation
by the defendant.
I witnessed it.
All these other officers witnessed it.
Your Honor, we have Modell's confession.
All we're asking is--
Your Honor, the evidence chain
to this case has been rather
difficult to establish.
We're asking the court's indulgence
while we complete our investigation...
and we'd like to have Mr. Modell
held for trial...
based on the strength
of his taped confession.
What about this audiotape,
Mr. Modell ?
Did you confess
to 14murders ?
Unfortunately, yes, Your Honor.
Not that I remember any of it.
This was, uh, basically
a drunken phone prank...
on the part of my client,
Your Honor.
A phone prank ? He had the details
of every case, Your Honor.
And Robert deeply regrets the distress
and confusion this situation has caused.
Do you deny these charges ?
Absolutely, Your Honor.
I'm not guilty.
Excuse me for a minute.
I believe you owe me
five dollars.
Hey, your shoe's untied.
I made you look.
How do you do it ?
Hey, Modell.
I know your name now.
I know where you live.
I dug up a few more things
on our Robert Patrick Modell.
Let me guess.
He was an average student.
He attended
an average community college.
He did an average stint in the military.
- Which branch of service ?
- Not his first choice.
He wanted to be a Navy Seal
and then he wanted to be an Army
Special Forces, Green Beret.
Promptly washed out of both,
though not for lack of intelligence.
He ended up being
a supply clerk at Fort Bragg.
Served two years,
general discharge.
Did you know that he applied
to the F.B.I. ?
- He didn't even come close
to passing the psych screening.
- You got a copy of that ?
Yeah. They found him to be
"acutely ego-centered."
He has no regard
for the feelings of others,
instead perceiving
people as objects.
He is extremely suspicious
of governments and authority.
Yet he wants
to be in authority.
The screener caught him in a dozen
self-aggrandizing lies.
Saying that he was a master
of martial arts,
that he had been trained by Gurk has
in Nepal and ninjas in Japan.
And ninjas are said to have the ability
to cloud the minds of their opponents.
Now, are we talking
kung fu movies, Mulder ?
He certainly clouded the mind
of that judge, Scully.
Even if Modell could, he didn't need to.
We barely had a case.
Oh, we had enough to get past
a simple preliminary hearing.
Modell psyched the guy out.
He put the "whammy" on him.
Please explain to me
the scientific nature of the "whammy."
I don't know. Maybe it's some mental
aspect of some Eastern martial art.
You know, the temporary suppression
of the brain's chemistry...
produced by a specific timbre
or cadence in Modell's voice.
His voice
seems to be the key.
Mulder, Modell's last known employment
was as a convenience store clerk.
He has never been trained by ninjas.
He has never even been out of the U.S.
He is just a little man who wishes
that he were someone big.
And we're feeding that wish.
That failed psych screening, if Modell
could actually control people's minds,
right now he'd be
an F.B.I. agent, right ?
He'd be a Green Beret,
a Navy Seal.
Maybe the ability came to him more
recently, like in the last two years.
Well, okay.
What's your big theory ?
How do you explain
what Agent Collins did ?
This is a sane man,
a family man,
with no prior history
of psychological problems.
Sets himself on fire. You witnessed
that. How does that happen ?
What do you need me to say, Mulder,
that I believe that Modell
is guilty of murder ?
I do. I'm just looking for
an explanation a little more
mundane than the "whammy."
Well, he's laughing
at us, Scully.
[ Beeping ]
Excuse me. Where might I find
the computer records section ?
Fourth foor, west wing.
Thank you very much.
[Machine Beeps]
Can I help you ?
I need to know some things.
Holly.
Great.
just let me have the keyboard
for a minute.
I'd love a printout of this.
And a cup of coffee
when you get a chance.
I wish I could get my hands on the guy
that did that to you.
I'd make him pay.
[Modell Speaking, indistinct]
- Can I help you ?
- No. No, thanks.
We're, uh--
We’re just fine.
Look.
We're in the middle
of something here, so--
- Who are you and
what are you doing here ?
- Take a walk, Mel Cooley.
[ Grunting ]
Let me go. Let me go.
Shut up !
Holly, call security.
Holly.
He's the one.
- He's the one who mugged you.
- Holly, call security now!
- Make him stop hurting me.
- Shut up ! Holly, now !
- Holly.
- Holly!
- Security.
- I've got a situation in here,
fourth foor--
[ Screaming ]
Ah, God !
Hurt him back.
[ Grunting ]
Sir,
I'm so terribly,
terribly sorry.
I don't know why l--
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
All right, let's
hit the bricks, huh ?
Holly, can you tell us anything more
that might help us understand...
why you attacked
Assistant Director Skinner?
It's like suddenly I was watching myself
from across the room...
doing these things.
It's like he was with me
inside my head.
Modell ?
That's the only way
I know how to put it.
Excuse me, sir.
Can we speak outside ?
Yeah, sure. Uh, Holly,
excuse us for a minute, please.
I reviewed the building
security tapes.
Modell can clearly be seen
entering and leaving unnoticed.
He had the word "pass"
on his lapel.
Guards that waved him by
don't even remember seeing him at all.
And you're saying this
same mysterious phenomenon...
is the reason I have
a size-seven heel mark on my face ?
I have to agree
with Agent Mulder, sir.
I can't even begin
to explain how,
but I think that Modell is
responsible for your injuries.
Why is this guy
so interested in you ?
-What do you mean ?
-He left with one file-- yours.
He didn't access any others.
Now he knows
where you live.
- And you know where he lives.
Go pick him up.
- Yeah, for what ?
About the only thing we got
on him now is criminal trespass.
That's enough for a warrant.
Police !
Hands up !
[ Shouting ]
Modell !
Lights coming on.
[Man On TV] Look me right
in the eyes. Right in the eyes.
[Woman On TV]
No, please. Let me go.
Svengali.
- All clear. No one's home.
- Search the whole building.
And nearby buildings too. We know that
Modell likes to watch from a distance.
Check the place out.
I'll talk to the neighbors.
Hey, Scully,
check this out.
Mango kiwi tropical swirl.
Now we know we're
dealing with a madman.
Right.
Thank you very much.
- Tegretol.
- What's that ?
It's to relieve Modell's seizures.
He has temporal lobe epilepsy.
I just talked
to his doctor's office.
They wouldn’t give me much
over the phone.
just that that prescription
dates back to April, 1 994.
What causes epilepsy
this late in life ?
- A head injury, neurological
disease, brain tumor or lesion.
- A tumor ?
The growth of brain tumors has
been linked with the reported
occurrence of psychic ability.
- Mulder, those reports
are completely unsubstantiated.
-Just bear with me for a second.
What if Modell's suggestive ability
is really a form of psycho kinesis ?
Brought on by the brain tumor ?
Well, it fits. All those
protein drinks in his fridge.
Maybe he's gotta replenish
the metabolic energy...
that he uses in the process
of controlling somebody's will.
Mulder, more to the point,
if Modell did have a brain tumor,
the effects on his health
would be more debilitating.
It's likely that he simply
wouldn't be well enough...
to play these cat and mouse
games with us.
Maybe he isn't.
Maybe that's the whole point.
- What do you mean ?
- His exhaustion at the driving range.
He didn't let us capture him.
He was too sick to escape,
too tired, too wiped out.
Why would a killer who’s so proficient
confess to murders...
that he'd already
gotten away with ?
- Maybe he's dying.
- And he wants to go out
in a blaze of glory.
Not with a whimper
but a bang.
[Phone Ringing]
- [ Continues Ringing ]
- Get the tracing gear.
- Hello.
- Hey, hey, hey, what do you say ?
What's up, Modell ?
How you doing ?
Long time no see.
Told you I know where you live.
Nice apartment, Modell.
Who does your decorating,
the Grinch that stole Christmas ?
[ Chuckling ] Agent Frank Burst,
the guy with the great name.
Say, Frank, are Agents Mulder
and Scully there ?
- Yeah, we're here.
- Perfect.
Frank, how much
do you weigh ?
- Excuse me ?
- About how much do you weigh ?
Anything to keep you talking you piece
of-- I don't know, about 1 90, 1 95.
Bah, 215ifyou'rea day.
You're totally the wrong weight
for your height.
I mean-- No offense, Frank,
but you’re built like a fireplug.
Yeah, and I got stubby legs that
are gonna kick you in the ass.
You goin' somewhere with this ?
[ Chuckles ]
It’s just that it can't be healthy.
And you look like
maybe you’re a smoker.
You probably take
a little drink now and then.
- You eat greasy fried food--
sausage, bacon, eggs over easy,
- Frank.
onion rings that soak those
dark stains through the cardboard.
And I'm guessing you shake
on that salt like a maraca.
- Frank. Frank, hang up the phone.
- How about it ?
What are you talking about, Modell ?
What's your point ?
You know what that's doing to your
arteries ? Terrible things, Frank.
- Terrible.
-[Mulder] Frank.
Waxy yellow chunks of plaque
are tumbling through your bloodstream,
sticking like glue
to your arterial walls.
- Hang up the phone.
- Keep talking, you bastard.
- Can you feel it, Frank ?
- Come on, man. Hang up the phone.
- Frank, hang up the phone !
- Back off !
Can you feel your aorta
squeezing shut ?
- Frank, hang up the phone !
- I said, "back off" !
- Hang it up !
- Finish the trace !
- Mulder.
- Somebody hang up the phone !
Ever hear of a medical condition
called pachyemia ?
It's when the blood thickens up
in your veins like strawberry jam.
- [ Gasping ] Finish the trace !
- Frank, hang it up !
Hang up !
Your heart fat lines.
[ Humming Steady Tone ]
- [ Gasping ]
-[Man] Frank.
[Modell]
You die, Frank.
Frank ?
Yo, Frank.
No pulse.
Get an ambulance.
[Man] We need an ambulance to 3083
Roseneath Ave., apartment nine.
A possible cardiac arrest.
- Modell ?
- Hey, Mulder. How's Frankie boy ?
What is it, Modell,
really, that you want ?
A worthy adversary.
It's obviously not that
fat lump lying at your feet.
No, I'm hoping it's you.
Why me ?
I've read all about you.
You're a top criminal profiler.
Oxford University grad,
all-around bright young man.
You know what makes
guys like me tick, right ?
You think you see
right through old Bob Modell.
Sick old Bob Modell, right ?
You're dying,
aren’t you, Bob ?
What, do you want to take a few innocent
people with you before you go ?
Biology tells us
we’re all dying,
and original sin tells me
ain't nobody innocent.
Yeah, and some are more innocent
than others. Why don't you just
tell me where you are ?
You want the phone number?
Sure, just, uh--
It's 555-01 97.
You know, it's just a payphone.
In two minutes, I'll be gone.
You mean you killed this man
for nothing, you sick bastard ?
[ Chuckling ]
Me ?
No, haven’t you
caught on, Mulder ?
They all kill themselves.
[ Line Clicks ]
- Where's Modell calling from ?
- A gas station parking lot.
1 200 block, Chain Bridge Road.
It’s payphone,
just like he said.
Fairfax Mercy Hospital is right down
the street from there, huh ?
[ Whispering ]
Fairfax Mercy Pharmacy.
" Fairfax Mercy Pharmacy."
He must need regular
treatment, Mulder.
Well, let's go find out.
[ Man On Radio ]
Keep moving in. Two is ready.
[Man On Radio]
Here they go.
[ Man On Radio ]
We found Modell's car.
The engine's still warm.
He's probably in the building.
[Man #2 On Radio] All entrances
covered. Do we hold or goin ?
Hold.
- Hold.
-[Man On Radio] Roger.
The outpatient office says
Modell is scheduled for a 2:30 M.R.I.
That's right now.
- How do you want to play this ?
- I think I should go in alone.
- Why ?
- My team can flush him out.
What if Modell turns one
of your men against the others
in a crowded hospital ?
- I think we should
give him what he wants.
- You.
We stand a better chance
if we’re separated.
I'll go in miked. That way
you’ll know what he’s doing,
where he is at all times.
You got a radio, something
to keep my hands free ?
I got just what you need.
Two lux video camera.
It can practically see in the dark.
It's designed for bomb disposal
wards to keep only one officer at risk.
See ?
- Think I can get The Playboy Channel ?
- [ Chuckles ]
Smile, Scully.
- Take it.
- No.
I wouldn't want to end up
pointing it at anybody except Modell.
Let's get the show
on the road.
Federal agent.
Go about your business as usual.
Scully, do you read me ?
I'm with you, Mulder.
Nothing out
of the ordinary.
SWAT team,
hold outside.
[Man On Radio]
SWAT team still holding.
- [Gunshot]
- Mulder.
- Two shots fired.
- SWAT team--
No, not yet.
Everybody keep moving. Federal agent.
- Let me see what the hell
is going on in there.
- Mulder, I'm losing you.
- Damn.
- Mulder.
Agent Mulder.
Wait. Agent Scully.
[ Static ]
Are you, uh--
you getting this back there ?
- Mulder, what happened ?
- Looks like the guard
shot the technician,
then he shot himself.
His gun is missing.
Brophy, tell your men
Modell may be heading your way.
SWAT team, suspect is armed
and is possibly making his way
out of the building.
[Man On Radio]
We copy. We're ready for him.
Mulder, wait-- wait.
- Get closer to the computer monitor.
- Over here ?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right there.
There. That light mass
in his temporal lobe.
Right here.
You were right, Mulder.
Now check around you. Modell's chart
should be somewhere around there.
We're batting a thousand, Scully.
Modell's dying.
He's got nothing to lose.
Mulder, just get
out of there. Go.
Mulder.
Mulder !
We think they're
three doors down.
We've got both ends
sewn up tight,
but there're six critical care rooms
we can't get to.
If we gas the halls,
we might kill those patients.
Why do we keep giving this guy
exactly what he wants ?
just wait for a signal from me.
You're clear.
Mulder.
Thanks for joining us.
We've got a dozen law enforcement
officers outside in the hall,
another 30 in the parking lot.
A regular convention.
So whatever you’ve got planned,
it's not going to work out
the way you want it to.
You don't know
what I got planned.
Two warriors of equal skill
fight to the death.
One is a student
of Japanese budo--
the way of war.
Budo teaches the warrior
to leave himself outside the battle.
In other words,
to disregard his own death.
Because of that,
the budo warrior always wins.
I am that warrior.
I don't fear my death.
So l--
I'm gonna give you...
one pull of the trigger
against me.
A one-in-six chance.
One. One pull.
Wait.
Mulder, look.
There's pure oxygen in this room.
There’s no telling what could happen
if you pull that trigger.
Piece of cake.
Your turn.
Mulder, no.
Mulder, yes.
- Go.
- Mulder, listen tome.
Give me the gun.
We can stop this thing
right now. You and I can just
walk outside of this room.
No ! Damn you !
You bastard !
Mulder,
hand me the gun--
Mulder, you don't
have to do this.
You're stronger than this.
Your turn, Scully. Gotta play by
the rules. Pull the trigger, Mulder.
Mulder, fight him.
You can fight this.
Come on.
Pull the trigger, Mulder.
She shot you. I read it in her files.
Payback time. Shoot the little spy!
- I'm gonna kill you, Modell.
- Yeah. Pull the trigger.
You get another crack at me.
Scully, run !
[ Whispering ]
Scully.
[ Alarm Ringing ]
Federal Agent. Get down !
Get down ! Get down !
There's no telling
how long he'll hang on,
but he'll never
regain consciousness.
You know how we thought he was
undergoing treatment ? We were wrong.
- What do you mean ?
- Read his chart.
The M.R.I.s were a way to gauge
how much life he had left,
but he consistently
refused treatment.
The tumor remained operable
right up until the end,
but he refused to have it removed.
- Why ?
- I think it's like you said,
he was always such
a little man.
This was finally something
that made him feel big.
I say we don't let him
take up another minute of our time.
Subtitles By
Captions, Inc. Los Angeles
[Boy]
I made this !