[Train Horn Blares]
Hurry up !
[ Signal Bells Clanging ]
Hi !
All clear.
[ Chattering ]
[ Speaking Japanese ]
[Car Engine Starts]
[Medical Instruments Rattling]
[Man Speaking Japanese]
[Japanese ]
[ Sucking Sound ]
[ Shouting ]
Aah !
Come on in.
What are you watching ?
Something that just
came in the mail.
That's not your usual brand
of entertainment.
What is it ?
According to the magazine ad
I answered, it's an alien autopsy.
Guaranteed authentic.
[Scully]
You spent money for this ?
29.95, plus shipping.
Mulder, this is even hokier than the one
they aired on the Fox Network.
You can't even see
what they're operating on.
Yeah, but it does
look authentic.
I mean, the setting
and the procedures.
I mean, it does look as if an actual
autopsy is being performed, doesn't it ?
Well, technically, I don't know why
they would be wearing gas masks.
Maybe it's because of
this green substance...
they seem to be extracting
from the subject.
Can you identify that ?
Olive oil ? Snake oil ?
I suppose you think it's alien blood.
It's widely held that aliens
don't have blood, Scully.
- I guess that begs the question.
If this is an alien autopsy--
- Where's the alien ?
What's so intriguing to me
is the striking lack of detail here.
Well, what do you want
for 29.95 ?
That autopsy you saw on TV
was so fake precisely
because it tried to show too much.
And this is real
because it doesn't ?
Yes, and because of, uh--
Because of this.
Who's selling these tapes ?
Some guy in Allentown,
Pennsylvania.
Claims he pulled it off the
satellite dish at 2:00 in the morning.
[Dogs Barking]
- The front door's boarded up.
- Back door's been busted open.
But nobody let the rat out.
Mulder, in here.
He's still warm.
[Door Opens]
Federal agent!
[Dog Barking]
Come on down.
[Yelling]
[Gunshot]
I get tired of losing my gun.
Okay, now face the fence.
Face the fence !
What's your name ?
[ Speaking Japanese ]
Do you speak English ?
[Japanese ]
Great.
Give me the bag.
- Give me the bag.
- Mmm.
Okay, let's go.
- Let's go !
- [Japanese ]
[ Chattering ]
[Phones Ringing,
People Chattering]
Either they can't locate an interpreter,
or the interpreter they located...
didn't interpret the instructions
and got lost somewhere.
- I don't know which.
- Did you try the F.B.I. field office ?
Somehow this is a tall request
in Allentown this time of night.
Oh, look at this.
A beacon in the night.
- Agent Mulder, Scully.
- This is a surprise, sir.
- You don't speak Japanese
by any chance, do you ?
- I wish I could.
- It might save us all
some embarrassment.
- What do you mean ?
I'm up here with a federal
attorney trying to sort out
a little international mess.
- He said you made an arrest tonight.
- A murder suspect, yeah.
- I'm afraid you're gonna
have to release him.
- What are you talking about ?
According to the
japanese diplomatic corps,
the man is a high-ranking diplomat.
This man sitting in here ?
That's Kazuo Sakari.
I didn't get his name.
I was too busy getting my ass kicked.
What about the murder victim
or the paperwork ?
It's all gonna be handled
by some other agency.
What are you two
doing out here anyway ?
Tracking down
a video piracy thing.
I suggest you keep your nose
clean, and head straight back
to Washington, Agent Mulder.
Before someone takes
another swipe at it.
I don't know, Mulder.
It just doesn't track.
What would a Japanese diplomat
be doing in that house...
with a dead man with his head
stuffed in a pillowcase ?
Obviously not strengthening
international relations.
Well, what do you
want to do now ? Drop it ?
I paid my 29.95, Scully.
I think I'm entitled to a few
more answers, don’t you think ?
[Scully]
What are you doing ?
I just remembered a piece of
evidence from the crime scene
that I forgot to turn in.
[Police Siren]
[Scully]
What are those ?
They look like
satellite photos.
What would he
be doing with these ?
What would he be doing with a list
of Mutual U.F.O. Network members...
in the greater Allentown area
with the name Betsy Hagopian circled ?
Maybe he was gonna fit her
for a pillowcase too.
Why don’t you stick around.
- Get a motel room and check
it out in the morning.
- What are you gonna do ?
I'm gonna go back to D.C. like
a good boy, like Skinner told me to do,
show these to
a few friends of ours.
[Man]
The name of the boat is the Talapus.
just gotta love
them German optics.
So you’re saying that's
from a German satellite.
No, the optics are German.
The technology is probably ours.
- But the satellite is
most likely Japanese.
- Launched from South America.
- Gotta love that global economy, huh ?
- Where'd you get this, Mulder ?
-Japanese diplomat.
- I'm surprised.
The Japanese are very secretive
about their espionage capabilities,
and extremely careful with
their intelligence data.
What exactly are they
spying on there ?
The Talapus was a salvage ship
out of San Diego.
They spent months looking for a Japanese
sub that went down in World War ll.
It was rumored to be carrying
a load of gold bullion.
- Did they find it ?
- Not according to all the reports.
But looking at this photo here,
the ship never returned to San Diego.
- Why do you say that ?
- In the rest of these satellite photos,
they track the ship through
the Panama Canal...
all the way to
Newport News, Virginia.
- The naval shipyard.
- But why would they go there ?
Maybe what they found
wasn't a Japanese sub.
Good evening, Mr. Sakari.
- [ Gagging ]
- [Engine Starts]
[ Clears Throat ]
Hi. Betsy Hagopian ?
No, I'm sorry.
Betsy's not here right now.
Is there some way that
I can get in touch with her ?
I'm sorry.
Um, my name is Dana Scully.
- I know you.
- No. I think you must be mistaken.
We saw you. Penny ?
Penny, come here.
I'm-I’m afraid I'm not
who you think I am.
Oh, my God.
She's one.
- One what ?
- One of us.
There must be some kind of mistake.
I-l work for the F.B.I.
- And I'm here conducting
a murder investigation.
- A murder ?
Cathy, I'm here at Betsy's.
Can you call the group and get
everyone over here right away ?
A man named Steven Zinnzser
was murdered about two miles from here.
- Penny, do you hear that ?
- Steve Zinnzser was murdered ?
- Did you know him ?
- He was a member of our chapter.
But you understand
I'm-I’m not a member.
- I'm an F.B.I. agent.
- That's what you said.
But at the door,
you said that I was one of you.
Did you have an unexplained event
in your life last year ?
Were you missing for a period of time
that can't be accounted for?
- Why did you ask me that ?
- I think you better sit down,
Miss Scully.
I think there's some people
you're gonna wanna meet.
Talapus ?
It's a salvage ship
registered in San Diego.
According to the harbormaster,
you went out to meet the boat...
when Customs wouldn't
allow it into port.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
But it wasn't Customs preventing
her landing. It was the D.E.A.
The D.E.A. ? Why ?
What was the problem ?
They were searching for contraband,
if I remember correctly.
Boat came through Panama.
There was some concern that her crew
might have picked up a shipment.
- Did they find anything ?
- We were never aboard.
I think there was a question
of confiscating the boat...
if the crew were
to be arrested.
- Were they ?
- Apparently not.
We were called off, and the boat
put out to sea the following morning.
- Well, that doesn't make any sense.
- Excuse me ?
The Talapus came nonstop from Panama.
She would've had to stop to refuel.
I don't have all
the details in my head.
Would you do me a favor ? Would you
see if there’s any paperwork on this ?
See if there’s a heading
or a destination for the Talapus.
- That might take some time.
- That's all right. I'm happy to wait.
But I've never met
any of you.
I-I’ve never seen any of you
before in my life.
You may not remember.
You've only had one experience.
Most of us here have
been taken many times.
Taken ? Taken where ?
The bright white place.
You remember it, don’t you ?
I don't know.
There are men there
performing tests.
What men ?
They don't reveal themselves.
They take our memories away.
But somehow they start
to seep back.
Some may have come back to you,
but they didn't make sense.
Do you know about
regression hypnosis ?
Yes, I'm--
Have you ever considered it ?
I'm sorry. I don't think
I'm ready to discuss this.
You're afraid to remember,
aren’t you ?
That's okay.
We were all afraid at first.
Agent Mulder ?
[Man] Got about five more
pallets here, Greg.
[ Air Horn Blasts ]
[Air Horn Blasts]
[Car Tires Skid]
I don't know. When I opened
that door and saw you standing there,
it was like a revelation.
The image of your face
was so clear to me.
But why is it
that I don't remember you ?
All you remember
in the beginning is the light.
And then sometimes the faces,
the men that performed the tests.
How do you know that you’re not
mistaking me for somebody else ?
You have the mark,
don’t you ?
What mark ?
Here, on the back
of your neck.
We all have them.
It's where they put the implants.
[Jars' Contents Rattling ]
I really have to go.
I just came--
- To see Betsy ?
- Yes.
To see Betsy Hagopian. Why are you
all at her house ? Where is she ?
What's wrong with her ?
Betsy's in the advanced stages
of an undiagnosed cancer ailment.
Her body’s full of tumors that won't
respond to any kind of treatment.
[Scully] And you think this is the
result of her abduction experiences ?
They've been taking Betsy
since she was in her teens.
- This is what's gonna
happen to all of us.
- What do you mean ?
I don't know if you
understand this or not, Dana,
but we're all gonna
end up like Betsy.
We're all dying because
of what they do to us.
[ Chattering ]
[Machinery Noise]
[Skinner] I think they found
what they were looking for.
Whoo.
I don't remember
giving you a key.
I came to see you.
Obviously, I was late for the party.
Yeah, I guess I should really
fire my maid, shouldn't I ?
Put the gun down, Mulder.
Somebody else might get hurt.
What are you talking about ?
Kazuo Sakari, the diplomat
that you detained yesterday.
Our murder suspect.
He didn't make
his fight last night.
This morning his body was found
floating face down in the C&O Canal.
I think we can assume
he wasn’t diving for pearls.
The Japanese government believes
that he was murdered for
the contents of a briefcase...
that he was carrying.
A piece of evidence that wasn't
logged in the time of his arrest.
What do they think
was in it ?
I've got the State Department
breathing down my neck, Mulder.
The Japanese are set to prosecute
this outside of diplomatic channels.
- So let's cut the crap.
- Am I being accused of murder ?
- Where's the briefcase ?
- Agent Scully has it.
- She has it in the trunk
of a rental car.
- And where is she ?
I don't know. I haven't spoken to her
since I left her in Allentown.
Then you better find her, because
whatever you stepped in on this case...
is being tracked into my office,
and I don't like the smell.
Mind if I tidy up
in here a bit first ?
This is bigger than me, you
or the F.B.I., Agent Mulder.
I hope you’ve got other
names in your phone book,
because I'm taking myself
off the hook on this one.
You're on your own.
- Hello, Fox.
- Thank you for seeing me
on such short notice.
I understand you're in
a difficult position.
Don't look so stunned.
I'm on the intelligence committee.
Secrets are the only
real currency we deal in.
- Then you already know
what I'm up against.
- Perhaps better than you do.
Which, I assume,
is why you’ve come here.
I need your advice
on how to proceed.
- Return the satellite photos.
- I'd be implicating myself.
A good chess player knows which
pieces to sacrifice, and when.
But I can't afford to become entangled
in a murder investigation. Not now.
- Why ?
- Because of what I've seen.
Because it would give them time to bury
it all where I might not find it again.
Do you trust me, Fox ?
Then let me earn your trust
with the truth.
I'm listening.
Several weeks ago
in Knoxville, Tennessee,
four Japanese nationals
were murdered.
All prominent doctors apparently engaged
in a highly classified project.
What kind of project ?
The autopsy of
an extraterrestrial life-form.
- Was that part of it ?
- I can't tell you.
Some secrets do remain secret,
Fox, even to me.
I was only just now given the names
of the murdered scientists.
Their credentials, however,
are a matter of public record.
Past deeds which may illuminate
present treacheries.
Your time is limited.
Before you become, as you say,
entangled in this...
past the point of
being about to...
fully understand or expose it.
What am I onto here ?
Monsters begetting monsters.
[Knocking At Door]
- Scully.
- Why is the door locked ?
I have something
to show you.
- Do you have any idea where I've been ?
- Allentown ?
I went to go see those MUFON
members to find out about
that woman, Betsy Hagopian.
What'd you find ?
I found out that she's dying,
along with a lot of other women
who claim to be dying too.
All of them who say that they
had these implanted in them.
It's the same thing that
I had removed from my own neck.
But you’re fine, aren’t you, Scully ?
Am I ? I don't know, Mulder.
Th-They said that they know me.
That they've seen me before.
It was freaky.
They know things about me,
about my disappearance.
Well, that is disturbing.
But I don't think you should freak out
until we find out what this thing is.
[Phone Ringing]
Mulder.
- I got a fax coming.
- What is this ?
That's a group of Japanese medical
officers taken during World War ll.
[ Scully]
I've seen this man before.
No, I don't think so. Not unless you
were in Japan in the last 50 years.
No, I've seen him before.
His name is Dr. Takeo Ishimaru.
He's been dead since 1 965.
He was the commander of
an elite section of the Japanese
medical corps known as 731,
a unit now known to have experimented
on human subjects.
They performed vivisections
without anesthesia,
tested frostbite tolerance
levels on infants,
exposed innocent prisoners
of war to diseases, the plague.
Like their Nazi counterparts,
they were never brought to justice.
What are you doing with these ?
Four of the doctors you see
were on that videotape I showed
you performing that autopsy.
Yeah, but they were in full
surgical dress. You couldn't
tell one from the other.
Somebody could, because those same
four men were murdered yesterday.
- Found here right on U.S. soil.
-[Beeping]
- Murdered for what ?
- That's what I'd like to know.
- Or murdered by whom ?
- Possibly our government.
Our government ?
For what possible reason ?
For continuing their work,
the work the Nazis were doing.
-Trying to create an alien/human hybrid.
-That is still a fantasy.
Scully, after all you've seen--
After all you've told me you’ve seen--
the tunnel filled with medical files,
the beings moving past you,
the implant in your neck,
why do you refuse to believe ?
Believing's the easy part, Mulder.
I just need more than you.
I need proof.
You think that believing is easy ?
-[Beeping]
- Well, we have proof.
I identified what those
five photos were tracking.
A ship that pulled a U.F.O.
off the bottom of the Pacific Ocean,
a U.F.O. that's in a warehouse
right now being guarded by
U.S. military personnel.
A U.F. O. that was probably carrying
that E.B.E. we saw on that autopsy tape.
- What am I looking at ?
- Part of our government's
secret railroad.
Train cars used
to carry test subjects,
used to conduct that autopsy
we saw being performed.
Where did you get this ?
From someone like you
who wants proof.
Who's also willing to believe.
[Man]
Hmm. Amazing.
Do you know what it is ?
Looks like some kind
of microprocessor.
So you’re saying
that this is manmade.
What else would it be ?
I mean, it's definitely
state of the art.
[ Beeping ]
The microlithography
is extremely complex.
I've never seen anything
even close to this density.
Anyway of finding out
who manufactures it ?
Uh, there are a few companies
out in San Jose, a couple in Boston.
It could be any one of them.
What are these chips used for ?
Video games, brake systems.
They're finding new apps every day.
I read about one being designed
to help the disabled operate
computers using brain waves.
How ?
Through direct electrochemical
interface with the cerebral cortex.
Pretty incredible, huh ?
Yeah.
[ Speaking Japanese ]
- [Japanese ]
- [Radio: Japanese]
[Japanese ]
[ Speaking Japanese ]
[Phone Ringing]
- Scully.
- Scully, it's me.
- Where are you ?
- The train yard in Quinnimont,
West Virginia.
A group of Japanese men just put
someone in one of those boxcars
we saw in the satellite photos.
I thought you said that it was
our government's railroad.
- Something serious
is going down here, Scully.
- What do you mean ?
The thing they put in
the train, it was alive.
- Mulder--
- I gotta get on that train.
It's hooking up with a Canadian
passenger train outside Cincinnati.
Mulder, I was right
about Dr. Ishimaru.
He isn’t dead.
In fact, he's on your videotape.
That's where you
know him from then.
No, that's not where
I know him from at all.
[ Chattering ]
[Voice From P.A. System:
indistinct]
[Man Over P.A.]
Your attention, please.
All passengers on Canadian
Northwest Express to Vancouver,
prepare for boarding
on track four.
Again, all passengers on Canadian
Northwest Express to Vancouver,
please prepare for boarding
on track four.
[ Tires Squeal ]
- Express Train to Vancouver,
what track is it on ?
- It just left.
- When did it leave ?
- You just missed it.
- It just pulled out of the station.
- Thanks.
Agent Scully.
What are you doing here ?
- Have you spoken to Agent Mulder ?
- No. Why ?
- He's in danger.
- How do you know ?
He's tracking a train.
You can't let him get on it.
I don’t know what
you're talking about.
You've got to get word to him.
Why should I trust you ?
You've lied to us before.
You're wasting time.
Do you understand ?
[ Tires Squeal ]
[ Phone Ringing ]
- [ Ringing ]
- Mulder.
- Mulder, don't get on the train.
- Why not ?
Because they know where you are
and they know what you’re doing.
Who told you that ?
Look, Mulder.
It’s just too dangerous.
Who told you, Scully ?
Scully, it's coming.
- Let it go.
- I can't.
Mulder, don't get
on the train ! Mulder ?
Mulder, don't !