Honey unit, I'm home! Monique!
Gunculon!
[BEEPS]
I wish I could believe that.
You're my half-brother, but there's no
law against killing the other half!
All My Circuits will return
after a word...
...from Slurm. It's addictive!
[PARTY MUSIC PLAYS]
Look! It's Slurms McKenzie.
He's the original party worm!
Ooh.
Whammy-wham-wham-wazzle.
Let's party!
Look at him go! Who says
there are no more heroes?
Hey, dudes! You can win
a chance to party with me...
...at the bottling plant on Wormulon.
Look for the golden bottle cap
inside cans of Slurm.
I won!
Odds are mathematically insignificant.
I like those odds.
Rats! Just another tooth.
Ahh.
Fry & the Slurm Factory
I gotta find that golden bottle cap.
I've never seen anyone so addicted.
This is nothing. In school,
I drank 1 00 cans of cola a week.
Right up until my third heart attack.
[GROANS]
-Bender, what's wrong?
-I'm sick.
[SNEEZES]
You poor baby. Let me check
if you have a fever. Ow!
According to his temperature gauge,
which you should use next time. . .
. . .he's running a fever
of 900 degrees.
[GROANS]
Bender, mon, lie yourself down.
You're paying for that.
I'll have a look, but I'm
an expert on humans, not robots.
I'm not Bender. I'm Fry.
-I thought you were the robot.
-Nope. Human.
All right. Spare me your life story.
What's the trouble?
My tummy hurts, and I'm having
this burning electrical discharge.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
Oh, boy.
I couldn't tell him.
It's fin fungus.
He'll be floating upside down
by morning.
You should try homeopathic
medicine like zinc.
-I'm 40o/o zinc.
-Then Echinacea or St. John's wort.
Or a big fat placebo.
It's all the same crap.
What's rattling around in there?
It may be the cause of his illness.
But, more importantly, it's a reason
to try out my latest invention.
To the laboratory!
I call this the F-ray.
It's an x-ray that lets you see
through anything, even metal.
The neutrino beam it emits
is dangerous. . .
. . .so you'll all need
protective goggles.
Huh?
You may feel a slight stinging
sensation. All of you.
PROFESSOR:
Ah-ha!
-That's the reason you're ill.
-That's my watch.
I was wondering where I put that.
Now I feel much better.
Thanks, professor.
And, Amy, I'm sorry I took your watch.
[SNICKERS]
[COUGHS]
I'll take this suit
to the decontaminators.
You lock up the F-ray.
And for the love of God, don't
let it fall into the wrong hands.
-What should we point it at first?
-Try it on me.
Ow! My sperm!
Neat. Mind if I try that again?
Didn't hurt that time.
Whoa, mama. Hold still, sexy lady.
-What?
-That's no lady!
One more upgrade and I'll
be more lady than you can handle.
Why are you so stupid?
-Bite my shiny, metal ass.
-You couldn't afford it, honey.
All this exposure to radiation
is making me thirsty.
If only we could know which
can had the winning bottle cap.
I didn't hear you. I was using
this to look inside of things.
Wait a second. I'm getting an idea.
No. False alarm. No. Yeah. No.
Yeah. No. Wait.
No. Yes!
[CRIES]
This stinks.
We checked 90,000 cans of Slurm
and all we won was this junk.
I never want to see another can
of Slurm again. I'm thirsty!
Fry, are you all right?
You did it, Fry!
You found the winning bottle cap!
[WHEEZES]
Hooray!
LEELA:
Look at that.
Welcome to the planet Wormulon!
I'm Glurmo, your guide to
the splendtacular Slurm factory.
Can we have our free Slurm?
You'll have all you can drink. . .
. . .when you're partying with my
good friend, Slurms McKenzie.
[PARTY MUSIC PLAYS]
All right!
Whammy-wham-wham-wazzle!
Lay some skin on me, dudes!
The original party worm!
Are you ready to get funky with us?
He better be.
That's why we pay him, right?
Right.
Slurms has to party all night
every night or he's fired.
WEARILY:
Rock on.
Before the party, you're in
for a funderful treat.
A VIP tour of the Slurm factory.
Enjoy the tour, dudes!
I'm gonna go lie down.
Welcome to the wondrous world
of whimsy that we call. . .
. . .Slurm Centralized lndustrial
Fabrication Unit.
[GASPING]
PROFESSOR:
Oh, my!
BENDER:
Look, flowers! And a boat!
[GRUNTING]
Who are those
horrible orange creatures?
Those are the Grunka Lunkas!
-They work in the factory.
-Tell them I hate them.
As we sail down the Slurm,
you'll see our mixologists at work.
They take 900
of the finest ingredients. . .
. . .add some child-like delight. . .
. . .and mix it with
glacial spring water. . .
. . .from our spring water generator.
Then we add the secret ingredient. . .
. . .that makes Slurm
so deliciously addictive.
-What's the secret ingredient?
-Whatever you want it to be!
-But what is it really?
-That's not for you to know.
Here the Grunka Lunkas are
inducing Wumpus berries. . .
. . .to release their flavor,
using sensual massage.
Psst.
-Those berries are the secret, right?
-No.
-You positive?
-Yes.
-Because they look kind of secret.
-Enough!
-There will be no more questions.
-Why?
Hey, look! The disgusting little men
are starting to sing.
Grunka Lunka dunkity doo
We've got a friendly warning for you
Grunka Lunka dunkity dasis
The secret of Slurm's
On a need-to-know basis
Asking questions in school
ls a great way to learn
If you try that stuff here
You might get your legs broke
We once found a dead guy
Face-down in the Slurm
It could easily happen again
To you folks
So keep your head down
And keep your mouth shut
Grunka Lunka Lunka dunkity dot
I don't pay you to sing.
You just used your bathroom break.
-Hard ass.
-I heard that.
On your right,
you see the Slurm Master. . .
. . .checking for color and bouquet.
So thirsty.
Then he tastes it.
He tastes it and tastes it.
Then tastes it more.
Could I have some Slurm?
No food or drink on the tour.
Wait until you party
with Slurms McKenzie.
-When is that?
-Soon enough.
-That's not soon enough.
-What's behind that door?
-Nothing.
-Is it the secret ingredient?
Grunka Lunka dunkity dinkredient
You should not ask
About secret ingredient
Okay, we get the point.
I was curious about the guards.
-Grunka Lunka dunkity darned guards--
-Shut up.
I could fire my staff and hire
Grunka Lunkas at half the cost?
That's right.
They don't have a good union.
They're like slaves.
What are you doing?
I'm thirsty. Grab my feet
and dunk my head in.
No. That's moronic.
Fine. I'll swim around
and drink as much as I want.
Help! I can't swim!
[WHISTLES]
Why did you jump in?
Everybody was doing it.
I just wanted to be popular.
[SCREAMING]
BENDER:
Ow!
Where are we?
And why is Slurm
pouring into this sewer?
This isn't Slurm.
Something's rotten on Wormulon. Look.
This is all about
the secret ingredient.
My God, what if the secret ingredient
is people?
There's already a soda like that.
Soylent Cola.
-How is it?
-It varies from person to person.
Do you have anything looser
around the thorax?
Yes, over in--
Weren't there more people
at the start of the tour?
Fry, Leela and Bender are missing.
If you'll excuse me.
Quick!
Phew.
Look! Slurm! Finally!
I'm never going 1 2 minutes
without a Slurm again.
This must be where they
put in the secret ingredient.
Whatever it is,
it's even better fresh.
Still warm.
-Oh!
-Ick!
Lordy!
Fry!
Phew.
That's the secret ingredient?
-That's the only ingredient of Slurm.
-Ew!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
I'll save us!
Oh, that feels good.
Thanks, Bender.
The exit! We made it.
Your Majesty, I brought the prisoners.
Well, my friends, you learned
the secret of Slurm.
That concludes the part
where you're alive.
You wish, you slimy worm.
Good work.
You have pleased your queen.
-Thanks, Your Majesty.
-Thanks.
People are drinking something
from your behind? It's gross.
Is it? Honey comes
from a bee's behind.
Milk is from a cow's behind.
Do you use toothpaste?
-Whose behind is that?
-I won't say.
We came to party with Slurms McKenzie.
-By the way, when is that scheduled?
-Never!
To the torture cave!
You, my metal friend. . .
. . .will have the honor
of becoming 1 74 Slurm cans.
This trip is a big letdown.
You will be submerged
in royal Slurm. . .
. . .which will turn you
into a Slurm queen like myself.
But she's a commoner.
Her Slurm will taste foul.
Yes! Which is why
we'll market it as New Slurm.
When everyone hates it. . .
. . .we'll bring back Slurm Classic
and make billions.
-What about me?
-You're free to go.
-Yes!
-If you can resist this SuperSlurm.
It's so delicious,
you'll eat until you explode.
Which reminds me, put a tarp
over that sofa. Bon appétit.
Mmm.
Farewell.
And congratulations again
on winning the contest.
Fry, untie us!
Here I come! Let me just--
One more taste.
You pig! Stop stuffing
your craw and save us!
-I can't see. Are we boned?
-Yeah, we're boned.
I can't stop eating
this delicious ooze.
But I won't let you die.
LEELA: Hurry!
BENDER: What's happening?
Phew.
Just in time!
No!
I could fit if I didn't
have these damn arms.
We're close. I can smell
those orange guys.
-Stop right there!
BENDER: Slurms McKenzie!
-Take me with you.
-Say what?
I'm partied out. All I want
is to stay home and rent videos.
-Is that so much to ask?
-Forget it!
This says you have to party with us.
All right! But not too many people.
I want to keep it small.
No can do, Slurms.
[SCREAMING]
This way!
-She's gaining on us!
-I'll hold her off.
But she'll crush you like a worm.
A smaller worm.
It's all right.
I'm so tired of partying.
So very tired.
I'll save you the only way I know how.
By partying!
-Babes?
-Mr. McKenzie?
You've served me well.
But this time, I party alone.
-But--
-There'll be other parties.
Now go! Go!
[PARTY MUSIC PLAYS]
Party on, Slurms.
Party on, contest winners. Party on.
No! We're ruined.
They know our disgusting secret!
My crew has made
a horrific discovery.
It seems that Slurm is produced
in a colossal worm hiney.
Hiney, you say.
With your testimony...
... we can finally outla w
this insidious Slurm.
Outlaw Slurm?
Don't pay any attention to him.
Grandpa 's making up stories again.
I'm not your grandpa.
You're my uncle from the year 2000.
Okay, Grandpa.
We'll take care of the bad worms,
don 't you worry.
I wish Slurms McKenzie
were here to enjoy this.
Yeah, he sure loved to party.
How about we all party
one last time for him?
-For Slurms.
[PARTY MUSIC PLAYS]
Hey, that's not that bad.
Mmm.