- Hi.
- Hey.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
When something's bothering me, I go running.
You've gone twice in less than 12 hours.
Hello?
Hey, Vaughn.
Yeah, she's right here.
Thanks.
Hey.
Sure. When do you want to meet?
It's definitely my father's handwriting.
But these entries --
- I know.
- I don't understand.
They're dated after his death.
Now you know about as much as I do.
I mean, either he didn't die when the CIA says he did,
which they may or may not know the truth about,
or someone wants me to think he's still alive.
You have nothing else but this?
I tracked down a guy -- Murdoch. He's mentioned in there.
He claims to have been on a mission with my father in 1982.
He says my dad shot him in the back and left him for dead.
He called my father a traitor.
I don't know what to believe.
What do we do?
Well, there are names of classified missions in there.
Let's get the details. I need access to all operational archives.
Now, I could put in a request to Langley --
But if someone is orchestrating this internally,
you don't want your name on an official request. I can do that.
You sure you don't mind?
Vaughn.
If your father's alive, we'll find him.
And if he's not, we will find the person who's doing this.
The Belarussian institute of science has developed a next-gen optical component.
It's called amplifying glass.
Now what is amazing about this is --
well, if my math is correct --
and it is --
what they've developed could boost a laser pulse by a factor of 10,000.
Maybe even higher.
Meaning you could take a simple aluminum gallium arsenide laser and --
uh, let me --
oh, you know how a cd player has a laser that will allow you to --
well, you take that laser, you amplify it by this lens,
you could shoot down a plane from the sky.
Or, you know, you take a tank, slice it in half.
Or you could even have an SUV --
Right. We got it.
We've been tracking intel which indicates
that the Jakarta faction wants the lens
and they've employed this man to acquire it for them.
His name is Cesar Martinez. He's an argentine resident.
Hola.
A few days ago, I tasked Nadia with working up a profile of him.
Martinez is freelance.
No loyalties. Excessive force -- that's his M.O.
He wrote his reputation with the execution of a former argentine intelligence officer --
Roberto Fox.
Any idea when Martinez is planning to make his move?
Signal intercepts indicates that he's developing a team.
It should be three days, a week at the most.
The institute of science is dedicating a new wing
to its research facility tomorrow night.
So our mission is to obtain the amplifying glass before Martinez does.
Sydney, you're on point.
Agent Vaughn, Weiss, and Santos, you'll be there for support.
This is a snatch-and-grab operation.
Are there any questions?
Cesar!
Hey.
I knew him -- Roberto.
The man Cesar Martinez killed.
If this mission is too difficult, too personal for you,
talk to your father and have him task someone else.
It's my job. I'll make it work.
Hey. Mitchell learned a new word.
- What was the word?
- Booshnot.
Mitchell's babyspeak for beta particle.
Uh,  anyway, here -- Sydney wanted me to give you these.
Access codes for the operational archives.
She wanted me to give them to you to give to her.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Anything else?
What's, uh...
what's going on?
Nothing.
You're lying to me. Right? Come on.
I'm smarter than you think.
I'll  tell you later.
You don't trust me, do you?
Marshall.
Yeah. That's my fault.
I propagate that image. Just like high school, junior high, elementary --
Marshall.
We should have lunch sometime.
Really? Yeah?
Oh, man, anytime. Absolutely. I'm there.
Today?
No.
No. That's cool.
I got a lot of stuff to do in the, uh...
- Thanks.
- You got it.
See you at lunch.
'Sup, buddy?
Outrigger, how we doing?
10 seconds, Phoenix.
The architect just arrived.
He has the PDA in his jacket.
Okay, great. Phoenix, you'll need to get right up next to him.
Cozy like.
The architect is a security freak.
He always carries copies of project files on him --
blueprints, schedules, even sketches.
So should show us which lab the glass is in.
What's she using to clone his PDA?
It's in her purse.
Low-frequency wi-fi scans and clones.
Thing is, its working radius, it's only a couple of feet,
which is why she needs to, you know, get right --
Oh, here it comes.
Oh, great.
Syd -- I'm sorry, Phoenix,
it's what I was afraid of.
It's encrypted.
The PDA -- it's protected with a handwriting recognition software,
so time to turn on the charm.
It's the look, the feel, the bend of paper,
but actually it's a microscopic layer of nonconductive polymer,
- and it's sandwiched --
- Marshall, not the time.
Vaughn asked me to lunch.
Okay. Signature...
plus a password...
plus a little Flinkman secret sauce,
and... nice.
Bow before me and weep, encryption gods.
Okay, blueprints and security protocols for the research facility.
I've got the location of the glass.
Evergreen, we're going to need that access key. You're a go.
Anyone have a visual on the scientist?
He's holding court, due east.
That was easy.
Okay, Merlin, showtime.
The  lab -- it's on the 15th floor. East corridor.
Martinez is here.
Cesar Martinez is in the building.
Anyone see his backup?
Sit tight, Evergreen.
This might be recon on his part.
If this was recon, we would have known he was here.
He's making his play.
- How do you know?
- Trust me.
We need to grab him.
- Phoenix is almost inside.
- You don't understand.
Phoenix, abort. Six hostiles on the move with force.
I can make it.
Who do you work for?
You forgot to say the magic word.
Now you're gonna have to say "pretty please."
Last chance.
Who do you work for?
She works with me.
Nadia?
He had his men secure us in the lab.
By the time we escaped, he was gone.
When I tasked you to do research on Cesar Martinez,
why didn't you inform me the two of you knew each other?
He was not supposed to be there.
I didn't know we'd make contact.
You knowingly withheld intel that would have altered options during the operation.
I've suspended agents from field duty for less than that, Nadia.
Her knowing Martinez was the only thing that saved my life.
The story, Nadia -- what is it?
We met when I was young.
After the orphanage, I was on my own,
and Cesar was one of the boys I ran around with.
We got in trouble with the police.
We went our separate ways.
Why do I feel there's more?
If you want me to sit at a desk after this, fine.
But it is personal now.
Please, let me get the glass back from Cesar.
I know how to contact him. I can do it.
She had a relationship with him. She can use him.
You of all people should appreciate that.
Reach out to Martinez.
He's acquiring this for somebody else.
Find out if we can buy it for ourselves.
Sydney, you and Weiss will be backup on this.
Let me be clear, Nadia.
I expect full disclosure from you.
Bueno.
Withholding information from Sloane I can accept.
I don't care much, really. But from me?
You and I are in the field together.
I need to know there's a level of trust.
What do you want to know?
What did Martinez whisper to you?
I told you. He said "call me."
Sydney, that's it.
Are you telling me there's nothing else?
For the last time, I'm sorry I didn't tell you about Cesar.
But there's nothing else you need to know.
Sí.
How's it going?
I cross-check my father's list against the CIA archives,
and there are still missions I can't verify even existed.
Am I insane to think this old journal's going to help me find my father?
These are the ones you can't find?
Yeah.
Give me the pen.
What if these aren't operation names?
What are you doing?
Substitution cipher.
Okay, how'd you see that?
My father used to encrypt my crossword puzzles when I was a kid.
The least of my childhood dysfunctions.
Try that.
When's your plane leave?
Half an hour.
I wish I could stay.
Yeah, I'll, I'll take it from here.
Nadia.
Hola.
Nadia...
Evergreen, you cannot proceed without comms.
Evergreen, abort this mission now.
Nadia...
What the hell is she doing?
Portugal.
All right, I'll go this way.
Okay.
Syd.
Anything?
Ah, come on.
Diego?
Diego.
Dios mío.
No!
Nadia...
No.
Diego. Diego.
Diego!
We lost him here at Plaza Del Camino.
Yeah, Martinez said he was taking her to his office
to make the exchange. It's got to be close.
Since learning of Nadia's history with Martinez, I did some digging.
Martinez owns several pieces of property,
including Roberto Fox's training facility.
Nadia.
Nadia!
I'm fine.
There's a safe inside.
The amplifying glass should be there.
All right, come on.
The first and only time I met your father,
he was covered in blood with a baby in his arms.
Nadia.
He brought her to the orphanage in Buenos Aires.
He said she was in danger.
He'd been shot in the shoulder.
I knew not to ask too many questions.
Your father, he stayed for a few days,
until he was well enough to travel.
One morning I woke up and he was gone.
I don't understand.
If he knew you in Buenos Aires,
why would he encode this address in Lisbon in his journal?
I don't know.
You thought he might be here.
I am sorry.
I wish I knew more.
Can you remember anything? Something he said, maybe a detail?
Nightingale.
Nightingale?
He was on the phone, and something in his voice --
It was important to him.
May I ask you a question?
Sure.
Nadia -- how is she?
She's good.
Synchro/Transcript: RaceMan/Travis
www.forom.com