Bonsoir, madame.
Margeaux Gerard.
She's in position. No sign of Connelly.
He'll reveal himself.
Madame.
Merci.
Okay, she's just made the announcement.
I thought you might not come.
You underestimate me already.
Well, I almost didn't come.
Why is that? Crisis of conscience?
I thought I might find a buyer willing to pay more.
I am not here for small talk, monsieur Connelly.
Are you selling or no?
I presume you brought the down payment.
We may have a possible third party.
Sending you a visual, Outrigger.
Got it. Searching for a match.
So what are your plans
with your new purchase?
Monsieur Connelly,
where...
is...
the chip?
This is my way out.
Anything, Outrigger?
Come on.
No matches, Shotgun.
With this sale, I can buy a new life --
a house on the Mediterranean.
Maybe get a dog.
We're under fire!
Lâche le couteau!
Freeze!
He won't get me.
My family.
I'm not gonna be made an example of.
I won't have it.
My wife...
my kids.
Put down the knife.
Marshall ran analysis of the memory chip recovered in Paris.
The downloaded information confirms that a biometric targeting device
is in fact being developed at a secure facility in Austria.
Attached to a weapons system,
this device would facilitate the targeting of an individual
based solely on a DNA sample or a biometric scan.
Next gen sniper.
Precisely.
That's why I want you on a plane to Salzburg by nightfall.
Standard retrieval operation.
But...
the man who killed himself?
He was sent there to intercept the sale.
When the assassin realized that the mission was a failure,
he killed himself to protect his family from his employer.
Sasha Korjev.
I don't know that name.
Korjev is a monster.
He's run arms to rebel forces in Rwanda, Sierra Leone, Angola,
and holds a very tight leash over his men.
Amongst Korjev's tactics is leveraging the lives of their families.
And it's Korjev's network that's developing the targeting device?
Yes, that's correct,
but now that we have confirmation that Korjev is alive,
I'm tasking Dixon to locate his whereabouts.
He'll report to CIA proper.
They'll send a tactical team to secure his arrest.
I have a liaison at the angolan chancery in D.C.
Put Dixon on something else.
You want to take this over?
For the sake of expediency.
What am I missing?
Okay, Jack. It's yours.
Good luck in Salzburg.
I'm telling you, this is a mistake.
You got to bring the team in on this one.
No way. Not until I find out more.
All right, let's just assume that your father did write those journals --
Look, I know my father's handwriting, all right?
Things were referenced.
Things he couldn't know about. I know it sounds crazy --
No, the Sox winning the series is crazy.
What we're talking about doing here is insane.
The nurse who led me to those journals, she disappeared. She was a plant.
Fine, so someone's trying to manipulate you.
What if my father's still alive?
What if it's his way of trying to contact me?
Okay.
Okay, but why now?
Why let you and your mother believe that he's been dead for 25 years?
I don't know. That's what I'm gonna find out.
Hey.
What's this? Who's Frank Murdoch?
The code name that you asked me to check in the journals.
He's ex-special forces.
Changed his name several times, finally settled on Frank Murdoch.
He runs a furniture repair shop outside San Diego.
You didn't tell anyone else about this, did you?
D ude.
Nadia?
Hey.
Thanks.
The angolan chancery in D.C. Hmm.
Don't you think that's a bit thin, Jack?
You should have brought this to me first.
The details of Sasha Korjev's mission are classified.
As far as anyone else is concerned,
the assignment is merely to tag the location.
The  CIA wants him assassinated.
Which is why I thought it unfair to burden you with this.
Dixon has the necessary experience.
With Dixon it would have to be a distance hit.
I'll be able to get close to Korjev.
Oh, I'm aware of that.
And frankly, that concerns me.
I'll be fine.
Korjev should have been eliminated years ago...
when I had the chance.
Man, look at you. Back from the dead.
Hello, Jimmy.
You look awful.
I keep telling myself -- green vegetables.
Got to eat more of them.
But, uh, you know how that is.
So, uh, Jack, you come bearing gifts?
Only the best.
This -- this was hard to find.
Is this, uh...
I thought that it was just a rumor.
Ah! Ha ha. Jack...
Uh, what do you want?
- Information.
- Anything.
The protocol for contacting Sasha Korjev.
Um... come on, Jack. You know I can't.
I'm disappointed, Jimmy.
I thought you were a true connoisseur.
Seriously, man, that's just not right.
Jack! Uh, please.
Korjev finds out it was me...
My life may not be worth much.
Wh-whatever.
Still --
Okay.
I'll, uh...
I'll lay it out for you.
One small step for Mitchell Flinkman,
one giant leap for mankind.
Look at those legs.
He's edible. He's delicious.
I've taken many a chomp.
Add a little salt and pepper.
He's the best. Makes it all worth it.
Sorry. Speaking of which -- Salzburg.
Now, according to the memory chip,
Korjev's storing the targeting system in the sub-basement
of a discotheque at he owns called the Club Felice,
which officially begs the question, what is it with these guys and nightclubs?
Korjev's regional security chief is a Jeremiah Gauster.
Gauster has instituted a security protocol based on access cards.
You'll need a level 3 clearance to enter the belly of the building.
Since the access card hardware is annoyingly difficult to duplicate,
you'll need to steal one from one of the nightclub employees.
Not bad.
Definitely in the ballpark.
Oh, my gosh, thank you for being an american.
I don't think I could bear mangling the language in front of one more local.
Shouldn't feel bad.
These people like to be offended. It's their comfort zone.
Let me guess. Upstate New York.
Yeah. Yeah, Rochester.
How'd you know that?
I went to Buffalo state. Undergrad.
Come on. Go Bengals.
Don't even say that. It makes me want to cry. God, I miss it so much.
This time of year, me and my girlfriends should be grabbing
two beef on weck and a six-pack, you know --
Oh, look at me -- root from the nosebleeds.
There's nothing like roast beef and pilsner in 30-degree weather,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Sam!
That's me.
Sam.
Sorry I can't help you with your drink.
Barback.
The good thing/bad thing about living in Austria --
smoking's not prohibited.
Ergo, you've just developed a smoking habit.
No, thanks.
Good answer. Just checking.
It is actually a mag strip encoder.
Just slide it through here like so.
It will analyze the access control algorithms,
extrapolate the clearances,
and then reprogram the card to give you full access.
- Hey.
- Sam.
- Do you need a light?
- No.
Thank  you.
I was just looking.
Didn't mean to scare you.
Whoops. Duh. Found it.
Um, so, listen. Uh...
I never do this. Really.
But, um, I've been here for six months,
and, uh, I don't really know anybody.
At least not anybody who knows about beef on weck, so...
That smile and those dimples are
pretty much the greatest thing I've ever seen, so
I thought if I didn't come over --
I have a boyfriend.
Right. No, right. Of course you do.
But thank you.
Guy's gotta try.
Where's the bathroom?
It's, uh, just -- just --
Merlin?
Okay, I got you, Phoenix.
Heading in.
No one's supposed to be down there.
Run a sweep on section Delta.
Pull up all the employee access records.
Let's find out who's down there.
What do you see?
Workstations cleared.
Hang on.
Status report, operation Hawkeye, dated... today.
Open it up.
Nothing.
The report's embedded.
"Transport protocol enacted. Delivery on schedule."
They moved the targeting device.
"Scheduled to leave the country at 0600 hours."
Okay.
Let's see. Checking airfields and shipping yards.
"Installation complete. Status -- field ready."
My god.
It's already weaponized.
Syd?
Syd? Syd, are you okay?
Operation Hawkeye -- where's it being shipped out of?
- Tell me.
- No.
Sam Houser.
Breach initiated by Sam Houser. Club level employee.
All units, locate and detain him.
Wasn't a yes or no question.
The name of the shipping yard.
Delongpre shipping.
Syd, are you okay?
We're going in.
Let's get him.
I'm okay.
Be careful, okay?
What do you have?
Houser, Samuel David.
Living for a half a year in Austria on a student visa.
Odd jobs, owes money on some overdue movie rentals.
Other than that, he's just a guy.
Hey.
Let's get out of here.
Uh, but you said you had a boyfriend, and I thought --
A girl can change her mind, right?
Uh, I don't get off for like another hour,
but you could wait for me at the bar or I --
Mm. Mm. Mm-hmm.
If you don't leave with me right now, you will regret it.
All right, well, we could slip out the back door.
You took the words right out of my mouth.
Go check over there.
Delongpre shipping is 30 miles outside of Salzburg.
I have an in-country contact.
Use him. Have him supply you for the mission.
We need to secure the weapon before it leaves port.
If we cross over to Filton, I know a great wine bar.
I'm sorry. I'm on the phone with my sister.
Where's the phone?
We have another situation. A civilian.
Korjev's team tagged him as my accomplice. I can't leave him.
Pass him off to your contact.
We'll have him reestablished stateside by the weekend.
That cell is insane.
The guy at the store told me mine was the smallest,
but I knew he was jobbing me.
Sam?
Yeah?
There's something I have to tell you.
You're having second thoughts.
It's not about that.
If it's about your boyfriend, let me just say --
Forget about the boyfriend.
Well, maybe we could just go back to my place and talk then.
It would be nice to have a normal conversation,
if you don't mind a mess.
- Sam.
- Yeah.
You can never go back to your place.
- What?
- Listen to me.
Your bosses at the club are bad men.
I  was there tonight to stop them from doing a bad thing.
Wait a minute. I'm --
I needed your access card, and I took it.
And now they think we work together.
Work together?
What about beef on --
Who the hell are you?
I need you to trust me right now.
Oh, is that what you need?
Okay, that's good, because
I got to get back to work so I can get away from the mind games.
Wait.
If you go back there, they will kill you.
You're serious?
But if you stick with me, I promise I'll protect you.
We have ways of handling these situations.
Who's "we"?
I can't tell you that.
Hold on. You've already lied to me once.
So how do I know that you're not one of the bad guys?
If I was one of the bad guys,
you'd already be dead.
Thanks, Joe.
Hi. I'm looking for someone. Frank Murdoch. Do you know him?
Nope.
Never heard of him.
Well, this shop's registered to his name.
What are you, a cop?
No, it's a personal matter regarding my father.
Tell you what.
If ever you get your memory back,
tell him Michael Vaughn's looking for him.
That's my number. Thanks for your help.
You're really Bill Vaughn's kid?
Yeah.
That's your dad in the middle.
That's me on the right.
Everyone else is dead.
You think he's still alive?
Well, I hope not.
When was the last time you saw him?
The Falkland conflict.
We were supposed to lead a team of locals to secure a british position.
Our men were ambushed.
And Bill didn't even flinch.
I broke command, charged in to defend our men,
and the next thing I know, my legs went numb.
He shot me in the back.
I don't remember hitting the ground,
but I remember lying there looking up at him completely paralyzed,
and he just stared down at me, lit a cigarette,
and walked away.
That's the last I ever saw him.
I can't believe that's true.
Yeah, well, if he's still alive,
I'll give you one piece of advice.
Don't turn your back on him.
Who are you calling?
Oh, right, right, right. Sorry. My bad.
Good evening.
Phoenix inquiring about a late-night snack.
And how many will we be serving?
Two. One house special, the other will be ordering off the menu.
When will you be joining us?
As soon as possible.
I'll make sure the table is ready.
Thank you.
Let me guess.
That wasn't a real restaurant.
Hello?
I'll have them for you shortly.
Good. I assure you, mr. Tauber,
Sasha Korjev will be made aware of your allegiance.
That is all I ask.
I'm looking for the Rug Merchant.
His shop is sixty kilometers up the Bantu River.
When are they coming?
It should be soon, Sam.
I'm not stupid, okay?
I understand what happens in the witness protection program.
I get shipped off to some boring suburb.
They pick a name right out of the episcopalian registry.
I don't get to see my family anymore.
You think my mother's gonna be able to handle that?
When I know everything's safe, I'll let her know you're okay.
You know what the real pisser of this whole thing is?
Is I came here to pump some thunder through my veins.
Try to find some inspiration,
maybe take a shot at writing something.
Didn't happen.
Just...
drank a lot of beer.
Here we go.
Agent Bristow. So good to see you again.
Is this the cargo?
This is Sam. Yeah.
We'll have him whitewashed within the hour.
Come, please. No worries. Your supplies are in the vehicle.
You have a weapon for me?
Of course, my dear.
But let's get out of the cold first, hmm?
We need to get out of here. We're not safe.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Sam, take my hand. We have to go.
Look at what you did to him.
We just got blindsided, and we dealt with it.
That doesn't meanwe give up. It doesn't change who we are.
I'm on your side.
I'm not gonna lie to you, Sam.
I'm not gonna have the supplies I was counting on.
I can't promise you how this thing is gonna turn out.
You don't have backup?
I'm it.
I need you to think.
Do you know any back ways to the Delongpre shipping yards?
I mean -- yeah, you could take the metro. Why?
The people who are after us have a weapon they shouldn't have.
I want to take it from them before they use it and people die.
Let's go to the metro.
Hey, hold on.
You do understand that I don't have any skills...
in the physical sense.
It's okay. I got you.
Come on. Come on.
This is your stop.
Remove his hood.
Untie his hands.
Did this man carry identification?
Yes, sir.
And do you know who he is?
Sir, I --
I didn't --
You strike this man, you strike me in the heart. Understand?
Jack, my dear friend.
Hello, Sasha.
I apologize for that scene outside.
I've always remembered what you taught me --
treat your men like children.
Give them rope to become their own men.
But if they make mistakes,
hang them with it.
I'd say my lessons have served you well.
I'd ask how you managed to find me, but I know you too well.
You can rest assured, you're well insulated.
I do what is necessary to stay alive.
After all, I don't have you or the CIA to watch my back anymore.
I must say, I was shocked at how abruptly our association ended.
One day we are working together, arming a rebellion.
The next, you're gone.
My mandate changed.
Yet here you are.
Why are you here, Jack?
I'm entering the private sector.
Now that I'm out from under their watchful eye, I was hoping
we could talk business.
It would be my honor to work with you.
Excuse me.
Yes?
The delivery of the package is proceeding on schedule.
Keep me posted.
Jack, I want to show you my zoo.
It was a dusty ride.
Of course. Forgive me.
I have an 18-year-old single malt that should remedy that, huh?
Excellent.
Jack, I'd like you to meet my wife.
Lani.
- Pleasure.
- The Jack?
The one.
Then the pleasure is all mine.
I hope you'll be staying a while.
I'd like to get to know the man my husband talks about.
That's very kind, but I'm not certain how long I can stay.
Well, dinner at least.
I'll see that the staff prepare something wonderful.
Truly, it's so good to finally meet you.
You too.
I need to steal Sasha from you just a moment.
Certainly.
Make yourself comfortable in my office. First door on the right.
Can you tell what it is?
UAV assault chopper.
It's kind of small.
- They customized it.
- What?
The biometric targeting system -- it's in the chopper.
Once that thing locks onto its target, there's no hiding.
So that thing kills people?
- Can you drive this thing?
- Yeah.
Remember whan you said you wanted to pump some thunder into your veins?
You're about to get your chance.
I'll get the weapon.
You drive the van into the warehouse.
Pick me up in three minutes.
Don't touch that. I'll be in my office.
You can do this, Sam.
Just... stay cool, man.
- Get in.
- Here. Take this.
Get down! Stay inside!
I missed.
I noticed.
That guy was my boss, and he shot me.
- It doesn't hurt.
- It will soon.
Oh. Oh.
We did it, huh?
We saved the world.
Something like that.
She's lovely your wife.
Indeed. We just found out -- she's pregnant.
Congratulations.
I'll be honest with you.
When we first saw the heartbeat, I was scared.
I thought, what kind of a father will I be?
But seeing you here, I'm reminded
of the tools you've given me, the tools of being a man.
I gave you the tools. You chose how to use them.
There was a time, Jack,
when we were both working for the higher purpose
but our goals were not the same.
That became clear when you and your agency decided to abandon me.
I realized on that day how naive I'd been.
I had no option but to pick myself up,
stay on course,
because that is the man you taught me to be.
I know there are some in your government that see my business as a form of betrayal --
You betrayed me.
Mr Korjev asked not to be distirbed. He'll be out shortly.
I need a car. I need to go to town.
- Hey.
When did you get back?
About an hour ago.
Did you find Murdoch?
Nah, I couldn't track him down.
Ready?
We should go.
We're going to the movies. Want to come?
Oh. No, thanks. Not tonight.
Is it important? We don't have to go.
Oh, no. No, no. You guys go. I'll see you tomorrow.
All right.
- Good night.
Hey.
I spoke to my people,
they spoke to people.
It's safe for you to go back home.
I think I'm done here.
It's time for me to move on.
Must kill you.
Get to do all these crazy things
and see all these amazing places.
You gotta keep it to yourself.
You know what? It's not so bad.
It gives people like us something in common.
"People like us," huh?
Hey.
I'll see you around the globe.
Goodbye, Sam.
Hey Dad! I heard you located Korjev.
Yes, I did.
Sloane said he was taken in a standoff. Were you there?
I saw it play out.
Heading home?
Yeah, I'm gonna grab some dinner first.
Okay.
- Good night.
- Godd night.
Dad!
I'm kind of hungry myself --
if you wouldn't mind the company.
What about your report?
It'll keep.
Transcript/Synchro: RaceMan/Travis
www.forom.com