Drop your weapons!
I need suppressive fire!
You wanted to see me?
Has Vaughn contacted you yet?
I'd have mentioned it, don't you think?
Sydney, we pulled Vaughn's phone records,
and they indicate that he sent you an SM message to your cell.
I would like to give you the benefit of the doubt
and assume that it got lost in transmission and that you never received it.
If you're looking to catch me in a lie, yes, I got the message.
When Vaughn took off, as I've already told you, I tried to stop him.
He hit me.
He contacted me to tell me he was sorry.
Which I didn't consider professionally relevant.
As far as where he is or what he's doing, I still have no idea.
He disappeared with a dangerous piece of technology.
I have no choice but to notify Langley.
Vaughn isn't a traitor. He would never do what he's doing without a reason.
Vaughn went rogue on a sanctioned mission.
Out of consideration for you,
I'll give him 48 hours to either return
or contact me with an explanation.
In the meantime, we will withhold his status from the rest of A.P.O.
Should this matter come to light,
I don't want anyone else complicit in this deception.
Thank you.
Sydney?
If Vaughn should contact you...
You'll know.
Non, merci.
Going somewhere?
- You're late.
- Hardly.
I've been watching you for an hour.
Yeah? Am I your type?
Had to make sure you came alone, followed instructions.
Beignet?
Can we just get this done?
Look around. It's Paris in the springtime.
I'm only interested in answers.
In exchange, you were supposed to bring me something today.
Your big prize is in a safe place.
That's not the deal.
It is now.
You're bluffing.
Don't forget, I know how desperate you are.
No way you're willing to walk away.
Oh, I suppose that depends on how badly you want it.
'Cause personally, what the hell am I gonna do with a transforming coil?
Talking personally?
I don't have a use for it either.
Well, then you can tell your employer exactly what I'm telling you.
You'll get the coil when you tell me everything you know about my father.
- A volcano?
- Yeah. Yeah.
It's all of yellowstone. It's like a funnel.
And the thing is that on average, it blows every 600,000 years.
Well, then I don't think we have to worry about it.
No, no, no. It hasn't blown for 600,030 years. We're due, sister.
What is this? Fancy chocolate?
That's not for you.
No, it is. I like fancy chocolate.
Where is the freezer bag? I left it in the car.
- I'll get it.
- No, no, no, no, no.
You chill.
Hello?
You have a collect call from prisoner 41958
from the Quantico women's detention center.
- Do you accept the charges?
- Yes, I do.
- Nadia?
- Hello, Katya.
I was worried about you.
I'm sorry. I couldn't get away yesterday,
but I'm planning to visit tomorrow.
That's wonderful.
I have a little gift for you.
Forgive me for calling. It's just that your visits,
it makes this place bearable.
I'll be there tomorrow.
Uh, you heard from Vaughn?
Mnh-mnh. Not yet.
It's got to be tough on him, right?
Going to visit your uncle, and all you can do is watch him die,
nothing you can do about it?
Yeah.
My mom used to do stuff like that.
Like what?
Scrub the sink
when she was worried about stuff that was out of her control.
I like a clean sink.
Mm-hmm.
But you would tell me if there was something that I needed to be concerned about?
Of course.
Yeah, it's me. No deal.
He says he has the coil but he wants answers first.
He wants to talk to you.
Hello?
You violated our agreement.
You listen to me. I'm sick and tired of these games.
Here's how we're gonna do things.
You're angry? Good.
You  can channel that into your next assignment.
No, no. No more assignments. You got what you asked for.
You didn't abide by the terms of our deal.
The price has just gone up.
Disobey again, and it will continue to do so.
No, that's it. I'm done.
- Check beneath the table.
- What?
Beneath the table there's an envelope. Open it.
If you still wish to back out, feel free to do so.
He's alive.
Your  father is very much alive.
The question, Mr. Vaughn, is how far are you willing to go to find him?
That was lovely.
It's a folk song our father used to sing about a russian robin hood.
It was one of your mother's favorites.
So good to see you again, sweetheart.
- Shouldn't be a problem.
- Sorry, I just --
Well, considering the hearings, I'm sure the D.D.O. has his hands full.
Of course. Give my regards.
Sorry, um, requisition forms.
The secure server to Langley went down.
I did what I could, but I'll need all-new servers and a VS-2 module, so...
Great. If you could also sign here...
Uh, by the way, since the, you know, incident,
have you had a chance to see a doctor?
'Cause the radiation levels in that chamber were near-lethal, so...
I'm fine, Marshall. Is there anything else?
No. Thank you.
Our family didn't have much. Just the necessities.
But your mother had no intention of denying herself.
After school, she would go to the St. Basil cathedral
where all the tourists were, so careless with their money,
so easy to pickpocket.
- How old was she?
- Young.
Still in grade school.
She used the money to buy us candy
until our father discovered what she had been doing.
Yelena and I were terrified, but not your mother.
She stood there finishing the candy, smiling.
We were waiting for her to get hit,
but instead our father laughed looking at this little rebel in front of him.
Your mother can be quite stubborn, much like your sister.
How is Sydney?
Katya, I've told you --
I know, I know. She's off limits.
Thank you.
Of course.
My mother --
Irina -- did she ever talk about me?
It's happening sooner than I expected.
What's happening?
I'm deathly allergic to chocolate.
In 15 seconds,
my breathing will become difficult.
Katya --
And I will lose consciousness.
Tell Sydney this is how far I'm willing to go to see her.
Guard! I need help now!
- Tell Sydney!
- Guard!
I know what you're thinking.
You'll find them on your own, right?
What are we doing here?
Waiting. I hired a team of independent contractors to help us with the job.
Which is what?
- Assume that's not important.
- Assume it is to me.
All you need to know is it's an instruction manual of sorts.
Now that coil you got for us --
apparently it wasn't being used properly.
That's terrific. Like I said, I don't care about the coil.
I'm just like you, man.
The less I know, the less guilt I feel.
Yeah, we're a lot alike.
Where do you think he was during the funeral?
I mean, when you were mourning by his grave with your mom.
You know, it's usually a girlfriend.
At least that's why my old man took off.
But I tell you what. My mom --
can't say I really blame him.
Coming?
Waste of time.
.45 caliber. It's not like you need to make it more dangerous.
Maybe not, but it makes me feel better.
You said an hour.
Yeah, well, we had to take a detour.
This is Mike.
So is he any good, or just eye candy?
Like I said, he's the man with the technical skills to get what we need done.
That's Sabina, this is Gregor, and that's Jan over there.
Mikey, pour you a pint.
I don't usually drink till the job's finished.
You drink with me, or you cut bullets with Jan. Your choice.
Yeah, well, how about I do neither and you tell me why the hell we're here.
Okay, so this is a two-pronged plan.
Now, tomorrow at midnight,
an armored transport will be leaving Darmstadt carried a very valuable item.
We will be stealing that item.
But to do it, we're gonna need a cold laser.
Prototype has not even hit the streets yet.
It's in a secure R&D wing in a private hospital in Bordeaux.
Heavily guarded.
C ivilians?
Yeah. You got a problem with that?
No.
I got your message. What is it?
Dixon has been taken out of the field of rotation.
I know. I authorized it.
Yes, I see your signature all over the release forms.
Do you really think we can afford to be down one agent
when Vaughn's whereabouts are still unknown?
We didn't have a choice.
The director of the DSR contacted me directly.
And since for the moment we're keeping Vaughn's status confidential,
I thought it best to comply with his request.
I see.
What exactly is the nature of Dixon's assignment?
I'm afraid that's confidential as well.
From you or from me?
Come on, Jack, you don't have to be a genius to know what this is about.
Rambaldi.
Now while I accept that these matters are above my purview,
Dixon is a member of my task force,
and it's my responsibility to know what actions and risks he's taking on.
It's a routine transport.
Darmstadt.
And I assure you the risks are minimal.
Syd, Clippers tickets. Third row, center. I can't go.
Langley's tasked me for a special assignment.
You're kidding.
Well, I would love to, but I'm swamped.
And I was going to go with my son,
so I tell him I can't go. He says it's actually good because he has a date.
He's 12.
Why doesn't he take her to the game?
Apparently she'd rather go to a movie.
I'm sure you've taught him well.
- Dinner when I get back?
- Yeah. Sure.
We need to talk.
How long have you been seeing her?
It was our third visit.
This is --
this is exactly why I warned you about her.
Katya's the only person
who has ever been willing to answer my questions about Irina.
Irina Derevko was manipulative and cruel.
She was also our mother.
Which makes it harder to accept, I know, but trust me --
I know her crimes.
I also know how once she helped you and the CIA.
Until she betrayed us. She always did.
There's more to her than what's in her file.
Katya told me stories.
And you believed her?
Some of it, yes.
Then you're deluding yourself, Nadia.
I'm sorry.
I've been through this before.
Katya is doing the same thing to you that Irina did to me.
Telling me what I wanted to hear,
appealing to what I wanted more than anything else in the world -- a mother.
A family.
It was all a manipulation.
Do you want to know the truth about our mother?
Our mother put a hit on my life.
Our mother tried to have me killed.
Why didn't you tell me?
There was never a reason to.
Oh, my god, Syd. If I knew, I --
Where is she? Katya?
She's in the hospital.
They're keeping her for observation.
I always hated going to the doctor.
Let's go get the laser.
There it is.
I need some light.
How long will this take?
Hold still. We can't risk destroying the emitter.
Wire cutters.
Can't we just unplug it or something?
Sure, if you don't mind blowing it up
and killing us both in the process.
Argon canister. It's under pressure.
So you're CIA.
Is that what Roberts told you?
He said you were in a period of transition.
I guess you could say that.
I went through the training program.
Camp Perry.
Cia was looking for female agents with russian language skills.
They rejected me.
Yeah, but you're probably better off.
That's what I figure. More profit...
and more fun, too.
This should do it.
Let me help.
I'm good, thanks.
Bon. D'accord.
Look out!
Let's go.
We need to leave now.
You could use a few stitches, I suppose.
That  won't be necessary.
Fine. Let it scar. Who knows?
It might toughen you up a bit.
I saw the look on your face when I killed that guard.
I saved your life.
Thanks.
Don't tell me you're torn up inside.
I thought you agency boys were tougher than that.
It was him or me. I'm okay with that.
You could have fooled me.
You haven't stopped brooding since we left the hospital.
Yeah, well, maybe it's because I don't like being here with you.
You know what I think?
This is exactly where you want to be.
Consider this the second time you've been rejected by the CIA.
Understand this.
Talk to my sister again, I will make sure you regret it.
The protective sister. How charming.
And how satisfying it must be for you to know
you have it all figured out.
I would think you of all people
should know the world is never black or white.
The last time I saw you, aunt Katya,
you tried to put a bullet in my head.
Given the opportunity, I wouldn't mind seeing you suffer.
Consider this visit a warning.
Leave Nadia alone.
I had no intention of killing you, nor did your mother.
What do you know about that?
I know you believe your mother put out a contract on your life.
Surely you must have asked yourself why she would want you eliminated.
And I'm willing to bet you haven't come up with a satisfying answer.
Your mother loved you.
And to look at you now and see how quickly you've abandoned her --
if she only knew, she would be ashamed.
I'm not having this conversation.
Before dying, Irina tried to contact me.
She believed someone was setting her up,
wanting it to appear that she was trying to have you killed.
I need you to get me that message.
Bring it to me.
It's the least you could do for her.
Marshall.
Mr. Sloane.
Hey. Sorry. You know the classics.
Never go out of style.
A test tube was sent to forensics for analysis. Did you authorize that?
Yes.
Yes, I did. Uh...
Is that a problem, or...
There's no problem. Just a curiosity.
It's indicated that the blood sample was one of Dr. Vlachko's test subjects.
I thought we already analyzed those.
Am I missing something, Marshall?
Uh, you know what? I haven't been getting a lot of sleep lately.
Mitchell's got an ear infection,
and I just probably forgot to send it in. Sorry.
Sorry about that.
Did the results come back?
It's nothing we didn't already know.
The subject was suffering from a large-scale genetic mutation.
However, Marshall,
I want you to know there are protocols in this office.
I'm sure your failure to notify me of this submission
is also due to your lack of sleep, yes?
Yes. It probably was.
I'm very tired, and I'm not...
Why complicate our life?
We could get on and off without the transport even knowing they were hit.
That item we want is extremely delicate.
I mean, we can't risk the transfer in a moving vehicle.
I thought you said we were stealing an instruction manual.
We are. A very old one written by an inventor in the 15th century.
You breathe on it wrong, and it will crumble.
Seems like a lot of trouble for an old book.
It's valuable to my employer, so then it's valuable to us.
Okay, it's gonna be a two-car caravan.
The lead car's going to be the armored transport.
It'll be leaving the depot at midnight tonight
traveling along this route.
- We're hitting a CIA convoy?
- That's right.
So this is why you needed me.
From the moment you contacted me,
you knew you'd need that bypass, even if I had given you the coil --
We'd have never told you where your father is. That's right.
Guess that makes us bad people, huh?
Nothing's changed, though. You still want answers.
You son of a bitch.
You know, by the way, you should be thanking me.
- You should be grateful.
- Thanking you for what?
For tracking your father down.
Let me tell you something. That wasn't no small feat.
Your father's been hiding for the past --
You're asking me to betray my agency.
Well, I feel really bad about that.
You know what? I'll say an extra Hail Mary tonight before I go to bed.
If I do this, I can't go back.
That has a certain poetry to it, doesn't it?
Like father, like son.
Me?
I came this far,
I'd have crossed the finish line.
But like I said
I'm a bad guy.
Oh, guess what? Your dad is, too.
I mean, he's not being held prisoner.
And for 25 years, he allowed his wife and his kid to think that he's been dead?
That's a bad guy.
You think on that. I'll be inside.
I need to speak with you.
Of course. What is it?
I wanted to tell you before you were notified through official channels.
I've been visiting Katya Derevko.
Your aunt? And I assume it's not on official business.
No. It was personal.
I thought Katya might be able to fill in the blanks about my mother,
tell me who she was.
I see.
Well...
thank you for telling me.
Nadia?
What did she tell you?
Nothing I didn't already know.
That she was a criminal. A murderer.
Sweetheart, no one is a single thing.
Look, I understood Irina.
We were both cut from the same cloth.
Both committed to our work.
And I suppose because of that,
we both did some things that are unforgivable.
But, Nadia,
Irina is also capable of having a great capacity for love.
I saw the way she looked at Sydney.
The way she held that child in her arms.
And I am absolutely sure she felt the same way about you.
She searched for you, Nadia.
She may not be here to answer your questions,
but the one thing I know to be true --
your mother loved you.
I'd like to believe that.
Then do.
Have a wonderful day.
Hi, I'm here to pick up a repair.
Of course. You have the service ticket?
Nope, just the number. 112402.
Give me just a moment.
Quite lovely, isn't it?
Open it.
How much do I owe you?
Nothing. It's already been paid for.
- Have a lovely day.
- Thank you.
Hello?
Vaughn?
Vaughn, say something.
We're gonna do this my way.
You want to pull this off, I'm taking charge.
Sure thing.
That truck will be heavily guarded,
loaded with state-of-the-art surveillance.
I want RF jammers on every team member.
Now, an item this important, the CIA is gonna use their best agents.
Even the smallest mistake will compromise our mission.
We can use the cold laser to open the safe,
but without the proper code, the safe's backup system will engage.
Once we're inside, I'll bypass the safe's backup system
while Sabina sets up the cold laser.
We'll have no more than three minutes.
One last thing,
because there'll be no shooting on this job.
CIA protocol.
They will not fire unless fired upon first.
If anyone has a problem with anything I just said, speak up now.
- We understood?
- All right.
All right.
You have a minute?
Of course.
I wanted to apologize about going to Katya.
I should have told you.
You don't have to apologize.
When I found out Arvin Sloane was my father, I was horrified.
My entire life I wanted to meet my parents, and the truth was so...
ugly.
But he's changed. There's good in him.
I guess I was hoping the same thing was true for our mother.
- I'm sorry.
- Me too.
That's Eric. We're going out for lunch. You want to come?
No, thanks. I'm just gonna hang out here.
- Okay.
- Have fun.
Here we go.
We've secured the hole.
Copy, strike team. They're clueless. No idea you're hitching a ride.
110 seconds till x-fer.
Now we'll see how good you really are.
Oh, I'm good.
You got 95 seconds.
- How you doing?
- Ready.
Almost there.
All right, here we go.
Nice timing.
Strike team, report. What's going on?
- What the hell is going on?
- Package secured.
Strike team, get ready for impact.
Turn back.
Let's go.
Drop the weapons!
No!
I need suppressive fire! Now!
Come on! We can still get away!
Dixon, report. Do you copy?
Two hostages escaped into the tunnel!
Hostages in tunnel. Do you copy?
Got to hand it to you, man.
You a closer. Let's see 'em.
Where's the manuscript?
He's been dead all along, hasn't he?
What?
My father would never have done this.
Man, have you lost your mind?!
My father's dead, you son of a bitch, and you used that.
The truth! I want to hear you say it. He's been dead all along.
Man, you've seen the pictures!
Yeah, I've seen a lot of things.
All right, you want me to say it? Fine. He's been --
The truth! Tell me the truth!
Whoa! Okay. Okay.
He's dead, man. Okay? He's dead.
- What else?
- What?
The rest of it. How'd he die?
- Man, you know the rest!
- Say it!
Irina Derevko killed him.
The pictures, the witnesses, the journals -- everything was fake.
Everything.
Who else? Who set me up?
- Who do you work for?
- Please, you know --
Who do you work for?!
Tell me!
Sloane.
I work for Sloane.
You found the message.
Bank records.
Payments to the assassin who tried to kill me.
- The records exonerate Irina.
- Yes.
Sydney, whoever did this,
for your mother, my sister, we have to make it right.
We have --
You already know who it was.
My mother traced the bank payments to their source.
She discovered who it was.
In that case --
Oh, if I would have gotten the message in time.
She would still be alive.
Who is it?
Before I tell you, you must promise me
Nadia can never know.
You're probably gonna want to kill me when I tell you this, but
I ran some tests.
What kind of tests?
You may be very sick, Mr. Bristow.
Now, you'll need additional bloodwork to be sure --
I thought I made myself clear, Marshall.
This is not something I care to discuss.
I understand. Just hear me out. You have a mutation.
Marshall, I've heard enough.
Damn it, you may not care what happens to you,
but what happens to you affects other people.
Sydney, for example. Have you thought about that?
You need to see a doctor now.
Is everything all right here?
We were just finishing up.
Yeah. Just finishing up.
Jack...
is there something we need to discuss?
Hi.
He's dead, Syd -- my father.
He's been dead all along.
I think.
You know, I've --
I've lived with his death for so long,
I would have done anything just to see him again.
But then I realized that
my father, he would have never left my mom and me,
not for anything.
The man I knew could have never walked away from the people he loved.
How did you know?
'Cause I couldn't either.
It was Sloane.
I should have seen it all along.
I swear to god, Syd, I am gonna kill that son of a bitch.
Come inside.
There's something I have to tell you.
Jack.
I just spoke with Sydney. Vaughn's returned.
Where was he?
I'll be debriefing him tomorrow. He retrieved the coil.
It's on its way to the DSR facility for analysis.
Good.
One more thing.
Dixon ran into some interference abroad.
He's okay. He had his vest on.
But you were right to be concerned.
What about the DSR transport?
The artifact has been secured.
Okay.
Unless there's something else, I'm headed out.
No. Have a good evening, Jack.
You, too.
Mr. Sloane?
I'm sorry to report, Mr. Sloane, we didn't recover the manuscript.
And Roberts hasn't reported in.
I see.
Nothing changes.
Everything proceeds as planned.
Transcript: RaceMan - Synchro: Travis
www.forom.com