Santa...
Gave me the wrong doll.
And i was so mad, i sort of
made all the christmas lights
On our entire block go out.
That's when my parents
first caught on that i was...
Different.
- Jessy?
- What?
That was not me.
You know, i don't know
why i came back here.
So miss goldilocks could put a
bull's-Eye on my freakish head?
Putting out cryptic ads
in alternative papers
And gathering us all
in one spot...  genius.
Look, you made the choice to
come here on your own, mary,
And i'm guessing it was for a reason.
Look, i'm not saying i couldn't
use a few friendly faces
When i'm lighting up the town...
... literally.
But people don't want us to exist,
And turning us into poster
kids isn't gonna change that.
I think this group is the best
thing that's ever happened to me.
That's because you don't know
any better, pocket protector.
Just wait till they spark up
their torches and come after us.
At least if we're not alone,
we're not such easy targets.
Okay, everyone who came here
tonight took a really big step,
And that is the first step
towards changing the way people
Look at your special gifts.
Thank you for coming.
And if you forgot to
sign in when you got here,
Can you please do so before you leave?
- And i'll see you next week.
- Great meeting.
Thanks a lot, chloe.
Great.
Smallville 806
Synchro : flolo
For seriessub.Com
You know, when i suggested we
have "dinner and a movie" night,
I didn't exactly think a $3.99
special number 2 combo with cheese
And a droning police blotter
was what i would have in mind.
Not to mention the communication
skills of a paperweight.
I'm sorry?
Look who decided to
join the conversation.
Well... it all happened so
fast, it was like a blur.
You know what...
I have paperwork to do, and
you have the world to save,
So... why don't we just call it a night?
We'll do this again, all right? Soon.
Right.
As soon as all the criminals are behind
bars and there are no more accidents.
Good night.
Try not to stay up all night.
Silent alarm triggered at
the jewelry store on main.
Robbery in progress.
Squads 17 and 33, please respond.
There isn't any more.
Please don't hurt me.
We have an alley disturbance
off gregory behind the arcade.
Help!
- What else you got?
- That's all my money!
I swear! Please!
I think he's lying.
All cars to the ace of
clubs, 12th and maryland.
Screams heard. No accounts from inside.
I repeat, all cars to 12th and maryland.
Davis?
Davis, you probably shouldn't sit up.
What happened?
I was hoping you could tell me.
There's no sign of a bomb or
any other kind of explosion.
- Did something attack these people?
- I don't know.
I was walking with take out.
You don't remember coming
in here? The screams?
No.
Must have gotten a concussion.
Yeah.
Yeah, i probably took
a pretty good blow.
But i'm fine now.
You're not fine.
You're covered in blood.
You're obviously injured. You
need to go to the hospital.
- Let them take care of you.
- I can take care of myself.
It looks like we were both too late.
Detective john jones.
Metropolis homicide?
I figured it was the best way for
me to help people without my powers.
I haven't forgot about them. We're
gonna find a way to get them back.
I found a place for myself here.
How'd you make detective so quickly?
We all have our sources.
Mine happen to be far-Reaching.
And now that you're
working in metropolis
And using your contacts at the
daily planet to help more people,
I wanted to be close
by in case you need me.
What i needed was to get here sooner.
I should have been able
to save all these people.
According to the mysterious calls
we got at the station tonight,
I'm guessing you saved your share.
You can't save everyone, clark.
The moment i believe that
is when i stop trying.
What have you heard about
what happened here tonight?
Well, people are pointing
fingers at everything
From a crazed lunatic
to a gang of murderers.
With lightning speed.
By the time i arrived here,
Whoever or whatever attacked
these people was gone.
Then you don't have any leads, either.
Not yet.
Looks like you picked up the
latest pastime around here.
Oh, i'm just trying to
corroborate my new theory...
Metropolis' very own mystery hero.
See, i've puzzled together
a couple of reports
Of a sneaky good samaritan popping up
over the city the past couple weeks.
Is that right?
Sounds like an urban myth.
Well, the truth has
got to start somewhere.
If your citizen "x" does exist, he
sure didn't come through tonight.
Well, i wouldn't give him too many
demerits on his hero badge, clark.
You can't get this city's savior title
By letting innocent
people die on your shift.
You stealing evidence from
crime scenes much lately?
No. I'm gonna return it.
But it may have recorded what
happened inside the club tonight.
Well, let's take a look.
Thanks.
Happy birthday.
Whoever did this is beyond steroids.
Hey. You missed sodas and
cookies, but maybe next week,
You can lead the session
with a rousing kent tale.
Thanks, chloe.
Sitting around with a bunch of strangers
Singing "kumbaya" isn't
my idea of self-Help.
What's with the 'tude?
There was a brutal attack
at ace of clubs tonight.
It was...
Special.
So, naturally, that means
it must be someone from here.
The metropolis police don't exactly
keep a list of all the crypto-Perps.
- Chloe, i need your help.
- Doing what?
Randomly pointing fingers?
Chloe, you've run the stats before.
Chances are they're not all innocent.
I can't believe that you, of all people,
Would throw someone in a lineup
just because they're different.
I let whoever did this
slip through my fingers.
I was right there. If this person
attacks again, it'll be on my hands.
Clark, i've learned to navigate
your field of guilty land mines
Better than anyone,
but these kids trust me.
I don't know what you expect me to say.
Can you tell me where
i can find davis bloome?
Uh, yeah. That's him right there.
- Davis?
- Thanks.
Yeah. That's me. What can i do for you?
- Jimmy olsen.
- As in chloe's jimmy?
She's mentioned you a few times.
I hope you don't mind me
surprising you like this.
No. It's no problem.
Uh, is this about chloe?
Yeah, i've just been
going through her pda,
Checking up on who she's
been hanging out with.
No, no, no. I'm just...
I'm just kidding. I'm not some psycho.
Yeah, you never can tell these days.
So...
So, i'm just trying to get a
scoop on this club massacre.
We've heard all sorts of stories
about this killer... the best
That he's a monster with bony eyelids.
Yeah, i gave my statement to the police.
I don't know anything.
You know how to drive, don't you?
Look, i just want to ride along. I
figure ambulances are first on the scene.
Maybe we'll beat
everyone to the next one.
Trust me...  you do not want
to ride shotgun on my watch.
You don't want to be
the first guy there.
It's not something that you
want to see, given the choice.
Come on. I mean, can't
you do a favor for a bro?
Okay.
Then... how about for chloe?
Meet me downstairs at 8:00.
Thank you.
- They all have meteor powers.
- Where'd you get this list?
I memorized it off chloe's desk.
I didn't realize that photographic
memory was among your abilities.
It's more like speed-Reading,
but let's not split hairs.
She couldn't just give you a copy?
Chloe and i don't exactly
see eye to eye on this one.
Well, what about your mouthy cohort?
She hasn't poked her nose
into this one, either.
She's on assignment, which is code
for "monster-Truck rally in lubbock."
And i assume your emerald
ally and his superfriends
Are still on hiatus, which leaves you.
Solo. I get it. Is there
a point to all this?
Obsession.
When someone's life is on the
line with every decision you make,
It's hard for anything
else to seem important.
- It's because nothing else is.
- Careful, clark.
Even when you save someone,
there are consequences.
You know, i thought you'd be happy.
I'm finally embracing my destiny...
out there making a difference.
Except for last night,
when i dropped the ball.
We need to find out if anyone on that list
was responsible for the attack at the bar.
It wasn't just one incident.
There have been at least five other
similar murders in the last few months.
Yeah, i know. I read up on it.
All the victims died the
same way... internal bleeding.
All their bones were crushed.
And the killer gets
away without a trace.
I'll look into these.
But i was working on another angle.
One paramedic has been
the first to arrive
On several of the crime scenes.
The driver's name is davis bloome.
Chance meeting in a moldy
basement over a corpse.
Will the romance never end?
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see the coroner's
latest report on the victim.
She was a new member of my isis group.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I mean, she was afraid of
being targeted, and now...
It wasn't your fault.
She was there because of me.
And to top it all off, there
are a few trigger-Happy people
Who are convinced that one of
my kids is behind all of this.
And you? Checking for strep throat?
Look, you don't have to worry, chloe.
I don't think that one
of your clients did this.
I'd like to think so, too.
But i still need to find a suspect.
Davis? What is it?
I'm afraid that i might be the killer.
Davis, i know that you are not
responsible for these killings, okay?
I know you. You save people every day.
What could make you think that
you were a brutal serial killer?
Look, chloe, i've run the
self-Denial mantra for weeks,
But how do you explain the blackouts?
How do you explain that
i was covered in blood?!
None of it was mine.
I want to believe that you're
right more than anyone, but...
Then it's just a matter
of finding the real killer.
You really don't believe
that it could be me, do you?
No.
Even though we just met?
You're really... leaping
out on a limb for me.
Well, if what they say is
true and fools do rush in,
Then i have definitely earned the
mantle of "village idiot" on this one.
And then you just toss it all aside
With a healthy dose
of self-Deprecation.
Please don't make me a saint.
What?
Luck isn't part of my
daily routine, chloe.
I just... i feel like...
I feel like you were sent to me.
You are not a serial killer.
Look, davis, when did those
blackouts start happening?
For as long as i can remember.
When i was a kid,
I would go a couple
months without a blackout,
But they're just...
they're getting so frequent.
Is that why you bounced from
foster home to foster home?
I've always felt like...
Kind of like there was
this darkness inside me...
Just fighting to get out.
So you closed yourself off to everyone.
After all these years
of keeping this secret,
Why are you telling me?
I think you know.
I've...  i've never met anyone like you.
Chloe, but what if i'm right? What
if you're looking at a murderer?
Davis, there are lots of people
who could have done these killings.
And we're gonna find who did.
I walked right by here last night.
It could have been any of us.
You think somebody's hunting us down?
Well, it wouldn't be the first time.
But so far, mary's been the
only victim that's been a...
... club member.
And after last night, we're all
at the top of their suspect list.
Look, i don't know
what flag you're waving,
But making them out to be all bad
Is no better than what
people have done to you.
You don't know what it's like.
People don't look at you the same
once you tell them you're a freak.
Some of them do.
And turning against each other
is not gonna stop all this.
Look, i came here tonight because
i want to help catch mary's killer.
I thought that maybe some of
you may have seen something
Or you maybe might have known why
someone would have wanted to attack mary.
Because you think it's one of us.
- No. It's just that...
- Come on, chloe!
Some cop's been showing up at our homes
Asking each of us if we know anything.
It's kind of a coincidence.
Unless you gave him our names.
No.
I would never betray you guys like that.
Well, somebody did.
Clark.
Chloe told me about the girl in
her group. It's a messed-Up world.
You know, davis, it took a lot to go
into that roomful of screaming people.
Who knows what you could
have been running into.
Yeah, well...
I suppose it should
be somewhat comforting
To know that good gossip
spreads just as fast as bad.
- So you didn't save those people.
- Haven't we been over this?
I'm not some larger-Than-Life hero. The
truth is, i don't know what happened.
But you do know more than
what you've told me, don't you?
I don't fish much, clark,
So why don't you just tell
me what the hell you're after?
What are you doing with a file stuffed
full of morbid pictures of murder victims?
You broke into my locker?
Collecting pictures of all the murder
victims is a pretty strange habit, isn't it?
Do you know how many murders in
this city go unsolved every year?
I show up, i take away the bodies,
case closed. Maybe i want to do
More than just clean up the
mess after it's too late.
Now the whole city refers
to you as a hero, huh?
Maybe i'd have an easier
time believing all this
If there was proof that
that's actually what happened.
Okay, you know what... i understand
If you don't want to join the
knee-Jerk ticker-Tape parade,
But let me ask you a question.
Are you really up in my face
Because you're trying to catch a killer,
Or is it because you're trying
to hide something yourself?
Don't try to turn this around on me.
Then why don't you take a
second look at those photos?
I'm not the only one that's
hanging out at these crime scenes.
There's another figure
in the background.
You seem to be the
city's own peeping tom.
I'm a reporter. It's my job!
These photos were taken
Before any press could
have made it to the scene.
So, uh, next time you feel anxious
To shine a light on things
that don't make sense...
You might want to stay closer to home.
Sharpening your pitchfork?
If you're gonna lead a marauding
posse, you better come prepared.
Clark, you gave the police
the names of my isis group?
How could you use your
powers to betray me like that?
I didn't mean to go around you,
chloe, but you were so defensive...
Like i've been defensive of you?
Clark, you don't get how much of my
life i spend protecting your secret.
And if you ever had
enough courage to actually
Step forward, like the
rest of these kids did,
You would be the first one on that pyre.
How could you, of all people, be
the ringleader for this witch hunt?
Chloe, you're taking the side
of people that you hardly know.
I would think after
eight years of friendship,
You might be able to give
me the benefit of the doubt.
That works both ways.
And your bonus features
Don't give you the right to
trump anyone else's judgment.
Fine. We'll let the facts
speak for themselves.
These are test results that
davis was trying to hide from me.
Davis?
I was thinking, with
your brainiac ability,
You might be able to
make sense of the results.
Oh, my god.
The skin under the
victim's nails is davis'.
Davis?
Ready to catch a killer?
Yeah.
So, how often do you get a dispatch?
Depends on the night.
Some nights are busier than others.
Well, i bet you see a lot
of horrible things, huh?
All units in the area, we have a 4-11
in progress. Corner of liberty and 8th.
Uh, what's a 4-11?
It's the reason you came along tonight.
Stay here.
Davis?!
His ambulance number is 17.
I'm surprised you haven't
enrolled the services
Of our friendly martian on the force.
Jones can't help us unless
we have some hard proof.
We need more than a few pieces
of evidence to arrest someone.
Yeah, and the evidence you
have isn't exactly conclusive.
I mean, the victim could
have easily just reached up
And grabbed davis when he
was trying to help them.
But i have to admit, davis
would have the perfect setup.
I mean, he attacks the people
And then pretends to arrive
at the scene to save them?
I know it isn't easy.
What? My perpetual knack for
getting into lose-Lose situations?
Got it.
Davis' ambulance just stopped.
He answered a call a few minutes ago.
Help! I'm at liberty and 8th!
Can anybody hear me?
It's some kind of monster!
Clark, that's jimmy.
Clark!
What did you do with jimmy?!
Davis?
Jimmy?
Davis.
Davis, you all right?
C.K.!
Jimmy, what's going on?
It could be anywhere. It's
some sort of shadow creature.
What?
Jimmy.
Jimmy?
Jimmy?!
You okay?
Yeah. I'm good.
I lost perspective.
I can be a little stubborn.
And i... hate to admit it,
But there was a part of me
that was really frustrated
That you trusted someone
else instead of me.
It's funny how that happens when
you go behind someone's back.
My obsession...
Pushed me past the line with you, chloe.
I'm really sorry.
But you were protecting a killer.
Yeah, well, then there's that.
I guess i just didn't understand
How you could hand over your trust
so easily to people you didn't know.
327.
That's how many of the meteor-Infected
i've profiled since ninth grade.
And you know how many
i've actually saved?
None.
I guess i've been so busy
rescuing people from them,
I never looked at it from that angle.
It's not just the damsels in
distress that need saving, clark.
You know, when i first thought that
you were one of the meteor-Infected,
I would have done
anything to protect you.
But i guess that's what scares me.
I'm afraid that someday you're gonna
put your trust in the wrong person.
Hey.
Been waiting long?
I don't know how to thank you
For believing in me when
i was up against the ropes.
We all need someone to
pitch a seat in our corner.
Yeah, i guess, but most of the time,
It's not a possible murder
suspect standing there.
Davis, you were scared
and paranoid. That's all.
Seriously, backing someone who's actually
innocent isn't much of a sacrifice.
Besides, everything with you is so...
So easy.
Yeah.
Easy.
Have you ever felt that
way with anyone before?
Once.
With jimmy.
No.
Look, chloe, i'm not
trying to get between you
And the rest of your life, but, uh...
Davis, i help people. That's what i do.
You know, this doesn't have
to mean any more than that.
Yeah, but it does.
Did you help me because of
some personal code of ethics,
Or was there more to it than that?
I shouldn't be here right now.
Why? Because you feel
guilty about something?
No. And i'd like it to stay that way.
I think it's best if i
don't see you for a while.
Sorry.
How could i have been
so wrong about davis?
This shadow guy confessed to every
killing in the last few weeks.
Sometimes what we
think is a good instinct
Is just our mind trying to convince
ourself of what we want to believe.
Well, he may be in
custody, but that just means
There's another psycho out
there right around the corner.
I've been here working every
night, and i still have to do more.
You can't allow yourself to get caught.
Combing through police blotters
at your desk every night,
Peeling back the sides of
a bus in broad daylight,
Speeding into a crowded bar.
You're so fixated on being a hero,
You're not paying attention
to who might be watching.
Is this your idea of a pep talk?
It's not my identity that's at risk.
Every day, i have to run
faster and faster interference
On these mysterious
good-Samaritan reports.
Well, that just means i'm doing my job.
Just have to make sure
no one sees my face.
Well, you can't be sure of that.
Unless you plan to put on a mask.
You're joking, right?
You are not in
smallville anymore, clark.
Metropolis has millions of
people walking the streets,
Every one of them watching for a miracle
To change their lives,
to give them hope.
You are that miracle.
And it's just a matter of time
before someone discovers that.
I'll be more careful.
Hey, clark.
Perfect. Officer, listen.
None for your fellow comrades... they
don't want to give me the time of day.
But you look like you're a
thinking-Outside- The-Box kind of guy.
There's a... there's a mystery hero
Roaming the streetsof metropolis
Look, scout's honor... out of nowhere,
These tires, they come
floating through the air.
And this mr. Shadow guy... he gets
knocked around like a ping-Pong ball.
Slow down.
Oh. Olsen, james olsen.
Photographer, daily planet.
Well, james, adrenaline can
play strange games with a person.
No, no. He's...  he's real.
I know it.
I hope you're right.
We could use the help.
And when you get some hard evidence,
I'll be more than glad to
continue this conversation.
Evening, mr. Olsen.
Mr. Kent.
I'm gonna prove that
this guy exists, c.K.
He's out there.
You look a little uncomfortable.
You're not a lawyer.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Congratulations on your page 1.
It's nice to have your work recognized
After so many years being the
good little boy in the shadows.
You have more admirers than you think.
My boss, miss mercer,
Has been gathering a small
group of talent, if you're game.
You've read my list of accomplishments.
I'm not really interesting
in sharing top billing.
Cut the bravado. You didn't
commit all those murders.
You're just a copycat
looking for attention.
Cops haven't found this yet,
But we have security footage of you
at an arcade during one of the crimes.
It's a crime i'm sure you've studied
If you were looking to
mimic the real killer.
You remember the nun at st.
Vincent's... crushed to death.
That surveillance timecode must
have been wrong, because that was me.
Really?
Then i suppose you can tell me
where her missing onyx crucifix is...
The one on the rosary.
You didn't kill her.
For seriessub.Com