Sorry about he heels.
I need the inches.
- I'm not sure this is such a good idea.
- Either R.A.O. Incorporated
is throwing a Valentine's Day party
for their workers behind this wall
or they are running double shifts on a
Saturday night a total union violation.
Lois, I'm sure someone is keeping an eye
on this situation.
Bingo.
They are moving more tech equipment
into that building than NASA.
And if they're skulking around
in the middle of the night,
they are definitely
hiding something.
Nice teddy. Next time, buy her
a silk one. She's not 6 years old.
I think we should drop this story.
You sound like you want it all
to yourself. Is there something
about that tower that you're not
telling me?
No. It's Valentine's day.
We should be out having dinner
together, by candlelight.
Valentine's day is just
a smarmy Hallmark holiday
engineered by corporate executives
to convince people
to spend hard-earned money
on dead flowers
and overpriced meals...
but not you two.
You're kind
of overreacting, even for you.
History has proven
that if I embrace V-day
in any romantic way at all,
it always ends in disaster.
Valentine for the lady?
- No, thank you. She doesn't really...
- Actually.
What?
I didn't have any dinner.
Happy Valentine's day.
Easy with the pixie dust there,
Tinker Bell.
Looks like it's too late
to follow that story anyway.
It's never too early for nachos and
too late for hard-hitting journalism.
Maybe we should put our relationship
before our work, just for tonight and...
Hold hands? You could come a-courtin'
on your horse and buggy.
All we need is a chaperone.
Sounds mighty traditional.
And what's wrong with that?
With all of our crossed text messages
lately, I thought maybe sometimes...
I want...
us to have a more
traditional relationship.
The R.A.O. has scheduled
a ribbon-cutting
at the solar tower in two days.
I'm gonna need the exposé now.
Two days.
Maybe I should check on those building
permits that you were talking about.
You wanted to avoid the whole
Valentine's-day-thing thing, right?
Anything for your career, sweetie.
Here's the scoop, buddy.
A traditional woman does not
spend her time in the office
when she can be at home
taking care of her man.
I quit.
Smallville 9x13 Persuasion
Synchro: Flolo
For Seriesssub.com
I was gonna ask you for the lowdown
on your v-day with Lois
but something about you being here with
me tells me it didn't go over so well.
Do you have the passports
and I.D. cards ready?
Or we could get right down
to business.
All the materials
you would ever need to escape
- your life and start a new one.
- Thanks, Chloe. You're a life-saver.
If by that you mean sweet on the outside
and empty in the middle,
that's pretty much exactly
how I feel right now.
I realize you're not on board
with me helping the Kandorians.
Yeah, you know how it is.
You find out that one of them
skewers you to death
in the post-apocalyptic future,
you kind of lose interest.
I know it seems like I may have
overlooked some of their mistakes.
By "mistakes" do you mean them building
a tower so they can give themselves
- powers to take over the world?
- I want to lead them to a better place.
The tower will be
completed in two days.
Granted, they haven't got
the satellites up and running
to change the atmosphere,
but come on.
We both know
one of them killed your father.
Maybe it would just be safer if we sent
the Kandorians to the Phantom Zone.
I know that you're saying
that because you want to protect people
but right now, I want you
to focus on watching my back.
Leave the rest of The Planet to me.
I will protect you...
no matter what it takes.
Faora. Alia.
I have the papers.
It's your new life. You'll have
your own identities.
I misjudged you, Kal-El.
I was born into the military.
I never had a choice
to live as a civilian.
We can't repay you.
Tell me who killed my father.
I know that Zod took him from Tess.
And was he the last one
to see Jor-El alive?
I know you want justice,
but be careful.
Zod has a lot of loyal followers
and if you go after him,
there will be war.
Hey, sweetie pie! Welcome home.
Lois, what's going on?
I moved in.
But don't worry, I'm camped out
into the guest room until
we get engaged.
Engaged?
Move over, Betty Crocker. I have got
this cooking thing down.
How's your pot roast?
Oh, it's delicious.
Wonderful.
It was really sweet of you
to do all of this.
I am just so proud of you
for bringing home
the bacon. The least I can do
is cook it up in a pan.
And, well...
never let you forget
that you're the man.
Lois, did something happen?
You just seem so cheerful.
You said you wanted
a more traditional relationship,
And you were very persuasive.
What if I miss the old Lois?
Too late.
I quit my job at The Planet.
- You did what?
- Yeah.
Now, instead of being chained
to a desk all day,
I get to be your ball and chain.
You can't quit reporting.
That job is your life.
And now my life is with you,
for better or for worse,
for richer or for poorer.
Lois, what are you talking about?
You're absolutely right.
What kind of adjective is "poorer"?
Somebody is gonna need an editor...
for their vows.
Right. There's something at the
office that I need to...
investigate.
All right, Mr. Cold Feet.
I'll keep the home fires burning.
Rain check on talking
about the big event for now.
You better make an honest woman
out of me, Clark Kent.
Security!
I'm afraid
they're otherwise engaged.
Ah... no.
I like you just where you are.
Then maybe you'd like to join me.
You're already in bed
with someone else.
Wrong choice of bedfellows.
I'm moments away
from completing my tower.
I thought you needed
the Book of RAU to finish it.
We found another way. And it seems
your satellite systems
are lagging behind schedule.
We're onlining the safety tests now.
- I'll handle that, thank you.
- Only I can run them.
Now that I've got your fingerprints,
I can access all of
the networking data without you.
Cheers.
You're digging your own grave.
Then, you better make sure there's
room in there for both of us.
You neglected to tell me
that Kal-El was supplying
new identities to my people.
They're no more your people
than they are his.
And eventually,
he will be their leader.
Now, don't underestimate
their loyalty to me.
But they don't see you
as the savior that he is.
There's blood on your hands. You're
tainted, a reminder of their past.
He's the promise for their future.
It's what you've always wanted,
isn't it...
Help give my people their powers
so they can save your doomed planet?
Hand over the reins
to Kal-El and then what?
Get rid of me?
If necessary.
We need the knowledge of your people
to help us reverse the damage
we've done here,
to show mercy to this planet.
When I take over
those satellites tomorrow,
and when I gain my own powers...
you will be the one who needs mercy.
It is amazing what four hours
of scrubbing a kitchen can do.
- It simply sparkles.
- Okay. Let's open a window.
I think you may have gotten a contact
high with that lemony-fresh scent.
And why is
your vinyl collection here?
Drum roll, please.
Chez Kent has a new resident.
I moved in!
Great. We can have you move back
to the Talon
and all packed up
before the sun's up.
I'm sorry that you're
having a hard time with this
but this love train
has left the station.
No, the love train
has jumped the tracks.
I've seen Clark in love before,
and it always holds him back.
You know what?
It's a little sad that the only
way that you can get close to Clark
- right now is to play mother hen.
- Clark is a very private person,
when the chips are down,
everyone can see your cards.
Clark knows that he can trust me.
Just like The Blur?
When you were secretly talking to him
and you announced it to everyone
on national television?
I never planned for it
to happen that way.
You know what?
As long as I've known you
you have always had to have the scoop
but when it comes to understanding
the real Clark, you are always gonna be
a second-stringer.
This whole Martha Stewart-makeover
thing isn't fooling anyone.
Once Clark knows you, the real you
underneath all of this Lois armor,
he's gonna see that
you're just a scared little kid
who runs away
the second anything goes wrong.
If you really love him,
the best thing you can do
for Clark is leave him.
Excuse me.
You sold my friend and I some
candies the other night.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
You were with the bitter chick.
Right. The bitter chick isn't feeling
so good. She kind of got sick.
I'm retracing her steps.
Was there anything
in that chocolate you sold her?
Yeah. Fat.
I ate two boxes
and gained three pounds.
Thanks.
Fairy dust.
That was cute. Where'd you get it?
Yeah, i don't know what it is,
but it comes from some quarry
in Smallville.
Meteor rock.
Is that your girlfriend?
No, she's not my...
we don't use that word.
Are you all right?
What's the emergency?
False alarm.
Are you sure?
'cause you seem kind of...
kind of pathetic. Right?
Why even bother going
through the motions?
This whole moving-in thing
together was a joke.
- You're not yourself right now.
- Come on! I'm not stupid.
I could tell that you just hated
that burned brick of meat!
Let's get you some water.
Stop trying to sugarcoat it.
I am not good for you.
Chloe was right
to protect you from me.
Chloe can be
overprotective sometimes.
No.
She hit the target head-on.
She said that it was gonna
wreck us, and she's right.
Clark, I don't...
I don't know the first thing about
family time
or dinners at home. I don't.
Lois, I'm glad
that you're opening up to me,
but there's something else
going on here.
You're right.
Something is going on.
I've made a fool of myself
long enough.
It hurts me to be around you.
I have to leave you, Clark.
Leave Smallville.
Lois, you need to sleep on this.
I promise things
will look better in the morning.
No, they won't. I'm a big girl.
I can pull myself up by my own
bootstraps, thank you very much.
I had hoped that somehow I'd be able
to pull it off,
The whole making-a-home thing.
Stop.
You are home.
No.
A home is for real.
For always and forever.
Not this.
Goodbye, Smallville.
Lois, you can't leave.
Not yet.
I promise we'll be together,
- always and...
- forever?
Do you mean it?
I do.
Guess we can move my stuff
out of the guest room now.
It's good you're here. For some reason,
Chloe has shut me out
of all of Watchtower's systems.
Everything's encrypted.
I'm sorry to hear that,
Emil But I have my own fires to put out.
- Do you know where Chloe is?
- She's gone.
She's activated laser trip wires
around the system core.
There's firewalls around
firewalls around firewalls.
I can't get into it.
I've tried every iteration.
Emil, look, I want you to calm down.
Just try to relax for once.
Whatevs.
This place goes nuclear,
it is not my problem.
I want you to go back
to the way you were.
There are no backsies
in this lifetime.
Where are you going?
I need a brew.
This job's way too stressful.
I need to figure out a way to reverse this.
I breathed in some sort of new meteor rock.
Dude, hasn't anyone
ever told you not to inhale?
This is serious.
It's like you and Lois
are doing whatever I say but then
I can't un-do it. Normally Kryptonite
only affects me, not other people.
Sounds kind of like hypnosis
to me. People are pathetic.
They're open to suggestion.
I bet it's great with the ladies.
How do I stop putting people
into hypnotic trances?
Well, maybe...
you don't need to stop.
Maybe you just need to chill.
Use it or lose it, Kent. Come on!
There's got to be something
out there that you're after.
There is no luck.
Oh, Mrs. K., can I really?
Thanks so much!
But actually,
I'm wearing it right now!
I found it
in the back of your closet.
I know. Clark will just love it.
Thanks...
Mom.
Okay, I have breaking news.
Brace yourself.
I am getting married!
Come on, dad. Can't we just
hitch a carrier to Greece?
I'm only getting married once.
We need to talk.
Why would I make time for you?
You're trying to isolate me
from my people.
You lost your right to lead
when you killed my father.
He was a brother to me.
We had our differences,
but I could never take his life.
I want you to tell me the truth.
Did you kill Jor-El?
I didn't kill him.
But I know who did.
Tess Mercer.
How is that possible?
She obviously had her own agenda and
was the only one who knew where he was.
She was the only one
who could finish the job.
You are his firstborn.
Only you can seek retribution.
- I'm not gonna kill Tess.
- It's the Kryptonian way.
You cannot let this injustice stand.
Kal-El.
You knew when you started on this path
that you had to get your hands dirty.
You must avenge him.
I can't.
I tortured him.
I beat him black and blue.
I threatened him, and he still
wouldn't give you up.
You were the son he never met,
he was still willing
to sacrifice his life for yours.
He died protecting you,
you won't even defend his honor.
You don't think I want justice?
You don't think I want revenge?
You don't think sometimes
I want to be a killer like you?
I can't believe
he piggybacks my cameras.
And I can't believe
you actually managed to be of some use.
Go ahead.
Hack yourself silly. You'll never crack
my system.
This isn't so much cracking
as it is bleeding out.
This is the digital equivalent
to the ebola virus.
You take down my firewalls,
and you'll be exposing Clark
to much greater dangers
than you can even imagine.
I've done everything in my power
to postpone this,
but the day has finally come.
The tower is ready. It's linked up
to the satellites.
The countdown has started,
and in t-minus 18 hours,
the atmosphere will turn red
and the Kandorians
will have their powers.
But I have lost my faith in Zod.
If Clark joins them,
he can rule over all the Kandorians,
even Zod.
But you and I have to work together.
It's quite the offer.
Let me think about it.
I'm sorry,
but embracing the red skies
definitely violates
my no-conspiring-with-baddies
policy.
Should have aimed a little higher.
My father was murdered,
and I'm here to collect.
Collect on what?
Justice, vengeance.
It just depends
whose side you're on.
You confided in me, Clark.
You revealed your powers.
You know I haven't
told anyone your secret.
Only to sell me out to Zod
and the others.
No.
So that you could lead them.
You've seen the future, Tess.
You know what happens.
Which is why you have to join
the Kandorians
and defeat Zod so he doesn't
take your powers away.
He doesn't take them, Tess.
Your tower does when it goes online.
No, the satellites just create
a shield that filters the radiation.
And block the source
of my power, giving them theirs.
You have to believe me.
I had no idea
that your powers disappeared.
Don't worry, Tess.
I'll save your world.
Just not with you in it.
Alia?
Why did you call me here?
I'm sorry.
I did it in the name of RAU.
Jor-El...
he thought we were abominations.
He would have destroyed us.
You killed him?
Justice must be served.
Yeah, mom, about the engagement...
there was a miscommunication.
They're gonna print a retraction.
Sure, I'll tell her.
Okay, I love you, too, mom.
My mom says, "when you're ready,
you can borrow it."
Do you have any idea
what she's talking about?
Nope.
It's greek to me.
Speaking of Greece,
your dad left a message.
You know what?
I just need to make
a few phone calls here.
Donna Reed on crack.
I just... I'm never gonna buy
chocolate from another fairy.
I promise you.
I wasn't myself.
I don't know
what she put in that stuff.
It's too bad.
I kind of liked your outfit.
You really are an old-fashioned
romantic, aren't you?
I guess it's easier to complain
about Valentine's day than it is
to give it a shot.
So, in the face of the candy-coated,
emotional manipulation of V-day,
Maybe I just need to trust that
what we have is something more.
It's Chloe.
She's been really sweet. She left 12
messages apologizing for what she said
after she found out that I moved
in together... with you, here.
Yeah, we should talk.
Right. When you asked me
to move in with you here,
I know it seemed like
a good idea at the time.
- Yeah, but it wasn't...
- and about the whole proposal.
It was a dream-come-true
level of "wow,"
but, things are moving
a little too fast for me.
Right.
I don't know what I was thinking.
We should just stick to our plan
and take things slow.
I am so relieved
to hear you say that.
We just have to continue
being honest with each other.
Yeah.
About everything, right?
God knows I spilled my guts.
Clark, if you had
a really big secret...
would you trust me with it?
You're the most
trustworthy person I know.
But I confessed to the whole world
that I was talking to The Blur
on national television
And I really meant
to keep that secret.
I don't think The Blur minds, Lois.
You were doing the right thing.
- You were protecting him.
- But that's not the point.
I know it sounds crazy,
But I'm just afraid that my big mouth
is gonna wreck our relationship one day.
Don't worry, Lois.
It's not gonna be that easy
to get rid of me.
How'd she die?
By my hand.
You killed her?
She confessed
she murdered your father.
She was one of the zealots who thought
he would find a way to destroy us.
She didn't deserve to die.
You've gone too far, Just like when
you did when you sent me to see Tess!
You want to become one of us.
You want to live by our ways,
and yet, you reject them.
Kal-El, when you came to us
with your powers, I thought...
I thought it represented hope
for all of us,
but because you were too weak
to do it,
I had to kill
one of my own soldiers...
... to get justice for you.
This isn't my kind of justice.
In the coming days, you will see
there is only one kind of justice.
And then you will have to decide
if you really are one of us.
If you were really
under a command to protect me,
why didn't you let me kill her?
Because sometimes protecting you
means protecting you from yourself.
You're someone
we all have to believe in.
Nothing can compromise that.
Zod took matters into his own hands.
He killed Jor-El's murderer.
It was Alia.
So, now Alia can't slay me in
the future like she's supposed to.
This means the future
that we saw is changing.
But there's only one way to be sure.
When the first rays of the sun
fall upon the solar towers
tomorrow morning,
it will herald the dawn
of a new age of infinite power.
For Seriessub.com