Previously on Smallville:
Say that Clark Kent,
the unassuming journalist--
Steps out of the shadow
into his red and blue,
creating two completely
separate identities?
No more than three tablets
a day.
They can be
highly addictive.
And you're sure
this is it.
This is where I belong.
Watchtower
is officially online.
There is something
about being around you
that seems to calm
the murderer inside me.
I want you
to stay with me.
Without a doubt,
I'm officially a true believer
in this red-and-blue
superdude.
I won't stop until I land
the first worldwide
interview.
Good luck with that.
If you're not a member
of the press society,
you won't be on my list.
Check again.
"Lois Lane."
I've written a hundred stories
for The Daily Planet.
I'm sure
you've heard of it.
It I've heard of.
You -- not so much.
Again, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Okay, obviously there's been
some sort of mistake.
It's not like I squeezed
into five-inch booted heels
for my health.
Miss Lane,
there's simply nothing I can do.
Actually, there is.
You can tell
Edward R. Murrow
that he can kiss this cub reporter's
sweet little ass.
Lois!
Chloe, thanks for coming.
The gargoyle at the gate was
letting in everyone but me.
Come on. My car's parked
around the corner.
That was the event
for journalistic achievement,
and Lois Lane
isn't even a "plus one."
Lois,
you're an amazing reporter.
Uh, correction --
was an amazing reporter.
You're only as good
as your last story,
and I wrote mine
so long ago...
It was practically
with a Feather pen.
I need
that news splash--
The pregnant man
or an impeached president...
Or, better yet,
a rendezvous with a superhero.
I thought you gave up
on the costumed crusaders
after the Red-Blue Blur
ignored your open letter,
begging for an interview.
Can you blame the guy?
What was I thinking?
If you want your first interview
with a rock star,
you don't start
with Springsteen.
I had no idea
you were such a groupie
of the red, bold, and blue.
Well, who isn't?
The man has reinvented
the American hero.
Think about it.
He saves people.
He's mysterious,
completely unavailable.
What part of that
doesn't scream "Lois Lane"?!
God, you seriously have a crush
on him, don't you?
I respect his heroism,
professionally.
But even when I did
lower the bar
and tried to slum
a Green Arrow interview,
it turns out
Mr. Emerald Chaps
is another closet case
when it comes to publicity.
Lois, they wear costumes because
they don't want publicity.
Now, hurry up.
I'm parked illegally.
Ugh. Hold on.
These heels are silent killers.
No!
Chloe.
Lois!
Just give me the keys.
Ohh!
This one's
for your friend.
Oh, G--
Who the hell are you,
some sort of superhero?
You bet I am.
Call me Stiletto.
S08E17:
Stiletto
I know, Davis.
I was sidetracked.
I'll be home in like
20 minutes.
You're still
in the basement, right?
- Good.
- Miss Sullivan?
You took a pretty hard
hit to the head.
You should stick around
for observation.
I'm fine, thanks.
It's my
professional advice--
I appreciate that,
but I do have to go.
Chloe,
is this what it takes
to get a call back from you
these days?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, thanks for coming.
Sorry about being
the invisible best friend lately.
Where have you been?
Um, Watchtower.
Just when I thought
I'd hit my fill
of, uh, high-maintenance men,
I take a job from Oliver.
I thought
he was off the grid.
He's in Syria...
Sort of incommunicado
with the rest of the world.
Which is why I'm glad
you're here.
My laptop
was in my backseat
when the carjacker
peeled away.
I've been using it
to update my Watchtower
databases from home.
Chloe,
those files contain details
of nearly every operation.
Hence,
the panicky flare
with everything
I've been saying.
And before you bite my head off,
I admit--
I know-- I never
should have taken it home.
Just tell me
it was encrypted.
But not un-hackable.
Okay,
I'll find your computer.
Did you get a good look
at the mugger?
I got a good look at the asphalt
after he hit me.
But there was
another witness.
When I came to
in the ambulance,
Lois was raving about
some mysterious heroine
who swept in and saved the day--
Stiletto?
Must be some kind
of knife expert.
Where is Lois, anyway?
There may be a new superhero
in town.
Where do you think
she is?
Page 10!
Why don't you just bury
my stiletto sighting
with the classifieds
while you're at it?
The next time you pull me
from a press-society banquet,
at least get me a story
with a picture.
Something tells me Stiletto's
got a bad case of camera shy.
She's not posing
for a head shot.
Get her in action
on the street.
Sure,
no problem.
I'll just ask to see
her schedule of upcoming saves.
What?
Did I misjudge you, Lane?
I thought your game was all
about the power of persuasion.
Get the picture!
Lois.
Chloe told me
about the attack.
She said you mentioned someone
named Stiletto?
Patience, Smallville.
Tomorrow you can drool over her
with the rest of the world.
I'm fine, by the way.
Thanks for asking.
Stiletto gave you
all these quotes?
She was talkative.
Look,
I need you to put me
in contact with her.
Get your own hero.
I have to respect
her request to keep a low profile.
It is not everyday...
that a superhero entrusts me
with her phone number.
She gave you
her number?
Sorry.
My eyes only, Smallville.
Lois, this carjacker took
Chloe's computer.
It has all her
Isis client information on it.
If this Stiletto was the last
person to see this guy,
I need
to talk to her.
Look,
if you want to help Chloe,
why don't you
go downtown
and talk to the thug
they did catch?
Maybe Stiletto left enough teeth
in his mouth
for him to rat out
his buddy.
Rye whiskey, double.
Right away,
Mr. Manheim.
Hey, ugly.
The boss wants to see you,
and he doesn't look very happy.
I bet he's not;
Mr. Businessman.
Hey, uh, real quick--
Sorry.
Look, uh,
I-I know I just started,
but I was wondering
if I could, uh...
Get an advance
on today's pay?
Yeah.
Just had some...
stuff... come up.
I'll talk to Ricky.
But this is
the last time.
I was hoping,
at the very least,
A.J. was arrested
for a Dolce & Gabbana.
Somebody clocked us.
We had to get out of there,
Mr. Milano.
Bruno, I'm trying to pull us out
of the streets.
We finally cracked
the metallic tint
with those green rocks
from Smallville.
We can make all the money
in the world,
and you're out there
snatching purses.
It's not
about the door prize.
It's about
reminding people
we're the ones
who own this town,
not some cape-wearing
circus freaks.
Yeah.
Between the gash on your mug
and A.J.'s shiner,
you two clowns are
real intimidating.
How can you
just sit back
and let these vigilantes
take over the streets?
Our streets?!
Enough!
We are done
with petty street crime!
We are a business now!
Yeah, you're--
You're right, boss.
Maybe it's time
for Bruno Manheim
to climb
that corporate ladder.
Next we say good night
to the wannabe heroes.
Starting with Stiletto.
That one's personal.
Lois?
Lois, come on!
I can't be late for work!
What are you doing?
Picking up your rebound.
Lois.
I'm, uh...
I'm really flattered,
but I just broke up
with Chloe.
Ew. No.
I mean
rebound your career.
Nothing numbs the pain
of a breakup
like good,
old-fashioned work.
Look,
I'm not here to be saved.
You mentioned
a 100 bucks.
Now, what do you
want me to shoot?
Metropolis'
newest superhero.
Incoming.
Meet...
Stiletto.
I was gonna sew an "S"
into the chest.
Is that tacky?
Lois...
You're not serious.
Well,
not about the whole
"Cleaning up the streets" part,
obviously.
But...
I sort of quoted Stiletto
in one of my articles,
and my editor said that I need
a photo to get a page one.
Well, I guess I didn't see
the giant asterisk
above
"Lois Lane's Rules to Reporting"
that said
"or just make it up."
Hey!
Unlike you,
some of us haven't gotten
our up-close-and-personal
with
the Red-Blue Blur yet.
Now.
You know, look,
I know that you're dying
for a story with the guy,
but he doesn't talk to
anybody.
No offense, but...
Why's he gonna talk
to you?
Exactly.
The Red-Blue Blur might not talk
to me at first,
but a fellow superhero
like Stiletto
might just get his attention
long enough
to pitch the writing prowess
of the great Lois Lane.
Ready?
[ camera shutter clicking ]
Hey, well,
good luck with that.
Last I checked,
he's kind of invisible.
But crime
in this city isn't.
And when that police scanner
goes off,
the Red-Blue Blur
is never far behind.
E-mail those photos
to my editor.
I'm off to talk
to a real hero.
Chloe, it turns out
Lois' superfriend
may be our only hope
in getting your laptop back.
According to Met P.D.,
Stiletto's takedown posted bail
before they ever got him
behind bars.
Well, I haven't been able
to find any more leads
on Stiletto's
whereabouts,
but you might want to take
a look at this.
"Blur-etto"?
You know you've made it
when you have your own fansite.
And it looks like
your fans
are doing
a little matchmaking.
"No one understands a hero's
life of solitude better
than a fellow cape"?
"These two lonely hearts
belong together."
Who thinks
this stuff up?
Are they that far
off the mark?
Look, Chloe,
romance is the last thing
on my mind right now.
I know,
but let's face it.
You thought you found your
superpowered soul mate in Lana,
and I haven't heard you say
a word about her since she left.
That's because
I have you.
Come on, Clark.
I know I haven't been the most
reliable sidekick lately,
and Oliver and his gang
are M.I.A.
Having someone on speed dial
who knows what it's like
to lead a double life
might not be
such a bad thing.
My double life and I
are just fine.
I'd rather focus
on finding Stiletto
and getting
your computer back.
Okay.
But bold as she may be,
I seriously doubt we're gonna be
able to call her out
by putting a spike heel
over a klieg light.
Isn't it almost your bedtime,
Smallville?
Just finishing up some work
while I'm still motivated.
Slow night.
I'm good
if you want to go.
If the Red-Blue Blur
calls,
I'll be sure
to patch him through.
Oh, that's right,
because your idea
of being a hero
is making sure there's still
paper in the fax machine.
Just doing my job.
Well, you're wasting
your midnight oil
because,
between the two of us,
the editor is only counting
the empty coffee cups
on my desk.
And that's because
you're in the big leagues
and I'm still just
a copy boy?
No, because you're doing way
better than anyone expected!
Attention,
downtown unit --
Silent alarm
at Riverside Jewelry
on Fifth and Water,
Handle Code 1038.
Well,
I better go feed Shelby.
I should hit the gym.
I know I'm late.
I, uh, I got caught up
in a little project.
Are you taking pictures
of the sunset, bar boy?
This is a nice
tele-macro zoom.
Used to be a...
journalist, didn't you?
What are you doing here?
Now,
this is interesting.
Blondie looks a lot
different
when she's smiling.
Adorable.
Give me my camera back.
Unh-unh-unh.
What's going on here?
Do you know her?
- Her?
- Yeah.
No.
That's just a fluke.
Where is she?
You having a hard time
hearing me?
I said,
"Where is she?"
Where's Stiletto?
I have no idea.
Look, I don't know
where she is.
What is wrong
with you?
It's like you want me
to kill you.
Who's the hero now?
Way to go.
Now he's out.
Ah, he's worthless.
But it seems everyone
is in on Stiletto.
Get Ricky to hack
into that stolen laptop.
In the meantime,
I want you to go
right to the source.
Let's see what else we can
squeeze out of Blondie.
Wonderful.
Very stealth, Lois.
Ugh.
Next time,
I call myself "Nike."
He beat me here.
Hello?
Are you here?
Are you the Stiletto?
Can I just say
it's an honor?
Lois?
Who's Lois?
I'm Stiletto.
I should get back
to my cave.
Lois, you could have a bag
over your head,
and I'd still
know it's you.
Go figure.
I want the Red-Blue Blur.
I get the exact opposite.
What do you think
you're doing?
What are you doing?
You're supposed to be
feeding Shelby.
Seriously, is there any woman
in your life
you haven't stood up?
I saw the way you looked
at that scanner,
and I know how much you want
this superhero story.
So I came here
to make sure you were okay.
You're obviously not if you're
impersonating the Stiletto.
Okay, first off,
it's just "Stiletto."
There's no "the."
And second,
I'm not impersonating anyone.
I am Stiletto.
You made up a fake hero
so you could write her story?
Yeah.
Stiletto's only the beginning,
Clark.
These heels could kick open
some major doors for me.
What if Stiletto could help me
land a one-on-one
with the Red-Blue Blur?
Oh, this blur, he...
He avoids reporters
for a reason.
What would you say to him
no one else already has?
I wouldn't say anything, Clark.
I'd listen.
What if he's not looking
for a best friend?
Superpowered or not,
every Fred needs a Barney.
Unless it's based
on a lie.
Besides,
it could be dangerous.
Eventually, you'll find yourself
in a situation
you can't Stiletto yourself
out of.
Stiletto kicked ass
last night.
You should have seen the guy
I sent downtown.
I couldn't --
by the time I got there,
some attorney named Moynihan
already got him off
before I could talk to him
about Chloe's car.
Chris Moynihan?
He represents Ron Milano.
The biggest crime boss
in Metropolis.
Then let's go save
the world.
I'm in the market
for a sidekick anyway.
Just don't slow me down.
I'll find Milano
on my own.
You're gonna do everything
you can
to make sure your Stiletto story
doesn't get published.
Did you know your
transmission slips a bit in third?
What are you doing here?
What do you know
about Stiletto?
Stiletto? I don't know
who you're talking about.
Let me go!
No!
Ugh!
You do not want
to lie to me.
I swear to God I don't know
who Stiletto is.
I never saw her.
Okay, sweetheart,
but if you do,
I'd like to leave
a message.
Hello to you, too.
Expecting Freddy Krueger?
What are you doing here?
I thought you were
tracking down Stiletto.
Well, the story broke
a proverbial heel.
It's not happening.
Oh. Bummer.
Oh, well.
I mean, it is Friday night.
There's bound to be
a tequila shooter
out on this town
with your name on it.
Why don't you go out,
you know, have fun?
I'm not actually here
to hang,
but 10-4 on the
loud-and-clear un-vitation.
Jimmy's not answering
his phone,
and I was just wondering
if perhaps you knew--
Where my ex was?
I thought that's what
Facebook updates were for.
Why are you even
looking for him?
I needed his help
photographing something,
and now I need his help
burning the evidence.
Fine.
You know what?
Surprise!
I'm Stiletto.
Lois.
Oh, my God,
you did this for a story.
Didn't you?
Okay.
Clark's diatribe is still
ringing in my ears.
I don't need it
in surround sound.
I get it.
I messed up.
Like you've never gotten in
over your head?
Actually,
Lois, um...
Can I tell you
something?
Sure.
Jimmy should be
at the Ace of Clubs.
I really need to remove him
from my Facebook friends,
don't I?
Yeah.
Thanks, Chlo.
And...
Thank you
for understanding.
Anytime, Lois.
Hey, Bruno,
check this out.
Yeah?
I just unlocked a
whole mess of files.
Who the hell
are these guys?
Ugh!
Jimmy?
Jimmy.
Ugh!
How the hell did
you get back here?
Do you know
who you're talking to?
who I am?
You want to mess with me?
You want to
push me?
- Oh, my God!
- You want to push me, punk?
Hey, come on, Bruno!
Back up, man!
- You're gonna kill him!
- Come on.
Seriously?
Ohh.
Clark Kent of
The Daily Planet.
Looks like you reporters think
you got a little story here.
Oh, that's it.
Wow, that's far.
If you want,
I can tell you how it ends.
Come on, Lois.
Ugh!
That worked.
Jimmy.
Stiletto has no idea
what she just stepped in.
Lois!
Clark!
Hang in there.
You're gonna be just fine.
Oh, my God.
Dial 911.
Why did you do that,
Clark?
You didn't need to be
some kind of hero.
Lois...
You have to get me
out of here.
Okay. Okay.
- Come on.
- The medics are on their way.
Come on, superhero.
You're gonna be fine.
Nothing like
a double-frosted bear claw
to ease the pain
of a flesh wound, right?
Oh, and I, uh, didn't know
whether you wanted your copies
single-sided
or double,
so I did both,
and then I thought,
"Hmm, three-holed
or no-holed?"
And I didn't know,
so I did both,
which is why there's...
so many.
Lois, you didn't have
to do all this.
But thank you.
Looks like you got
your cover story after all.
I guess.
You guess?
The last time your name
was above the fold,
you held
a champagne toast.
Is there something
about this article
that's still
bothering you?
Fine, I admit it.
Sometimes,
the Lois "Fast" Lane ambition
ramps into cruise control
and gets away from me.
Those mob guys
would still be on the street
if you hadn't come
to my rescue.
Your rescue.
Yeah, right.
You're the one
with the...
Smallville,
if you hadn't been there to...
You're welcome, Lois.
I hope this means
that Stiletto's hanging up
her heels for good.
Gladly.
Those heels were giving
my blisters blisters.
Besides,
if Manheim had better aim,
you'd be dead.
And it was really sweet
of you to, you know...
Throw yourself in there,
but, uh...
I never should have put you
in danger.
It's not like you save lives
for a living.
No, there's only one
Red-Blue Blur.
Honestly,
I don't envy the guy.
After walking a mile
in Stiletto's shoes,
I was reminded
that I am not cut out
for that life
of solitude.
I didn't know there was
room for introspection
underneath that costume.
Wow.
Look who got grazed
by a funny bullet.
You weren't gonna eat this,
were you?
Hey, man.
Didn't think I'd be hearing
from you again.
Yeah, well, let's just get this
over with, okay?
You're the one that said
he was strapped for cash.
Well,
I guess things change.
Hey, Clark!
Thank you.
I never thought
it would feel so good
to be reunited with a bunch
of silicone microchips.
I grabbed it
before the police arrived.
So hopefully Manheim wasn't able
to pull any files off it.
Well, rest assured,
Tony Soprano Jr.
is my last close call.
I am done traveling
with all of my techno treasures
in one basket.
Are you
expecting company?
Uh, no.
Turns out that my
body's natural reaction to stress
is to bake undigestible amounts
of food.
Really?
After all the near-apocalypses
we've been through,
I've never seen more
than a chocolate-chip cookie
come out of that oven.
Are you okay?
It's...
I mean,
you almost died yesterday...
For my computer.
Chloe,
you made an honest mistake.
I'm fine.
I know you better
than that.
This is not
about a computer.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Really, I'm fine.
Look, I apologize if I've been
a little off my game lately.
It's just
that after my divorce
and Brainiac
and now...
playing Watchtower
to a bunch of needy superheroes,
I forget that I need to be
all smiles all the time.
Chloe, no one expects you
to bounce back
from everything
you've been through.
I just want you to know I'm here
for you if you need me.
I know.
But right now I really just need
a little bit of space...
Not a supersave, okay?
When am I gonna learn
that a wild-goose chase
for a story usually ends
with a rotten egg?
Hello?
Is this Lois Lane,
the reporter?
Who wants to know?
This is
the Red-Blue Blur.
Yeah, right.
How do I know you're not
some deep throat wannabe
with a lot of time
on his creepy hands?
Look down.
I received your letter,
Miss Lane.
Call me Lois...
if you want.
And while we're at it,
do you want to weigh in
on the whole
"Red-Blue Blur" thing?
Because it's kind of a mouthful
on this end.
I think there's probably
a better name out there.
And if there's anyone
who can find it,
it's you, Miss Lane.
I'll put my best men
on it.
And by "men,"
I mean me
because I work
in the basement
and employ
pretty much no one,
unless you count
my intern.
I'm sorry.
I'm rambling.
You're nervous.
Can you read my mind?
Who am I kidding?
It's Saturday night,
and I hightailed it
down here
because I have one obsession
right now, and it's you.
And when you didn't respond
to my skywriting,
I just...
It was a nice one,
by the way.
Between you and me,
I could use a little work
on that subtle thing.
You know
there's nothing wrong
with taking your job
seriously.
There is when you don't know
who you'd be without it.
Something tells me
you know yourself
better than you think.
Lois,
you're a great reporter...
All on your own.
You don't need a hero
or some gimmick
to make a headline.
Thanks.
My editor would kill me,
but...
I don't want this story.
What I've really been
wondering is...
What is it that you need?
I mean,
you've dedicated your life
to a city
full of strangers.
And I'm not saying
that I know what it's like
to be a hero,
but...
Even the fastest blur
in the world
can't outrun loneliness.
I guess
what I'm saying is...
If you ever
want to talk...
Totally off the record...
I'm only
a phone call away.
I'll keep that in mind.
And, Lois...
When I'm ready to tell
the world my secret,
you'll be the first
to know.
Ripped: LeapinLar
[OpenSubtitles.org]
Final Edits: VeRdiKT
[Subscene.com]
www.tvsubtitles.net