I didn't mean to cut your head off.
I'm just under a lot of pressure here.
Who wants cake?
Another glass of bubbly?
And throw in a shirley temple
for the lady.
Lois, don't you think you might
want to pace yourself?
Believe me, smallville, i am
a lot more obnoxious sober,
And the last thing anyone wants is me
making a scene at this blessed event.
Chloe is barely legal,
And she is getting herself
hitched to the first guy
Who's shown her any attention,
present company excepted.
I have suffered
enough heartache
To know real love when i see it,
and looking at those two...
I don't know.
I don't see it.
Are you sure
you're not just jealous
That your little cousin's
beating you to the altar?
This isn't a competition.
Then why are you keeping score?
Listen, lois, it may not kill you
to just show a little support.
You want support?
I'll show you support.
Good idea.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my name is lois lane.
Most of you know me
as chloe's cousin,
A.K.A., the maid of honor.
When chloe and i were little girls,
we made a promise...
Neither of us would get married
until we found our soul mates...
... the one person
in the whole wide world
That we were destined to be with...
Which is why you can't take
a 10-Year-Old on their word.
Okay, come on.
What i think lois is trying to say
is that you can't predict
When you will find
that special someone.
And jimmy is, without a doubt,
that special someone for chloe.
I've known chloe
since the eighth grade, and...
We've been through a lot together.
In all those years, the truth is
i've never seen her so happy.
Congratulations. To jimmy and chloe.
To jimmy and chloe.
So, we'll see you guys in a few months.
Thank you so much.
You guys are great.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
You know, it's a shame your parents
couldn't be here tonight.
I would have really loved to celebrate
your impeccable taste with them.
Well, they send their love.
Dad is this close to closing
a big deal in london.
His, um, priorities are a little
out of whack, but he means well.
Oh, well, i still hope
you enjoyed yourself tonight.
You know what was my favorite
part of the evening?
If you say lois' toast,
i'm getting a prenup.
God, no.
When clark was toasting us,
i looked over at you,
And you had the most wonderful
smile on your face.
You know, it really means a lot to me
that you're finally okay with clark.
Me being uptight about you
and clark is yesterday's news.
There may be a textbook's worth
of history between the two of you, but
The future is all chloe
and jimmy's story.
You know, i think it's about time
We head upstairs for some
much-Needed alone time.
Oh, i think that is a fantastic idea.
Smallville 805
Synchro : flolo
For seriessub.Com
Smallville?!
Good afternoon, lois.
I thought you might need one of these.
Please tell me we didn't...
You're hysterical
when you're hung over, lois.
Don't worry.
You got changed all by yourself...
In the middle of the kitchen
for like an hour.
I take it i took a little drive
on the porcelain highway.
It was more like
a cross-Country trip.
You know, i...
You didn't have to take care
of me last night.
I would have been perfectly fine
on my own at the talon.
I don't think jimmy and chloe
would have been up
For the white snake sing-Along.
Chloe!
I was supposed to meet her
For a dress fitting
first thing this morning.
- Do you need a ride?
- You may have held my hair,
But i don't need you
to hold my hand, smallville.
This may shock you,
but i can still drive a car.
Not if it's not here.
This may shock you,
but you were in no condition
To get behind the wheel
last night, lois.
Thanks for the ride.
What do you mean
you can't find the i.P. Address?
The e-Mail came
through a ghost router.
As soon as we saw it, the router
vanished from the grid.
At the very least, this could prove
mr. Luther is still alive.
Or it could prove that someone
is toying with me.
Find out who took the crystal,
or find a new line of work.
You know what's amazing to me?
That you can't find time
to return my calls,
But you do manage to fit it
into your busy schedule
To buy the star city towers
right out from under me.
Business is business.
Well, this is not about business.
And to be honest with you,
revenge is not your best color.
Don't flatter yourself.
One of the most important things
that lex taught meis you can't afford
To live in the past.
Did professor luther also teach you
a thing or two about deception?
Or how about obsession? I hear his
class in murder's an easy "a."
He's done more for this world
than you ever will, oliver.
He dedicated his life
to making it a safer place.
You know, mercy, it seems to me
Like lex may have been a little
bit more than a mentor.
If you're done wasting my time,
i have phone calls to make.
Look, uh, i'm sorry.
Really, okay? I didn't come here
to battle with you.
Actually, i came here
to raise the white flag.
How civil.
What do you propose...
a... a truce?
Well, truce, yeah...
Over dinner.
You haven't changed one bit.
Oliver always wants
what oliver can't have.
You know, sometimes a meal's
just a meal.
You pick me up at 7:00.
7:30 it is.
Chloe?
Jimmy?
You know what lois likes to see
when she comes home...
Pants... pants on everyone.
I had no idea jimmy
was so romantic.
Guess the olsen's
not so wholesome.
Chloe! It's your coz!
Guess who came to my rescue...
not oliver queen.
Clark kent.
He's just the sweetest boy
i have ever known.
Chalk that one up
to alcohol poisoning.
This is smallville p.D., impound for
a chloe sullivan and a james olsen.
Your vehicles were just brought in
for obstructing a street cleaner.
You have ni...
They didn't even come home last night?
Then where the hell are they?
Chloe! Are you okay?
I think so. Where are we?
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
To find out if these two
were truly meant to be.
Lois, i checked the metropolis
and the smallville hospitals,
As well as the airport...
no sign of jimmy or chloe.
You covered a lot of ground.
We need to find the right people to ask.
Did you find anything?
Chloe and jimmy aren't the only
couple that's gone missing, clark.
At least three couples in the last two
weeks have vanished without a trace.
- All engaged.
- Credit cards haven't been touched.
Phone records show no sign of activity.
The list goes on and on. So unless
oprah said eloping was in for fall...
They've all been abducted.
I called the police. They won't even declare
jimmy and chloe missing for 24 hours.
What kind of person would prey on people
during the happiest time of their lives?
You know, if i hadn't been
too drunk to go home last night,
- I would have been there to stop it.
- Or you would have been missing, too.
Don't worry, lois. We'll find them.
We should cross-Reference
jimmy and chloe
With the other two victims, see if
they have anything in common.
One step ahead of you.
Jimmy, chloe, and the other couples
All visited the same wedding
vendors within the last 10 days.
A bakery, a jewelry store,
and a stationery shop.
To name a few.
That stationery shop
is right around the corner.
I'm gonna check it out.
I'll call if i find anything.
No way am i putting
my cousin's life
In the hands of a mild-Mannered copyboy.
Try to keep up.
The art of abduction is
surprisingly difficult.
It's easier
when i find couples together.
It saves time.
Well, we'd hate
to inconvenience you.
It's no trouble at all.
It's my duty.
What...
- What is that?
- This is a lie detector.
It's fairly harmless
and not complicated at all.
In fact,
when you get right down to it,
It's really quite simple.
All it does is listen to your heart.
I guess you expect us to believe
that that's harmless, too.
No. This is electricity.
Electricity hurts.
Is this how you get your kicks...
Torturing innocent people?
It's not torture.
I'm doing you a favor.
Not everyone is meant to be married.
Countless couples rush
headlong into marriage,
Ignorant to responsibility
of the burden of truth
That comes with that level
of commitment.
Those that are truly dedicated
have no secrets.
Let's warm up with an easy question.
James...
Have you ever cheated
on your fiancée before?
No.
Stop! Don't hurt her!
I'm the one that lied! You hurt me!
Lies don't hurt you!
Lies hurt the ones you love!
You be honest.
Chloe...
Look, it wasn't really cheating.
I mean, this...
This crazy woman... she kissed me,
And i had a freakin' heart attack,
and i wound up in the hospital.
I know. I know it wasn't your fault.
You are the only girl...
That i've ever loved.
That will do for now.
Let's see what the bride has to say.
I wonder.
How many lies is she hiding behind?
If this were the last place on earth
and i had to write an s.O.S.,
- I wouldn't come here for a nib or a quill.
- Thank you for your time.
Lois, we're not gonna get anywhere
If you shake down
every single person we talk to.
He was stone walling us. You have to put the
screws to a perp when the clock is ticking!
He was 70 years old, lois.
He spent the night in the hospital.
He still had his bracelet on.
Clark, my cousin,
your best friend, is missing.
She could be hurt or dying or worse.
Which is exactly why we can't
waste any more time.
Okay, genius,
what do you want to do?
You should go back to the daily planet,
See if those background checks
we ordered came in.
And just what do you plan on doing
alone that we can't do together?
A lot.
Wait a minute. The guy is preying
on couples, right?
Don't even go there.
So, if we walk in there
pretending to be the bait,
We'll have him
eating out of our hands.
No one will believe it, lois,
not even for a second.
Clark kent...
Will you marry me?
A smile every now and then
wouldn't kill you.
In short supply, lois.
I wouldn't want to waste one.
May i help you?
Well, we are finally out ring shopping.
Who's the luckiest girl in the world? I am.
Some friends of ours said
that your store
Is the best place in town
to find engagement rings.
Is there a certain piece
that you'd like to see?
Well...
What about this one, pumpkin?
Anything you want, muffin.
Must be great seeing so many happy
couples come through here every day.
It certainly is.
It's very fulfilling helping to solidify
the bond between husband and wife.
Excellent craftsmanship...
A perfect circle,
no beginning and no end.
Try it on. See how it looks.
Don't get stage fright, poodle.
You're gonna have to do this
center stage
In front of a packed house
sooner than you think.
He has performance anxiety.
Look at that... perfect fit.
What are you two doing here?
Oliver, you didn't get
the invitation yet?
My invitation to what?
Tell him, cupcake.
Lois and i are...
... we're getting married.
You're just full of surprises
lately, aren't you, clark?
I know, right?
I mean, we've been friends for so long,
But we just had
this one magical night,
And we couldn't deny
our feelings any longer.
Is this true?
I'm afraid so.
See you at the wedding.
She has great taste.
You're a very lucky man.
You have no idea.
I swear, if you're this afraid
of pretend commitment,
What's gonna happen
when some poor girl
Makes the mistake of actually
falling for you?
This isn't working, lois.
We need to split up.
We can track down more leads
if we go in opposite directions.
- And what if you get into trouble?
- I think i'll be okay.
You know, you're drifting
dangerously close to cocky.
What, no snarky comeback
from the peanut gallery?
Please don't do this.
You should be pleading with me
to continue.
If only someone had taken the time
to do this for my wife and i.
Did you hook her up
to your little machine?
Something tells me
she didn't walk out of here.
I cherished her, james.
I honored her.
I did everything that i promised
when i took my wedding vows,
And how does she reward me?
With one lie after another.
She never knew, but...
I could smell him on her.
So you killed her.
You see, the heart and the mouth
are not always on the same page.
Get the hell away from her.
Chloe...
Have you ever cheated on your fiancé?
No.
Excellent. Next question.
Are you in love with anyone else?
Look, don't answer him, chloe.
Don't give him the satisfaction.
No!
Your fiancé is not the best person
to be taking advice from at this moment.
Now i'm gonna ask you
one more time.
Are you in love
with anyone else?
No.
Only you, jimmy, forever.
Congratulations, james olsen,
chloe sullivan.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Mercy?
We got dinner reservations
at hobbs bay in just under an hour.
I like to work up an appetite.
You used to be better at this.
What happened to not being
interested in revenge?
This is not revenge.
This is just practice.
Weak men like you make me stronger.
So, you learn that lionel kills
your parents, and what do you do?
You drink yourself onto the society
page for, what, like a month?
Well, you know me.
I like to keep myself busy.
You still can't take anything
seriously, can you?
Just like our relationship.
You know how much
you meant to me.
Yeah, that became clear when
i caught you with the waitress.
Or was she a hostess?
- How many times do i have to apologize?
- I don't want an apology!
I want an explanation.
What the hell were you so afraid of?
You.
Clark, it's lois.
I spoke with the police.
They told me
that they think i should...
Do you mind?
Your high beams are burning
holes into my skull!
Look, i don't know
what to do anymore,
So can you give me a call
as soon as you get this? Bye.
You'll be seeing
your fiancé soon enough.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, my god.
Jimmy?
Jimmy, wake up.
We're okay.
What the hell happened?
The last thing i remember,
that guy pulled out that gun,
- And then everything went black.
- I told you we'd make it out.
Is this that masked man's idea
of some kind of a twisted joke?
I'm gonna have to take
the credit for this one.
And for the record, it was
a lot less creepy yesterday.
You know, i don't think
i'd still be alive
If i was sitting across
anyone else in that room.
Because we're meant to be together.
'Cause... things like that don't
happen to people by accident.
No.
Because you don't have any secrets.
We should call the sheriff.
Okay.
I'm glad you two are okay.
- Clark, what is it?
- It's lois. I can't find her.
She left me a voice mail, and then she
never made it back to the planet.
She was saying something
about car headlights.
Headlights? That's what he used
when he took us.
- Why would he want lois?
- It's a long story,
But if there's anything you can
remember, it might help me find lois.
This guy, he's a certifiable
whack job, c.K.
He was talking about how secrets
kill, and, our bond.
Stuff about... lies begetting lies.
What did he say about your bond?
I don't know. He was talking about
how important it is to
Solidify the bond
between husband and wife.
I know who has lois.
Tell me right now.
What'd you do with my cousin?
Where is she?
Lois?!
Lois.
Clark, you got to find
chloe and jimmy.
He let them go. Listen, i'm gonna
get you out of here,
But you need to tell me...
where is he?
Right behind you.
Clark!
Clark?
Wake up.
Clark.
I know who you are!
Then i suppose i won't
be needing this anymore...
Now that we're all acquainted.
Let's begin.
What's the point?
Now that we've both seen your face,
you're gonna kill us anyway.
Don't be so certain.
You must really care about her,
storming in here.
That's very gallant of you.
Yeah, he's stupid that way.
- Let her go.
- After her turn, you'll get yours.
My turn?
What is this, some kind of game?
No.
No, it's a test,
To reveal how much you two have
been hiding from one another.
If you pass, you'll want
to invite me to your wedding.
If you fail...
Well, the guest list will be
the least of your worries.
Ladies first.
Have you ever cheated
on your fiancé?
Of course not. Don't be ridiculous.
What are you doing?!
You're killing him!
- No. Your lies are.
- Okay, okay, i take it back, then.
I'm sorry! Just...
just don't hurt him again!
Killing us...
It won't take away the pain
that pushed you here.
I'm doing this for you.
What?
The broken hearted
are the walking dead.
Either way, i'm saving you both
a lot of unnecessary pain.
Okay, crazy, this is the deal.
We're not even really a couple.
So this twisted test
doesn't mean anything.
Next question.
Deep down, underneath it all,
do you love this man?
Answer the question, lois.
Don't out think it.
Just tell the truth.
Do you love him?
Tell the truth.
Yes.
And you... do you love this woman?
Speak up. She can't hear you
if you don't speak up.
Lois.
- Clark?
- Lois, are you okay?
I'm not sure.
Let's get you out of here.
The one person in the whole wide world
that we were destined to be with,
Which is i guess why you can't
take a 10-Year-Old...
Yeah, that's pretty much how i felt.
Oh, my god, chloe, i am so sorry.
I mean, i know my face is under
"faux pas" in the dictionary,
But this is a whole new low.
I would say that this is
a close second,
Behind the time you crashed
lana's engagement party.
In fact, you may want to start
avoiding engagement parties all together.
Chloe, it's not funny.
I ruined your special night.
Lois, considering
how the night ended,
I'd say that the party
was a rousing success.
Besides, you were just being honest,
Though you could he been
a little less public about it.
Lois, why didn't you just tell me
that this is how you felt?
I don't know.
Look, clark and lana went south.
Things fell apart
between me and ollie.
Just knowing that i had everything
that i wanted right in front of me...
And having it slip away.
I just didn't want to see you
have that kind of heartache.
Lois, you are the most wonderful big
cousin in the world for thinking that.
But trust me.
I wouldn't have said yes if
i didn't know it was meant to be.
How can you be sure?
Because when i look at jimmy,
i can just feel it...
In my heart.
I mean, sunset or dungeon, he's my guy.
Color me jealous.
Clark was right after all.
He usually is. Get used to it.
Get used to what?
To being a member of the family.
Congratulations, jimmy.
What was that all about?
You and me, oddly enough.
Speaking of which, i have
something you need to see.
After the spanish inquisition,
I was thinking we deserve
an extra-Long honeymoon.
- So, maybe bora bora, st.Tropez?
- Chloe...
Before you start booking anything,
there's something you need to know.
As insane as that guy was,
he made a great point.
If we're gonna make it, we can't
have any secrets from each other.
Yeah. It's that we don't have much
left to hide.
Yeah. There is.
I'm not who you think i am.
The sudden knot
in my stomach tells me
This isn't you embracing
your inner nietzsche.
My parents aren't coming
to the wedding.
They...
Well, they actually don't exist.
Well, i mean, they do. Of course
they do. They exist. It's just that...
My dad's not an investment
banker in manhattan.
He's a part-Time mechanic
and full-Time alcoholic in oklahoma city.
I never even really met my mom.
Why would you keep something
like this from me?
This city... it's huge.
It's the top of the world
coming from where i come from.
And the only way
i could fit in was to...
... be someone else.
Why didn't you trust me?
I know.
I'm sorry. I'm...
So sorry.
I screwed up big-Time.
And i totally understand if you
need some time or even if...
If you want out.
A guy like me...
Doesn't get a girl like you, chloe.
Life... it doesn't work like that.
Yeah, it does.
So much for breakfast in bed.
I'm late for a meeting in metropolis.
You know, some of us still have
corporations to run.
Oh, that's right. I forgot about that,
although i've got this really funny feeling
That you could probably find
somebody else to answer your phones.
I'm thinking more like...
Dinner in malibu in time for the sunset.
What do you say?
Is that a hint of romance i detect?
I can't stop myself.
Save it, in case you want
to tip another hostess.
There was nothing romantic
about last night, oliver.
I had an itch. You scratched it.
Tess, what happened to you?
I grew up.
And you left right when things
started to get interesting.
You know the way out.
You're not avoiding me, are you?
Me? Why would i be avoiding you?
I was just shopping for wedding
gifts for chloe and jimmy.
So you're finally on board
with the happy couple.
Yep. All it took was them passing a madman's
electro-Cosmic death quiz,
And i am sold.
In or out?
You know, all things considered,
the stairs are better for cardio.
Come on. Statistically,
this is the safer way to travel.
He confessed... the jeweler.
I heard. Five couples?
So, about that test...
Who would have thought
you were such a good liar, huh?
You even beat that machine.
Even though i'm a natural master
of deception, i needed a little help.
I mean, that machine was a piece
of kaiser-Era junk.
Well, it did work the first time,
you know, when you electrocuted me.
Exactly.
So while he was off
playing game-Show host,
I slipped the sensor off my finger.
Pretty crafty?
So you weren't telling the truth.
Please. I mean,
we do make a good team,
But don't let our cover go
to that big old head of yours.
I didn't.
- Good.
- Great.
Let's just be happy that i was
under the gun and not you.
And why's that?
Smallville, everyone knows
you're a terrible liar.
Who knows where we'd be if you'd
answered that question?
For seriessub.Com