Previously on "smallville"...
- Who do you think you are?
- Tess mercer.
I'm now the acting c.E.O.
Of luthorcorp
And all its subsidiaries.
Will you marry me?
Don't move!
Chloe sullivan,
you're under arrest.
Jimmy, get clark!
Chloe sullivan was never arrested
by the department of domestic security.
He's got a research compound
in montana called black creek.
This was retrieved
from the excavation site.
- And the montana facility?
- Completely dismantled.
And the guests
have been re-Assimilated.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Yes.
I've been holding on to a life on
this farm that hasn't existed for years.
I'll see you bright and early
monday morning.
You're looking at the newest
recruit tothe daily planet.
Looks like we're gonna be
neighbors, lane.
Well, big points
for punctuality, smallville. But...
What's with
the wardrobe malfunction?
What?
This is a nice shirt.
Human resources is gonna be
down here any minute,
And you do not want to meet them
looking like...
The brawny lumberjack.
Hold on.
Hey! Personal space, lane!
Remember?
Gq here needs
some roadside assistance.
Let me borrow your spare.
Come with me.
Don't tell me
i have to wear a tie.
Always dress for success.
No time for the men's room.
Let's change in here.
- A phone booth is not exactly pri...
- Burning daylight hours, clark! Change!
Lucky for you it's a slow
news day and i was at my desk.
Otherwise, you could have
spent your entire career
Being nicknamed "farm boy"
or "flannel man."
Trust me, the news game
can be brutal.
You do not want to bomb
on your first day. Hi.
So, how do i look?
Good.
So much for the slow news day.
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Get away from the bus.
Guess this must be
my stop.
Smallville 802
Synchro : flolo
For seriessub.Com
Are you okay?
Can somebody help us
over here, please?!
Over here!
- Was she on the bus?
- I don't know.
I need you to, uh...
hold on to this for me.
What's your name?
Bette.
You inhaled a lot of smoke, bette.
We're gonna give you a little fresh air.
Take slow,
deep breaths.
Try to stay calm,
okay?
I'm gonna check you over.
Tell me if anything hurts.
Just hang in there,
bette.
It's okay.
You're doing great.
You too.
Thank god you heard me.
You were hard to miss. Look at me.
Well, bette, apart from
breathing in all that smoke,
You're gonna be okay. We should still
get you to met general just to be sure.
You think you can make it
to my rig?
- Can you grab my bag?
- Yeah, of course.
- Thanks, uh...
- Chloe.
Davis. You make a good wingman,
chloe... or wing person.
Thank you
for your help.
Straight to the hospital.
You're gonna be okay.
You'll be all right.
- Excuse me. Mind taking a look?
- Yeah.
There was a woman with red hair.
I helped her get out of the bus,
and the paramedics took her.
Do you know if she's all right?
A lot of people
have been coming in and out,
But the most seriously injured
are at the hospital.
You should try there.
Thank you.
Hey. Clark.
Chloe?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I just got here.
I just helped this girl
who was on the bus.
- What happened?
- Well, i heard there was a bomb on the bus,
But i haven't had a chance
to check it out.
Even a dress shirt can't hide
the hero in you, huh, clark?
- Heck of a first day at the office.
- Well, that's why i'm there...
So i can be around
to help more people.
Working at the daily planet, i'll hear
about every cris as it happens.
I just wish that
you were there with me.
You know, now that lex
isn't running things...
Yeah.
I've spent almost my entire life
praying to the gods of journalism.
It might be kind of nice
to try something new, you know?
See how it feels.
Now you're ready for a change?
Actually, uh...
There's pretty big changes.
Apparently the goddess of journalism
is wondering where i am.
With lois on the case,
it's gonna get harder
To duck away to save the day.
If i could hide my secret from you,
i think i can handle your cousin.
Good luck with that.
I got to go.
Uh, tell lois that i said
to take it easy on you.
Whoa, clark. What happened?
Are you okay?
Why? Were you worried about me?
Uh, no. I'm trying to chase down
a lead on this story.
I don't want to have to
chase after you, too.
Hey, did you happen to hear anything
while you were out there
- Making your ash angels?
- Actually, i did
The police think the bomb misfired
since there weren't any casualties.
Didn't feel like a misfire
to me.
All right. Who's your source?
I'm sorry, lois. I didn't get a name.
I was too busy...
you know, helping people?
Rule number one...
Always know your source.
I understand.
Look, if you're gonna teach a class
on lois lane's rules of reporting,
I think i'd rather read
the cliff notes.
Boss wants to
see you... now.
Okay, my first official meeting
with our latest leader.
Not you... kent.
Well, you're gonna want
to clean yourself up.
Uh, rule number two... always
make a good first impression
And don't screw up
with the boss.
I think
that's two rules.
Whatever.
Try not to get fired
on your first day, okay?
Mr. Kent. Go right in.
Have a seat, mr. Kent.
Tess mercer,
acting c.E.O. Of luthorcorp.
You're my boss?
You weren't this shy when i was
the damsel in distress, kent.
Don't tell me you're intimidated
by a powerful woman.
No, i just... i'm surprised to see you
back at work so soon.
I have big shoes to fill.
And the paramedics said
that i was fine.
It's unusual, isn't it...
For the new c.E.O. Of luthorcorp
to be taking the bus to work?
I'm going green.
You know, doing what i can
to save the planet.
But, for the sake
of the shareholders,
Let's keep that
between ourselves, hmm?
Seems we were destined
to meet.
I already had you
on my to-Do list today.
Lex told me
all about you.
Well, not much to tell, really.
He said you have a thing
for saving people?
And after this morning,
i'd say that's true.
Ever since
lex's disappearance,
I have used all of luthorcorp's
resources to find him.
Do you have any leads?
The world's a big place.
I was hoping his good friend
could tell me where to look.
The lex luthor that i knew
disappeared years ago.
It's been a long time
since we were friends.
I don't know
what happened to him.
Fair enough.
But if you do think
of something, please give me a call.
And, clark...
You were extraordinary
out there.
Thank you
for saving my life.
I saw how this job
consumed lex's life.
I'd hate to see the same thing
happen to yours.
- Handsome.
- And a liar.
He's hiding something.
I'll have someone
watch him.
No. I'll keep an eye
on this one personally.
Hi.
Doc says i'm okay,
But i feel like i just threw
down with a carton of cloves.
Well, i figured
you'd be hungry,
So, unfortunately,
it's meat-Loaf mondays,
But i did score you
some curly fries.
Are you kidding? Hot food's good
any day of the week.
Thanks.
I, uh, i'm surprised
your parents aren't... here.
Look, it's really cool what
you did for me and everything,
But it doesn't mean i have
to tell you my life story.
I wasn't asking.
I haven't seen them
in years.
I'm kind of in between homes
right now.
You know, why don't i grab you
a soda to wash that down?
- Davis. Hi.
- How's she doing?
Uh, she got
a clean bill of health.
But, um, i just found out
that she's a street kid.
So i was gonna drop her off
at the city shelter tonight.
She's a 15-Year-Old girl,
chloe.
You really think she's gonna be safe
at the metropolis shelter?
Not too streetwise,
are you?
I was just trying
to help.
If you have any ideas,
please, step up. Do something.
So, i hear that you need
a place to stay?
Not really.
But if you did,
i have a friend,
And she runs a home,
and it's pretty nice.
Is she some kind of religious nut?
'Cause i don't really roll with the holy.
It's not like that. She helps girls learn
some skills, score a job.
I can get you
an application.
Or... you can forget it.
It's your choice.
Look, bette, you can
stay with me tonight if you need to.
You're nice, chloe.
Kind of like a girl scout.
I don't want to be
your latest merit badge.
I'm gonna take my thin mints
and head home.
I thought you might want
a safe place to stay tonight.
But would i still be
a free agent?
As long as you promise
to think about davis' offer.
Okay, i'm in.
Great. Let's go.
That new boss, she really
came out of nowhere, huh?
You tell me. You're the one who just spent
quality time with her.
She just wanted
to welcome me aboard.
Don't try to keep secrets
from me, clark.
Tess mercer is
a pit bull in prada.
There's no way she'd roll out
the welcome mat
For a copyboy, no matter
how charming his smile is.
You think i have
a charming smile?
I think you're about to lose some teeth
if you don't tell me what she said.
Lois, you sound like
a jealous girlfriend.
Jealous. Of you?
Please, that would be like willie mays
being jealous of a batboy.
Watch and learn.
Hi.
Lois lane...
daily planet.
- Care to show me around?
- No press allowed.
Swing and a miss?
I'm just getting started.
Excuse me.
Do you like baseball?
Who's your
favorite player?
Because i can get you a signed
photograph of anyone you want
If you just do me
this little favor.
Sorry, ma'am.
No one's allowed in.
What's your name,
officer?
Officer derek.
It's got to be
a mistake.
No mistake, sir.
We haven't found one shred
of explosive material.
No residue. There's no
detonator. There's nothing.
I'm telling you...
there was no bomb on that bus.
Wake up, smallville.
Our cop's about as stiff
as his starched uniform.
- Let's move on.
- Lois
I just heard
there was no bomb.
That doesn't look like
the engine overheating.
Look, we need to talk
to somebody who was on the bus.
Chloe called. She's helping
a homeless girl who was there.
Maybe you could ask her what she saw,
and i'll track down the others.
The thing is,
not so good with the kids.
Why don't you take little orphan annie
and i'll do the rest?
Bette!
Thank you so much.
It's just a grilled cheese.
No big.
All this take-Out, i thought you could use
something home-Cooked.
It's okay. It's just my friend clark.
Don't worry about it.
What's up?
Wait. I remember you.
You helped me get off the bus.
Yeah, i'm glad
you're okay, bette.
Do you mind if i ask you
a few questions?
Did you see anything
before the blast?
Anything unusual?
Anything strange?
- What are you, like a cop or something?
- Clark,
She's been through a lot today.
What's going on?
The police say
there's no evidence of a bomb.
I think someone with a meteor power
may have caused the blast.
What's a meteor power?
Uh, sometimes,
people develop special abilities
After being exposed to
a certain type of meteor rock.
Tommy.
Another street kid.
He told me he found this
weird rock a couple days ago,
And now whenever he gets angry,
things heat up.
I thought
he was messing with me.
We got into a fight today.
He was being a jerk, so i ran on
to the bus to get away from him.
- Do you know where i can find him?
- I know where he hangs.
I think i can remember
how to get there.
Wait, bette. This guy sounds
dangerous. I don't think you should go.
Well, i'll wait in the car.
I can point him out to you.
He's over there,
sitting down.
I saw him earlier.
He was running away
from the bus.
Tommy!
It's all right.
I just want to talk.
Tommy, it's okay.
Stay here!
Tommy!
- Don't be afraid!
- Get away from me!
It'll be okay, tommy.
I promise.
No! No!
No, you're lying!
Just be calm, all right? There's no
reason for anyone to get hurt.
Get away from me!
Bette, stay back.
It could be dangerous.
How could you
do this to me?!
Just stay away
from me, okay?!
Tommy!
He was scared, lois.
I don't think
he meant to hurt anyone.
He just couldn't control
his powers.
He blew up a bus, clark,
almost killed a lot of people.
I'd say
this was textbook karma.
Thanks.
Hey, you didn't tell me
that you were recording that.
Don't get your tights
in a twist, smallville.
I'll just refer to you
as "sources say."
Besides, if i'm gonna write
"tommy was a human bomb,"
I need scientific proof.
We could check
the autopsy report,
See how much meteor rock
was in his system.
The coroner won't release it if it's part
of an on going investigation.
But i bet we could find a copy
lying around the hospital.
By "find,"
i'm assuming you mean "steal."
Rule number three... do whatever
it takes to get the story.
You really should be
writing these down.
Lois, be careful. There's some lines
you shouldn't cross.
The only line
i'm worried about is a byline.
And so should you, clark.
We're in this together.
You want to share a byline
with me?
Oh, god, no.
But i got you the obit.
Tommy's obituary?
Absolutely. You helped
break the story,
So you get to commemorate
the kid in 10 lines or less.
Don't be so squeamish. Most of us
got started writing want ads.
You know what there was a time
when i would have killed for an obit.
Are you coming?
Shoot.
You know, if you just reach
a little bit higher,
You'd definitely need
an ambulance.
Guess i'm lucky there's
a paramedic in the building.
Yeah, well, you asked me
to bring over this application.
Gimme.
Oh, i did talk
to my friend.
And she says that there's a spot
open at the home for bette.
That's great!
She could really use
some good news right now.
Her day got even worse
a little while ago,
And she needed some space,
so i came here.
Thank you.
At least she had a place
to stay, thanks to you.
Thanks.
Isis foundation. So, what...
Adopt a pyramid, save a sphinx,
that kind of thing?
Cute.
Uh, actually, it's more like
a counseling center.
I'm housesitting for a friend of mine
till she finds someone to take it over.
I'm surprised i haven't heard of it.
The hospital sends out updates
On all the mental-Health
facilities.
Well... she has
very specific clients...
People with special skills
that are sometimes
A little dangerous.
What, you mean like...
meteor types?
I drive an ambulance in metropolis, chloe.
I've seen a lot of things...
At least enough to know
that they could use the help.
Have you ever thought
about helping them?
No, i don't...
I saw you with bette today.
You cared enough to take her
under your wing. That's rare.
And think how hard it must be
for these meteor people
To find someone
they can trust.
But am i
streetwise enough?
Okay, forget
what i said earlier.
I can come off
a little strong.
It's okay. At least now i
understand where it comes from.
Understand how?
Well, i googled you.
And i read an interview
that you gave
About running away
from foster homes as a kid.
You researched me?
Well, you know, i always
kind of wanted my own stalker.
No.
It isn't like that, davis.
It's just that... no, really,
i used to be a reporter,
And so i have a serious...
curiosity complex.
And i'm engaged.
You're the first person
i've told about that.
Well, um,
congratulations.
That's... a very unique
engagement ring.
Uh, well, you know,
it's the story behind the ring
That really
makes it special.
I went away for a little while,
and he never gave up on me.
Well, chloe, i grew up hearing
a lot of four-Letter words,
And "love" wasn't exactly
one of them.
If you found it,
real love,
Hold on to it.
And if anyone tells you that's a cliché,
i'll personally kick their ass.
Did you find her?
She's gone off the grid
again.
Don't come back
until you do.
- Is there something else?
- The girl's dangerous.
You tried to approach her
on the bus, and she blew it up.
Mr. Luthor would have had us
terminate the problem on-Site.
I'm your boss now.
And since
we've never worked together,
I can't trust that you'll see
this through to my satisfaction.
Bring her here.
I'll handle her.
End of story.
Lois, you can't just walk in
and steal a file.
It's a crime.
You'll go to prison.
I have a plan, clark.
Would you like to share it?
'Cause i'm having doubts.
When in doubt...
Charge it.
City hall... 13th precinct...
15th precinct...
Metropolis general.
If i could just get mileage points
on these things, i'd see the world.
Cover me, smallville.
Uh, you know, patients are
on an entirely different floor.
You know, i thought i got off
the elevator a little early.
Wait. You're one of the rescue workers
from the bus, right?
I thought
i recognized you.
For a guy without a uniform,
you helped a lot of people.
Oh, i didn't do anything.
I mean,
you're the real hero.
You help people
for a living.
I'm clark kent.
Davis bloome.
I met your fiancée.
Clark, congratulations.
She's a real catch.
I'm getting married?
Well, i thought that... 'cause
i saw you and chloe together,
And you seemed pretty close.
When she said she was engaged...
Chloe's engaged?
Oh, man. Okay, my brain's
gone completely d.O.A.
Clark, she said
she hadn't told anyone yet.
Do me a favor.
Don't tell her i said anything.
I won't reveal my source.
Hey, bette!
Davis, the paramedic
we met on the street,
Came by
with the paperwork.
His friends
want to meet you.
Change of plan, chloe.
I'm leaving metropolis.
Don't you think that
you should read this first?
I mean, this place
sounds really great.
Maybe it is,
but this city's gone sour...
Like, way past
its shelf life.
I have to go.
Look, i know what happened
with tommy was awful,
But running away
is not the answer.
Besides, it's not safe out there
for you by yourself.
You think the streets
are dangerous?
Try a locked door with
someone else holding the key.
- No, thanks.
- They're not gonna lock you in.
Look, tell you what...
i'll call them for you.
Chloe, stop.
I don't need a den mother,
and i won't go see those people.
Then they'll come here
to see you.
You're not listening
to me!
I'm just trying
to help you, bette.
I wish you hadn't
made me do that.
There's nothing in here
about a meteor infection.
Here.
Let me take a look.
Knock yourself out.
I'm not sure we're
on the right track, lois.
Tommy's death
seems suspicious.
Of course
it's suspicious.
The guy blew himself up just by
rubbing his hands together
Or wrinkling his nose
or whatever he did.
They didn't find
any meteor rock in his system,
But they did find metal shrapnel
from the barrels.
Lois, if tommy's responsible
for the blast,
Then the barrels would have
blown away from him,
Not into him, right?
Don't clear his name
just yet, sherlock.
That kid was dangerous,
a real live wire.
Check his rap sheet
at the back.
Armed robbery, b&e,
and carjacking.
Basically, that firecracker was
a major menace to metropolis.
But there's no mention
of explosives in any of these crimes, lois.
If you were a criminal
with these abilities,
wouldn't you use them?
Well, if tommy didn't
kill himself, then who did?
Bette claimed that tommy
blew up the bus.
But she was there
for both of the blasts.
Oh, my god. My cousin's
babysitting psycho spice.
Clark, what if...
Oh, come on.
Believe me,
i understand.
It can be tough
to control your powers
When you're angry
or afraid...
Like on the bus
or...with tommy.
Those weren't accidents!
I knew what i was doing!
There are some bad people
chasing me.
They cornered me on the bus.
I had to fight back.
So you set up tommy
to take the blame?
Bette...
You killed him.
He helped them find me.
Three years ago,
Some corporate types locked me
in their private prison.
It was a nightmare.
They ran tests on me every day.
Last week, something happened,
and we were all let go.
They tagged us
on the way out.
I ran before they could
do it to me.
This place... were there lots
of people there with powers?
Yeah.
I told tommy
all about it.
And you know what he did?
He sold me out.
He led them
straight to me.
He got
what he deserved.
The prison was in montana,
wasn't it?
Black creek?
How did you know that?
Because i was there.
I had a meteor power, too.
I could heal people.
I know
how awful it was there.
Then you know i had to do
whatever it took to get away.
They had me
backed into a corner.
No matter what they do to you,
bette, you don't kill people.
Sometimes
i don't have a choice!
Chloe, i'm sorry,
But i can't risk you
turning on me, too.
Goodbye, chloe!
No!
Stay away from me!
I'll hurt you!
No. You won't.
You're not afraid of me?
No.
I just want to help you.
After everything
i've done,
Why would you want to help
a monster like me?
Because you're not
a monster.
You've just been led
down the wrong path.
Whenever people find out
about me,
They get afraid
and they try to hurt me.
So i have to lie.
I have to hide what i am.
You don't have to anymore.
Not from me.
We all have something
we think we need to hide.
It's hard.
But it does get better.
It's a good thing
you called lois
And told her
you were okay.
She was about to call out
the national guard.
Bette almost killed me,
clark.
Chloe, there's no way
you could have known
how dangerous she was.
Her power was hidden.
Some sort of
high-Frequency energy blast?
She fooled everyone.
That's because
she didn't trust anyone.
I mean, i was only in that cell
for a few weeks.
I can't imagine being in there
for three years.
Hopefully, she'll find the help
she needs at belle reve.
Yeah, i seriously doubt
that being locked away
In another cell
is gonna do any good.
Do you think
if you knew her sooner,
You could have helped her
deal with her power?
Chloe, sometimes people
who need help the most
Are the ones
who push it away the hardest.
Which is why someone
should be talking to
them from day one.
Looking for this?
I found it downstairs.
You must have lost it
when bette was chasing you.
Is there anything
you want to tell me?
I was...
On my over here this morning
to tell you, but...
How did you find out?
Did jimmy call you?
Well,
it's rule number... 11...
Always protect
your source.
But i would like
the whole story.
How long
have you been engaged?
A week.
I said "yes" the night
i came back from montana.
You could have called...
anytime.
It's just that...
We've been friends
for such a long time.
We're more
than just friends, chloe.
When jimmy and i
get married,
Things will
probably change...
Between us, i mean.
And i don't know if i'm ready
for that just yet.
Are you?
I know that your happiness
Is one of the most important
things in the world to me...
And that you and jimmy will have
a wonderful life together.
Don't worry
about anything else.
Hello, bette.
You should have died
on that bus.
The last time we met,
things did get a little fiery.
Lucky for me, i ducked.
So, they're taking you
to belle reve.
I'm sure after a few years
of good behavior,
They'll let you
see the sun again.
Or you could come
with me.
I'd rather
be a prisoner there
Than your lab rat
in montana.
Go push your cheese
somewhere else.
I didn't build
that place, bette.
And after i heard about
all the terrible things
happening there,
I closed it down.
I tried to tell you.
If you shut down
the thunderdome,
Then why are you still
coming after me?
Because you're
a very powerful person.
And i think
it's about time
The world started
treating you accordingly.
Don't you?
Listening.
I want to introduce you...
to some people like you.
A sort of team.
But only if you want.
A team?
Take a look at my file, lady.
I don't play well
with others.
I think once you meet everyone,
you may finally feel like you it in.
I remember what it was like
to be your age...
Alone...
Angry...
Trapped.
The injustice of it all.
I can help, bette.
A team is only as good
as its weakest link.
And look what happened to me
on the bus.
Why scout out somebody
Who's just gonna choke
on their own smoke?
Don't be so hard
on yourself.
We'll make a hero
out of you yet.
Looking good, smallville.
Clothes make the man who helped
me make the front page.
Wow. Try to hold back
the journalistic fervor.
I'm glad you got
your story, lois,
But it took a few more turns
than i would have liked.
So did you, houdini. You're there one minute,
gone the next.
We were standing
next to an elevator.
I don't know why
you had to take the stairs.
Well, i'm sorry
that you can't keep up.
The important thing is
That chloe figured it out
on her own and she's okay.
Yeah, tell me about it.
If she hadn't defused
little miss land mine,
We'd be fitting her for a coffin
instead of a wedding dress.
When did you hear
about the wedding?
She just called.
I can't believe
my cousin is getting married.
To jimmy olsen.
They're in love, lois.
You should be happy for them.
Well, at least
the rest of us have work.
Here. I finished
proofing the obit.
Wow, lois.
Don't hold anything back.
Those aren't notes
of discouragement.
They're notes
of encouragement.
You've got talent,
smallville.
What?
Look, when i first srted out
at the inquisitor,
All i cared about was
getting the best stories
on the front page.
Well, it seems like
a dream come true.
Sure, but sitting here now
with you,
I think i'm more proud
that we uncovered the truth
Than i am
over having a headline.
Thanks for helping me
break the story, clark.
Keep up the good work.
You've got a long career ahead
of you at the daily planet.
Hey, this is davis.
Leave me your story.
I'll call you back.
Hi, davis.
It's chloe sullivan.
I, uh, i just wanted
to call and say thanks
For helping out with bette.
It's too bad that
that didn't, uh, work out.
But i also wanted
to let you know
That i've decided
to reopen the isis foundation,
And a few things that you said
helped me make that decision.
So... thanks.
Okay, well...
Stay safe out there.
Take care.
For seriessub.Com