Previously on Smallville...
There are aliens among us.
If you don't stand with us,
you stand against us
it's time for you to pick a side.
There's only one way
to leave Checkmate.
I finished tracing the
nber of our rogue blur.
It was Zod.
You lied about having powers.
How'd you get them?
From your blood.
Your father left the book
of Rau on this Earth.
And what with all of this there is
no limit to what we can achieve.
Don't act like there isn't some
agenda you're not telling me about.
If it wasn't for Zod,
I wouldn't be alive today.
Let's just say I know him
better than you think.
A group of your people are
looking to a new leader ...
The time has come to
share in your birthright.
I know what I have to do.
Don't tell me you forgot
about your favorite customer.
I thought you forgot about me.
You're late.
I'll have the usual, please?
- All I got left is strong and burnt.
- As long as it's hot.
I've been meaning to ask what kind
of a job has a pretty young lady
working all night, every night?
Actually, I work for a
nonprofit organization.
We help people in need.
Trying to save the world?
All night, every night.
Verify.
Chloe Sullivan. Password 051409.
Vocal and bio analysis confirmed.
Welcome to Watchtower, ms. Sullivan.
Ready to save the world from itself?
How did you find out my sceret?
Oliver's voice wavered
when I told him that
Watchtower had been kidnapped.
And I've seen the
way he looks at you.
It's the little things a
girl tends to notice.
And yet you somehow
missed an unloaded gun.
Watchtower safety compromised.
Initiating lockdown.
It's in your best interest to
get these doors open now.
Securise breach. Access denied.
We're not going anywhere.
Watchtower's in control now.
Smallville - 9x19 - Sacrifice
Synchro: Flolo
SeriesSub.com/Sous-Titres. Eu
I let myself in.
Terrific. You hop up to the helipad
or just superspeed past security?
I used the elevator.
How human of you.
You're obviously not
on patrol tonight. What's going on?
I need to find Zod.
Chloe, she's got this
really big building
filled with a lot of expensive
stuff I paid a lot of money for.
- She could help you out with that.
- The last thing that we need
is to have a weapon like Watchtower
fall into the wrong hands.
I want to keep Chloe out
of the line of fire.
I figured you'd agree with that.
"Keep Chloe out of the line of
fire." What the hell's going on?
He went after Lois.
He pretended to be The Blur,
and he put her in danger.
I think it's time we
take off the gloves.
I need you on this but I can't have you
starting a fight with Zod
- if I'm trying to keep the peace.
- You like to see the goodness
in everyone but you know what this
guy's capable of?
And I know what you're capable of.
I understand how you feel.
Don't think I'm not angry, too.
I can't have you firing off the first shot
and threatening everything I've worked for.
These are my people that
we're talking about.
My first real chance to
have a kryptonian family here on Earth.
And we need to find Zod and
confront him my way.
Yeah, all right, man,
I got your back.
Let's suit up. Check the mansion.
Before Tess went off the grid,
she got close to Zod.
She may have left behind some intel.
I have another lead I want
to run down on my own.
You know, those Kandorians...
they're not the only
family you have here.
In the event that I die of starvation
or say a ricocheting bullet
do you mind telling me
how you got in here?
You're sloppy.
I've got thousands of
samples of your DNA
from all the times
you've spied on me.
It's called a DNA cloak.
Aren't you fancy?
Getting in doesn't really seem to
be our issue right now.
- How the hell do we get out of here?
- Short answer. It's impossible.
When Checkmate kidnapped me,
I upgraded Watchtower's security
to contain intruders like you.
The only problem is,
I was supposed to be on the outside.
Seriously?
The lockdown prevents any
signals from getting in or out.
Treat confirmation still active.
Watchtower didn't react
because you attacked me.
We're on lockdown because some hacking
transmitter was detected.
The initial signal managed to pirate some
data before my firewall blocked it and
the thing is still alive. It's trying
to break through another firewall.
It's trying to give away our location.
What did you bring in here?
Nothing. All I wanted to do
was erase any info
you had on the Kandorians,
not reroute it.
You were the Kandorians' lapdog,
but I didn't realize you were Zod's
little bitch, too. All right, look.
If you're not behind this, there's
only one other group I can think of
that wants Watchtower this badly.
The signal's scrambled,
Agent Campbell.
Watchtower threw up some
kind of halo of interference
as soon as the tracker went live.
Waller coming online.
We're trying to sort out the data we siphoned
from Watchtower before they blocked us.
What is your status?
We've narrowed the location
within a 20-block radius.
Good. We can't afford to
make a mistake
with the red queen so close.
Don't make me regret putting
my little white knight back in play.
There's no need to worry.
We're gonna have Watchtower
in Checkmate's hands by dawn.
Godspeed, Agent Campbell.
Waller out.
You heard the wall, gentlemen.
Let's show Mercer how we feel about
a little thing called treason.
If I was hiding a
transmitting tracking device,
I would want to make it
as unassuming as possible.
Which means I can probably
count this out.
Fever-colored lipstick? Really?
I was gonna go with plain Jane but you
seem to have that market cornered.
Really, how much could have been
leaked in the blink of an eye?
Watchtower downloads what amounts to the
Library of Congress
every three seconds, which mean half
that time Checkmate could have attained
my entire team's database.
And all of your files
on the Kandorians.
Firewall breach.
Cluster 4458.
Now, if it wasn't planted in
your things, it must be on you.
What?
This is ridiculous, okay?
It's in your body,
just beneath your skin.
Get it out of me, now.
Oh, my God.
It moved.
When it feels threatened,
it burrows deeper into the host.
We'll never get it out now.
How did you know that?
It's a Checkmate device.
A mechanical parasite powered
by the host's biorhythms.
You know what they say.
You lie down with dogs,
you end up with fleas.
Laugh it up but when Checkmate finds us,
we'll both be dead.
I'm glad you found a way to preserve our
culture here on earth.
I wish everyone saw it that way.
Zod disappeared and took the
rest of our people with him.
I don't understand. I thought all of
you had found a new life here on Earth.
We were wrong to follow you, Kal-El.
When we did what you asked
and tried to assimilate with the humans,
we were left behind.
We're gathered here waiting for
Zod's return to ask his forgiveness.
I'm sorry, Faora.
I never meant to divide our people,
- but you cannot realign with Zod.
- You've never trusted him.
All Zod wanted was to give us power
so we could protect ourselves.
Zod already has powers.
He's had them for weeks.
Faora, there's something
you need to see.
You are unmistakably the one
they call Green Arrow...
A rebel with many causes.
I'm glad to know my reputation
still precedes me. You must be Zod.
Soldier with no army.
I see my reputation
precedes me, too.
I'm guessing by the looks of him,
we're not the only
ones waiting for Tess.
Oh, yeah, "him."
I find it disgusting how quickly
you humans can betray your own.
Now, that one...
he ave up all sorts
of useful information before he died,
about something your
government called Checkmate...
and about who they're after.
Not too long ago, a gift-wrapped me
was at the top of that wish list.
And now Tess is.
Checkmate is using her to get to us,
hunting us to the death.
Having been on the receiving end
of their terrorist schemes...
why don't you join me
against our common enemy?
I'm flattered but if I let you
go after Checkmate,
you'll start world war III.
It's not an option.
Your conviction is admirable.
But you can't possibly think
you're faster than me.
I've always been taught to
favor accuracy over speed.
Bull's-eye.
Air supply terminated.
We got three minutes of air left.
You think Checkmate will
find us before then?
Asphyxiation or a firing squad.
Damned if we do, damned if we don't.
Just damned.
I just wanted to save the world.
That's funny.
Last time I checked, you were just
trying to get rid of everyone in it.
Paint my ideals however you want,
but you and yours don't trust
people any more than I do.
This entire building was programmed
to prevent anyone from
getting close to you.
Yeah, I guess I lost
my faith in people a long time ago, too.
That's why you won't let
Oliver get close to you.
And why I can't blame him
when he eventually leaves.
He's not gonna leave you.
With you, he has a purpose
I wish I could have given him that.
And it kills me...
'cause you have everything
right in front of you...
and you can't even see it.
Final breach imminent.
They broke through
the final firewall.
Checkmate's gonna
be here any minute.
As long as they torture
us with the A.C. on, I'll die happy.
Cold.
Watchtower's cooling system
uses a special mix of
liquid helium and nitrogen.
Cold enough to shatter steel.
What are you waiting for?
If I pull these tanks,
then the mainframe melts.
All my work, Watchtower is gone.
If you don't, we die.
Critical oxygen level.
Warning... temperature variation
detected.
System failure imminent.
They're back on the grid.
Safeties off, gentlemen.
Shoot to kill.
He destroyed Krypton.
My father sent those
messages here to Earth
to help me stop history
from repeating itself.
I trusted Zod, too. That's why
I didn't tell you any of this sooner.
The circumstances may be different
but Zod cannot be trusted.
On Krypton, he destroyed
that planet to prove a point.
We can't let hm do the
same thing here.
I'd hoped what Zod had given
me would reunite our people.
What he gave you?
At the ceremony,
your sister was protecting you.
You're pregnant.
And Zod's the father?
This baby is proof that you
can still have a life here...
Apart from Zod, without powers.
Faora...
Krypton lives on through you.
Why don't you just murder me now?
Isn't that what your race does?
Sometimes.
And I would love to, believe me.
But, although inconvenient
and a lot less fun.
I made a commitment to Clark to
help save the world peacefully.
Now, that said,
you bulldoze me again,
I might have a change of heart.
Zod's been looking for something
ever since we arrived.
The book of Rau.
Zod said the book of Rau
was some sort of kryptonian bible.
It's so much more than that.
It wields great power.
And if Zod were to get
his hands on it...
then who knows what he would do?
Oliver, what's wrong?
I found what we're looking for.
I'll give you a little hint.
- It's bigger than a breadbox.
- Zod?
I'll be right there.
Why don't you take your sweet time?
Because I have everything under...
control.
No.
- Change of plans, agent Campbell.
- Change of plans?
We just made contact
with Mercer's tracker.
I don't care about Mercer
or Watchtower.
We decrypted the data.
We found the aliens.
Checkmate is going to
stop this war before it gets started.
Waller out.
We've got our 20.
Now lock her down. I'm not losing her.
Sir, you heard Waller.
We have our orders.
I just spent the last
five months in recovery
from what Mercer did to me.
Now, this op
is over when I
say it's over, understood?
I don't get it.
You're in the clear.
We escape before Checkmate got
a hit on Watchtower's address.
That doesn't make you any
less of a liability.
You still know the secret identities
of all my most valuable players.
There's no sense in both
of us getting captured.
I'm not letting you out of my sight
until we get rid of
your little friend.
I know how much I am asking of
you in standing against Zod.
I will not let my child be
raised under a tyrant's rule.
We cannot let our future be
guided by a tyrant's hand.
Our past ended in war.
Let our future begin with peace.
Enough!
You heard her.
Enough's enough.
The leader comes with me.
We have a few things to discuss.
Dispose of the rest.
I'll have Dr.
Hamilton check in with you
once we get him into surgery
and assess the damage.
Checkmate's after the Kandorians.
Only you can save your people.
Please.
Our people have done nothing.
Where are you taking us?
- Vala, where's your sister?
- They took her.
Atropine?
What the hell are you
gonna do with that?
There's no time. Look.
If you're right and that transmitter's
powered by your biorhythms,
then the only way that I can turn
it off is to stop your heart.
I have to kill you, Tess.
And this is the only way
I'm gonna bring you back.
You're asking for a pretty
big leap of faith here.
You're gonna have to trust me.
You ready?
Do it.
The signal just went dead.
Let's move.
Keep looking.
You bitch.
I really didn't think you'd do it.
Bring me back.
Neither dd I.
Just for the record,
I just saved your ass.
You say anything about
me or mine to anyone,
next time you won't wake up.
You understand?
Guess you'll have to trust me.
Our field offices were just leveled
by the one you call Zod.
We knew nothing about this.
Zod is acting alone.
We stand part. We only want peace.
Dozens of my agents are dead.
We are way past peace.
Then we will help you stop him.
Defecting means
betraying your own kind.
I'm only betraying one.
Checkmate's actions demands justice.
Murder isn't justice.
Seems like a lifetime ago when I...
pulled you out of that rubble,
doesn't it.
The Siege of Argo.
There were many losses that day.
Not for me.
Because I found a young and...
beautiful cadet who would
become my trusted right hand.
You were so brave
in the face of death
I knew then that you
would be a true partner.
I've trusted you...
for so very long.
Depended on you...
across time and space.
But in your eyes,
I just see contempt.
I see betrayal.
Now, why would you
turn your back on me?
I shared my bed with you.
I didn't turn my back on you.
You turned your back on us
when our only crime was trying to forge
a life for ourselves on this planet.
If I ever learned...
that insurrection had
spread across my ranks,
if I ever discovered that my men
had aligned themselves against me,
I would raze this planet.
I would burn it to the ground
till the last ember went
cold beneath my boot!
Now only
i will lead us to the next age.
All will follow Zod.
You already sacrificed
one world for your ego.
You know nothing of sacrifice.
I know more than you ever will.
Kneel.
Never.
I think I found a way to
prioritize our satellites
to get a location on Mercer
when she left the hospital.
Zod destroyed the Metropolis field
office and six more went dark.
The black king is still missing,
and we're at war. Contact the U.N.
We have to regroup
before they strike again.
Run.
Please tell me you found
that z-branding bastard
so we can slap him back
across the universe.
Zod's on the move, there's no sign of
Faora or the Kandorians.
Maybe if I can reach the others,
I can talk some sense into them.
We may be too late for that.
That's the Castle.
Oh, God.
Zod's attacked Checkmate.
Oliver was personal.
With this, Zod just declared war.
You're not gonna like where
he's gathering his troops.
My eye in the sky above
the fortress is picking up movement.
What was to be the first
son of Kandor is no more.
Now we, the last sons and
daughters of Krypton,
have no choice but to
preserve our birthright.
The humans killed the
mother of my unborn child...
the mother of your future!
That's a lie.
The last time that I saw Faora,
she was alive.
And she was alone...
with Zod.
Why should they believe you?
This traitor...
saved the life of the woman
who held you hostage,
the woman who wanted to dissect you,
who wanted to torture you...
murder you.
Vala...
If there's anyone who really
knows what your sister wanted, it's you.
It was peace, Vala.
She wanted peace.
No.
Zod's right.
The humans will never
allow Kandor peace.
They will hunt us to the last man.
But they will fail,
for we shall never be defeated.
We will follow general Zod
to the ends of this earth.
Krypton will rise again.
And all humankind
will kneel before Zod.
I'll never let that happen!
You won't be able to stop us.
SeriesSub.com/Sous-Titres. Eu