Previously on Smallville...
You're too late, Kal-El.
Lana?
Miss Lang had a full recovery.
Where is she?
Oh, she's already checked out,
but she wanted me to give you this.
But I knew that if I looked into your
eyes, I'd never be able to say it.
If I ever discovered that someone withheld
information that could help me find Lex,
I'd be forced to respond accordingly.
Nobody questions my loyalty.
LUTHORCORP EXEC MISSING
I can't believe it!
Lana, you're back!
Why are you staying?
Leaving is harder
than I thought it would be.
You still haven't told him
the reasons why you disappeared...
and what you plan
on doing next.
Lex saved my life.
I owe him everything.
This is how a Luthor rewards
that kind of loyalty.
You've been Lex's eyes and ears
for quite some time.
I've done everything.
But not anymore.
Goodbye, Lex.
What if the rest of the world
didn't have to come first?
- The world needs you, Clark.
- What about what we need?
Sir, it's not too late
to suspend the procedure.
Our orders
are to move forward.
At what cost?
I know Mr. Luthor wants to get back
on his feet as soon as possible,
but we are nowhere near ready
to attempt this on a human being.
The studies on mice
have barely even started.
It doesn't matter. Mr. Luthor wants us to
proceed, and that's what we're going to do.
Where are we
with the molecular transfusion?
- Prepared for absorption.
- And the subject?
Vitals normal. We're all set.
Begin the transdermal evisceration.
Stand by.
Energizing!
"Somebody save me"
"Let your warm hands
break right through me"
"Somebody save me"
"I don't care how you do it"
"Just save me, save me"
"Come on"
"I've been waiting for you"
"I've made this whole world shine for you"
"Just save me, save me"
"Come on"
SMALLVILLE 8x13 "POWER"
Subtitles SubXpacio
We thought that we were
meant to be together, Clark.
But the truth is,
we were fooling ourselves.
I need you...
but the world needs you more.
And as long as I'm in your
life, I am holding you back.
Please, don't...
Clark...
you know you're bored when you resort
to watching a repeat of your breakup.
I needed to remind myself
that Lana left for a reason.
Did something happen
that made you suddenly forget?
Last night, we...
kind of kissed.
I know. It was a mistake.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Clark, you're acting like
you committed a crime.
Now, I'm not a lawyer,
but I really don't think...
that a little trip to first base
is exactly a felony.
But I'm digging up feelings
from the past that need to stay buried...
for both our sakes.
You know, you have an arsenal
of abilities at your disposal,
but suffocating feelings that want to come
up for air definitely isn't one of them.
Lana thought she was holding me back,
and you know what? She was right.
Look what happened after she left.
I got off the farm, I got a job,
I started using my abilities to help people
when they needed it the most.
Did you do that
because Lana left
or because you simply grew up and realized
what you wanted to do with your life?
Clark, maybe she isn't the liability
you're making her out to be.
How does she feel about it?
It's on that disk.
She doesn't want to be together.
She made that disk seven months
ago, Clark. People change.
You certainly did.
Look, stop playing the guessing
game and talk to her.
She's probably
at my apartment right now.
Lana?
Clark.
I didn't know it was you.
I didn't realize that breaking and
entering was one of your hobbies.
The damage was done when I got here.
Look, I was worried about Lana,
and I came to warn her, but...
I was obviously too late.
Warn her about what?
It seems that she's been...
poking around some classified
LuthorCorp technology.
The last time I checked, you
were in charge of LuthorCorp.
Everything but the nanotechnology
dedicated to sustaining Lex's life.
The bear may be hibernating,
but that does not mean...
that he's gonna sit around
and let his honey get stolen.
You think Lex is behind
what happened to Lana?
I don't think, Clark. I know.
And I am really concerned for her.
Since when did you and Lana
become close friends?
I will forever be grateful to her.
Lana's responsible for finally showing
me the monster that Lex really is.
The least that I can do
is repay the favor.
I knew Lex was still alive.
I had no idea he was capable of
kidnapping Lana from a distance.
It wouldn't be the first time
he's abducted her from afar.
She didn't tell you.
Tell me what?
Do you remember that DVD
she made for you last spring?
Did you ever wonder how Lana got
her hands on a video camera...
right after she awoke
from a deep coma?
As long as I'm in your life,
I'm holding you back.
Please, for both of us,
don't come looking for me.
I love you, Clark...
more than you will ever know.
Now let me go.
It's for your own protection, ma'am.
Is that what Lex told you?
You've been in a coma
for the past three months.
We're here to make sure
you stay safe.
No! No!
No!
Get her in the van.
I'll meet you at the compound.
That disk was a lie.
Lana never wanted to leave.
She left because
she was escaping from you!
- Clark.
- You're no better than Lex.
If I had known what I know now,
I would have never been part of it.
Lex convinced us
it was for her own good.
How nice of him
to kidnap her.
Lex also said that she was
in that asylum because of you...
that your relationship was so dysfunctional
you were constantly hurting her.
Where are you taking me?
To a place where you'll be protected.
Here.
Lex has been watching me, hasn't he?
Waiting for me to wake up
so he can kidnap me.
Mr. Luthor just wants to help you.
I'm not feeling very well.
You're dehydrated.
You should drink that.
No, I think I'm gonna throw up.
Here.
Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Just calm down!
Leave the keys in the ignition
and get out of the van. Now!
The thugs that Lex used...
he could've used them again.
What are their names?
What are their names?!
They're both dead.
The people Lex employs now
are brand-new,
without any ties to his past.
What did you got there, Clark?
I'm not sure what it is.
It doesn't seem like Lana's taste.
It's not.
Have you seen this before?
My strategic advisor, Carter Bowfry...
it's his.
What did you do with Lana?
- I don't know who you're talking about.
- Don't lie to me!
I found your medallion
in her apartment!
My medallion is right here.
They're exactly the same.
How do you know Lana?
Son, I suggest
you back down right now.
Lana has been kidnapped.
Look, if anything you know
may help me find her, please...
you can trust me.
You must be Clark.
How do you know my name?
I gave Lana that medallion
last spring in Edge City.
I don't know how she
tracked me down, but she did.
Money means nothing to me.
I'll pay you whatever you want.
I don't need your dollars, ma'am.
I'm just a retired teacher
living off his pension.
A teacher who trained
green berets and navy seals...
to withstand extreme pain and torture.
I've done my homework.
I need your help.
What I have to teach,
you're not ready to learn.
You'd be surprised.
Please, just give me a chance.
Well, you're not a soldier, and you're
definitely not a government agent,
so why are you here?
I want to be invincible.
Well, good for you.
Look... I'm all for girl power,
but you're gonna have to go find
yours on your own, okay, sweetheart?
I'm not asking you,
I'm telling you.
If you help me, I promise
you'll be helping the world.
You were barely under.
It's too cold.
You're weaker than I thought.
Yeah, well, life hasn't exactly
been a walk in the park lately.
Oh, poor, poor, pitiful you.
How long have you been
feeling sorry for yourself?
Let me guess.
Your entire life.
- You tortured her?!
- I trained her.
- That's how she came back stronger.
- She's always been strong.
Now she's missing because of you.
All I did was help her get over the
one thing that was holding her back.
- What are you waiting for?
- Just not used to scorching myself.
Get used to it.
No fear, no pain.
I can't.
It's not fear
that's stopping you, is it?
You're holding on to something...
or someone.
Do you see anyone else here?
Oh, I can feel him.
So can you.
As long as you're trying
to be someone you're not,
you are gonna be vulnerable.
You are gonna feel the pain.
What's the name?
His name's Clark.
And if I had an ounce of his strength...
I'm not training you
to be like someone else.
I'm training you
to be Lana Lang,
to rise from the ashes
of your previous life,
stronger, more powerful...
fearless.
It's time to rise.
You don't look ready for class.
Carter, I have learned
so much from you,
but what I need,
I- I can't get it here.
What you need are skills, Lana...
maturity.
I need power.
And you'll have it.
But it just doesn't happen overnight.
I've had it before...
skills and abilities
beyond what you can imagine.
But I wasn't ready for them
physically, mentally, or emotionally.
And now, thanks to you, I am.
This thirst for power, Lana...
I've seen it before.
Most of the time,
it doesn't have a happy ending.
Well...
before you fly off
to change the world...
- I've got something for you.
- I don't deserve it.
Take this so you'll always remember.
As you rise higher and higher,
never look down.
After Edge City, where'd she go?
Metropolis.
She was so full of hope.
Wanted to imprint this stamp
of positivity on the world.
I couldn't let anything
happen to her.
After all the death and destruction
I've been responsible for,
Lana was my chance at redemption,
so I tracked her down.
When you found her,
what was she doing?
Investigating LuthorCorp.
I told her to put it in the past,
but she wouldn't listen to me.
So I joined her cause.
Keep an eye on her. And I
got this job on the inside,
feeding Lana information
while I advised Tess Mercer...
on defense-contract strategies.
Did Lana contact anyone else
when she was in Metropolis?
A blond woman.
They went to high school
together in Smallville.
- Chloe?
- Sullivan.
Sir, she's barely alive.
It's the only way to apply the nanites.
Begin the grafting.
Applying the Prometheus layer.
The cloak-and-dagger existence
suits you well, Regan.
So, how's your new career,
breaking and entering?
Did you find what you were looking
for in Lana Lang's apartment?
Still looking, just like you.
Only I'm trying to find the
technology to keep Lex alive,
not to destroy it.
The world already believes he's dead.
I'm just trying to make
a fantasy a reality.
You actually believe you can
declare Lex Luthor dead...
and not end up dead yourself?
You're a pretty pathetic
guard dog...
loyal to a master
that can't even feed himself.
Why don't you come
and work for me?
I'll give you more milk-bones
than Lex ever did.
I think I'd rather shovel cow dung.
Oh, you see, it's not really a choice.
Once you discover the Prometheus
technology, I want you to bring it to me.
I'm afraid that...
you're gonna be waiting
a long, long time.
Find me the Prometheus technology,
or I'll have to take it... by force.
Regeneration complete, Dr. Groll.
Pull her out and get her quarantined.
Clark, no more superscares, please.
I'm this close to a cardiac arrest.
Why didn't you tell me?
So now I'm keeping secrets
I didn't know I was keeping.
Lana.
How could you not tell me
you spoke to her?
Because she asked me
not to.
I have to respect that.
Now it looks like your respect
may have gotten her kidnapped.
What?
Chloe, if I'd have known
what she was doing,
I could have stopped her
before she got hurt.
I wasn't about to betray her trust, Clark,
just like I would never betray yours.
You of all people
should understand that.
This is different, Chloe.
I have abilities. I can take
care of myself. Lana can't.
Look, Chloe, all that matters
now is finding her.
Please, you have to tell me
everything she said to you.
Okay, first of all, just so you know,
she didn't come back to see me.
She was on a mission.
Am I hallucinating, or is that the
long-lost Lana Lang in front of me?
- Hi, Chloe.
- Hi!
Oh, my god, I thought I'd never
see you again. Now you're back.
Actually, I'm only here
for a short stay.
I am so impressed with what
you've done with Isis, Chloe.
You've turned my dinky little operation
into a place that really helps people.
I'm just carrying on
the torch you lit.
In other late-breaking news,
I'm getting married next month.
That is a huge headline.
I am so happy for you.
You two make a perfect couple.
Speaking of which,
does your short stay...
include a pit stop
at the Planet to see Clark?
Uh, not this time.
But I read about the red/blue blur
saving the citizens of Metropolis.
I've got to say that, when I saw that
article, it brought tears to my eyes.
I am so proud of him.
Lana...
I know
that you miss all of us,
but something tells me there's
more to your trip back home...
than simply checking in
with the old gang.
I actually came back here to
find out more about project Ares.
Project Ares... wasn't that Lex's scheme
to genetically enhance injured soldiers?
Using alien DNA.
Lana, this is all in the past.
Lex is out of your life now.
Why don't you just put this
behind you and move on?
I am moving on.
Really?
Because it seems to me like
you're not just playing with fire,
you're stepping
into a raging inferno.
- Clark should know about this.
- I plan on telling Clark...
when the time is right.
Chloe, I want you to promise me
that you won't say a word.
I can take care of myself now.
All I did was honor
my friend's secret.
And now I feel like
this is all my fault.
That must have been
the way she wanted it...
so she could do what she had to do
without anyone getting in her way...
especially me.
Did you check on project Ares
after she left?
Yeah, it turns out the project
was mothballed over a year ago,
even before Lex
went missing.
Tess Mercer told me Lana's been looking
into technology that could keep Lex alive.
She thinks that Lex abducted her.
Since when are you trusting what the
first lady of LuthorCorp has to say?
Since she came clean with me.
She told me when Lana made that
disk, she was being held at gunpoint...
by a team of Lex's men led by Tess.
Wait, Clark.
If Lana didn't make that disk on her own,
then why didn't she come home to you?
She was too busy
planning her revenge on Lex.
Chloe, I need to find Lana before
she does something she'll regret.
That's a ballsy move,
sitting in the boss's chair.
Either you have good news for me, or you
like to live dangerously close to the edge.
I guess it's the latter.
He did have good news
for you...
the address of the Prometheus lab.
Unfortunately, he told me first.
So working for Lex gives you
carte blanche to kill innocent people?
Innocent?
He worked for you, Tess.
Give a mid-level bureaucrat a little bit
of power, and it goes straight to his head.
You're the expert.
You know, I actually
used to be envious of you.
Of course, that was before
I found out Lex was using you...
as his eyes and ears.
I happen to have
my own eyes and ears,
hidden in the security cameras
in this office.
Not only did they record
your illuminating conversation...
with my security guard,
but also his tragic murder.
Yeah.
But that footage is nothing compared
to the memorable moments I saw.
Lex was nice enough to let me
catch some of your, uh...
highlights.
I'll make sure a few of them
make it into your obituary.
There's a classified LuthorCorp
project called Prometheus,
but now that I'm Brainiac-free, I
couldn't even begin to hack the firewall.
You said the first time
is radiator.
Yeah, I think so, but I don't know
what the building's heating system...
has to do with any of this.
Whoa.
Looks like Lana's got
her very own secret stash.
She obviously didn't want to leave
any of the good stuff on my gigabytes.
Why do I feel like
I'm cracking open her diary?
It might be the only way
we can save her, Clark.
- Who's this guy?
- Edward Groll.
He's been with LuthorCorp
since the first meteor shower.
If they gave out PHDs
in all things alien,
this guy
would definitely have one.
I know you were involved
with project Ares.
But more importantly, I found
out you designed Prometheus.
I want to commend you. That
is an amazing achievement.
You must be mistaken,
Mrs. Luthor.
It's Ms. Lang.
That will never change.
I promise, doctor, I don't intend
on destroying your technology.
I want to put it to good use.
I'm an academic. I hold the chair in
biophysics at Metropolis university.
Where you designed and built
a meta-dermal skin graft
that will not only sustain
Lex's health...
but will give him
superhuman abilities.
Superhuman abilities?
Have you taken up
reading comic books?
For someone intelligent enough...
to harness alien DNA
into the ultimate power suit,
you are dangerously naive.
What good will your technology
do in the hands of a madman?
You and I both know that Lex
is too dangerous to wear it.
But I can.
I'm sorry, Miss Lang. I don't
have time to discuss fictitious...
If Lex ever puts on that suit,
he will corrupt its power.
He will become a god among men,
and the world will never recover.
Do you want your legacy to be allowing
Lex Luthor to become the ultimate weapon?
Or do you want to be remembered
for saving people's lives?
For improving the human
condition all over the world.
I have a space in east metropolis...
in a warehouse on 95th and
Bristol. You can set up your lab.
It's not just me.
I work with a lab full of researchers.
They'd never allow it.
Tell them it was on Lex's orders...
that he wanted me to be the guinea pig.
It's not so far-fetched, is it?
I don't think
she was kidnapped, Clark.
Lana doesn't want to destroy
the technology.
She wants to use it
on herself.
Thank god.
Her blood pressure's rising.
For now.
The machines
are what's keeping her alive.
She's going to be fine.
She has to be.
Where's the Prometheus suit?
Stop!
Don't enter that chamber.
Any contaminant could kill her.
Her?
Lana.
It was Lex's orders.
Prometheus must be destroyed.
It's too late. You can't destroy
the suit without murdering her.
Lana Lang was born
to be a martyr.
No!
You will never be able
to help Lex Luthor again.
You find her before she finds me.
This woman is lethal.
Lana, you got to believe me,
I didn't know you were in there.
Yes, you did.
I'm not here to hurt you, Tess.
I'm here as your friend.
My BFF who tears open
my safe with her bare hands...
and burns
all of my research?
I think that you're stretching the
definition of friendship just a little bit.
I don't want you to make
the same mistake I did.
I know how much you want to get
revenge on Lex, and who can blame you?
I have felt that exact same rage.
He didn't implant a microchip
into your brain.
All that anger will lead you
down a long tunnel...
that you will never
find your way out of.
Yeah, that's a really
easy position to take...
when you're clad
in an invincible suit.
I didn't put the suit on
for protection.
I did it so that I could actually
do some good in the world.
You are an amazing woman, Tess.
But it's hard to see when
you're stuck in the dark shadow...
of an even darker man.
Why do you think I want Lex gone?
You may have gotten rid
of the microchip...
but every second
that you're consumed by hate...
is another second
Lex is still in control of you.
Don't be a victim anymore.
Kent.
What are you doing
rising before the roosters?
Couldn't sleep.
Clark.
Meet me up on the rooftop.
Lana!
I've been looking all over
for you. Are you okay?
I've never felt better,
Clark.
It's because you're wearing
that suit, Lana.
You have powers,
and the last time that happened,
it didn't end well.
I'm different now.
This time
I've prepared myself.
Those months that you were gone, why
didn't you tell me what you were doing?
You would have never
let me go through with it.
Because it's dangerous, Lana.
It's never been tested
on humans.
Give Lex credit
where credit is due.
When it comes
to all things scientific,
he's pulled off the impossible
on more than one occasion.
Clark, you don't
have to protect me anymore.
You don't have to
worry about me.
How can you say that, Lana?
We have no idea
what's gonna happen.
Exactly.
And that's why it's so important
to live in the present.
Whatever happened in the past
and whatever happens
in the future,
it doesn't matter.
It does matter, Lana.
It matters if you get hurt.
I know how much
you care about me.
You always have.
That's why when I came back
for Chloe's wedding, I...
I didn't think
we could be together.
Clark...
the last thing I wanted was to be
some distraction in your life.
You're not a distraction.
You never were.
I'm not anymore.
Clark, nothing can hurt me anymore.
You and I are equals now, and together,
we can help make
the world a better place.
Unless that's not
what you want.
No, Lana,
that's exactly what I want.
But it's a dream, Lana.
We both know dreams
normally don't come true.
There's never been
anything normal about us.
Subtitles subXpacio and TusSeries