I'm sure there were moments
when king arthur regretted
pulling the sword from the stone.
But he never gave up
his quest.
So why did you?
Or have you already
found the traveler
that you and the less fortunate
members of veritas were looking for?
The traveler.
Why doesn't it surprise me
that you've fallen
for patricia swann's
vid imagings?
I didn't imagine the deaths of virgil
swann or oliver queen's parents.
You think I can control the fate
of individuals? Oh, god.
You give me too much credit.
You certainly controlled mine.
It wasn't an accident
we were in smallville
the day of the meteor shower, was it?
The factory was just a cover.
You were really there
to meet this traveler
that veritas
wanted to protect.
I remember everything, dad.
those are the memories
of a small boy in shock
trying to cope with the trauma
of a meteor shower.
A trauma brought on
by my own father!
My life changed forever that day.
You sacrificed me
for the traveler.
why?
Who is it, dad?
Who is it?
Who is it?!
What if I told you now
that you are you traveler?
You're right. Your life
truly changed that day.
I told you in the helicopter that
you were destined for a great future.
That's why I've been so hard on you,
trained you so relentlessly.
Think, lex. Think.
You have survived
mortal injuries so many times.
How else can you explain it?
Because I was trained
never to accept defeat.
When I get my hands
on that box in zurich,
I have a feeling all
my questions will be answered.
I know how strong it is...
The attraction
of the dark power.
But it will destroy you.
I can't let you go down
that terrible path.
You must not open that box.
I can't open it...
Because
I need a second key.
Give it to me.
I've swept every possible place
you could have hidden it.
And I finally realized
there's only person
you would trust it with.
Yourself.
Lex, if you open that box,
if you get hold of that secret,
there will be no redemption for you.
No redemption. Ever.
I was raised
in your shadow.
Now you're gonna die in mine.
No one will even remember
your name.
Smallville 716
Transcript : swsub.com
Synchro : Flolo
For SeriesSub.com
i'm sorry, clark.
I traveled halfway
around the world via satellite.
There's no trace
of kara and brainiac.
I can't let lana sit
in that asylum in pain.
The only way to help her
is to find brainiac.
I've tapped every radar screen
known to mankind.
I mean, there's no bogey or blip
unaccounted for.
It's like they just flew off the map.
What about
brainiac's power sources?
Check the electrical grid
for any power surges again.
Stay focused, chloe.
Busy night out there.
What's going on?
Someone at luthorcorp just
jumped out their office window.
Rumor has it
it was lionel luthor.
Let's go.
I just talked to him.
You said you were  working down
the hall from your father tonight?
I heard him yell.
Then he was gone.
I know how difficult this
must be for you, Mr. Luthor,
but I need
a positive identification.
Whenever you're ready.
Yeah.
Thank you.
you killed him?
You killed dad?
Not that I want to
speak ill of the dead,
but lionel luthor left a lot
of damage in his wake, clark.
Remember he locked you
in a kryptonite box?
Lionel did a lot of things, chloe,
but he'd never commit suicide.
I don't know about that,
clark. He was beyond disturbed
- when he came to the daily planet today.
- Doesn't mean he'd take his own life.
He was pretty rattled
the last time I saw him, too.
He was desperate to give me
something... a locket.
What does a locket
have to do with
lionel luthor falling 40 stories
from his office window?
Mr. Luthor...
I just wanted to tell you how sorry
I was to hear about your father.
When I was a boy...
We took a trip together
to washington, d.c., just...
It was just the two of us.
I thought I was just tagging along
on another business trip, but...
... he wanted to show me
the air and space museum.
He knew I loved things
that could fly.
We were looking up
at the apollo 11 command module.
I couldn't believe
it went to the moon.
My father held my hand.
And he told me, "the right man
can make anything possible."
You have his locket.
How did you get him to...
Lionel was a cruel, sadistic man.
What are you suggesting?
No one will ever know, lex.
I promise you.
Where's the key?
It was empty.
My father must have given it
to someone.
I asked you
to keep an eye on him, gina.
Lionel stopped by the daily planet
before going to luthorcorp.
He was spotted
in the basement.
Get the helicopter ready.
Of course.
You killed dad
for a necklace?
You're not real.
He was mean sometimes,
but he loved us, lex.
Get out of my head.
Get out of my head!
You shouldn't
have done it!
I had no choice!
"for kal-el,
in the event of my death."
in my lifetime,
I've known many famous
and powerful men...
Presidents, sultans, kings....
And I believed that I was
superior to them all.
But I've come to know
the truth, kal-el.
My greatest accomplishment
is that I have dedicated myself
to protecting your life
and serving you.
For that, I am grateful.
But if you are reading this,
it means that I cannot protect you
any longer from a terrible truth.
Two lockets exist... two.
Each one has its own key.
These keys, used together,
unlock the secret
of controlling you.
You must find the keys, kal-el,
or your destiny will fall
into the hands of another man.
You must save yourself.
What is it with the luthors?
I swear death follows that family
around like a stray puppy.
- Lois, you are not gonna believe this.
- You know, I wanted to search
luthorcorp tonight for evidence
that lex had patricia swann killed.
But you, no, genius that you are,
you wanted to stay here
and search through meaningless
memos in lex's office.
So while we were
over here atthe daily planet
photographing everything
but the bottled water,
the story of a lifetime was
happening right across the street.
Just take a look at the view.
One of tonight's shots
from lex's office.
What?
The schoolboy crush is sweet, jimmy,
but you need to adjust your focus
in more ways than one here.This is serious.
Bodies are literally falling out of the sky.
And we have the picture to prove it.
Lex's office
looks out over luthorcorp.
and?
It's lionel luthor
right before he died.
What? No way.
Creepy.
I can't believe
you got this, jimmy.
Well,
it's gonna get creepier.
There's someone else
in the room.
Look, lionel luthor
might have been pushed.
You think this blurry
blob of pixels is the killer? Come on.
Trust me. This has pulitzer
written all over it.
Yeah?
What are you waiting for?
Sharpen the shot.
Well, it's not that easy. My computer's
not powerful enough.
Hey, what about
that heavy-duty hardware
that lana has stashed
at the isis foundation?
Nice.
I can upload this bad boy to the
foundation's server right now.
And, you know,
if we're on lana's system,
we could probably use
chloe's mad skills with a cpu.
That is, if we can pry her
away from clark.
Chloe and I
share the same dna.
Trust me, jimmy... she is
gonna want to be in on this.
I'm so sorry
about your father.
Thank you, chloe.
He visited you
here tonight.
Yeah,
he really wasn't himself.
I fear,
in his deluded state of mind,
my father disposed of
some valuable family heirlooms.
Did he give you anything?
Other than the feeling that
something was definitely off?
no.
I mean, he was only here
for a few minutes.
And then, to be honest,
I got scared, so I...
Have you checked
your desk?
He didn't give me anything, lex.
I swear he just came here to talk.
This was my father's.
I've never seen it before.
Why were you hiding it
from me?
Lex, if I knew it was yours,
I wouldn't keep it from you.
Why would he even
give it to you?
Do you know
what this key is for?
Lex, lionel wasn't in
his right mind when he was here.
I don't know
why he left that.
You're fired.
Escort Miss sullivan
from the building.
Aren't you gonna give me a second
to clear out my private things?
Your personal items will be
boxed up and sent to your home.
Lex, your name may be on the building,
but that's my personal stuff. I have rights!
If anything is missing, lex, I swear to god,
you won't hear the end of this!
I'll pack up
miss sullivan's belongings.
You go
back to the mansion.
Get some sleep.
We did it, lex.
Okay, that's it.
I'm leaving.
Lois, I want to start working on
this picture as much as you do,
but we haven't heard from chloe yet.
I really think that we should wait.
News waits for no one...
Not even chloe.
You texted her, you left her, like,
three voicemail messages at the apartment.
She's not helen keller. She'll get
the message and meet us there.
Well, it wouldn't kill us
to wait a few...
More minutes.
I agree with Mr. Olsen.
Why are we outside
of the kitchen?
It's a little late
for a snack, isn't it?
I've seen you around here before
haven't i? You work for lex.
Mr. Luthor has nothing
to do with this.
I'm here about
that photograph you took.
Which photograph would that be?
Because I take a whole lot of pictures.
Lionel luthor in his office
before he killed himself.
I want that photo destroyed. His
death was tragic enough
without it being sensationalized
by the media.
Well, you could have said that before
you broke out the heavy artillery.
Yeah, as soon as we saw it, I immediately
jumped on the delete button.
This is all a big,
big misunderstanding.
You're lying.
Ideleted it.
After I saw
your text message,
I went into the mainframe and
pulled it from your hard drive.
But the transfer log shows
you uploaded the file
to a second server
with a cloaked i.p. Address.
I want to know
where you sent it.
- You shot me?!
- You weren't cooperating.
- How about a warning?
- Tell me or she dies. Where's the server?
It's the isis foundation. It's 3rd and
broadway. It's a 10-minute drive.
I'll come back for you
when I'm done.
You're really bleeding, lois.
I guess trying to take on
one of lex luthor's fembots
doesn't make me the smartest
icle in the freezer.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna get us out of here.
hey!
Is anyone out there?!
Is anyone in there?!
Help!
Can anyone hear me?!
Hey. Jimmy and lois here?
Not yet, but jimmy's message
said he already sent the files,
so I was about to get started.
I got a message that lionel
left for me in his vault.
Chloe, I think I know
why he was killed.
He was trying to
protect me.
Lionel did say
something terrible was coming.
There's something on earth
that can be used to control me.
Control you? As in "do my
bidding," like some sort of puppet?
I mean, what could possibly
pull your strings?
I don't know. But whatever it is,
it takes two keys to unlock.
Clark, when I went back
tothe daily planet tonight,
there was a key in my desk.
Lionel left it there for you.
- Where is it?
- Lex took it.
I was trying to hide it
from him, but then...
He fired me. Which is fine
because I wanted to
get out of
that black hole anyway, but...
Besides, we don't have time to
talk about my nine-to-five right now.
So you think that that mystery
man was after the locket?
I don't think our mystery man
is much of a mystery at all,
considering that lex went
to the daily planet tonight...
The same night
that his father died...
And fired you
over that key.
How long till we get an i.d.
On this picture?
Jimmy wasn't kidding when he said there
isn't a lot of photo in this photograph.
I mean, it's gonna take me
at least a couple of hours.
Keep working on it.
My father just died,
and you're already
breaking and entering?
Lionel would never take
his own life.
I thought you'd at least try
to offer some words of comfort.
Get out.
I'm not going anywhere.
You can still be good, lex.
Tell clark what you did.
He's our friend.
I'm not gonna debate my father's
mental state with you.
I'm grieving, clark. I think you know
what it's like to lose a father.
Don't bring my father
into this.
Why not?
Our fathers
were a lot alike...
Smart, strong-willed,
and both died prematurely.
You know,
you're right, lex.
Lionel did die too soon.
I want to know the truth
about how he died.
The truth is...
Our dads were alike
in another way.
See, they both felt that you
were the kind of son
a father could be proud of.
He would have felt the same way
about you, lex,
if you would have tried.
What happened to you?
I did try, clark.
In fact,
when we first met,
you inspired me.
All I wanted
was to be your friend,
but you turned your back on me.
So you're the person
you are today because of me.
I tried to be
your friend, lex.
But all you care about
is power and control.
This is smallville!
Meteor freaks, alien ships,
cryptic symbols!
These threats are real.
Someone had to
take control.
- Someone has to protect the world.
- Listen to yourself, lex.
You're so caught up in your own
delusions, you've lost track of reality.
Have i?
Then let's talk about something
you can't deny.
After years of pleading with my
father to show me some compassion,
he turned to you
with open arms.
Now, what would a worldly
billionaire have in common
with a simple farm boy?
Maybe he just knew
he could trust me.
Of course.
Everyone can trust
clark kent.
You're the perfect son.
So... so why did jonathan kent
always seem so stressed?
I mean, was raising the perfect
son really that much work?
I wonder how much of a strain
it put on his heart.
Are you blaming me
for my father's death?
Are you?!
You're the guilty one, lex,
not me.
And this time, you're gonna
own up to what you've done.
I know you killed lionel.
- Who's delusional now?
- I have proof.
You really did it, lex.
Chloe, you in here?
Chloe, what happened?
You okay?
Somebody hit me.
Here.
They destroyed
the picture.
But you were right,
clark.
I saw the picture.
It was lex.
When I went to see lex,
I found lionel's locket.
But without that photograph,
we can't prove anything.
What about the key?
I x-rayed the entire mansion.
It's nowhere to be found.
What happened to jimmy and lois?
Where are they?
I don't know.
And I'm worried.
The last I heard, they were
leavingthe daily planet.
If whoever attacked me followed
the photo from there to here.
He may have stopped jimmy and
lois from leaving the building.
I got to go.
Clark, if lex has
both of those keys,
not only will he discover
your secret,
but he'll have total
and complete power over you.
Now, that's not
justyourworst nightmare...
It's everyone else's, too.
Be careful.
I've got an exclusive
for you.
When we get out of here...
... lois lane and jimmy olsen
are gonna be world-famous.
You know what, lois?
We really do make a good team,
you know?
Our name in lights. I can see it now.
It's gonna be great.
Hi, lex.
It's gina.
Please call me back.
I found who you've
been searching for.
I know who the traveler is.
After the funeral,
I plan on taking some time off.
Get the jet ready.
Zurich.
You can't run away, lex.
No matter where you go,
i'll always be there.
You can't get rid of me.
You need my help.
There's still good inside you.
I know it.
I don't want your help.
Don't go to zurich.
I'm going.
I have to.
Dad was right.
If you open the box,
it will destroy you.
It's all I have left.
It's not true.
You still have me.
no.
I'm done
listening to you.
You make me weak.
Long night.
It's good to see
the sun again.
It's too bad
lionel's not here to see it.
Lex closed the funeral
to any and all guests.
In other words,
lex is the only one invited.
Lionel deserves better.
At least we know how lionel
truly felt about you.
I mean, he thought of you
as his second son.
Another person who treated me like
a son and died because of it.
Jor-el died
getting me on that ship.
My dad died
of a heart attack
from the powers he took on
protecting me.
And now lionel's been murdered
for protecting my secret.
They did die for you,
clark.
But ultimately,
they died for all of us.
There was a reason
those men were in your life.
Each of them added something
to the man that you are today.
How could lex have done it?
How does a son...
Murder his own father?
Total absence of love.
Some say that's
the definition of evil.
You have to get those keys
away from lex, clark,
before he kills anyone else.
He's not gonna have
the chance.
I won't let him.
For SeriesSub.com