So, it turns out global
warming's just another excuse
To take your clothes off.
I know what it looks like,
but oliver claims they raise
- A ton of money at this thing.
- Yeah, at 500 bucks a plate, i'll bet.
I'm just glad
you've got your press pass.
Although, as much as
i love the one-On-One time,
I got to say i'm actually surprised
lois unattached you from her hip.
What do you mean? Lois and i
aren't always together.
Clark, you see her more than
i see jimmy, and we're engaged.
What are you
trying to say?
Never mind.
I guess i just always thought that i
would be the one circling your typos.
Lois doesn't circle typos.
She underlines them
two or three times.
And she couldn't
skip out early.
In typical lois fashion,
she's already on tess' bad side.
Tess. That's assuming that the
luthor wannabe has a good side.
I know she's a die-Hard
lex supporter.
But up until this point,
she's been civil.
And i'm sure the flowing hair
and piercing green eyes
Didn't sway you at all.
It doesn't change the fact
that lex knows my secret.
And if she truly is following
in lex's footsteps,
Then she may not be far behind.
You're right. And if lex chose her
to carry on his legacy,
She must be handled
with extreme caution.
Looks like ollie's party
started in the limo.
No.
He'd never show up drunk.
Excuse me.
Oliver, come on. Stand up.
- I'm fine.
- I know you're not drunk.
- Come on, let's get you to a hospital.
- No, clark!
Oliver,
what's happened to you?
Poison.
I have 12 hours to live.
Smallville 803
Synchro : flolo
For seriessub.Com
Chloe,
he's getting worse.
If it's poison, we need to
get him to a hospital.
- Davis is on his way.
- He needs a doctor, chloe.
Clark, if oliver said he wants to
avoid all mds and hospitals,
I'm sure he has
a really good reason.
I'm not gonna stand here
and watch my friend die!
Do you think
this is easy for me?
I know oliver, too. I've worked
side by side with him.
And when he says to do something,
it's always for a reason.
This time it's different! His life's at stake!
If you were lying on that couch,
I would do whatever you asked,
down to the letter.
I wouldn't hesitate.
Now trust him.
I'm gonna check his phone,
see if i can find the number
Of the girl he was with tonight.
Thank god. Davis.
He is a lot worse
than you said he was, chloe.
- We think he may have been poisoned.
- Can you help him?
His pulse is racing...
and he's burning up.
He's stable, so i can set him up
with a heart monitor,
Take his blood to the lab,
but if things don't look better
- In one hour, i got to bring him in.
- I know you're risking your job to do this,
But you can trust me.
Watch him. If anything changes, call.
I'll get the monitor.
His date's name is adrianna.
It showed up in the calendar.
And she didn't call after
he disappeared from the event?
No, and she won't pick up,
either.
I'm gonna go to the bar
and see if she's still there.
Let's hope for oliver's sake
that she knows something.
Latest dish with a side order
of spell check,
"Grisly murders down on hampton."
I haven't fired you yet?
Guess you're too busy
printing my stories.
What's with
the oliver queen collage?
I figured the news had trickled down
to the basement by now.
You know, for a renowned party boy,
queen sure can't hold his liquor.
Unbelievable.
Metropolis may have its very own
jack the ripper,
And you're preoccupied
with smearing a humanitarian.
Do you even know
oliver queen?
Not like you do.
Come on.
You can't tell me you don't get
a twinge of pleasure
Seeing your ex
take a public nosedive.
Look, he's a good person
who stands up against corruption
And social injustice.
I was gonna offer you the story. But
after that bleeding-Heart testimonial,
You're obviously not objective enough
to uncover the rest of it.
Well, it's not exactly a news flash.
You drink, you get drunk.
When someone leaves a club fall-Down
drunk, the story only gets better.
I need someone to get
to the bottom of this
Without suffering
from an emotional meltdown.
Please. You know, you need to
read your gossip column.
Oliver and i were through
a long time ago. I'll take the story.
What happened to her?
Someone found her passed out
in the bathroom,
- O.D.'D on something or other.
- Did she say anything?
She's barely breathing. Lucky if
she makes it to the hospital alive.
Come on, oliver.
Whatever's going on inside you,
you can beat it.
Hello!
Can anyone hear me?!
All right.
Here's the deal.
Normally, i don't eat anything
with more than 99 legs on it,
But i haven't eaten for days.
Kind of a bummer
for both of us, right?
Okay, you win. Go.
Hey, have you seen ollie? Apparently
he's boozed his way into a...
Who's he been partying
with, motley crue?
- It's not what you think.
- Find me a 24-Hour market.
I need a sports drink,
as much vitamin b
As you can get your hands on,
and one dill pickle.
Let's go! Ticktock!
He's no thung over, lois.
What's going on?
Clark's trying to figure it out,
but we do know that it's serious.
He's poisoned.
Oh, my god.
Ollie? It's lois.
What's he doing here?
He needs a real doctor.
He specifically said
no hospitals.
Well, i'm actually conscious,
and i'm saying he needs one.
Lois, i know
what it looks like, okay?
But right now, oliver needs
people he can trust,
And this is what he wanted.
You're right.
I know ollie better than anyone,
and if he said no hospitals...
... then i guess we have to
take his word for it.
- Mercy.
- Ollie?
What are you saying?
Mercy.
Can you hear me?
Get these things off me.
I hate leeches.
We can't take them off yet.
What the hell happened?
What is this?
You need your rest.
What's going on here?
What is this?
I promised them
that i could save you.
With leeches.
They produce
a curing enzyme.
You were poisoned
by a very highly toxic plant.
It's not that i don't appreciate
the sentiment.
I know it sounds crazy, but i'm a marine
biologist. We study this stuff.
Without this enzyme,
you'd be dead in 12 hours.
A hospital would have mis diagnosed you,
pumped you full of adrenaline,
And killed you instantly.
I guess... you're lucky.
And that shotgun
at the door...
Should i feel lucky
about that, too?
My friend and i...
We've been kidnapped.
Davis. I'm looking
for oliver's date.
She was just admitted.
I'm bringing oliver in.
Look, we just need a little more time.
We couldn't identify
what the poison was,
But we think it was something
that they drank in the limo
On the way to the fundraiser.
- Adrianna's a victim, too?
- Was a victim.
She's fine now.
We treated her with adrenaline,
and her stats evened out.
- But 10 minutes ago, she was dying.
- Modern medicine, clark.
That girl's living proof that oliver's too
sick to know what he's talking about.
Code blue!
Get a doctor.
Her pupils are completely dilated.
And her fever's through the roof.
We need 40 cc of nitro...
now! Now!
She's going into shock.
Stay with us.
It's not quite the scenario i pictured
if i ever ran into a woman
On this island.
Just be glad
that it worked.
What did they do to you?
We were in fiji
doing marine research.
And this speedboat
came out of nowhere.
And it attacked us.
And they killed everyone.
They killed our guide,
three of my classmates.
Well, how many are there?
There's the one at the door,
and there's a guy named marcos.
They were on their way
to thailand when the boat
Started taking water,
so they stopped here to fix it.
How's your friend?
She'll be okay.
We'll all be okay.
We just have to get out of here.
So, how's our golden goose?
You don't think
i know who you are?
Oliver queen?
No idea
what you're talking about.
You're famous!
Everyone knows you're that rich brat
who took off with his friends
On a yacht and partied his way
into a ship wreck.
And lucky for us,
not all of you were shark bait.
Just let them go, huh?
I have a different idea.
We'll ransom him
for millions.
No! No!
If you kill her, you're gonna
have to kill me first.
You're not gonna die
for her.
I have been stuck on this god
for saken island for two years!
So i figure if i die...
At least i die
for something.
The boat's almost done.
Then we're out of here.
Look at us, the noble couple.
I let you go. In return, you were
supposed to save the world.
This, ollie...
This isn't saving the world, is it?
This is you backing out
on your end of the deal.
You know, maybe...
Maybe we had it wrong.
Maybe our...
... story ends
and neither of us are heroes.
Because you're not the only one
who couldn't hold up
His end of the deal.
The truth is...
... sometimes i wonder if
i should have ever let you go.
How's he doing?
Clark, can i talk to you
for a second?
The hospital couldn't
identify the poison.
That's because the profile
doesn't match any public database.
But how are we supposed to find an antidote
to a poison that doesn't have a name?
Name it ourselves.
The cyanobateria
In oliver's blood shares a similar
molecular makeup
To the chloroplast found
in a flower of the nerium genus.
Here. Now, there's only one species
of nerium oleander,
But that doesn't exactly narrow things down.
However, the high concentration
of cardio glycoside
Rules out several subspecies,
orienting us in the south pacific.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
You mean like
i'm at a met your lecture?
Chloe, you're the smartest
person i know by a long shot,
But since when can you trace
a few chemicals from an obscure flower?
It's no big deal. I'm just
expanding my knowledge base.
You're getting smarter.
I don't have time to discuss
this with you right now.
What is all this, chloe?
Thanks to lex's obsession
with toxins and viruses,
Luthorcorp has the most
comprehensive collection
Of organic material
on the planet.
You're reading all this,
aren't you?
There it is.
If luthorcorp has this flower,
then they have the antidote.
Listen, chloe,
as much as i appreciate
Whatever it is you just did here,
this is all because of brainiac, isn't it?
All right, i admit it. After he attacked me,
my hacking skills
Went from analog to digital.
And whether i like it or not,
i can read and process
Data at lightning-Fast speed.
Now, i knowthat right now
you are making a list
In your head of all the possible ways
this could be your fault, but please don't.
If this is because of brainiac,
then we don't know what can happen.
Exactly! No one knows.
So let's not worry about it
until we have to. Clark, this is my life.
And for once, something good
came from something horrible.
I'm choosing to look at this
as a gift,
One that could help us
save oliver's life.
Now trust me.
I think it's time to call in
a favor with your new boss.
It does bring out your eyes.
That tie.
I was wondering if you could
help me with something.
A friend of mine has been poisoned.
The doctors can't help him,
but i think luthorcorp owns
The lab that makes the antidote.
Believe me, my heart
goes out to your friend. But...
I don't have some secret
stash of toxins or antidotes.
There must be something
you can do.
Lex never abandons
a project.
He doesn't, does he?
I'm still catching up on the ones
he's named after constellations.
But if this lab exists,
i don't know about it.
Look, miss mercer,
i realize that you're my boss
And that your job requires
a certain level of secrecy...
But the antidote to this plant
could save my friend's life.
Who exactly is your friend?
His name is oliver queen.
He doesn't have much time to live.
I'm not gonna stand here
and lie to you, clark.
But i can't help you, either.
The lab was relocated
to campo grande, brazil.
Even if i made a call, we'd never
get the antidote here in time.
You must be lois.
You must be the one who's
actually qualified to do this.
He's dying.
I'm sorry.
Here is what's gonna happen,
dimples.
You are going to reach
into that handy little
Tackle box of yours and
pull us out a miracle.
Oliver queen
does not die today.
The best i can do is keep him
alive a few minutes longer.
Then do it.
I gave this bracelet to megan
for her birthday.
She was my best friend.
She was joking around when she said
That she'd wear it
till the day that she died.
Okay, easy, easy.
There you go.
Come here.
I'm so sorry.
What are you doing?
They'll kill us.
I swore that if i ever made it
off this island, i'd change.
I wouldn't waste my life.
That starts now.
Boat's ready. Let's go.
Hurry up.
Careful.
That flower's poisonous.
You're not gonna
leave me here to die.
You want to live?
You crawl down
to the leech pond.
Make some new friends.
Are you ready to go home?
Just hit 106! He's on fire!
It's just like adrianna.
We need more ice and towels.
In the back.
Come on, ollie.
Hold on. Come on.
He can't take much more
of this!
Out of the way.
Lois, i need you
to breathe for me.
Breathe.
Come on, ollie,
stay with me.
Clark, he's dying.
Use it.
I don't get it.
This... antidote doesn't exist.
Queen industries.
They have a lab nearby.
Mercy.
- You have to go find mercy.
- What?
Tess mercer.
Clark, please.
Whoever did this to me,
they're gonna go after her next.
- You know tess?
- There's no time, clark!
She was working late.
She's at the daily planet.
Damn it.
Miss me?
You left me
on that island to die.
You're not an easy person
to track down, are you?
There's that scared little girl
i remember.
You haven't changed a bit.
I think you'd be surprised.
I meant to write you a postcard
to say "thank you."
You were one of the men
in my life that taught me
How to fight back.
Really?
Whatever happened to the party boy
hanging up his beer bong
So that he could do good
for the world?
Well, i'm not the guy
in that article anymore.
Of course you're not. You're oliver queen,
world-Famous samaritan.
And i was his first save.
Excuse me, you, um...
You know you were
much more than that.
I'm glad you're okay, oliver.
After all, i need the chief
of queen industries
Alive and well if luthorcorp is
gonna keep its competitive edge.
I'm happy to help.
This is great.
A few pay grades up from your days
studying jelly fish
And protesting
whaler ships, huh?
You're not the first person
to wonder how i arrived
At the helm
of the luthor dynasty.
Well, what's to wonder?
You play to win.
I found out how ruthless
you were a long time ago.
After what you did to me,
did you really expect me to just
- Sit around and eat ice cream?
- No.
You'd rather work
for my greatest enemy, and then,
Just when i think the knife
can't twist any farther,
You take over
his entire company.
Oh, so that's what you do
when you're not writing checks
And grinning for the cameras.
You sit around pondering ways
that i've dedicated my life
To your downfall.
I'm sorry to break it to you, oliver,
but everything i did, i did for me.
Well, then i guess our past
is behind us.
It has been since the day
that you said goodbye.
Oh, wait.
You never actually did, did you?
Is that why you
called me here?
Because it's on the tip
of my tongue.
No.
I called you
to give you this.
I realize that lionel luthor
is dead and buried,
But maybe this will help you
sleep at night.
- Hey, lois.
- Hey, thanks, smallville.
Starting to get the hang
of things around here.
I spoke to chloe. She said you
didn't come home last night.
So not what you're thinking.
I may have played nurse with oliver,
but it never progressed to doctor.
I've been working here
all night.
"Kitten-Adoption fair
this sunday"?
You gave up your article
on oliver for this?
Doesn't sound like you, lois.
Is it possible you're more shaken up
about last night than you realize?
You think?
I was practically
a three-Shot martini.
Yeah, but it doesn't mean you have
to bury your emotions in your work.
This is the most heart breaking
kitten-Adoption story you've ever read.
What am i doing?
Ollie and i are through.
Maybe, but just because
your relationship's over
Doesn't mean
the feelings go away.
I'd be lying if i said
i didn't watch the goodbye tape
- That lana sent me more than once.
- Well, i'd rather avoid a ride
On the clark-And-Lana
roller coaster.
No offense.
It's okay.
I've got a delicate enough ego
as it is.
I am not cut out to date a guy
with a hero complex.
I mean, you were there.
You saw him at the fundraiser.
He's practically an icon,
"the man of tomorrow,"
And i'm just lois lane,
the girl who writes about it.
Lois, there's nothing wrong with that.
Right. So, when the occasional feelings
flare up,
You just got to trust your gut,
as hard as it is,
And realize that you broke up
for a reason.
Exactly.
That one's on the house,
smallville.
You should know,
i'm allergic to cats.
Get to work.
Chop-Chop.
I thought i closed those.
- I'm sorry. They were open.
- What are you doing here?
Uh, well, i was, uh,
checking in on oliver.
It was a hell of a close call last night.
He's got a pretty great crew of friends.
Renegade paramedic
included.
You must have done pretty well
on your s.A.T.S.
I thought you said
you studied journalism.
Well, yeah, journalism,
and then there were the core
Classes and some, you know,
electives and stuff.
Level with me, chloe.
Are you some kind of genius?
I'm embarrassing you.
There's a reason i like to try
and keep the doors closed.
You know, there's nothing wrong
with being smart.
When the seating chart at your wedding
looks more like a euclidean
Algorithm than a ding hall, you know
you've got something seriously wrong.
And the guy next to you
on that seating chart,
What does he think
about all this?
He doesn't know.
Well, it's all sort of
just happening,
Which is why i would really prefer it
if we could keep it between us.
Look, chloe, i think that,
in some weird way,
We all have some part of us
that we hold underneath the surface.
Even i do.
So, i hear i'm not the only one
in town who owes you a drink.
Tess mercer's attacker
was arrested last night.
Why didn't you tell me
you knew tess mercer before?
It was in the past.
Not exactly proud of the way
things turned out.
Doesn't change the fact that she
knew the guy who tried to kill you.
Yeah, well,
it makes sense to me.
The guy came after me.
Then he's gonna go after her.
She's the other captain
of industry in town, so...
Oliver, with all that poison in your system,
are you sure adding more
Is the best idea right now?
Yeah, clark, why don't you
stick to your milkshakes, huh?
I'll know
when i've had enough.
Lionel luthor
killed my parents.
You figured that out
from flight records?
I mean,
it was a plane crash.
Yeah, it was a plane crash,
and according to that,
There were luthorcorp employees
on the maintenance lot.
And you think lionel paid them
to sabotage the plane?
Did you know about this?
You were the son lionel never had.
The guy knew everything about you, right?
So don't stand there and tell me
that you didn't know a couple
Of his dirty little secrets.
Look, oliver, i was afraid that
you'd do something you'd regret.
"Something i regret." Like what, clark?
You thought i was gonna kill him?
Is that it?
I wouldn't have killed him!
I survived for two years
on an island by myself, clark!
When it wasn't pouring rain,
it was blistering sun!
There were mosquitos
that ate me alive!
It's okay, because you know
what? It made me strong.
You may be invincible,
but you are not fearless, are you?
You're afraid to trust your friends,
and you're afraid to face
Who you were really meant to be.
You're afraid of everything.
Maybe you haven't been
put to the test yet.
Maybe your island's
still out there, clark.
- Take me to the airport.
- Right.
What the hell...
You.
Who do you think
paid your bail?
Jail's too good for you.
I think he's having
a heart attack.
You might want to take him
to the hospital.
What am i, an ambulance?
They'll know what to do
with him.
For seriessub.Com