Previously on "smallville"...
- lex deserved to die.
- Are you listening to yourself?
Oliver killed lex luthor.
You're not one of us anymore.
You're making a big mistake.
Maybe i'm selfish.
I can't share you
with the rest of the world.
You may be on
some death-wish fast track,
but i could really use
a little dose of hero about now.
You know that you're meant
for more than this. This isn't you.
"My name is oliver queen,
and i am..."
we have to get
these people out of here now.
Oliver's standing on a land mine.
How'd you know
the pressure plate wasn't real?
I didn't.
Is there any part of the person
i used to know still there?
Maybe not. I took a look in the mirror,
and you were right.
I've been running away from
myself for a long time now.
But now i know who i really am.
Now, that's the face of a guy
who's down on his luck.
I think my luck's
about ready to turn around.
I don't remember seeing you earlier.
Maybe not.
But i've seen you before.
Your type.
And what type is that exactly?
The player who can't find a game
to satisfy him.
I'll admit i've lost
a certain lust for life...
but luckily not other things.
Then play a game with me.
I'm all in.
It's not exactly
the kind of game i had in mind.
You can only choose one.
You're not joining me?
Trips are more fun
when they're for two.
This is just for you.
I promise, it'll be worth it.
Of course, you do have a choice.
But...
what do you have to lose?
Absolutely nothing.
What the hell?
What the hell is...
Smallville - 9x05 - Roulette
Synchro : Flolo
For Seriessub.com
about time you got home.
Shelby's great and all, but the
conversation. A little one-sided.
Shouldn't you be riding a mechanical
bull somewhere? It is friday night.
Correction. It's movie night.
I hope you like sharks.
We're gonna start
with my favorite one.
You have your hands full
with all your laundry.
Maybe we should make movie night
another weekend.
It's called "multitasking."
You should try it sometime.
I hope i have enough detergent.
How do you even have
anything left to wear?
Most guys wouldn't complain
if i suddenly found myself shirtless.
Poor clark. Here.
F.y.i....
that did not just happen.
Come on!
It is called "smallville"
for a reason.
What else do you possibly have
to do tonight?
It'll be fun.
Stop! Stop it!
You know what we need?
Some popcorn.
Don't forget the extra butter.
Please!
See? We're already having fun.
Can anyone hear me?!
Come on... think.
Just think.
Come on.
The last time i trust
a woman with a dragon tattoo.
You got to be kidding me.
It's a hell of a game
you're playing, winslow!
If the toyman wants to play,
you're gonna have to come out here
and face me like a man.
Winslow schott isn't responsible,
mr. Queen.
Care to guess again?
Enough. This ends now!
If that's what you want,
just say the safe word
and the game will stop.
What the hell are you talking
about? I didn't get a safe word.
Because you didn't ask.
If you don't care enough
to learn the rules,
you can't complain
about the game continuing.
Who is this?!
I'll give you a hint.
Tell me, mr. Queen,
who did you destroy?
"Destroy."
I've ruined a lot of lives.
I better keep this simple.
Here's a yes-or-no question.
Have you had your rabies shot?
Are you like this at the
movie theater, too?
These concession runs
are really sweet,
but you're up and down more often
than the cubs' batting lineup.
It's all the onscreen suspense.
I guess it makes me hungry.
What'd i miss?
There was this thing about a boat.
And then just lots
of dum-dum-dum-dum,
dah-dum da-da da-da-da-da dum.
All right. You show up with every
shark movie known to man
and 11 loads of laundry when i've seen
you take socks to the dry cleaner.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why wouldn't i be fine?
I'm totally not fine.
Even if it is stupid.
But it's not stupid.
It's oliver's birthday today,
and we always go out
for beer pong on our birthdays.
But today is about to become
yesterday in t-minus...
negative minutes.
It's over. He totally missed it.
How does a guy with nine phone
numbers not return a phone call?
Probably just celebrating
with someone else.
Tall, dark, and single.
Go figure.
Do you know something?
You would tell me if you did, right?
I'm sure oliver's just fine.
But paying him a visit
wouldn't hurt.
Great idea. Anchors up, captain.
Let's go.
- It's oliver. I really need your help.
- We're sorry,
but your call cannot
be completed as dialed.
- Come on!
- You come on, mr. Queen.
Did you really think
it would be that easy?
Who the hell is this?
Just the woman i'm looking for.
I know exactly how you feel.
Don't make a scene.
The people who set the game
in motion are here.
If they realize you're here,
they'll kill you.
- And why should i trust you?
- Trust your instincts.
When the chips are down,
they're all you have.
All in?
Wait.
I don't even know your name.
It's victoria!
We don't have time for this!
We're gonna make time. Now, you tell me
who's behind the game!
I work for some nasty guys. They don't
exactly have an h.r. Department.
It's my job
to knock their targets out.
If you hadn't taken that pill,
they would have killed me.
I'm gonna help you out
of this, okay? Look at me.
In order to do that, i need to know
what these people want with me.
- You understand?
- I wish i knew. People hire them.
They never tell me the client's
identity or end game.
Hell, i guess you're the only one
that can answer that question.
Who did you hurt so badly that
they'd want to see you dead?
Pick a name.
My personal wars have left
a serious casualty list 'cause...
i kind of always figured it was easier
for me to hurt the people i cared about
than to stick around
long enough knowing
eventually i'd end up
disappointing them anyway.
They found us!
Come on.
Listen to me. Look at me.
Let me go.
This is the only way i'll be free.
You listen to me.
You got to fight, okay?
You got to hang on.
Look at me.
Hands up!
No, wait a minute. You got
the wrong guy, okay?
- Get up, now!
- Listen to me!
You got the wrong guy!
Pants on, birthday boy.
Party train's arrived.
I think people
would prefer "knock" over "pants on."
We've already checked his jet
and his apartment.
Unless he's under the couch.
Looks like his party train
already left the station.
Without me on board?
Doubtful.
Why don't you let me take you home?
Why would oliver want to relive the
night someone tried to hindenburg him?
We should respect his privacy.
I can't imagine what he was going
through just standing there.
He looks like he didn't even
know the bomb got defused.
But then why is he...
oh, my god.
He didn't know.
Oliver tried to kill himself.
Come on.
And you knew.
How could you keep something
this serious from me?
I was trying to protect him.
From who? His friends?
Wait.
I didn't think
he wanted anyone to know.
I'm not just anyone.
You lied to me.
You lied right to my face.
You said everything was fine.
Nothing about this...
is fine.
Let me get this straight.
You've no i.d., no witnesses,
and no alibi.
Why should i let a murderer
walk free?
The people she works for...
they came after us, okay?
- They shot her.
- Gentlemen.
This case just officially
became fbi jurisdiction.
Don't let me keep you.
Fbi.
I thought you could use those.
Thanks.
I apologize for the way
you've been treated, mr. Queen.
You know who i am?
And we know about the game.
We've been tracking this group
for some time.
Their m.o. Is to target
wealthy individuals
and eventually hack
their bank accounts.
Really?
I never thought i'd be happy
she didn't want me, just my money.
How they seem to get their kicks.
They toy with you, keeping you
distracted while they wipe you out.
I suggest that you check
your accounts immediately.
Nothing's
been touched. It's all here.
You're lucky.
Need you to fill out
some paperwork. Then you can go home.
Thank you.
They're taking everything!
They're draining my accounts!
You hear me?! Come on!
Come on!
Let me out of here!
I found the invitation to roulette.
It's only a few blocks away.
I could hear you yelling.
What is all this?
It's game over.
I just got taken.
Oh, my god.
Are you okay?
South of there
by a few horror movies.
Someone's been using oliver
as a pawn in their game.
- We need to figure out who.
- Just tell me where to start.
The name of the club is roulette.
He met a woman there named victoria.
At the risk of taking a belly
flop into an awkward pool,
what kind of game
puts people through hell?
The kind that starts with being
buried alive and ends with bankruptcy.
That was quick.
It looks like the two clues
are one and the same.
Meet victoria sinclair,
a.k.a. Roulette.
Seems as though she's made
a career out of betting for high stakes,
i.e., everything you have.
Get my gear.
When you turned your back on us,
i locked up your arsenal,
hoping that one day you would
want it back but not like this.
This is my fight, chloe.
I'll handle it how i see fit.
Where'd that line lead you
last night?
I got into this mess
on my own. I'll get out the same way.
With my lawyers. Okay, scout?
He just needs to cool off
a little bit, okay?
Right now, you have bigger problems.
Trust me.
Now, my relationship with oliver
may have dissolved,
but i didn't lose everything
in the meltdown.
Our computers are still linked,
which is how i found this.
Oliver was watching this
on his laptop.
It's a long story about lois
and laundry and lacy things.
- Lois saw this video?
- Not only it, but me on it.
On a scale from one to chernobyl,
how big was the fallout?
Let's just say if there was an antilife
equation, i think i found it.
Check this out.
That's the assassin
who attacked lois and i.
I buried her before this video was
taken. How could she be on it?
If we're looking
for a kryptonian assassin
who's from the future and supposed
to be dead in the present,
i'm out of answers.
Maybe jor-el won't be.
When you say "close," are you
talking feet or zip codes?
Mr. Whatever-your-name-is,
you're a gps tracking service.
You can probably see me
on your satellite,
how much farther
down pepper spray lane bdo i have to go?
Never mind. I found it.
Thanks.
If you're not lost,
then get that way.
I don't like smudge marks on my car.
Nice try, vice city. Go grand-theft
someone else's auto.
I've sat in that excuse
for a front seat enough
to know that this car belongs
to oliver queen.
If you know oliver,
then you know
he likes to give gifts.
This is one of them,
so i suggest you back off.
Sorry, but backing off...
not exactly my strong suit.
Where's oliver?
I prefer to make my own luck.
I guess your luck hasn't run out.
I'm disappointed.
You lack the killer instinct
after all.
Toss the gun.
True gamesmen...
they don't cheat
by stacking the deck.
Everything was aces
until your girlfriend showed up.
As always, i had to play
the hand i was dealt.
Why don't you just let her go?
You didn't play by my rules.
Why should i play by yours?
You were supposed to shoot her.
That's what i don't understand.
You could have killed her yourself.
You could have shot me when i walked
through the door. Why set the scene?
One can tie up loose ends
with a simple square knot or
one can choose
the more elegant cloverleaf.
It's all a matter of style.
I'd say i'm sorry
for taking your money,
except, in your case,
it hardly matters.
You can't take it with you.
How do i know this isn't
just part of your game?
Right.
Shoot her.
She knows i won't,
not if there's a chance i'd hit you.
Gasoline.
I thought i'd torch the place
when we're done.
Clover knot.
I just like playing with fire.
Never bet against the house.
Help! Help!
Help me!
Help!
Oh, hell.
Help me!
Look at me.
It's all right, okay?
I'm gonna get you
out of here. Come on.
Why did you come?
You could have left me here.
After everything i put you through,
no one would blame you.
I'd blame myself. I don't care
what you did or who you are,
i'm gonna get you the hell
out of here, all right?
I'm not gonna let you die.
Now, come on.
What the hell is this?
You kept asking me
who did this to you.
My question was always the answer.
"Who did you destroy?"
I hear you're some sort of hero.
One that tried to bury
that part of himself.
You've just proven that that hero
is still alive.
Now it's time to resurrect him.
Nice to play.
I just started asking myself
who knew about lex,
about toyman.
The things i'd given up,
what i tried to do.
Then it all occurred to me.
Dinah shattered
the glass in the warehouse,
bart rescued me from the car,
victor faked the computers,
and watchtower kept an eye
on the whole thing. Right?
You were living like you had
a death wish.
You had to face your demons if you
were ever gonna make it out alive,
and i had to push you over
the ledge in order to pull you back.
Did you have to push
with a 3-ton truck?
I didn't think a tricycle
would be a strong enough point.
You're a fighter.
You fought for yourself
and for a second chance.
I'm not the only one
you put at risk.
If you're worried about our
little club and lex, don't be.
I played my cards close to my chest.
And lois was what? She was,
just another ace up your sleeve?
No. I never meant
for her to get involved.
She was chasing after you
when she accidentally
ended up storming the field.
That's when victoria
went off script.
I could have killed her.
No offense to your manhood,
but i made sure that your gun
was loaded with blanks just in case.
I trust you, just...
not that much.
Did clark know about this?
You can't be serious.
Clark would never in a million years
risk what needed to be done.
He's led a different life
than we have, hasn't he?
I can't expect him
to know me like you do.
The places that i had sunk to,
the depths you must have
had to go to bring me back.
Thank you.
You proved it to yourself.
Even with your face in the gutter,
you still had the hero in your heart.
You saved my life.
Both the myth...
and the man.
What was that about?
I've seen that look before,
usually right before
you sock me in the jaw.
Tempted. But if you're unconscious,
you can't answer any questions like
who the hell was that dragon lady?
She was a psycho ex-girlfriend
who watched "fatal attraction"
too many times.
What am i, the bunny?
You really need to take a dip in
the sane-chick pool.
That dress...
that was a bigger red scare
than cold war russia.
Although, i thought
you wore it pretty well.
But...
you never should have been dragged
into this mess i made
of my life, and...
i'm sorry.
Was the mess so bad...
that cleaning it up seemed harder
than throwing it all away?
I saw the video.
That's enough to send anyone
on a binge.
Why didn't you come talk to me?
Pride.
Fear.
And...
regret.
The truth is, i've fighting my demons
for so long i just...
wanted this war to end.
And you felt...
like there was nothing in life
worth fighting for?
I never felt that way
when i was with you.
I mean...
i just, i think what i mean is i...
i lost sight of...
what was good in my life.
I know things between you and me
have changed, right?
Some things haven't changed.
Ollie, i will always
be here for you.
And if you forget that again...
i will knock you out.
Now, i believe there's
a certain birthday
tradition we have to uphold.
Ready to get your ass kicked?
I'm ready.
I've got to stop giving out keys.
I take it jor-el knew something
about the alien assassin.
He recognized her. It turns out
the symbol tattooed on her shoulder
is her family crest.
Her name's alia.
She's kandorian.
I thought kandor exploded
with the rest of krypton.
So did i. But jor-el said if she's here,
there may be others.
And they'll have each left
a kryptonian symbol
marking their arrival.
We better start looking.
We can use watchtower
to run a search algorithm that
would cross-reference all the satellite
images with my kryptonian lexicon.
In other news, oliver's back.
It seems like more than
just a cooling off. What happened?
Maybe the scam artist
really did a number on him.
Or he just needed to get
some perspective.
Found one.
Alia definitely didn't come alone.
I heard you were back.
You do know, you look absolutely
ridiculous in that, right?
And i got a great tailor. Hook you up
with a little color maybe.
Nice to see you finally discovered
something worth living for after all.
Yeah. More like
a rediscovery, actually.
You've done a hell of a job
keeping the world safe on your own.
I'm here to help you now.
Good.
Something tells me...
soon the world will need
all the help we can get.
Synchro : Flolo
For SeriesSub.com