Previously on "smallville"...
bless me, father, for i have sinned.
I have hurt many people...
- that i care about.
- No more than three tablets a day.
They can be highly addictive.
Please, for your own
good, get out of here now!
I put up with years of your taking
someone else's side over mine...
first clark and then davis?
Marrying you was the
biggest mistake of my life.
There is a savior among us.
Until you fulfill your destiny,
he won't have his great
challenge to overcome.
You were destined to kill each other.
Sorry about being the
invisible best friend lately.
Just when i thought i'd hit my fill
of high-maintenance men,
i take a job from oliver.
Watchtower is officially online.
There is something
about being around you
that seems to calm
the murderer inside me.
Will you stay with me?
We all have our inner demons...
... but we must learn to control them.
Davis, is everything okay?
Sorry if i woke you.
i had another one.
It's just a dream.
You know you're safe with me.
Could you come down
anyway? I need to see you.
Of course. I'll be down right away.
You know, this isn't exactly the
typical response to a bad dream.
Most people just get a night-light.
I wanted to surprise you.
It's beautiful.
But i don't remember ever seeing
a box of candles down here or flowers.
There weren't any.
Davis, we talked about this.
- You can't leave the basement.
- I was careful.
I know how much you're risking by
helping me. I only wanted to thank you.
I don't need thanks. I
need to able to trust you.
I won't do it again. I'm sorry.
You've helped me when no one else would.
Well, friends help each other, right?
Friends help you move. They
take you to the airport.
You can't think that's
really all this is.
Okay, so maybe it was a 9.9
on the richter scale of favors,
but that doesn't
change our relationship.
We met in a flurry of
smoking ash, burnt-out cars,
people freaking out,
but for a moment there,
it felt like everything
disappeared except us.
Those feelings haven't changed.
I do care about you, davis.
- But...
- Stay.
Please.
Without you, the man that
i want to be doesn't exist.
Davis, is that blood?
What did you think was gonna happen?
No!
Smallville 820 "Beast"
Synchro : Flolo Transcript : YYets.net
For seriessub.com
you okay?
You can usually make
cappuccinos blindfolded.
Yeah, i just didn't get my full
seven hours of sleep last night.
And judging from the look on your face,
you didn't come here
to join me for pancakes.
Tess named davis the serial killer.
She devoted the whole front page
of today's paper to the story.
Headlines can't hurt
davis now that he's dead.
That's the thing, chloe. I'm starting
to believe that davis is still alive.
Come on, clark. We both watched him die.
- Oliver buried the body.
- But it says in this article
they found one of bruno mannheim's
thugs in a dumpster, torn apart,
the same way that doomsday
dismembered his victims.
That body was probably there for weeks.
The murder happened after davis died.
I love a good ghost story
just as much as the next girl,
but there has to be a
more logical explanation
than the resurrection
of an alien monster.
There could be a copycat killer.
Chloe, he's come back
from the dead before.
Not from meteor rock.
Look, clark, i understand why you're
paranoid. Davis was sent here to kill you.
I mean, that would make anyone believe
there were monsters under their bed.
It doesn't change the fact
that davis is a murderer.
But, clark, davis is dead,
and the only thing that's keeping
him alive in your mind is fear.
Let him go.
Gentlemen, luthorcorp is going green, and i
certainly don't want all the old-money investors
to think we're wasting all of
their money on hemp bracelets, so...
we could send some cameras into
the geothermal energy facility.
It's innovative. It's profitable.
Okay, perfect. Call tess.
Arrange a press release.
Nothing screams "photo op" like a
10-mile hole in the ground, right?
Hey, oliver, um, can
we talk for a quick sec?
not the greatest time
right now, actually.
I wouldn't ask if it wasn't important.
Okay. All right.
Gentlemen, excuse me.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry to barge in on your lunch...
yeah, jimmy, listen, those
guys aren't my frat brothers.
- I'm here on business.
- Yeah, i know. I know.
Real quick.
I was hoping that you could
spot me 600 bucks, stat.
My mechanic called a code
blue on my alternator.
Well, you work here. What are they
paying you, in shirley temples?
They, uh... they let me go.
Cutbacks. I mean, you know how that is.
I do.
That's why i'm pretty sure it's not
your car that needs the fix, buddy.
You think that i'm lying?
I got three bus transfers to prove it.
Listen, i know a really great place you
can go to, get back to being yourself.
It's very discreet, staff's
very supportive, food's great.
Now, if you're worried about
paying for your treatment, don't...
'cause i can take care
of that for you, okay?
Great.
You gonna drive me there, too?
'cause my car doesn't work.
All right, hey...
... this road that you're on,
man, it is lonely, all right?
Now, if you need someone to
talk to, if you need a friend...
then i'm that guy, but, uh...
i'm not gonna give you
any money for drugs.
You know, i thought after everything
that happened that we could be friends.
But seeing you don't
trust me, i guess not.
You've been caring for davis
bloome in your basement?
Who else knows about this?
No one.
Not even oliver.
And i came to you directly
because he can't be trusted.
Chloe, he created our organization
to help with exactly
this kind of problem.
Oliver killed lex luthor.
And the stakes are too high to have
someone involved who can't think clearly.
Webmd doesn't exactly have a
lot of intergalactic infections,
so you were the only person
that i could turn to for a cure.
No, i'm glad that you came to me,
but there's only so much
i can do with a few cells.
You have his dna. What more do you need?
The subject in person.
That's not gonna happen.
I can run some preliminary
tests on the saliva.
But, chloe, are...
are you sure this is something
you want to take on alone?
I'll be fine.
Call me when you get the results.
- Who was that?
- Davis, you shouldn't be outside.
What's going on? Who
were you talking to?
Look at me. It's fine, okay?
Calm down. It's just a friend.
Now, you know you're not supposed to
be out of the house. What's happening?
Nothing helps.
I tried looking at photos of you, i
tried holding strands of your hair...
none of it works. This thing inside me,
it starts to claw its way
out as soon as you leave.
I can't be away from you now.
You are now metropolis'
own cornfield killer.
Now, i didn't tell you about this earlier
because i didn't want to upset you,
but the police are hunting
for you as we speak.
And by accepting your help, i put
you directly in their cross hairs.
Only if someone finds you, which they
won't because i won't let that happen.
But what about when the cops find you?
- What then?
- Then we leave.
We load up the car and never look back.
You've done more for me in a few weeks
than anyone's done in my entire life.
But i can't ask you to run away with me.
Then it's a good thing
you're not the one asking.
You wouldn't be able to say
goodbye to anyone, not even clark.
Can you do that?
Can you honestly tell me
that i am the most important
person in your life?
... i would do anything for you.
Well, then maybe this is
our chance to start over.
Let's leave smallville.
So, this is actually happening.
i just need to close a few accounts
and dead-end some paper trails first,
but we can be on the road by sundown.
... i don't know where
i'd be without you.
Oliver, i checked the quarry
where you said you buried davis.
- He's not there anymore.
- Your vision must be getting blurry.
I buried that body myself. I still have
the dirt under my fingernails to prove it.
I saw the grave. It's empty.
Why would someone move the body?
I don't think anyone moved it. It doesn't
look like anyone dug into the ground.
Looks like something...
clawed its way out.
Then that thing's still alive.
It went after chloe before.
I think it may try again.
Have you warned her yet?
She thinks i'm being paranoid.
Paranoid?
She knows he's obsessed with her, right?
Which is why i need you to find
her. Take her someplace safe.
I need to head to the fortress, see
if i can find a way to send doomsday
to a place he can't hurt anyone again.
No need to pack your parka.
I can tell you how to conquer the beast.
Kick his ass, clark.
Get this thing out of our
lives once and for all.
You want me to kill him.
No. I need you to kill him.
We all do. You're the only one who can.
That doesn't make it right.
I'd still be taking a life.
You'd be saving thousands, clark.
The only way any of us are
ever gonna be safe again
is if doomsday is destroyed... for good.
Doomsday is my problem,
and i will handle it.
Just, please, take care of chloe.
I'm down to my last card, emil,
and i really don't want to play it,
so please take another
look at the samples.
There has to be a cure.
His nuclei are in a
constant state of mutation.
I tried to destroy a cell,
and somehow, it got stronger.
You said you wanted
to see him in person.
I mean, how 'bout i bring
him down to your lab?
Frankly, i don't want
him anywhere near me.
He's not always a monster.
I mean, something is keeping
him from transforming.
Well, sometimes, dramatic
changes to the body
are caused by intense emotions...
love, hate...
obsession.
Which is why my presence
stops him from morphing.
Chloe, this creature
puts us all in danger.
- We need to warn people.
- You don't want to do that.
You betray me, you betray davis,
and you sure as hell don't
want to be on his bad side.
Fine.
But if you do have this power
over him, then it's all on you.
You're the only cure.
Were you just talking to someone?
Just one of my patients.
Have you heard from oliver lately?
Not since he asked me to hack into a
stream of transmissions from tehran,
and considering the fact that,
farsi isn't exactly my strong suit,
i should probably get
back to translating.
Chloe, davis is alive.
I have proof, and i need to find him.
Well, i'm sure that when he
resurfaces, we'll hear about it.
He has a habit of crashing
his way onto the 6:00 news.
Well, i intend to find him and bring
him to the fortress before that happens.
I got a faint signal from the console,
and i found the crystal that
brainiac used to release zod.
Okay, putting aside my serious
distrust of all things brainiac,
how is the crystal gonna help?
It's gonna open up a
portal to the phantom zone.
Clark, you can't send davis there.
Chloe, he has killed over 50
people. He put jimmy in the hospital.
- There's nothing more i can do for him.
- I'm talking about you.
I mean, what if, when you open
the portal, it sucks you in.
You once told me if
there was no other choice,
that you hoped i would put
the good of the world first.
Exactly. And losing you
is not good for the world.
It's a risk i have to take.
Okay, then maybe i can help.
I've been hearing about a string
of suspicious murders in alaska.
Now, i didn't pay much attention to them
because they weren't trademark doomsday...
it's okay. It's a lead. I'll find him.
Good luck.
So, you're stealing
money from chloe now.
I guess your car really
does need those repairs.
It's just a loan.
I'm gonna pay it back.
Holy...
oh, what the hell?
Hey, you okay?
Aside from being snatched
by a crazed serial killer?
Yeah, i'm great.
Any idea who did this?
Not to sound like a broken
record, but it was davis bloome.
- Where the hell are we?
- Looks like the talon basement.
My god, what's he done with chloe?
Never hurt chloe.
She, uh...
she saved me.
No way.
Now, chloe might be a sucker for
the strange, but she's not crazy.
Bit of advice...
you really don't want
to upset me right now.
Yeah, trust me, i know.
I've seen your horns.
You give a whole new meaning
to the term "bridezilla."
You're the beast.
Hey, davis, it's me. I'm
just on my way home right now.
Chloe, hurry. I can feel myself changing.
Please get back here and stop it.
Chloe, stay away!
Is there someone there with you?
Some guys broke into your
apartment. I'm holding them here.
Why did you leave the basement?
Because i thought you were in danger.
Okay, you trust me, right?
So trust me on this and let them go.
As soon as we're out of smallville.
Just come home, chloe. Hurry.
I'll be there as soon as i can.
Why did you do it?
Come on.
Every killer's got a sob story.
You know, i hear that an
unhappy childhood, that's...
that's pretty popular.
You wouldn't understand.
Of course not, because you, uh...
you brooding types... you
guys are all so complicated.
Jimmy, come on, man. Chill out.
No!
No, that monster destroyed
my life and brainwashed chloe,
and he's trying to ruin hers, too!
You have no idea what
chloe really wants!
We have to be together.
Hey, man, look, i know what
it's like to jones after a girl.
Really, i do, but you can hold
on a little bit longer, okay?
- You have to. Chloe's on her way.
- Oh, i hope so.
I really do, because if she's not,
the only way that i can control
myself is if i kill one of you.
Then kill me...
because you've taken everything from me.
All that's left is scar tissue.
Jimmy, that's enough.
What are you, anyways? Because
you're sure as hell not human.
Stop talking.
Do you really think
chloe could ever love you?
Whatever lies that you told her...
she's gonna find out the truth
eventually, and when she does...
no, davis! Davis!
Chloe's never gonna forgive
you for that! You understand?!
Please!
Please.
You're right.
You mean too much to chloe.
It has to be you.
I'm sorry.
Davis, don't do this, please.
Please, no!
Where's chloe?!
What are you gonna do to me, clark?
Oh, my god.
Was davis holding jimmy in the basement?
They're lucky to be alive.
Jimmy, i'm so sorry.
Whatever you do, chloe...
- stay away from that monster.
- Let's go.
You know, chloe, i thought
about calling the police.
Instead, i figured i'd give
you a chance to explain yourself
before i let them haul you off to
prison for harboring a serial killer.
I shouldn't have left davis here alone.
This is all my fault.
When did you become
one the bad guys, huh?
For whatever reason, i calm the
beast inside him. He needed me.
He needed you.
So, the needs of the cornfield killer outweigh
the needs of the rest of the world. Is that it?
- It's complicated.
- No, it's complicated, yeah.
That's the same thing your
psychopathic boyfriend told me.
Look, either i keep him with
me or let innocent people die.
Oh, come on...
if you really believed that, you would have handled
things a little bit differently, don't you think?
Instead, what do you do? You cook him dinner,
you fluff his pillow, you rock him to sleep.
Okay, look, i understand what
it looked like from the outside,
but trust me, i had the
whole thing under control.
You didn't have anything under
control! Speaking as davis' next victim,
i can tell you, your
plan was seriously flawed!
How did you think this
was gonna end, chloe?
I'll find him, okay? I'll fix this.
No. You won't.
I think you've done enough. We'll
let clark handle it from here.
Wait, oliver.
Where is clark?
Well, he took davis.
He's finally gonna finish this.
I don't care if this place
trapped me once before.
You want to throw down
with me, good luck.
I didn't come here looking for a
fight. This fortress can help you.
It's all that's left of our planet.
How did a piece of krypton get here?
My father created it using
kryptonian technology.
It'll send you to a world
where you don't have to
hide who you are any longer.
A world without chloe?
No, you better have a plan
"b" because i'm not losing her.
If you truly cared about
her, you would let her go.
You got it all wrong, clark.
She chose to protect me.
It was her idea for us to
leave smallville forever.
Chloe would have done that for anyone.
She believes in second chances.
She doesn't actually
have feelings for you.
Why? Because of what i am?
I didn't want this, clark.
I even killed myself to try to
escape this life, but the darkness...
it doesn't come out when chloe's around.
She makes me...
human.
What happens when that changes?
It won't.
Look, she is my chance to be happy.
Why can't my own kryptonian
brother let me have that?
I'm sorry, davis. I was wrong.
We're not brothers.
I don't want to hurt you, davis.
Don't worry. You can't.
If i go, i'm taking you with me.
Chloe, what are you doing?
I can't let you do this.
This is the right choice, chloe.
Trust me.
Trust you? Clark, the only
reason why you won't kill him
is because you don't
want blood on your hands.
I can't believe you
were willing to force him
into a life of hell for all of eternity.
I know you better than anyone.
I can't let you do this.
You would never forgive
yourself for giving up on him.
Tell me that your search
team has a read on that beast.
I have people on every
continent, jimmy, but so far, no.
No castle to storm.
Sorry.
You know, i'm not sure the beast you
need to be fighting's out there, jimmy.
I think maybe, uh... maybe it's in here.
Look, if this is another attempt to
turn me into the poster boy for rehab,
cancel the photo shoot,
'cause i'm not interested.
I didn't call you here for a lecture.
Just this.
It's the money you asked for...
for your car.
Forget it.
i don't need your handout.
Oh, it's not a handout.
It's your first paycheck.
Let me guess... got 12
steps attached to it.
Well, only if you decide not to
take the elevator to your office.
The truth is, there's
an opening on my staff,
and something tells me
you'd be perfect for it.
I ran a little background check on you.
It seems to me there's
more to your story than
you write on your cover letter.
Unfortunately, what
you see is what you get.
I'm a mediocre photographer
turned failed bartender.
I don't remember seeing a job
posting for that on careerbuilder.com.
I don't know, jimmy. Everybody
knows you take great action shots.
What i didn't realize
until recently was,
when called upon, you're pretty
damn good in action, as well.
You make it sound like
i'm some kind of hero.
Trust me, i'm not.
I wouldn't be so sure.
You figured out davis bloome's
serial-killer secret before any of us did.
You took on the beast all
by yourself. It takes guts.
You got good instincts, jimmy.
- That's enough for me.
- Yeah. Thanks to those instincts,
my life is really awesome these days.
Well, if you don't like it, change it.
Why don't you start
by accepting my offer?
What's the catch?
No, no, no catch. No catch,
just work, and a lot of it.
It's a full-time gig.
What do you say?
If you're looking for chloe,
you're wasting your time, clark, but
i guess that's what
you do best, isn't it?
She's gone, man. She
doesn't want to be found.
If there's anyone who can make
themselves invisible, it's chloe.
Davis must have done something to her.
Chloe would never have lied
to me if she weren't trapped.
Either that or she just can't
resist tall, dark, and doomsday.
Besides, davis isn't a
monster when he's around her.
- He's got real feelings for her.
- Whatever his feelings are for her
chloe would never care about him.
Clark, she sent you on a
wild-goose chase to alaska
when she was hiding that
psycho killer in the basement.
Take it from a guy who spent $10 billion
on a merger with the girl that got away.
You don't always
choose who you fall for.
The chloe you're talking
about does not exist.
She'd never choose
davis over her friends.
Well, people change, clark.
Maybe it's time you did, too.
You should have killed that
thing when you had the chance.
Clark, i know you
want to save everybody.
But eventually, you're gonna
have to make the tough decisions.
It's what heroes do.
Who is this?
Clark, it's chloe.
I just wanted to let
you know that i'm okay.
Where are you?
Davis and i are gone, but please don't
try and find us, okay? We're fine.
You think that you're safe, chloe, but
you aren't. You are not safe with him.
I'm sure everyone's fitting me
for a straightjacket right now,
but, clark, i do know what i'm doing.
And i knew that if i told you any sooner
that you would have found
a way to stop me, so...
look, everything i've ever done,
right or wrong, i did for you.
By running away?
Admit it, chloe. You
have feelings for davis.
That's why you're protecting him.
Clark, i'm protecting you.
I meant what i said.
Condemning davis to a life as that
monster is worse than killing him.
But what about you, chloe?
Chloe, i'm gonna spend
every second looking for you.
I will find a way to save you.
Clark, you're not here
to save one person.
You're here to save all of us.
And you think sacrificing
yourself will help me do that.
Chloe, you're wrong.
You're wrong, chloe.
I must have thrown a
million green rocks away,
and i have never really saved you.
Now i can.
Chloe, listen to me. This is your
life that we're talking about.
Don't do this.
If there's one lesson
i've learned from you,
it's that choosing the greater
good is never a sacrifice.
You said that road trips
give you a sweet tooth, so...
Thank you.
We better get moving. We want
to hit the border by morning.
Let's disappear.
For Seriessub.com