Mr. Luthor.
You received another one, sir.
Thank you.
That's, uh, it for tonight.
Lana?
Take him down.
I can see why they want you.
Target acquired.
Smallville 714
Transcript : www.yyets.net/ swsub.com
Synchro : Flolo
www.SeriesSub.com
Lana?
Hey. I came as soon as i got your...
Oh, my god. What happened?
I don't know.
I came home and clark was gone.
He talked about going to the fortress.
Last time he went to the fortress,
jor-El trapped him in ice for a month.
Why would he chance
the big chill a second time?
We just found out that kara
moved in with lex at the mansion.
Clark was hoping that jor-El would give
her back her memories and her powers.
Before lex uncovers her secret.
He wanted to get up there fast, but he
needed something from the loft first.
I don't think he got
what he came in here for.
This key opens the portal
to the fortress.
How did you know that?
I kind of followed him there
a couple of years ago.
- The key's still here.
- Then he never made it to the fortress
So something must have stopped him.
Stay in the center of your cell.
Where am i?!
What is this?
Come out here.
Come out here and face me!
You just experienced
a 20% increase in charge
From the meteor rock lining your cell.
Do it again,
i'll ramp it up 50%.
You try for three,
i'm guessing 100% will kill you.
Whoever would have guessed
that skinny little patty swann
Was the author of those
alarmingly cryptic messages?
It's patricia.
Nice to see you, lionel.
The last time i saw you,
you and lex were both children.
And your father, virgil swann,
He adored the great outdoors.
Then he shut himself away inside
That dank, musty planetarium.
We both know that those
family get-Togethers
Weren't about
the great outdoors.
When dad died,
i inherited his estate.
After a long probate, i've recently
received all of his research.
He was obsessed with one subject
in particular...
A traveler from another galaxy
Who came to smallville
in a meteor shower.
A great scientist
with a vivid imagination.
My father wasn't the only one
who believed in the traveler.
Four powerful families
would gather every summer...
My dad, the queens,
the teagues, and you.
According to his journals, the group
formed a secret society...
Veritas.
Veritas... that's right,
our astronomy club.
You were preparing to welcome the traveler.
The group planned on sharing
the responsibility
Of keeping him safe
once he arrived.
But everyone died...
... except you.
Where are you going
with this?
You killed edward teague
And robert and laura queen.
And i am sure that you had
a hand in my father's death.
A pity his brilliance was lost on you.
I have proof.
I found evidence my father collected
and stored with his journals.
You wanted the traveler all for yourself...
For your own personal gain.
Turn over the son of krypton,
Or i will release the evidence
linking you to their murders.
The traveler from another galaxy,
A clandestine cabal,
a series of murders...
That's quite a story. You be careful
who you tell it to.
Don't test me, lionel.
Take me to the traveler now.
You haven't changed.
You're still that bossy
little girl you used to be.
But this time, patty,
You're swimming
way out of your depth.
Hope you like your room.
I only moved in last night,
and it already feels like home.
Thank you for letting me
stay here, lex.
Taking another look
at your alleged biography?
Yeah, i thought i'd give it another try.
I still don't feel like
i was ever this person.
Kara...
You should really consider having
the procedure we talked about.
I don't know. I mean,
i don't have my memory,
But i'm pretty sure
i don't like hospitals.
It would be done in my private clinic
By a team of the world's
top neurologists.
You said you trusted me.
Trust me now.
Let me help you.
Okay, lex.
I'll do it.
Good.
I'll pull my team together
as soon as possible.
Good night, kara.
We've been watching her
since she arrived, sir.
So far, nothing indicates she's anything
more than a pretty girl from minnesota.
I don't pay you to comment
on her appearance.
Besides,
looks can be deceiving.
Kara's agreed to do the procedure.
Sir, if i may,
we just started observing her.
Her mind may contain answers to
questions i've had for a very long time.
Now, i've waited long enough.
How soon can the lab be ready?
Tomorrow.
Keep an eye on her.
If she shows any sign
her memory is coming back,
Lock this place down.
Stop! You stop it now!
What the hell
are you doing?
I built that cell to contain him, not
for you to use as a torture chamber.
Mr. Luthor, you hired me because of
my experience with these freaks.
If anything happens to him,
anything at all,
Because of your appetite for cruelty,
You will be held responsible.
No.
Well, i don't agree with you.
Absolutely not.
Lionel.
I'll get back to you.
Lana. Miss sullivan.
I've got my people searching...
Discreetly, of course...
the government agencies.
If any of them are responsible
for taking clark,
- We'll know very soon.
- Maybe you could help.
Do you know what this is?
Believe it's an electrode.
Probably from a taser gun.
This is kryptonite.
We found it in the barn
after clark was taken.
As far as we know, everyone that knows
about clark's weakness is in this room.
It wasn't chloe,
and it wasn't me.
What about kara?
I told you and clark she'd been spending
time with lex. Now she's moved in with him.
- But her memory
- Might be coming back, little by little much.
Wouldn't take much.
Just a few simple words. Enough
For lex to work out clark's secret.
Oh, i'd hate to think that
My son is responsible for any of this.
This is clark's worst fear.
Wait a minute.
Lx dynamics.
Lx dynamics
has military contracts
Developing combat technologies.
I'll do some research,
See if any of it involves
electroshock or...
If he harms clark, i will kill him.
I'll deal with him, lana.
He's my son.
I want clark back safely
as much as you do.
I dug around for some
information on lx dynamics.
Lionel was right. Lex is having them build
experimental tasers for the military.
Actually, i've been wielding
my own shovel,
And i think i may have found
where clark is being held.
About a year and a half ago, luthorcorp bought
a abandoned airstrip just outside the city.
Now they've rebuilt the hangar.
Check out the construction manifest.
"Concrete reinforced plexiglas in a
ton of refined meteor rock"?
- Lex built another 33.1 lab.
- Wrong luthor.
According to all of these
records, this was all lionel.
Construction started around the same
time lionel found out clark's secret.
The department of water and power said they
turned the lights on for the first time two days ago.
Lionel's been planning
this kidnapping for months.
And if these specs are accurate,
the place is built like fort knox.
We need kara.
Chloe, kara can't help if she
doesn't have her powers back.
Clark was on his way to the fortress
of solitude to ask jor-El for help.
Now, maybe we can polar express
kara there ourselves.
The key... do you know how to use it?
If we can get her out of the
mansion, i can get her there.
She wanted to move in with lex. I don't
think it'll be easy getting her to leave.
Lex probably quadrupled his
security since she moved in.
We won't be able to get past
the mailbox.
I'm thinking something
a little more stealth.
When i was married to lex, he showed me
these escape passageways
He had built in case
of another home invasion.
So use his secret way out
to sneak in.
It's good to see a friendly face
from my childhood.
What brings you to smallville?
I'm rarely in metropolis, but i have
some business there,
And i remembered
you'd moved out here.
Well, i'm glad
you came by, patricia.
I have to admit,
I don't recall much
from when we were kids.
After getting caught
in that meteor shower,
The years leading up to it
became something of a fog.
You were so young, lex.
It must have been traumatizing.
I survived.
What about you?
Where did you disappear to?
I spent most of my life studying abroad.
When dad died,
i decided to stay in europe.
I always admired
dr. Swann's genius.
I was sorry to hear about his death.
Thanks, lex.
I'm doing my best
to carry on his legacy.
That's a beautiful locket
you're wearing.
Dad gave me this
right before he passed away.
I've worn it ever since.
Actually, i have a gift for you.
A child's painting?
It's your painting.
I was going through some
of my father's things, and
I found it.
You gave it to me
when we were kids.
Well, i guess i thought
i could romance you with my abc's.
It's an insignia...
From when our parents would get
together with the queens and the teagues.
Really?
I don't remember that.
That "v" was the symbol
for their astronomy club.
You must have seen it once
and copied it.
They called
themselves "veritas."
While we were off playing,
they were discussing
Secret things behind closed doors.
Do you know
what they talked about?
No idea.
But considering your father's
the last surviving member,
He can probably explain it all to you.
You should tell him i say hello.
Where did you find this?
Patricia swann visited me today.
Apparently i made it while i was still
learning my way around a paintbrush.
Well, if you're looking for some validation
of your artistic talent
As a child, it's a little late, isn't it?
Patricia told me
it's the symbol for veritas,
But she's not sharing
the whole story.
It's the misguided musings
of a few youthful idealists
With a little money and too much
time on their hands.
We took ourselves much too
seriously, i'm embarrassed to say.
What secret was so important that you
and your friends built a group around it?
Oh, think about it, lex.
Skull & bones, scroll & key, the delphic.
The rich have secret societies.
The others have poker nights.
Well, it seems life dealt your charter
members a poor hand.
Besides you, everyone else is dead.
Why'd you kill them?
Will you give it a rest, lex?
Let the whole business rest in peace.
Sorry, dad.
I can't do that.
Why don't you treat this sketch
for what it is?
A reminder of what you
could have become.
If you won't tell me,
i'm sure patricia will.
Yeah. He was just here.
He delivered your message.
I'm ready, patricia,
to make a deal.
Lex likes to keep his women
on a short leash.
Sounds more like a choke chain,
if you ask me. Let's get her out of there.
Okay, the passageways open up
onto a steep hill.
It's pretty far off the road. It's gonna
take us a while to climb up there.
If it means saving clark,
i'd climb mount everest.
Is she ready?
- Yes, sir. And so is the lab.
- Good. It's time to find some answers.
What happened?
- The feed's been cut.
- Lock this place down!
Now!
What are you doing?
Kara, you have to come with us right now.
We'll explain everything later.
Just trust us.
You're not getting out, you know.
I helped build this cage.
What do you want from me?!
I've seen a lot of terrible
things in your town.
How could a place called
smallville be filled with such
Death and destruction?
I think it has something
to do with you.
Maybe you want to reconsider
keeping me in this cage.
You work for the government?
I was head security for 33.1.
I've tracked down a lot
of meteor freaks, but you...
You're in a category all to yourself.
The government wouldn't know
what to do with you.
But i do.
Enjoy your stay... freak.
What is this place?
It's freezing in here.
It's clark's fortress.
We're way up in the north pole.
Right, fortress, north pole.
And how did we get here?
Through the portal.
Oh, and if there's a sudden
shift in weather,
Just get out of here
as fast as you can.
That's reassuring.
Hello?!
Jor-El?!
Who are you talking to?
Clark's in trouble.
Now, i know that your brother
started all of this,
But right now, the only way
we can help your son
Is if you restore kara's memory and powers.
Whatever jor-El is, i don't
think he's here right now.
Jor-El!
Out of all the planets
across the universe,
You decided to send
your only son to this one! To earth!
You trusted us to protect him!
Now, please, jor-El,
i need you to trust me!
I love your son!
He's in danger
and he needs our help!
Chloe, why are we
in the fortress?
We have to save clark.
Patricia.
My lawyers now where I am, lionel.
If you kill me,
they'll know who did it.
Of course. Is that the evidence?
My father raised me
to keep my word.
Before i hand this over,
i need to see him first.
You put him in a cage?
What i have done is fulfilled
my part of the agreement,
And i expect you to do the same.
Not yet.
I want to meet him face-To-Face.
I need to verify
he truly is the traveler.
I hope you've said
your goodbyes, lionel,
Because if he is the traveler,
Leaving with me right now.
Put her on the plane. When she's on
her way to europe,
return Mr. Kendiscreet
to his home. I'll take it from there.
That monster
isn't going anywhere.
- What are you doing?
- You rich people...
Your money makes you stupid.
Anyone can see that thing
is dangerous. It could kill somebody.
For all we know, it might be
a threat to national security.
Pierce, listen to me.
You know, in all the time
that i worked for lex,
Not once did he put the interests of a
meteor freak above the safety of the world.
He knew when to terminate a project.
But you...
You're not your son.
And i'm gonna terminate it for you.
You don't know what you're doing.
Clark kent is not a threat.
You really think after
everything that i have seen
That i'm just gonna let you and the
swann princess here just set him free?
He must be terminated.
No.
He's a human being, pierce.
You'd be committing murder.
It's nice having you back.
How could i have
ever forgotten you?
Here you go.
Somehow, i never pictured
the last son of krypton making coffee.
Just clark.
You know, my father thought
the world of you.
Dr. Swann was a great man.
I have something for you.
Dad's journal,
transcribed by his assistant.
It's actually the last of many
he kept throughout his life.
I want you to have it.
Thank you.
"The traveler will bring
great change to the earth."
All these prophecies
about the traveler.
I just hope i can live up to what
everyone thinks i'm supposed to be.
I've just met you,
And there's no doubt in my mind
That you're a force for good in this world.
What if that's not enough?
You're right, clark.
And there are some people
out there like lionel luthor
Who are willing to destroy
others to get to you.
Lionel had robert and laura queen's
plane sabotaged so it would crash.
He poisoned edward teague,
And i think he did
the same thing to my father.
- Why would he do that?
- They were all part of a group
Who swore to protect the traveler.
Lionel wanted you all for himself.
He killed all those people
because of me.
My father often reminded me that
despite the power of the sun,
It's always night on half
the planet.
For all the good you do,
there will always be darkness.
People who would kill you
Or abuse your power
for their own gain...
Lionel luthor's just one of many.
Clark, i wish you would
reconsider coming with me.
As long as lionel luthor
is alive, he's a threat to you.
I'll deal with lionel.
Then i'll take an apartment
in metropolis.
I want to be there for you.
Just like my father was.
Someday,
I hope to see the traveler
change the world.
Clark, i...
I'm... sorry.
I'm sorry that you had to be
locked in that cell, but
It was the only way i could
be sure you were safe.
Safe from what?
I got... i got these letters,
You see. They... they threatened...
To...
Kidnap you,
to take you away.
I didn't know who was sending them
until i met with patricia swann,
But i had no idea how many
people were involved or
How much they knew or what they
intended to do with you.
Why didn't you just tell me
there was danger? Lee my own decision.
If i told you, you would have rushed
out to search for your enemies.
I couldn't take that chance
that you might get hurt.
So instead you shoot me
with kryptonite tasers.
You trap me in a kryptonite cell.
Why would you even
build that thing?
Clark, you're not the only
kryptonian who's come here.
Your fellow travelers are
violent... extremely
Violent. I built that cell for them.
- Then why imprison me?
- Clark, son...
You're not my father!
I spoke to patricia. She told me
about the veritas murders.
The truth can be
very easily manipulated.
You would know that better than anyone,
lionel. You've been doing it for years.
I'm different now.
I'm a different man.
No, you're not.
Hey, cousin.
Need any help?
You've already done
more than enough.
I have something for you.
I was saving it till you got
your memory back.
Thanks for saving my life.
I didn't do it alone. I mean, if it
wasn't for chloe and lana,
Lex would have dissected
my brain by now.
I can't believe i trusted him.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You're not the only one
to be fooled by the luthors.
Lex and i used to be best friends.
And i thought lionel was my ally.
But it doesn't make
any sense.
I mean, lex tried to save me in detroit.
His father saved both of us in washington.
Lex and lionel are only capable
of doing the right thing if it benefits them.
I want to see the good in people, kara,
But i think the luthors
are a lost cause.
Why have we stopped?
Www.Seriessub.Com