Previously
on criminal minds...
police in dayton, ohio,
need our help with a serial rapist.
He was waiting for them
when they got home.
We need a female
undercover agent.
Think elle's ready
for it?
I'm good.
What's she doing
with her gun?
??? Easy, easy.
Fbi.
Get out
of the car!
???
I was... i was
just stopping
to look at my map.
Don't say
another word.
You're letting him
walk?!
The only reason
he's walking
is because
you panicked.
I'm supposed
to believe that
you've got my back?
The last time
you sent me home,
hotch,
you got me shot.
You've made
a lot of women very happy.
I didn't
let you walk.
Thank you.
Hey, lee.
[Gunshot]
I got your message.
Close the door.
This is william lee's
case file. Sit down.
The bureau has concluded
its internal investigation,
and they accept
your claim
that you went to lee's house
to confront him
and you defended yourself
when he attacked.
As your supervising agent,
i've ordered
a psychological status report.
After
the bureau's cleared me?
I don't need
a shrink, hotch.
It's up to me
to make that assessment.
You think i'm lying.
You know, you're not
a prosecutor anymore.
You're the only one
who knows what really
happened that night,
and i think you need
to be honest with yourself
since you've
got to live with it
for the rest
of your life.
I appreciate
your concern.
I'm fine.
Are you?
Yeah.
You're anxious,
you're on edge, you're nervous.
More than reid
or morgan?
Neither of them
confronted a suspect
and then shot
and killed him.
Yeah, because they
didn't find themselves
in the position
that they needed
to do so.
I've been doing this
long enough.
I know hypervigilence
when i see it.
Your first evaluation's
in an hour.
Not even one
ounce of sympathy.
???
You're the boss.
[Crow cawing]
Boy: None of us are safe.
That little boy,
he was only, like, 6.
Nobody ever
saw him again.
What happened
to him?
He was walkin'
alone in the woods,
and then, he stepped
in somethin' wet.
And when he looked closer,
he realized it was blood...
everywhere.
Then he heard somethin'
comin' from behind him.
Somethin'
comin' after him.
He kept lookin' behind him,
he didn't see
what was there,
but, whatever it was
just kept chasin' him.
And then, he ran
into this old man,
and when he tried
to ask for help,
the old man
just smiled back...
with sharp fangs,
drippin' with blood.
He tried to back away
from him,
but before he could,
he was tortured
and eaten.
By... by... by who?
That evil old man.
He watches us
all the time.
He just watches us
from that big, old
house on the hill,
the one that's...
haunted.
Why does he watch us?
'Cause he wants
to eat one of us.
He's just deciding
who's next...
next to be hunted
like a deer...
skinned...
eaten.
It's just
a matter of time.
Aah!
Nicholas faye
of ozona, texas,
was beaten to death
roughly 13 hours ago.
Blunt force trauma
to the head.
He's the second young boy
in ozona
to die the same death
in the last 2 months.
Local hunter found his body
in the woods.
The first victim's name,
robbie davis.
Are these boys
connected somehow?
Ozona's population's
roughly 2,500.
Everyone has
some kind of connection.
Well, if they weren't
linked before,
they most certainly
are now.
Both murdered
by the same offender.
Who's hunting children.
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:FRM@XXY
Sync:FRM@¾ÆÄÒ·¹´ü
CM S02E06
Morning.
A moment, sir?
What's up?
Agent greenaway
never showed
for her evaluation
last night.
You're kidding.
The notice came through
this morning.
I called 3 times,
left messages,
but she isn't
calling back.
Thank you.
Gideon:
Doesn't look good.
No. Let's be honest.
We know exactly
what it looks like.
Elle let emotion
get in her way.
And it goes against
everything we stand for.
So don't you
make the same mistake.
She's innocent
until proven guilty.
I'll go to texas.
You find elle.
[Cell phone rings]
[Ring]
Gideon: Plato once wrote,
"we can easily forgive
a child who is
afraid of the dark.
"The real tragedy
of life
is when men
are afraid of right."
You guys hear
elle was cleared?
Self-defense.
So it was
a good shoot.
She hit what
she was aimin' for.
That's not what i meant.
I know.
If they cleared her,
how come
she's not here with us?
Or hotch?
Focus on the case.
Ozona police
and autopsy report
for nicholas faye
and robbie davis.
Well, the bludgeoning
could suggest
frustration or rage.
With no apparent
sexual motivation.
That's rare when
the victims are this young.
This unsub seems
to be taking pleasure
from the kill itself.
So if it's not sexual,
what's the
significance of
targeting young males?
Most serial killers
prey upon specific types
to carry out
their fantasies of revenge.
[Cell phone rings]
Bundy killed women
that looked like
an ex-girlfriend
who jilted him.
Dahmer claimed
that schoolyard harassment
fed into his fury.
Ok, so then maybe
these kids
represent someone
who victimized the offender.
Like a young male
from his past.
Maybe a bully,
a older brother,
someone
who abused him.
No, that's unlikely.
They just found
another body.
11-year-old girl.
Why would the victimology
just suddenly change?
Maybe the girl
wasn't the target.
Maybe she
just got in the way.
Or the sex of his victim
isn't significant.
The pace he's killing
certainly indicates
a velocity of change.
We can surveil
every kid in ozona.
How are we supposed
to keep 'em all safe?
Enforce a curfew?
Children shouldn't
have to worry
about something like that.
Tell me about it.
The woods were
the only thing
i was afraid of
when i was a kid.
Seriously?
Thought you grew up
in a small town.
Yeah, surrounded
by woods.
Bummer for you.
Yeah.
Only thing i was
afraid of was the dark.
Some of us still are.
When we land,
morgan and reid go
to the new crime scene.
The little girl.
I'll look at the scene
where nicholas faye was found.
This is where
he dumped the body.
This isn't
a dump site.
Murder happened
right here.
Autopsy report indicates
no signs of a struggle.
Poor little guy,
never had a chance.
So far
into these woods,
no one
could hear him scream.
Exactly how his killer
wanted it.
The last 2 months,
we've lost more children
in this town
than we have
in my whole lifetime.
The others
were car accidents.
The residents
are terrified.
Got an 8-year-old
myself.
Victims
knew their killer.
They followed
him to this spot.
What makes you
think that?
The kids went this deep
in the woods
because
they trusted him.
He stashed his weapon
here beforehand,
which means we're
looking for someone
intelligent, methodical.
Methodical?
Bashed the kid's
head in,
looks like a moment
of rage to me.
I agree.
That's what's confusing.
Doesn't make sense.
This is just
a quarter mile
from where the 2 boys
were killed.
Bludgeoned to death
the same way.
Not entirely true.
I found some markings
on her scalp
that indicated
that that psycho
beat her post-mortem.
Suggests the unsub
is getting more brazen.
He's getting brazen,
all right.
I've bagged 3 children
in the last month.
Now he's spending
more time with the victims
even after death.
He had to know he wasn't
gonna be interrupted,
but how?
How could he
be so sure?
The forest goes
for miles and miles,
but nobody goes
walkin' in it
unless they're
lookin' to kill.
Or hunt.
In which case,
you don't want to be
on the trail.
Reid, whoever killed
these children
is very familiar
with this area.
In my opinion,
he probably lived
in ozona his whole life.
It could be someone
you know,
or it could be a stranger
you pass at the grocery store.
It's vital that we keep
our eyes open
and our children close.
Now, as ozona's
guidance counselor,
i can only help
your children
with the aftermath,
but our police department
is working
with the fbi,
gathering information
on the case.
To elaborate on that,
agent jason gideon.
We want you to know
we're doing
everything we can
to find the person
responsible.
Until we do, there are
a number of precautions
that you'll need to take,
so let me go over
some of them with you.
First and foremost...
it's something we call
the buddy system.
That means you always
go everywhere with a friend.
That's right
because bad men
and women
are more likely
to talk to us
only when we're
by ourselves.
Jj: We don't know what
these guys look like yet.
Might be someone you know.
Yes, sweetheart,
you got a question?
There was this little girl
once on the news,
who just got grabbed
right in front
of her house.
Could that happen
to us?
Nothing's gonna happen
to any of you
as long as you remember
this buddy system, ok?
Any more questions?
Did you ever
find his hat?
Gideon:
Excuse me?
This is
nicholas faye's mother.
The red one
that i put on him?
He had it on
when he left.
I'm sorry, mrs. Faye.
We haven't.
Mandatory curfew at 5 p.m.
Just make sure you know
where your children are.
You just gotta
move fast.
Old man finnegan
can't eat you
if he can't
catch you.
I want to go home.
Come on.
Just ring the guy's bell.
Why don't you?
I already did
when i was, like, 5.
[Loud thuds]
Oh, no, it was
just the wind.
Now, come on.
It'll be fun.
Not if he catches me.
Come on, it'll be easy.
Just ring and run.
We'll be right here.
Yeah. Now go.
Go.
Go, go.
[Crow cawing]
Henry?
Simon?
Hotchner.
Hey, hotch,
what's up?
I went to her apartment
to talk to her,
but she was leaving
with an overnight bag.
So she's running.
I don't know.
I hope not.
I'm following her.
All right,
keep me posted.
Just wait for me up front.
No wandering.
Ok, dad.
It's too scary to let 'em
out of your sight.
I know.
Can i have
your attention, please?
Good afternoon.
I want to make
something clear.
Due to the velocity
of change,
we predict
this offender
could try to strike
again anytime.
His confidence builds
with every attack.
Look for someone
physically fit,
shy, kind disposition,
someone you may trust
with your own child.
Because the killer
targets kids,
he may be small
himself.
And though we keep
referring to
this unsub as "he,"
do not rule out
a woman.
Excuse me.
Chief?
You're gonna
want to hear this.
My son matthew never
came home today.
Morgan: Here we go.
When was he
last seen?
His teacher saw him
in the parking lot
after school.
Search team.
Deputy: Yes, sir.
Timmy, charlie.
The grid
at the school zone.
If the boy was abducted,
then this area would be
the most secluded nearby.
Morgan: So jones
can put his guys
at the gas station...
ma'am, here,
sit down.
Thank you.
Hey. So how old
is matthew?
Uh, he turned 8
in august.
I have a niece
that's 8.
Very resourceful
at that age.
What are you
thinkin' about
over here?
Nothing.
Well, you look
awful upset
to be thinkin'
about nothin'.
You look like
you have a secret.
Secret's important.
Is it
about your brother?
Honey, is that true?
Are you hidin' somethin'?
You want to protect him,
right?
That's what
a brother's for.
Matty said he was
just gonna ring the doorbell
at the haunted house...
on the hill.
Finnegan's place.
Who's finnegan?
This old guy who lives
in that house.
Forever. Kind of
a local legend.
Ghost story.
Reid: About?
Supposedly,
he watches the kids
from his window...
hunts 'em,
skins 'em,
eats 'em.
Standard.
Kids have been
tellin' that story
since i was a kid.
Morgan: Why haven't we
heard about this?
Fables are often sparked
by an ounce of truth.
We should exhaust
every possibility.
I'm sorry, dad.
You've been
following me.
What's going on?
Elle, i'm listening.
Ok.
I really wanted to be
a part of the team.
You were.
But when i needed
thteam,
i was all alone.
I was alone
in the one place
that i have the right
to feel safe,
and that's my home.
Just like
those women in ohio
who were attacked
had a right to feel safe
in their homes.
Does that justify
taking the law
into your own hands?
What makes you say
that i have?
Because you're here
confessing your sins.
You know i don't have
any evidence,
and you know how quickly
i'd arrest you if i did.
So what are we
gonna do about it?
Sure looks
like a haunted house.
Gideon:
Morgan, you and jones
take the front.
Reid and i will cover
the outbuildings.
Come on.
[Creaking]
Mr. Finnegan!
Ah!
Upstairs is clear.
Finnegan's not here.
Yeah, neither
is the missing boy.
Electricity's out.
I know.
Maybe he's been away.
No. His paper
was delivered today.
So finnegan
was here earlier.
Yeah. Question is,
where is he now?
Stairwell.
Fbi. Don't move.
Boy: Ok.
Matthew?
Yes.
No.
Are you hurt?
I didn't want
the old man
to find me.
It's all right.
No one's gonna harm you.
Come on. Let's go.
Reid:
Did you get anything?
Garcia: Only that finnegan's
house on the hill
is like the bates motel
of ozona, texas.
Yeah, we heard
the legend.
Reid, seriously,
people that go into that house
supposedly never come out.
Spooky.
Garcia, could you please
pretend not to enjoy
that rumor so much,
since i've actually
entered the house.
Sensitive. Sorry.
Besides, local police
say there are no reports
of that
actually happening.
This is true.
All complaints filed
were false alarms.
But then there
is that matter
of his missing wife.
Wife? What wife?
When did she go missing.
Almost 50 years ago.
No record of her
ever being found?
I got two words
for you, my friend...
rear window.
That guy probably
chopped that lady up
into delicious,
bite-size little pieces.
[Footsteps creaking]
Think about it.
She may never
have left.
She may still be
in the house.
Garcia, i'm sitting here
in the dark alone. Thanks.
While you're waiting
for a potential murderer
to come home?
Kinda dangerous.
Kinda sexy.
???
You're having
all the fun.
I wish
i was there.
Aah!
You really are afraid
of the dark.
I'm workin' on that.
Morgan: You should
work a little harder.
My deputy got the boy
home safe.
Turns out the poor kid
got spooked by a tree branch.
This whole town's
on edge.
Maybe that's why
finnegan's in the wind.
Hey,
that's interesting.
The unsub
didn't use a gun.
Bet he knows
every trail in ozona.
Finnegan's
an avid hunter.
Why didn't he use a...
robbie davis.
First victim.
"Sarah p."
Sarah peterson,
right?
I guess finnegan
brought the kids
back here first
before baitin' 'em
into the woods.
But why wouldn't he
get rid of the evidence?
Considers them trophies.
When this is
all said and done,
i'd like to hang
his head on my wall.
[Crow cawing]
Sheriff called
the search off.
We located the boy.
He's home
safe and sound.
What about
old man finnegan?
???
First blush,
it looks like
joseph finnegan
died
of natural causes.
His heart
probably gave out
while he
was setting this.
Yeah, karma's
a bitch.
Those coyotes
were gnawing on him
for a week.
Before the second
and third murders
ever happened.
This area's
off the traveled path.
It's a wonder anyone
discovered him at all.
Is it?
Those leaves didn't
cover him up
by themselves.
He's right. The deputy
may not have been
the first to find him.
But our only suspect's
been cleared.
Square one?
No.
If finnegan's been dead
all this time,
who's livin'
in his house?
Let's go.
Here's a question...
if a tree
falls in the forest,
does it make a sound
if there's nobody
there to hear it?
What the hell
are you readin' over there?
I was just thinking.
The unsub found
finnegan's corpse
in a lightly traveled
part of the woods,
and no one else knew.
So he was able
to use this house,
an no one
was the wiser.
Actually,
i was referring
to finnegan's wife.
What are you
talking about?
She was rumored missing,
perhaps killed
almost 50 years ago,
when, in actuality,
she left finnegan
for another man.
He writes about it
in his journals,
how he would
look out the window
on a daily basis
to see if she
would come home.
She never did.
He never recovered.
He ended up turning
into a recluse
that people in town
misunderstood.
Found
somethin'.
Come here.
Provisions, delivered
by the church
to every elder's
doorstep,
each one dated
after finnegan died.
So the unsub
ate everything.
Almost everything.
Unopened bowls
of creamed spinach
thrown into the trash,
each one wrapped
with duct tape.
One with each tray.
So we're lookin'
for a guy
who really, really
hates spinach.
Who doesn't?
Ritualized, meticulous,
organized.
He would eat
with the same particulars.
Full prints.
[Cell phone rings]
Have garcia run 'em
for a match.
[Ring]
Hotch.
It's about elle,
isn't it?
I don't know.
You know, i talked
to her in ohio.
Reid,
we all talked to her.
No, l... l... i talked
to her before.
I went to her room
one night,
and she was drinking.
She almost died.
I'd be drinkin', too.
Why the woods, jj?
Hmm?
Your fear.
You said
it was of the woods.
Uh, i used to be
a camp counselor
as a teenager
in the woods
up in vermont,
and the night shift...
tuck the girls in,
turn off the lights,
you know,
the typical drill.
Everything seemed fine,
all the kids were asleep.
You know, nothing seemed
out of the ordinary...
until i noticed
that there was some blood
on the hallway floor,
so i followed
the blood trail
out to the camp director's
cabin,
walked up to his bed,
and he was just lying there
underneath his covers...
dead.
Someone stabbed him.
I ran out of there
so fast.
Out the door,
down the hall.
I just remember it
being really dark.
Once i got to the door,
there was
another counselor there.
I guess she heard me scream.
They caught the caretaker
on his way to town.
I guess he still
had the knife on him.
Anyway, i guess
that's probably
when i decided
i didn't like the woods.
You're serious.
No.
[Scoffs]
No, i...
you fell for that?
Come on, i don't know
why i'm afraid of the woods.
I just... i am.
Why is he still afraid
of the dark?
Yeah, reid, why are you
still afraid of the dark?
Because of the inherent
absence of light.
[Cell phone rings]
Oh.
Jj, that was pretty good.
Just remember,
paybacks are a bitch.
I'm shakin'.
Yeah.
I love o relationship.
We hardly need words.
Hey, girl, you got
somethin' good for me?
I pulled
two sets of prints
off those food trays.
Two?
One belonging
to a child.
Ok, but which one
of the victims?
Why don't you coordinate
with the ozona coroner's
office for a match?
Oh, baby,
that's so yesterday.
I already have
the minions working on it.
In the meantime,
your intrepid hacker
found you a match
to the other set
in the database.
His name
is james charles.
He's a local
guidance counselor.
Yeah, he
a local guidance counselor,
helping us
on this case.
You're kidding.
His address
is 3725 briarwood lane.
I know exactly
how to find him, garcia.
Thanks.
Call gideon.
We just found our unsub.
You sure about this?
Charles?
Born and raised
in ozona,
knows the territory,
works with children.
Highly organized,
slight in stature,
injected himself
into the investigation.
Anything happen
the last 6 months
that would have
changed his life?
His wife walked out
on him and his kid.
There's
your trigger.
Guys,
he's on the move.
Mr. Charles!
Don't do it!
Hold it!
Uh!
Why you runnin'?
???
What's this?
What's this?!
What's so important
about the hat?
???
Here's the deal.
I could stand here
and tell you
what i think you were
doin' in finnegan's house
for the last two weeks,
or you could do us
all a favor.
Sign a confession,
maybe get
a little somethin'
taken off your time.
What do you say?
I never stepped
inside finnegan's house.
That's not really
the answer
i was lookin'
for, james.
See, fact is,
we got your fingerprints
inside the house
all over the trays
of food.
Of course, you did.
I delivered 'em
every week.
It's true. He started
workin' at the food bank
after his wife left.
Fingerprints aren't
all we have.
What are you doin'
with nicholas faye's hat?
Hmm?
Maybe you were tryin'
to dispose of it.
Or were you so proud
of your keepsake,
you just wanted to find
a nice safe place
to hide it?
How these last 6 months
been for you, james?
Not too good, huh?
Oh, no, your whole life
is fallin' apart,
isn't it?
Oh, yeah,
you gotta be feelin'
a loss of control,
sense of abandonment,
and i would guess, uh...
little impotent maybe.
Come on, man,
give me somethin'.
Why did your wife
leave you?
What happened, james?
She get bored?
I mean, you don't seem
all that exciting to me.
She start feeling
a little uninspired?
Hey, you're not
a minuteman, are you?
Oh, that's what it is.
You're done before
she even gets started.
She left you
for another man
who has... ok!
James,
that was exciting!
Did i hit a nerve?
I want to go home.
Oh, you want
to go home?
Yeah.
Well, i'm sorry.
That ain't
about to happen,
so why don't you
come over here
and sit your ass down?
I said sit down!
I'm done
talkin' to you.
I will tell you what
you are done doin',
you hear me?
[Cell phone rings]
Yeah.
What'd you find out?
The second set of prints
didn't match
any of the victims.
So there might be
a fourth victim
still out there.
Check surrounding towns
for missing children reports
and get
right back to me.
You know,
it's bad enough
his mother left.
Now his father's
in custody,
and we gotta take
the poor kid
into child services.
It's the law.
So's jaywalking,
but i don't have
to like it.
Good afternoon,
this is agent jareau
with the fbi.
We're going to be
picking up
jeffrey charles
in about 20 minutes.
If...
ok, i see.
Thank you.
What is it?
Morgan: James,
i can't help you.
If you don't talk,
Jeffrey never arrived
at school today.
His father
said he was sick.
Morgan: Somethin'!
[Cell phone rings]
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, i got it.
I got it.
What were you doin'?
Workin' your way up
to the victim
you wanted to kill
the most?
Your son?
What'd you do
with him, james?
Are you
really that weak?
You gotta blame
your own kid
for your failed marriage?
Shut up!
No, you talk to me!
'Cause i need
to understand this.
You beat those children,
who trusted you. Why?
So you could regain
your power?
I got a newsflash for you.
You never had any
to begin with.
That's right.
Keep it comin'.
I am so far
from finished with you,
you son of a bitch.
I will go all night.
You understand me?
You make me sick!
What is that?
It's an epi pen.
Weird.
Whoa.
Think i just
found something.
[Ring]
Yeah.
An epi pen
and a refrigerator
that's filled
with dairy products
that have been sealed
with duct tape.
Gideon: Thank you.
That's helpful.
You know
what happens to guys
who mess with kids
on the inside?
Can i have
a word with him?
Yeah.
It's a rough day,
huh?
Coffee?
Yeah, i wouldn't mind.
Milk?
Please.
Say when.
When.
How long
have you known?
Known what?
That your son
is a murderer?
What are you
talkin' about?
You might
have been the one
who brought
the food trays
to finnegan's,
but your son
ate them.
Everything
but the creamed spinach.
Do you want me
to confess?
I mean, is that
what this game is?
'Cause that's fine.
You bring me another pen,
i'll write out
my confession.
And we found
an epi pen in your kitchen.
So what? That proves
that my kid has an allergy.
To milk.
How did you know that?
You just told me.
What's it matter?
Jeffrey's allergy
is dangerous.
So much so, he wrapped
the only dairy product
with duct tape
so he wouldn't
accidentally eat it.
You taught him well
to protect himself.
I found
the baseball cap.
I found it
this morning.
[Crying]
It was
in my son's drawer.
Where is he,
mr. Charles?
Tracy!
Cut it out!
"Cut it out!"
Let's go, simon.
Where are you going?
We're supposed to walk
each other home.
I'm walkin'
to henry's.
But he doesn't live
on our street.
I'll walk you home.
Hey, jeffrey.
Because you shouldn't
be walking alone.
You know, the whole
buddy system and all.
Yeah. That's
really nice of you.
Thanks.
Come on.
I know a shortcut.
where is he,
mr. Charles?
I left him at home.
But he's not there.
If he's not there,
i don't know where he is.
An 8-year-old girl,
tracy belle's been
reported missing.
Last seen getting
off her school bus
on fuller road.
Get a team there now.
Let's go.
Mack, get yourself
over to fuller road.
Tracy: How much longer?
You're walking
too slow.
This book bag is heavy.
My legs are tired.
Uh!
Why'd you do that?
Shut up
and keep walking!
I don't feel good.
I told you to shut up
and move!
Aah!
You know,
after his mom left,
jeffrey probably
resented the fact
that his dad spends
more time at work
with other kids
than with his own.
And took out
that rage
on any kid he viewed
as having what he didn't.
So tracy's mom said
the bus would have dropped
her off here after school.
She was supposed to walk
home with a neighbor.
That's most likely
when jeffrey approached,
but where would he
have taken her?
There's such heavy
patrolling in this town.
How do you manage
to take a little girl+???
Because we taught him.
Nobody's gonna think
anything of two kids
walking together...
the buddy system,
remember?
In the process of
educating the public,
we educated a killer.
When it's off-season
from baseball,
where would
a 12-year-old kid hang out?
The park.
Surrounded by woods.
Let's go.
Tracy!
Let's just go.
I was only playing.
Why do you have to be
such a baby?
Tracy!
It's tracy belle's.
They're in these woods.
Split up.
Aah!
[Tracy screams]
[Shouting]
Aah!
Gideon: Hey!
You ok?
[Song begins]
Why'd you hurt
those kids?
Because
i wanted to.
What?
To gideon or hotch
or any of you guys.
I talked
to elle that night,
and i knew
she wasn't right,
but i should have
told someone.
Reid, listen to me.
Do not do that
to yourself.
You were just trying
to help a friend.
You hear me?
Don't go there, kid.
Elle made
her own choice.
That's on her.
She hasn't
admitted anything?
No.
Well, you're doing
the right thing.
Yeah, i know that.
Gideon: So i'll see you
in a few hours.
Ok.
Gideon?
Yeah.
Tell him
i said good-bye.
This is not
an admission of guilt.
Right.
You know, when i
first started this job,
the sound
of my phone ringing,
a call from the bureau,
i used to get
so excited.
The blood would race
through my veins.
And now, that same sound,
it paralyzes me.
I'm not the same person
anymore.
That night at lee's,
if i had to do it
all over again,
i wouldn't change a thing.
Even though
you killed someone.
I guess
that's it then.
You know, when i first
joined the team,
i couldn't figure out
why you never, ever smile.
Now i think i'm
actually gonna miss that.
I'm gonna
miss it, too.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com