Nobody move !
Let's go...
Hey ! I can't get down !
Get back in !
Yo get back in.
Damn it.
Come on out of there, punk !
I'm warning you !
Aah ! Aah ! Ohh !
Ah ! Ah ! Ohh !
This is houston's fifth ward.
It accounts for a large percent
of the city's growing homicide rate,
Due to gang violence
And a bustling narcotics trade.
Although in the last 48 hours,
There have been
3 distinctive murders in the ward.
Distinctive ?
3 men, 3 different
socioeconomic groups,
All killed on the street
with their necks snapped.
There appears to be
no other injury,
And there's no apparent
connection between the victims
Or motive.
The ward's detectives
are inundated with homicides.
Gang violence is a big problem.
Shootings,
Armed robberies,
it's an everyday occurrence,
But this type
of street attack
Is new to them.
Could it be gang related,
Maybe some new type
of initiation rite ?
The gangs in the ward use guns.
In fact, no known gangs
exhibit this type of m.O.
What about dope ?
These guys come up with
pretty freaky ways
Of killing the competition
to get their message out.
Yeah, but there just
doesn't seem to be any connection
Between the victims
and the drug world.
Homeless man,
A construction worker...
Security guard.
Just 3 dead men and no witnesses.
We're looking for
a homicidal serial criminal
In a neighborhood
populated by criminals.
The challenge will be
separating him from the rest.
We have no evidence, no apparent
interaction between the unsub
And the victims
pre- Or postmortem,
And an indistinguishable M.O.
Should be simple.
"Criminal minds" 217
"our life is made
by the death of others."
Leonardo Da Vinci.
We got a construction worker...
Outsider in the community.
We got a security guard...
That's an authority figure.
And then we got a homeless man.
That's a powerless victim
that no one would notice missing.
So who's he targeting ?
Let's see if any of the victims
frequented the same stores or sites.
He used blitz attacks,
Which means he most likely lacks
the interpersonal skills.
He needed to coerce his
victims into coming close.
And he also used
the element of surprise,
Which means he may have stalked
his victims prior to killing them.
Well, if that's the case,
i want to go to the last crime scene
To see where
he may have been hiding.
I want to see
the neighborhood for myself.
Good.
I'll go with you.
The rest of us will go to
the precinct and set up shop.
I'll map out the area
and see if i can find any places
The victims would have
visited in the neighborhood.
Good. Maybe we can find
a connection between them.
I'll help you with that.
I can handle it.
I wasn't suggesting
that you couldn't.
You know what "i'll help you
with it" means ?
Reid. Prentiss will help you
with the geographical profiling
And victimology.
Fine.
Remember, this is a high-Crime area.
Be vigilant.
Nobody goes anywhere alone.
FBI, right ?
Agents Morgan,
Gideon.
Hi, how are you ?
Nice to meet you.
We really do
appreciate your help.
Oh, we're glad to assist.
The vic, the security guard,
Was patrolling construction sites
in the neighborhood.
Some equipment was vandalized.
You think
the murder's related ?
The damage was kind of
unspecific,
More like something
kids would do.
The guard had a pistol,
which is now missing.
This whole area,
it's empty ?
Except for a liquor store
around that corner
And the locksmith on this end.
And what about this
building right here ?
Oh, empty for years.
Where's he going ?
Find out when he comes back.
Detective Fuller !
Let me see
what this here's about.
Her son was at
the community center last night.
I've lived in this
neighborhood all my life.
So has my son.
I didn't raise him to be a vandal.
Yes, ma'am,
i'm sure you didn't.
Kelvin !
Well, i was...
We was up here last night.
We messed up some of
the equipment over there.
I found some spray paint
on his clothes,
And i knew he was up to trouble
with his no-Good friends.
He will not be vandalizing
his own neighborhood again.
Will you, son ?
No, ma'am.
I was gonna drive him
to the police station,
But i saw you already here.
How much damage was done ?
Actually, we're here because
there was a murder last night.
Murder ?
What murder ?
Security guard.
Oh, my god.
No. No.
He chased us,
But i lost him.
I swear, i ain't touch him.
Don't say another word, Kelvin.
Kelvin... I only have one question
for you and then you can go.
Did the security guard
fire his weapon at you ?
No. He, like,
shot into the air to scare us.
And that's why we ran.
Thanks. You can go.
We can go ?
Yes, ma'am.
You just sent away the last person
to see our victim alive.
A boy that frightened
of his mother and that slight
Doesn't have the skill,
courage, or size
To kill the way
this unsub does.
Hey, guys.
Over here.
Someone was living here.
There, you got
a dirty blanket,
Hamburger wrappers,
and soda cans.
Those kids weren't
the only ones here last night.
What's that ?
One of the detectives' wives
made us cookies.
Wow. Homemade cookies ?
Yeah, I guess that's what
they mean by southern hospitality.
What are you saying ?
Southern hospitality !
I need to concentrate...
How can anybody hear
with all this work going on ?
Well, you're gonna
have to get used to it.
Construction crews
are working around the clock.
Saw it on the way in.
City's trying to return
to its splendor,
And that means that
houston's poorest
Are being kicked out
of their homes.
Unsub might be homeless.
Appears to have been
living in a building
Next to where the security
guard was attacked.
These are the locations of the last
3 murders, all near abandoned buildings.
I noticed the neighborhood.
Maybe he was recently displaced.
Could be a motive.
Construction worker,
security guard at a construction site.
Payback ?
What about the homeless man ?
We get a lot of beefs down
there among the homeless.
That one could have just been
a fight about space or food.
Let's get a list of residents Who've been
kicked out of their homes by the gentrification.
You and Reid
check the shelters ?
Yeah, we're on it.
Unless...
you ok with that, Reid ?
I'm fine with that.
We should check to see if there are
any mental hospitals in the area,
Maybe someone who was recently
released into the streets.
Mm-Hmm. Got it.
Morgan, can you cover
the police records for the last week ?
If it's someone
who's been recently made homeless,
He might have stolen food,
comfort items, blankets,
Toiletries... We might be able
to track a pattern of theft.
Thanks.
Done.
Are you lonely
in the lone star state ?
Are you wearing chaps ?
Only in your dreams, Garcia.
Oh, not necessarily.
I have photoshop.
Hey, hey, behave.
Focus your little
twisted mind for me, ok ?
I need police records
from the fifth ward...
Small thefts and burglaries.
Can you do that ?
Aren't you at that
very station right now.
Yeah, but it's a small precinct
And these guys are stretched. Trust me.
Got it.
Oh, Garcia.
See if you can find before and after
pictures of demolitions in the area.
Maybe we can nail down a building where
the unsub may have worked or lived in.
How far back ?
A week.
And Garcia...
I better not ever find
any photoshop pictures of me...
Oh, trust me, my vision.
You will never find them.
Get out !
Victim's name is Travis Overby.
That's his buddy over there.
He was working
a jackhammer on a new trunkline.
He said one second
travis was going down the sewer,
The next second
he was down at the bottom dead.
From one second to the next.
Someone has to go down.
Aw, see, this ain't cool.
I'm putting in for hazard pay.
Good luck with that.
It's pretty clean for a sewer !
The trash is pretty much
cleared away.
Yeah, i got a dirty blanket...
Something else rolled up
in the corner.
It's obvious he made himself
a place to sleep, but...
He cleared it all away.
It looks a lot like
the last place he was in.
Huh.
A new temporary home.
Guys, it looks like
the jackhammer
Must have knocked
some of the ceiling loose.
It fell down all around him.
I'd be pretty scared, too.
It's about survival.
Carved out a place of his own,
Saw a threat, he attacked.
That's got to be why
the victims were so random.
He didn't have
a relationship with them.
They just happened to be
intruding on his home.
We'll need to see
the other crime scenes.
Sure ! Let's go !
You all right ?
Yeah. You owe me.
You all are looking
for someone in charge ?
I'm angie, one of
the administrators.
Hi. I'm Agent Prentiss.
This is Agent Reid.
We're with the fbi.
Really ?
Really.
It looks like
you have your hands full.
With the demolitions in the projects
and the abandoned buildings,
There's no place else
for people to sleep.
Well, thank god there are people
like you who take the time...
Do you have a list of everyone
who comes through here ?
Angie: uh, we have
a sign-In sheet,
But we don't force
anyone to sign if they don't want to.
Some who do don't even
use their real names.
Elvis eats here a lot.
We would appreciate
any lists you have.
Why ?
Have you noticed anyone who acts
Unusually aggressive
towards the other residents ?
What's this about ?
A series of murders in the area.
The perpetrator
may be a homeless man.
Maybe someone who stays here.
He may even be in this room
as we speak.
My god, Reid.
Have you noticed anyone
who acts paranoid or displays
Explosive, unprovoked
bursts of violence,
More than just
pushing and shoving ?
I mean, someone who really
tries to harm others.
There are territorial fights
over food and places to sleep.
The nurse treats people
for minor injuries all the time,
But no one's seriously hurt.
If anyone does come to mind,
give us a call.
Thank you.
A murderer ?
I'm sorry. Uh--Um...
This investigation is still...
No one's actually
been hurt in a shelter.
We're just... We're acting with
an abundance of caution.
So, please, let the police know
If anything unusual occurs.
Thanks.
There's a high presence
of mental disorders with the homeless.
Yeah.
What the hell
was that in there ?
What ?
"He may even be in this room as we speak" ?
We have nothing to support that.
We're investigating
a serial homicide.
Should i have pretended
there's no danger ?
We just left that woman
potentially afraid
Of every man who walks
into this shelter.
Again, until we find
this unsub, how is that a bad thing ?
What is the matter with you ?
What do you mean,
what's the matter with me ?
I have never seen you act like this.
Oh, really ?  Oh, in the months
that you know me,
You've never seen me
act this way ?
Hey, no offense,
Emily, but...
You don't really know what
you're talking about, do you ?
Good. Thanks.
Just got back from
the local homeless shelter.
The administrator hasn't noticed anyone
new displaying aggressive behavior.
He's not in
a homeless shelter.
I just talked
to Gideon and Morgan.
They think that he's killing
To protect some makeshift
shelter of his own.
So are we ready
for a profile yet ?
We're missing something.
How did this homeless man
learn to kill so efficiently ?
You know what we need ?
We need to get lucky.
We need him to make a mistake.
Hey.
Come on, man, get out of there !
I see you right there !
Iaqui tengo mi tienda !
There's a shelter
a couple of blocks from here.
Vayase...
Papa !
Please help my daddy !
I need help !  I was attacked !
Can i get some help here, please ?
Please... Call my house
to come get my daughter. Please.
Maria...
Is my papa gonna be ok ?
Yes.
Maria, could you answer
a few questions for us ?
It would really help us
find the bad guy.
Did he say anything
to your papa ?
No.
What were you and your papa
doing before the bad guy came ?
Papa took out the garbage.
And then he jumped out...
And he hit my papa.
I was screaming at him.
Don't hurt my papa !
I thought he was gonna
hit me, too.
But then he stopped...
And he looked at me funny.
What do you mean by "funny" ?
He looked...
Sad.
He did say something.
Not to my papa.
To me.
What was it ?
He said...
Are you ok ?
Why are you crying ?
And then we ran.
Go away !  Go away !
Maria...
What you did was very brave.
Can you help us
with one more thing ?
Can you tell us
what the man looked like ?
He was white.
And tall.
And dirty.
And he had a ring like yours.
Like that ?
I remember his ring.
Thank you.
Iabuela !
Gracias.
He asked if she was ok
and why was she crying.
He wasn't aware of what
he was doing to her.
Garcia's on line one.
Go ahead, Penelope.
All right, cowgirls and boys.
Hey.
I've got the comparison
satellite images
Of the before-And-After
pictures, and i found something.
Check it.
Do you see it yet ?
Yeah.
Yeah, an s.O.S.
Yeah, it's made of debris
and other rocky bits of gobbledygook.
This is the building
where the security guard got killed.
He's asking for help.
Wait, guys. Listen outside.
Chaos. S.O.S.
He's a war veteran.
He thinks he's in a war zone.
He left a distress signal
on the roof of one of the buildings.
The quick strikes
are consistent with trained military
He must have served in a place
That looked or sounded like this ward.
Well, we were right
about him being homeless, in a sense.
Wherever he is, in his mental state,
he's certainly not at home.
He may not even be aware
he's killing.
Now, how's that ?
When soldiers suffered
from anxiety, depression,
And flashbacks in world war i,
it was called shell shock.
In world war ii,
battle fatigue.
Now we refer to it as ptsd,
Post-Traumatic
stress disorder, war related.
A side effect of which
is slipping into dissociative states.
The mind divorces itself
from reality
So it can cope
with the trauma.
He's reliving a memory.
He's trapped in his head
in some war zone.
Hiding and defending himself
from the enemy.
Ok, so how do we find
a man who's trapped inside his head ?
He's got a wedding ring.
Someone's missing him.
Good. I'm with detective Fuller.
Morgan has last crime scene to check.
J.J., check
missing persons reports,
See if anyone matches
the description.
It would have been
filed recently,
The last 2 or 3 days.
Ok.
Thanks.
Hey.
You shouldn't be out here.
It isn't safe.
Dana Woodridge and Max Weston...
Her husband and his best friend.
Roy Woodridge
has been missing since tuesday.
He was on his way home from work.
He called before
he left the office
And said we needed to talk
when he got home.
He sounded upset.
That was the last
I heard from him.
What was he upset about ?
He didn't say.
Dana called me that night
When Roy didn't show up.
So...
The next morning we filed
a missing persons report.
Mrs. Woodridge, where
does your husband work ?
He's a consultant
at a security firm downtown.
Did your husband
ever serve in combat ?
Excuse me ?
Is he a war veteran ?
Yeah.
Uh...
We both are.
We were in
special ops.
75th ranger regiment,
Bravo company, 3rd battalion.
But Roy...
He retired shortly after
things went bad in Mogadishu.
That was back in 1993.
Let me ask you this... Does he display
any sort of, uh...
Behavioral tics...
Certain everyday things,
They make him jumpy or startled ?
Why ?
Does he ?
Is this going to help find him ?
Mrs. Woodridge, please.
We need to know everything
we can about your husband.
We all had a...
hard time over there,
You know... you bring
some things home with you.
Like what ?
He has a hard time
with loud noises.
He can't be in crowds.
He has nightmares
And wakes up in cold sweats.
The smells are the worst.
He...
If he smells
something burning,
Like a barbecue or gas or fire...
He gets sick.
It really only got bad
about a year ago.
What happened to him in Somalia ?
Nothing.
Combat happened.
What does that mean ?
I'm gonna get a drink of water.
You knew your friend
was suffering from symptoms of ptsd ?
He was a changed man, wasn't he ?
He was anxious,
Paranoid, distant.
He was far away in his head.
I tried to get him
into a vet center to talk to somebody,
But he said he was all right.
What happened
in Somalia ?
What's he reliving ?
You can't tell Dana.
Roy never wanted her to know.
Thank you.
Could somebody please
tell me what's going on ?
There have been some
people hurt recently,
And we think that there
may be someone lost on the streets.
Someone who thinks
that he's still at war.
But Roy would never hurt
innocent people.
Well, why would he even
be in this neighborhood ?
Hey, Garcia. We have
Mrs. Woodridge here with us.
Oh, uh, well,
I found an '02
white ford f150 pickup truck.
Oh, my god. That's his truck.
It was impounded.
Uh, it had a flat tire
and was picked up on Lyon street
About a quarter of a mile
from highway 59.
He takes the east tex freeway
to work every day.
Mrs. Woodridge,
I'm very sorry...
But this is definitely
your husband.
What  ?
Roy and I...
We were escorting
a u.N. Aid caravan to a refugee camp.
Our convoy was ambushed.
The front received heavy fire,
But we were in the rear,
So we managed to escape.
We hid for 2 days
in and out of abandoned buildings that...
Insurgents were looking for us.
One night I was sleeping,
Roy kept watch.
When I woke up, there was
an ak-47 pointed right at me.
A child.
Yeah.
They were all babies
back in Mogadishu,
But this one...
He couldn't have been
more than 11 or 12.
Then what happened ?
We finally found a radio...
Fixed it,
called for an extraction.
Did you put out an S.O.S. ?
Yeah, we...
We used rocks to put
an s.O.S. In the dirt
So the blackhawks
could locate us.
How did you know that ?
Look,
If this is roy,
you're not gonna find him.
He's trained and skilled
at survival.
He knows how to hide.
We think he has a gun.
Well, he doesn't miss.
We need to put
a s.W.A.T. Team together,
Plan a grid search
and go building to building.
He's reliving the war, isn't he ?
A specific incident
in which he killed a child.
Guys, the s.W.A.T. Team's
gonna have guns, right ?
What happens if he tries
to fight them ?
Can I get you something,
Mrs. Woodridge ?
Those men are going
after Roy ?
Do they need so many guns ?
He's just one man.
It... It's protocol, ma'am.
How badly were they hurt ?
Y'all said
that people were hurt.
Some people were murdered.
Murdered ?
Mrs. Woodridge...
He never really came home.
I lost him 14 years ago.
It's been like
living with a ghost.
Help him.
Please, help him.
We'll do everything we can.
Ok ?
Reid, what are you working on ?
3 days ago police shut down
the freeway
At 5 p.M. For 10 minutes.
Cars were stalled and Roy must have
tried to exit on the surface streets.
Sadly, he ended up in an unfamiliar
area with a flat tire.
He was changing that tire
when an 8-Story building
On market imploded
5 blocks away.
He heard the explosion
and reacted
Like a mortar bomb
had landed nearby.
This explosion is what
triggered his dissociation.
And since then,
he's been stuck in that state.
Running when he needed to,
sleeping when he could,
Camouflaging himself
into his surroundings,
And hiding from
his perceived enemies.
He's relieving
the worst moment of his life.
He's gotta be
terrified.
Yeah.
Yeah, what do you have ?
Why isn't Derek
answering his phone ?
He's probably stuck
underground somewhere.
Underground ?
I'll explain later.
Oh. Ok. So,
I finally got through
All those recent police reports
he asked me to check,
Which, by the way,
it was no hopscotch through the park,
Because that precinct you're at
Is kind of tragically behind
on their paperwork.
Yeah, they're undermanned.
Oh, Jeez, really ?
I can't imagine
what that feels like.
Oh, no, wait.
Yes, I can, 'cause...
Garcia, do you have
anything for me ?
Well, he told me to look
for anything unusual,
And it's all usual.
Minor break-Ins,
apartment burglaries,
Televisions, stereos,
car thefts, and smash and grabs.
Common stuff in the world
of burgling.
Nothing a guy
lost in the streets
Might use for survival ?
No, nothing reported.
It... like I said,
it's all petty.
There's a...
Some vandalism
at construction sites.
Communications radio
missing from one of them.
Wait... Did you say radio ?
Yeah. Construction Foreman
reported that one of their
Trucks had been broken into
and a hand-Held radio was stolen.
Yesterday.12 hours ago.
Is that what you're looking for ?
Reid ?
This is Roy Woodridge,
6'1", 195 pounds,
44 years old.
Brown hair,
former army ranger.
It's imperative
you don't try to apprehend him alone.
He won't understand
what's happening.
He may try
to defend himself.
He's armed, and he's an excellent
marksman.
He may have stolen a radio,
A walkie-Talkie.
We were right.
He had a nest of sorts
right near every murder scene.
There was a burglary
of a two-Way radio
From a construction site
recently.
That could be Roy.
We only used uhf
back then.
He's looking for help.
And he'll keep trying to
contact operations command.
Detective, can we get a dozen uhf
radios set up in this room,
And each of them tuned
to each of the preset channel frequencies ?
Right away.
Wait a minute.
When he calls,
we need to be very careful
With the communication,
Because we set up
specific responses to contact op com
So we could avoid
hostile interception
And to establish
"no danger" signals.
And we had specific names
to identify our squad to the operator.
Do you remember
the language you set up ?
I couldn't forget it.
Roy and I wrote it.
The callout was, "this is John Doe
looking for mark rippen."
Rippen was our hero
at the time...
Number 11, quarterback
for the redskins in 1993.
Now we know where he is
in his head.
He calls in, we'll be
on the other end when he does.
What if he doesn't call ?
What if he just
kills someone else ?
Well, we'll deal
with that if it happens.
Kind of easy for you to say.
This guy may be messed up,
but that doesn't change the fact
That he has killed
4 innocent people.
Now, why don't we
just do the grid search ?
If you set up
a grid search
And he confronts
one of your men,
You'll be planning a funeral.
I can guarantee you we're
right about his profile.
This man wants to get rescued.
All i'm asking is that you just
give us a chance to bring him in.
It's channel 11.
Are you ready Garcia ?
I've got nat recon
satellites all over the ward.
Stand by.
This is John Doe
looking for mark rippen.
Can you help us ?
You know how to do this
better than we do.
Roger that.
This is number 11, all clear.
Maxey, boy, am I happy
to hear from you.
I'm taking heavy fire.
Request immediate extraction.
What are your coordinates ?
Unknown. I lost my land
navigational aids.
I went high, but i don't
recognize anything.
I don't have a fix
on my grid coordinates.
Any other way for him
to signal his location ?
Did you put up any flags ?
Yeah, you bet
your ass I did.
I'm holding cover here.
Roger that.
Hold your position.
He triangulated. We need to look
for 3 large, colored flags,
Maybe on rooftops.
They'll be identical
in size and shape.
Did you get that, Garcia ?
Yeah, I got it.
Number 11,
do you still read me ?
Garcia.
I'm working as fast as I can.
I can still read you
loud and clear.
Stay put.
I found one.
I got them.
I see...
Housing projects
and a courtyard.
We need street names,
Garcia.
Farmer and Capron !
I know where that is.
There's some abandoned
buildings right there.
I'll have construction sites
to halt work and secure the streets.
He's gonna expect
men in fatigues and a chopper as cover.
I can take care
of the choppers.
We're in black suvs. Tell him
we're security executives.
You're coming with us.
We need to do this fast.
Tell him to stay there,
we're coming to him.
Roy, we're coming to you, buddy.
Let's go !
Thank you, god.
Sergeant Woodridge ?
Got him.
Where's Max ?
Roy.
It's all right.
It's time to come in.
He's got a weapon !
No ! No ! Stop !
Stop
Look, it's all right.
It's all right.
No !
It's not safe !
It's a boy, sergeant,
it's just a boy.
Roy !
It wasn't safe.
I know.
Is the boy all right ?
Yes.
Yes, sergeant.
The boy's all right.
That's good.
Folks. Uh...
Thank you so much for coming here.
No one ever makes this place
a priority.
We're grateful to you.
I wish it had ended
differently.
Yeah. Me, too.
Hey, has anyone seen Gideon ?
Agent Gideon
left some time ago.
Said he meet you all
at the airport.
Did he say
where he went to ?
I think I know where he is.
Hey.
It's quiet.
Construction's taking
the rest of the day off to honor the victims.
You know, the first
reported war was...
2700 b.C.
Probably earlier wars, but...
Writing hadn't been
invented yet.
Almost 5,000 years
of killing each other.
One thing human beings
have been consistently good at.
We did everything we could
for him, you know.
Yeah.
Sometimes knowing that
just isn't good enough.
I know.
"if there
must be trouble,
"Let it be in my day,
That my child
may have peace."
Thomas Paine.
Transcript : www.1000fr.com
Modification transcript : Flolo pour www.seriessub.com