www.1000fr.com present
woman: Rib eye,
adam and eve on a wrap,
steak-umm,
and a strawberry shake
for the gentleman
at table 8.
???????
Ah, finally!
You walk into my life.
What took you
so long, handsome?
Honey?
Waitress:
No, thanks.
I don't need anything.
Mind if i sit here?
Please.
you should try
fat sam's milk shakes.
I'm cold and tired.
Man: You're also not
from around here.
Where are you from?
man: You really
should try the shakes.
what's your name?
come on.
Names are
a hobby of mine.
Jason gideon.
Jason.
From greek mythology.
To heal.
Gideon.
A hero from
the old testament
who led the israelites
against the midianites.
Your parents had
great ambitions for you.
I'm frank.
Germanic.
Third century.
Derived from the name
of a type of spear.
I wonder what aspirations
my parents had for me.
Why don't we cut
the crap, frank?
Where is she?
Now, that's direct.
You're right.
I'm not from
around here.
I'm an fbi agent.
The bau?
You didn't disappoint
your parents.
We're looking
for a man
in his mid-
to late-fifties.
Listens to beethoven,
wears a corduroy jacket
with fleece-lined collar.
He's left-handed.
In his right inside
jacket pocket
will be a notebook,
and it will give
the extensive
detailed accounts
of the torture
inflicted on every
one of his victims.
That's quite a magic trick.
No magic trick, frank.
Just a profile of
a sadistic serial killer.
Gideon, this thing
is brand-new.
There's only two
entries in it:
"Black male,
220 pounds, portly;
white female,
early twenties."
This doesn't
prove anything.
Guess what.
When i'm finished
with my shake,
you'll get what
you're here for,
but then...
i'm going to get up...
and i'm going to
walk out of here...
and you...
and your lapdog...
are going to let me.
You know what,
frank?
That would be
a magic trick.
Capture:FRM@XXY
Sync:FRM@LePetitPrince
Criminal Minds 213
Gideon, voice-over:
Aristotle once said
evil brings
men together.
I don't give
a rat's ass.
Feds or no feds...
that bastard doesn't
give her back to us
in the next 15 minutes,
we go in! Agreed?!
Agreed!
Agreed?!
He's looked
at that clock
3 times in as many minutes.
He's waiting for something.
If i had
your looks...
do you know how much
easier my life would be?
If you think you're
gonna negotiate
you way out of this one,
you got a whole
nother thing coming.
Want to know how
we caught you?
Please.
Derek: Gideon, those men out
there want to kill this guy.
We're in the middle.
We don't have time
for explanations.
Frank: You have
the time it will take me
to finish this shake.
That's all i need.
We got a request from
sheriff georgia davis.
Jj: 1996.
The ribcage of
a male was found
in the desert rose
national park.
It was never identified.
This morning,
the remains of two victims
were found in almost
exactly the same area.
Well, one year
later is cause
for concern,
but 10 years?
That could be
a coincidence.
It would be...
if the unidentified
male wasn't missing
a right rib bone.
And the torso
found this morning
is missing exactly
the same bone.
Both of them
seem to be
surgically removed,
and the advanced rate
of decomposition
on the male means
that he died
far before the female.
Oh, katherine hale.
They found
a bracelet
on her wrist.
She ran away about
two weeks ago
from her small
colorado town.
Unsub's crossing
state lines.
He's mobile.
Derek: If the remains are
related to the same killer,
where's he been
for 10 years?
Killing.
Unsolved case files
going back 30 years.
Every case,
the victimology
is the same.
The unwanted.
This box is just
the tip of the iceberg.
13 cases spanning
30 years.
Same m.o.
Right rib bone
is missing.
It's him, hotch.
It's the same killer.
All the remains were
dumped in remote areas
and always near
interstate 80.
And up till now,
no remains this intact
or this close to
the actual time of kill
have been found.
Never two victims dumped
at the same time
in the same place.
All of these
killings
the work
of just one man?
The most prolific
serial killer ever.
Wow.
You truly think...
i know it.
Which is why
we came here...
to nevada.
You seen enough, kid?
Go on, get out of here.
George!
They're here.
That cop
drive 60 miles
just to barf.
No good reason
to be here,
not even from
this department.
What is it
about death that
fascinates us?
He didn't contaminate
the scene, did he?
No, uh...
sheriff georgia davis.
People call me
george.
This is deputy
rick silo.
Aaron hotchner.
This is
derek morgan,
and the guy who
sometimes forgets
his manners
is jason gideon.
Stood here
10 years ago,
this exact spot.
Same feeling
i have now.
Which is what?
Someone in my town
might be responsible
for it.
Hope you tell
me i'm wrong.
Oh, my cell.
That's my husband.
That's our song.
Excuse me.
Silo: Lucky we found anything.
Been a recent spike
in the coyote population.
Maybe that's
why the unsub
dumps the bodies here.
Silo: You people
really think
we have a serial killer
in our town?
At least one that
passes through
from time to time.
Is it just me,
or do you get
the feeling
that we're not
welcome here.
Oh, it's not us.
It's what
we represent.
Government's not all
that popular out here.
Woman: No!
No, you can't
make me go!
I know what my rights are!
No, don't make me go!
No, i don't
want to go home!
I know my rights!
Come on!
What are you
looking at, princess?!
Ok, ok!
If that's the way
you want it, jane,
back to jail.
Ok, ok, ok.
He's coming.
He's coming back,
and there's nothing
you can do about it!
Do you hear me?!
Nothing, nothing!
Come on, jane!
Come on!
Excuse me.
She dropped this.
It's harmless.
Thank you.
What is it?
A psycho
with a whistle.
That's not
too weird.
Derek: Looks like
prison gang tattoos.
This unsub has extensive
anatomic anomalies.
Well, the pen marks
are a guidelines
for a surgeon's knife.
That's for sure.
Did he cauterize
the main arteries?
Yeah, all of them.
What do you mean?
He cauterized the arteries
by burning them.
Why?
It stops the blood flow.
The victims
were alive
when he cut off
their limbs.
Garcia's gonna love this.
Garcia: Oh, this is so
not a way to
a girl's heart.
What are you doing?
I'm mapping out
where all the victims
were found...
starting with gideon's
first case file.
Ow! Stabby.
Ok, so katherine hale...
was last seen here
in salt lake city, utah,
and then found
right here
in golconda, nevada.
Ahh.
Well, the tattoo is
from a prison gang.
It was photographed
and logged
in san quentin.
This one belongs
to reno rodriguez, 42.
Jumped bail 7 months ago,
picked up by cops in
salt lake city 5 weeks ago.
Ok, so say he
was abducted
somewhere close to where
he was last seen.
Next was katherine hale.
It appears this unsub
is traveling
from east to west
towards golconda.
If he lives there,
where's he coming from?
The only these
two victims
have in common is
they were killed
by the same unsub.
There is another
connection.
?????????
Derek: Excuse me, miss?
Yeah?
You ever seen
that man before?
Waitress:
Over the years, yeah.
He never eats.
He just orders
a strawberry milk shake.
Thank you.
Sure.
Frank: You were saying?
The story involves
wind chimes,
trailers,
alien abductions.
Gripping.
I thought i'd seen
the very worst
of what humanity
had to offer
until you.
Can i ask you
something?
Please.
Do you think me insane?
Do not play me.
You know exactly
what you are,
a psychopathic
sexual sadist.
You get off
on the brutal
torture of others.
Derek: And you knew
the moment we arrived
in this town
you had no way out.
Which is why
you took her.
Who's playing who now?
You don't care about her.
You only ever cared
about catching me.
It isn't the victims
that drives you, jason.
It's the hunt.
Derek: Look out
that window, frank.
Hunt's over.
You aren't
denying it.
Men, women,
young, old.
Didn't matter
to you.
You took them all.
From san francisco's
muir woods
to the hills
of the poconos...
you took them all.
Garcia: If they
are all connected,
he's killed
hundreds of people
all over north america.
How many years
do they go back again?
30.
All right, keep going.
Sacramento, california...
lincoln, nebraska...
gary, indiana...
if we can figure out
where he's been,
maybe we can figure out
the significance
golconda has to him.
Want to hear
the really bad news?
Can it get worse?
Just did.
Early toxilogical
investigations
of the victim's
blood indicated
high levels of ketamine.
Ketamine is primarily
a horse tranquilizer.
It's also used
as a date-rape drug.
In street lingo,
it's known as being
stuck in a k-hole.
So his victims were
completely conscious
when he killed them?
Imagine what she must
have gone through.
It's essential
for this unsub
that he sees the terror
in his victim's eyes.
That is what
gets him off.
Hotch: He's either
had medical training,
or he's honed his skills
over the years.
Gideon: Look for
a man in his mid-
to late-fifties,
highly intelligent,
methodically
and obsessively clean.
Emily: His vehicle is
most likely an rv,
muted in color,
neither old nor new,
in perfect working order.
Derek: It will have
a cb, radar detectors,
and police-band radio.
All these things have
helped him evade you.
Hotch: And this vehicle
is his killing room.
It'll be soundproofed.
Surgical instruments
are on the walls.
There's a stirrup chair
or an autopsy table in it.
Gideon: All of his
kills are recorded...
if not on video,
in a journal
that he carries
with him
in his right-hand
inside jacket pocket.
How could you know that?
Tool marks
on the remains
indicate that
he's left-handed.
This man is void of all
normal human feelings.
Gideon:
A killing machine...
incapable of remorse,
compassion, love.
What's the matter,
frank?
Something
i said?
Got him all
worked up, gideon.
Frank: Beauty...
can cover
a multitude of sins,
but underneath...
we all look...
exactly the same.
I know what gets you off...
fear... seeing it
and feeling it.
Well, look out
that window, frank.
You are not leaving
this diner.
I don't want to.
Not until
the story is done.
Silo: We have roadblocks
on every interstate,
track or laned
in or out of this town.
We'll shut down this
state if we have to.
Stop every rv,
truck, and trailer.
Something troubling you?
That profile you gave,
it reminds me of
a story i once heard.
There's someone
you should meet.
How you feeling, jane?
I don't want to
go home, george.
Please don't
make me go home.
Jane...
these people
are from the fbi.
I'd like you to
tell them your story.
Why, so they can
make fun of me, too?
It's very pretty.
Did you make it?
It was a gift.
Oh.
What happened to you?
My car broke down.
The engine went
out on me and...
you know, in those days,
they didn't have
cell phones,
so i tried to
fix it myself.
?????????
And then everything
went white.
I was in a spaceship.
And i could see myself.
It was like time
was suspended.
I could feel everything,
and there were strange
maps on the walls...
diagrams of all the stars.
I was cold.
It was very, very cold.
And the alien,
he did things to me.
He touched me...
very softly,
and he stroked my hair,
and he drew lines
all over my body,
and the whole time,
he was standing there
smiling down on me.
And then i looked
into his eyes...
and i wasn't
afraid anymore.
I don't know why.
Then what did he do?
And then i...
was back in my own bed,
and it was
the next morning.
Emily: How long ago
did this happen?
I was 19.
It was 30 years ago.
Emily: And did you
ever see him again?
Oh, i see him.
I see him every time
i shut my eyes.
The strange maps
on the walls
could have been
anatomical drawings.
What about the fact that
she could see herself?
A mirrored
ceiling.
So his victims
could see
themselves
being
dismembered.
Every time i think
it can't get any
worse, it does.
Gideon: Her
subconscious mind
has created a delusion
that she was
abducted by an alien.
Emily: It's possible
she's the only one
who's survived.
Why did he
let her go?
She said when she
looked into his eyes,
she felt relaxed.
And in that moment,
the one thing
that he wanted...
she didn't give him.
Fear.
Frank: I read
about a woman
whose body was found
in her apartment...
upper east side,
i think.
If this is
a confession,
start with the woman
you just took.
She had killed herself.
But her body
wasn't found
for more than a year.
Surround by over
a million people,
and not one of them
missed her.
What does that
say about society?
Fills me with
profound sadness...
but it doesn't make
you feel anything.
Those that society
does not care for...
the throwaways,
the runaways,
destitute,
disenfranchised,
the forgotten...
are the very people
you target.
But not last night.
Something changed.
You took a person
of prominence,
someone that
mattered to everyone.
Why?
That's the interesting
question, jason.
Why?
Silo: Mark,
don't do it!
Back off, silo!
Gideon!
Derek: Sir, do not
come any closer!
That man
has my wife.
Please put the gun down.
Tell me where
my wife is,
or so help me,
i will shoot you.
Sir, i said put
the gun down now!
Where's my wife?!
Sir, we are trying
to find your wife!
Tell me where she is,
you son of a bitch!
Put the gun down now!
Frank: But you know
what's an even more
interesting question?
??????????
open it.
Put it down!
Open the bag!
Hand over your gun.
I'll open it.
I'll kill you.
I will kill you.
It's not her.
Oh, thank god.
Who is this?
I believe the correct
question would be:
"Who was this?"
You are one crazy
son of a bitch!
We are all sons
of bitches.
Outside.
Outside, please.
Let us deal with him.
Let us try
to find her.
What is this,
frank?
He's irrelevant
beyond being my
ticket out of here.
Your ticket
out of here?
Even if you
think you can
get out of that
booth and pass us,
i promise you those
men out there
will tear you
to pieces.
I rather doubt that.
Finish the story, jason.
We set up
a nationwide tip line,
but all we've
really got so far is
white male, mid-
to late-fifties,
tall, with
a medium build.
Gideon: From the remains
discovered this morning,
we know he doesn't
keep his victims long.
We've got more
cops arriving
by the hour to
help find this guy.
We also put out
a nationwide a.p.b.
Derek: If he is
still in this town,
and we believe he is,
he has absolutely
no way out.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go catch this s.o.b.
Thank you very
much for your time.
How can you even be
so sure he's here?
He could have
left town
when we found
those remains.
Of all the cases
where remains were found,
yesterday's discovery
was unique.
That's one way
of putting it.
Hotch: He's never
dumped the remains
of two victims
before. Why?
Silo: I want to know
why he's managed
to get away with it
for so long.
Spencer: To get
away with murder,
you simply don't
tell anyone.
And the only
people he told
were the people
he killed,
and then he took from
them what he needed...
cash, credit cards.
I'm gonna call garcia
and see if anything
katherine hale owned
was used after her death.
And then he moved on
to his next
victim...
...till he
reach golconda.
And for some reason,
emptied his vehicle
before driving in...
...where he dumps
his first two victims
in the exact same spot.
You know...
it's almost like he's
purging his vehicle
before he drives
into town.
Yeah, i don't know.
It almost seems
like the unsub
is always traveling
from east to west,
passing through
every state
the same month
every year.
The remains that
were discovered
10 years ago was
the same month
as this, right?
Right, and then for
a week after that,
the trail goes dead.
Yeah, it's like
he takes a vacation
in golconda.
So where is his rv?
Maybe he's not
using an rv.
Maybe he's towing
a trailer.
That way he could unhook
and move about freely.
He could also
hide it.
That's why
we can't find him.
He's waiting for
the roadblocks to clear.
Ok, if he has a truck,
it's gonna be just
like his trailer...
muted in color
and american-made.
It's gonna
be dark soon.
We should to back
and call gideon.
I think the unsub's
in town somewhere.
Yeah.
Gideon: We have to
get back into town
and search garages,
warehouses,
any place someone could
hide a large trailer.
Like you said, he
never takes victims
when he's here.
So if he's not
going anywhere
and he hasn't
got anyone,
we can wait till
the morning.
Wait? We can't wait.
The men
are tired,
i'm tired.
We got roadblocks
on every road.
Gideon,
she's right.
We could wait till
first light, gideon.
Do what you like.
I'm gonna find him.
It's gonna be
a long night.
I'm sorry.
I got to relieve
my men
and get back
to the office.
I understand.
I'll talk to him.
Hey, garcia...
aah!
I like knocking.
Oh, well, i have been
going over the tip line
for hours going
over all the calls,
and i think
i found something.
An anonymous caller
claimed they saw an
that matched
the description
of the one we gave
to the media...
leaving golconda.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Firstly, not a single
rv or trailer
has passed through
any of the roadblocks...
i checked.
Secondly?
Why call anonymously
i need you to
trace this number.
It's 303-555-0126.
It's a cell phone...
belonging to...
katherine hale?
It's from golconda.
This guy, he could have
just kept on going.
We may have never
caught him.
With all this
heat on him,
whatever is keeping
him in that town
must be freaky special.
Mark's away
at his mother's.
Took tommy with him.
Come on in.
You're safe here.
Well, you said you
didn't want to go home,
and i couldn't
leave you in jail.
Machine: You have one new message.
I'll make up the guest bedroom.
Can i get you
something, a soda?
Jane: Thank you
for being so kind.
Man on machine:
Hey, gorgeous george!
I love you, wife.
I miss you.
Tommy misses you.
Yeah, i guess you're
busy catching bad guys...
is he good to you?
Ever since i met him.
We were both 15.
Grape juice?
What the hell?!
Mark: Hey, tommy?
He's here,
george.
Mommy,
i want to come home.
Who the hell are you?!
You know who i am.
Don't you, jane?
Stay right where
you are, jane.
I want you to back off.
Come with me, jane.
He came for me.
This man is
not an alien.
He's a murderer.
Jane: It's all right.
He came for me!
Tommy: Oh, mom,
dad let me eat candy.
Jane, run.
Tommy: Don't be mad at him.
Run, jane!
Run, please!
Jane, no!
Tommy: Twice.
Love you.
Jane!
Tommy: I love you, mommy.
Good night, mom.
Bye!
He keeps checking
that clock
because whatever
it is he came for
is coming here
to this diner.
Derek: Ok, then we
need to figure out
what we missed, gideon.
And soon.
I'm almost finished.
It's clear.
Silo: All clear.
Derek: Silo, silo,
don't touch anything.
We need to
profile this room.
Profile?!
You said the call
was made 5 hours ago
by the unsub right
outside this house!
Now what's
the profile?!
He took george!
Why?
Hotch: All right,
we need to work fast.
Derek: All right,
she enters the house,
and then it's habitual.
Emily: Ok,
she drops her keys,
hits the answering machine,
takes off her gun belt.
Then moves throughout
the kitchen.
Gideon: He's never taken
anyone of prominence.
Why take the sheriff?
And not her gun.
Silo, call your office.
See if she was planning
to meet anyone.
No way a cop
would take chase
without their gun.
Definitely
looks like
she tried to make
a go for it.
But she didn't make it.
Silo: Guys...
george brought crazy jane
home with her.
Derek: So, he takes
control of george,
then goes after what
he came here for.
Crazy jane.
Those footprints,
they got to
be jane's.
They go to the back.
She escapes.
The unsub knows
the ketamine's
gonna wear off,
so he's got to act.
No. He hasn't got
what he came here for.
Hotch: So for leverage,
he takes the sheriff,
which means sooner or later,
he'll contact us.
It turned back on!
It just...
jj, the cell phone,
it turned back on!
What?
Katherine hale's
cell phone,
it turned back on.
Hotch: Katherine
hale's cell phone
just came back on
in the middle of town.
Let's do this.
He thinks
we have jane.
Which means he
wants a trade.
Whatever he wants,
we need to find jane
and the sheriff fast.
Hotch:
You go to town,
we'll go to jane's.
Derek: Ok, listen up!
He should be driving
a truck or suv
muted in color...
black, dark brown.
Or blue!
??????????
Like you boys said,
he'll have a cb,
police-band radio,
and radar detector.
Hotch better find
jane, and fast.
Emily: Guys!
These wind chimes
are made of bone!
I think it's
human rib bones.
He's waiting for us.
Well, let's go
get that bastard.
No, we still don't
have the sheriff.
Well, when i get
a hold of him, we will.
Derek: Hey,
wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
He's smart.
We got to be smarter.
He turned that
cell phone on
because by now,
he knows we're onto him.
Well, you boys have
just 15 minutes,
then we're coming in.
15 minutes.
That's all i need.
waitress: Rib eye,
adam and eve on a wrap,
steak-umm,
and a strawberry shake
for the gentleman
at table 8.
Finally you walk
into my life.
What took you
so long, handsome?
Honey?
waitress:
No, thanks.
I don't need anything.
mind if i sit here?
Please.
Hotch:
Completely empty.
She's not here.
Well, he's obviously
been here before
and left these
gifts for her.
How romantic.
His version of romance.
What... are you
trying to say
you think he keeps
coming back here
because he's
in love with her?
That's impossible.
A sexual sadist
can't feel love.
Hotch: Well, define love.
Chemically, it involves
surging brain elements
called monoamines,
dopamines,
norepinephrine,
and serotonin.
Love chemicals controlled
by phenethylamine,
also found in...
chocolate.
I love chocolate.
Peas, too! It's also
found in peas!
Peas?
Reid?
Indeed, some
veritable...
reid, stop.
Please.
Spread out, everybody.
Keep looking.
Fbi!
Clear.
I thought i'd
seen everything.
Guys.
What is it?
It's a coffin.
Hotch,
there's another
coffin over here.
It's ok. Don't try to speak.
We've got you.
Thank god.
Ahh.
One is perfection.
Two is decadent.
You take another step,
and i will shoot you.
No, you won't.
Was it that jane
said to you?
She looked
into your eyes.
That wouldn't
have been enough.
She said something.
What?
It's important.
I'm a sexual sadist.
I can't feel anything.
Remember?
You said so.
Yeah, hotch?
There are no absolutes
when it comes to
the human mind.
They just found
his trailer,
the remains
of another woman
and the sheriff alive.
He doesn't care
about the sheriff.
To walk out
of here with jane,
he'd need more
than that.
Frank: Jane said...
how beautiful
my eyes were.
I looked at her
like i've never looked
at a woman before.
My hands began to sweat.
I dropped the knife.
I tried to pick
it up, but...
it fell again.
I got butterflies
in my stomach.
Isn't that love?
??????//
Gideon!
Found george.
She's alive.
Get on the floor!
Take it easy!
No!
Silo: What?!
No.
That's impossible.
??????
George?!
George, baby?!
You all right?!
Ha!
Thank god.
He killed tommy's teacher.
I saw it.
Oh.
Annie.
She was just 22.
What's wrong?
They found the school
bus abandoned
just outside of town.
Tommy's supposed to
be on that field trip.
Where is he?
Safe. He's fine.
He's with my mom.
But that man,
he also killed
the school
bus driver.
How?!
We had the whole
town shut down.
There was no way out.
What was
the one vehicle
we weren't
looking for?
A school bus.
Hotch: More importantly,
where are the children?
Gideon: You have
the town's children.
Just the little ones.
You profiled me, jason.
You know i have
no interest
in harming children.
We will find them.
We have
helicopters, dogs...
the desert is over
25,000 square miles.
Silo: You shut up!
And what with
the rising coyote
population...
derek: If it's jane
you're after,
we don't have her.
Yes, you do.
Sir, i found her
walking the streets.
Jane, he's been
coming back to
this town for years to see you.
All those why?
He says he's
in love with you.
He's in love
with me? Why?!
That's what he says.
He hides out in
your old barn,
and he watches you,
and when
he leaves,
he leaves these
wind chimes as gifts.
They're beautiful,
aren't they?
They're not beautiful.
They are the remains
of people he took,
tortured, and killed.
He is not an alien.
You were abducted
by a serial killer.
But he did come
for me, didn't he?
Not george! He came
Hotch: That's what he says.
You told me to run,
but i didn't
want to run.
I wanted to
see him again,
to see his eyes
and see his face.
And i don't know...
somehow it just felt
like i was coming home.
Jane!
Oh!
He has
the children, jane!
Silo: He has our children.
And we will
find them.
And if we don't,
they'll die
of exposure!
He hasn't got
tommy, george,
but what if he did?
Hand him over.
Silo.
What choice
do we have?
Not this one!
Tell them, jason.
Tell them i'm
not interested
in harming children.
You've studied me
for years.
Have i ever once
harmed a child?
It does
nothing for me.
Give me jane...
and they'll have
their children back.
Is she part
of this with you?
George:
Look at her, rick.
She's not
a part of anything.
She's as much his
victim as you are.
Frank: With jane in my life,
i will never harm
another human being.
Oh.
Leave her alone!
Derek: Hey! Don't
even think about it.
Gideon: No matter
what you do to him,
he will never give
you what you want.
George: I'm
telling you, rick,
they'll find
the children.
Trust me.
Take me with you, frank.
Just you and me.
And my jane?
You'll take me to
where the kids are?
Happily.
I couldn't have that
on my conscience.
Frank, voice-over: I will take
a vehicle of my choice.
Jason will drive.
Once i'm satisfied
no one is following,
i will take jason to
where i have the children.
He will then call.
If anyone follows,
the story will end in tears.
I've been coming to see
you for so many years to...
to try and make sense
of what i feel.
Jason says i'm incapable
of feeling anything,
but here i am.
And i feel.
Where will we go?
Wherever we want.
Stop the car.
Gideon: What he's feeling
right now will pass,
and when it does,
like all the others...
he'll take your life,
and then he
will really feel.
Jane: I don't
believe he will.
I don't believe
you know what
this feels like.
Frank: If you did,
you would not be here.
You'd be with
the one you love.
Where are the children?
That way.
Two miles.
No deal.
So you're just going
to stand here with me
while the children
suffer exposure
to the elements?
It's gonna be
dark real soon.
You are not the hero
your parents
thought you'd be.
I will never stop
hunting you.
Not ever.
Then i promise
the same thing.
I will never
stop loving jane...
until you catch me.
You are insane.
Love is insanity,
isn't it?
Frank: Not
a good insanity.
My hope is
that one day
you'll feel
the way i do, too.
If i ever find myself
feeling the way you do...
i'll kill myself.
Call me first.
I'd love to pick
your brains.
Emily: He told you
where they were?
They were just
over that ridge.
Which way did he go?
West.
Silo: All units,
all units,
we have the children.
Get search planes up.
Start a grid search westbound
from this location.
The tracks,
they disappear.
We'll find them.
welcome to www.1000fr.com