Previously on Criminal Minds...
Please, I don't want it.
I don't want it.
What is the matter with you ?
What do you mean, what's
the matter with me ?
Really ?  Oh, in the months
that you know me,
Hey, no offense, Emily, but...
You don't really know what
you're talking about, do you ?
Earlier this morning katrina
crashed into the gulf coast,
As many houses are being destroyed.
Are you listening to me, pop ?
The buses are filling up.
Dad.
What the hell am I missing here ?
The... Whole world's
gonna be underwater.
I got another letter, Billy.
They're opening the superdome.
I'll be damned.
... Please, I'm begging you, pop.
Pop ?
Behavioral analysis unit
Who killed at least
3 men pre-Katrina.
Believed that the serial
killer died in the storm.
A fourth body was found in
the french quarter last night.
Throat slashed, eviscerated.
A year and a half ?  That's a
long cooling-Off period.
He claims to be.
The head detective on the case.
He died in Katrina.
His son is actually
leading the case now.
Well, we need to pour over the evidence
Katrina washed everything away.
Witness statements.
So, basically, all we have
to go on is the latest victim ?
Yeah.
Until he kills again.
Criminal minds 218
Robert Kennedy once said,
Not a guide by which to live."
Hey, Reid.
What's goin' on up there ?
From Las Vegas... Ethan.
I'm pretty sure he lives
in New Orleans now.
Grew up competing against each other
Spelling bees, science fairs.
First day at quantico he backed out.
He probably just couldn't take the heat.
It's not really for us
to judge, is it ?
Right.
My bad.
Dating back to early august 2005.
He killed 3 times,
he stopped for 18 months,
We should have garcia run a list
Anyone who spent the last year
and a half doing time.
What is the victimology
in killing a mechanic,
With ages ranging from 22 to 45 ?
They just don't seem to have
very much in common.
Which is notorious for muggings
off the main drag.
A slaughter like this takes time.
And then torturing and mutilating them
The city's barely back to life.
Something like this could
cripple its psyche.
Well, with no case file there's
only one place we can start.
At square one.
You must be B.A.U.
Bill Lamontagne.
Well, ok, then.
I pictured you different.
Uh, these are agents
Gideon and Morgan.
Appreciate you guys being here.
My daddy was too stubborn
to ever ask for any help.
I understand you received a letter.
My daddy received 2 letters.
They passed it on to me.
It's a detailed account
of what he did to the body.
4 layers of fatty tissue
sliced through like butter.
I only seen that 3 other times.
Nah. You don't forget victims like this.
It's like they were dissected.
This is New Orleans.
The victim has no defense wounds.
No hesitation marks or rapid thrusts.
Almost procedural.
So you think he might have
some medical training ?
And leave each one intact ?
Anyone we could speak with ?
Left to collect dust in storage.
It's a wonder I still have room.
It'd be pretty easy to hide out
in one of these alcoves,
Yeah, all 4 murders occurred
within a 10-Block radius
On any given night, there'd
have to be thousands of people
Tens of thousands.
I worked the quarter.
Every sunday I'd get off
work around sunrise,
My daddy'd be waiting
for me at my house.
Make me drive him uptown to Frankie
and Johnny's for poorboys.
Called it communing with New Orleans.
Did your father tell you anything else
about this case that we should know ?
He tried to.
But you guys should
see that for yourself.
This wall is still standing
where daddy carved the message
There's no doubt he's still
working from the grave.
"Jones." That name mean
anything to you ?
No. I ran it through the database
And you can imagine
how many hits I got.
But in your dad's final moments,
Learned how to play
the drums in this house,
Grew up with 2 dogs in this house.
All it's gonna be now is the word
"jones" carved into that wall.
Detective, if he had
written the unsub's name,
Jones is the one
piece of the puzzle
He trusted you to figure out the rest.
But I've pored over
it a thousand times
I can't get it out of my head.
You ok ?
Yeah.
I just don't want to disappoint him.
Is that the letter from the unsub ?
I'm back with a vengeance.
The last guy made it easy,
being out so late,
I enjoyed slicing around his organs.
He was asking to be ripped,
don't you think, boss ?
Hey.
Ok.
To say that the victims
were asking to be killed
Most sexual sadists rationalize
their own behavior
But there was no evidence
of sexual assault in the autopsy.
He could be a homosexual male
Every kill he's acting
out a fantasy of revenge.
What if he's trying to act
out something else ?  Like what ?
What are you talking about ?
All 4 victims were found with
their throats slashed, eviscerated,
Investigators taunted with
the letters addressed to "boss."
The only difference is that
case was 100 years ago
Jack the ripper.
The unsub wants us to think
Please.Don't
So the 3 of you were out
together last night ?
Mark had just paid his tab at one bar
You guys get in any trouble ?
Drunken brawl ?
Anyone get out of hand ?
We were just out
to have fun, you know ?
Minded our own business.
Maybe upset her boyfriend ?
No, sir.
He struck out like we all did.
Thanks, guys.
Getting hard to keep up
with this guy.
Well, if he's mimicking
Jack the ripper,
He terrorized london for months
I'd appreciate it
if you'd gather your men.
We'd like to give you a profile
of who you're up against.
The offender we're looking
for is friendly,
Agile, somewhere between 30 and 35.
He'll allure with charm
And kill with rage.
We believe he's murdering men
This unsub suffers
from low self-Esteem,
He dresses impeccably
to feed the facade.
Jack the ripper himself
Whereas this offender is organized,
Calculating.
He might even stalk
his victims for days
We believe this killer identifies
with Jack the ripper
Maybe through years
of child abuse...
Or some catastrophic event.
Because he overcompensates
to hide his insecurities,
And since we think he's had
medical training,
Please be careful.
For this unsub,
He's certainly already proven
he knows the terrain.
Jeez !
Reid, you scared me.
Yeah, whatever helps
you sleep at night.
I'm glad you called.
It's good to see you.
You, too.
Let's get a drink.
Prentiss.
Jack the ripper took from
one of his victims ?
Besides, well, you know, her life ?
Mmm.
Tick tock...
Tick tock.
I don't know.
A kidney.
How horrify ingly
fantastic is that ?
Just that I found an unsolved murder
that happened 4 months ago
With the same M.O.,
That very organ.
I amaze myself.
Great work.
What's that ?
A lot of Katrina refugees
relocated there.
He removed the kidney
just like Jack the ripper.
Call Reid and Morgan.
I want the 3 of you on a plane
to Texas tonight.
So...
Are you gonna ask the question ?
What question ?
It's me here.
We haven't talked
to each other in years.
Ask the question.
Why did you quit after only
one day of fbi training ?
Well...
I'm sure you've
considered the evidence,
Analyzed the signs.
You were battling what's
your own demons.
Not bad. Not bad.
Those days, I did prefer
Jack Daniel's to Jeff Dahmer.
They both weigh on
your soul eventually.
Sorry
The bat phone.
Let me ask you this, Ethan.
Do you ever regret it ?
You know, I may not be
changing the world, but...
My music makes me happy.
It doesn't take a profiler
to see that you're not.
It's not easy. And it's not...
I... don't think you'd believe some of
the things that I've seen.
John Coltrane.
He was a genius, too.
But most people think
it was the booze and heroin
What are you tryingsay ?
You look like hell.
I'm fine.
I'm a jazz musician
in New Orleans.
This may be the one time
I can tell you something
That you don't already know.
That might help you forget,
But it won't make it go away.
And if I can tell...
You're surrounded by some of
the best minds in the world,
And if you think they don't notice...
Well...
For a genius,
That's just dumb.
Hey. Hey.
Where's Reid ?
I was hoping he was with you.
I did, 4 times. Nothing.
The victim's fiancee is expecting us.
What are we supposed to do ?
We got one option.
Wheels up.
Thank you.
It's not right.
The french quarter's one of the only
parts of the city that dodged Katrina.
Now there's a serial killer loose.
It's a small area,
We'll find him.
You always drink while
you're still on the clock ?
This is New Orleans, honey.
It's a cultural thing.
Where are you from ?
Pennsylvania.
I take it the folks
Are a little rigid about
the rules up that way.
Well, if it makes you feel better...
We'll play it
Pennsylvania style tonight.
I just hate that this guy
has a leg up on us, you know ?
I promise, as soon as my team
knows anything, we'll hear.
Why aren't you married ?
Uh, that involves this case how ?
I'm just flirtin'.
It's unprofessional.
You don't have to answer that.
Excuse me.
Compliments of the woman
in the blue top.
Wow. That was... bold.
She might have thought
we were just working.
We are.
Are you jealous ?
No. I just... I...
I'm surprised, that's all.
You haven't had much practice, huh ?
It's a culture thing.
You see.
There you go.
Everybody kept sayg
You just never think
it's gonna happen to you.
The report said that your fiance
On the night he was killed.
We were supposed
to be married in october.
He was just out
celebrating that with friends.
Was there anyone at Leonard's
bachelor party
We all grew up together.
They're like family to me.
Whether they met
somebody out, you know,
They're a rowdy bunch.
And they'd party with anybody.
Each of the last 2 victims
was traveling in a group.
Both were drinking, both
in public arenas, bar-Hopping.
It like when a lion preys
upon an antelope.
You lost me.
That's because you,
Emily Prentiss,
Oh, scratch that.
You totally lost me.
The antelope travel in packs.
So the lion just sits and waits.
Waits for just one of the antelope
So when he's alone,
Vulnerable, and completely unprotected,
That's when the lion strikes.
Wait a minute. Her move ?
That's gonna make a straight man
And it'll make him leave every time.
One of the victims was out
for his bachelor party.
Another one out with just the guys.
What's the only temptation
J.J.
Ok.
Yeah, he's right here with me.
Thanks.
What's going on ?
Hey.
We're not making a media
spectacle out of this.
People need to know that
this killer is a woman.
What ?
Listen.
Tourists are just starting
to filter back here.
That's not the issue.
Besides, we'll be playing
right into her hands.
Look, um...
I'm trying not to go
above your head here.
Yeah.
I got that.
Hey, you guys are
back from Galveston ?
First light this
morning. Where were you ?
I was out with a friend.
I already told you.
I called you 4 times.
I didn't have any cell
phone reception,
Right.
What's going on ?
Our unsub's a woman.
We just found another
body in the quarter.
Throat's been cut.
He's been disemboweled, too.
Reeks of booze.
It's more than a pattern.
Only this time he cut
off the earlobe.
What do you mean ?
In one letter
of correspondence,
Of his next victim.
He did.
So she's gonna kill again
by the end of the day.
Basically, you have 2 types.
Cold, calculating.
Preys on men for money.
It's more likely
we're dealing with
Motivated by paranoia and fear,
Our unsub's organized.
She follows a routine.
And suggests that they consummate
the evening in an alley.
We need to be in those streets.
Office just brought me this.
Dear boss,
By now I have rid the
world of one more.
So many men, so little time.
I hope you don't mind the mess.
They make is so easy,
Yours truly.
So were looking for a woman
who will approach men,
Comfortable being
the aggressor, no ?
And I'm guessing she'd have
to be quite attractive
Most of the women are out in groups,
"So many men, so little time."
So she's on a quest...
To wipe out the race.
Or... the father
who molested her ?
Some people think Jack
the ripper mutilated women
For someone so enraged...
This unsub sounds oddly apologetic
Why ?
That might be what
Lamontagne figured out
You gotta admit, these guys
are making it pretty easy.
No matter how wasted I was.
Testosterone will follow
a woman to Thailand.
It's just a fact.
Did you give that newest
letter to Reid ?
He knows that ripper case inside out.
He might see something I'm missing.
What is it ?
Nothing.
Come on.
You think I'm not aware
something's going on with him ?
You gonna tell me why you missed
that flight to Galveston ?
I already told you.
Right.
What ?
With a better answer,
I'm standing right here.
Dark Curls, 3 o'clock.
I got it.
She's eyeing those guys
outside that bar.
Let's go.
Oh !  Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
I hate it when that happens.
What can I do to say I'm sorry ?
How about a drink ?
Have a drink. That's cool.
Sure.
Yeah...
Yeah.
Danny.
You fool.
You dropped your wallet out there.
Thanks.
Next drink is on me.
So...
Where are your friends tonight ?
I didn't bring any.
They get in the way.
Now, see, I like that.
'Cause, uh, most girls,
They won't go nowhere alone.
I'm not most girls.
We got nothin'.
Well, the day's almost over,
Your hair's wet.
Oh, my god !  Aah !
She's mocking us.
And she's true to her word.
Do you have any tweezers ?
Thank you.
What is that ?
It's a note from the unsub,
Addressed to your father.
Dear boss,
With that sharp tongue
and vulgar hand.
Thought you'd like to know
Yours truly.
It's weird. Typically, offenders
write letters to be heard.
Jack the ripper bragged
about not being caught.
To flaunt her latest kill,
It's possible she considers
herself a vigilante.
That the men she's killing
deserve to die.
Or maybe she's contacting your father,
Not because he was the lead detective
Because she believes he'd understand.
You think he knew her somehow ?
Can you think of a woman
in your dad's life
Might be another police officer,
I don't know, a prostitute
he helped get off the street ?
He hasn't dealt with prostitutes
The unsub wrote,
"he was asking to be ripped."
What if she's mirroring
the man who raped her ?
Where are the files stored
from your sex crime division ?
Most of them were washed away.
Did your dad have a partner ?
Yeah. J.R. Smith.
Smitty, they called him.
He might remember something.
Yeah, but they had a falling out.
What about ?
Do you have a problem calling him ?
Not if it means breaking this case.
May I borrow your hand for a minute ?
I'll be damned.
The stamp on the victim's hand...
It's admittance into the mon cherie.
Oh, yeah ?
9 years ago it was called Jones.
Bingo.
Get Garcia on the horn.
O captain, my captain.
Anything. Talk to me.
About a rape at a bar called Jones ?
Zilch.
About 9 years ago.
Nada.
Ok. Uh...
With Jones bar.
Bull's-Eye.
Police blotter...
Answered a disturbance
February 19, 1998.
You are the best ever.
Ohh... and you're the
most perceptive.
Smitty.
How are you ?
I hope you got a good reason
Well, I was hoping
You might remember
being called here
Is that a joke ?
No.
My name's Jason Gideon.
We're investigating
the series of murders
What's that got to do with me ?
We need you to tell us
what happened
In this bar.
Am I missing something ?
You really don't know, do you ?
After that night, your daddy
Why ?
Some girl claimed she was raped.
I wasn't buying it.
Brass backed me up.
They ended up transferring
your daddy out
What happened here ?
It almost cost me my career.
Do you mind telling us what happened ?
My best recollection,
With 2 friends.
One of the boys asked her
if she wanted to play some pool.
Witnesses claim she was up
for anything.
She followed him up here ?
His friend not far behind.
She knew he was there.
That girl was a tease.
Anyway, a couple of guys
were going along with that.
Did she yell for help ?
She said she did.
But not a single person
claimed that they heard her.
That's what you registered
as a disturbance ?
It was mardi gras.
Listen to me.
To jewel a small city.
Anyone exposes themselves
that much in one day
But she wanted to press charges.
I knew one of the accused.
He didn't need the stink
of that accusation.
So you protected a rapist ?
Well, that right there
As far as I was concerned,
Are you gonna tell me
You know the serial killer
She was your victim.
We're trying to find a name.
You don't even remember her name ?
What about the name of the
"good kid" who raped her ?
Smitty...
You tell me right now or I'll file
a new sanction against you,
And I guarantee you,
this time it'll stick.
Mr. Tibideaux, we need you
to answer a few questions
I don't know what you're talking about.
It was mardi gras.
Well, then,
I must have been drinking some,
'Cause I don't remember a thing.
We just need to know the name...
The statute of limitations is up.
Someone accuses me of rape,
I'm going to remember her name.
I guess she didn't make
that good of an impression.
You know, I'm guessing if someone
Then she was probably asking for it.
Maybe even liked it.
Guy's not giving up anything.
Right after the double murder,
He mutilated and
dismembered Mary Kelly
It's believed to be his most
vicious kill of all.
And time to torture his victim
before killing her.
Maybe we're not too late.
She murdered these men,
And I'm guessing it's only
a matter of time
She really wants to kill.
She make an impression now ?
Work me.
1141 Sherman Avenue.
It looks like she was
a med student at tulane,
Let me guess... February 1998.
Yeah. Thanks.
We got her.
I'm John, by the way.
John.
Take off your clothes.
Sarah Danlin, F.B.I. !
Open the door.
The things I'm gonna do to you.
Me first.
F.B.I. !
Clear. Clear.
She's not here.
Guys, there are some ripperologists
Was actually killed in a flat
I'm going to have Garcia
check Sarah Danlin's
But maybe we can trace her room
back to her charge cards.
Aah !
What the hell was that ?
Shh.
You never did explain those
"things" you could do to me.
Souvenirs.
These are from bars
in the french quarter.
She's trolling for victims
in the place where it all began.
The rape isn't the whole story.
That contributes to her rage as well.
She was trying to kill
something within herself.
Yeah, mama, what do you got ?
Sarah Danlin's visa was charged
Ah, baby girl, you never
disappoint. Thank you.
Royal Ruby Inn.
Let's go
Please !
I have... I have children.
You asked...
FBI !
Drop the knife. Drop the weapon.
Put it down now.
What are you waiting for ?
Be such a shame to waste this.
Do you want it, too ?
Come on.
Don't fight it.
Men.
Sarah, my name's
William Lamontagne JR.
You knew my daddy ?
Yeah, yeah.
You trusted him. So trust me.
Where is he ?
The storm took him.
Come on. It's over.
It's over.
Hey.
Hey there.
The medic says that her
victim's going to be ok.
I heard what you did in there.
Your dad would be really proud.
It's weird.
I spent all this time focused
on closing this case for him...
And now it's over.
Yeah.
I thought I'd feel happy,
but I just feel lost.
Because you've...
And now you're leaving ?
How will I survive a woman
like you going so far away ?
Well, despite what
you may have heard...
Cell phones can be very
good for your health.
See ya.
How'd you find me ?
You're not all that hard to profile.
Your friend is good.
I missed that plane on purpose.
I know.
I'm struggling.
Well... anybody who's been through
Would.
This is all I was groomed for.
I never even considered
another option.
Now you're questioning
whether or not
Yeah.
I have been playing at this job
In one way or another
for almost 30 years.
I've felt lost.
I've felt great.
I have felt scared,
Sick,
And insane.
I don't know.
I guess the day this job stops
gnawing at your soul and...
Hands... your hands stop feeling cold...
Maybe that's the time to leave.
I guess I just needed
to try to figure out
And ?
I'll never miss another plane again.
Transcript : www.1000fr.com
Modification : Flolo, Aleksandra
Synchronisation : Aleksandra