Mr Carver.
The word is now.
- Yes?
- Got a job for you. Big one.
You available?
Yes.
He's a mercenary?
More like THE mercenary.
Nice ringtone.
It saved
a friend of mine's life once.
How?
It made me laugh.
Drink?
- What's this?
- It's a cheque.
There's no figure.
Use your imagination.
- It goes down seven floors.
- Six.
- There are seven on the plans.
- Six that concern you.
Six floors
you can do what you like with.
We've got more money than God.
We've got weapons tech
that would give a nun a hard-on.
Welcome to the world
of you want, you got.
What's on the seventh floor?
This place was built
to hide a secret.
- Now we need a fortress.
- More than a fortress. A trap.
Dr Tom Jackman.
What about him?
- I think his neck's broken.
- Tell him thanks.
- Hello?
- Hello, it's me, Benjamin.
The word is... go.
The word is go. Get the men ready.
We're going to London.
- We're bringing him in.
- Sir!
Mr Lennox?
I'm sorry, Benjamin can't
come to the phone right now.
The word is now, Mr Carver.
Dr Jackman?
Mr Hyde?
Mr Hyde,
I've waited a long time to do this.
Best you got?
'Cause if that's the best
you've got, Mr Syme,
I'll tell you what the word is.
The word...
...is hide!
Your children must be starving.
I know what boys are like.
Are you hungry, boys?
Would you like some breakfast?
There's brekkie inside,
bacon and everything. Come.
You really think I'd trust you
to feed my children?
You have a point.
What you don't have is a choice.
You have beautiful boys, Mrs Jackman,
and they're perfectly safe with us.
Mrs Jackman...
Mrs Hyde, for now.
Just so you remember. Just so you
keep in mind what's coming.
I'm Mrs Hyde.
And, honey...
just you wait
till my husband gets home.
In the meantime, I'd offer you
breakfast, but the truth is...
we don't have any.
- No!
- They're fine, Mrs Jackman.
Completely safe in these things.
Get them out of there,
for God's sake! They're children!
Get them out of there!
Mrs Jackman, we don't want
the equipment damaged.
Mummy, I can't see!
I can't see!
- Eddie! No!
- Mummy, I can't see!
Harry! No! No...
There you go, dear.
Give that a minute.
- Please...
- Sit her down.
There. That's better, isn't it?
Claire.
It's all right, it's me.
Don't be afraid. He's gone.
Do you hear me, Alice?
Do you hear me?
Claire?
Oh...
Don't look so scared.
I'm not one of them.
They don't even know
I'm here, so shhh.
Then what are you doing here?
How did you get in?
Who are you?
You're every bit as beautiful as your
pictures. He's a lucky boy, my son.
Tom's mother is dead.
Then I must be a ghost.
Where am I?
At the beginning.
This is Klein & Utterson, mark one.
There are a lot of secrets here
and they keep them underground.
Buried deep below this building.
What secrets?
Do you want to know the truth?
About Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde
and how they came back from the dead?
I just want my boys.
- That's all I want.
- It's the same thing.
Then of course I want to know.
Good.
Claire?
Just wanted to make sure
you were all right.
They've unpacked everything. Er...
For anything else, there's a phone.
Strictly internal, I'm afraid.
I want my children.
- They're perfectly safe.
- In boxes?
Safest place in the world,
those boxes.
You should get back to sleep.
They gave you a bit of a hefty dose.
Be in your bloodstream for a while.
He's coming, Peter. My husband.
And do you know what?
He'll be coming for you first.
Goodnight, Mrs Jackman.
She has a point.
I've seen what he can do.
He's remarkable, yes, but he's alone.
No one to turn to,
no one he can trust.
Everything he knew has betrayed him.
No friends, no home, no hope. No one.
Not even Tom Jackman,
not even Hyde himself's a threat
when they're completely alone.
Well, well.
Look what the cat dragged in.
It's the next stage
of human evolution.
- Hello, Dr Jackman.
- Cup of tea?
What are you doing here?
Those people can track you anywhere.
Oh, I know. Right now they're
tracking us all over Dartmoor.
They just called in another team,
sent us straight into a bog.
This is Gavin Hardcastle.
One of the men who tried to shoot us
last night and bury us in a ditch.
- I hit him with a bit of wood.
- Clever old Gavin (!)
He's got us cornered
and he's calling in the troops.
Hardcastle,
we've not got a visual yet. Over.
Hardcastle, are you receiving me?
Please restate
your last position. Over.
So, whose turn to choose
a map reference for Mr Hardcastle?
Please confirm your last location.
We all seem to be standing
in the middle of a duck pond. Over.
They've taken your family,
haven't they?
Yes.
What we need is the current location
for your wife and children.
What we have is a man in his shorts
in the know.
It's a start, Dr Jackman.
We're not beaten yet.
I... I...
I don't know what to say.
Can I vote very strongly for nothing?
- None of you needed to. I didn't...
- Cup of tea?
Yes, thanks.
We've got the good one?
- There's only one tea.
- Yes, but the one I like.
We've only ever had one tea.
I always give you the same.
Oh... I'll just...
Kettle.
She really likes you, Dr Jackman.
She prefers you to Mr Sexy Pants,
so there's no accounting for taste.
Mr Sexy Pants can hear you. We're
doing double shifts. He's awake.
What did he say?
It's a boy.
I said it was.
I did, didn't I? I said.
I take it Mr Sexy Pants has made up
his mind whose side he's on?
For now.
Right, so we need to find
your wife and family.
Knock yourself out.
I know what Klein & Utterson
can do to people.
Do you really think
I'll sell them out to you?
No.
Not to me.
Where's Hardcastle?
Probably Glasgow by now.
And still running.
- Got what you needed, though?
- Yes.
What's wrong with your hand?
Nothing. That's what's so odd.
Hyde's got a cut across his palm.
He got it late last night.
Hasn't healed properly.
But I don't have it,
and I've never had it.
It's like we're not sharing
the damage any more.
I didn't know
you could be injured separately.
Hasn't happened till now.
Maybe he thinks
I can't cope any more.
Can you?
I'd better.
Your suitcase is packed in the hall.
And the letter you're writing
is addressed to me.
You're leaving now, aren't you?
When I get back, assuming I get back,
I won't be needing this place
any more.
Or me.
I'll be gone in a minute or two.
You should probably get back to bed,
get some sleep.
Anything you need before you leave?
No, I'll be fine, thanks.
OK.
Goodnight, Miss Reimer.
Good luck, Dr Jackman.
Tom!
Tom...
Oh, Tom, what have they done to you?
Tom, can you hear me?
It's OK. It's OK, I'm here...
Oh, baby...
Oh, God!
It's all right. They're harmless.
You're perfectly safe.
What are they?
Syme told you they attempted
to clone Dr Jekyll, didn't he?
Did he tell you how far they got,
or how many times they tried?
This is where Klein & Utterson
made its fortune. These rooms.
Drugs created from the antibodies
in these poor creatures.
- You said you were Tom's mother.
- Yes.
You're not, are you?
You just work here.
This is where Tom comes from.
I don't work here.
I'm not even supposed to be here.
What does that mean?
- Tom is not a clone.
- Then where did Tom come from?
From me. I'm his mother.
He's a Jekyll.
A direct descendant
of the original man.
Dr Jekyll didn't have
any descendants.
- Dr Jekyll died a virgin.
- You're not making sense.
You know how this works
better than anyone.
If Dr Jekyll is a virgin,
then what is Mr Hyde?
Edinburgh in the 1860s?
No birth control and Hyde rampant?
The world is full of Hyde's bastard
descendants, teeming with them.
Split personalities, Siamese twins.
Tom Jackman
is just one of many descendants.
But he is the only perfect one.
The only perfect throwback,
a chance in a million,
a perfect genetic duplicate,
generations later.
We tracked him yet? Any word?
Look at that.
Birds flying at night.
Looks like they're flying
away from something, like a fire.
Freeman?
- Is there a fire?
- Sorry, what?
Is there a fire? Has anyone checked?
Um... I don't know. Don't think so,
no. We would have heard.
Then what's in the forest?
Why are they... flying away?
Why are they leaving?
"Run if you want to live."
Here, look.
It doesn't matter what I type. Look.
People think Hyde is rage...
...or hate, or greed, or lust.
But Hyde is far worse.
What is he?
What was the first day you knew
you could kill anyone if you had to?
The day I first held my children.
It's our oldest, deadliest impulse.
The need to protect our own at the
expense of any other living thing.
And we give that impulse
such a nice name, don't we?
Hyde...
is love.
And love is a psychopath.
Dr Jekyll loved.
In 1864, he fell in love
with a serving girl.
That's her.
Alice Cameron.
She's standing at his shoulder.
They found themselves a new Dr
Jekyll, but it was Hyde they wanted.
To summon Hyde,
you need Alice Cameron.
They needed to bring back the only
woman Dr Jekyll has ever loved.
Tom Jackman isn't a clone, Claire.
You are.
No.
What the hell's happening
with these lights?
- I just got a text.
- What?
I'm real! I have a life!
Of course you're real.
You're as real as anyone is.
But you were a baby in these rooms.
You came from here.
Grown from the cells
of Alice Cameron.
You've dreamed of this place,
haven't you? You always dreamt of it.
- No, I have a mother and a father!
- Who love you very much.
They should.
They were chosen for you.
What's happening?
Run if you want to live.
- What's happening?
- Run if you want to live...
Jesus Christ.
That's not possible.
Did somebody do this?
Is this a joke?
He's in our heads.
He's messing with our heads.
Look, the real words are still here,
it's... it's like he's transmitting.
It's bleeding into everything.
That's impossible.
Yeah? You want to tell that
to the guy who switched off London?
- Mr Freeman, you stay here.
- Mr Syme, no, I won't.
- You get one warning!
- Mr Syme, the devil is coming!
The most powerful thing alive on the
planet is coming, right to our door!
And we've got his missus
locked up upstairs.
Do you seriously think anyone
in this room is frightened of you?
Sit down.
Give that to me. Give it to me!
You sit down!
You're not serious?
Jesus Christ.
Sorry about that,
it just... just, er... just went off.
Bloody hell, that hurts!
Sorry, everyone. Er... is everyone OK?
Just a stupid mistake, that's all.
Er... lf everyone just, er...
If you'd just stay calm...
Er... just stay calm and sit down.
You'II... I think...
Please, just... just sit.
If you just stay where you...
What's happening to the lights?
- Is the power going?
- It's your husband.
Love has arrived.
It's everywhere.
Oh, my God!
It's them! It's my boys.
Help me!
Oh, God!
Your men. Will they stay?
I'll round up those who will.
I'll kill those who won't.
Yeah, well, try and get that
the right way round, won't you?
Christ.
Most of my staff
seem to have taken the night off.
Very impressive.
How does it feel to be half a god?
I'm the other half.
Sounds a bit Denis Thatcher.
Yeah.
Drink?
You look bloody awful.
I'm dying.
To old times?
To twenty years of lies?
To friendship.
So. Where do you want to start?
How long has this been going on?
Oh, since the beginning.
It was my job to befriend you.
That's why we met.
There wasn't a day I betrayed you.
It was the deal from the beginning.
Your defence is that it was all lies,
not just most of it?
I was never lying. We WERE friends.
- How can you say that?
- Because it's true.
I was your friend. I am.
As it happens, I'm also...
My enemy.
Oh, for God's sake, Tom, you know me.
I don't like anyone.
Except for my daughters. I mean,
I don't talk to anyone except you.
- You're the only friend I ever had.
- And look what you did.
Oh, for God's sake, Tom, grow up.
No one's who you think they are.
- Haven't you learned that yet?
- Learning it now!
People have different sides.
Sorry, just remembered
who I'm talking to. That's...
Is Hyde going to kill me?
I don't know.
Is there a way for me to... to?
Tell me how you...
...justify what you've done.
Explain to me how you can be forgiven
for what you did.
Is he listening?
Yes.
- He's a psychopath, for God's sake!
- Aren't we all?
OK, OK. Um...
There is such a thing
as the greater good.
Hyde is a marvel.
The next stage in human evolution,
no exaggeration.
With Hyde, we could cure
every illness known to man.
He's... he's a blueprint
for a better kind of human being.
To have Hyde back
is worth almost anything.
And one day people will understand.
One day people will thank us
for what we're doing now.
Even you, even your family,
even Claire will thank us.
There have been sacrifices along
the way. There are always sacrifices.
You don't start out that way,
but it's inevitable.
It's the way things are.
Advancement comes at a cost.
Sometimes at a cost to your friends.
What does that count against the good
that can be done? The greater good.
No. I can justify myself, Tom,
because I believe...
I do, I absolutely firmly believe
there is such a thing
as the greater good.
Now!
This would kill a normal man.
Be Tom again. Let it kill him.
You don't have to share the damage!
Actually, let him die. He's dying
anyway, he's ageing to death.
That means
genetically, you're separating.
You don't have to
physically share the damage.
Become Tom again. Let Tom die!
Oh, God.
Shut it off.
Shut the gas off.
Extractor fans. Now!
What happened?
You said it wouldn't kill him.
It wasn't supposed to!
He's dead, for God's sake!
He's bloody dead!
We've killed him! What's the point
in any of this if he's dead?
The gas is at non-toxic levels now,
Mr Syme.
Keep your mask on,
but it should be safe.
- Keep your mask on, until we can...
- Oh, shut up!
Strange, his...
his lungs are expanded
like they're full of air.
- Do you think he's faking?
- Not unless he can stop his heart!
He can.
Mr Syme, that's not air in his lungs.
Tom. Tom...
Tom, Tom, please don't let him...
Tom...
Old friend.
We can stop him.
What for? He's going
exactly where we want him to.
Tom?
Tom!
Claire!
- Oh, Christ! What's this? What now?
- Where are the boys?
In there. They're in those boxes
like you were. I can't get in.
Wait. Try this.
- Where did you get that?
- Just get the boys out of there.
Dr Jackman.
We have your family. We have you.
It is over.
Excuse me. Talking to my wife.
Claire, we need him again.
- I'm sorry.
- It's OK.
It's not OK. He's not OK.
He's you. You're him.
And it's OK. It's always been OK.
I mean, what the hell?
You bag yourself a handsome doctor,
there's bound to be a bit of baggage.
Dr Jackman!
You'll be kind enough
to turn around now.
- Don't dim the lights this time.
- What?
I want to see it happen.
I want to see you change.
Why?
Been over a hundred years, you and I.
Did you know that?
- Yeah.
- Well, then...
don't you think it's about time
I saw my husband naked?
Just for you.
No one else sees this. Not ever.
Hello, toots.
Hello, sugar.
Look at you, Mrs Jackman.
Look at you.
- Wasted on him, you are.
- Well, I have been, many times.
Ooh, let's make that a date.
It's a date.
But not for you.
I might peek.
- I might let you.
- Ooh, baby...
- Dr Jackman...
- Talking to my wife!
Mr Hyde!
Nothing has changed.
This is over. We have your family.
You have six guys with guns.
Make it interesting. Give me names,
I'll do 'em in alphabetical order.
Move!
Mrs Jackman, get the kids.
We're leaving.
Talking at the back! Something
you want to share with the class
- Tom, I don't know how to open them!
- Mummy?
- Harry.
- Mummy!
Eddie... Oh, God. Eddie, it's OK.
I'm here. Mummy's here.
- Mummy, we can't see.
- I'm right here, baby.
- Mummy! We can't see!
- Mummy, please let me out!
What's happening?
We have cut the power
to the life supports, Mr Hyde.
No! Please, you can't! No!
If you want to know how long
your children have to live, Mr Hyde,
hold your breath.
Switch the power back on,
right now.
- Change back to Dr Jackman.
- Why would I do that?
Because we can take Dr Jackman.
Then you'd have my family.
So will you.
You're not having my family!
Tom, they're suffocating!
They can't breathe!
It's me you want.
They're dying!
Now there's an idea.
Coming down there, boys.
Just coming to turn the power on.
Don't want any trouble.
- Stop, or we fire!
- Hold your fire. Nobody fires.
- I'm coming, boys...
- Stop or we fire!
Got a problem with that?
- Nobody fire! Nobody...
- Didn't think so.
Stop, stop!
Stop shooting!
Look at that. Look what you did.
This was clean on this morning!
You want to be careful with those.
You could put someone's eye out.
What? You think that's enough?
For me?
I'm Mr Hyde!
Show a little respect!
Colonel Hart,
when he's done, freeze the body.
I'm sure we can find
something we can use.
Your family will be safe to leave.
Someone's...
...going to kill you for that, Colonel.
Then...
...I'll die.
Here it comes.
Ooh...
Tickles.
Tom!
Mrs Jackman!
Your children.
Oh, God!
I'm sorry, Tom.
Tom, I'm so sorry...
Oh...
Are you all right?
Let me look at you.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, Mummy.
How do you feel? Do you feel OK?
Were you scared?
You must have been so scared.
It was scary
when we couldn't breathe.
Of course it was.
Of course it was scary.
But it was boring most of the time.
Why did they put us
in the boxes, Mummy?
I don't know.
They were stupid men.
Stupid, stupid men.
They even put you in the wrong boxes.
No, we swapped.
What do you mean, you swapped?
They didn't know, but we did.
We swapped.
You mean
you got out of the caskets? How?
We didn't get out.
We just got so bored. We swapped.
Sorry, Mummy.
Where's Daddy?
Come here. Come and give Mummy
a great big hug.
But Daddy...
He can't...
He's not...
- Daddy.
- I'm sorry, Eddie.
Eddie, baby, I'm so sorry.
Daddy, why is Mummy crying?
He didn't share the damage.
He let me go.
Mummy. Here I come!
- Oh! Mwa!
- Be the horsie.
Let's go over here.
# You can't catch me
# Oh, yes, I can
You all right?
He's gone.
He's really gone.
I didn't think
it would feel like this. I thought...
I thought it would feel good.
Did you know he could do that?
Take the bullets for you?
It wasn't for me, Claire.
It wasn't for me.
It's over, though.
I promise you.
You know that, don't you?
Shh.
How did you find me?
I know a good detective.
I imagine you have questions.
I am not a direct descendant
of Henry Jekyll.
This is my father.
There's no connection
with the Jekyll family line,
bastard or otherwise.
Not possible.
I am not a direct descendant of Henry
Jekyll, so where do I come from?
- How are your wife and children?
- They're very well, thank you.
And you?
I still have three bullets in me, but
I seem to have healed around them.
The legacy of Mr Hyde.
The legacy?
You think it's over, don't you?
You don't even know how it began.
Not really.
And it's never over, Tom.
Never, ever.
I need to know where I come from.
I need the truth.
I need to know why you left me
at a railway station.
Why you had to protect yourself by...
...rejecting me.
Your father was a good man,
a very good man.
- I miss him.
- But he wasn't a Jekyll.
A good man until the day he died.
What did he die of?
What killed him?
Hm? Oh, I expect I did. I must check.
- What?
- You still don't understand, do you?
What do you think
I've been fighting all this time?
You should know.
You didn't get the curse
of the Jekylls from your father.
You got it from me.
Hello, darling.
How smart you're looking.
What's wrong, sweetie?
Don't you have a kiss for Mommy?
Come on, sweetie, kiss for Mommy.
Kiss for Mommy.
A kiss for Mommy...