Oooo... yes... Barry.
Oh... oh... uh-huh...
I can honestly say
I never thought I'd be
doing anything like this.
- Shh, shh, shh.
Stop wiggling around.
Oh, Barry.
I hope that was good
for you, because
it's going to cost you.
- Whew!
- I think I'm going to love stake-outs.
Oh, that... stop. We don't want
the client to hear that on playback.
Men these days have no idea
how to treat a woman.
He could have at least
sprung for a motel room.
Um... no.
No motel - no receipt.
No receipt - no paper trail.
Which is why the wife has me
following him around.
Let's see.
Oooo... yes... Barry.
Oh... oh... uh-huh...
You know, I was once
caught in 'flagrante delicto',
with the girlfriend
of a Vegas mobster.
The mug popped me
twice in the gut.
I'm having a hard time
picturing you as gangster.
When Bugsy caught me
bumping uglies with his twist
he went off the track,
clipped me on the spot.
Had his boys dump me in the Vegas
landfill like I was yesterday's garbage.
He figured, he figured I was
down for the long dirt nap
but by the next night,
I was back with ns skirt,
ribbed up with the perfect song.
Hey, wait a minute,
you need blood to heal.
There's lots of life in a dump,
and beggars can't be choosers.
Oh, wow, I hope
she was worth it.
Love is always
worth the risk.
Eternity is a long time
to live with regret.
Did you ever consider
writing greeting cards?
Dad, I already did that.
The muscle tone
isn't nearly supple enough.
What if his wife were to reach out and hold his hand?
All she would
feel is his death.
Now apologize.
Sorry.
Not to me.
Mr. Swanson, I apologize.
Now you may
activate the pump.
Let's give Mr. Swanson
some privacy, shall we?
Stagione 1 Episodio 10
- "Necrodome" -
Traduzione italiana: AlexandraD. e Icegirl
Synch: AlexandraD. Revisione: LordThul
www.subsfactory.it
Words can not begin
to express how terribly sorry
I am about this, Mrs. Swanson.
Rest assured this has
never happened before.
Diesel's funeral was
supposed to be this afternoon!
As soon as your
husband is retrieved...
Retrieved!
He's not some bone for
a dog to find, Mr. Ulyanov.
I'm going to the police.
No one wants
this sad final chapter of
Mr. Swanson's life to
become public knowledge.
Ms. Nelson, thank you
for coming so quickly.
Well your message
did say it was urgent.
- Yes, very urgent.
- Mrs. Swanson, this is
private detective I was
telling you about.
She will ensure that your
husband is found as quickly
as possible.
- You'll find my Diesel?
- I'll do my best.
- If you'll excuse me,
I believe Mr. Ulyanov and I have some
particulars to discuss about your case.
Thank you Ms. Nelson.
You come highly recommended.
Dr. Mohadevan assures
me I can expect results.
Well in the future, you
might want to make sure I'll
actually take the case before
you start making promises.
And you can
be discreet, yes?
This matter requires
discretion above all else.
And results.
Discretion and results.
Why don't you just start by telling me
what happened to the late Mr. Swanson.
He arrived two days ago.
Liver failure.
Jaundice wreaks havoc with
the skin tones, so he was
scheduled for an overnight.
When I came in this morning
to check on the status of his
embalming procedure,
he was gone.
Was there any
evidence of a break-in?
The back door
was jimmied open.
He must have came
and left that way.
Are you sure?
Ivan and I were in the front
office working on some paperwork.
We would have seen
go out the front.
Dr. Mohadevan also assures
me that I can afford you the
courtesy of full disclosure.
Any you haven't call
the police because... why?
There are aspects
of this situation that
the authorities wouldn't
necessarily comprehend.
This was taken by
our security camera.
What is he doing?
I need that disc.
And a very large retainer.
Take a look at this.
What are you doing?
There's something
different about you.
I don't think so.
Same soap.
Same shampoo.
Same detergent.
Something more primal.
I changed my
fabric softener.
You smell like death.
Okay, how is that
even remotely a turn-on?
Decay is a common
base-note in most perfume.
Usually derived from jasmine.
- Oh.
The fusion of attractive
and repulsive scents
creates a sense of urgency,
don't you think?
Not really.
Now watch, please.
- Who is that?
- 'Sweet' Diesel Swanson.
Not exactly my type.
He was the Heavyweight
Champion for about 10 minutes,
until the Boxing Commission
found out he'd bet on himself.
Are you investigating
his death?
Not exactly.
There!
What is that?
Is that some kind of voodoo?
It's a form
of necromancy,
a particularly foul magic
practiced on the dead.
From the looks of that
mask, I'd say Egyptian.
- Hm.
- What else do you have?
Well, the guy who broke in,
I mean, he knew the location
of every one of the
surveillance cameras
so he picked the door
closest to the prep room.
Never shows his face.
He left no fingerprints.
He knows his way
around this place.
Boris Ulyanov a necromancer?
Impossible.
He hired you to
find Mr. Swanson.
Well unfortunately, in my
business, client does not
always equal innocent.
- How long have you know him?
As long as
I've worked here.
He is a most
dedicated mortician.
A heinous crime has been
committed against Mr. Swanson.
There is nothing worse
than an Easter Weekend.
I take it you don't mean
the holiday with the bunnies
and the chocolate.
She's talking
about a resurrection.
There's a code word
for 'walking dead'?
Well, many
colleagues have had
experiences that would sound
'crazy' to a lay person.
When I started, I would see
things out of the corner
of my eye that I chalked
up to tricks of light.
Now I accept the supernatural
as a fact of life.
And apparently
a fact of death.
All right, thanks.
So if Boris Ulyanov didn't kill
him, perhaps a disgruntled employee?
No, disgruntled employees
take office supplies.
So where does
that leave us?
Well, why
resurrect the dead?
Love.
His wife.
Maybe he arranged
all this for himself.
- Is that what you think?
- No, I think it's
a possibility.
He found out he had liver
failure, he couldn't face it,
so he went out and found
someone who could resurrect him.
For the record,
Swanson is re-animated.
I am resurrected.
There's a difference?
Diesel Swanson is
still walking only because
of the dark magic to serve the
Necromancer who raised him.
He has no freedom of will.
He has no life.
I maintain my personality,
my intelligence, my wit.
Your humility.
My soul.
This whole walking dead thing
must be pretty weird for you.
Pays the bills.
I've seen a lot
of weird stuff.
I grew up here, you know.
Was that difficult for you?
No, it was a pretty
typical childhood, actually,
except for all
the dead bodies.
I used to hide under the
caskets during the funerals
and pretend to
drive the hearse.
This whole place was
like my play room.
I think the other kids thought
I was pretty cool, you know,
in a freak show kind of way.
When my Grade Seven teacher
died in a car accident,
they brought her body here
and everyone wanted to see it.
Ha, here I was
having slumber parties.
Billy, my best friend at
the time - we were
pretty young
- he dared me and I dared him back, and you know how that goes.
He pulled back the sheet
and she sat straight up.
- She wasn't dead?
- Oh, she was dead.
Yeah, head-on collision.
But I could swear, though,
she was looking right at me.
I thought my dad was
going to kill us.
How about recently, have you
noticed anything strange?
Dead body walking
around is pretty strange.
What about disgruntled former
employees or dissatisfied customers?
No, it's just my dad and I.
And we've never had
a dissatisfied customer...
until now.
Hi, I wonder if I could
ask you a few questions?
If you don't mind,
I'd like to get this done.
- You moving?
- To my sister's.
I have to,
no insurance.
Diesel tried hard but he
wasn't the best with money.
Do you mind if I ask you
some questions about his
activities in the
last few months?
If he wasn't here,
he was at the Dome.
It's a sports
joint down on King.
Big screen TVs, big breasted
waitresses, big everything.
He took a job as a host.
Six hundred a week plus free
food and booze to sit
at the bar and schmooze
the paying customers.
It was embarrassing.
He was only 36 and he was
acting like his career was over.
Yeah, he was quite a boxer. 46
and 1, every victory a knock-out.
He disserved that
championship belt.
I heard about the bet.
The Commission decided
to make an example of him.
Fined him and lay
down a 10 year ban?
Must have made
him pretty angry.
He gave up.
I tried to tell him
that his career wasn't over,
but he couldn't get over
the guilt and the humiliation.
That's when he
started drinking.
What does this have to do
with someone stealing his body?
Nothing.
How about friends or family?
Is there anyone else who
might have taken his
death particularly hard?
He traded them all in for
bartenders in the last few months.
You can tell me if you're
not going to find him.
I'm not going to make you any promises
but I will do everything I can.
Thanks for your time.
No one could ever
hover as well as you.
Hey, you remember
Diesel Swanson?
Diesel, the boxer, yes.
Yeah, his body was stolen
from a mortuary
a couple of days ago.
- And the reason the police weren't called is...?
This is where it
gets a little tricky.
It was theft by
resurrection, reanimation.
He's walking around.
At first I thought maybe
it was somebody who had
something against Swanson.
And then I thought,
maybe had something
against the funeral home.
I got to thinking,
and I wondered, you know,
maybe this has happened before.
Maybe he's not the only one.
Well, if body-snatching
is the new joy-riding,
I haven't heard anything
about it.
- Could you check?
- What? Body-snatchers?
- Yeah, or grave-robbers.
- Look, Vicki, I find out
why people go into the ground,
not why they come out, okay?
Call me when he
starts eating brains.
- He's eating brains.
- Nice try.
- His body was stolen.
- Making it a case
for Major Crimes.
- And he's walking around.
And that is a Vegas act.
Look, Vicki, I have five
active cases here, okay?
I wish I could help
you, but I can't.
All right, if you find
anything out,
will you let me know?
- If I find something
I promise you will be
the first to know.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
The mask is a
representation of Anubis.
Ah, the Egyptian
God of the Dead.
According to the myth,
he resurrected Osiris
from the dead.
My friend's a security guard
at the museum.
He lets me borrow reference
material from time to time.
- You stole this.
Borrowed - can't find
everything on the Internet.
Ah, now all I have to
do is find an Egyptian
Necromancer operating
somewhere in the city.
I love my job.
Thanks for this.
Good work...
Klepto.
- You could knock.
- You could call.
You didn't seem all that
interested in the case.
Because I didn't
consider the well-being of
Mr. Swanson's corporeal husk
to be an urgent priority.
Well, I've got to admit,
you seemed a bit flippant.
You're searching
for a body.
I have absolutely no doubt
that his soul was at peace...
Yeah, I'm not
so sure about that.
Egyptian Funeral Rituals and
Resurrection Mythology
by William Carmichael.
- Sounds exciting.
Well, it's 300 pages
of university grade
double-speak, complete
with footnotes.
He did have the courtesy
to throw in a few photos.
Is there anything
of value in it?
Well, let's see, the
Egyptians believed that the soul
was divided into seven parts.
- The Ren is your name.
The Sekhem, energy.
The Akh is best described
as your ghost.
Ka, life force.
Ba, soul.
Sheut, shadow.
And the Sekhu,
your physical remains.
Well, gee, you'd
pass the pop quiz.
I spent a little
bit of time in Egypt.
Yeah, I figured.
The important ones for us though
are Ba and Sekhu, soul and remains.
The Ba is what was summoned
back into the Sekhu during
the resurrection ritual,
'cause they believed that
if the soul didn't recognize its
remains it wouldn't return to it.
Hence mummification
of the corpse.
But what does that have
to do with Swanson?
Welcome
to the Necrodrome.
Ready?
Fight!
Winner!
- Hey.
- What's up man?
Nothing like a body dump
first thing in the morning, huh?
Don't be like that, brother.
I mean, this is
our bread and butter.
- Aw, come on.
Trace evidence is
completely spoiled.
We've got no witnesses.
There's never any way
in with these.
- Why do you always got to
look at the down side
of it, man?
I mean, here we are, you know,
out here in the fresh air,
you know,
checking some fresh anatomy.
It never fails to amaze me
how much you actually
enjoy these.
Here give me that.
That's my childhood, man.
Walking by vacant lots,
checking for, you know, any
kind of corpse I could find.
This is why you
joined the force?
That's why every day's like Christmas,
man, except for the dead bodies.
Yeah, and you're the
normal part of my life.
Just great.
- Dispatch said the body's
been all beaten up.
Chest all cut apart.
Yup, that's a
thoracic abdominal incision.
This guy's had
an autopsy already.
Well, how do you know it's not some
guy trying to play amateur pathologist?
Carl Blundell?
The Iron Fist?
Local wrestler?
- Yeah?
What did they do to him?
The guy died of a brain
aneurysm a couple of months ago.
Yo, this dude is famous!
Oh, shoot man.
You've got to get
a picture of us, man.
You just...
Just playing, man.
You know, it's interesting,
Vicki's working a body snatch
case involving a missing boxer.
Man, that lady sure
does get some weird cases.
Blundell's supposed
to be six feet under.
What do you want to bet that Swanson
and Blundell were taken by the same guy?
Yeah, but we're Homicide
not Lost and Found.
What?
Two dead athletes in a month?
Two corpses taken?
That doesn't raise
any red flags for you?
Well, it don't
add up to murder.
- Hey, Doc.
- Hello.
Did you get anything on those
names I fired over to you?
Carl Blundell died
of a brain aneurysm.
Diesel Swanson succumbed
to liver failure.
So they both died
of natural causes?
Blundell, definitely
natural causes.
I can't be as
certain with Swanson.
According to Swanson's
toxicology report, his blood
contained high levels
of paracetamol.
Oh, it's an over-the-counter
pain medication.
A high level of paracetamol can
cause irreversible liver failure.
The attending pathologist
should have flagged it.
Are you saying that
somebody poisoned him?
Or he poisoned himself.
You were
supposed to call me.
Yeah, Swanson's not
the only body that's gone
missing this month.
- I know - Carl Blundell.
Mohadevan called me.
- Ah, the things you girls
talk about.
- Look, Mike, you need
to be careful.
This is not your usual
body snatching.
- Yeah, maybe not,
but one's a possible homicide.
Swanson may have been poisoned.
- Have any suspects?
- Maybe.
We both know the type of killer that
prefers poison as a murder weapon.
Naw, I don't think the
wife's good for this.
Well, thank you very much.
I'll take that under advisement.
You know, this kind of
connects our cases.
Oh, ho, ho, yeah, and you've
been so helpful up 'til now.
Come on, come on, come on.
What do you got?
Actually, not much.
All I know was that Swanson
was resurrected by a type
of Egyptian necromancy.
Okay, you got anything
that I can actually use?
I'm not sure, but I think
there's a connection between
his death and his abduction.
- Right.
Well, you know what?
I'm going to use good
old-fashioned reality and see
what the wife has to say.
What do you think
about that, huh?
- Knock yourself out.
- I think I will.
As I told Detective
Celluci, some of his
postmortem injuries
are suspicious.
There is something
in his throat.
You know on that
surveillance tape,
the Necromancer put something
in Swanson's mouth.
Really?
Perhaps this is the
evidence you seek.
Before Mr. Swanson
passed away, was he
on any medication?
- Not that I know of.
Was he taking
Aspirin or Ibuprofen?
Any kind of pain-killers?
- Alcohol.
You're asking a lot of
questions about a man whose
liver gave out.
- Well, Mrs. Swanson,
the coroner found abnormal
levels of paracetamol
in your husband's blood.
It's a headache medicine
or poison,
depending on the dosage.
You think
I poisoned by husband?
For what?
The money?
I'm not blaming anyone
of anything, it's just that
if Diesel were hitting you or
you found yourself not being
able to take it anymore...
Should I be calling a lawyer?
You tell me.
Diesel was a good man
who gave up on life.
Or maybe somebody
helped him along.
If anyone poisoned him,
it was those bastards
at the Dome who fed him
all that booze.
Why don't you go
and arrest them?
- Hey.
- Oh, we're not open
for another hour.
- Detective Celluci, Metro PD.
Mind if I ask you
a few questions?
Ever see this guy
hanging out here?
Yeah, Diesel, yeah, yeah.
He works here.
Or he used to.
Nice guy.
He tipped even when
his booze was comped.
So you guys must
have talked a lot, huh?
If he wasn't talking to a
fan he wasn't really talking.
Ever see anybody that
had a beef with him?
Naw, everybody loved him and if they
didn't, they'd sit out of his way.
The coroner found something
suspicious during his autopsy
so, you know how it goes.
Well, thanks for your time.
I didn't catch you name.
William Carmichael.
If you can think of
anything else with Diesel,
I'appreciate a call.
- Sure thing.
Oh, one more thing.
Did you ever see a guy named Carl
Blundell, hanging around here?
No.
If he did, I didn't see him.
All right.
Thanks again, William.
Well, I think they might
be the same on both sides.
Yeah, that's Bennu bird.
- And that's Osiris.
- That's the Ba.
- What is that?
- Diesel Swanson.
How do you know that?
Am I the only one in the
room who read the Rosetta Stone?
You gotta be kidding me.
God, I feel old.
Okay, Bennu bird,
Osiris, Ba.
Diesel Swanson?
I think this is a
requisition form for a soul.
There would be rituals involved in
enchanting the tablet but essentially, yes.
But why does he snap
the tablet in half?
Maybe the guy who
wrote this can help.
He mentions a lost chapter
of the Book of the Dead
that describes
a resurrection ritual.
It involves a clay tablet.
He's the closest thing
we've got to an expert.
I think he may
be more than that,
in the same magic he
describes in his thesis
is being practiced
to raise the dead.
I think William Carmichael
might be our Necromancer.
- Anybody home?
- I don't sense anyone.
Never a good sign.
Stay away or
I'll kill you, too.
- He can talk?
- He can do a lot more than that!
You can really
hear Swanson.
He's trapped in there.
I'd feel sorrier
for the man if he didn't
try to take my head off.
What are we looking for?
Anything.
Is that really necessary?
This from a man who spent
a weekend in a Vegas dumpster?
What you found was code
for some kind of Internet site.
And here we go...
What's a Necrodrome?
- Necro. Dead.
Drome. Arena.
It's a snuff film.
Technically
they're already dead.
Okay, I've seen enough.
Excuse me.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Shall we?
See what's next?
Less than 24 hours
'til the next fight.
Man, I hate
working to a deadline.
Who are you calling?
Hey Mike, it's me.
I've got something for you.
Motive.
No! Screw your schedule!
I haven't had time to
find another fighter yet!
Well, because I was busy stripping
the apartment of any evidence.
Because some cop was asking
questions, all right?
No, you know what?
You find yourself someone.
I'm busy.
Hey!
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Get in there.
Come on.
All right, that's enough.
Where did you get this?
Coreen dug up a thesis on
Egyptian resurrection rituals.
We went to go talk to the
author and found Swanson's
corpse guarding his apartment
and then I, yeah...
- William Carmichael?
- What, you know him?
Swanson's
favourite bartender.
So wait, Blundell dies
of natural causes,
gives Carmichael the idea for Necrodrome,
and then he needs a challenger.
So Carmichael slips
Swanson a paracetamol soda.
- He had ample opportunity.
- Steals the body and sets
up his next little cage match.
Yeah, but take
a look at this.
It's a count-down timer
to the next match.
Carmichael's promising
another fight which means
he needs another fighter.
- Yeah, all right.
We're going to send an APB out
on Carmichael and I'll see
what our tech guys can
find out on this Website.
- Okay, Henry and I will...
- You're going to stay
out of it.
- What? I give you
information and you cut me off?
- What, didn't I say thank you?
Okay, you know what?
Finding Carmichael is your
case, but retrieving
Swanson's body is mine.
Knock yourself out.
Did you have
any luck with that site?
Tech Server's in Bulgaria.
They tried hiding it with
a re-routed IP address.
That's a bad thing.
Uploads originate
here via wireless.
And that means what?
Sourcing location.
Triangulate.
Okay.
That's here in the city.
- Yup.
Oh, great work, Jeb.
Thank you.
You got it.
Go get 'em, sir.
Vicki!
Please tell me
you've got something.
Maybe, I can hear
something in the background
on this audio.
- Can I?
You're going to have to
trust me on this one,
unless you can hear
subsonic sounds.
- Okay, what is it?
- Train 79 Montreal.
Now boarding.
Okay, there's
a night train to Montreal
out of Union Station. We'll head
down there and work our way out.
You know this can't
have a happy ending.
When we find Swanson, we're
going to have to stop him.
Literally.
Yeah, well at least Darlene will
be able to say goodbye properly.
That should be
worth something.
Swanson?
Please...
Let me die.
Looks like we
found our next challenger.
Let's go!
Move it. Move it.
They're on in a few minutes.
- That's Mike's car.
- He must be close.
I'm going to have to have a little
chat with him about sharesies.
Hm!
- Must be something.
Well, I guess
I should have dressed up.
Oh, I'm looking
forward to this.
I wish I could share
the same enthusiasm.
Looks like this
could be a tough party
to crash.
- Looks can be deceiving.
Ohhh...!
Okay, uh... you know
what, go to Mike's car,
give me three minutes,
then switch on the sirens
then head back in here.
- How do I do that?
It's the switch
marked 'sirens'.
Sirens.
Connoisseurs
of the grotesque!
Welcome to the Necrodrome!
Any time now, Henry.
NOBODY MOVE!
VICKI WAIT!
HE'S GOT MY...
gun.
Great.
You and Carmichael partners.
Nice business plan.
We were partners,
'til somebody got scared.
Billy!
Come forward.
The power to resurrect the
dead and this is how you use it?
This is how it
was meant to be used.
I'm not going to grow old
massaging dead people's hands.
I spent years watching my
father fawning over them like
they were something special.
More concerned about them
than his own family.
The dead...
are meant to serve us.
They will serve me.
- They're people.
And you're enslaving
them for some sick sport.
A fight?
Ah, it's a promotional tool
just to showcase their skills.
And when the right
people realize what
I've accomplished here...?
I'd be lying if I said
I hadn't thought about the
military applications.
Billy! Take her!
Billy, of course, William,
your friend in the prep room.
I told you to keep
your nose out of this.
Yeah, well, I ignored you.
Besides, somebody's got to
save your cute little ass.
Yeah, and you're doing
a wonderful job, by the way.
It gets better.
Don't worry.
All right Ivan, I'm going to give
you one last chance to surrender.
I got you prisoner.
I've got the
zombies and the gun.
Kill them!
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
Diesel!
Don't!
Arrrhhhgggh!
Safety's on.
Diesel! Stop!
Can't... stop!
You can beat this!
You're strong!
You're stronger than him!
Diesel, you're wife sent us!
Darlene...
- HENRY!
- NOO-O!
This is
what you want.
This is what you want.
Henry, are you sure
this is such a good idea?
Vicki, on your left.
Diesel!
Give him to me!
As much as I would like
to do that, Diesel,
he's our responsibility now.
Diesel! Stop!
Time to find out what
a head shot does to a zombie.
- He's not a zombie!
You let him
do this, it's murder!
Where's he going?
Oh, god!
I think I know where!
Diesel! Diesel! Stop!
- I want to see her.
You're in no condition.
No.
Tell her I..
- She knows.
And she loves you.
She knows you love her.
Maybe there is a way.
Oh, baby.
I'll always love you.
It's like he's asleep.
Proceeds from the door.
I'll take care of it.
It's time, my friend.
Thank you.
What's going
to happen to Ivan?
With any luck,
he'll go away for life
for Swanson and
Carmichael's murders.
Being caught in
a warehouse surrounded
by dead people shouldn't
help his case any.
I think I get it now.
That sweetness of death.
It's an acquired taste.
transcript: swsub.com
synchro: www.subsfactory.it