???
??
I've gotta rest.
I told you, you shouldn't
have done that last hit, man.
You've been doing too much lately.
're not doing enough, friend.
I love the venom and the
sweet venom loves me.
Yeah, come on we got to go.
The last night bus is in ten minutes.
Don't touch me!
Fine, sleep it off.
I'll see you later.
Sweet venom.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:Evelyn~zx
Sync:ÈğÈğµÄÀÇ
The reaper's influence
has fallen over my sanctum.
Sorry, the reaper?
Oh, the grim...reaper.
A dead body was found
outside Lexia's club.
My sweet angel,
you read my mind.
Death's hand touches us all
but this boy's passing
might doom the Underground.
And the Underground
is the name of your bar?
The Underground's not a bar,
it's more of a...
Booze can for blood
sucking wannabees?
A sanctuary for children of the night,
where they can congregate.
At nine dollars a drink.
I thought you said she was open to those
who choose to live alternative lifestyles.
She is. You are.
Believe me.
Okay, here's the part
I don't understand.
If he died in the alley,
what exactly do you
want me to investigate?
I have enough problems
with the city already.
I don't need them trying
to blame Dante's death on me.
Is there any reason to believe your
establishment might be connected to his death?
My customers
are like my children.
I nurture them,
like Coreen...my favourite.
The most spiritual
of the night breed.
Okay I'll take the case.
- My fee is...
- $500 a day, plus expenses.
What a sweet girl.
Do you think she uses a forklift
to g her hair that high?
Before you start,
Lexia's my friend.
After Ian died, she was
totally there for me.
She doesn't really strike
me as the warm, fuzzy type.
You just don't know her.
Lexia is guarded
when dealing with mundanes.
Mundanes?
You know, normals,
outsiders.
You mean me.
This is why you should let
me work the case with you.
Coreen, I don't even
know if there is a case.
And if there is, ever since I got these,
half of my cases are a horror show.
I don't want to drag you into it.
Excuse me?
I almost became a demon bride twice.
I had my mouth stolen
by a voodoo queen.
I can handle anything
that they throw at us.
Oh, I'm sure we'll read that
in the book of famous last words.
The first thing you need to do
is find out about the dead guy.
I bet he's chalk full of clues.
Did you just say'chalk full of clues'?
I'm in, right?
I mean, Vicki, this is
going to be so much fun.
I don't know if I agree
with your definition of fun,
- but all right you can help.
- Yes!
Coreen, be still,
no one likes a perky Goth.
Gene Hansen is proving to be
a bit of a conundrum.
We know he was last seen alive
at around 4 o'clock in the morning.
But his physical condition
belies that estimate.
Oh!
Looks like
he's been dead a lot longer.
Area's swarmed by something.
Exactly what I was thinking.
On areas not consumed by insects,
I found blisters,hives and swelling.
Anaphylactic shock?
From insect bites?
Anything could have triggered
the allergic reaction.
My cousin, if she
even looks at a peanut?
Blowfish.
Well, these are insect bites,
and that gets Lexia off the hook.
Still, I mean that is
one hell of a bee sting.
We need to go to the Underground
and find out what Gene Hansen
was doing before he died.
Oh? Underground?
I have to go change.
I can't go looking all corporate like this.
Corporate.
- Hello.
- Hey.
I got a case that's taking
a tour through weirdsville.
- You care to join?
- I'm a little tied up at the moment.
I got a dead...line to meet.
Oh, all right, you don't
have to explain yourself to me.
- I've got a life.
- I thought you were dead.
I'm busy.
- You're wearing that?
Okay, this is strictly
a fact-finding mission,
- do you understand?
- Right.
We're here to find out what Gene Hansen
was doing the night he died.
I got it.
If you suspect someone,
don't accuse them.
Don't let on that you suspect.
Okay?
Do not pass go.
Do not collect $200.
You come directly to me.
- Do you understand?
- Okay, okay, can we just go in now?
All right.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't you think
we should go in separately?
You don't think I fit in?
Yeah, sure, narc.
Okay, you take the customers.
Don't let on that
we know each other.
What?
So what are you serving?
This is a private club.
It's okay, Wynter.
This is Vicki Nelson.
She's doing some work for me.
She'll have some questions for you.
Please feel free to give her
any assistance that she needs.
Taking a walk on
the dark side are we?
Unfortunately, I live there.
How long did you know Gene?
Since eighth grade.
Drama club.
I never should
have let him stay.
I should have dragged
him into that bus.
It's not your fault.
All that talk about
death's sweet embrace.
You know what?
It's not sweet.
It hurts.
Did Gene have any allergies?
I can ask his mother.
Absinthe and wine are
the only things Lexia drinks
so it's all we serve.
I've got to say I could go
for a tequila every now and then, you know?
And Gene Hansen, what was
he drinking the night he died?
Absinthe.
Anything else?
Not that I know of.
Drugs?
In a nightclub?
Half the kids here are using.
Did Lexia know that?
She'd have to be blind not to.
Yeah, she sure would.
Now this is truly a surprise.
I need your help, detective.
I don't do parking tickets.
It's not about parking tickets.
Really?
Well, you must want to know
what to get Vicki for her birthday.
You know what?
Between you and me,
she really loves kitten posters.
This was a mistake.
Hey, hey, Fitzroy, come on.
Hey, come on.
Tell me, what's going on?
Somebody left a dead body
on my doorstep.
There's another vampire
in this city.
And it's just getting started.
???
Under the circumstances
it made the most sense.
No, you totally
compromised the evidence.
I preserved the body
to the best of my ability.
No, you should have called the police,
that's what you should have done.
And that's why I came to you.
You know my life
doesn't bear scrutiny.
Isn't your job
to serve and protect?
Actually, I don't think that
motto was meant to extend to the undead.
There's another vampire out there,
and this one is killing people.
Detective...
I need your help,
unless you'd rather me
handle this on my own.
Okay.
Fine, what's done is done.
Let's just move on, shall we?
What happened?
This is what I know.
The body appeared
at my door around 9:00 p.m.
She was already dead.
The neck had been savaged
and she was drained of all her blood.
So...what? This is
the vampire equivalent of a gift basket?
It wasn't a present.
Vampires are solitary predators.
It's in our nature.
It keeps us from over populating
and depleting our hunting grounds.
He wants my territory.
- Does Vicki know about this?
- No.
And I don't want her to know.
I've been targeted and that
puts everyone who's close to me in danger.
Oh, gee...
Thanks for bringing me
into this.
Okay, if only one of you
can work this town,
how do I know I'm not going to
like this other vampire more than you?
Because I'm the devil
you know, detective.
Yes, you are.
Okay.
Okay...
Two conditions.
One, we find this thing,
we put it down.
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
- What's the second?
- Full disclosure.
I ask you something, you answer.
I want to know what colour your
underwear is, you tell me.
You got it?
Red. Silk, actually.
I'm not actually asking,Fitzroy.
When do we start?
As soon as somebody phones
the police about a dead body.
Got a quarter?
I feel so bad
for that Evan guy.
He blames himself
for Gene's death.
Does he have reason to?
Typical Friday night.
Go train in from the burbs.
Burger and a movie
after the Underground.
They must have up to something.
Come on, you don't go out for a burger and
wind up as the main course at an insect buffet.
What are you thinking?
Well, if it was
an allergic reaction,
then maybe it was
something they took.
Were they into drugs?
No, didn't seem
like the type.
Yeah, people don't always
seem like the type,
that's why you have to ask.
You think I screwed up?
Coreen, you're the
investigator, right?
So you have to consider
all the options.
If it's any consolation,
if he was doing drugs,
chances are he wouldn't have
been honest with you about it.
But what makes you
think he was doing drugs?
Because they dress in black?
Oh, yeah, yeah, I always
judge a person's character
based entirely on their
wardrobe decisions.
If Lexia knew that drugs
were for sale in her place...
No, I know her.
Look, never let your emotions
cloud your investigation.
Because you're the only
one that can do that, rit?
Look, Lexia is not involved.
Believe me.
Are you sure you wouldn't want to
wait for my report, Detective Celluci?
Doc, you and I both know that
what you find
isn't going to end up in any report.
Meet Jane Doe.
I see.
Extensive t
rauma to the neck.
The flesh looks
torn, doesn't it?
Yes, most likely by hand.
I thought they
used their...you know.
Well, if that's the case
then maybe we should be talking to Vicki.
Well, you see she's
so busy these days
I hate to see her torn in
too many different directions, so let's not.
- I understand.
- Good.
- Hi, guys.
- Oh, hey.
Say, did you get Gene Hansen's
toxicology report back?
I'm looking for any
evidence of narcotics.
I'll check and see when
the results are due in.
Okay, thanks.
Hey.
What's up?
You working that beetle mania case?
Yes, I am.
I have reason to believe the club owner might
have known about drug dealing in the establishment.
If the drugs led to the kid's death,
she could be held responsible.
Uh-huh, you got it.
Speaking of which, I need you to check
some names for me - her and her staff.
See if they had any priors.
- Do you mind running them?
- Sure, let's go.
Yeah, I'll even throw in
a little lunch, maybe a few...
Wait a minute.
It usually takes a few minutes of sparkling
repartee before you'll give up anything.
I'm trying to be nice.
Is that a crime?
No, no.
Who's the customer?
Hey, we doing this or not?
Let's go.
All right already.
Oh, glasses.
Hi.
You know...when you're
around someone long enough,
you can spot their little clues,
their 'tells'.
And this is apropos of...?
Well, I was in the morgue
today and Mike was there,
you know, investigating that Jane Doe,
and he offered to help me
gather information, no questions asked.
That was nice of him.
Yeah, he's never done that.
Not in the ten years
I've know him.
Well, there's a first
time for everything.
Hm, apparently, like you
hanging up on me last night.
I have to get some
pages to my editor.
Henry, what's going on?
Vicki, I've been thinking...
It might be a good idea if we
don't see each other for a while.
Oh.
I have to focus on my work.
Yeah, sure.
Whatever.
I have to go.
You, um...p, nn..g on bringing
your portfolio with all those pages in it?
Thank you.
Lexia Chang had no priors.
Told you.
However, Mohadevan did find
an unknown substance in Gene Hansen's blood.
That doesn't mean
she's selling drugs.
All right then,
spin me a better theory.
Something supernatural.
It used to be that would
be my last suspicion.
Noit's my 'go to'.
All right, hit me.
The bugs there are loe
of references from myths.
There's the curse of the locusts
from the Bible,
and there are spells specific
to insect infestation.
And Beelzebub, that's often
referred to as Lord of the Flies.
Why did it go after Gene Hansen?
They running some kind of
black magic thing down at the club?
Goth's are sometimes
into Wicken, not black magic.
Listen Coreen, I know you
don't want to hear this,
but somebody is into something
nasty down there,
whether it's drugs or black
magic or whatever.
Chances are your
friend knows about it.
Are you coming with me or not?
Molech.
Molech, do you
want another drink?
It's Evan.
No thanks.
Sorry about Dante.
Gene.
They figure out
what killed him?
What does it matter?
He's dead, right?
There have been people
around here asking questions.
You haven't said
anything, have you?
Of course not.
Good boy!
No thanks
I'm just trying
to make you feel better.
Yeah, well, it didn't
do much for Gene.
You don't think this
is what killed him?
He was doing a lot.
Yeah and he was
sleeping it off in an alley.
Who knows what could
have happened to him.
Hey, I know how we can make
each other feel better.
I have a new piercing.
Where are you?
There's evidence to indicate that
Gene Hansen died of anaphylactic shock.
The pathologist found an unknown
substance in his bloodstream.
Yeah, an unknown substance.
I need you to be straight with me.
Are you selling drugs here?
I'm not even going to
dignify that with a response.
Coreen, tell her
I'm not selling drugs.
You have to tell her,
whichever way it is.
You have to tell the truth.
If Gene died from something
he bought here, you are responsible.
Are you selling drugs?
No!
And we are done here.
You said you could help me.
You call this help?
She's practically
accusing me of murder.
We're just trying to
get to the bottom of this.
She's just the same
as all the other mundanes.
They see the way we dress
and they think we're freaks.
She's really
just trying to help.
It's okay, Coreen, I see who you're
siding with -your minimum wage paycheck.
I thought you knew me.
I thought you understood the dark beauty
of what I'm trying to create here.
I do!
Lexia!
Hey, Coreen.
You came into this with an attitude
about my friend and me and our lifestyle.
You were never looking to help her.
That is not true!
Oh come on, think about it, Vicki,
you can't ever trust anyone, can you?
Hey, excuse me,
excuse me.
Oh my god!
Eew!
Yuck! Eew!
Get off him!
911? Yeah, we need an ambulance
to the Underground Club.
It's at Queen West
and Crawford.
Thank you.
- Gotcha.
- Good idea.
I'm going to take
them to Dr. Mohadevan.
Oh, unless of course,
you want to do it.
No, you're perfectly capable.
We can't risk letting Vicki
find out about this other vampire.
You don't understand the potential
fallout from this conflict.
You just love to dramatize
everything, don't you?
This is a two-bit turf war, nothing more.
This is much more
than that, detective.
Fin..
inside.
I'm all ears.
In the late 1700s a vampire
ensconced in a Polish village
found himself under siege
by another vampire
who had set out
to take over his territory.
And don't tell me.
They both wound up killing ach other.
That would have
been preferable.
The newcomer methodically disassembled the life
the first vampire had so painstakingly created.
He killed friends and
acquaintances, lovers.
Those closest to him
were the first to die.
Which one were you?
The one still alive.
The rest of the village?
You're not exactly winning
me over here, Fitzroy.
Just be careful
how you act around her.
The less suspicion we
arise in her the better.
If the other vampire
believes she's with me,
Vicki will most certainly die.
Well, speaking of aroused suspicions,
do you often stand her up to go meet
with your editor in the middle of the night?
Point taken.
What do you have?
Her name was
Gabriel Claremont.
That's it?
A name?
Yeah, and it's more
than I had a few hours ago.
But now that I do have a name,
I get to meet with her parents
and tell them that their child
was murdered for no apparent reason
while trying to find out
what they know of her last 48 hours alive.
That's what I get to do.
Then I'll leave you
to that, detective.
Keep in mind Fitzroy,
I'm not doing this for you.
I don't even like you.
Since we are affording each
other the courtesy of bluntness,
I don't like you either.
Vicki seems to trust
you with her life.
That's good enough for me.
Any luck with the insects?
I sent them to the
morgue this morning.
Dr. Mohadevan is sending them to an entomologist
at the university for identification.
What about the second victim?
Evan Crane has a puncture
wound on his arm.
I was just talking to him
the night before and now he's dead.
I know, but you're just going to
have to put that aside for now.
Okay, tell me about
the injections.
Well, it's either that or
a sting - her words, not mine.
So it's bugs or drugs.
Maybe it's both.
Okay, now you're losing me.
No, listen.
What if there is a substance
common to both victims that is
somehow attractive to the bugs.
- Like some kind of pheromone?
- Yeah,
maybe it's being sold
as a party drug down at the club.
And you think whoever's selling
the drug doesn't even know it?
No, I didn't say that.
But why?
Let's start with who.
It is feasible.
I know that wasp venom has a pheromone in it
that signals other members of the hive to attack.
Of course one question still stands.
If this is a pheromone,
then how did it get
into their bloodstreams?
Are you kidding me?
People will try anything if they
think it's goingto get them high.
Remember a few years ago,
people were licking the backs of cane toads?
Do I!
Awful things.
So, this substance, it could
ostensibly be attracting the insects.
It is possible,
but to be sure
I need to be able to
run some tests with a pure sample.
All right, I'll get on it.
Oh, hey, did you have any luck with that thing
you were working on the other day?
What thing?
The Jane Doe, you and Mike.
Yes, we were able to get
an ID off her dental records.
You going to tell me or what?
Why wouldn't I tell you?
It's, uh...Gabriel Claremont.
Oh, okay.
The thing I'm not supposed to tell you is that
this may have something to do with Henry Fitzroy.
Oh, trust me.
According to her agent, Miss Claremont
had a photo shoot three days ago.
Nobody's heardthrom her since.
So the last person to see
her would be the photographer.
I'm still working on that.
I did however find
the address to the studio.
Do you want to go check it out?
- I'll get my coat.
- Okay.
Oh, one other thing -
if this photographer does
lead us to the vampire,
how do we stop it?
- I'll take care of that.
- Oh, really?
What? Surely Detective you don't have
a problem with vampire and vampire violence?
What if this vampire
is stronger than you?
Come on, Henry, anything
is possible here, okay?
I just want to know
how to kill the thing.
All right, I swear that if
I ever try to kill you again,
I won't use any method
you tell me about.
Strangely enough
detective, I believe you.
Thank you.
A stake through the heart
always works... sunlight, emolation.
Come on, I've seen the movies,
give me something special here.
What?
Like a secret word that
makes our heads explode?
That would work.
Is there one?
No,
but decapitation's
always effective.
Watch where you
swing that thing.
If we are confronted
with the other vampire
it will attack me first.
How can you be so sure?
It won't find you
any kind of threat,
and we can use
that distraction to our advantage.
Hey, I'm the one wearing
the badge here, remember?
And I'm the vampire.
If you want the killing
to stop, you'll do as I say.
Oh, hey, what
about holy water?
Shall we?
Grenfield?
- Live photo release forms.
- Yeah.
Let's see what we find here.
All right, looks like your
basic super model diet.
Diet pills, vodka, cigarettes.
Gabriel.
At least this confirms
that she was here.
- No sign of a struggle.
- No sign of anything.
- What about blood?
- No.
All right.
Well, I guess we're done here.
Somebody's coming.
Hey!
Hi!
If you guys were planning a party,
you could have at least put me on the guest list.
All right, who's going
to tell me what's going on?
- It's best if you don't know.
- Best if I don't know what?
Telling you would
kind of defeat the purpose of
'it's best if you don't know'.
Okay, you two have been
skulking around the city for two days.
I want to know what's going on.
I can't believe neither of them
would tell me what was going on!
This is a little hard to picture.
Mike and Henry are hanging out..
No, not just hanging out,
they're working together.
They're investigating
that fashion model murder.
You know what drives me crazy?
They didn't even want me involved.
They didn't want my help, nothing.
Yeah, there's nothing worse
than when you find out somebody
close to you doesn't trust you.
It's not the same thing,
Coreen.
Of course not.
So what are you going to do?
Well, we still have
a case to work.
That might be a little difficult
since our client isn't talking to us anymore.
It doesn't mean we drop the case.
Listen, two men are still dead.
The police aren't treating
this as a homicide.
You still think it has
something to do with that drug.
Well, unless there's some kind of
insect infestation that we don't know about,
the drug is the only thing
those two deaths have in common.
We need to get a pure sample of that drug
so we can find out what the hell it is.
You're going to have to go in.
Me? You don't think
I'll mess up your investigation?
Coreen, I trust you.
Clearly you're the one suited to this.
I don't know that world.
To be honest I wasn't really
serious about it to begin with.
Is this your way of apologizing
or are you just trying to
avoid having your hair dyed black?
Is it okay if it's
a little of both?
All right, listen.
There is one condition.
You're going to have
to wear this transmitter.
I'll be able to hear
you at all times.
- Okay.
- All right, you have one hour.
If you don't make contact during that time,
I want you to get out.
If you look nervous,
you're going to draw heat,
so be careful.
If you do get into trouble
I want you to say,
"my mother is not going to like this,"
and I will come right in.
I know what I'm doing.
All right, don't accept
any drinks from anyone,
and don't leave your drink unattended.
If anyone gives you drugs,
take them, but do not take them.
Do you understand?
And I will look both ways
before I cross the road,
and I will floss after every meal,
and I'll wear a sweater
just in case it gets cold.
I'll be fine.
Well, you better be
or I'm going to kick your ass.
I'll meet you back here at midnight.
I have to run an errand.
Hey.
Aww...Did Mike stand you up?
Vicki, if you're here
to grill me again, I just...
Listen, Coreen's going to
go undercover tonight
and I need someone who can blend to
the Goth scene, keep an eye on her.
I can't.
Not tonight.
Henry, there are two men dead
and I think there's going to be more.
I need your help.
And I'm working on something
that could prove to be just as dangerous,
- for both of us.
- I know.
That's why we should
be working together, right?
- We're supposed to be partners.
- Yes!
Just not tonight.
Okay.
Sure.
Can't blame a girl
for trying, right?
You know if you feel like it,
we'll be at the Underground later
...you know,
if it's not too much trouble.
Christina, what
do you want from me?
I'm in.
Over.
Aw, come on, Coreen,
it's a one-way radio.
Hey, have you heard
the good news?
Hey.
I'm looking to score.
You know, party favours.
Come on, Coreen.
Do you want
angel tears or crow?
Angel tears?
Come on, come on...
angel tears is acid,
crow is cocaine.
Come on.
I'm actually looking for
something a little different.
Evan told me about it,
but I can't remember the name.
Venom?
That's it.
Venom.
Do you know where
I can find any?
Something I said?
I've got a lead.
Over.
Oh!
Wynter.
Hey, I hear you're
looking for some venom.
Yeah, do you know
where I can get some?
Um-hum...
???
First time's free.
- You don't have to do this.
- You're wrong.
- I do.
- Ugh...oh...!
Let's be on our way.
- Why?
- Well, didn't you know?
Your friend has a powerful enemy.
It's open season on her
and I wanted to be the one to do it.
VICKI, IT'S ME!
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN HEAR THIS!
IT'S WINTER!
SHE'S SOME KIND OF DEMON.
WATCH OUT!
You're too
late to save your friend.
I'm over here!
Nope!
Here!
- What are you?
- What I am.
- You know.
- Demon.
There are all kinds of us,
with all kinds of hungers.
What are you doing
slumming it down here?
Nothing is without purpose.
You want me, right?
Why'd you kill the kids?
I hook them on the bottle,
then move them up to the spike.
That's when I feed
all their sweet juices.
I had to sacrifice a few
to get your attention.
If your kind get too much
of the bug in them,
my little ones go crazy
and they feed, too.
That's kind of a win-win, right?
That tickled.
Darkness is waiting.
Let it wait.
It'll take a lot more
than that to beat me, bitch!
Henry?
Sorry I'm late.
Sweet ride.
All right, Mov, thanks.
Well, Mohadevan says it was
some kind of insect venom
although it's unlike
anything she's ever seen.
It's a good thing you didn't
get too much of that in you.
She said you should just keep
taking the antihistamines for the next 24 hours
and you should be fine.
That thing used me
and my friend to get to you.
I almost got you killed.
You were right not to trust me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No, that's not the point.
You did fine...
all right?
You have a little work to do
on the whole trust thingy.
What do you think?
Is it me?
You just rest, okay?
Just, take it easy.
So what the hell
was this thing again?
A demon bug?
It's actually
the other way around, a bug demon.
Well, I think you
actually both might be right.
ou two, you're just like
peas in a pod lateju.
Hey, you know what?
I am so ready to take my pension
and retire somewhere else sweetheart.
- What did it want?
- Apparently it wanted me.
It was killing those kids
to draw me in.
It's dead now, so you don't have
to worry about that anymore.
Which means I am free to help you two
find that vampire you're been looking for.
Oh yeah, yeah, I figured
it out all by myself.
I can do that.
I'm a private detective.
- NO!
- Henry's right.
- You're out, too.
- Hey, wait a minute, Henry.
We had a deal.
I help you, we take it down together.
The deal's changed.
I don't want anyone else to die.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who's going to die?
Since when did you
become altruistic?
What the hell's going on?
It was a mistake to involve you.
Wait a second.
You know who it is, don't you?
Anyone else dies Henry
and I am holding you
personally responsible.
I work better alone.
Stay out of my way.
She's too powerful.
Henry!
That's great!
I mean that's just great.
So now I've got two of them
running around the city.
He's doing it to protect us.
She's been watching him.
She's probably been
watching him all night.
She?
And he's figured out who it is
and he's protecting her.
The woman behind the
vampire...Christina.
And who the hell is Christina?
Trouble.
welcome to www.1000fr.com