Now where would you go
if you were an accountant
who had just stolen
15 million dollars?
Mike  Fifteen million!
Where wouldn't I go?
Well, he's routed the money
through the Turks and Caicos.
Well, follow the money.
Or, follow the phone bill.
Let's see...
20 calls to a number in Paris
from his cell phone.
Girlfriend?
Sylvie Girard,
325 Rue Montaigne.
Man, what did we do in the days
before reverse directories?
And another case solved.
Yes, and a potential payday.
My landlord has called me
three times this week.
Oh, so I take it
I'm buying dinner tonight.
Look at you.
You just solved a mystery, too.
Yes, look at me.
Listen, I was wondering what
your weekend is looking like?
Besides tracking down the
accountant that's blown
all of my client's money
on the Champs Elysee?
Not much, you have
a better offer?
Well, it's Dylan's birthday.
No way!
How old is he now.
Like, seven?
No, eight.
Can you believe it?
Wow.
Hm...
Do you think that might be
kind of weird though?
Actually, he asked if
I could bring Aunt Vicki
to the party.
I was at Molly's the other
day and I guess he overheard
me talking about you.
What exactly were
you talking about?
I don't know... that
I was seeing you again,
you know.
That you were seeing me
or that you were 'seeing me'?
I don't know... that
I was seeing you... around.
And Molly was happy.
She always did like you.
It's just I'm so close
on this accountant thing.
I think I should probably stay
in and follow it through.
Oh, absolutely!
I mean, you gotta make hay.
I totally get that.
But, um...
we're still on for dinner
though, right?
You're damn right we are!
Great.
Annie  Turkey soup at the
mission tomorrow, Francine!
Too damn salty!
Every time.
They can keep their
damn salty soup.
Who's there?
Annie?
Is that you?
- Sottotitolo non tradotto -
- Synch: AlexandraD. -
Coreen  Oh, could you put
that down, please?
It's from a friend.
Swarovski?
I think so.
I used to sell these things.
Ms. Nelson should
be back really soon.
Can I get you a coffee?
Hey, I know you.
This is the panhandle queen
of Yonge and Carlton.
And you were the only
decent cop on that beat.
I work Yorkville now.
Less coins, more bills.
Good stuff.
Annie Howard.
Word on the street is
you went private.
I looked you up.
Well, I hate to break this
to you, but if you're going
door to door, you may have
picked the wrong door.
My friend Francine was
killed last night.
People just keep getting killed.
How do you know
they're being killed?
Some of them
just disappeared.
Last night I heard Francine
screaming, and then
she was gone, too.
How may people are we
talking about here?
Frankie, Tyrell and Lynda.
Four at least, maybe more.
Annie, we have got to
call the police.
You were a cop.
You know that they're not
going to listen to us!
Maybe they'll listen to you.
Vicki, I don't know which one
of us is going to be next.
I can pay you.
A bunch of us chipped in.
I've got almost
a hundred bucks.
That's okay.
I'll open an account.
Really, this...
Do you want me to take it?
Let me.
Okay, okay, great.
That's great.
Coreen  I got it.
All right, take a big breath.
And we're just going to start
from the beginning, all right?
Dave  So, um... looks like
she was a working girl.
And you're gonna love this.
Mike  Yeah? No ID?
Dave  Better.
No blood.
Oh yeah, baby.
Looks like return of the
vampire killer on both screens.
Look, it can't
be the same guy.
All the other vics, they had
their throats ripped open.
But this..
Maybe he's getting neater.
Everything pointed to that
Norman Bridewell dude, right?
I mean, we never did
get our hands on him.
Crowley heard about this?
Oh yeah, she's got all
the dogs out on this one.
All hands on deck.
Like that'll help.
Listen, Dave,
see that guy over there?
Does he look like
a local to you?
Seems a little upscale
for this 'hood.
How about we go say hello.
Yeah.
Listen, make sure you get
a photo of this guy, right?
Don't even worry about it.
I've been taking pictures
for the last half hour.
Vicki  She lived here?
Annie  Francine didn't
like crowds.
Actually, she didn't
like individuals either.
Not a people person.
Did you notice anyone
new around the park lately?
Anyone on or off their meds?
People are in and out,
and on and off.
What about anyone who
might have had a specific
beef with her.
Not with her or
any of the others.
It's just someone who
likes hurting people.
Vicki  Where's her stuff?
She had some
good stuff, man.
Her sleeping bag
was almost new.
If something happened
to her, that's evidence.
Nobody killed her for it, if
that's what you're getting at.
Annie, look,
I believe you, all right?
I just need some kind of
proof that someone took her.
What's this?
Looks like drag marks.
Annie  That's
Francine's bag!
Oh... that's the kind
of evidence I mean.
No! Don't touch that!
We don't want your
fingerprints on that.
Looking for something?
I am surprised that you
have time to go digging
through cold cases.
There could be
a connection to our case.
What, you think someone
broke out of the retirement
home to kill a working girl?
There are similarities
with all of this
and our girl, okay?
It could be a copycat.
It could one of those on-going
ritualistic things.
You said Norman Bridewell
looked good for it.
That's why I put out
a national warrant.
Is he back or what?
I still think Bridewell
did those murders.
But this is a different guy
and I'm developing
some theories, okay?
Involving 75-year-old crimes?
Yes.
Well, I look forward to
hearing it, detective.
It should be entertaing.
Do you know what it's like
trying to draw with somebody
looking over your shoulder?
It makes you want to stop
working and discuss my case?
I have a deadline.
If this book isn't in to the
printers by the end of the
month, my editor's
going to kill me... again.
So much for a timeless
existence as one of the
children of the night.
Welcome to
the 21st century.
Look, Henry, these
people need our help.
I gave at the office.
What, the Little Prince
doesn't help the homeless?
I wandered Europe for
years after the Great War.
I know what it's
like to have nothing.
What do you need?
Well, I've called the
police in on this, but I just
think that a vampire's nose
for blood will find things
in the sewer that they
will miss.
Sewer?
Well, you didn't say
anything about a sewer.
That's because I was
saving the best for last.
I have to meet Annie at
the coffee shop around
the corner, but I will
call you later, okay?
Going alone?
Vicki?
Nice picture.
You should get a better
frame, man...
like something in a rustic
with a linen liner...
Yeah, you wanna put the
picture down, please?
Vicki  It's okay, Annie.
Mike's going to help us.
I picked this up in the park.
It's Francine's.
It's covered in blood.
It's okay.
Mike  Yeah, it's covered in
blood and you have no victim.
I have half a dozen
witnesses who heard screams.
Vicki, come on, you know
how this is going to play out.
Even if I get a statement, by
the time I need her in court,
she's going to be gone.
She's going to be on something.
She's going to off her meds.
Mike, I just handed
you a bloody bag.
Annie says there are four
people missing, maybe more.
We might be dealing
with a serial killer.
Or, this Francine woman
decided to move into the
sewer, cut herself on
the grate, or she OD'd.
Look, Vick...
Vick, I just have a really full
caseload right now, okay?
So give me someone
who can spare an hour.
I can't sell this!
Send out a uniform,
at least to bag
and tag the evidence.
Why don't you handle it?
Fine! Loan me the
forensics team and
I'll get right on it.
All right, you know, I'll
make a deal with you, okay?
I will help you with your case,
if you'll help me with mine.
You still need me for
the tough stuff, huh?
There's something
I want to show you.
Follow me.
Vicki  Five minutes.
This isn't Henry.
He doesn't do this.
Mike  Oh, really?
Fang Boy doesn't eat?
He doesn't kill.
He tell you that?
You've never actually
even asked him have you?
I trust him.
Who are you and what have
you done with Vicki Nelson?
Look, Henry is not a killer.
No?
And how do you know so much
about his drinking habits?
How many times has he
sucked your blood, Vicki?
You really wanna know?
Once.
Are you insane?
He was dying.
Any idea who he was
with two nights ago?
Two nights ago
he was with me.
All night?
Most of it.
Well, I hope I never
need you as an alibi.
Listen, I've got a body with
two puncture wounds, no blood,
and no sign of struggle.
Even if I didn't believe
in vampires,
I'd be thinking vampire.
So help me out here, Vick.
Is it Henry, your new partner?
Or are we talking about
some kind of blood sucking
convention in town?
Maybe it's a wannabe,
or a cult.
Maybe it's another demon.
Okay, fine.
If Henry didn't do this,
then he won't mind
helping me out, will he?
Stop!
You killed the woman.
Francine.
Peter  I didn't kill anyone.
I'm hunting.
Hunting what?
The Windigo.
Vicki  What the hell's
a Windigo?
Hunger, pure hunger.
It doesn't happen to
drink blood, does it?
It eats your flesh,
cracks your bones and
sucks out the marrow.
To each their own.
So what is it then,
some kind of animal?
Some say Windigo was once
a lost man in the woods.
A cannibal spirit came into
him and kept him alive,
killing other lost
souls he'd meet.
It killed Francine.
How do you know that?
Did you see it?
We've met before.
When I was ten, my father
took me out to shoot a deer.
There was no deer.
There was a sound like the
wind, but not like the wind.
My father went to meet it
and that's when it took him.
That's when I saw
it and it saw me.
I grabbed a branch out of the
fire to keep it back,
but it never came for me.
Next day, I found
my father's bones.
Do you believe in
destiny Ms. Nelson?
Not a big fan.
My people say when
you see a Windigo,
you're marked for death.
No matter how far you
run, it'll find you.
You can't believe
it followed you here.
Maybe it just moved
here for better hunting.
But maybe if it would've
killed me back then,
all these other people
would still be alive.
Vicki  Do me a favour, Peter,
would you stay in
a shelter tonight?
I like it outside.
It's my home.
Do you believe him?
I believe he believes it.
Great. Aboriginal cannibal
spirit's infesting city ravines.
Maybe he's got
the right idea.
Maybe somebody should put
together a hunting party.
That's the spirit!
Actually, 'us' not being
the somebody I was referring to.
My book's still got four
pages that need inking.
The police can
handle this, Vicki.
Okay.
Yeah, Mike did say he
would look into it for me.
Good.
Um-hum, had to make
a little deal, though.
He's got a body.
Puncture marks on the neck,
no blood.
He wants to talk to
you about it.
Imagine that!
Henry, you're the
only vampire he knows.
What do you think?
That you didn't do it.
Henry, it's just
a conversation.
It's nothing to worry about.
That's what my father said
to Anne Boleyn...
right before he took her head.
You have a visitor.
Did he say what he wants?
He said it's
a personal matter.
Detective Sergeant Celluci,
what can I do for you, Mr...?
Javier Mendoza.
I saw you the other day
at the place where they found
that poor young girl's body.
Yeah, I saw you, too.
Make it a habit of hanging
around crime scenes,
Mr. Mendoza?
I was there for the same
reason you were, detective.
I'm hunting for the killer.
Oh really?
Well, do you have any
suspects for me?
We both know who did this...
Henry Fitzroy.
Coreen  Pretty much every
northern culture has its own
variation of the Windigo myth.
Some researchers figure it's
easier to have a supernatural
explanation for cannibalism
rather than admit people
actually eat each other.
The Windigo is human?
Depends of the legend.
Some cultures say they
possess a person, make
them crave human flesh.
This sounds more like
the monster version.
I'm not going to like
the monster version, am I?
You know what
a Sasquatch is, right?
Bigfoot?
I've got it, a Sasquatch.
It's like a Sasquatch,
only it's taller and
thinner and less hairy, and
Sasquatches are vegetarians.
Vegetarian?
These things eat people.
Well then, the burning
question is, how do we get it
to stop eating people?
You've been following me?
I've been tracking him.
Like you, I'm an officer
of the law - Canon law.
I work for the Church.
I deal with anomalies.
That's what you
think Fitzroy is?
An anomaly?
I think he is an abomination.
And we both know that your
law is ill equipped
to deal with his kind.
If he killed this girl,
he'll pay for it.
Really, detective?
I mean if you can catch him,
how do you intend
to prosecute him?
Do you think a
cell can hold him?
And even if you can imprison
him, are you prepared for
what will happen on his
first sunrise in captivity?
I know this is
difficult for you.
Men like us, we follow a code.
Then you know that this
badge means that I don't believe
in vigilantes or lynchings.
I don't kill vampires.
I have a means to neutralize
them so they won't kill again.
I offer them salvation.
Mr. Mendoza, saving souls
is a little outside of
my jurisdiction.
And that poor girl
we saw earlier,
was she outside
your jurisdiction?
I don't think
the law can help.
But you can.
Delphine Guillaume, age 26,
a lover of Fitzroy's.
These photos must be
at least 50 years old.
A little more than 60.
Fitzroy killed her,
after he seduced her.
My number's in the file.
How do we do this?
Do you hit me with phone
books until I confess?
Mike  Yeah, if you like.
Ever meet her?
She's not exactly my type.
Oh, and what exactly
is your type, Henry?
O negative?
Mike, what are you doing?
He's trying to help.
That a vampire bite?
It might be.
Might be or is?
I told you already,
I've never met her.
Any other vampires in
town I should know about?
We don't all belong
to the same book club.
Now, I've answered your
questions, are we done?
Not quite.
Any of these
ladies look familiar?
Vicki  What is this?
You going to try and pin every
cold case in the files on him?
No, just the ones I think
he might actually have done.
If I'm going to kill
somebody, I'm not going to
be that sloppy about it.
Really?
Well, maybe it's
an accident, huh?
You know, you start
going at it...
things get a little too frisky,
before you know it...
If I take the life,
I remember it.
Let's test that, shall we?
Know what, Mike?
This is enough.
He's answered your questions.
Delphine.
Old friend?
Where did you get this?
You first.
Did you kill her?
Yes.
Now unless you want to try to
charge me for something that
happened in 1944,
we're done here.
Don't worry.
Annie will watch your ride.
Are you ever going
to talk to me again?
Are you going to tell me
why you had Celluci do
your dirty work?
No, he told me he just
wanted to ask you about the
girl they found the other night.
I had no idea he was
going to ambush you.
Who was the woman
in the old photo?
It was a long time ago.
What about those
other women, though?
If you didn't know them,
why not just say so?
Who says I
didn't know them?
Henry  You should go back.
It's my fight.
What is it?
Death.
Peter.
Vicki  Oh, shoot.
Peter  That jacket
belongs to Francine.
Oh Peter, I'm sorry.
Henry  LOOK OUT!
Vicki  PETER! NO!
Peter  HE'S MINE!
Vicki  Why did it let us go?
It has its food.
We've got to go back,
Peter's still in there.
No, it's too late.
It's too late.
God, I thought you
could take that thing!
So did I.
What's the matter?
You're not healing.
I lost too much blood.
I need to feed.
I wasn't asking.
I'll drop you downtown.
Have you been here all night?
What, it's morning already?
I think you need
this more than I do.
God bless you!
Kate?
Hypothetical.
Hit me.
All right.
There's this case and
you know who done it.
I mean you just know.
But you can't
make it stick.
You've got evidence,
maybe even a confession.
But it's not good because
of how you obtained it.
Or because of
who the guy is.
They're connected?
Untouchable.
But, there is someone at
another agency who can put
this guy away.
Only this agency doesn't
play by the same rules.
FBI?
RCMP?
Military?
Right,
hypothetical.
Hypothetical.
How bad is this?
Serial killer.
Lots, over a long time.
You hand it over.
No matter what
they'd do to him?
We both believe
in due process.
We wouldn't be having this
conversation otherwise.
The important thing is to get
the bad guy off the street.
No more killing.
Peter said that once
the thing sees you,
you're marked for death.
What does that mean?
I have a new stalker?
That's one version.
Great.
Before you know it, the
supernatural types are
going to have to line up
to take a shot at me.
Henry, too.
You guys should stick together.
That's a bit
complicated right now.
Is there anything else on
the aboriginal connection?
What's Peter's heritage?
Iroquois? Mohawk? Algonquin?
You know, I never
thought to ask.
What difference
does that make now?
The Windigo has over
60 names and more than
twice as many stories
of how it kills and why,
and how to stop it.
If it is Peter's Windigo,
maybe I could narrow
down the options.
All the myths are
culturally specific.
Okay, best guess.
How do we kill this thing?
You could try
silver bullets.
Oh, come on, even I know
that's a werewolf thing.
A lot of cultures believe
silver has mystic properties.
I've got a documented case
from 1864 where the Ojibway
go hunting for a Windigo
with silver bullets.
They have documented cases?
How cool is that, right?
Well, I guess I'll be
melting down Grandma's
bracelet tonight.
Also, a lot of cultures
believe that Windigos' hearts
are made of ice,
or turn to ice, or freeze.
Some people say that's
a metaphor, but there are
stories about burning Windigos
or boiling them alive or...
Wait, that's it!
When Peter was little,
he hid by the fire.
When Francine was killed,
Annie was by the fire.
It's afraid of fire.
I mean it didn't go after
Peter until after
he dropped his torch.
That's why it
lives up north.
It can stand the heat.
Well, that's great.
All we need now is
a flamethrower.
Done!
I'll need an hour.
I made one last
year for a party.
Of course you did.
You look better.
Did you have a nice dinner?
The body's in the next room
if you'd like to take a look.
Yeah, I'll take
your word for it.
Listen, Henry.
We've got to go back.
Into the sewer to kill
an unkillable spirit.
Unless you have
a better idea.
Not going to the sewer?
This isn't your problem.
Henry, I have
an obligation.
One hundred dollars...
That's all it takes
to risk your life?
Actually it was
98 dollars and 56 cents.
Look, Henry, it killed Peter.
It's going to keep killing.
And who's going to go out
there and stop it, huh?
The police aren't going
to go near this.
Why does it have to be you?
There are things out there
that people can't or won't see.
Now that I've seen it, I'm
not just going to walk away.
You know how I surviv
500 years?
Mega doses of vitamin C
and complete danger avoidance?
Picking my battles.
Then if I were you,
I would put your coat on.
Because if Peter was right,
the Windigo seeing us means
that we are firmly on the
entr\e section of his menu.
One doesn't win an
argument with you?
Don't even bother.
Mike  Javier.
Sorry I'm late.
You're here now.
Listen, I need to ask you
something right up front.
Anything.
How many people
has Fitzroy killed?
Including this latest girl?
He's lived nearly
500 years.
He feeds every night.
I mean, how many do you think?
You said that
he has a pattern.
Most of these creatures
are quite predictable.
Fitzroy prefers women.
He seduces them, brings
them into his world.
Once he's gains their trust,
perhaps even their love, he
consummates the relationship
with the only thing that is
real to a monster like him.
Their blood.
Does he ever drink from
them before he kills them?
Always.
But once he tastes a lover's
blood, they will die.
The only question is how soon.
Javier, what...
What do you need from me?
Why me?
I need somebody he trusts.
You think Henry trusts me?
Of course.
You know what he is,
and you're still alive.
Henry Fitzroy wouldn't let me
anywhere near him, but you...
Not my style.
The Iluminacion del sol.
It drains a vampire's power.
It allows me to deal with him.
Look, Javier...
I've seen what Henry can do.
How's this going to stop him?
Believe me, detective,
I've trusted my life to this
many times.
All you must do is to
place it on his chest.
And that's it?
You have feelings for
this Victoria Nelson.
And you know he's
already tasted her.
If you fail to do what
I ask, she will die.
You must know that.
Henry  If I ever had any
doubts about your plan,
seeing that certainly
allays them.
Vicki  Bring on the Windigo.
I'd better let you lead.
I don't think I can
trust my back any more.
Henry, don't do this.
I don't judge you.
How generous.
Then what does it matter
what I've done?
My life is my business.
I drink blood or I die.
You chose to be a vampire.
I chose to give my life
to be with the woman I loved.
I chose to experience hundreds
of years of human history.
And every time I feed,
I am choosing to live.
What is your choice, Vicki?
Javier  It's time Delphine.
Delphine  Oh! Oh! Oh! OH!
Thank you.
Thank you for
your confession.
You made me a promise.
You said if I confessed,
you'd set me free.
And I always
fulfill my promises.
In a few short hours the
sun will set you free.
AH! YOU BASTARD!
How many have you killed?
I don't kill.
I give them salvation!
You should be grateful!
AH!
Thank you for giving me
the one I've been looking for,
the one who made you.
Henry Fitzroy.
I'll save him, too.
Why don't you just ask me
what you really want to know?
What is it that
I really want to know?
About the woman in
the photo, Delphine.
I'm not sure
I want to know.
She asked me to
turn her and I did.
Oh, okay.
But you have to understand.
I have killed people
and I will kill again.
It's part of who
and what I am.
I was raised to be a king.
I learned the art of war
when children today are
learning to colour.
I thought I had a
dysfunctional childhood.
I killed for my country
and I killed for honour.
And when I met Christina
I became much more
intimate with death.
Couldn't you control
it or something?
When you turn, you don't
see people anymore.
You see prey.
I spent a long time learning
to control my impulses.
I'm not human, Vicki,
and every once in a while,
somebody's going to die.
Mike  Oh, hey, Coreen.
Hey, Mike.
She's already left.
Did she go to the ravine?
Is Henry with her?
Yeah, vampires...
Don't leave home without 'em.
So, you know what he is
and you're okay with that?
He's amazing.
It's like, if vampires are
out there anything's possible,
you know -
Sasquatches, UFO's, angels.
He hasn't sucked
your blood, too, has he?
I wish.
You guys are all insane.
Mike, if you're going
out there, take these.
What, bullets?
Silver bullets.
Do I look like the
Lone Ranger to you?
For the Windigo.
I've been reading more
about the purification
properties of silver.
It's like demon penicillin.
You know what, Coreen...?
This might be the only
thing that could stop it.
So, just take them, okay?
Okay.
Oh, hey, how did you know
my gun's caliber?
Glock nine millimeter, nine
by nineteen casing, right?
I've seen you use it.
Sweet piece.
Yeah.
You'll going to be able
to smell him right?
Maybe.
Think 'reassuring tone'.
This is your plan.
You're the one who was
learning military strategy
in his diapers.
You must have some ideas.
I'm not the one who
needs to be worried, Vicki.
It's not my blood
he'll be able to spill.
Good work on the
reassuring tone.
It's not here.
It's here.
Vicki  Not working!
Henry  USE THE ELECTRICITY!
LIGHT IT UP!
Vicki  GET OUT OF THE WATER!
Henry  DO IT!
You okay?
Fine!
Vicki  You gotta be
kidding me!
Mike?
How did you...?
Silver bullets.
Coreen said they'd
come in handy.
But what are
you doing here?
I have something...
for Henry.
What?
OH! AH...!
WHAT DID YOU DO?
vier  We meet
again, Henry Fitzroy.
NO!
Time to pay
for your crimes.
What did you do?
Henry has killed
too many people.
I can't let him
kill you, Vicki.
You let him go.
Javier  The vampire's whore.
You think I haven't seen the
devil's own marks on you?
Hey, hey, hey!
Mendoza!
Sorry, detective.
This wasn't part of
our deal.
What are you doing to him?
If you care about this
creature, then do as I say.
Give me your gun.
Lock those gates
with your handcuffs.
Mike, don't!
Now!
You bastard!
The key.
Thank you.
HENRY!
Vicki, I didn't know.
Don't say a word!
transcript: swsub.com
synchro: alexandraD. www.subsfactory.it