Transcript: Mickey & JonathanSadowski
Subtitles: www.sub-way.fr (V.1.00)
My name is detective Brett Hopper,
and this is the day
that changes everything.
Put your hands up!
You're under arrest for the murder
of assistant D.A. Alberto Garza.
I will be framed for murder...
Who the hell are you people?
... my girlfriend Rita
will be in danger.
I know all this
because I am living the same day...
over and over again.
The day is the same,
but different things happen.
Every day, I get another chance.
For every decision,
there's a consequence.
Every day, I get another clue.
Hopper, you should have received
a package today. It's important.
So far I've got an hourglass
with a fingerprint
and a photo from an old crime scene.
I'm looking into a homicide from 1991.
- That's when I met your old man.
- My father was there?
He was the lead detective on it.
But he didn't close it.
Evidence went missing,
and it just all fell apart.
To find out more about this evidence,
I have to get past
Rita's ex-husband Chad...
Why do I get the feeling
- you know more than you're telling?
- Because I do.
... and go to the one place
that's most dangerous to me:
police headquarter.
- Give me that.
- No.
- Stop playing.
- What's a "Nitzberg"?
A Nitzberg...
that's a name I'm using
for this undercover thing.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You're so not a Nitzberg.
- Well, that's the point.
And who's Sid?
Sid? There's a Sid on there?
Here. "Take hourglass to Sid."
That's S-I-D, silly...
scientific investigations division.
After I drop you off at work,
I'm going downtown.
The hourglass is evidence,
and I need to see if S.I.D.
can pull a print on it for me.
Sounds like a busy day.
Yeah, it's pretty crazy,
but, for the first time in a while,
I think I see some daylight.
- Watch commander.
- Yeah, this is Hopper. Any messages?
- Anybody looking for me?
- Hang on, let me check.
All right.
Na Hop, nothing but crickets
on this end.
All right, cool. I'll call back later.
Hopper! Hold up.
I'll be there in 15.
Hey, lieutenant.
I know what's going on.
You do?
What time is your I.A. meeting
with Shelton?
- At 3:00.
- All right.
You hang tough,
and don't do anything stupid.
A little late for that.
Don't touch the bubble head.
I need you to run a print
on this hourglass.
Here you go. You know the drill.
- Call you in a week.
- No. I need it today.
That's gonna be a problem. I already got
20 guys who need it yesterday.
Hey, here's a thought.
Why don't you come back last week,
and then I can have it
ready for you this afternoon?
So are we doing this or not?
All right. Can you run
this D.R. Number for me instead?
Is it connected to this hourglass?
Yeah, that's what I'm trying
to figure out.
Come on, it'll take two seconds.
What's the number?
- "91-11"
- 91? As in 1991?
Yeah.
"91-118394641."
- That's weird.
- What?
You're the second cop to open up
this Jane Doe in a couple days.
Who's the first?
Some tool in I.A.: Chad Shelton.
Hey. I need to talk to you.
That's why we have a 3:00.
Fix your watch. Come back then.
Jane Doe. 15-year-old homicide.
Sounds fascinating. Talk to cold case.
Yeah, well, I hear
you're looking into it.
- Doesn't ring a bell.
- It's a case my father worked on,
an unsolved homicide.
Your dad had a lot of those.
Be more specific.
D.R. Number 91-118394641.
- 4641?
- Yeah.
Well, let me think.
Is that the murder book?
Is that the case?
Maybe.
Hey, man, why are you messing with me?
'cause I don't like you.
Shelton.
Yeah, yeah.
I understand.
For you.
Detective Hopper,
you're under arrest
for the murder of Alberto Garza.
Why'd you do it, man?
I'm not saying a damn thing
until you bring me Rita Shelton.
It's embarrassing, isn't it, chained up?
I've got to get to my brother!
I thought it'd be different this time.
Didn't you?
You know what I'm talking about?
You and me are the same,
salt and pepper,
a couple of flies in the ointment.
You don't believe me? I can prove it.
Give me your arm.
Quick, before they take one of us
away. Come on, hurry up.
I told you... we taste the same!
We all taste just like chicken!
Look, it gets worse before it gets
better! Just ask my brother!
Okay, listen to me.
Everything is gonna be all right.
I'm gonna get you out of this.
I wouldn't make any promises just yet,
detective Hopper.
You and your friend Ms. Shelton are here
because you're going to confess
to the killing of Alberto Garza.
Okay, okay, whatever you want.
Okay? Just let Rita go.
- Well, it's not that simple.
- Yes, it is.
You got me.
All right? I confess. I killed Garza.
Oh, you're scared, rightfully so,
but I don't think you understand
- the importance of what I'm asking.
- What are you talking about?
I'm cooperating.
What else do you want from me?
The hourglass?
You want that picture
with the girl on it? Is that it?
It seems I underestimated
your awareness of the situation.
I don't know what they mean.
You can have them.
Take 'em. Just let her...
Let her go.
Tell me,
do you believe in déjà vu?
What did you say?
I'm reminded of another time,
another place...
and a different detective Hopper.
What are you talking about?
You see,
a long time ago,
I made an error in judgment.
Now it's come back to haunt me.
You know what that error was, detective?
Compassion.
People will promise anything
to avoid pain.
Get away from her.
Get away from her!
Now remember...
there are other people you care about.
Your sister...
- Please, no! Okay...
- ... her children...
I'll do whatever you want.
I will do whatever you want.
It's an empty promise.
It needs to be clear.
You need to understand
just how serious I can be.
It was hilarious.
So the father stops for a second
to put a new tape in his camcorder.
He was one of those scary,
overinvolved dudes
who probably videotaped
the moment of conception...
So he puts back the tape,
and rushes into the delivery room...
- I'm so boring you.
- No, no you're not.
- Please keep talking.
- No, no, it's okay.
I know my nurse stories
aren't as exciting as, you know,
"Tell me where the bomb is!"
What?
I'm just really glad you're here.
Who are you right now,
and what did you do with Brett Hopper?
Okay, so you offer to drive me to work.
Now we're sitting here having breakfast.
Is there something you want to tell me?
Actually, there is.
I've been working on this new case,
and it involves
some pretty scary people,
and I'm afraid of what these people
might be willing to do.
So, honey, promise me, all right?
If you ever, and I mean ever
find yourself in a position
where you cannot get in contact with me,
I need you to call Chad.
He'll keep you safe.
What's that supposed to mean?
I know it sounds crazy...
but believe me...
Hey, man, don't ever wake me up
this early again no more, all right?
- All right, man, thanks.
- All right.
What the hell was that?
Just a present.
Tomorrow night, behind the dugout.
Gotta get me prints
on this bad boy A.S.A.P.
Done... and done.
Excuse me, lieutenant Graves?
I have some paperwork here
for you to fill out.
Sorry, not now.
You'll have to put it on my desk.
Captain wants to see me.
Something about Brett Hopper
and this Alberto Garza murder.
I see you.
Hey, where is it?
- Where's what?
- The murder book.
D.R. Number 91-118394641. You have it.
No, I don't.
You're lying.
- I'd be careful if I were you.
- I need the files in that book.
What, did you sniff some glue
this morning?
Where did you put it?
All right, it's not in your office.
My office, you went through my office?
You went through my stuff?
I.A. has classified files.
I can have you arrested for that.
I'm not leaving without it.
Then we'll do this the hard way.
I need that book... now.
Gun.
Gun!
Way to go, genius.
All right, guys, let's hustle up.
S.W.A.T. Command at R.H.D.
in five minutes.
Hopper's always been a bit
of a bull in a china shop.
Any bad blood between the two of them?
You mean other than Hopper
banging Shelton's wife?
Ex-wife.
Andrea, this is lieutenant Romero,
S.W.A.T.
Detective Battle.
She's Hopper's current partner.
Your Lt was just telling me
about this Garza business.
How much do you know?
Enough that I can tell
something's not right here.
This isn't Hopper.
Your honest assessment...
how tough is this gonna be?
Hopper's stubborn, you know?
Sometimes that's a good thing.
Sometimes...
let's just say I don't envy Shelton.
Stay close.
I want you in the command post.
Okay, Hopper's here in the I.A. bullpen.
There are exterior windows,
but they don't open.
Everything's locked tight.
I've got shooters down each
of these hallways: here, here, and here.
There's only one way out,
and that's through us.
Hopper's not dumb.
He knows what's coming.
Then we won't disappoint him.
We’re just gonna talk. I like to talk.
Ask my last two wives.
99 out of 100 times,
that's all a person wants.
And what about the one person
who doesn't?
I've been doing this a long time.
We don't explore other options
until my jaw falls off.
Says here we'll have eyes and ears
on Hopper in a couple of minutes.
I want to put my men in these halls.
Nothing personal. Don't want anybody
getting nervous, going all cowboy on us.
So has anyone tried to call Hopper yet?
Yes. He's not answering his phone.
Typical Hopper.
You gonna pick it up, or what?
Hello?
You know they're just gonna keep
letting it ring
- until somebody answers.
- I know the protocol.
Get demands, kill the A.C.,
Eyes and ears--
- What?!
- Hopper, it's Graves.
I'm gonna hand you over to S.W.A.T.
Lieutenant Romero. He's been doing this
- 20 years, so...
- All right, put him on.
Everybody okay in there, Hopper?
Yeah, well, Chad's ego's a bit bruised,
but I think he'll be just fine.
- How about you? You okay?
- I've had better days.
Look, I know you're wanted
for Garza's murder,
so I won't sugarcoat this.
I've got 10 S.W.A.T. Guys,
about 40 cops,
two snipers
and one meat wagon out here, Hopper.
Give me a reason to send
the meat wagon home.
Okay, send 'em home, then.
We can forget this whole thing
ever happened.
- Love to, but I can't.
- But you have a lot of people out here
who really care about you...
Yeah, who care, who wanna
see me get through this alive...
Whatever, man. Let's just get to it.
All right, now...
these are my demands.
All right,
I wanna see my girlfriend, Rita Shelton
and my sister, Jennifer Mathis
with her kids, brought here.
- Anything else?
- No.
That's it. Bring them here
so I can see them, and
know that they're safe.
That's it.
Found the murder weapon
in Hopper's closet.
Yeah, I heard.
Hey, look, pretend you're a cop
for a second.
- Okay, but it's a stretch.
- Just pretend that you killed Garza.
- I can do that.
- Now would you hide the murder weapon
- in your closet?
- No.
Would you go into a police station
afterward and take a guy hostage?
I see your point,
but you're forgetting something.
- What's that?
- People are stupid.
This is a D-2
we're talking about here, man.
Other than us, who on the whole force
knew that Hopper was being taken down?
- Maybe a half dozen.
- Exactly.
Hopper knows the drill,
knows that word wouldn't go wide
until late this afternoon.
So he's smart enough to know that,
but stupid enough to pull a gun
on a cop in a police station?
'Cause that makes sense.
- Who did he take hostage, anyway?
- Shelton in I.A.
Really? Looks like Christmas
came early this year.
You know you're wasting your time.
S.W.A.T.'S wiring the place.
You're never gonna find anything.
Hey, sit down.
At least put the cuffs in front.
I'm losing circulation here.
What was that crap
about Rita and your sister...
- all you want's the murder book?
- That's between me and you,
I don't trust any of the cops
in this place.
Why were you looking into one
of my father's old cases?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Come on.
I.A. Pulls old files all the time.
I can't remember half the crap
I sign off on.
It's standard procedure. Get it,
or should I talk slower?
You want the book,
why don't you just ask for it?
Why use Rita as leverage?
She's not leverage.
The worst part is,
she's gonna come running
- right in here to save you...
- Do I need to gag you?
You don't deserve her. You never did.
That ship sailed a long time ago, Chad.
Let it go.
Picture's up.
I know it's hard to watch a friend
do something this irrational.
If Hopper pulled a gun on Chad Shelton,
he did it for a rational reason.
Gonna see how we're doing
on Rita and his sister.
Ballistics are a match.
The gun in Hopper's closet
is the one that killed Garza.
- What about the prints?
- Oh, the lab's backed up.
Roknowski has some rush job.
Any chance we might get
audio in my lifetime?
We got sound.
Hopper's sister and her kids
are en route
but there's no word on Rita yet.
If you really give a damn about Rita,
you'd keep her out of it.
- I'm trying to protect her.
- You're bringing her into harm's way!
- Sit down.
- You want to see her hurt,
- is that it...
- Get your ass back in that chair!
You give up now, they'll bring her in.
I can't do that.
You can if you care about her.
If I get caught, she gets killed.
- Is it a threat?
- There are people after me.
- They'll kill her.
- What people?
- I don't know.
- Because you're a liar!
- I'm not lying. I've seen it.
- You've seen Jack...
I've seen it happen!
- I'm not listening any more...
- I've seen Rita die!
I have seen Rita die three times.
I get caught, she gets killed.
What are you talking about?
I'm living this day over and over.
If I get caught,
Rita will die...
again.
Yeah. This is gonna end well.
This is perfect.
It's just so you.
Basically, the whole world,
the very concept of time,
revolves around Brett Hopper,
'cause you're so special.
Man, and people say I got an ego.
I know how it sounds,
but it's the truth.
So every morning at quarter past 6,
Rita, Andrea... all these people
who've died the previous day...
they're all alive again?
Well, if there's some cosmic reset
button, why waste time with civility?
Why not just march on in here,
machine guns blazing,
perforate us all, take what you want?
Gee, I don't know...
maybe because it's wrong?
Why don't you just give up now
- and start again tomorrow?
- I can't do that.
- Why?
- Didn't you just hear a word I said?
I've seen Rita die three times.
Imagine...
seeing her executed...
hearing the gunshot
that takes her life...
hearing her screaming.
Would you want to live through that
over and over again?
I can't un-see that...
and you know what the scariest thing is?
I don't know when tomorrow's gonna come.
What if this day stops repeating?
I get caught, and she dies,
and then tomorrow comes
and she's gone...
forever.
Would you take that chance?
Thanks for coming in, Mrs. Mathis.
We just want to ask you
a few questions about your brother.
Of course. Anything I can do.
You know, I...
I knew your father back in the day.
He was a good man.
Thank you.
It was a real shame what happened.
Yeah, it took us all by surprise.
So, you're close to your brother?
Very close.
Great, and if he were going through
a difficult time, he'd confide in you?
You know, it's hard to say.
I mean, you get it...
the whole stoic cop thing.
He's very much like our dad that way.
Nothing ever seems
to faze them, and then...
you know, one day...
Has your brother ever expressed
any ideas that you'd describe
as paranoid or conspiratorial?
- Conspiratorial?
- Yeah.
No. What are you implying?
- We're just trying to determine...
- No, you're implying
that Brett is doing all this
because of a history
of mental illness in our family.
I'd like to see my brother now.
Yeah.
I've got somebody who wants
to speak to you.
Remember what we talked about.
Hey, Brett. It's me.
Jen, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- And the kids? How are the kids?
- They're safe. We're all here.
- Okay, okay.
We all want what's best for you, Brett.
We want you and...
and Chad to get out safely.
- Satisfied?
- Did you find Rita yet?
We're still working on it.
Look... we had an
agreement.
I came through for you.
Your sister is safe.
Now I showed good faith--
I know where this is going.
I'll give you Chad
when you bring me Rita Shelton!
Let's get another camera in there
right now. Move! Move!
What are you thinking?
I have concerns that Hopper
has a different agenda
than he's been telling us.
- You think he's saying good-bye.
- I've seen it enough times.
That's ridiculous.
He's concerned about his girlfriend
because we can't find her.
What if we do, we bring her in,
then what?
What if we find her and she's dead?
Thank you, detective.
Let's take the A.C. out in there.
I don't want Hopper
to get too comfortable.
- You were shot?
- Yes.
- When was this?
- Today.
- I mean, like, how many "todays" ago?
- I don't know. I lost track.
Your wounds carry over
even though no one else's do?
Yep, except for the bandages.
- I gotta patch this up every day.
- So you get shot, you can die.
- I'm guessing, yeah.
- Good to know.
While you're over there
cracking yourself up,
you realize
they still haven't found Rita.
- For all I know, they already got her.
- They'll find her.
You hear that?
Yeah, they killed the air.
I hate this part.
Gotta say, even though
you're riding on the short bus,
I applaud your attention to detail.
Swapping the cell phone battery,
the girl at the pool,
the bus and Margo, is it?
It's good stuff.
What comes after the bus thing?
I'm serious. I want to know.
I go to my mailbox and I get a package.
And what's in it?
Evidence...
Something that might clear me.
Hi!
Who in the hell is calling him?
- Yeah.
- Before you say one word to me,
they still got ears on you in that room.
For the record, you sound like
a complete whack job.
I got more important things
to worry about right now.
I wouldn't be so sure.
They've got you on suicide watch.
- What?
- Listen, there's a suction mic
on the window west side of the room.
Lift up the blind, you'll see it.
Oh, and you might also
notice the half-dozen snipers waiting
to ventilate your bughouse of a brain.
Get in the chair.
Hurry up, get in the chair!
Where the hell is my picture?
He's losing it.
I need you to do something for me.
I need three guys.
Move, move!
So... let's just say
that you're not completely nuts.
Let's...
posit the notion that you could
be living the same day over and over.
How is that possible?
What with the laws of physics...
and all?
You're not gonna start with
that discovery channel stuff, are you?
You know,
in these last few wonderful hours,
my thoughts have alternated between
why you'd be trapped in the same day
and the most painful way i could
kill you when I get my hands free.
I'm thinking about this theory
I read about in an actual book, Hopper :
"Time as a texture."
Sometimes it's smooth,
sometimes it's soft...
But other times,
it can be sticky.
- Sticky?
- Yeah.
Maybe you're stuck.
Here I thought you'd blame it
on all the tree huggers
like you do everything else.
Or maybe it's more rooted
in quantum physics.
You ever read "Möbius transformations
and the Doppler shift",
or "Spacetime mediation
of quantum interactions"?
That is just so you...
- What?
- Just like back in the day,
always showing off that education,
like all these plaques
you got up in your office.
I'm not showing off.
Forget my theories.
Maybe your mom just dropped you on your
head too many times when you were a kid.
At least I put some thought into it.
Why do you think it's happening?
You gotta have some theories.
It's irresponsible not to.
I don't know.
I mean, at first i thought it was 'cause
i was injected with that drug, but...
I'm not talking physical,
"how" it's happening.
I'm talking the metaphysical "why."
Well, maybe it's not about why.
Maybe things just happen to people.
Maybe you were chosen.
No, I...
definitely have not been chosen.
Well, then
how do you explain it, Buck Rogers?
In your gut,
what does it feel like it is?
I feel like I'm being punished.
Punished...
For what?
Maybe you're the victim
of some government conspiracy?
I hear they've been doing
some experiments on
- stupid cops.
- Sit down!
That would explain a lot.
Sit down!
Initiate, now!
Move, move, move!
Get the hell back!
- Stand down!
- You.
Get back!
- What the hell was that?
- Is everyone okay?
Shut up, shut up!
I'm only dealing with Andrea Battle.
I should blow your head off.
- You tried to kill me!
- I saved you! Thank you'd be fine...
Stop lying! Stop lying!
Sniper was gonna put
a bullet in your head,
but I pushed you out of the way.
Guy had a .45. Real bullets.
Shoot to kill.
That's not protocol.
They should have entered non-lethal...
flash-bangs and bean bag rounds.
The second team did.
Why'd you do it?
What, save your ass?
You may be all psycho right now,
but we were friends once...
Partners.
I didn't want to see you
go out like that.
Yeah, we were partners but...
we weren't...
I mean...
We rode together
every day for two years!
Fine.
Whatever way you wanna put it.
By the way, you owe me $171.53.
What?
I bought coffee
twice as much as you did.
About time you paid your debts.
You kept a tab?
I'm thorough.
It's what makes me good at what I do.
Here you go.
The print was in the system.
Hopper. Isn't that the...
Thank you.
Hopper will only talk to you.
Come on.
I've got a solution.
If everyone you care about
is in trouble because of you,
why don't you get out of the equation?
- What are you talking about?
- Kill yourself.
Seems to me if you die,
everyone else will be fine.
- You're not getting off that easy.
- Pretty please?
I can't. Not if I can change the day.
What about Rita?
You think you can do
something to change her situation?
Maybe.
What about the guys that are after Rita?
What do they want from you?
They wanted me
to confess to Garza's murder.
- So confess.
- I did!
But they said
that I didn't take them seriously.
What could be more serious
than taking a cop hostage
in a police station
to save the woman you love?
Come on man, what kind of cop are you?
All these days, you haven't figured out
one way to contact these guys?
You remember Baxter, right?
Yo, Hop.
Been looking for you, man.
Damien, I need to speak to Baxter.
Well, if I see that fed,
I'll pass word along.
That should be easy, 'cause I know
he's stuffed in the back of your truck.
Please...
It's for you, it's Hop.
- Hopper?
- Baxter, listen good,
'cause I only have time
to tell you this once.
Now you gotta follow my exact
instructions, or Damien will kill you.
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
I know about the guys
who've been squeezing you,
in the blue sedan.
I need you to contact them for me
and tell them I'll give
them whatever they want, okay?
I will confess,
but only if they let Rita go.
All right, you got that?
Yes.
You also gotta tell them...
Now this is really important! Listen...
I know how serious this is.
I understand how serious this is.
Repeat that back to me.
You understand how serious this is.
All right.
Now Baxter, if you screw me on this...
you will die.
I need to make a call.
Detective Battle's here.
Thanks for coming, detective.
Rita Shelton's car was just found
on Cahuenga boulevard...
Keys still in the ignition,
she's nowhere to be found.
What do you need me to do?
Yeah.
Hey, Hopper.
Heard you missed me.
Did you get it?
That thing
you asked about matched
a guy named Miguel Dominguez.
He's been in Pelican Bay since '89,
serving five consecutive life sentences,
so there's no way he could've killed
anyone in '91, let alone Garza.
I thought they were connected.
What about Rita?
He deserves to know the truth.
No, it's the only card we have.
They found her car. She's missing.
That was irresponsible.
You might've just cost us two lifes.
Now get out!
We're ending this now.
This is all your fault!
All you had to do
was give me the murder book.
You come storming on in here...
Did you even think to look in cold case?
You know, where they keep
the unsolved murder books?
You didn't even look, did you?
No, I didn't go down there,
'cause you told me
it was in that damn
filing cabinet right there.
- I never said that.
- Yes, you did!
- When?
- Today!
Yesterday...
How the hell am I gonna get down there?
How am I gonna get the murder book?
Looks like your time is up.
Yours, too.
Don't shoot!
- Don't shoot, we're coming out!
- If I die, he dies.
If I die, he dies!
Did I ever tell you about our honeymoon?
Rita and I were on our way to Vegas.
It was a Saturday night.
I had this big special dinner planned...
And there was this dog.
Thing got nailed on the 15.
It was this mangy stray.
It was all bloody on its last legs...
And meanwhile,
I got bottles of Dom on ice,
a 7-course feast,
violins, the whole shot.
Rita had to stop,
had to try to save the thing...
Hopper, where you going?
It took a while, but I finally
convinced her we had to go.
She was just so torn up over it.
That's when I knew, that's...
that's when I knew
I'd made the right decision,
That this was the woman for me.
Hopper, you are leaving us no choice.
A woman with that much heart...
You know, the only reason she's with you
is she pities you, Hopper.
Is that right?
She's a rescuer.
She needs things she can save.
That why she married you?
No, that's why it didn't work out.
I don't need saving.
Never did.
I was fine just the way I was.
Stop right there, Hopper.
I ain't going nowhere.
I'm just trying to get to cold case.
You promised to release Chad... if we
brought your sister and Rita Shelton.
Yeah, and you failed.
Rita, did they hurt you?
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
We need to know
that you are a man
of your word.
We need to know how serious you are.
I don't think you understand
the seriousness of what I'm asking.
You see that? You see that?
Yeah.
Now we kept our part of the deal.
I need you to keep yours.
I confess.
I confess to killing Alberto Garza.
All right? I did it.
You hear me?
Hey Chad...
- Yeah?
- Just so you know...
It was never loaded.
Let's go! Move, move!
Don't worry...
I'll look out for her.
Oh, and if you're right?
The book's in the front seat of my car.
You're under arrest for the murder
of assistant D.A. Alberto Garza.
You have the right to remain silent.
If you give up the right
to remain silent, anything you say...