Seven years ago,
I was recruited to work for SD-6,
which I was told
was a covert branch of the CIA.
I was trained as a spy,
warned not to tell anyone what I did.
I thought I was working
for the good guys
until I told my fiancé about SD-6,
and they had him killed.
That's when I learned the truth,
that SD-6 is part of the enemy
I thought I was fighting.
Now, I'm a double agent, working
with the real CIA to bring down SD-6.
My only ally is another double agent,
a man I hardly know. My father.
It seems that during the Cold War,
six nuclear weapons
were smuggled into
the United States.
When SD-6 picked up our nuke,
it went on a plane bound for Egypt.
- What?
- They sold the thing to Hassan.
- You're going to Cairo.
- Yeah. I need your help.
SD-6 can't know I'm there.
I'm holding the core.
I'm holding enough plutonium
to liquefy our insides in 48 hours.
Put it down.
- I put it down, you'll kill me.
- Now.
I'm going to count to one.
OK.
You're falling behind, Sydney.
And I don't accept late papers.
OK, you know what?
Good point, you shouldn't,
but I do have a really good excuse.
OK. I was on a business trip
and my flight was delayed.
I have the ball
and I'm ready for instruction!
- ETA two minutes.
- I might not have two minutes!
If you recall,
I made it clear in my syllabus
I would receive papers via email
if you can't get them to me directly.
- You have email, don't you?
- Yes. You're not gonna believe this,
but there was a blackout
where I was staying.
Honestly.
OK, stop.
I can appreciate the complexities
of pursuing a degree
with a full-time job,
but it seems your work is taking
precedence over your education.
Now, admit it, Sydney.
You're dropping the ball.
My job is a means to an end.
And your class makes me feel like
maybe, someday, I'll be able
to do something more with my life.
Alright.
Next paper's due Thursday.
That won't be a problem?
No, not at all. Thank you so much.
Are you sure about that?
How's Friday?
It's confusing.
Charlie has an amazing offer
from Flemming-Letterman.
It's the most prestigious law firm
in LA.
- But Charlie's not excited?
- He's gone weird.
He never wants to talk about it,
he doesn't brag.
Wouldn't you brag?
I would be non-stop talking
about myself if they wanted me.
You and Charlie
come from different places.
In his whole family,
he's first-generation college.
- True.
- Not to mention law school.
He's probably nervous.
He's probably terrified.
I called my dad last night
to ask him what he thought
and he said, "Give it a rest."
"Charlie is one of the good ones."
- He's right.
- It's weird having the feeling
that someone you love
isn't telling you everything.
I can't believe you call your dad
for advice. I just can't imagine.
The worst
is having a dad who is always right.
No, it's not the worst thing.
I ran into my father... last week.
- Where?
- Just...
Just out shopping.
It was... It was so empty.
It wasn't empty.
It was full, actually.
Full of awkwardness
and lame pauses and...
I don't know.
Your dad, you know, he's just...
He's just your dad.
I don't want it to be like that
any more. I'm sick of it.
I mean, I always had this feeling
that maybe, someday,
I don't know,
my dad and I would connect,
and that things
could start to get better.
You know my opinion of your dad.
I know.
But if you can find it in your heart
to forgive him for being
who he's been all your life,
which I would find impossible
and could never do,
then you should make a real effort.
How do you start something that?
I have so many questions, I just...
You can call the man.
I won't reconnect with him
on the phone.
Go to his work. Go to the aeroplane
factory and just start talking.
You're really good at talking.
Dad?
Sydney, what are you doing here?
I would've called.
I didn't know if...
You shouldn't be here.
I told you
I have a thousand questions.
They're keeping me awake at night.
Then take something.
Did you know SD-6
was gonna recruit me? Did you help?
- This isn't the time.
- I need to ask about Mom.
- Sydney...
- Was it just an accident,
or did you tell her about what
you were doing, like I told Danny?
Look where you are. You're exposed.
Dad, please.
Don't come here again. Not again.
The device that you withdrew
from Taipei last month
remains in Analysis.
We're trying to figure out
what it does and how it does it.
At the time, I told you
that Oskar Müller was the designer.
The truth,
Müller was just an academic,
a scientist
who took another man's sketches,
translated them into construction
plans and put it together.
- So, who designed it?
- A man named Milo Rambaldi.
- Never heard of him.
- That doesn't surprise me.
He died in 1496.
Rambaldi was Pope Alexander VI's
chief architect.
Excommunicated for heresy,
sentenced to death
for suggesting that someday science
would allow us to know God.
After his death,
his workshop was torn apart.
His plans and sketches were traded
and sold for next to nothing.
In the next five centuries, his work
was scattered throughout the world.
No one is sure what's left.
Which is unfortunate
because, last March,
a Russian historian happened upon
one of Rambaldi's early designs.
She recognised something
that looked a lot like a transistor.
I don't understand.
Do you understand?
It seems that Rambaldi
was a prophet.
We acquired one of his notebooks
from San Lazzaro.
This is the analysis report.
Rudimentary schematic for
a transportable vocal communicator.
He was designing a cellphone around
the time of the Ottoman Empire.
- Come on!
- Ridiculous, right?
You know me.
I'm not a New Age kind of guy.
I don't believe
in the power of the pyramid.
I'm not a big granola fan.
This stuff
typically makes me roll my eyes,
and then my eyes came across this.
Written in 1489.
Rambaldi wrote machine code?
If I could,
it's probably not machine code.
The concept of zero has been
around... Well, it precedes Christ.
The numeral one
has been around even longer.
Ptolemy used zeroes as punctuation.
In Indian text, zero is more of
a spiritual concept than a number.
When I say Indian,
I don't mean bows and arrows and -
Thank you, Marshall.
We don't know what it is.
Rambaldi has become a priority.
We want to learn what it is
before anybody else.
- Have you run the sequence?
- It's incomplete.
The sequence was written on
the back of two Rambaldi sketches.
We possess one. The other
is in this man's private collection.
Eduardo Benegas, Spanish VC.
Auto enthusiast.
He also owns the largest collection
of pornographic art in Madrid.
Which I thought
was an interesting fact. Sorry.
We negotiated to buy one of the
sketches and he withdrew the piece.
We believe he was tipped off
as to its real value.
We think it's K-Directorate.
They're on to Rambaldi too.
It's possible K-Directorate
stole a key from Benegas.
Our data-reconnoissance division
thinks, although it hasn't confirmed,
that he's surrounded at all times
by six bodyguards.
We're talking about guys trained
under UEl Special Forces.
We also have reason to believe
that Benegas keeps the key
on his person at all times.
So the big question is,
how did K-Directorate swipe the key?
Anna.
It was Anna, wasn't it?
Eduardo Benegas has a sketch
drawn by Milo Rambaldi.
There's a code written on the back.
SD-6 wants that code.
The sketch is in a case.
The case is in a vault.
The vault is on the top floor
of a car museum owned by Benegas.
So I'm going to Madrid.
What's my counter mission?
So it's 2,000 words or less
on gene sequencing
in virus-resisting cabbage.
And I'm realising slowly that
I might not
have a real handle on it.
Which part?
Just the part
about the gene sequencing
and the virus-resistant cabbage.
Doesn't your paper have
a science correspondent? Hello?
Hi.
OK. Yeah.
- Hello?
- OK, thanks.
- I will come by.
- Sorry, man. Wrong number.
So you're busy.
You OK? You looked like...
It was Danny's landlord.
They found some of his stuff.
- You alright?
- Yeah, yeah.
D'you want me to...
I can get that stuff, bring it back.
Would you mind? It's just
I have to go to San Diego tonight.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
It's done.
Thanks.
- So, who called?
- It was a wrong number.
They were looking for a pizza place.
I think I'm gonna go for a quick run
before my cab comes.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Devlin wants you to follow through
on Sloane's orders.
We're both after
the same missing code.
- You're kidding me?
- No.
- You knew about Rambaldi?
- I didn't. The agency did.
Da Vinci meets Nostradamus.
I don't buy it.
Tell the CIA chief in Barcelona
to prep for a dead drop.
Worst case, I'll encrypt the code on
an MP3 and leave it on Audiogalaxy.
How'd the Russians
find out about Rambaldi?
You're the Intel guy.
What can you tell me
about this woman, Anna Espinosa?
Born in Cuba, raised in Russia.
One of the last Cold War babies.
Go-to officer at K-Directorate
for wet work and active measures.
A year ago, I met
with an informant in Yugoslavia.
Just a guy with Intel
who needed the money.
Anna recorded the conversation with
a mic from the building next door.
How do you know?
Because as I shook his hand to leave,
she blew out his brains,
even though she got what she wanted.
Her way of telling me
I was out of my league.
- Be careful out there.
- I'll see you when I get back.
No, actually, you won't.
I'm being replaced by a senior.
I wasn't experienced enough
to be your handler.
It was really good to meet you.
Good luck in Madrid.
He's an idiot!
I mean, that's the problem.
So is Davenport.
They're so involved in their own...
- Protocol.
- Know who's replacing me?
- Lambert.
- Lambert?
Can I say something?
And not just as a fellow officer,
but as a very smart man.
- What?
- You're too emotional.
- Not again.
- You're attached to this woman.
- It's your answer for everything.
- If I analysed you...
- Shut up, stop it!
- I'd say maybe you're jealous.
Of Lambert? Gimme a break!
He may be senior, but he's junior.
Now he can see Sydney
and you're crazy.
- This is not about me!
- It is.
No, it's not!
She's going to Madrid.
There's another agent with
K-Directorate who is dangerous.
I'm scared for Sydney.
I know I'm off the case,
but I want her to come back.
There's nothing you can do about it.
You don't know if this K-Directorate
woman will be in Madrid,
so why worry?
You sure wrote a hell of a lot
about this Bristow girl.
Anything else
I need to know about her?
You'll find Sydney's
capable of speaking for herself.
Look at her.
Wouldn't kick that out of bed.
You're going to Madrid tonight
and the fund-raiser's
at this auto museum
and you wanna dress nice,
dress to thrill.
I thought maybe you'd like
to wear this... necklace.
The pearls are fibreglass.
Better to transmit vibrations
from your larynx to the mic
right inside the pendant.
You don't wanna try it on or...?
I could... sample it,
but it wouldn't match my...
Senora.
Gracias.
- I'm in.
- Roger that.
Last year, Benegas lent money to the
paramilitary in Columbia which...
Well, it didn't fly well
with the guerillas
so everyone will be jumpy tonight,
but we can use that,
because we've got a normal-looking
Spanish peseta, right?
Wrong. Sonic wave emitter.
Make you sure you drop it
near a window.
Anna just crashed the party.
Careful, Syd.
I don't want tell you what to do
when you're in the field.
But the unveiling of the prototype...
It'd probably be a good time
to activate the coin.
They'll be looking at the car,
not you.
Benegas Racing is proud to present
its new 627 quantum prototype!
You take this pen right here,
a normal-looking pen you write with.
Click that like that, and boom!
Now, the vault is on the top floor.
So, you're gonna have to bypass
all the security cameras.
I got a remote modem, remote modem.
What you do is you wire it
in the central junction box
on the first floor, then Dixon
can loop the video signal.
Central panel, junction box A.
- Damn it!
- What?
Anna's been here.
She's tapped into the alarm system.
- Remote modem?
- Yes. Which means she's got backup.
Alright. Leave it there.
We'll piggyback off their signal.
We don't wanna trigger
the central alarm.
- Is Anna on any monitor?
- Not on any of the feeds.
She's in the ducts.
I'm heading for the elevators.
Did you rig the cameras?
Looping the feed now.
I'm running the lock descrambler.
Anna's in the vault.
The vaults will be unlocked
in five seconds.
What's wrong with the descrambler?
They're jamming your frequency.
I'll try and find them.
The elevator's locked down.
- The descrambler's still jammed.
- Hold on, Sydney.
I see them.
Hurry!
They're coming up!
We're back on line!
Senora? Senora?
She's taking the north corridor.
I'll try to head her off!
I'm headed for the chopper now.
Dixon, she's going out back.
Sydney!
Syd, up there!
Give me your gun.
Give me the gun!
Hi. I'm Will Tippin.
I'm a friend of Sydney's.
She asked me to pick up her stuff.
This is all of it.
Did they arrest anyone yet?
For the murder?
No. Not yet.
Do you know how long
that traffic camera's been there?
No, I don't.
Do the cameras take a picture
at every red light,
or just when there's a car
at the intersection? Really?
Can we get a hold of every photo
taken on June 8th
between midnight and 6am at
the corner of Alta Vista and Sunset?
OK, great. Call me back.
Fighting a traffic ticket?
I swear, the genetics piece
is practically
arriving on your desk now.
- Practically?
- Nearly.
Concurrent with this conversation.
So out of 2,000 words,
how many have you practically typed?
Counting the headline?
Don't make me regret
hiring people in their 20s.
Yeah?
Hi. I don't know
if I'm talking to the right person,
but I need to borrow a million bucks.
The Olsen twins went public.
I want to invest.
You'll need collateral.
I don't think you have any.
Have you seen my blue Chevy?
With the hula girl on the dash?
Yes, sadly.
- Welcome home.
- Thanks.
How was San Diego?
Boring. How'd the article turn out?
Boring. Listen,
you may be too wiped out,
but some of us are having dinner.
Love to. I could use some fun.
Wanna do it at my place?
I'll order in.
- Great. Seven?
- How about 7:30?
OK. I better get going before
I get fired, which is inevitable.
- Will?
- Yeah?
Nothing. It's just...
It's nice to be home.
Yeah. I'll see you tonight.
OK.
You're gonna like working with me.
Really?
Must have been...
I almost don't know how to say it.
Devastating, when Kenny was killed.
But I want you to know
you can trust me.
I understand you. I empathise.
- His name was Danny.
- Danny? Yes, of course.
Well, what happened to Danny
was a tragedy,
and yet, you didn't give up.
Mr Lambert, I got your message.
Is there a reason I'm here?
I just wanted to introduce myself.
Grab a little face time with my girl.
I wanted to make sure
you don't have any queries.
- I've got a query.
- Yeah? Shoot.
Are you insane? Calling me in here
for a social event?
SD-6 has a division
whose sole responsibility
is to track agents
and report back suspect activity.
Your girl is risking her life,
and you yours,
every time we see each other.
So do me a favour.
Don't be so friendly.
I just love your spirit.
That's heartening. Are we done here?
- Yeah, honey. We're all done.
- Great.
I'm legally blind
without my contacts in.
- Great. Another eye story.
- First day in my apartment...
Give me two.
In the kitchen
eating cereal for five minutes.
I hear someone coughing
and I put on my glasses
and there's three men
painting my walls.
- I forgot they were coming.
- That's bad.
- The bad thing was, he was naked.
- I was.
- Naked.
- I naked-clean.
Oh! He loves to embarrass me.
Wait, wait. Define "naked-clean".
- I clean naked.
- Please don't!
I clean our apartment naked.
He loves to embarrass me.
- I'm gonna see that. Raise it five.
- You're bluffing.
The most obvious tell on the planet.
What? First of all,
not even in the hardcore-est
of ways do I bluff.
You only raise when you're bluffing.
- No, I don't.
- Full house.
Man!
Damn it!
- When Will bluffs, you can tell.
- I'll be right back.
How come I can never tell with you?
OK, OK.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are you saying? All traffic
cameras were out that night?
OK. Hold on.
Within a mile of Danny's apartment?
Is that a normal thing? No, that
doesn't sound like a normal thing.
I got a review at 6am, maybe
we should go while we're ahead.
We should go. Sure.
Thank you, Sydney.
- Goodnight.
- See you later, Will.
Bye, Will.
Thank you, Jenny. Thanks.
That is weird, isn't it?
Yeah, OK.
- What's weird?
- A stupid article I gotta write.
Look at this.
What is it about tequila?
It's like a trigger.
I always get this craving.
No, it's more than a craving.
When I drink tequila,
ice cream becomes...
- Like a chaser?
- Like oxygen, like a requirement.
Freshman year,
I didn't go to many parties.
But I did go to this one, I remember,
and I had some punch, mostly tequila.
And I got so wasted.
It was pathetic!
I went to this 24-hour market.
I bought three pints
of chocolate-chip ice cream.
- My God, is this story gonna end?
- Shut up.
- Oh, my God, this is excellent.
- So much better.
You gotta try this.
It's a combination of chocolate
and chips, and it's genius.
- Isn't it?
- Here.
Thanks. No, thank you.
- Oh, my God
- Thank you.
It's good. No, this is good.
My shirt didn't have enough
ice cream on it.
Listen, I...
Will?
I left that box in my car.
It's Danny's.
I'm gonna go get it
before I forget it.
- Right.
- OK.
Marshall couldn't open the box.
In my defence,
it was rigged with a new tech,
a device that destroys anything
inside if opened without the key.
Please go back to work.
- I'm not being fired?
- Back to work means not fired.
We needed a contingency plan,
so we called in
our best game theorist.
Hello, Sydney.
Have a seat.
We mapped out a scenario where
you infiltrate the K-Directorate lab
where the key is being held.
Jack thought...
Your father thought
it could be too big a risk.
It sounds like the right move.
Obviously, we need the key.
Obviously, they need the box.
Six hours ago,
I contacted K-Directorate
and we settled on an arrangement.
You and Anna meet
at a neutral location,
under cover
of both agencies' security.
Together, you'll open the lock box.
Is this a joke?
The Directorate doesn't know the
code was divided into two sketches.
We have nothing to lose
by doing this.
This symmetric scenario
compels both sides
to adopt a mutually reinforcing
course of action.
Close cooperation is one of the
most stable strategic paradigms.
Assuming all the players
are rational.
Plus, I'm just supposed to trust
Anna Espinosa?
I need to brief the advance team.
- Their first plan was suicide.
- I could handle myself.
Then we disagree.
My way, you have a fighting chance.
Then I guess I should thank you.
- It never crossed my mind.
- Dad?
Before I go,
just answer my question about Mom.
Your mother knew I was CIA.
It was no secret between us.
She died in the accident.
I never lied to you about that.
What is this?
Two-way earpiece and tracking chip.
We want you to tag Anna.
We've got a surveillance team
in Berlin.
- No. Whose idea was this?
- This is my op, Agent Bristow.
This only works if everyone's
on their best behaviour.
I won't be the one to break rules
when snipers are waiting for me
to look the wrong way.
I hate to pull rank,
but time is a factor here.
It is a factor. You know
how much time? Seven years.
That's how long I worked for SD-6
before I knew who they are.
Now that I know, my days of
blindly following orders are over.
- Who do you think you're talking to?
- I know who I'm talking to.
Tell Devlin if Vaughn isn't
on the other end of this earpiece
when I turn it on,
the CIA gets nothing.
Vaughn is a junior officer.
Then promote him.
Daniel's apartment was here.
The cameras were off here to here.
He was in the centre
of a one-mile video blackout.
Unless this is a coincidence,
which is doubtful,
there's no way
this is straight B and E.
Maybe, but Eisenberg
is on the crime desk,
and you are a staff reporter
way past deadline.
Don't make me regret
working for people in their 50s.
40s.
One week.
Francie, sweetie,
you're overreacting.
Charlie's cheating on me.
I have proof. I found something.
It's a matchbook with some girl's
name and phone number written in it.
Copy. We're five minutes out.
- That could mean anything.
- It says, "I loved tonight. Rachel."
- The matchbook is from a hotel.
- Fran.
Don't assume the worst yet.
You won't know until you know.
The truth isn't what it seems.
Bitte, nicht!
- Where are you?
- With a client. I'll call you back.
Clear to land the bird.
Listen up. Per agreement
with the Directorate,
we'll divide the stadium
down the middle.
They get the west, we get the east.
Alpha team, you're on rear overwatch,
in case they surprise us.
Bravo and Charlie,
you're on countersnipers.
The rules of engagement are,
you're authorised to fire
only if our assets are fired upon.
K- Directorate are taking position.
Hold positions. We're waiting
for Bristow to go hot-mic.
- Who am I talking to?
- Your invisible friend.
Good. Where are you?
Satellite relay station back in LA,
watching you from a 200-mile orbit.
My guardian angel.
I was gonna say the same thing
to you.
- Thanks for the promotion.
- You're welcome.
Heads up.
- Team leader, we're hot.
- Copy that.
She's coming.
Have you two spoken,
about her mother?
Yes. She asked me about her death.
Did you tell her the truth?
How's your Russian these days?
I heard about your fiancé.
Very sad.
I thought it was a security execution
sanctioned by your employers.
Maybe you said something
in your sleep you shouldn't have.
But then, why would you be here
in service
of the men
that killed your true love?
- I take it you brought the key.
- I take it you brought the box.
Once we see what's inside,
we go our separate ways.
Oh, my God!