My name is Sydney Bristow.
Seven years ago, I was recruited by a
secret branch of the CIA called SD-6.
I was sworn to secrecy, but I
couldn't keep it from my fiancé.
And when the head of SD-6
found out, he had him killed.
That's when I learned the truth.
SD-6 is not part of the CIA.
I'd been working for the people
I thought I was fighting.
I went to the only place
that could help me take them down.
Now I'm a double agent for the CIA.
My handler is Michael Vaughn.
Only one other person
knows what I do,
another double agent inside SD-6.
Someone I hardly know.
My father.
There's an FBI tribunal flying in.
They'll question Sydney about the
prophecy and decide the next move.
- It was just a question.
- No, it was an accusation.
You are questioning
my honour, my loyalty,
based on a prophecy in a book you
wouldn't have if it weren't for me.
Look at this. There.
"This woman will have had her effect,
never having seen Mount Subasio."
According to Rambaldi, the woman,
the subject of this prophecy,
will have never seen Mount Subasio.
If Sydney were to go there
and see it...
- She couldn't possibly be the woman.
- That makes sense, doesn't it?
We'll have to extract her.
The plane is ready
to take you to Italy.
Dad, I just drove a car
into the ocean.
I knew the police
were waiting for me.
I used the air from the tyres.
I was underwater for ten minutes.
And as that car
started to fill with water,
I knew what my mother
had done in the same situation.
- Sydney...
- Mom's alive.
I know it.
- Agent King.
- Agent Otley, please.
Tell him it's about a fugitive
the FBI has been looking for.
The fugitive is me.
I don't know
how to thank you for helping me.
Don't thank me. Devlin said the FBI
is focusing their investigation
where it should have been all along.
Instead of persecuting you, they
should have searched for your mother.
But they were convinced
she was dead.
No. While you were in Italy I did
something I've never done before.
I violated the CIA's trust.
I broke into Langley's
classified archives.
I pulled the operational file
on your mother,
to see if I could find anything that
might prove your intuition correct.
Apparently, after her accident,
an internal commission was formed
to assess the damage
she'd done to US intelligence.
The commission was comprised of
people I'd worked with at the agency,
but one name
stood out in particular.
20 years ago, back at the CIA,
you were on a commission
that investigated Laura's death.
When I heard that, I couldn't imagine
why you never told me.
Unless the commission
discovered something
it didn't want me to know about.
Laura didn't die in the accident,
did she?
Given my state at the time, they
thought it best that I wasn't told.
They don't know what happened
to her, where she went.
She could still be in this country
for all they know.
Dad...
I'm gonna find her. I have to.
Searching for that woman
will accomplish nothing.
- I need to know where she is.
- We're not sure she's alive.
- And it doesn't change what she did.
- Dad, I know.
- You expect her to say sorry?
- I don't know what to expect!
You'd better know
exactly what to expect!
What could she ever say
that would satisfy you?
I have this memory of my father.
I was maybe five years old.
We were camping with my mother.
I broke my leg.
And he picked me up
and carried me miles back to the car.
I remember looking up at him
and thinking he was
the strongest man in the world.
Seeing him there in the car,
looking so damaged.
I'd never seen him like that.
The idea that I wanna find my mother,
it scares him.
Well, I don't have a neutral point of
view, but your father's got a point.
I know, and maybe I'm being
reckless or selfish or masochistic.
But if my mother is alive,
then I just have to know that.
Can you help me get
everything the CIA has got on her?
I can't. All information on her has
been classified Omega 17 by the FBI,
including her connection
to the prophecy.
Dozens of agents
must be looking for her.
They won't let me be part of that.
I know you need help, but this time
I just don't have it to give.
I'm sorry.
Apologise to Emily for me
if I woke her.
Emily is used to the phone ringing
in the middle of the night.
You've been avoiding me.
When I found out that
my mother might still be alive,
I just needed some time
to sort it out.
I understand.
And now you want to know how I
could have hidden the truth from you.
No. I don't want an explanation.
I came here because
I need you to help me find her.
Sydney...
...how much do you remember
of the year
after you were told
that your mother died?
I remember just feeling
disconnected from everything.
My father was away on business.
No.
Your father spent six months
in solitary in a federal prison.
He was suspected
of being in collusion with Laura.
The FBI almost tried him for treason.
And even though
he was eventually vindicated,
the damage was done,
and he began to unravel.
- Unravel?
- He drank.
He started taking unnecessary risks.
Come on, Sydney. You know the
father he was to you all those years.
He took a long time to fully recover.
I was under direct orders
from the DCI
not to let him know that
Laura had survived the accident.
Unfortunately,
that also required lying to you.
Now that I know the truth,
I am removing myself from active duty
until I find out
what happened to her.
And I am in no position to allow you
to go off on what appears to be
a rogue operation
that would compromise the agency.
Every day you send me on operations
that could compromise this agency,
but as long as it's for SD-6,
the risk is acceptable.
It is time that SD-6
took a risk for me.
A daughter has a right
to know her mother.
I'll help you find her.
OK, we do not put
chocolate chips in the pancakes.
I got news for you. Yes, we do.
- Hey, guys.
- You still live here?
- I know.
- That finance seminar took a week?
Any questions about
offshore tax shelters, I'm your girl.
What are you doing today?
Francie's gonna take me to look for
a new tuxedo. For the awards thing.
- Can we come?
- Not a chance in hell.
- He's too embarrassed.
- We're definitely coming.
My God!
What happened to your arm?
On the flight back from Seattle,
this guy hit me with his carry-on,
pulling it from the overhead.
- Are these chocolate chips?
- Thank you very much!
We've identified Alexander Khasinau
as the person referred to
in underground
intelligence circles as The Man.
He controls more assets
than the Russian Mafia
and, thanks to
his old Cold War connections,
he has the legitimacy
of a fledgling government.
Sorry I'm late.
And sorry that I have hives.
I'm developing
a dermal pigmentation capsule and...
Not quite right... react...
Never mind. Should be gone
in a couple of hours.
Excuse me.
For five years
we've had two deep-cover agents
in the Russian embassy in Vienna.
One of them is this man, Kyle Wexler.
We recently received
a communiqué from Wexler,
indicating that Khasinau
has just converted
250 million dollars' worth
of assets into cash.
We need to know
what he's spending that money on.
He's acquired evidence
of Khasinau's transactions
which he's encoded onto a microchip.
He's scheduled a brush pass
at the embassy.
They're holding their annual
Maslyanitsa celebration.
We've arranged for you to attend.
I told you, I can't focus on...
Khasinau has become this agency's
top priority. It will become yours.
- What I have to do can't wait.
- I understand.
What does Khasinau
have to do with my mother?
He has everything
to do with your mother.
He was her superior.
When you identified him as The Man
I recalled his name
from your mother's investigation.
I thought,
"This has to be coincidence."
I did some checking.
He was her superior
back in his days at the KGB.
This is the only clue
I have to offer you.
Get the microchip.
The more we find out about Khasinau,
the closer you get to your mother.
Sydney!
- I saw you with Sloane.
- I was gonna tell you.
You asked Sloane
to help you find your mother?
Yes.
I thought you'd know
not to ask him for a favour.
You'll spend more time
than you care to paying it back.
- What choice do I have?
- You can choose not to go.
Dad, Khasinau was Mom's superior.
- May I have this dance?
- With pleasure.
- I'd like to talk to you.
- Il y a un problème.
Of course. What's on your mind?
Interesting development
about Khasinau.
I see. So you spoke to Sydney.
You have every right to be angry,
but... I was under orders to keep the
commission's findings confidential.
That I understand.
I don't understand why you agreed
to help Sydney find her mother
without consulting me.
She was gonna pursue this
with or without our blessing.
She'll only find disappointment.
That depends on
what she's expecting.
You are different people, Jack.
Is this affecting you
more than you admit?
I assure you,
my concern is only for Sydney.
Your assurances notwithstanding,
it would be best
if you took a break from active duty.
Just, what, a few days.
Clear your head.
I wouldn't feel comfortable
leaving Sydney alone right now.
If she were your daughter,
I'm sure you'd understand.
You should know by now that
my interest is in protecting Sydney.
It's always been my pleasure to fill
in for you when you were indisposed.
- You ready?
- Ready.
These earrings'll
make you look radiant.
And I mean that literally,
because once you activate them,
they emit an infrared pulse
invisible to the naked eye.
But thanks to our SOP
for high-visibility brush passes,
the agent you're meeting will know
to wear IR-capable contacts.
That's how he'll ID you.
- Excuse me. May I cut in?
- Of course.
But I should warn you,
she likes to lead.
That's good.
Maybe I'll learn something new.
Listen to me carefully.
Wexler's dead.
It's only a matter of time
before my cover's blown, too.
- Who are you?
- Wexler's partner.
That's my ring you feel on your neck.
It's a jet-injector for a neurotoxin.
- I gave you the oral bona fides.
- How do I know this isn't a setup?
Credit Dauphine
is SD-6's front company.
Marshall runs the op-tech division.
And Sloane
is a humourless son of a bitch.
Dixon, Wexler's dead. He may have
talked. I'm going for the microchip.
I'll have the car
brought around front.
- Is the ring one of Marshall's toys?
- I was bluffing.
- Were you recruited out of college?
- Yes, Berkeley.
- My God.
This is a restricted area.
How you been?
- I can't believe it's you.
- Yeah.
What are we doing here?
Wexler was undercover
as executive secretary.
The ambassador
is on Khasinau's payroll.
- What are we looking for?
- This.
Khasinau ships everything through
the embassy to avoid inspections.
It's Wexler!
The ambassador did not know he had
the chip. I guess he stashed it.
Or he swallowed it.
OK, what...?
Sydney, abort. They knew we were
coming. I'll meet you out front.
We need another minute.
We almost have the microchip.
- Dammit. His stomach's empty.
- It could be in his oesophagus.
You wanna give me a hand here?
You spread.
A little bit wider.
- So, you've been good, generally?
- You know, work.
- There it is. See it?
- Got it.
- Get in.
- I'm not gonna ask.
- Dixon?
- Noah?
Let's go.
I'm not real anxious
to see Sloane's face
when he hears
we had to pull Noah out.
What choice did we have?
Do me a favour. Until he goes through
debriefing, don't get too friendly.
That's ancient history.
It was five years ago.
Does anybody have change?
There's a lady back in coach
who's about to kill me.
- I was gonna stretch my legs anyway.
- Really? Thanks.
I should get some sleep.
Syd, if you're mad, that's fine.
I understand.
You don't wanna talk, it's OK.
You don't have to be polite.
But I'm not mad any more and
I don't think you should be either.
You're not mad? What did
you ever have to be mad about?
It must have been hard when I left,
but you didn't even put up a fight.
What kind of fight
was I supposed to put up?
I waited for six hours. You didn't
show up. You didn't even call.
Sloane told me
you were transferred abroad.
- I wrote you. I wrote.
- What?
I told you to meet me in San Pedro.
- I never got a letter.
- I didn't send a letter.
I couldn't discuss my reassignment.
I encoded a message in a junk email.
You should have picked it up
from the subject line.
I always set my computer
to filter out junk email.
This constitutes a major setback.
Extracting Agent Hicks
has squandered five years' work.
- We didn't have a choice.
- It's not her fault.
Your investment was burned.
The same thing that happened to
Wexler would have happened to me.
The fact that we got the microchip
means he didn't die in vain.
I'll hear your report after you've
been evaluated by security section.
Dixon, would you escort Agent Hicks
to McCullough, please?
Now, I have done you
a favour, Sydney.
So should the need ever arise...
...l'm sure that
I can count on you to return it.
In '97 I was admitted
as a graduate student
to the Moscow Institute
for International Relations.
Worked as a courier
for the Russian embassy in Baghdad.
On the visa desk
at the consulate in Cape Town.
In November of 2001 I was put on as
an attaché at the Viennese embassy
and given a low-level clearance.
While under alias as a member
of the Russian diplomatic corps,
were you approached
by any other agency for recruitment?
- Yes.
- Which agency?
- K-Directorate.
- Did you accept their offer?
Yes, I did. They're listening
to this conversation right now.
Please answer
the question truthfully.
Of course not.
Why did you volunteer for prolonged
undercover assignment to begin with?
I fail to see how my motives
are relevant. My reasons are my own.
Unfortunately,
Agent Hicks, they are not.
OK.
Because I was in love, and I was
afraid to admit that to myself.
I saw that as being a sign
of weakness in this work, so I left.
The only reason I can speak
with any perspective about that now
is that I've had five years
to regret my mistake.
May I have the name of the person
to whom you are referring?
Absolutely not.
You are aware that I have
the authority to take steps
that will compel you to answer?
Yes, but the only other deep-cover
agent near Khasinau is dead,
which makes me a valued commodity.
So I suggest we limit the questions
to subjects SD-6 needs to know about.
Besides, where I come from,
a gentleman doesn't kiss and tell.
Our station chief got your dead drop.
I read your debrief.
Sorry you had a rough time.
Thanks. If anything turns up
on the microchip, I'll let you know.
The agent you extracted, Noah Hicks.
You mentioned him in your report
when you made contact with the CIA.
We met when I was a trainee.
We actually dated for a while.
- Really?
- We kept it under the radar.
SD-6 discourages
fraternisation among agents.
So does the CIA.
One more thing. Do you know
where your father's been lately?
I talked to him an hour ago. Why?
Kretchmer's left two call signals
for a meet. Is he OK?
Club soda, please.
- How'd you find me?
- Your car was still in your garage.
I thought you might have
walked somewhere close.
It's the fifth place I looked.
Mike, can I get the check?
Dad, it's two o'clock in the
afternoon. What are you doing here?
I think you might
wanna talk to someone.
Noted.
Six months ago I wasn't...
I didn't even know
how to talk to you.
But now at least I feel like
I can come to you and say...
What's happening between us,
Sydney, is temporary.
I'm not suggesting the person you
talk to should be me. It shouldn't.
But the CIA has counsellors.
- I think you should see one of them.
- You are not responsible for me.
It's not irrational for me
to be worried about you.
Keep your voice down.
I didn't think
you'd listen to my advice,
so I made it official.
I came here to pass along
an order from Devlin.
You're going to see a counsellor
for trauma evaluation.
I'm sorry you had to come down.
It's my fault really.
We're uploading the microchip.
There's 10,000 files,
14 different languages.
Linguistics needs
all the help they can get.
- So you're cleared?
- Yeah.
You survived the debriefing.
Yes, I did. And I forgot
how much I missed McCullough.
Let's get started.
- So how long are you staying?
- I'm not exactly sure.
It's somewhat complicated.
- Why?
- Long story.
Remember when you had just
got back from endurance training,
before you were sent out
as a field op,
and you came back
and you had this incredible glow?
I remember thinking, "Man, this girl
is really having fun."
I remember being worried about that
because I knew inevitably one day
you would not feel that way.
You were not aware of
what you were getting yourself into.
You thought I'd get myself killed?
Maybe.
Is that why you left?
No.
You were right about one thing.
I'm not having fun any more.
- We're gonna be late.
- I can't find my jacket.
- I don't wanna miss the previews.
- I'm just gonna borrow one of Syd's.
- You think I bought the right tux?
- For the amount of money you spent.
What's that supposed to mean?
What?
- Didn't Syd say she went to Seattle?
- Yeah. So?
There's a return ticket
from Italy in her pocket.
- Probably from another trip.
- It's dated last week.
Why wouldn't she tell us
about a trip to Italy?
You are looking at a schematic
of a Westbury 23 supercomputer.
It's capable of making 500 trillion
calculations per second.
- Khasinau bought two of them.
- What for?
They are ideal for simulating
theoretical engineering design.
So, for example, if Khasinau has
acquired enough Rambaldi artefacts,
he may be able to assemble
these artefacts correctly
and extrapolate what missing pieces
remain from the overall design.
And that's why you need to steal
the data core. How are you?
May I? Thank you.
Thanks to the microchip,
we have an image of the data core,
and trust me, this core, hardcore!
It's a photo-refractive crystal cube.
It acts like a sponge.
It has enough capacity to serve as
a backup archive for both computers.
But it's gotta be kept in a cryogenic
chamber halfway to absolute zero.
It is cold enough to freeze your skin
to stone in under a minute,
even if a millimetre of it
is exposed.
Khasinau's computer complex in
Arkhangelsk is a mile underground.
The surrounding forests
are patrolled by private security.
Given this high level of security
surrounding this computer network,
it is likely that Khasinau
is using it as his primary archive.
Account numbers, old contacts,
every agent
who's ever worked for him.
This is a two-person operation.
You've been on assignment
a long time. I'll go.
I know the area pretty well. I did
a lot of recon there as a courier.
Noah's right.
We need every advantage on this one.
You leave in an hour.
My feet hurt.
Can we stop?
I gotta take my boots off.
Leave them on,
or your foot will swell up.
We're Americans!
You were speculating that perhaps
Sydney's desire to find her mother
could be interpreted
as criticism of you as a father.
I suppose it's understandable.
Much like a normal family
after a divorce,
when parental jealousy
is stirred over a child's affection.
And how would you define
a normal family?
I suppose it's one
in which the family members
aren't under orders
to lie to each other.
I see what you're getting at.
Maybe there's no such thing
as a normal family.
Well, OK, Mr Bristow.
I guess we can call it a day.
I prefer Jack.
One more thing, Jack.
I don't believe a single word you've
said to me over this past hour.
Don't get me wrong.
I think you're a master.
You have all your subconscious
tells under control.
You're smart enough
to struggle with words.
But I think you told me what I wanted
to hear so you could get out of here.
I also think that someone
so skilled at deception
is in danger of deceiving himself.
I am going to recommend
that you see me once a week.
You haven't got a clue...
what's required to lead
the kind of life I lead,
to maintain a balance
between two lives
and protect my daughter
in the process.
The kind of person who does that,
the kind of person I have to be,
is not the kind of person who would
come in here and talk to you.
Then I guess
we're making some progress.
See you next week.
Is there any chance we can contact
the American embassy?
- What were you taking pictures of?
- Just the scenery, I swear it.
Why don't you just take the film
and give her back the camera?
Just the scenery.
Keys. Take 'em.
Let's go.
Move!
- Let's go, Syd.
- I'm disengaging the core.
I'm in.
Don't forget to keep
that core temperature constant.
Got it.
- How are we doing?
- Almost there.
Got it.
- Noah, I'm freezing.
- Hang on. The system is in lockdown.
Wake up.
Come on.
Good girl. Come on. Up!
Syd, come on, baby. Move.
It's weird, I don't know. Italy.
What if she met somebody
on a business trip?
- Why would she keep that a secret?
- Maybe she's embarrassed by it.
Why?
What?
The bruise. What if he's beating her?
Are you kidding me?
Sydney would never put up with that.
Maybe she's sleeping with her boss.
Sloane? No.
Should we just forget
that we even found the ticket?
- You think she's in trouble?
- When she gets back from...
- Where did she say she went?
- San Francisco.
Which I'm sure she did.
We're blowing this out of proportion.
There's an explanation.
We'll ask her when
she gets back from... San Francisco.
- Did you get through?
- Yeah.
It was hard to get a signal, but
we've got an extraction set at 0800.
- That's what, six hours?
- Yeah.
We should prepare
in case Khasinau's men show up.
The floorboards over there lift up.
This safehouse has saved me before.
You know what would be great
right now? A fire in that fireplace.
I heard a chopper.
If it's thermal-equipped,
it'll pick up the heat signature.
What were you looking for
in that database anyway?
It's a long story.
We've got six hours, so that's good.
I was looking for information
about my mother.
- Your mother?
- A lot's happened since you left.
I wanna fill you in, but I don't know
if I feel comfortable doing that yet.
Fine.
You're still mad.
No.
When you left,
and you just disappeared,
it was a kick in the stomach,
and I carried that around
for a long time.
You were the last person that
I ever wanted to see again. Ever.
And you were the only person
that I ever wanted to see again.
Wait.