Sydney, time's up.
OK.
Then I'll... just... finish
my... little... essay.
Thank you.
- I'm sure I got a D.
- You didn't get a D.
I got a D, I think I got a 64.
- You've never gotten a D.
- I've gotten a D.
High school, Home Ec.
Remember the...
Yeah, what did you do?
Embroider a T-shirt?
- Sweatshirt, that was my assignment.
- It was obscene, about the teacher?
That sexist pig.
I deserved a scholarship.
- Wait. Hold on.
- This time, I deserve a D.
I didn't prepare,
I didn't... have enough time.
We've had this conversation.
Quit the bank.
What are you doing?
I can't go through double shift
again holding on to this.
- Did you get Dave Matthews tickets?
- Will you stand up, please?
I wanted to wait, maybe do it
at the weekend, but...
- I couldn't.
- What's going on?
Remember our first date?
The bowling alley?
- The loud guy?
- Oh, God.
Build me up
Buttercup, baby,
then you bring me down
And mess me around
And then worst of all
You never call, baby
when you say you will
But I love you still, I need you
More than anyone, darling
I know that I'm yours
from the start
Build me up, buttercup
Don't break my heart
Shut up!
Sydney, I can't tell you how much
I hope you'll marry me.
Despite what I just did.
Yes.
I love you.
- Oh, Fran.
- I know. I cry at every damn thing.
Let me see it again.
Oh, honey, it's beautiful.
- I know. I'm getting married.
- You're getting married.
- So, d'you tell Will yet?
- I'm meeting him if you wanna come.
No. I've got 300 orthopaedic surgeons
to feed, and no desire to exercise.
- What about your dad?
- I haven't told him yet.
I don't want him to ruin this.
- Not this, you know?
- Yeah, I think you're right.
If you call him,
he's gonna let you down.
Yeah, I know.
Your mom would be so happy for you.
- You know that?
- She would.
Maybe I should call my dad.
Unless you're talking about
importing airplane parts,
that man has nothing to say.
Let him get the invitation.
It's exporting airplane parts.
He already knows.
Danny called him to ask permission.
Danny called your dad? Your dad?
And how did that go?
Yeah?
- Oh, Mr Bristow?
- Yes.
Hi, it's Danny Hecht.
Sydney's boyfriend.
- Is Sydney all right?
- Oh, yeah, she's fine.
Nothing to worry about.
I'm calling because I'm planning on
asking Sydney to marry me,
and I was hoping
to get your approval.
- Danny, let me ask you a question.
- Sure.
How well do you know my daughter?
We've been dating for two years.
If you need to ask me about this, I
have a sense you don't know Sydney.
I love your daughter, I want
to marry her. That's why I'm calling.
First of all, the truth is,
this is just a courtesy call.
Like saying to a neighbour, "We're
having a party, if that's all right."
What you really mean is,
"We are having a loud party."
Mr Bristow...
Sydney doesn't give a damn
what my opinion is.
What interests me is that you do.
It's just a custom to call
the father, that's all this is.
I'll tell you what. I may become
your father-in-law, that's fine,
but I will not be used as a charming
anecdote you tell your friends,
so they can see what a quaint
old-fashioned guy Danny really is.
Are we clear?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Then welcome to the family.
You're in late.
Sorry. Executive elevator.
Come on, man, drop me off at 12.
All right. Damn...
- Zachary feeling better?
- Much, yeah. Thanks.
See ya.
God, I hate this.
If only Ramadan Abadallah Shallah
still taught in Tampa.
Not my case work.
These new headsets pinch.
Give it to me. Any word from Declan?
Not since Tehran.
I'm telling myself he's fine.
He's done this before.
Disappeared for days.
- What's with you?
- Nothing. Why?
- You've got, like, a glow.
- I don't have a glow.
Yeah, look at that!
- Here. Come on. There's no glow.
- Is she glowing?
- Big time.
- You hear that?
Yes. Better. Good.
Oskar Müller was killed last month.
He was riding a moped
and was hit by an ambulance.
We had kept an eye on this guy
for some time.
He fancied himself
a modern day alchemist.
His IQ was one of the highest
on the planet.
But he was riding a moped.
There was a frenzy to recover
Müller's notebooks and experiment,
but none were found,
at least not by the West.
Cultural affairs building, Taipei,
Hsincheng North Road, section two.
This building is also
an FTL cover station.
We received word that one of
Müller's plans surfaced here.
- Who's the mole?
- Antonio Quintero.
This is his last transmission.
Uplink was on the 15th,
brush pass scheduled for Tuesday.
Quintero did not show.
- What is that, hieratic?
- Good try. Actually, it's demotic.
Notes in ancient languages was one
of Müller's quirks. He had a few.
- Quintero's been burned?
- We don't know.
The Ambassador's throwing
a reception next Tuesday.
You fly to Taiwan on Monday.
You're employed by Modira Plastics.
Looking for
a new manufacturing plant.
Based on the notes,
you'll case the east wing,
measurements, lock specs, IO.
Locate the lab where the plans
are being held and come home.
That's all. No retrieval.
We can't risk it. OK, Marshall, go.
Yeah. Thank you.
OK. How is everyone? Good?
Alright. The first... thing...
I have here is a...
Well, looks like a lighter.
Something to light a cigarette,
but actually it's an RF scrambler.
It disrupts any video for 420 yards.
If I were to hit this switch,
the whole block would be in panic.
What the hell, right? Yep.
You see?
Everyone's totally freaking out.
"What's going on? My computer,
my DVD's not working."
And we're back. OK.
I got a 20 volt cell in here,
so you only get
four minutes of charge.
So, you wanna get in,
do a thing, then get out.
Four minutes two seconds
and your f... screwed. OK.
The other thing I got here...
This is good. You're gonna like this.
It's something I'm excited about.
Looks like lipstick, you know,
something you'd do for your lips.
You see? In the woman's...
Refresh or something.
But... This is the amazing thing.
It actually takes pictures,
and it measures space
in three axes from one vantage point.
It assembles images based on GPS,
and creates an accurate blueprint
of any building, but that's not...
It's got a camera, a short-pulse
laser, plus a grid analyser.
I got it to 42 snaps right now,
but I wanna get it to 47,
cos that's a prime number.
You might think this is simple,
but until we know about Quintero,
we assume the enemy's waiting.
So I want you to do us a favour.
Come back.
- Good run.
- Thanks.
So, where were you last night?
I called you.
Oh, yeah.
I don't wanna talk about it.
My sister set me up on a blind date.
Was it good?
- For the date it was.
- You didn't like her?
Not so much.
I don't like my sister any more.
That's the problem
when siblings live with you.
They make you meet people
you aren't supposed to meet in life.
- Why was the date so bad?
- Her favourite movie of all time?
Are you ready for this? Pretty Woman.
So? I'm sure
it's a lot of people's favourite.
That's probably true, but
of all time? That includes like...
Well, every other movie ever made.
All of 'em.
You see Lawrence of Arabia's
at the Egyptian?
- Yeah, I did.
- You wanna go?
- I'd love to, but...
- Danny's working late.
- I'm taking him dinner.
- We can go to a late one.
- It's only playing on Thursday.
- We're getting married.
Look at that, you're wearing a...
You're wearing a ring.
I didn't even see it. That's...
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- You wanna get a couple more laps?
- I'm done.
OK, I'm gonna get a couple more.
I called Todd. They haven't rented
that place yet if you wanna go look.
Impossible, isn't it?
One day,
there's gonna be a baby in there.
My patients would love that.
Knowing that their doctor still can't
believe women can get pregnant.
Get undressed.
I work for the CIA.
Sydney...
I'm an operations officer
for the CIA.
It was during the fall
of my freshman year.
A man approached me. He told me
the US Government might talk to me
about a job.
When I asked why me, all he told me
was that I fit a profile.
I didn't feel I belonged anywhere,
even at college,
and I needed the money anyway.
So, I met with him,
and they offered me a job.
A job with the CIA?
Not exactly. It's...
It's a covert branch.
This is crazy.
OK, OK. So, covert branch.
Then what?
After the first month, I asked if
I could test for agent training.
The test was easy.
They said I was a natural. Maybe
I was because I advanced quickly.
It was exciting.
This isn't real.
Danny.
Since my mother died, I've always
hoped that I'd find someone
to give my life meaning.
That person is you.
I just met the agency first.
I can't quit.
Syd, I love you.
But this...
I've... I've just gotta figure out
what I'm thinking.
You can't tell anyone about this.
About what I do.
No-one.
- I...
- Danny, I'm not kidding.
I got it.
I need a... I need to walk.
I'll call you tonight.
I've got my trip.
San Diego?
I'll call you when I get back.
Be careful.
You know, Sloane doesn't like it.
- That you're still in grad school.
- I know.
He'd rather none of us have
a life outside. I'm not giving it up.
You all right?
How long have you and Diane
been married?
11... No, 12 years. Damn.
You love her?
Of course I do.
- And you never said a thing?
- About what?
About what we do.
Diane is married to an investment
analyst who loves his job.
- I'm protecting her from the truth.
- And you don't...
You don't feel like
you're lying to her?
If there's one rule you don't break,
that's the rule you don't break.
It must just get easier, after.
- Hey, this is Sydney.
- This is Danny. I don't live here.
Leave a message. I'll call you back.
Thank you.
She meant to say thank you.
You're not there. Well, I know
you're not there or in San Diego.
You could be anywhere,
doing anything.
Which is...
Which is the crux of the issue.
Can I live like this?
Not knowing where,
or why, or when?
Can I live in the dark?
And the answer...
The only answer
I came up with, Syd, was...
...was yes.
Syd, I don't care.
The whole world's
a nightmare, anyway.
It's all dangerous,
no matter what we do.
I couldn't live with myself, saying
goodbye to you because of risk.
It's all a risk.
I...
No, the kids thing.
That we have to talk about
because I want kids.
I love kids.
But, you see,
maybe there is a way out, cos...
People aren't spies forever.
At some time,
people have to be able to say
they used to be spies.
I miss you, Syd.
Come... Come home.
Yeah?
Who?
What else?
Yeah, well, get me
the audio right away. Yeah.
I'm so lost. Oh, my God.
I was looking for the bathroom.
There should be signs. In English.
I don't know
if you're in charge, but...
This area is restricted.
Please, I was just
going to the bathroom.
You don't know my boss.
If he found out I'd been drinking,
that I'd gotten in trouble,
I swear, I will lose my job.
I swear it.
The rest room is this way.
Thank you. Bless your heart.
I like your tie.
We have a breach.
It appears Daniel Hecht
has become aware
of Sydney's affiliation
with the agency.
You understand what that means?
Yes, I understand.
I appreciate you
telling me yourself.
- I'm sorry, Jack.
- Don't be.
You know me well enough.
You know where my loyalty lies.
- Mr Gonzales.
- Mr Dixon. Where's Bristow?
- Looking for this?
- Looking for her. Where is she?
- She left me at the gate.
- Left you at the gate?
Said she was grabbing a taxi.
What's the problem?
Hey, I'm back. I didn't even
go home first. I took a cab...
What did you do?
I might ask you the same question.
Security became aware of the breach
and performed their function.
You're familiar with the codes
of conduct, Agent Bristow.
You knew the codes applied to you,
even as you put at risk
the lives of every man and woman
working at this agency.
Danny wasn't a risk.
He was... He was just a man.
He was a doctor. He was just...
Listen to me. Information about
this agency is treated like a virus.
There is only one response.
That is containment.
You put us into
a compromised situation,
and though I despise
that countermeasure we had to...
Stop saying "we".
Stop talking about the agency.
You killed the man I love.
No, Agent Bristow.
You did.
Let me out.
I can't imagine
how difficult this is for you.
Let me out.
However, before you go anywhere,
McCullough needs to see you.
You see, you're a risk now, too.
Are you an operative of SD6?
Yes.
How long have you been
an operative of SD6?
Seven years.
What is your identification and
classification number with SD6?
My identification
and classification is...
Have you ever been so entertained
by the cleverness of a crook
that you hoped he'd get away with it?
Did you reveal information
regarding SD6 to Daniel Hecht?
Do you ever lie? What is
your relation to Daniel Hecht?
Covert branch of the CIA.
If a person is arrested for stealing
and others have helped,
should he reveal his helpers?
Yes.
Wow!
I don't know
what you put in that stuff. Wow!
I'd rather not
make this too painful.
Me, too. Thanks.
Glad we're on the same page.
That's good.
Who are you working for?
I will not ask you again.
OK.
Get a pen.
Write this down.
E... M.
E-T-l-B.
- You got that?
- Yes.
OK. Now reverse it.
BITE ME
I've got bad news for you, man.
I am your worst enemy.
I've got nothing to lose.
That's not exactly true.
You have teeth.
These questions
resonate even louder,
when you lose somebody
through a senseless act of violence.
But we hear them,
echoing in our minds.
Why?
- Hey, this is Sydney.
- And Danny. I don't live here.
Leave me a message
and I'll call you back.
Thank you.
She meant to say thank you.
Hey, this is Sydney.
Leave me a message.
Thank you.
She loved a man,
and she lost him.
This isn't a new theme in literature,
but it seems to be
one of the favourites.
For instance,
what does Tennyson
contribute to this subject?
His work is mildly out of fashion
but I would like you to consider
his exploration of this theme.
It seems that...
It seems to be...
Syd.
- Need a lift?
- No, thanks.
I'm just going to the library.
How've you been?
OK. You?
Good. Better.
Thanks for the flowers. It was nice.
Look. Sloane's getting impatient.
They gave you a month off.
It's been three.
- I've talked to Sloane.
- Apparently not to his satisfaction.
I know they sent you here
to bring me back. I'm sorry.
I just can't yet.
They got word. FTL has built
the Müller device. Sloane wants it.
- They don't need me.
- They do.
- Tell them to call Quintero.
- Quintero's dead.
We got confirmation Thursday. Syd?
They need you active,
and if they don't have confidence
in someone
who's in as deep as you are,
they'll fix that problem.
I really am sorry.
- I'll see you.
- Syd?
Hello?
- Francie, hi.
- Wanna hear the worst day ever?
Could you call my cell phone?
- I can barely hear you.
- Just call me right back.
OK.
Get in.
Daddy?
Now!
Dad, you have a gun!
- Hello?
- I'll call you later.
I rang twice.
You won't believe the day I had.
Me, too.
- Hang on.
- Dad, what are you doing?
There might be others.
Put your seat belt on.
There are many things
you won't understand tonight.
You must understand
that the agency doesn't trust you,
and they're gonna kill you
unless you do as I say.
I work for SD-6, just like you.
Undercover at Jennings Aerospace.
You leave tonight. Fly to France,
a connection to Switzerland.
You'll be stopped at customs
so I got you new papers.
- I thought you sold aeroplane parts.
- I don't. I never did.
That car's taking you to the airport.
I have to get back.
- Who are you?
- Get in that car.
In two minutes they leave,
with or without you.
There's no time not to trust me. You
don't know who you're dealing with.
What does that mean?
Who the hell am I dealing with?
About a decade ago,
a pool of agents went freelance.
Russian, Libyan, Chinese...
- The Alliance Of 12.
- What do you know of them?
They're an enemy of the US.
Mercenaries.
I'm one of them. SD-6 is not
a black ops division of the CIA.
SD-6 is a branch of The Alliance.
You work for the enemy
you thought you opposed.
- That's impossible.
- Why have you not been to Langley?
You've been lied to. All lower-level
agents have been lied to.
I am trying to help you here.
So you're saying
I'm working for the enemy.
- And you are the enemy.
- Sydney, this is your last chance.
You have to go.
Who are you to come to me
and act like a father?
If you wanna help me,
stay away from me.
OK.
Let's try one more time.
Who do you work for?
I...
I just wanna say...
Start with the teeth in the back,
if you don't mind.
No!
Yeah. Wait.
Let me ask the quest... No.
The newspaper's doing you a favour.
Yeah...
I'm on a counter run. Want anything?
- No. Is Liv in?
- What do you think?
- She still work here?
- Hope not.
Meet me on the roof? Perfect.
Some guy just totally hung up on me.
So I got an hour. Wanna get lunch?
- What happened to your face?
- I need your help.
- Are you OK?
- I can't explain so don't ask.
You just gotta trust me.
Of course.
I need one of your sister's
credit cards. A $3,000 limit.
I'll pay her back. Can you get it?
Syd, what is this? Do you
owe somebody some money?
There's something else.
Do you know where
Amy keeps her passport?
How many bags
are you checking in to Taipei?
Just this.
What's your lipstick? I love it.
- Allex Jane Lux, Concorde Grape.
- Totally pops.
Thanks. May I see your passport?
Ever tried this? I think
it's too light for me. Do you?
- It's pretty.
- Thanks.
Window or aisle?
The pill I gave you helps the pain.
I could tell, because
you stopped screaming so loudly.
That medication, however,
only lasts for two hours.
And it's been...
two hours, almost.
So...
...you have a choice.
Which way...
we go next.
Tell me
and you get one more.
The agency.
- Louder.
- I can't.
Who do you work for?
You... pretty little girl.
No... No...
Hey, guys.
Yeah?
Send her in. Now.
Yeah, make sure Ravel knows.
I'm back.
- All right.
- I'm taking the week off.
I've got mid-terms.
May I help you?
I need to speak
to your director, Mr Devlin.
I'm sorry. Mr Devlin's not
available. May I leave a message?
Tell him he has a walk-in.
Roxanne, we have
a walk-in for Mr Devlin.
Yes.
Come with me, please.
CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENC Y
- Did you do the report?
- I know.
I'll get to it, I swear. Thanks.
There's some more coffee
and something to eat.
Just let Mr Weiss know
if you need anything else.
A new pen. This one's dying.
Thanks.
- This could be interesting.
- So am I in?
Not yet.
They're reviewing your statement.
- It's... You wrote a lot.
- I know.
I mean, it's like Tolstoy-long.
Devlin says
it could take weeks to verify.
But I know we could use
another double agent in SD-6.
We'll be in touch. I'll get you
out of here, keep you concealed.
- Why shake your head?
- You said "another".
So?
So if you had one, you wouldn't
tell me until I was authenticated.
- Unless I had an instinct about you.
- You don't have another double.
- We might.
- But you want me to believe you do.
So if I aim to be a triple agent,
I'll report an existing mole,
to upset the balance of my agency.
- I'm not trying to play you.
- We'll see.
I have an instinct.
You need a dentist. Do you have one?
I can get you a name.
I'm all right.
I'll be right back.
- I wanted to say I was sorry.
- You don't have to.
I'm back at work.
I guess you know that.
I meant sorry about Danny.
There was nothing I could do.
I'd like to be alone,
if you don't mind.
I know what it's like
to lose someone.
I don't know what you expect.
Just because we're on the same side,
just because I know the truth now,
it doesn't change a thing between us.
I accept what I'm doing now
because I have to.
That doesn't mean
I have to accept you.
I asked Devlin
if I could come tell you myself.
They verified your statement.
You're in.
I read what you wrote.
I appreciate your not naming me.
That was... kind.
You're CIA.
You don't know
how dangerous this is, Sydney,
doing what I do.
I wish you'd taken me up
on Switzerland.
How do I know
what you're telling me is the truth?
I guess we'll just have to learn
to trust each other.
Hello?