Previously:
-I can't believe you won't be there.
-I know.
Why can't you take
a couple of days off?
-Because I can't.
-This is my wedding.
-I can't wait to see it!
-Her parents got married there.
It's the most beautiful place.
It's over--
Oh, my God!
Postponing it is not an option.
This wedding won't happen.
If you don't love this, then we'll
do it any other place or time.
It's perfect.
I'm going to London.
It's not over
until someone says, "I do. "
I do! I do!
Rachel, no!
The Waltham residence.
Is this Emily's parents' house?
This is the housekeeper.
And, by the way, that is not how one
addresses a person on the telephone.
First one identifies oneself...
... and then asks for the person
with whom one wishes to speak.
This is Phoebe Buffay.
I was wondering, please...
... if it's not
too much trouble, please.
Might I speak with
Miss Emily Waltham, please?
Miss Waltham is
at the rehearsal dinner.
And it is not polite
to make fun of people. Goodbye.
I'll be nice, I swear.
Could you just give me their number?
I'm afraid I'm not at liberty
to divulge that information.
Somebody is on their way to ruin
the wedding, and I have to warn them.
So give me that number
or I'll come over there...
... and I'll kick your snooty ass
all the way to New Gloukenshire!
She knew I could kick her ass.
The One With Ross' Wedding - Part Il
Subtitles and Rip by
.:staz:. (staz@post. cz)
Hi, sweetheart.
Mom, Dad.
Sorry, we're late.
My fault.
I insisted on riding the tube.
Judy, the kids!
That's what they call the subway.
I thought--
Dad, we got it.
Here comes my dad and stepmom.
Mr. and Mrs. Geller.
This is Steven...
... and Andrea Waltham.
very nice to meet you.
Darling, the Gellers.
Darling, it's the Gellers.
She's self-involved.
I should never have married her.
-It's the Gellers.
-Where?
That's one and that's another one.
Lovely to meet you.
Nice of you to pay
for half the wedding.
The hell with tradition!
We're happy to do it.
We know how expensive
weddings can be.
Besides, this may be
the only wedding we get to throw.
A joke that's funny in all countries.
-What's in it?
-Goat cheese, watercress and pancetta.
That's not food.
Everything's different here.
I want to go home.
I miss my family, the coffeehouse.
I can't remember
what Phoebe looks like!
It's been three days.
You're just homesick.
Would you just try to relax
and just enjoy yourself?
You're different here too.
You're mean in England!
What the hell?
What's up, Dad?
This bill for my half.
It's insane.
Why is it so much?
The reception's at their house.
Flowers, liquor.
Re-carpet first floor?
New guest bath, landscaping.
I'm paying to remodel this house.
I'll give that son of a bitch
a piece of my mind.
Please.
I don't want anything
to upset Emily.
She's had a hard enough
couple of days as it is.
Here.
Let me go talk to him.
You tell him no one takes advantage
of the Gellers.
Sometimes I forget
how powerful you can be.
And I'll go get drunk.
Your next flight to London?
There's one leaving in 30 minutes.
And I do have one seat left.
Thank you, thank you.
The last-minute fare
on this ticket is $2700.
I don't have enough left
on my credit card.
You can split it with another card.
How about five?
Thank you.
I need to see your passport.
I don't have it, but I can tell you
where it is on my nightstand.
You know what?
I have my driver's license.
And I have a 20.
My father is not going to pay
for the built-in barbecue.
And believe me, you can
kiss your gazebo goodbye.
I might be able
to get you the new lawn.
Then you have to give us
the lawn ornaments.
I go back there with lawn ornaments,
he'll laugh in my face.
Will you say something, Steven?
Don't take that tone with me.
All right, you can.
Thank God!
You changed your mind.
You probably don't want
to talk about it.
You're doing the right thing.
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
Why am I always pregnant
when she does that?
I'd like to toast Ross and Emily.
My big toast is tomorrow.
This is kind of my little toast
or Melba toast, if you will.
I knew Ross when he was going out
with his first girlfriend.
I thought things would work out
until he over-inflated her.
Oh, dear God!
Hello, Waltham lnteriors.
Mrs. Waltham.
I need to speak with
one of the best men or Ross' sister.
-Who is this?
-Phoebe, one of Ross' best friends.
If you're Ross' friend,
why aren't you here?
I can't fly.
I'm having my brother's babies.
Am I on the radio?
Can I talk to one of them?
It's important.
I'm bored of you now.
I'm going to cut you off.
We're excited that Ross and Emily are
getting married at Montgomery Hall.
To think, my friend getting
married in Monty Hall.
Come on, Monty Hall!
Let's Make a Deal.
Come on, you people!
All right, forget it.
Congratulations.
Best man number two, Joey Tribbiani.
I'm not good with the jokes
like Chandler here.
Congratulations to the happy couple.
I first met Ross
in this coffeehouse back home.
Home.
New York City.
Where everybody knows my name.
Anyway...
... I love you guys.
But not as much as I love America.
Can we please go home now?
Are you going home?
I was hoping to get
to know you better.
I'm not going anywhere, sweetheart.
I was laughing.
Out loud?
I didn't want everyone
to think I was stupid.
How are you?
My mom's driving me crazy.
But Ross is getting married!
I'm happy.
I won't let anything spoil that.
I just want to say that
Ross is a wonderful young man.
Thanks. We like him.
My God! You must have been
a teenager when you had him.
There's no way in hell
I'm paying for it.
Look, we're down to just one point.
Could we please just settle it
after the wedding?
Fine, but I'm not paying
for your wine cellar...
... you thieving, would-be-speaking-
German-if-it-weren't-for-us man!
The guy was hammered. There's
no way you look like Ross' mother.
-Then why would he say it?
-Because he's crazy!
Earlier, he thanked me for my very
moving performance in Titanic.
My mother's right.
I'll never get married.
You know what, that is--
Who wouldn't want you?
Please! I'm a single mom
with a 30-year-old son.
I'm getting married!
Morning.
I'm getting married today!
Do you think he knew I was here?
I've never done that with you before.
So how are you?
You okay?
You?
We did you.
-I better get going.
-Absolutely.
Could you not look?
I don't want to look.
Excuse me, if you plan on
doing that the entire flight...
... tell me now, so that
I can take a sedative.
Or maybe slip you one.
It's just that I'm kind of excited.
I'm going to London
to tell this guy that I love him.
Where the hell have you been?
I spent the night out.
I met this cute bridesmaid. She is--
I don't want to hear it!
Pheebs, you know you're still
my number one girl.
We have an emergency.
Rachel's coming to London.
Great!
No, she's coming to tell Ross
that she loves him.
But he loves Emily.
I know that!
You have to stop her.
She's going to ruin the wedding.
I've done my part, okay?
It's your responsibility now.
The burden is off me.
So tell me about this girl.
Have you seen Monica?
I'm not seeing Monica!
We got to find her. Rachel's coming
to tell Ross she loves him.
-Oh, my God!
-Do you know where Monica is?
What's with the third degree?
Why not just shine a light in my eyes?
Then I realized all this stuff
I had been doing...
... proposing to Joshua,
lying about why I couldn't come...
... was all just a way of--
I'm sorry. Can I interrupt?
I just want to say that you are
a horrible, horrible person.
Pardon me?
You're about to ruin
the happiest day of his life.
I have to agree
with your friend Pheebs.
This is a terrible, terrible plan.
-But he has to know how I feel.
-But why?
He loves this Emily.
No good can come of this.
I think you're wrong.
Oh, no!
By the way, it seems to be clear
you were on a break.
Oh, my God!
It's like a fairyland.
I know. It's horrible, isn't it?
I love it. I only hope
my wedding looks this good.
-I just--
-You can let some go by.
Start looking out for Rachel.
I'll cover the door.
You watch that big hole.
I've got Chandler covering Ross.
Why would I care where Chandler is?
You know...
... sometimes I don't even
like Chandler.
I do.
It's the second one.
Right?
Hello, Joey.
Hey, Felicity.
I thought about you all day.
Talk New York to me again.
Forget about it.
How you doing?
We're not paying
for your wine cellar.
You have to meet me in the middle.
My foot will meet
the middle of your ass.
-What's going on?
-Everything's under control.
You want a piece of me?
ls that what you're saying?
That's it!
Parents! Parents!
Back away!
This is our wedding day!
From now on, everyone gets along.
And if I hear one more word...
... no grandchildren!
That's right!
Sorry, old boy.
I could kill you
with my thumb, you know.
What was that about?
It was this disagreement over--
My God! You look beautiful.
You can't see me before the wedding.
It's bad luck.
I think we've had all the bad luck
we're going to have.
My God, Rachel!
You're here.
I can't believe it.
Why are you here?
I just came to--
I just needed to tell you...
... congratulations.
Waltham lnteriors.
Mrs. Waltham? It's Phoebe.
Can I talk to one of the best men?
This is going to be the last time.
There's a girl on the phone for you.
Great!
It's Phoebe.
Did you stop Rachel?
But she just hugged him.
That's it.
Nothing got ruined?
That's so great!
So what's going on now?
I'm walking down the aisle.
Still walking.
I'm at the front with Ross.
It's Phoebe!
He looks pretty mad.
I better go.
Wait! Hold it up so I can listen.
-What we did last night was--
-Stupid.
Totally crazy, stupid.
What were we thinking?
I'm coming over
tonight though, right?
Definitely.
Friends, family...
... we are gathered to celebrate...
... the joyous union
of Ross and Emily.
May the happiness of today...
... be with them always.
Now, Emily, repeat after me.
-I, Emily...
-... take thee, Ross...
-... take thee, Ross....
... as my lawfully wedded husband
in sickness and in health...
... till death parts us.
As my lawfully wedded husband,
in sickness and in health...
... until death parts us.
Now, Ross.
Repeat after me.
I, Ross...
... take thee, Emily...
... take thee, Rachel--
Emily!
Shall I go on?
Hurry up!
The flight leaves in four hours!
There could be traffic!
The plane could leave early!
In London, there could be
a line at customs! Come on!
London might have gotten started...
... because we needed to take advantage
of the show's popularity...
... and go do the show on
an exotic location...
... and have a good time.
There's so many people here
from all over the world.
Lately, the show's been about us
getting excited to go to London.
And then we realized in real life,
we're doing that same thing.
Passport, check. Camera, check.
Traveler's checks, check!
Are you ready yet?
-Got the tickets?
-Right here. Check!
Yeah!
London, baby!
It's all London, baby!
Here we go.
Ross is getting married...
... to this young woman named Emily.
And I set them up by accident.
Why don't we?
Why don't we what?
Get married.
I've started to...
... fall for this character, Emily,
played by Helen Baxendale.
And we decided to go all the way,
I guess, and get married.
Ross has asked me to marry him.
I say yes.
And so we arrange
a big wedding in London.
Things go a bit wrong.
We're not paying
for your wine cellar.
You have to meet me in the middle.
My foot's gonna meet
the middle of your ass!
You want a piece of me?
ls that what you're saying?
That's it!
Parents! Parents!
Back away!
This is our wedding day!
From now on, everyone gets along.
And if I hear one more word...
... no grandchildren!
That's right!
Sorry, old boy.
I could kill you
with my thumb, you know.
We knew the show
was popular in England...
... and so it seemed like
a natural fit.
I knew how big the show was over here.
It was exciting to be welcomed.
Everywhere, walking down the street...
... bunches of kids watching.
So we've been signing autographs.
They're just big fans of the show,
I guess.
I watch it all the time
because my children love it.
They absolutely love it.
Tell my friend you like my hat.
-What's your friend's name?
-Chandler.
Hi, Chandler!
We wanted it to
still feel like Friends...
... and so we shot a lot of it
in front of an audience.
And it seemed like
a really exciting opportunity...
... to shoot an American sitcom
in front of a British audience.
-Do something!
-I am. I'm ignoring you.
I'll be the on-camera guy.
All right. First stop...
... Westminster Abbey.
What is that?
That's London, baby!
We were really afraid, going over,
that either they'd be...
... far more sedate and wouldn't laugh....
They were great!
-Big laughers!
-They waited in line for hours!
-We traveled 329 miles.
-She's lying. It's more like 200.
The show's doing so well over here
that it just seems like...
... they're real, real receptive.
It's really wonderful and flattering
and overwhelming, truthfully.
We didn't have
a single bad audience.
Also, there was
a greater sense of "event. "
I think it energized everybody:
the actors, the writers....
We're just excited to be here.
Like, look back there.
Look how cool that is!
We missed Lisa.
That was probably the only
drawback I can think of.
I first thought, "How exciting!
I wonder if I'm going?"
It's awful that Lisa's not here.
We feel like
we have a limb missing.
Let's try some aversion therapy.
Look at the picture.
It's strange when one person's
not there. We miss her.
It's weird for all of us
to be here without her.
She's in the episode, on the phone
and things like that.
Hey, Pheebs!
It's Joey.
Hey, Joey!
I just saw someone that looks just
like you, on the subway.
I was going to say hi, then I figured
he doesn't care he looks like you.
That just cost me four bucks.
Part of me wishes I could go.
But I'm very happy to not get
on a plane for a lot of hours....
Sorry.
I'm not a good traveler.
The Waltham residence.
Is this Emily's parents' house?
This is the housekeeper.
And by the way, that is not how one
addresses a person on the telephone.
First one identifies oneself...
... and then asks for the person
with whom one wishes to speak.
This is Phoebe Buffay.
I was wondering, please...
... if it's not
too much trouble, please.
Might I speak with
Miss Emily Waltham, please?
It was also interesting because
we had shot about a third of it here.
And a bit of it
on the streets in London.
All right!
Westminster Abbey!
Hands down, best abbey I ever seen.
What do you think of the Abbey?
I think it's great! They're thinking
of changing the name.
-To what?
-To "Put the camera away" !
Man, you are Westminster "Crabby. "
It was a really gratifying experience.
Pretty much everything we'd hoped
to get out of it, we got.
When you can go on location even
in Los Angeles that's exciting...
... much less have your whole crew...
...come out to "jolly old England. "
It's really, really exciting.
Just the idea of bringing
our entire "family" over here...
... is, like, wild.
Yeah!
London, baby!
It's amazing to me how many people
are excited about the show.
I knew how big the show was over here.
It plays a lot on television.
I saw it three times in one week.
They're very popular at home,
but I didn 't know they would be here.
It's got a massive following
in Britain...
... particularly among my generation.
It's quite sarcastic.
That's why it's popular.
We have great English character actors
who are working with us.
And an opportunity to interact
with the English crew.
We're about to be Ross' in-laws.
We're the Brits
that you love to hate.
We worked with
Sarah Ferguson this morning.
She was great and funny.
I was excited to be here today.
It's the first time I've ever done this
and I enjoyed it.
I am a great fan.
I think they are all marvelous.
Most British people tried to hate them
for being beautiful and funny.
I got a phone call:
"Small part, a few lines.
Do you want it?
Next to Jennifer Aniston. "
And I went, "Oh, wait a minute....
Oh, okay then. "
It's basically a "Iet's kick the Brits
up the butt" episode, really.
You're gonna see a lot of comedy,
a lot of romance...
... and a lot of surprises.
And you get to see England.
Call the Queen Mum,
say you enjoy watching Friends...
... and that you know us, and she'll
have you over for tea like that.