- Previously, on psych...
- I need to talk to you.
- Just say it. Say what it is.
- I don't wanna feel guilty
about moving on with my life.
Your mother's not a part of it anymore.
Look, I don't care what you do, okay?
I don't care!
Mom.
Dispatch, we've located
the stolen vehicle.
Occupants inside.
Approaching now.
10-4. Proceed with caution.
Henry.
- You don't want to do this.
- I don't have a choice, ray.
Think of the consequences.
We're way past consequences.
This needs to end tonight.
It's my neighbor's car.
We were gonna put it back.
- It was just a dare.
- Is there a problem here, officer?
You wanted my attention, shawn.
You got it, buddy.
Wait, you guys know each other?
Yeah, he's sort of my dad.
I'm afraid
i'm gonna have to ask for that
- world's greatest dad mug back.
- You just keep talking, shawn.
You keep talking.
Don't worry, I will. Like
when I read you your rights.
I have rights.
That'll be new and fun.
- What am I gonna tell your mother?
- I don't know.
You think you can get
ahold of her new phone number?
I hope it was worth it, smart-ass.
This officially ends
your chance of being a cop.
Let's be honest. I gave up wanting
to be like you a long time ago.
That's it! Somebody book him!
You... beanpole. Get over here.
Fingerprint him now!
Oh, I'm so... I'm sorry. Me?
Never mind, rookie.
I'll do it myself.
Dude, I'm freaking out.
You have to help me.
- What's wrong?
- My mom's here.
- She's back in the country?
- Back in the country? Try...
try back in this city.
Try downstairs in my dad's kitchen.
- Where are you?
- Hiding out in my bedroom.
Oh, my god. Holy crap.
I just found an entire,
unopened box of shrinky dinks.
You're hiding in your bedroom
because your mom came to visit?
Dude, you've got problems.
Are you hearing what I'm saying?
My mom is standing downstairs
in my dad's kitchen,
laughing it up,
having a grand old time.
You don't think
that's a little weird?
And you're unhappy she's here.
No, I'm not unhappy she's... here.
I don't know, I haven't seen her
in three years.
She used to...
- Tell me everything.
- What is she doing here?
- Working.
- For the police department?
I guess. I don't know.
I haven't... found out much,
because, apparently,
it's 1988 in my house,
and no one felt the need
to tell me anything. But...
i know my dad
is behind all of this.
Oh, my god.
Dude, did you know I had a furby?
Shawn, I have no time for this.
I've got my own problems.
I have to go see frankjim ogletree.
Frankjim ogletree? Is that
a person or a hippotamus?
He's the new regional sales manager,
my immediate boss, and a tyrant.
They call him the little pinochet.
That's too abstract.
Why don't they just call him
jerk pants or suck mcjones.
They're m.i.t. Guys, shawn.
Now go face your parents.
You've been wanting
to see your mom forever.
And tell her I'm coming by
for some jell-o cake.
Holy... dude!
I just found a pristine
issue ofdynamitemagazine.
Square pegson the cover.
Hold on, I'm gonna read
"bummers" to you.
The cheese knife
is in the same place, right?
Yeah, it's right there. You want me
to give you a hand, hon?
Did you just call me honey?
I did not. I was going to say...
- Hunchback.
- Oh, shawny, look at this.
Not only does your father
own a very expensive bottle
of bordeaux, he hand-made
little cucumber sandwiches.
Do you believe that?
He is just chock full
of surprises today.
What? I'm allowed
to expand my horizons, right?
I'm so glad to see you, mom.
What are you doing in town?
Well, some police departments
occasionally call me up
to come back
and do psych evaluations.
How long have you known about this?
Not long. I almost didn't do it.
I changed my mind
at the last second.
I'm doing santa barbara p.d.,
a few in san diego the bay area.
When are
our dinner reservations, henry?
There's dinner plans tonight!
- You can make it, right?
- Of course he can make it.
Of course I will come. I just...
Need to cancel a date.
But that is not a big deal.
- You made other plans?
- I didn't make other plans.
- I... I didn't know.
- Didn't know what?
That you were coming.
Why didn't you
tell him I was coming?
He doesn't have a phone.
- You don't have a phone?
- I do.
Are you having money problems?
Why don't you buy him a phone?
Mom, I'm fine.
I'm not having money problems.
I'm... I dropped my phone
while I was solving
a very important crime.
It was on the front page
of the newspaper yesterday. Yeah.
May I speak with you privately?
What the hell is going on in there?
I tried to tell you.
Allow me to demonstrate trying.
"Shawn guess who's coming back
into the country on friday.
Your mother."
That's it... mission accomplished.
Look, I wanted to clear
the air on a few things
- before she got here.
- Clear the air?
You think you can undo 15 years
of hard feelings
- with a bottle of pinot...
- Bordeaux.
I didn't even know wal-mart
had a wine cellar.
Look, would you give me a break.
I'm just trying to make
a nice night for her here.
You're sabotaging me.
- Why would I do that?
- I don't know.
But I'm gonna figure it out.
You wanted to see me, mr. Ogletree?
Shut the door, burton.
I... was reading the paper...
Yesterday...
And something caught my attention.
Have to say I was surprised,
considering you seem
to already have a full-time job.
This is... just...
Something I do on the side.
A hobby, really, like...
Collecting thimbles
or, raising carrier pigeons.
- You raise carrier pigeons?
- No, not at all. That's totally lame.
I just said that
because I was flustered.
I raise carrier pigeons.
I'm glad you said that.
Because I was afraid
to tell you how cool
I thought carrier pigeons are.
Flying around and...
Carrying stuff.
Coming back.
Awesome.
I hear that.
Are you familiar with the
exclusivity clause in your contract?
It means we
don't allow second jobs.
Jobs?
No, no. Psych is more like
community service.
- And it never affects my work.
- Well...
this photo
was taken thursday night.
I notice that you
signed out early that day.
I think the important thing
is I signed out.
Let's roll back
the clock, shall we?
Monday, the 28th.
You had three appointments.
You missed all of them.
Tuesday, the 29th,
you disappeared after lunch.
And, wednesday, well, here you are.
You did your entire week's work
in one afternoon.
- It was a crazy week.
- Seems to me you had a crazy year.
I have taken the liberty
of preparing this for you.
What is this?
It's a termination notice.
Or... you could quit
your other job.
You tell me.
Good choice!
Psych 301
"Ghosts"
Synchro : Flolo
For SeriesSub.com
you don't have to walk me
through the whole building.
I used to do
quite a few sessions here.
- This is where I met your father.
- I know. I heard the story.
He did his evaluation
after he shot some drug dealer.
He told you that?
He twisted his ankle doing security
for the cinnamon festival.
I had to clear him for duty.
Figures.
That's about par.
What happened?
He said the two of you
were getting along better.
Mom, the last thing I wanna do
right now is talk about henry.
Okay, that's fair.
Let's talk about you.
Who is that date you had
to cancel on friday?
It was just some girl I met.
She's a... museum curator.
It's not a big deal, mom.
I doubt it would have
worked out anyway.
- How many dates?
- That would have been the first.
- mom.
- Come on, goose.
Whenever we talk,
you're always about
to not go on a second date
with somebody new.
I happen to be excellent
at first dates.
You know who is
having multiple dates?
Dad. I believe he's up to number eight
with his jekyll-and-hyde
english girlfriend.
You guys should connect more often.
He told me they broke it off
a few weeks ago.
- We're talking about him again.
- Yes, we are. Let's stop. I should let you go.
How many of these
do you have to do, anyway?
Three uniforms and a detective.
- you wanna see me, chief?
- yes.
It has come to my attention,
detective,
that you've discharged your weapons
in the last four cases you've worked.
- Thank you.
- That wasn't a compliment.
I'm just trying to keep
the streets safe, chief.
The last incident
was at a cat show.
Well, let me just
go on record as saying
that I would never shoot a cat.
I guess I could find
some solace in that.
Unless it was approaching
in a threatening manner.
Or refused to stop upon my command.
I would probably just fire
a warning shot
to make my point,
but it's really a field decision.
I can't commit to it
at this juncture.
I've requested
a department-sanctioned
psychologist
to come here and have...
A session or two with you.
I'm just... Gonna have to say no.
That wasn't a question.
Could you phrase it like one?
- What the hell are you doing here?
- I should ask you the same question.
I work here.
I should ask you
a different question.
Why didn't you return
my calls all weekend?
I had no other choice
about all of this.
Oh, my god. This isn't a joke.
- You're really quitting psych?
- I'm so sorry.
In a text message, no less?
I couldn't think
of any other way to tell you.
I knew you would just try
to convince me to stay.
Listen, maybe we could
still do it on the weekends.
If you're ready
to hear some good news,
I have worked out a compromise
that will solve all of this.
- Really?
- Yes. You quit this job. This job you quit!
We take on extra cases
to make up the difference in salary.
I make 48 grand a year.
What is that, yen?
Who needs $48,000 to live?
I need 32.The other 16
generally goes to you.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I claimed you on my taxes.
Holy crap. Is this bianca's
pappardelle?
I found it in the kitchen fridge.
Oh, my gosh, she's gonna go insane.
She hand rolls her pasta
every weekend.
They take all day. She grinds her
own spices.
Well, I thought
it was for everybody. Crap!
- Paul would like to see you.
- Mr. Haversham?
Really? Lovely.
I'll be there in a second.
What does she do?
She's haversham's secretary.
Is haversham the guy
who tried to fire you?
No, he's that guy's boss.
Everybody's boss. He's the vp.
Perfect he's the one we have to convince
to let you keep doing both jobs.
I need a second. I'm gonna
clean my teeth before we go in.
No, no, no, shawn.
You're leaving now.
Gus, I'm not budging
until we make this nice.
All right. But you asked for it.
- Asked for what?
- Let go of me.
Don't you dare go boneless on me!
Okay, my ba...
You see, that's why it's not...
you son of a bitch!
You wanted to see me?
Yes, I did. I have a project for you.
Have a seat.
- Is that your wife?
- It's my grandmother.
Tell her I said she's lovely.
- She died.
- I'm going to sit down now.
Lots of talk about this
in the office.
Yes, sir, i'm aware of that,
and I've already taken care of it.
I don't think you have.
When my wife and I moved
into our house, we were met with
a series of unexplained disturbances.
Perhaps fueled by my wife's
predilection for the supernatural.
Well, after a while, it stopped.
But recently,
these occurrences have returned,
to the point where my wife
is staying with her mother.
Mr. Haversham,
why are you telling me this?
Because I believe my wife believes
our house is haunted.
And I would like to hire you.
I... Had a strange feeling
I was needed.
Looks like word getting out
about you moonlighting
- isn't the worst thing in the world.
- Let's be clear:
haversham is the most
powerful man in this office.
He's gonna be running
this company sometime soon.
- Give the man the respect he deserves.
- What is this?
- His company bio.
- Learn it. "Bred for success."
His father is william haversham,
genius entrepreneur.
This guy grew up under the tutelage
of a business master
and real estate magnate.
I know him. He's the one that built
the poliodome.
Polodome.
That's a much less depressing name.
- Shouldn't we go?
- No.
Meet me at haversham's at 7:00.
- Think I can handle that.
- And no whimpering, no screaming,
no running from anything. I don't
care how spooky his old house is.
Haversham thinks my nickname
is fearless guster.
Well, do you want to start
some sort of recording device?
No, I don't record
my sessions. I prefer just to talk.
How do you remember
the important things?
You've heard of
a photographic memory?
Well, I have a bit of, I guess you'd
call it an eidetic tonal memory.
So you'll remember
everything I've said.
Pretty much, yes.
Would you like to start?
Yes. First question:
where's the bug?
- The what?
- The bug.
Nothing new in this area.
Must be concealed on your person.
I honestly don't have
anything on me.
Then you wouldn't be opposed
to me patting you down.
Actually, i'm very opposed to that.
Would you be willing to submit
to a polygraph?
Don't do this to me. You're late.
At this moment,
you are officially late.
Just call me when you get here.
Hello?
Is somebody there?
I just heard you squeak.
Damn you, I thought you
were a ghost from outside.
And yet you still came in,
all by your lonesome.
- Fearless guster impresses.
- How did you get inside the house?
Hadewych, the housekeeper.
She was leaving, so she let me in.
Tiny little dollop
of a woman. Dutch-indonesian.
Enormous forearms.
She made me apannekoek.
It's like a pancake,
but it is the size of a manhole cover.
- Are you wearing haversham's robe?
- Yeah. You should try it.
The worm that spins this silk is
extinct. You can't find these.
- Take it off.
- I can't.
- Hello?
- Where are your clothes?
- In the dryer.
- In the dryer?
Well, the sauna was a little
bit hotter than I was expecting.
- Mr. Haversham, we got here early.
- Hadewych let us in.
We love her, and we'd like
one of our own.
- Is that an ascot?
- yes.
Yes, it is.
I like it.
It's a classic accoutrement.
It's nice to see someone
with a sense of tradition.
Gus and I are both
huge fans of the classics.
To be completely honest, I'm surprised
he isn't wearing his spats this evening.
Can we see the epicenter
of the ghoulish activity?
Please don't touch anything.
I'm sorry, Mr. Haversham.
But I'm afraid I'm going
to have to touch absolutely everything.
Including this naked lady lamp.
I also might
have to sniff some stuff.
Possibly lick some things.
These tootsie roll pops
come to mind.
Are you a skeptic, sir?
Elaine's the real believer,
so I guess you could say that.
Just as I thought.
- Please leave.
- What?
I'm sorry, sir. You are a skeptic.
Therefore, you must wait
in the hall preferably at the end.
You're killing all of my jubes.
Jubes are candies.
Exactly.
You better take off that robe.
I will. And I know
what you're trying to do.
What, innocently flip
through a photo album?
No, you're sabotaging this
on purpose.
Why would I do that?
To get me fired, so I have no other
choice but to go back psych.
That's actually an ingenious plan.
But that's not how I play, gus.
I play fair. And I roll hard.
I'm gonna find this man's ghost,
and I will rid him of it.
Did haversham have any enemies?
Not really. Corporate thinks
he's a magician.
He completely revamped
our inventory system.
Really? Whole system,
from "a" to "z"?
Including "m"? All the vowels.
This guy sounds like
a real maverick.
Mr. Haversham, allow me to say
this is my most
valuable work experience yet.
Allow me to say
that I'm not impressed.
Duly noted.
Magnum...
Quiet, boy!
Stop that!
I dont know. What is he barking at?
Come on, boy. Come on.
Come on, that's it. Here we go.
Dude... look at you.
You were cool as a cucumber
while that went down.
Fearless guster's a badass.
Let's check the basement.
- I can't.
- Why not?
My feet won't move.
So how did it go?
- I'm winning.
- How are you winning?
I answered every question
in character as tom "gunny" highway.
Who is tom "gunny" highway?
Clint eastwood's character?
In heartbreak ridge?
It's not a contest, carlton.
Don't kid yourself, o'hara.
You'll only come out losing.
Losing what?
Why are we going to the basement?
Because, gus, that's
where ghosts do their thing.
- It's cold and dark and dusty.
- Excuse me.
Can I help you two?
Yeah, we're just gonna
check out the basement.
- We don't go to the basement.
- He doesn't go to the basement.
- Why is that?
- Mold spores.
My wife had some workers here.
You can get to the door,
but you can't get in,
- 'cause it's bolted shut.
- Still think it's probably worth...
Is that hot chocolate?
It's dutch cocoa.
Hadewych makes a pot
for me each night before she leaves.
I see. Mr. Haversham, in order
to fully understand
the connection that you have
with this ghost,
I will need to see what you see.
Wear what you wear.
Drink what you drink.
You're saying you'd
like some hot chocolate.
Yes, with marshmallows, please.
Right.
What?
It's dutch.
Tastes like it was dipped
straight out of willy wonka's river.
Would you get serious?
Well, he's not the most
gracious host, you know.
If he'd just offered,
I wouldn't have had to ask.
And that pannekoek, not nearly as
filling as it may have seemed.
You're getting hot chocolate
on the floor!
Did you see that?
What the hell is...
Magnum! Down, boy!
That dog is kind of an a-hole.
- It sees something.
- Yeah.
Urine stains on my pants.
So what do we do now?
I think we stay here.
We close the blinds,
we lock the doors, we call it a night.
Del taco? Del taco.
No... not me.
- I'm going out there.
- Are you kidding me?
Shawn, this is what we do.
Yeah, but there's
a ghost out there...
okay, fine.
Do you have high-end,
energy-efficient xenon flashlights?
Pardon me for saying so...
But fearless guster sucks.
I don't care what you say.
We're solving this case. So suck it up.
Suck what up?
- What are you talking about?
I don't know.
You got my mind all messed up.
- I'm going that direction.
- She went that way.
- Good luck.
- What...
Hey, it's me.
Not letting you do this alone.
Where's... There.
I got her!
What do you mean you got her?
What is going on here?
I don't know.
I realized something.
Yesterday, with all that talk
about weapons,
I neglected to ask you
a very important question.
What kind of gun do you carry?
- Would you like to see it?
- I would love to.
Picked this up
with a little extra cash
after I decided not to go
with a divorce attorney.
You're going through a separation?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, it's...
She went with one of these
high-powered ambulance chasers,
but, that's just her...
Insecurities, you know.
You know who you remind me of?
Who?
Did you ever see that movie
heartbreak ridge?
Mold spores, shawn.
Well, I'm attracted
to places I'm not allowed to go.
Good luck
with your stachybotrous virus.
Listen, man, we need
to wrap this up quickly.
I have dinner plans
with my mom tonight.
I've hardly had a chance
to see her at all.
What?
Hadewych!
It's okay, I'm...
I'm shawn spencer. It's me,
and my partner,
lemongrass gogoloab.
Have you noticed anything strange?
Only now.
We saw a woman
in the woods last night...
That may not have been alive.
Saturday, the missus...
She leave. Go to mother's, yes?
Sunday, I forget my bag,
come back, I hear voices.
- Lady voices in the house.
- What did you do?
I leave... too much
strangeness here lately.
Something's off
with that woman, shawn.
Okay, nothing's happening.
I gotta go.
- What?
- Gus, we made plans.
My dad has been
manipulating her time all week.
Let me be clear.
I'm not leaving here
until haversham not only
wants me to keep moonlighting
at psych forever,
- but also makes me a partner.
- Sorry, buddy.
What... Wait, what's this?
Are you leaving?
Mr. Haversham, it is my belief
that we have done
all there is to do here tonight.
Tomorrow, we will look
into the history of the house,
see if there's anything
there that can help us.
Just don't have
any leads at this point.
So! I think we should all
pat each other on the backs
for a job well done so far.
Reconvene first thing in the morning
for a nice farmer's breakfast.
I have dinner plans with my mother.
Oh, you made it.
I was sure
you weren't gonna make it.
I'm sorry, ma.
You have no idea
the day I just had.
Well, I'm just running
to the ladies. We're right over there.
We?
Your father was lonely,
and I thought I might
have to eat dinner alone,
so I let him tag along.
That's fine, right?
You're absolutely certain
he's my father?
Grab a menu. We already ordered.
I'm sure it's all right.
- All right, what is this?
- What is what?
This. What is all of this?
The aftershave, the pumiced scalp.
- The suit.
- I can wear a suit.
Which one of the three tenors
did you borrow that from?
- Not the dead one, I hope.
- It's my suit, shawn.
I dress up occasionally.
You have a problem with that?
No, I have a problem
with this pretend henry
that showed up
when mom got to town.
I don't know
where you're going with this.
You're acting like a phony.
And you know it, and it's
bugging the hell out of me.
- Look at yourself.
- Shawn, I order a braised quail salad,
and all of a sudden,
you think I'm putting on airs?
Excuse me, who here has the guinea hen
crostone with the liver pancetta?
That would be me.
Everybody here is ordering it.
Look, I'm...
I'm just gonna make this easier
for both of us, okay?
I know exactly what you're up to,
- and I'm not gonna let it happen.
- Let what happen, shawn?
Yeah, if you don't mind
my saying so,
you've been a real jerk
to me all week.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you that your
mother was coming back into town.
I'm sorry you think that I
messed up your whole youth.
I'm sorry you think
that I screwed up your life.
Get over it.
You had your chance.
Now leave her alone.
Did you know that ogletree
raises carrier pigeons?
Hello.
Hello?
That's strange.
Who called?
Me.
You?
There it is again.
That's my number.
- From work?
- No... from here.
The call is coming
from inside the house?
Put it on speaker.
Hello?
Who is this?
Does this number have
any other extensions?
No.
Just... well, there's one,
but it's not plugged in.
Where is it? I'll go check it out.
Up in the attic.
The attic?
I'll... stay on the line.
You... good luck.
Come on, don't be mad.
You haunted my boss's house?
It was the only way to show him
how important and need you are.
Look how brave you've been.
If we're being honest, I think this has been
a real confidence booster for you, buddy.
Plus, once you solve
the case, you're a hero.
He never bothers you again.
Maybe you'll get a numbered
space in the green lot.
Shawn, stop it. How did you even...
Friday, after you quit
our business,
I went to your office in hopes of haunting
your regional sales manager. Ogletree.
Unfortunately,
he doesn't believe in ghosts.
So I had to go
a little higher on the rung.
Luckily for me,
katie from accounts receivable
gave me a little tip
about haversham's wife.
Finally got to use my air conditioner
and heating guy disguise.
I had an ultrasonic beeper
in my pocket for the dog.
I actually thought you
caught that one for a second.
And, dude, hear me.
Don't ever, ever
put dry ice in your mouth.
It doesn't matter
how well you wrap it up.
- Okay, what about the old woman?
- Young woman.
She does shakespeare
in the parking lot.
Down at the albertson's
by la cumbre plaza.
She was all stoked
to finally have a paying gig.
And ditching the dress in the woods,
well, that was just an improv.
Because who knew fearless guster
would come after her, you badass.
The rest of it
was pretty simple, really.
I even visited alice bundy
in prison to get a few pointers.
- How do we solve it?
- Solve what?
The ghost. How do we solve a case
where you're the culprit?
That is a very good question.
I hadn't thought that far ahead.
- You haven't thought that far ahead?
- Well, give me a second.
I'm hiding under the towel.
And then I realize
the towel's my life.
And... and the pool is third grade,
and the high dive is my father.
I poured out to you secrets
even I didn't know I had.
That was... amazing.
I mean, it's so...
Liberating to...
To trust someone
with your darkest innermost secrets.
Where have you been?
Why haven't you been here before?
I used to be here quite a bit.
I just recently came back.
I know someone here who works
for the department occasionally.
Actually, he's my son.
Really?
You know, I know pretty much
everybody who comes through
the department. What's his name?
- Ghost... gone.
- Just like that?
Just like that. It's split, it's history.
Will not be bothering you again.
And that is a guarantee.
100%.
- How can you... guarantee.
Please don't ask. Just enjoy.
And now, regarding our fee...
Of course, there will be no charge.
Knowing that you appreciate the work
that gus does for the community.
And for the company.
It's more than enough reward.
But if you were to insist
on some sort
of expense reimbursement,
we, of course, would not accept.
Please, have a seat.
I have a bit
of the sixth sense myself, mr. Guster.
Helps me out when a business deal's
about to go south.
And it's bothering me right now.
I don't understand
this... guarantee. And I don't like it.
Last night, when that call came in,
guster, you went upstairs.
At the end of that call,
I heard something
that made me question all of this.
- What was it?
- It was the voice.
- Something was wrong with it.
- What was wrong with it?
It said... "gus."
Just like that.
Well, sir...
I'm pretty sure that
that can be easily explained.
Yes, I'm sure that it can.
But there's something I really need
for you to do for me right now.
Yes?
Leave!
And, Mr. Guster,
I will carefully ponder
my next move and your future
with the company.
Let's talk, burton.
Well, thank you for your time,
mr. Haversham.
I'm... sorry you don't believe me.
But I do understand.
Can we speak privately?
Just one second.
What's your game?
I have two games.
Red rover and lawn darts.
We'd need at least four
for even the most
rudimentary game of rover, and they
don't make lawn darts anymore.
Too dangerous.
But that's not why I'm here.
I sensed several things
in that house that...
I couldn't tell you
with other people in the room.
This is getting desperate,
mr. Spencer.
But, please, wow me.
You weren't raised by your father.
You were raised
by your grandmother.
It was her ring.
Her ring that your wife wears now.
Perhaps my father
wasn't as present as I'd hoped,
and, yes, my wife
wears my grandmother's ring.
- That doesn't mean anything.
- Maybe not to you.
But the sanctity of marriage
means a lot to your grandmother,
and having an affair with, what...
A secretary?
That just feels wrong.
No matter how good
her pappardelle is.
And just what the hell
are you accusing me of?
You're getting hot chocolate
on the floor!
Is this bianca's pappardelle?
I hear voices.
Lady voices in the house.
No accusations here.
I'm just telling you, your grandmother
is very disappointed in you.
And she doesn't want you
to go to jail.
Well, nothing you've
accused me of is illegal.
He completely revamped
our inventory system.
Repackaging samples and reselling them,
while lucrative, is highly illegal.
So what is this now?
- A shakedown?
- No, there's no shakedown.
I'm just telling you what I know.
I'm a psychic, and with great power
comes great responsibility.
And that responsibility
I share with gus.
All we want is the opportunity
to continue doing our work.
Just between us?
I'm a psychic.
I can't lie.
Mr. Guster, back to work.
As per our conversation, your raise
will be reflected in your next check.
I'm sorry, i'm confused.
Spend a little more time
on your own business, frankjim.
Excuse me.
I know about you too.
His hair is horrible.
- She who bore me.
- What are you doing here, goose?
I finished working on my case.
And I had this amazing idea
that I would come by,
and scoop you up, and take you to
a movie, and it would just be us.
Actually, your dad
was planning on coming by.
Of course he was.
- Okay, I'll go.
- Wait... enough.
- What happened?
- When?
Between you two.
Mom, that is a veritable
lifetime of conversations.
- Follow me.
- No, mom. Mo... come on.
Sit!
- Are we really gonna do this?
- Sit down!
What happened? Don't mince words.
With dad? Mom, we were both there.
You know. We don't need
to revisit the past.
Maybe we do.
Well, I'm not sure I wanna forgive him
for what happened.
- The divorce?
- It wasn't what happened, mom.
It was the way that it happened.
I mean, let's call it what it was.
He left us.
He left you.
He ended up with the house, and he left
you by yourself to pick up the pieces!
That's not exactly what
I call hero material, you know?
I left him.
Come on, mom, you don't...
You don't have to spin this
for me, okay?
Let me be clear.
Your father was wonderful to me.
He wanted to keep
going to counseling.
He kept saying we could make it, but
the writing
was on the wall a long time.
You're losing me here, mom.
What are you...
When I got that job out of town,
it was an incredible opportunity.
I was afraid I would
never have a chance again, so I took it.
You were into your senior year.
Your... your path was set.
It seemed the right time,
if such a thing is possible.
I thought, of all people,
that you would be okay.
And I am so sorry.
Mom, you don't ever...
You don't ever have to be sorry.
- About anything.
- Don't you spin this.
Sometimes I get
the worst realizations.
I know...
That I failed you.
But... i think...
That day, my life began again.
And that sounds terrible, but don't
you ever think I wanted to leave you.
For SeriesSub.com [V1.02]