Okay, come on.
Move it out.
Listen, Franks...
You have the right not to get shot.
Make the wrong move,
you lose that right.
Put down the bomb.
Good move.
We recently obtained intelligence
of a bomb plot
by an antigovernment radical.
His intended target was
this very building.
We owe the success of this investigation
and, indeed, our very lives
to sergeant Henry Spencer.
Well done.
Sergeant Spencer, would you like
to say a few words?
No, thanks, chief.
A police officer doesn't deserve
any special attention
for just doin' his job.
You may be able to sense
the electricity in the room.
That's because our arrival usually
signals that a huge case is going down.
- Step in here please, gentlemen.
- That's the chief.
She likes the two of us very much.
- I'm sorry, you are?
- Oh, sorry, chief.
I got roped into doing a silly interview
with the independent.
They've been calling and begging
for weeks, and I finally relented.
- But... you called me.
- And you called me back.
Which means we're both right.
The important thing is that
you got your cover story.
Actually, it's page 64.
Depends on how you fold it, doesn't it?
She can't be in here,
so get her the hell out.
Come to think of it, I think
you'll probably get a better shot
here through this window.
Now, try to catch me with
a good expression,
preferably with this eyebrow raised...
Like so.
Or my serious face.
Best-case scenario, snap a shot
when my signature look comes up.
I call it senor gotcha!
How will I know what that is?
You'll know. Good luck.
We're all counting on you.
Lassie, you're here!
I need you... Here.
Thank you.
Chief, what's up?
Mr. Spencer, as you may be
aware, a cal...
California prisoner's advocacy...
- Are you okay?
- Right as rain.
Long story short,
a handful of convictions,
some of them decades old, have been
recently called into question.
Unfortunately, the biggest one was
a Santa Barbara P.D. conviction.
So we're reopening the case
and launching a new investigation.
Now we're hiring y...
You to provide us with any psychic
leads that you may have.
Now, normally, we don't devote
department resources to this,
but these are... special circumstances.
Could you do the handoff again, chief?
Thanks.
Oh, no.
What is it?
It's my dad's biggest case.
Psych 3x05
The disco didn't die, it was murdered.
Synchro: Arrow, Golgi, IceFre@k
www.seriessub.com
www.sub-way.fr
It goes without saying,
Mr. Spencer, that
your father is in no way to participate
in this investigation.
He's no longer on the force,
and his meddling could compromise
the case in court.
- Do I make myself clear?
- Yes, you do, chief.
What isn't clear is why people always
say, "it goes without saying,"
yet still feel compelled to say
the thing supposed to go without saying.
- Doesn't that bother you?
- No. And frankly, I could care less.
Now, that's the one that bothers me.
Why do people say, "I could care less"
when they mean "I couldn't care less"?
Why don't you tell me
how to properly say this:
if you share any official information
about this case
with your father or let him anywhere
near any new evidence,
then the two of you will have to find
another police department to work for.
And I will personally see to it
that each f you is charged
with obstruction of justice.
- You split an infinitive.
- Good catch, Gus.
You two realize I carry a gun, right?
That was perfectly elocuted.
My dad's gonna freak when he sees this.
We have to go into stealth mode.
No taking his calls.
This won't hit the news till tomorrow.
That should give us
a 24-hour head start.
Hand it over.
Dad, how did you get in here?
The unlatched window.
The unlocked back door.
Maybe this key that I made.
You choose one.
What do you want?
I dropped by to share my new chocolate
chip raisin bread recipe with you.
What do you think?
I know chief Vick just
gave you the new Franks case.
Why don't you let me take a look at what
you're hiding in that folder
so I can get moving on this?
Okay, you're right.
Chief Vick did just hire us.
But there is no way that I'm showing you
what's in this folder.
You're lucky I'm asking you.
I could do this the simple way.
I could grab it,
clean up any evidence of struggle before
you and your friend knew what hit you.
- In some states, that's child abuse.
- I think all of them.
Look, chief Vick
made it clear that you, specifically,
were to come nowhere near this case.
This shouldn't even be a case.
The son of a bitch was let out on
some microcrap problem with
my search warrant.
- Everybody makes mistakes.
- There was no mistake!
It was the 70's.
We did what we had to do.
But only when we knew we had
the right guy, and I got the right guy.
Period.
Okay. You got the right guy.
Still doesn't mean I'm gonna
put you on this case.
Nor would I even want to.
Dad, you have no idea how
Gus and I roll... Gus, tell him.
You know what? You go ahead
and handle this half-assed
like you do everything else.
But you bear this in mind.
This case is important to
a lot of people who could have died
if he had blown up our headquarters.
It should be important to
their family members too.
Never seen my dad beg before.
That's how he begs?
He's clearly not gonna let this go.
So look, if we're gonna investigate
this thing undisturbed,
we're gonna have to jump a few steps,
fill in the blanks when we're done.
We should go straight
to the D.A.'s office.
Beat you by eight minutes.
Not too embarrassing.
Dad, I knew you would come and try
to investigate this on your own.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous this is?
Why? I'm a tax paying, voting citizen.
Therefore,
I have a right to speak to any elected
official, such as the D.A., I please.
You don't have to be a...
- Tax paying, voting citizen, do you?
- May I help you?
Yes. My name is Shawn Spencer.
I am the head psychic for
the Santa Barbara Police Department.
- And that is my partner...
- Yeah, yeah, that's his partner,
methuselah honeysuckle,
which makes me old scratch johnson.
We need to see copies
of the original court transcripts
for the Eugene Franks case.
I'm not sure I can release those.
I'm getting a very soft,
cuddly vibe here.
It seems like you and your wife are...
They're gonna have another kid.
It's a boy. Congratulations.
Do yourselves a favor.
Don't call it Shawn.
Problems.
More importantly,
according to the freedom
of information act,
those transcripts are
available for viewing.
So...
Very well. Good point.
I'll have our records department
make copies.
Thank you very much.
You know, you're putting a damper
on the proceedings.
You call it a damper.
I call it working.
All right, that's it.
Come here.
All right, I need you to hear me, okay?
If you insist on staying involved
in this case,
there are going to be rules.
I was hired by the police department.
Therefore, it is my ass on the line,
and those rules will be made by me.
You are no longer a cop.
And unless you plan on going back
to the academy
climbing the wall, doing the obstacle
course where you shoot the bad guys,
but not the lady with the sack
or the guy with the cane or the squirrel
with the tail and the big, fat nut...
That started off well.
It really fell apart at the end.
You should have had a name
for the wall or something.
What I'm saying is that you need
to listen to me, is what I'm saying.
All right, Shawn.
Point taken.
You got a deal.
That means you're workin' for me now.
Why don't you grab some coffee for us?
Black.
Two sugars.
I don't understand...
You guys had to handwrite everything?
What if you need multiple copies?
Well, we had one computer,
but it took up the entire second floor.
Generally, we would use
the mimeo machine.
How long did that take, a week?
All the high-tech fancy gadgets
they use today
don't solve crimes any better
than we did.
A good detective is born with all
the tools he needs right here.
Hello. Chief, what's the good w...
My dad, down at the D.A.'s office?
No, I-I don't think so.
I think I can clear this up
for ya, chief.
That wasn't my dad.
That was Phil Collins.
We saw Phil down at the courthouse.
My dad gets mistaken for
him all the time.
I don't look... Shawn...
I don't look anything like phil collins.
No, I'm... I'm fairly certain
about this, chief.
He was humming invisible touch,
if that helps you.
No.
I- I wasn't aware that Phil Collins
lives in switzerland.
How does she know so
much about phil collins?
I don't know.
Yes. I do hear you.
I will make sure he stays away.
Love you too.
Do you see?
- We have to be more careful.
- Okay, hot shot.
All right, I get it.
Tell me what you can glean from this.
You'd like to know what I can glean?
Glean.
The D.A. arrested after only submitting
the initial evidence?
Correct-a-mundo. The evidence
I uncovered in that department
was so strong, the D.A. didn't need
anything else to get a conviction.
But all the evidence is poisonous fruit
because of the search warrant.
This evidence, yes.
Good thing I got a different warrant
for the second round.
The D.A. didn't submit any of that stuff
which means we can use that now.
All the high-tech gadgets in
the world won't tell you that, will it?
We gotta get the chief
to let us into the county archives
so we can take a look at that evidence.
- Gus, gimme your keys.
- That would be a no.
- Ogletree's checking my mileage.
- We'll take my truck.
No, we won't. That raises the chances
of you being seen again.
We'll have to take my motorcycle.
I've always wanted to try threesies.
Who wants the handlebars?
- Gus, feels like you.
- No.
That shouldn't draw any attention.
We'll cab it.
Fine.
It's funny.
It's usually me who can't show
my face in public.
Just think, the contents
inside these boxes
could determine whether someone spends
the rest of their life in jail.
Catch.
Better hope they don't reopen
the handyman killer case.
Your fingerprints are all over
the murder weapon.
- That's not funny, Shawn!
- Dude, I'm kidding.
It's not really evidence.
It was just lying here.
Well, stop it. You know I'm afraid
that being wrongfully convicted
is the tragic way my story ends.
Would you two girls stop bitching
and see what we got here?
What is this stuff?
Various possessions, personal effects of
Eugene's we found after he was arrested.
All right, what do we got here?
Pawn ticket made out to Eugene
a few days before he was arrested.
"Goldstein's pawn."
Anybody?
Wait. That place is still around.
Desperate people pawn things.
Let's see what eugene pawned
and never got back, huh?
Two new cases just came in.
One involves an international
diamond smuggling ring.
- Sweet!
- Bingo!
The other involves fraudulent permits
at a plastics factory.
Well, I'll leave it up to the two of you
to decide who gets which.
- I am the head detective.
- Who owes me.
I covered your butt on
last month's paperwork.
Damn it.
Follow my lead.
Mcnab!
Get over here!
I don't know, O'hara.
I don't think he's ready.
Yeah, I... I don't think he is either.
No. I'm ready.
All right.
Mcnab, how would you like to
do some real police work?
I'd love to.
Now, technically, you'll be working
under detective O'hara and myself, but
we'll let you take the lead on this.
It will be such a
good experience for you.
It might even earn you a spot
on the detective bureau someday.
Wow! Thanks, guys.
This means a lot. The fact that you
think so highly of me
- to trust me...
- We love you. Get back to work.
This ticket is from
30 years ago when my dad
ran the shop.
I'll have to go look through the box.
Box?
What do you think the box is?
A giant room like in raiders?
I think it's a box.
Secret catacombs underneath
the building like in national treasure?
Shame on you for knowing that.
This is where we keep all the
old unclaimed stuff from over the years.
- As I said, a box.
- What do you think's inside the box?
- Will you calm down?
- I can't, man! There's stuff in there!
All kinds of stuff, old stuff,
shiny stuff, secret stuff...
- How come you're not as excited as me?
- Because I'm not a raccoon.
- You look like a raccoon.
- Hey, you're in luck.
This ticket here...
Matches this old receipt.
Not a lot of info on it, i'm afraid.
I know what that...
- Right. Your case.
- Oh, I'm getting something here.
Oh, this is intense.
I can see Eugene.
He's desperate
and he's sweating nervously.
He's stinky, he wants to get rid
of something, cover his tracks,
hide where he's been.
He brings in the title to his car.
That must be
the V.I.N. right in there.
Right.
Whose benefit was that for?
Don't ever question my methods
in front of a civilian. OK?
Never do that.
Come here.
I always thought that Eugene
was gonna use the car in a bomb plot.
That was a common M.O. back then.
He probably pawned the title
- to cover his tracks.
- If nobody reclaimed the title,
we would have sold it.
We could use the VIN number
to track where it ended up.
That could take us over the city
or the state, for that matter,
thus increasing the chances
that you'll be seen by someone
you work with
and you being caught by the police.
Unless...
Nobody recognizes us.
I feel ridiculous.
Speak for yourself.
I've got this shirt at home.
- His mother used to love it.
- Yeah, like 30 years ago.
Kid, I wore it to lunch last week.
There it is.
It's been sittin'
in some old lady's backyard
- for dang near 30 years.
- You got the keys?
- Let's take a look inside.
- Make me an offer and it's yours.
You gotta be kiddin'.
Just... give us a second here.
- How much money do we have between us?
- What?
I think I got about...
50 bucks.
I got about 400
between my wallet and my sock.
It's my "just in case" money.
All right. Add in what I have,
and we've got about...
450.
All right, let me go talk to him.
You stand down, popeye doyle.
I'll handle this.
Got about $450 here.
Now, how much is this gonna cost me?
- $450.
- Done.
He's good!
Nice goin'.
That was all of our money.
That's what happens
when you send in the one guy
who's never bought a car before.
- We had exactly enough.
- All right, look at it this way.
It isn't a car.
It's a time machine.
This little kitty's gonna tell us
about Eugene 30 years ago.
Well, looks like a car to me.
And if I bought it, i'm drivin' it.
That means my same car rules apply.
Wipe your shoes before entering.
No slamming doors.
No food.
Looks good up here.
Doesn't look like factory soldering.
Smuggler's hatch.
Gotta get this down to the crime lab.
Let me guess. This is where we take one
step back before involving the police.
We need to see
what's on that film first.
That's how we roll.
I think I need a tetanus shot.
Got it.
Miracle anything came out.
This guy really loved his car?
After seeing it all cleaned up,
I like it too.
In fact, I love it.
Bingo! You think these two other ones
could have had something to do
- with the bombing?
- From the AK-47s they're holding,
they had something to do with something.
It's worth checkin' out.
There's no telling where they are,
if they're even still around.
You know, back then, I used to have
this snitch working for me.
His name was Pookie.
Real weasel.
The guy would turn on
his siamese twin for a buck.
If these two had anything
to do with this,
- Pookie's the guy who would have known.
- Sorry. What...
- What was his name?
- Pookie.
- Do you know where we can find this...
- Pookie?
Yeah, his name is...
His name is Pookie Wiggington,
and I know where to find him.
- What's so funny?
- Stop, please!
Nothing's funny, you just...
But you're keepin' it real right now.
- Right on.
- Let's see if we can find Pookie.
See if he still remembers the'70s.
If that had been on purpose,
that would have been totally cool.
I need to get that power steering fixed.
Not to mention the seat is jammed
all the way to the front and makes
my entire left side fall asleep.
And remember, tomorrow night will be
ladies' night
at the top flight dance club,
where it's the'70s every night!
Don't worry!
I think Pookie remembers
the'70s just fine.
By the way,
I'm just puttin' this out there.
Once we re-solve this case,
preserve your legacy as a detective,
you don't have to say thank you.
- No biggie.
- Course it is.
Heck, let me say it right now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That's Pookie.
Let's go.
Officer Spencer.
Long time no see.
What brings you gentlemen
to my establishment?
As you may have heard,
the D.A. recently overturned
the conviction on the Eugene
Franks bombing case.
Maybe I heard.
Maybe I didn't.
Right.
We're lookin' for information on a few
people that might have used to run
with old Eugene.
Sorry. I don't know
what you're talkin' about.
All right.
I know how this works.
Hit the other sock.
Give him some money.
No offense, guys,
but I don't need your pocket change.
I can see two of Eugene's partners
in crime, a man and a woman...
Dangerous, highly skilled
with military weapons.
But not U.S. military.
Smuggled
weapons.
I used to trip like that.
Always looking for the escape.
Pookie, he's cool.
He's...
Psychic.
Really?
Then I can dig it.
Spiritual.
- Third eye.
- That's where it is.
You guys are deep.
Like me.
Gimme five.
So listen,
you were dead on it.
Check this out.
The cats you were describing
ran with Eugene, all right.
There were two of 'em.
Derek Ford, white guy, stringy hair,
and his old lady
Melanie.
Really fine... I got shot
over a white girl like that once.
Anyway, they were together in a militant
organization with Eugene called S.A.G.
Soldiers Against Government.
They were into all kind
of radical stuff.
Why would Eugene go all those years
and not rat them out?
Word on the street was
that SAG was ruthless.
Nobody dared cross them,
not even one of their own.
So Eugene was just a Patsy?
You didn't hear it from me.
No, them suckers are dangerous!
He had partners.
My biggest bust...
And I was wrong.
Everything hurts.
You had to be a tough guy
and go in first.
Let's just fill out the incident report
and be done with this fiasco.
What happened to you guys?
The diamond smuggling case
that detective O'Hara
wanted to take didn't go quite
- as planned.
- That I wanted to take?
You're the one who insisted on it,
Mr. Head-detective.
Basically,
we conducted a stake out to catch
the smugglers red-handed,
but when we opened
the cargo container
to seize the evidence,
we discovered we had the wrong one.
This one belonged
to exotic animal smugglers.
And it was filled
with wild marmosets.
- I hate marmosets.
- Apparently, they don't like
- being shot at.
- No, apparently not.
All I can remember after that are
hundreds of those... tiny,
razor-sharp claws and teeth!
Lower primate, my ass.
I recognize a military formation
when I see one.
You'll be happy to know
that case you gave me took a fun turn.
That's great!
It turns out that plastics factory
was a front for real-life sea pirates.
- You're kidding.
- They've been using high-tech boats
and GPS to rob freighters
in the shipping lanes.
Now, I'm teaming up
with the coast guard for a showdown
- of the Santa Barbara coast.
- On the high seas?
Appears so.
Gosh,
I'm sorry, Buzz, but...
you need a certain level of clearance
to work with the coast guard.
It's... It's department rules.
- Really?
- I'm afraid we're gonna have to...
Take over from here.
But good work
on getting us to this point.
- It was fun while it lasted.
- Yeah.
Good work, buddy.
- We're gonna capture pirates!
- I know!
- Almost makes up for the rabies shots.
- Almost.
Let's face it, Shawn.
I blew the case.
- You're quitting on me?
- I'm not quitting.
I just realized
that maybe chief Vick is right.
I should stay out of it.
Dad, this was your big case.
My big case. My big bust.
You see, that's the problem right there.
That's how I started seeing it.
But in reality,
it's a Santa Barbara P.D. case
- and always has been.
- You don't believe that.
A good detective knows
when to let it go.
That's a lesson both you
and I could learn right now.
- Where's your dad?
- He's not coming. He says
it's to protect the case,
but I can tell
it's really bumming him out
that he got fooled 30 years ago.
I can't believe I'm about to say this,
but instead of lording over him
that this is our case, our rules...
We have to convince him that we can't
solve this thing without him.
How do we do that?
Most likely,
through the use of trickery.
What kind of wood are we
gonna use for these bookshelves?
Cypress?
Cypress? Really?
It's a good wood.
It's what Noah's ark was made of.
You wanna use something
that breathes a little more,
don't worry, we'll hit
a lumberyard on the way there.
At least I get a chance
to use my new laser level.
Why are we stopping here?
No reason...
I just randomly selected this spot.
Don't be a smart-ass. You're reading
an address of a piece of paper,
we're sitting in somebody's driveway.
Whose house is this?
Actually, we're dropping
in on some people that we know.
Shawn, I think that's them!
- What the hell is going on?
- Don't lose 'em. Go, go!
Come on!
- So what do we do now?
- I don't know.
I've never cornered anyone before.
They better hope
they're not uneven in there.
I'm gonna blind 'em
with the laser, Shawn.
May we help you?
Derek and Melanie Ford?
Or should I say
"Soldiers Against Government"?
You sure your father
doesn't want to come inside?
He's clinically insane and a biter.
Sorry again about running
from you guys,
but when we saw the mercury cougar
in the driveway, we just figured
it was Eugene...
coming after us for revenge.
Revenge for what?
He thinks
that we set him up to take the rap
- for the police headquarters bombing.
- He's been asking around town about us,
trying to figure out our whereabouts.
We thought he'd finally found us.
Well, don't you worry about that.
You help us with this investigation,
we will make sure the police
protect you from your old pal.
Thank you.
Tell him everything, honey.
After Eugene got arrested 30 years ago,
we freaked out,
and we stopped our radical ways.
We became soldiers for government.
We built this great life.
You have to believe us. We had
nothing to do with setting Eugene up.
I mean, we were all brainwashed.
We were all caught up in the movement.
Do you know of anyone else
who would have wanted to set him up?
Honey, are you okay?
I cut myself pretty good.
Excuse me. I'm gonna have
to go put something on this.
Sorry.
We should get going.
Thank you for your cooperation.
And rest assured,
Eugene will not learn
of your whereabouts. Thanks again.
- Hope your finger feels better!
- Thank you!
Good news, pop!
The trail is hot again.
Like I said, count me out.
Damn it, Dad, do you have to be
so prideful all the time?
So you made a mistake 30 years ago.
Nobody cares. Just get over it.
Not everybody's as comfortable
screwin' up as you are, kid.
I'm comfortable 'coz my mistakes is the
only thing that was pointed out to me.
Here we go, here we go.
Would you put away the violin?
I pointed out the good stuff.
But usually, you were too busy bragging
and showing off to take notice.
Enough. I'm sick of you two
fighting all the time.
Listen, Mr. Spencer,
Shawn needs you on the case because,
frankly, you're old,
and we were barely even alive
during the'70s.
And Shawn,
your dad needs you on the case
because even though you can be annoying,
you actually have a brilliant idea
every now and then.
But you're too damn stubborn
to admit you need each other.
Now can we go, please?
Thank you.
Is he always such a know-it-all?
- You don't know the half of it.
- Very preachy.
So tell me what you have.
- I think there's another SAG member.
- How do you know that?
Did you see Melanie when we asked
if anyone who'd want to set up Eugene?
She cut herself right there,
right there on the spot.
No, maybe they were telling you
what they wanted you to know,
not what you needed to know.
I think they're protecting somebody
from Eugene.
But there were only three people
in the picture.
No, there was four.
The three of them
and whoever took the picture.
Maybe they're protecting an old mentor.
I'm pretty sure
that Eugene met Derek and Melanie
when they were all students
at Santa Barbara University.
Let's see if they shared
any professors or advisors or RAs.
- RA... That's a thing, right?
- It is.
Okay, let's do this.
Back to undercover.
Got it. Thank you, Jules.
All right, according to Juliet,
University records show that our
SAG members only shared one professor,
and that is Dr. Richard Colbert.
I think Eugene got here before we did.
I've been waiting for you guys.
Yeah, we got your call
when we were out on the open ocean
chasing down our sea pirates at flank.
That's a nautical term
for maximum speed.
We cordoned the private vessel
before they could club haul...
That's the nautical term
for evasive maneuver...
- And make it to international waters.
- That sounds awesome.
- What do modern sea pirates look like?
- We have no idea.
Once you get three miles out,
it's out of our jurisdiction,
so the coast guard has us sequestered
to a tiny, windowless cabin
on the lubber deck.
Yeah, apparently that's a nautical term
for place they send you to puke.
- Had to wash my hair three times.
- Still sorry about that.
Let's do this.
So, what do we have here?
The deceased is one Dr. Richard Colbert.
Male, 60 years old,
professor of chemistry.
Apparently, he died from a lab accident
involving poisonous hydrochloric
acid fumes.
When will people ever learn that alcohol
and hydrochloric acid don't mix?
Technically, they do.
See, the hydrogen atoms in the acid
form a loose bond with the chlorine...
What the hell are you wearing?
I'm gettin' some serious jive,
and it is fly.
I can see the struggle.
There's a rag on Colbert's face.
It was him who masterminded the bombing,
30 years ago.
He set Eugene up.
And eugene has murdered him...
In revenge.
But... Wait!
There's more.
The field is strong.
I am gettin' it.
And it is a bad mother...
- Shut your mouth! I can dig it.
- I'm havin' a vision.
It's a big birthday cake.
- Make a wish!
- What?
Bomb.
Eugene's built another bomb!
He built it here in the lab!
That's how he's gonna exact his revenge
on the remaining members of SAG!
We've gotta stop him now!
That's all I got. The jive's over.
We should go before people explode.
Found him lookin' around out back.
Must have hidden this under the house.
We got a bomb!
Which... hasn't been activated.
Call the bomb squad.
Eugene, looks like you've been up
to your old tricks.
I'm only here because
they called me saying
they were finally ready to come clean.
Invited guests don't go
snoopin' around the back.
I was just checking to see
if anybody was home.
- I swear!
- Save it for the trial.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Richard Colbert.
Wait, wait!
Colbert's dead?
And the attempted murder
of Derek and Melanie Ford.
Thank god you stopped him in time.
I cut myself pretty good.
I need to go put something on this.
Maybe they were telling you
what they wanted you to know,
not what you needed to know.
Lies, lies, lies!
Lies!
You two.
You were two young kids
in way over your head
with the militant SAG
So you used Eugene
as a scapegoat, didn't you?
Set him up to take the fall
for the police headquarters bombing
so you could make a clean break.
But then you heard he got out early,
and you were afraid he'd
he'd come track you down
and expose your criminal past.
We know he's been asking about us,
trying to figure out our whereabouts.
We thought he'd found us.
Because of the four members of SAG,
only two of you are doin'
okay for yourselves.
Eugene has lost 30 years,
and he will be marked
as a criminal forever.
And Dr. Colbert,
his drinking destroyed his career.
But you two...
Your life is picture-perfect.
And you would kill to protect it.
First, it was Dr. Colbert.
His guilt-ridden conscience
and drunk mouth
would cause him to confess
everything to Eugene.
And then the plan was simple.
Frame eugene for that murder,
and then blow Eugene up
right along with all the traces
to your past
so you could move on
to a very bright, white pickety future.
That's a preposterous theory.
- Preposterous!
- You have no proof.
Really?
What if I did somethin' like this?
Spencer, what did you just do?
In exactly one minute,
we will all be blown to smithereens.
Or the people responsible
for making that bomb
will deactivate it.
Don't look at me. He's crazy.
I don't know how either.
I demand that someone
disarm this bomb right now!
Arrest them.
Come on.
Go.
Spencer, I'd appreciate it in the future
if you just played with your own life.
Come on, lassie.
If derek hadn't caved,
I would have just deactivated it myself.
Very easy.
You just clip the red wire
and the green wire at the same time.
- There is no green wire.
- Really?
In that case,
we all would have died.
I am starving.
Who's up for fajitas?
My treat.
Come on, you guys.
Not everybody would have died.
A couple of people would have lived.
Those are the...
The odds are that at least one...
Gus would have made it.
It'll only take a few minutes for me
to finish my interview.
I still don't see
why you drag me into this.
I told you... They're gonna wanna hear
about my last case,
which was originally your case,
and without you,
- it wouldn't have been solved again.
- Interviews, press, hair...
Those are your things.
A little attention isn't gonna kill you.
- One more thing.
- What?
Thank you.
As the bomb ticked down to zero,
we held our ground.
And I looked those culprits in the eye,
and they knew that their time was up.
We don't seek out
the high-profile cases.
They just have a way of finding us.
- Well, we should just show her.
- That's a great idea.
- You were there. You were here.
- I was here?
No, we walked up,
and then they walked out.
- They did?
- Yeah, they came out with the...
- So they had the bomb.
- No, they really did.
They didn't know it was a bomb.