Get in here a second.
Gus, what are you doing here?
I'm representing shawn
in this situation.
Shawn!
Get in here.
Take a look around.
Well, what am I looking at?
Something's missing.
I took something of yours.
You need to figure out what it is.
Dad, you robbed me?
No, robbery's the taking of property
by force or fear.
I'm not afraid of anyone in this room.
So you're a burglar then?
No, gus.
Burglary involves breaking in.
This is theft, pure and simple.
You need to figure out what it is...
or you're not getting it back.
Concentrate.
You thief!
You stole my bb gun.
Technically, yes, theft makes
me a thief.
- You're learning.
- So can I have it back now?
No.
I told you not to play with
it in the yard.
It's too dangerous.
But you said if I figured out
what was missing, I--
thieves always lie.
Remember that.
How'd you even know I was playing
with it in the backyard?
Mr. Coburn, we are interested
in anything you can tell us.
They were big and scary, these guys.
Didn't you say you didn't see them?
That's... right.
Of course they were big and scary.
Look at this place.
- The man's lucky to be alive.
- Carlton, I've got this.
- What time did you begin your shift?
- 8:00.
- Are you the only watchman?
- Yeah.
Would you mind showing me where you
were standing at the time of the attack?
Yeah.
I was walking through here.
Spencer, what the hell are
you doing up there?
Right now I'm putting my hand
in my pocket, sans thumb,
pointing at an imaginary seagull.
But earlier I got a call from the chief.
She sounded serious.
Third break-in of its kind
in as many months.
- No leads.
- Chief told you that?
No, she did.
She looks like the venus de milo,
but she prefers to be called
Traci with an "i."
She saw everything.
Said I should check the videos
in the surveillance room.
- The mannequin told you that?
- No, chief did.
Come on, Lassie, keep up with me here.
- I need you paying attention.
- Do you think you can make that happen?
I only opened my book
for a second, Shawn.
- You know I have to study for my exam.
- Right.
The RX... something.
RX Rep, RX.
Pharmaceutical rep
re-certification exam.
That is the second worst
name for a test ever,
right after the proctological practicum.
My job depends on it and you said
you were gonna help me.
I'm not sure how I can.
You keep such sloppy notes.
What is this green slime on your book?
Did you come from kids' choice awards?
- This place is filthy.
- Maybe it's a clue.
- Maybe it's urine.
- Smell it.
I'm not gonna smell it.
Are you gonna help me or not?
We've never had more
than two people in this room.
It's cozy, which means I'll need
everyone's hands where I can see them.
That means yours, too, chief.
- Who's this?
- That's our psychic, Shawn Spencer.
Psychic, and treasurer of
the american wicker council.
I'm up for re-election.
I'm running on a rattan platform.
- Stuart.
- This is my favorite booster,
- detective carlton lass...
- Would you just play the tape?
That's a lariat move.
These guys are ex-military.
No question.
And that one there is calling the shots,
so there appears to be a pattern here.
Well, detectives,
when you know something,
you could find me in my office.
Hey, chief.
All right, we definitely
need to check out
all the local paramilitary groups,
the security contractors, rotc.
Santa barbara ladies auxiliary.
Oh, they're women.
It can't be women.
This kind of thing took
some kind of muscle.
It's a little shocking, isn't it?
Not as shocking as this:
these are 31s and they're really
pulling through here.
Make yourself useful.
Get me the 32s.
I don't have time for this.
Either you have something or you don't.
Got it.
Let's go see the chief.
- You got it?
- Let's just say I've got suspects.
Good.
Let's go and give them the names.
I got studying to do.
How many suspects are we talking?
Eh, give or take--
80 suspects?
Really, Mr. Spencer.
It wouldn't be possible perhaps
to narrow it down just a bit, would it?
Not without help.
It's a tight group, chief.
It's a clique.
It's a sisterhood of the ya-ya variety,
and it's gonna take
a lot more than a smile
and a pack of pall malls
to get 'em to talk.
Not a problem. Tough-to-crack suspects
are right in my wheel house.
Negative, we cannot go about this
using a typical lassitarian technique.
We need someone...
On the inside.
Are you saying you want
to go undercover?
Undercover? Yes.
Me? No.
Unfortunately I'm not qualified
for this sort of thing.
Don't worry about it.
I've been itching to do
some undercover work and
I've got a new moustache guy.
I like where your head's at,
because this is going to take
a very specific skill set.
There is only one person in this room
that can pull it off.
I've just got one question.
Can you skate?
And it's looking like we're in for an
an excruciating jam as maniac
cuts through the pack like a machete.
That defense had better get on
the defensive or else.
Ooh, look out below!
Psych 3x07:
Talk Derby to Me
Synchro: Arrow, Golgi, IceFre@k
www.seriessub.com
www.sub-way.fr
Berman auditorium is about to become
the garden of beatin'!
And it's Miss anthropy
around the outside.
Don't let her through!
Pick her up!
Somebody pick her up!
I couldn't have called
a better assignment.
Yeah, right.
You're a rocket scientist.
I thought the police had a suspect from
the roller derby, like, a month ago.
- Seven-- seven--
- Seven deadly cinderella.
Yeah, but it didn't go anywhere.
What did you find that got chief Vick
back onto this roller derby angle?
Oh, just everything.
Damage, the hand signals.
The scuff marks on the floor
were caused by
62-millimeter core composite
competition skate wheels.
Vick wouldn't buy it until
I threw in some roller babble.
Think about it.
Who better for a smash and grab job...
than an organized team?
You think they were all on wheels?
At least one of them was.
What makes you so sure
it was one of these teams?
You want to take this one?
What?
Check the schedule. These were
the only two teams who were off
on all the nights the break-ins
occurred.
We call that detective work.
It's a rare and beautiful thing.
Like clubbed thumbs.
I don't know how we're gonna solve
this case. These women scare me.
Are you kidding?
It's a cake assignment.
I used to do some security work
for the roller derby back in the day.
Those broads, they knew
how to get the job done.
This is-- I don't know.
This is like a fashion show.
- These broads, they don't hit
- That's why we brought you down here.
To hear you say "broads"
repeatedly.
Why don't you explain to us
how all this works.
Do you see the one with the star
on her helmet?
She's the lead jammer. She scores points
when she passes the opposing skaters.
All right, look at her, right there.
The one they call fox--
She's reaching down.
She's up to something.
See that piece of tape?
Number 13.
She's been marked.
She's gonna get hit.
She's gonna be taken down.
Watch this.
Watch it. Here it goes.
Oh, and there's another one
for the suicide seats!
It's happy times for westwood, wilde,
and captain denise "kamikaze" fox.
This is our only chance
to snoop around, gus.
Let's go.
- Dad, you all right?
- Hit her!
No, hit her now!
She's down!
He's fine.
Would you--
hit!
What are we doing, shawn?
Well, for starters, we're both
growing moustaches
very, very slowly,
but we're also investigating.
This is Juliet's investigation.
We're gonna blow her cover.
- We need to stay out of her way.
- You're exactly right, gus.
Or we do the exact opposite.
I vote for number two.
Be my lookout.
No, there's only a few minutes left,
shawn, and you want to go inside...
Worst lookout ever.
You didn't see the girl walk in?
And I round this corner,
and there's maniac.
And I'm, like, "where'd she go?"
And she's, like, "where'd who go?"
She moves pretty good for fresh meat.
That's totally a compliment.
Where'd you learn to skate like that?
Oh, you know, college roller-skate team.
And Xanadu.
That's funny.
I get it.
Dude, you are leering.
And if by leering, you mean
staring oddly
in a creepy way, yes, but it's for
an investigation, gus.
They're all scraped up
from burglarizing.
Burglarization?
Burglarism.
Of course they're scraped up.
It's a full contact sport.
Since when do we get injuries
underneath our elbow pads.
And that's a glass cut on the other one.
Check it out.
That's leering.
- Shawn, what are you guys doing here?
- I'm moving on this case.
I'm pretty sure I found the extra
sensory vortex in this building.
- Where?
- Women's locker room.
Which is a place I've always wanted
to hang out,
- so it's totally a win-win.
- I get this is how you work.
But this is not how we are going
to be doing things.
I am lead detective, and this is first
and foremost a police investigation.
So if we are going to be partners,
we are going to be doing things my way.
All kidding aside, I got some
serious vibes in there.
And possibly athlete's foot.
Great, i'll check it out and
come by your office later,
but right now I need you guys
to get out of here.
Is this guy bothering you, maniac?
Wilde, fox, this is--
- This is...
- I know who this guy is.
We see gawkers like him all
the time around here.
Really easy to spot.
There's always one thing off about them.
Clothes, hair,
teeth.
You just named my three best features.
Fourth on the list, posture.
Fifth, elocution.
Maniacmaniac19, president pro-tem,
maniac fan club.
This is my vice president,
longbranch pennywhistle.
I'm just looking to score a little
face time with the maniac,
you know, for the blog.
689 hits and climbing.
Nothing I can't handle.
I was just about to give 'em
an interview.
It was only gonna be two words.
Okay, come on.
I'll see you tonight.
Bring the outfit.
One of us might wear it.
Get lost!
Might I have a word in my office?
Oh, sorry, chief.
I have to break these things in,
and you know how my family is cursed
with bad arches, right?
Please take them off.
I was just gonna suggest that.
Later.
Did you break somebody's nose?
Yes, I did.
Thank you.
Oh, but it was a clean hit.
It was actually more of a dislocation.
You know, it just popped right back in.
Yeah, she curled into my wingspan,
so I was totally justified.
We're friends now.
She has a cat.
I'm concerned for your safety
and that this might be a mistake.
No, no, no.
It is not a mistake.
It's actually a very smart call.
I have found a scad of priors
on my suspects.
Aggravated assault, battery.
Oh! And reckless endangerment.
So you're saying putting you
in danger is a bonus?
I'm telling you I can handle myself.
I didn't want to do
this in the first place,
and I'll be candid, O'Hara.
You tend to dive in a little too deeply
when you go undercover.
Look, chief...
First off,
roller derby is better than therapy.
If I were into that sort of thing.
And secondly, these girls,
they're not making any money.
Most of them are paying out of pocket,
they are all the right element
for this kind of behavior.
Hunches and profiles
are not gonna keep this thing going.
I need concrete proof...
soon.
I want every single one of those
suspects from that security video.
Done.
This a typo, right?
$800 for skates?
Would it help if I told you
the other pairs weren't cute at all?
Get me results.
Hurry.
This is "maniac".
Tonight?
Yeah, I can keep it quiet.
Okay.
I'll be there.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Oh, my God.
Is there somebody here?
Are you on a date?
I didn't know if you'd be hungry,
I threw something together quickly.
We gotta get right to this.
I was just at the station,
- I really think I am on to something.
- That's great.
We have all night to talk about it.
- Gewurztraminer?
- Yes... No!
I can't stay.
I got a call from one of the girls.
- Are those crab cakes?
- Yes, they are.
With dill and coriander.
- Which girl are we talking about?
- They call her
"toxic waste",
but her name is Shelly.
Said she was talking to some of the
other girls and that they were very
impressed by me,
I am perfect for something
they have going on downtown tonight.
A money-making opportunity.
Don't go.
I ran some of their names.
- They have records.
- I've already eliminated "toxic waste".
- She wasn't at the break-in.
- I don't think you understand.
I am undercover right now,
things can get real sticky, real fast.
Sticky how?
Listen.
This thing that's happening tonight,
it's not what you think it is.
Now, sit down, have some endives.
Are we working together or not?
Technically we're working together
on this case, but you know what?
- I'm not feeling together right now.
- Then support me.
Because I really think
I am on to something.
I gotta go
and you're either in or you're out.
North exit, south exit.
Nobody gets out.
You do realize
we're outside of a warehouse.
That's not the point.
Even if it's not a burglary,
it's likely some kind
of criminal activity.
This place isn't like
any of the others.
I am really sorry
I have to do this to you, but...
Spencer, you're in the way.
Go.
We're gonna let her get in here.
And on her signal,
we're gonna light this candle.
- Brilliant! Beautiful!
- Stand down.
Do it again!
Reset the playback, please.
A music video shoot?
I sent nearly a dozen uniformed officers
and six black and whites,
and none of your suspects
were even there.
I'm gonna need a pretty damn compelling
reason not to pull the plug on this one,
because right now, we've got nothing.
It was me.
I felt a vibe.
I got a message.
You did?
Yes.
Turns out it
was a major metaphysical snafu.
O'Hara said it was a non-start.
I threw a tantrum.
I was crying,
kicking, and stamping my little feet.
They're not abnormally small.
Chief, I can get results.
Let me in on this.
Sure, chief.
Lassie seems like a smart choice.
We know he's a demon on wheels,
and he's so very good with women.
Under the circumstances,
I might consider you.
But you're never more obvious than
when you're undercover.
Perhaps you've forgotten
the prosthetic nose debacle of 2005?
Chief, we are definitely onto something.
Last night's robbery fits the pattern
we've seen between criminal activity
and specific teams. We've narrowed
it down to a few suspects.
Three suspects.
Teammates, friends, pen pals.
Solid suspects.
Maybe four.
Possibly five.
- Six could...
- The idea is to have fewer
suspects.
You don't get paid by the suspect.
I see us closing this by tomorrow.
- Tomorrow then.
- Absolutely.
Fine.
But I'm gonna need results
without another incident, metaphysical
or otherwise.
You're all dismissed.
She really unloaded on us.
Thank you
for taking the heat on that one.
That's how it goes
when you're partners.
If I could count the number of times
that Gus has left my cheese in the wind.
- What?
- Nothing. Study on, buddy.
Arteriosclerosis, rosacea, croup.
- Croup?
- You'll have to owe me one.
Or... you can give me
one of these bracelets.
They come in teal?
- Can't do.
- Can't do teal?
Westwood gave it to me.
A roller derby thing.
Think of something else.
You can dial back the "maniac" routine.
Stop pulling rank on me.
- Ordering me around.
- Fine.
And smoothies
are on you until we nab someone.
I want to figure out the next step
by seeing how you work.
I want to get close to your process.
Get some hard evidence.
Yeah. That's a good idea.
Why don't you bring her right
in on your process?
Here's the thing.
Close is good.
Very close is even better.
But not for this.
My process is not a tandem bike,
it's a unicycle.
You belong at practice.
I can see fox.
- You gotta keep an eye on her.
- That's gonna be difficult.
She's always surrounded
by Westwood and Wilde.
Perfect.
Keep an eye on them too.
There.
The lists... from Vick's desk.
They make absolutely
no sense whatsoever.
Why don't you arrange them
in alphabetical order?
That's not the point.
They stole a dvd of spanglish.
- They weren't after the merchandise.
- That's not exactly hard evidence.
- Thank you, professor no help.
- What?
I'm sorry. Did you miss that?
Maybe I should've said MC no help
or Doctor do-nothing because
you're bringing nothing to the table.
I have a test, remember?
No pass, no job.
No job, no driving you around.
Besides, you're doing perfectly fine
with your new partner.
- Who? Jules?
- "Who? Jules?"
Who do you think?
- Don't be jealous.
- I'm not.
Don't be vexed. You're still number one
on my myspace page.
Jules and I are just working
a case together. Nothing more.
What is this green slime on your book?
You come from the kid's choice awards?
This place is filthy.
- Wilde was there.
- What?
Cynthia "speed freak" Wilde
was there at Zilk's
during the break-in.
She uses this green oil
to lubricate her skates.
Looks like she left some behind.
Good clue, buddy.
You have fox with the broken watch and
now wilde. Why don't you call the cops?
According to the tapes,
there were at least three more.
If we don't get them, they're gonna
doing their thing. That...
is the oath of thieves.
That... is the code of the roller girl.
I never thought
I would hear you say that.
Even more than sinkhole sissy feet
flapjack go-go boots?
Juliet isn't answering her phone.
You know, those crab cakes are,
like, three days old or something.
Okay, remember, "maniac",
the key is to just get through the pack.
- Whatever it takes.
- We don't want to injure anyone
- in practice, do we?
- Of course not.
If someone's shoulder has to get
dislocated,
make sure it isn't yours.
Back to it, boss?
- Wait, where is "lethal weapon"?
- Oh, Westwood?
She had to split a second ago,
go visit her mother.
- Let's go kick some ass.
- Cool.
- I'm just gonna grab something.
- Okay, see you on the track.
- You leaving?
- Yeah.
- Everything okay?
- I have to go meet my boyfriend.
He's kinda got car trouble, so...
I have to go.
He's kind of stranded out
on the mesa somewhere.
Okay, all right, make sure
you bring him to the bout tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll try.
See ya later.
I found a couple of hand-held
scanning machines here at the hall.
You feel anything on scanning machines?
Scanning machines?
For making copies.
Copying devices are notoriously
unreliable psychic fetters.
Now, if they were
three-hole punchers, different story.
I'm gonna look around some more,
but I wanted to let you know
Westwood left practice early today.
She gave me some lie
and then she just took off.
I'm getting something now. Street
clothes, green tank top, jeans, belt...
Terrible, terrible belt.
- Do you see her?
- En mi cabesa.
I got a psychic track on her now.
Okay, I gotta go.
Call Lassiter if you find anything out.
Of course.
I'll call Lassiter.
I'm not calling Lassiter.
Follow the bouncing Westwood.
Not too close.
She's gonna see us.
- Dude... is that...
- What?
I think there's a body
in the back of that truck.
It's not a body.
It is! That's a head.
This test has got you all jacked up.
You're not thinking straight.
You're distracted trying to remember
the difference between lermacil
- and hermacil.
- Lermacil is for fever blisters.
- Hermacil is for eczema.
- What about chermacil?
No such thing as chermacil.
Studying.
Sweet fantasy island,
that is a body!
I told you.
Not too close.
Westwood is ditching a body.
That's the break in the case we need.
We need is to call Lassiter
like Juliet said. And back off a little.
- She's gonna see us.
- We're not calling him. You know
how this works. I really have
to explain it to you every single time?
You lost Westwood.
Damn it!
Bingo.
- Let's go.
- I'm not going out there.
Dude, it's only gonna take a second.
You cannot sit here
alone in the dark in a parked car.
- You'll get picked up for Mopery.
- Mopery?
With intent to creep.
Trust me,
it'll kick a big hole in your future.
I guess it wasn't a body.
Well done, Spencer.
I don't know, chief. You want me
to try and get her statement?
Of course, I don't speak mannequin.
Cute.
You might want to hold off on that
because we still have all the
merchandise from the zilk's burglaries.
- Excellent work.
- Thanks, chief.
It's all right.
I accept your apology.
So the burglars
weren't after the merchandise.
- That's right.
- So what were they after?
One, two, three, four, five.
Five, four.
- Four, five.
- What?
I'm seeing four and I'm seeing five.
Lassie, four and five!
- Nine? The number nine?
- No, four times five.
- 20?
- 5 and 20.
- 5 times 20.
- 100.
- Minus 4 times 4 times 5.
- 4 times 4 times 5?
- 80.
- No, 20.
100 minus 80 is 20.
We all have our math facts straight.
Is this going somewhere?
Skater number 20.
She's the one who dumped all this stuff.
That's Rita "lethal weapon" Westwood.
Great, we got one.
We need all of 'em.
Correct.
This is bigger than Westwood.
A lot bigger.
Juliet's close.
Let's get someone on the lookout
for any more dumping sites around town.
We've got to get to Zilk's,
and check something out.
If you say "pants,"
I'm gonna sock you in your Adam's apple.
Sock you in your...
Hey, it's me.
Listen, we got a situation.
- What is it?
- Westwood screwed up again huge.
The cops found everything.
She's gonna talk.
- This is bad.
- Yeah, and it gets worse.
Maniac's fan boy's also here.
- Doing what?
- He's working with the cops.
- Are we compromised?
- I don't know,
but after we handle Westwood,
I think we need to have a talk
with Maniac.
What are we doing here, Shawn?
We know it wasn't the merchandise.
But it was something else.
Let's go.
Dude, I can't believe this.
You lifted your look
right off this mannequin.
On the contrary, Shawn.
Clearly, someone is stealing my look.
Right.
I did see tommy hilfiger creeping
from bush to bush sketching you.
And we're moving.
But your friend can't come.
The thieves were after something
in this room.
Dude, we can't go inside there.
Read the sign.
"Laura noid. Employee of the month."
You know her?
Not that one.
"Employees only."
Gotcha. Be my lookout.
No problem.
I'll just keep it safe from the outside.
It's okay.
It's all right.
My name is Shawn Spencer.
This is my partner...
I can't believe I'm blanking.
I've done this a million times.
- Nice work.
- Office, code blue.
It's okay.
We're not here to rob you.
Your buddy stole the clothes
right off the mannequin.
These are my clothes.
Look, we don't keep the cash back here.
This is the credit department.
We just want to talk to you
about the burglary.
Oh, do you, mannequin man?
Well, why don't you tell that
to my little can of pepper spray?
Tell her!
It's all right.
These guys are with the police.
Why is your friend dressed
like the mannequin?
That mannequin is dressed like me.
Thank you.
- Can we go, shawn?
- Hold up. What were you doing?
Oh, uh, it's friday.
I was shredding
credit card applications.
It's the only fun thing I get to do.
Burglary happened on a thursday.
The day before
they shred the credit applications.
Thanks, guys.
It was good to see you, Stu.
Jules, I'm getting some strong messages.
- Okay, what are they?
- First one's from Keanu Reeves.
He's living in a house
I built on a lake two years in the past.
How will I meet him?
The second is that the thieves were not
after the merchandise.
Well, we already know that, Shawn.
They were using the hand scanners
to steal information
off credit card applications.
They're stealing identies.
So then ransacking the store
was just to throw us off the trail.
Right-o.
A handful of fake credit cards
is worth more than everything
in that entire store times ten.
It's a pretty brilliant plan.
Only slightly less brilliant
than that Youtube video
of the monkey bathing the cat.
We need you to come with us, Maniac.
Right now.
Jules, who is that?
Who's talking?
We gotta go.
So we have three suspects.
Two to go.
- You think they're on to Juliet?
- They might be.
- We're gonna find out pretty quick.
- What do you think they'll do to her?
Westwood gave it to me.
It's a roller derby thing.
They may've done it already.
That's Westwood's truck.
- I can't see anything.
- Look for something to jimmy the lock.
- Thank god.
- Thank god?
- It's a dead person.
- Yeah, but it's not Juliet.
It's still a human being, Shawn.
It's Westwood.
What's the matter with you?
You're saying you'd rather it be someone
that we know and care about?
Fine, next time I see Jules,
I'll tell her you wish she was dead.
I never said
that I wish Juliet was dead.
Lead jammer Mrs. Bash is trapped
in the pack.
Speed freak trying to slash
through pismo's vulnerable inside line.
The trollops are gonna have to do
a 180 in the second half tonight.
Unless Hayseed wanna be
and off-white trash have their way,
it might just happen.
It's down to the wire, friends.
- The roller girls are onto Juliet.
- Which ones?
The bad ones,
and I know who they are.
They're marking their own teammate.
They want to hurt her or worse.
We gotta do something.
Things are heating up out here, people.
I hope you've brought protection.
- What are you doing?
- You've been complaing about me
not being any help here,
and that's about to change.
They're gonna try to make a run for it,
but not before they take juliet down.
- Yes, but this is a terrible idea.
- I can skate, shawn.
I got this.
What are you...
Now it looks like we got
a guest on the track.
You're taking your life
in your hands, pal.
And oh, speed freak goes down!
There's something you don't see
every day.
Oh, man!
Four suspects.
It was identity theft, chief.
They were only after the information off
the credit card applications
the customers fill out.
All of the stores they hit had similar
credit card programs.
They break in, wreak havoc,
and split before the clock runs out.
Just the kind of anarchy
their fans pay for night after night.
I got prints off a key piece of evidence
I found here.
She got 'em when she wasn't busy
kicking ass.
Can I hear something for maniac?
She really brought it, huh?
Am I right?
Who's with me?
- Lassiter, take them away.
- Whoa, whoa, wait.
I'm seeing the fifth suspect.
- She get away?
- no.
Rita "lethal weapon" Westwood.
Unfortunately, you'll find her body in
her pickup truck in the parking lot.
She's the one that botched
the merchandise drop.
She paid dearly for it.
Anything else?
Not really.
Did I mention juliet's
roller derby awesomeness?
Maniac, Maniac, Maniac.
I can't get anything from these people.
They're murders, shawn.
They're going away for life.
I gotta study.
Lassiter, take them away.
All right, ladies.
You two work together well.
I certainly think so.
We're available for more cases,
by the way.
Embezzlement, extortion, espionage.
Pretty much anything
that starts with "e."
Elephant theft.
I'll take that under advisement.
- Elephant theft?
- Oh, yeah.
- People steal elephants?
- Major problem.
Pretty much out of control.
Hey, jules.
What are you doing here?
I'm returning my equipment.
Just hangin', you know?
Chillin'.
I was actually feeling
a little nostalgic.
Remember when we cracked that case here
and the criminals turned out
to be roller derby girls?
Yeah, I remember that.
Gosh, seems like it was just yesterday.
Probably because it was yesterday.
Why are you wearing skates?
Oh, yeah, look at that.
I guess I am.
I don't know.
I guess I just thought it was a shame.
We have this big, beautiful track
and no one to skate on it.
It's also been a while since
I've had a good blister.
This will be a couples skate.
Couples only.
Come on.
- Did you do that on purpose?
- No.
Maybe.
Okay, yes.
Yes, I did.
No hands.
Damn!
- What is it?
- It won't let me log in,
and I have to take my exam by today.
Really?
It's probably because
I just took it for you.
What?
I can't believe you're still using
"chocolate thunder" as your password.
You took my exam?
Little harder than the river raft test.
Way easier than the secret service test.
Any of the questions I didn't know
I just answered "c," right?
Oh, my god.
- Oh, my god.
- Dude, it's done.
Relax.
And you know what?
Nailed it!
Well, almost nailed it.
At the very least,
definitely didn't blow it.
I don't think...
Hey, you're in, okay?
Sadly, you're still
a pharmaceutical rep.
But hey, whatever.
I studied for this test all week
for nothing.
Yes, you did.
But that's the sort of thing
that builds character.
Knowledge is power!
Don't you want to feel powerful?