Dad, dad!
- Dad, dad, dad!
- Wait, whoa.
Slow down. Slow down. Fire.
Dad, you'll never believe it.
I know what I wanna be when I grow up.
A fireman!
I never woulda guessed.
What exactly brought this on?
Fireman Paul.
He came to our school.
He is so totally rad.
Fireman Paul?
Did he happen to be sober?
Shawn, come here.
Listen to me.
You...
you do not wanna be a fireman.
What? Why not?
Because you wanna be a cop.
What do you think I've been
teaching you all these years?
But being a fireman is the coolest.
Being a fireman is not
cooler than being a cop.
Well, they have cooler uniforms,
Cooler trucks, and cooler sirens.
They even get to carry axes!
Axes? I get to carry a gun.
A real gun, with real bullets.
I get to shoot bad guys.
I'm like dirty harry.
Can you even name a famous fireman?
Smokey the bear?
First of all, Smokey the
bear is not a fireman.
Number two, he's not real.
Number three, he's a bear.
He takes his poops in the woods.
Is that what you want?
Fireman Paul said you'd say that.
What is going on in there?
She never closes her blinds.
You know I don't like
being out of the loop.
Shawn, what're you doing?
Jules.
How 'bout an update on
this blind situation?
Oh, just some case with the
fire department or something.
Fire department? Did you hear that?
Of course I did. I'm standing
2 1/2 feet away from her.
So what's the scoop?
Well, apparently some building
burned down last week on Benedetto
Under suspicious circumstances
and they're looking for backup.
Sorry, guys. I gotta go.
Dude, that's us. We're backup.
What?
- I strongly believe--
- Excuse us.
We're looking for the fireman.
He's probably wearing a
yellow or red hard hat,
Maybe carrying an axe,
possibly a large bucket of sand.
And a Dalmatian.
Discounting your interruption
to a closed-door meeting,
Miss Conrad is the
city's arson inspector.
- Arson.
- Miss.
Hello.
- Arson. That's fire?
- Yes
Shawn Spencer,
Head psychic, SBPD.
I'm available.
For cases as well.
Um, I'm not gonna do that.
I understand.
Obsessive-compulsive.
If you're finished, Mr. Spencer,
We'd like to proceed
with our meeting, so...
ah, how rude of me.
I'd like to look at the
criminal activity for that area.
- I believe her.
- What?
I'm sensing that lassie
Is skeptical that this is arson.
Of course I'm skeptical,
she's an arson investigator,
They always want it to be
arson. Keeps their job viable.
Can I go now?
All I need is access to some of
your files for the last few years.
- I can do that for you.
- What?
Come on, chief. I know
where the file room is.
Besides, when you get down
there, things can get tricky,
Some of those drawers stick.
Who gave you access to the file room?
Irrelevant and immaterial.
Chief, you're not gonna
let him do that thing
Where he only uses
courtroom jargon, are you?
Mr. Spencer--
He is making a mockery of these
proceedings. All I'm saying is that...
She is making a very
compelling argument.
You're an idiot.
That's less compelling. Move to strike.
- Please remove him.
- Good.
Sidebar, miss Conrad.
I think I can help you.
You have no idea why I'm here.
I'm sensing something
happened on Benedetto street
And you're not getting the support
you want from your department,
And you're looking for a
little outside assistance.
That's actually spot-on.
Yes, I know.
Chief, I believe we have a match
Made in heaven.
Crap.
This place is like, completely burned.
It's called a fire, Shawn.
And it's all evidence,
so don't touch anything.
All right.
I'll try to speak slowly.
Let's review.
I believe the fire started
in this general area,
And spread in this direction.
Conrad.
What're you doing here?
Now you're dragging the cops down here?
And this is...
Army Johnson,
Fire Prevention Bureau.
And your supervisor, in case you forgot.
- Well, if this is arson, then--
- Look. At the bureau,
We have a policy of
supporting our rookies.
Rookies?
So I gave you a lot of
latitude on this case.
I read your report, and I
surveyed the scene myself.
It looks like an accidental
fire to me, not malicious arson.
I respectfully disagree.
Honey,
The last time this city had an arsonist
Was so long ago I was
still on the big, red truck.
Besides, this building
had no fire insurance.
So no one profits.
A firebug doesn't need a motive.
Yeah, enough.
Just finish your report.
Now I'm late for my hot yoga class.
I'm teaching this year.
An accident?
Is there something we're missing, here?
Well, we did find some empty
liquor bottles and cigarette butts
Around the fire's
point of origin, but--
And we've had several reports
of teenagers looking
for places to party.
I think lassie's on to something.
Have we ruled out teenagers
who meet in abandoned buildings
And make banas foster?
It is not teenagers.
One of the firemen remembers smelling
A distinct sweet odor
while putting out the fire,
And that is a sign of a
stronger accelerant than alcohol.
And if this is a firebug,
He is just getting started.
Dude.
That wall over there
doesn't have any insulation.
I think that's an external wall.
Look, if no one from your
department is on board,
I'm on board!
Gus, what's happening to me?
What the hell are you doing?
There's something off
with this wall right here.
I can feel it.
- Oh, my god.
- What the...
did not see that coming.
Miss Conrad, this wasn't just arson.
It was murder.
wWw.Subs-Team.Tv
presents...
In between the lines
there's a lot of obscurity
I'm not inclined to resign to maturity
If it's all right, then you're all wrong
But why bounce around
to the same damn song
You'd rather run when you can't crawl
I know you know that
I'm not telling the truth
I know you know they
just don't have any proof
Embrace the deception, learn how to bend
Your worst inhibitions tend
to psych you out in the end.
Psych - S03E12
Earth, Wind and… Wait for It.
Synch by: Safes.
I'm sensing that this man...
is it a man?
I don't-- I don't
know what it is.
Yes, based on the pelvic girdle.
Burned to death. Hell of a way to go.
He didn't burn to death. M.E.
Pulled a .22 slug out of his sternum.
He was shot, then burned?
It's sad, but that's what they
do to guys who wear girdles.
This man is the reason the fire was set.
According to the M.E.'s
preliminary report,
The bullet entered the body
at a downward trajectory,
Based on bone fragments
containing lead residue.
See, so from behind and
downward means our shooter
Dropped him down on his knees,
Popped him execution style. Bang.
You trim that fingernail,
Ming the merciless.
Then the killer torched the building
to make the body unidentifiable.
Or to remove any trace of
his own fingerprints or DNA.
We couldn't even pull a print
off the bullet. Smart move.
In case you missed it, detective,
this is my "I told you so" face.
Which is kind of hard
to distinguish from your
"I thought this was gonna be
a new episode of law and order
But turns out it's a repeat" face.
A dead body changes things.
That's his e-mail signature.
So, we're on board. And because it's
a homicide, it's our investigation.
No, it's arson. And I've already
briefed Army on all of this.
He says it's my case, I'm
on point, you report to me.
Look, when we find our murder,
you'll find your arsonist.
No, when I find my arsonist,
I'll find your murderer.
- No.
- Guys, please.
Can't we come up with a term that
covers both killer and arsonist?
How about arsassin?
The skeleton had trace
amounts of methylbenzene
the primary component of TNT.
You can get it at any hardware
store, and it has a sweet odor.
All right, fine. But no one
Outside this room can know
we recovered a skeleton.
And make sure the city treats
the site like an accident,
- All right? I want our killer--
- Arsassin!
- Or karsonist.
- Arsassin.
I want the killer to feel safe,
I want him to think
that his plan worked.
Secondly,
The key to solving this case is
to figure out who this guy was.
Come here often?
You know, you could afford
to slow down a little.
You walk any faster, you're
gonna travel through time.
So what's our next move?
Well, I assume we're
gonna team up, right?
Travel cross-country solving mysteries,
Maybe set up shop on
the side of the road,
Form a bluegrass trio.
Look. I appreciate you guys getting
the cops to take this seriously,
But you don't have a lot
of experience with this,
So I prefer to handle point alone.
You know,
Sun Tzu says that teamwork
can be very sensual--
I'll e-mail you the rest!
I'd go after her if she wasn't
walking at cougar speeds.
Right. So what're we
doing? Are we really done?
Gus, don't be William
Zabka from back to school.
We need to get in with the
firemen that put out the fire.
Shotgun on fire pole.
You can't call shotgun on a fire pole.
And why them?
I think we're looking for a fireman.
Someone who knows fires
someone who knows the system.
They started the fire somewhere else,
Then moved the flames
towards the victim.
Because the first thing an
arson inspector looks for
Is a point of origin.
Okay.
How in the world do you know all that?
I rode the back draft ride at
universal studios like 74 times.
Shawn, you can't base a
whole theory on a movie.
There's a movie?
Now, when we get in here, don't do that
thing you used to do when we were kids.
Hi, fireman.
Help you?
Shawn Spencer.
Hunting an arsonist.
Step Anthony, Wally Ali.
Cat stuck in a tree.
Conrad told me about you. The psycho.
Psychic.
But before we get down to business,
Is fireman Paul around?
We heard he used to work
outta here back in the day.
We just wanna say hello. He came
to our school when we were kids.
No, we're sure he'd rember us.
Gus accidentally peed on
him, and I gave him impetigo.
Over here.
Died fighting the Renkel fires of '98.
Set by a bunch of vandals.
So you think it's arson, too.
You been canoodling with Conrad?
Is Conrad a canoodler?
Did she say anything about me?
Can I get her note through you?
I'm not sure I like random
people interrogating my men,
Especially based on psychic hokum.
Hokum?
Well, that "hokum" found traces
of methylbenzene at the scene.
- Really?
- Yeah, so
My colleague would like to try and
glean more "hokum" from your men.
Listen, it's been a long day,
my shift is over. Manetti!
Manetti's my right-hand man.
These guys are here about the
fire. Deal with it, would ya?
So. You were the guys who
put out the fire a week ago?
That was us.
Thanks to Manetti, here.
Well, that's a given.
You don't look old
enough to operate a hose.
We doused that fire in 33 minutes.
Really?
You know, domino's can still
get you a pizza in under 30.
That might be more impressive.
Yeah? Well, you should've seen how fast
I booked the perps back in my cop days.
Wow, well we're police-affiliated too,
So can we ask you a few questions?
We don't have time.
Starting traing drills.
Perfect. We're supposed
to do them with you.
Really?
Who told you that?
Yeah, it sounded weird
to us too, but it's
Imperative that we get this
information as soon as possible,
It's a headquarters thing.
Look, between you and me,
There's nothing we'd rather do less,
So why don't you just grab us a couple of
these costumes and we'll get it over with.
You mean uniforms.
I've heard it both ways.
Can I ring the bell?
Move! Move!
Come on! Come on! Get moving downhill!
This way! You're going
down hill! Move it, move it!
So how many people did
you pull out of the fire?
None! Building was empty.
Keep moving! Move it!
Move it! Go, go, go!
Did you notice anything weird about
the fire besides the smell? Oh!
Lotta open spaces. No furniture
cluttering up the joint.
Hey! This isn't a picnic!
Move! Go, go, go, go!
Nope, I didn't see anyone
suspicious in the crowd.
I questioned him already, Shawn.
Dude, he was doing the pole.
Did anyone miss their shift that night?
No.
No one wants to lose out on the O.T.
Anybody here with a criminal record?
Shh! No talking. It kills the illusion.
How much more of this do I have to take?
Man, in order for him
to stay certified in CPR.
He has to practice on a live person.
He's gonna use a tongue guard
when he gives you mouth-to-mouth
- So it's not even really like kissing.
- What?
If you find yourself becoming
aroused, don't beat yourself up.
You must be outta your damn mind.
Everybody move it!
This isn't part of the drill, let's go!
No, Shawn.
The arsonist might still be
there. And we're already geared up.
They won't even know
I'm driving the truck!
We should stay here. Get some gelato,
And read the fire department's reports
from the comfort of
our not-on-fire office.
Dude, if we go,
You can drive behind
a speeding fire truck.
All right. Repeat after me:
We are not going into
a burning building.
We are not-not going
into a burning building.
Break!
Hey!
Thought you said your shift was over.
I heard about it on my scanner.
What is this, Halloween?
Why, you got candy?
I'll take some good & plenty.
Or good & fruity.
How bad is it in there?
I haven't been inside. I'm
patrolling the scene from out here.
So just try to stay
outta the way, all right?
This is command. First floor is secure.
I'm sending more men to the
second floor. Alpha side over.
No, Shawn, we're not going into
a burning building. You promised.
- Actually, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
The first floor is secure.
Those things flare back up all the time.
And you know how fire's attracted to me.
Can you blame it?
Man, look at you.
Blair Underwood can't
touch you right now.
Blair Underwood never
played a fireman, either.
Exactly. Come on. I
need the super sniffer.
Shawn!
This is not a good idea, Shawn.
Dammit.
I-I don't know.
Maybe we
should try, uh--
Gus, where are you?
Down here!
The key is to stay underneath the smoke!
Would you get up?
Start sniffing!
There's something sweet in the air!
I need to see what the ceiling
looked like before it was scorched!
Anything else?
Nope.
We're good.
In all the years of fighting fires,
That was the dumbest
thing I have ever seen!
If I was still a cop,
I'd put you both in jail!
I definitely smelled something.
This fire was not an accident.
I'll do you one better.
The chief had flakes of the
unburned ceiling in his hair.
He was in there before the fire started.
We've found our arsonurder.
What?
Firearsmen.
Senor pantalones de fuego?
Your psychic hunch was right, Shawn.
This body was found in a wall
space at the site of the fire.
Yes.
I could sense that
the fires were related,
And since the first one
was set to cover up murder--
There might be a body
at the second fire too.
Nice work.
I'm sorry?
It was either "nice work" or "ice fork,"
But I couldn't tell which.
According to the M.E.’s report,
There's a unique purple rubber
melted in between the victim's toes.
- Unique how?
- It has real specks of gold in it.
They think it came from
the victim's sneakers.
Purple and gold specks.
That's jet jaguars.
Gus owned them.
They're the ugliest and most
uncomfortable sneakers known to man.
I had a pair. They weren't that bad.
They were proven to cause polio.
I have elongated metatarsals
and inverted phalanges, Spencer,
I have to wear whatever fits.
Well then you know they
were only sold in '98,
And then discontinued immediately.
The victim was wearing
ten-year-old sneakers?
Who holds onto tennis
shoes for that long?
Especially painful purple and gold ones?
If this man was wearing them
at the time of his death,
Then he was definitely killed in '98,
Possibly by the fashion mafia.
Ten years ago, that makes no sense.
Why would someone hang
onto a body for a decade
And then burn it to a crisp?
Unless...
the bodies have been
there the whole time.
Just rotting for ten
years? That's your theory?
Actually, come to think of it,
both buildings were built in '98.
An empty construction site is
a good place to kill someone,
And it'd be easy to slip
a body behind the drywall.
What...
you're sure you're not a germaphobe.
All right, let's just confirm the
sneaker thing, and if Spencer’s right,
Let's get a list of all the buildings
that were built ten years ago.
What?
You can just get a list
of that kind of stuff?
I'd like a list of all
available Zoltar machines.
For a little 14-year-old
friend of mine.
Thanks, Jules.
So, miss Conrad.
Anything else I should
know about the second fire?
Just that the
firefighters caught a break
Because there wasn't sufficient
ventilation on the top floor.
Without the oxygen, the men had
no trouble putting out the fire.
- Yeah, that was us.
- Thanks to Manetti, here.
We doused that fire in 33 minutes.
So both fires went
out relatively easily.
I guess, yeah.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
I will bet every penny
I have that I'm not.
The arsonist made the
fires easy to put out.
Have you at all considered
that this is an inside job?
Well, this building wasn't insured
either. The owners don't get anything.
Inside your department.
A firefighter?
What're you doing?
Do you see a bruise on my
chest from all that CPR?
All I see is chocolate with hair on it.
You know the rules, Shawn.
No sliding down the
pole while I'm not here.
But you are here. You're right here.
You know what I mean,
Especially when I'm stuck
tailing fire chief Dan all day.
And they don't even have
a Dalmatian here, Shawn.
Would you stop with
the Dalmatians already?
I'm just saying it'd be nice to
see one in his natural habitat.
They're not indigenous
to firehouses, Gus.
Did you find anything out or not?
Well, I hid in a corner while
he got a picture framed  of him,
- John Denver, and the Muppets.
- Muppets?
- Hey, Gonzo's was the shot, boy.
- What?
Sounds productive.
Then I just had to stand
around while he spent an hour
Figuring out what type
of rotiller to buy.
Well, it's not an easy
decision, Gus. After all,
It's harvest season, pa.
Jeb can't work the plow.
You know he ain't been right since
he come down with the consumption.
Will you stop, Shawn?
It did get interesting.
He's our guy, and I know it.
He was on his cell phone constantly.
And I think I heard him
ask about the accelerant.
After that,
He came rushing back here in a panic.
Dude. It's sabotage.
He's making it harder for
the men to put out the fires.
We gotta stop him.
He's heading to the all-purpose room.
There's only one exit to that room.
Here's the plan: we corner, we confront.
He confesses?
We get samosas.
Bet.
Dude, is that really necessary?
I don't play with killers, Shawn.
Hello, children.
Yes!
Field trip to the old fire station.
What're you two doing?
We are here to help with the lesson.
Clearly.
So, uh, kiddies,
Always rember to put out your cigarettes
When you're finished smoking them.
Uh--
Excuse me?
Uh, I mean,
Don't smoke.
Uh, in bed.
Or in restaurants.
Or in...
- caves?
- No smoking.
Absolutely no smoking.
And don't listen to anyone
who says that a pipe is cool,
Because I'm telling you, it is not.
Get out. Get out. Get out!
Well, that was a waste of time.
Or was it?
What is that?
I accidentally mixed up fire
chief Dan’s phone with mine.
They're similar shapes, and my
hand was in his jacket pocket.
You stole his phone?
He was throwing
us out--
Gus, I plead the third.
The third amendment is no soldier
can live in your house
against your will.
- You mean the fifth.
- I've heard it both ways.
What other ways have you heard it?
Just look at this.
Five calls in a row to hardware
stores all over the city.
Where one might go to buy methylbenzene.
That's what I'm talking about.
Fire chief Dan?
Honestly?
That's why you brought me
down to this death trap?
Death trap?
This office is in violation of almost
every fire safety code on the books.
Not to contradict, but
We are 100% up to code.
I don't walk into a
building unless it's safe.
Much less work in one.
Your smoke detector is a paper
bowl with an M&M stuck to it.
Shawn, where's the Ryerson smoke
detector I bought for the office?
Oh, that thing? It kept
beeping during seance week.
Where is it now?
Charleston chew?
Charleston chew.
You also have an overloaded socket,
and a hotplate on the ground.
I like soup. I won't apologize for that.
It's next to a stack of old newspapers.
I also like to read while I eat.
Can you please just tell
me why you think it's Dan?
Well, it's not like I stole
his cell phone or anything.
'Cause I mean I don't
do that sort of thing.
Although I'm sensing someone
did, I'll solve that later.
No, this, this was just deeply-rooted
Psychic vibage.
I know it's hard to believe.
No. Actually it's not.
It kinda makes sense.
He never thought it was arson,
And he hated it when
I questioned his men.
What did the cops say?
We haven't told them.
We thought you'd like to make the bust.
After all, this is your case.
That--
I mean, to
say that--
I mean, that-- That
you would think of me.
That-- You
would do that.
This seems like a great
opportunity for a hug. C'mere.
No?
- Rotator cuff.
- Right.
There's been another fire.
With another body?
Forensics is on the way.
Another body. You were right.
As a courtesy, I want
to let you know my office
Is going to be bringing in
Dan Trombly for questioning.
- The fire chief?
- Correct.
That could be a problem.
Why?
Because...
that skeleton wasn't
the only body we found.
Lift that, please.
It says here that the fire
chief died of asphyxiation.
Smoke inhalation.
Oh, I'm getting something.
How much more of this
do I have to endure?
Do you see the bruise on
my chest from all that CPR?
There was someone else there. They
tried to give him CPR before he died.
Maybe someone who knew him.
Of course they knew him. It's
like practically kissing him.
What the hell was the fire chief
doing there in the first place?
I mean, I don't think
he started the fire.
He wasn't wearing any protective gear,
There weren't any traces
of accelerants on him.
We got a break.
The latest skeleton is still
too burned to get an I.D.,
But our killer didn't know that
our victim had an iced in his body.
Ew. They make those for men?
It's like a pacemaker.
Tracked the serial number back
to central coast components
Who sold it to Saint Mary's
Who implanted it into
our victim 12 years ago.
Okay, what do we know about our victim?
Wait, our skeleton was a criminal?
That's right. His name
is Steven J. Renkel.
As in the kid from Family Matters.
- No.
- As in the Renkel fires of '98.
- Yes.
- Guys, bring it in.
So our victim is a firestarter himself?
Yeah, they were a bunch of vandals who
liked going around and starting fires.
These are Renkel's
only known accomplices.
Whoa.
Oh, I'm getting something.
The second victim is in
one of those pictures.
What? How do you know that?
He's telling me he was murdered,
He's saying it poorly 'cause
he speaks with a whisth-le.
A whithle, like thith,
he thpeakth like thith.
Which would be endearing on an
eight-year-old, maybe Terry Thomas,
Or the original
supermodel Lauren Hutton.
But this, this just
screams for adult braces.
Any form of simple orthodontia,
really, it's not that expensive.
You're saying it's the guy
who has the gap in his teeth?
Don't say "gap."
He prefers "tooth
alley," but yeth, it ith.
I remember these guys.
They all disappeared
around the same time.
We figured they'd just skipped town.
That's it!
The third victim is up there as well.
He's not speaking because he's afraid
you'll criticize his appearance,
Just like you did with tooth gap boy.
Look, now you got me doing it.
Someone must've hunted them down
and killed them ten years ago.
And now they're burning
off the evidence.
It's a long time to
wait to clean up a mess.
You should see how long it takes
Gus to clean his cereal bowl.
Only one guy in the crew
Has been a suspect
in other arsons since the Renkel fire.
And that's Bodie Lambert.
All right, so why is Bodie the
only one we're still hearing from?
Maybe he turned on his partners.
Happens all the time.
This could be our killer.
Furder.
What?
Fire murderer.
Furder.
Put a bolo on him, asap.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
you're gonna issue these guys bolo ties?
It stands for "be on the lookout."
What are you doing? Army will kill you
if he sees you messing with this stuff.
Well, why are we here?
The cops are following the bodies.
I thought we'd take a different avenue.
The buildings.
What do we know?
They're all commercial and industrial.
And...
they were all built in the same year.
After the Renkel fire.
Correct.
Lotta open spaces. No furniture
cluttering up the joint.
Also.
They seemed to be abandoned.
Yet none of them are for sale.
Why would three different owners
Leave valuable real estate
like that sitting around empty?
What can I do for you guys?
We need to see your files on
the three burned buildings.
Sure, just fill out
requisition form ig88,
You can get 'em upstairs.
Army, that will take
forever. We really need to s--
Paperwork is paperwork. It's
the basis for civilization.
Just fill out the forms, I'll
give you everything you need.
Fire alarm.
We'd better evacuate.
All right, everybody outta
here. I gotta go deal with this.
Good thing we had a plan b ready.
You smell like a peach meadow.
That's the incense I used to
set off the smoke detector.
You didn't just pull the fire
alarm? It's right there on the wall.
Uh, that's a crime, Shawn.
I remain not culpable.
I didn't set off the
detector. The smoke did.
Who burned the incense?
I plead the fifth.
Element, dimension, beatle?
You can't plead "Billy Preston."
All right, what're we doing?
Bring up the burnt buildings.
Okay.
Here we are.
Dude.
All these buildings
have "SR" next to 'em.
That stands for "seismic retrofit."
It applies to any building built in '98.
Looks like all the safety codes
were just changed last week.
Right before the first fire.
That's why they're all empty.
They're no longer
considered earthquake safe.
They're gonna open up the
walls to bring them up to code.
Dude, that's it. That's what
started this whole thing.
The killer realized that the
bodies he stashed in those buildings
Ten years ago are gonna be discovered,
and now he's torching the evidence.
There's, like, 20 buildings
scheduled to be retrofitted.
Lemme print out the list.
Well, step it up.
We still have a few minutes before
they let anybody back in the building.
Dude, trust me.
You wanna hurry.
You coulda pulled me outta there.
Dude, I gave you two full warnings.
My underwear's soaked.
- Just like old times.
- Kiss my--
Guys.
One of those buildings is gonna
be targeted next by the arsonist.
Are you sure?
I'm al b. Sure watching Diane
Schuur apply sure roll-on.
While viewing the sure thing.
That's pretty sure.
It's all-day sure.
You are a strange person,
but extremely effective.
See? A little teamwork
isn't the worst thing.
Psychically, I could sense
That there was information in
that office that we need, so, uh,
We'll go check with the cops
while you scope those out.
Carpal tunnel.
Hey!
That's fair.
Hey.
We got a hit on that bolo.
Sheriff in Barstow found Bodie Lambert
Holed up in a motel 6
under one of his aliases.
Excellent.
Dobson!
Get a hold of Barstow pd, tell
'em not to make a move without us.
He is mine.
Police!
Clear.
O’Hara, you got anything?
Nothing here. All clear.
Do these things come in different sizes?
Because my movement is very constricted.
I feel like it's creating
all the wrong lines.
Maybe if they were v-necks, or lapels.
Or epaulets.
- What're they doing here?
- I may have given them a heads-up.
It wasn't exactly an invitation.
Well, he must've bolted out the
window. He's not gonna get far.
Aerial two, you got
a twenty on the perp?
- You called in air support for this?
- Of course I did.
'Scuse me.
If I may.
- What're you doing?
- Uh, you might wanna stand back.
Freeze!
Put your hands behind your back.
He's not talking.
I sense that he's superstitious.
He might talk to someone
from a higher ethereal plane.
May I have a shot?
Knock yourself out.
Gimme a second. I have to go outside
and get something off the ground.
Hey.
Shawn Spencer.
Psychic interrogator.
Maybe you remember me from
when I apprehended you?
Remember back then?
No? That's okay.
I got everything I need.
Have fun in prison. Word to the wise:
Don't drop the bar of soap.
Oh, please. Don't try
that routine on me.
No, literally, man. Don't drop the soap.
There's so much
bacteria on those floors.
I'm pretty sure they only
issue one bar a month, so...
why are you eating that?
Raw leaves is what the earth
mother allows me to eat.
It banishes all negative entities.
What, are you a fairy?
Hardly. I've seen little
darlings like, 11 times.
But I am a male wiccan.
You're not wiccan.
I'm level eight, jack.
I'd be level nine if it wasn't
for my seasonal pollen allergies.
What's your coven?
Say what?
What's your passphrase?
I don't know you, man.
Same time. One, two, three.
- Gardnerian.
- Knight rider.
Wait, what?
Gardner...rarian.
Exactly what you said, man.
It is so dope
To connect with other weirdos.
But right here, man, you and me?
We understand each other.
All that fairy stuff aside,
I dig you, Bodie.
I...dig...Bodie.
Now, I only got a minute before
the cops come in and haul you out,
So I'm gonna level with you.
The earth force mother is
pretty P.O.'Ed at you, man.
Me?
You're crazy. I didn't do anything.
She sent me here to stop you.
How do you think I found
you in that ceiling, bro?
Luck? No.
I got a message.
Why is the earth spirit after me?
She knows you lit those fires, bro.
We found the crewmates you
murdered in the buildings.
I didn't kill nobody, brother.
It must've been that guy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait,
wait, wait, what guy?
Ten years ago,
Somebody started hunting us down.
Someone grabbed me outta my car.
Took me to some construction site.
Made me get on my knees.
Told me I had to pay for
killing those two firemen.
Then he pulls the trigger.
Nothing happens.
I get the hell outta there.
I haven't been to Santa
Barbara since that night.
I found Wicca.
And reformed.
Where'd this mystery man take you, bro?
Like, an address or something?
Had a bag over my head most of the time.
But that night is burned in my mind.
I was about to die,
And all I remember hearing is birds.
Lots of them.
Sounded like hundreds.
Birds.
Yeah. Chirping.
Wicca out, brotha.
Shawn, I still can't believe
the police thought
your bird-chirping clue was too vague.
Well, they're still trying to figure
out what building Bodie was taken to.
Hey.
Well, at least Bodie told
us the killer's motives.
Someone is avenging the deaths of the
firemen killed during the Renkel fires.
Maybe it is a firefighter.
I warned you, Shawn.
Firefighters are trouble.
I did everything in my power
to keep you off the pole.
And you succeeded, dad,
in every conceivable way.
But, since our bad guy
was targeting criminals,
Rogue cop is now added to the list.
Look, we have all the
potential arson targets.
Since our killer scouted
one out for Bodie,
He may have still used
them for other victims.
And all you got going
on is your bird chirping.
Wait a minute.
What about Mrs. Mugglesworth?
- My cockatoo when I was eight?
- Yeah.
Wow. I haven't thought
about her in years.
Remember when she died, your
parents fed you some story
About taking her somewhere?
The bird sanctuary.
But she's not dead. She's still there,
Living amongst other
relinquished avians.
Gus, have you seen her since
your parents took her there?
Of course not.
She had a rare bird disease
Where she would lose her feathers
if anyone ever looked at her.
So she has to be kept in
a special mirrored cage.
What?
Gus, your parents lied to you.
We do it sometimes to protect our kids.
Your bird bit the big one. Sorry, pal.
Yeah, not all pets can go live on a
special wheat farm like my rabbits.
That's right, son.
Where is this bird sanctuary?
Third street and d.
- Third and d.
- Yeah.
Really?
Dude, hundreds of birds chirping.
That never occurred to you till now?
Leaving Mrs. Mugglesworth
was a painful memory, Shawn.
I blocked it out until 12 seconds ago.
Guys, guys, guys. The Daedalus building.
It's right there. Right in that area.
Well when is it schedded
to be retrofitted?
Tomorrow.
Well that means your pyromaniac
is gonna get to work today.
Shawn, we told Morgan to
check all these buildings.
I gotta call her. Tell her
not to go in without backup.
Dammit, I still can't
get a hold of Morgan.
I got a bad feeling about this.
You call Lassiter and
the fire department?
They're on their way.
Morgan!
Army Johnson?
Stay where you are.
Don't make a move.
Dude. Start talking.
Stall him till everybody gets here.
Don't let him toss that flame.
I know you killed those criminals.
But I know why.
Honey, the last time
this city had an arsonist
Was so long ago, I was
still on the big red truck.
Because
Back in the day, you were a fireman.
And those vandals set fires that took
the lives of two of your colleagues.
Died fighting the Renkel fires of '98.
Set by a bunch of vandals.
I served side-by-side with
those firemen for years.
They had families.
You're right. They did.
So you left the department.
You took a job
Inspecting buildings
for code violations.
And you discovered...
those are pretty good
places to hide a body.
So you stalked and killed your victims,
You covered them with lye,
And then plugged them into walls.
But your old buddy the
fire chief figured you out.
Made a few calls.
Five calls in a row to hardware
stores all over the city.
Affirmed that it was you
that bought the accelerant...
then finally,
He caught you in the act.
Army, what are you doing?
Don't do it! Don't do it!
But it was too late, wasn't it?
Always the fireman,
he tried to put it out.
You even tried to save his life.
Come on, Danny.
It wasn't my fault.
Danny wasn't supposed to be there.
What about us?
What about your arson inspector?
We didn't do anything.
Do we deserve to die?
I don't...
- no.
- No.
But--
But I can't live with this anymore.
No.
Gus!
Get Morgan, get Morgan!
This is a mess. Where's Shawn?
His car's over there.
I can see somebody coming out.
You guys okay?
What the hell happened?
What is Army Johnson doing here?
Army
tr--
He is the--
He is--
He's the bad guy.
Really?
Well, look at that.
Got you doing the grunt work, huh?
Well, all the new
volunteers have to do it.
- How's it going so far?
- I'm pretty much a hero to the newbies.
I mean, I've already been in two fires,
Carried a man out, stopped an arsonist.
Yes, you have.
Well, I just wanted to drop something
by before I visit Morgan in the hospital.
- What's that?
- Meet...
your new firedog.
Lady Godiva.
That's a boy, Shawn.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
Now I've already cleared
it with the new fire chief.
You just gotta walk him, feed him,
clean up after him and whatnot.
He needs eye drops at
2:00, ear drops at 3:00,
And he may or may not have mange.
You're not leaving that thing
here. I'm not taking care of him.
Gus, if you don't take him,
Cruella will turn him into earmuffs.
Good-bye, lady g.
Shawn!
Did you paint these spots on?
www.tvsubtitles.net