What are you doing?
Just playin'...
Board grass.
Let me see what's behind your back.
Tap shoes?
Are you kidding me?
I like tap dancing.
In fact, I'm pretty good at it.
When people pick on me,
I just pull out that tap board
and show 'em who's bad.
All your permanent teeth are in.
You're playing for keeps now.
You should try it.
It's cool.
- All right, what have we got?
- Female victim.
Looks like she was trapped
inside her vehicle and drowned.
Must have been horrible.
O'Hara, maybe I should handle this one.
Until you get your sea legs back.
I am fine. I want to help.
Take notes.
Tall coffee, black.
I'm off the cream and sugar.
I'm sorry, O'Hara.
I'm pulling rank on this one.
There will be plenty of other females
who die horrific deaths,
and you can investigate
all of them when you're ready.
Get yourself something too.
I'll get the next one!
Hope she doesn't remember that.
I'm still covering a butt-load of cases
I took on while O'Hara was on vacation.
She was on stress leave.
Tomato, tomahto.
Until she's ready for duty again,
I need an extra set of hands.
- So pad up.
- Copy.
Keep your pie hole shut
until I assess my crime scene.
Nothing shuts my pie hole but pie.
Come on.
We're gonna have to get close enough
to that body to get a reading.
Why do you need to get
a reading off a soggy corpse?
Why can't you just
point at it from here?
Or touch the car instead?
Why don't you read off of that bird?
This vehicle matches the description
of the one our missing person
was last seen in.
- Copy.
- Stop saying copy.
Roger.
Victim is identified as...
Desiree Blake.
Rained last night, right?
She took this curb too fast,
lost control,
went down the embankment,
drowned in the car.
Put time of death as sometime
yesterday on the 12th.
She wasn't in the car alone.
We're on.
I'm afraid we don't have
an accidental drowning here.
Our Desiree Blake was murdered.
You are so predictable.
As predictable as your next date
ending with the words,
"I hope this never happens
to someone else"?
Stop wasting my time.
You want in.
You make your case to your father
who's done nothing but say no to you
ever since he is here...
Thank God.
I'd be lying if I said I like having
to ask my dad for case assignments.
I'd also be lying if I said
Val Kilmer still looks like Val Kilmer.
- I still have hope.
- Me too.
We gotta convince Lassie
to put us on this case.
You have to do that.
I don't have time.
My new tap class
starts in half an hour.
You're really taking... tap?
That wasn't just a bit
we were doing?
I'm doing something for myself,
getting back to things I love.
For a brief period in '93,
I was known
as DJ Cold Cuts.
Now, do you see me
dusting off my turntables
and playing the curves downtown?
The curves burnt down last year.
- No wonder they won't return my calls.
- I'll see you after class.
May I have a word?
Am I to understand
you're taking a... tap class?
Is it court-ordered?
Will it make you faster?
Are you investigating
some sort of dancing drug ring?
Then, why on earth
would a grown man do such a thing?
Look, it's something
I've been doing since I was a child,
and I don't care whether
you or Shawn don't get it.
All right, let's try that
one more time.
Some of your timing
was a little off.
Not necessary, Mr. Guster.
I can see everyone in the mirror.
- Nice moves, by the way.
- Thanks, I been tapping since...
Excuse me.
Let me guess. They wanna move me
to the advanced class?
There's a coworker
waiting for you in the hall.
I'm so sorry about this.
What are you doin' here?
I thought you were working on your case.
I gotta wait for
the science monkeys in forensics
to analyze the evidence
from the scene first.
I know this is a little weird,
I can't believe I'm here myself but...
Long story short,
ever since the divorce,
my therapist has advised me
to step out of my comfort zone
and try new things...
And since I don't like books
that aren't about military strategy
nor do I care
for the company of women,
I thought I'd see if you can
get me into your little class here.
If you're doing it,
how hard could it be.
You realize you're insulting me
and asking me for a favor.
Give me a break. My insurance
only covered four therapy sessions.
The kind of tap that I do
is not something you can just jump into
without experience.
I'll have them send over the transcripts
from walking and chewing gum school.
Can you get me in the class or not?
I don't have much time.
- I'll see what I can do.
- You're a peach.
Cramp! Got a cramp!
All right, hold on.
You were...
It's a wrap for today, everyone.
Great work.
Remember... Keep it in the pocket.
I'll see you all next time,
all right?
It's great.
You okay?
This is... awesome.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about it. Everyone has
a hard time the first time around.
It wasn't hard.
It was just a waste of time.
I hope my therapist
doesn't make me come back.
- Wait... you're quitting?
- No, I'm not quitting.
- I'm simply choosing not to continue.
- Realize how hard it was.
I didn't want to make you quit.
Especially because I believe
that people who carry guns
should do what their therapists say.
Let's try it again.
Come on.
- It's ridiculous.
- It'll be something simple.
All right, let's try a cramp roll.
Ready?
- That's it?
- That's it.
- Just like that.
- Really?
I'm actually starting to get it.
There might be something
to this pansy stuff after all.
I don't know if pansy's
the right word.
The alternative seemed a little offense,
so I thought I'd water it down.
I gotta tell ya...
I'm actually starting
to feel a little more relaxed.
Let's try something different.
Let's try a shuffle.
Ready?
Just like that!
You know, it's like...
focusing on the step,
it's actually helping me
clear my mind.
Exactly.
This is the clearest
my mind's been in years.
I actually feel the stress
just melting away.
All right, try this one now.
Ready?
So what are you stressed about?
Work.
The neighbor's suing me
for killing his squirrels.
Mostly work.
You know that case
you guys walked in on earlier?
Something about it
just doesn't add up.
Found this bag
of unmarked pills in her purse.
- Crap!
- What?
While I'm sitting here
fooling around with you,
I forgot to call the lab
about the results.
It's Lassiter. Did you analyze
that sample I brought in yet?
Are you kidding me?
How long does it take?
I thought maybe you could
tell me something,
like what they are,
where she bought 'em, anything.
Those pills weren't bought.
They were made.
- They're lab trial samples.
- How do you know?
- I'm in pharmaceutical sales, remember?
- Since when?
Doesn't matter.
Can you tell me who made these?
There's only a handful of local labs
that use that pentagonal shape.
Really?
Gus, are you busy right now?
There you are.
Your class let out just in time.
KFC is giving away double downs.
They're just giving them away.
- What are you doing here?
- I discovered,
after you two left the crime scene,
that I have a need for Guster's...
Pharmaceutical expertise on this case,
so I came here to find him.
You convinced Lassie
to put us on the case. Good work, buddy!
I said Guster's expertise.
- Not yours.
- Yeah, we're a package, Lassie.
You don't get Jake "the snake" Roberts
without Damien the python.
- Gus doesn't work solo. Tell him.
- That's not actually true...
You have offended him
by merely suggesting it.
- Don't be angry.
- I'm not.
Now he's indignant!
You'd better back off, Jack.
Without breathing fire
through your sweet nostrils,
tell him to back off.
I don't have time. If you decide
you wanna help on the case alone,
you're welcome to come with me.
- Why aren't you laughing?
- I'd only be helping. It's no big deal.
No big deal?
You'd be working a case without me.
- You've worked cases without me.
- Because I knew I could solve them.
Are you saying
I can't solve a case without you?
No.
Because if we've learned
anything over these few years
it's that you really can't
do it without me.
First of all... We haven't learned
anything over the years.
Second of all,
I'm the one with this.
- So?
- So, all you have is this...
You know what?
It's on.
- It's not on.
- It is on, Shawn.
Like mascara on Prince, it is on.
Lassie, count me in.
It's on.
- I'm thrilled. Get in the car.
- You know who has shotgun?
- You.
- Me.
- Lassie's already behind the wheel.
- Because it's on.
All right, fine. If this is
how you wanna play it, it is on.
I decide
when it switches from off to on.
- So it's off?
- Yes.
Now it's on!
"Feet Dont Kill Me Now"
Timing: Psych Team
www.sous-titres.eu
I'm Detective Carlton Lassiter.
This is my associate Burton Guster.
What's wrong?
I'm not used to getting
introduced by my real name.
Ma'am, are you familiar
with these pills?
Those look like our trial
HCG hormone pills.
A fertility drug.
You are correct.
- Very nice, Guster.
- Thank you.
They're an experimental
fertility treatment
currently in phase three
of clinical trials.
They're not for public use.
Any idea how someone else could have
gotten ahold of those?
- Not a clue.
- Unless they were a test subject.
True. But I ran the trials alone
and kept all of the test
subject logs to myself.
Ma'am, those pills were found
on a dead woman.
So we're gonna need to see
those logs immediately.
Of course.
You scared the crap outta her!
But a phase three trial
is a double blind trial,
meaning there has to be
at least two administrators.
The test group can have a different
administrator than the placebo group.
- So you're saying she lied?
- There has to be another technician.
Nice insight, Guster.
Why didn't you say something
when she was here?
You know Shawn.
I usually can't get a word in edgewise.
That's funny.
O'Hara usually just
blurts out her opinions.
As if I asked for them.
Or wanted them.
Or needed them.
Because women ruin everything.
Maybe now's a good time
to call your therapist.
No, let's check out those logs first.
I'm gonna see where she went.
Look, Gus.
I'm getting handsy.
How's your little murder
investigation coming along?
Why are you here?
You missing a murder weapon?
You can take the knife out of my back.
How did you find me?
I installed GPS
parental controls on your phone.
- Is that why it keeps beeping?
- It tells me if you use your card
to buy condoms, liquor, or glue.
It's a little wasteful,
don't you think?
- I'm a player, Shawn.
- You're not a playah.
What are you doing here, Spencer?
We already interviewed the technician.
If Gus is allowed
to show off his expertise,
then I'm allowed to show off mine.
We don't have time to watch you make
a snowman out of mashed potatoes.
That's funny.
I'm getting something.
There's someone else...
Someone el... writing...
With their right hand, right-handed.
Yes. She had a partner.
We already know that.
- You do?
- Yes. We do.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
Guster...
Good luck getting hired
on a case that I'm already on.
on my case that you're not on.
That doesn't make any sense.
Dad, I know
exactly what you're gonna say.
Yes. You can work on the case
with Lassiter and Gus.
- I had no idea you were gonna say that.
- Lassiter only requested Gus,
we still have to pay psych
your full rate.
I don't like the idea of you
sitting around on your ass all day
collecting a check
for doing nothing.
I'm putting you to work.
So even when you do something I want,
it still counts as some punishment?
You're welcome...
Now I need to find you a partner.
I'll do it.
What case are we talking about?
The one Lassie's working with Gus.
Even better. He's been treating me
like a rookie ever since I took leave.
I am itching to get
back out into the field,
even if it means babysitting Shawn.
Fine. You two are working
the case together.
No reason for anything
to fall through the cracks.
- Babysit? Really? Come on.
- Shawn, what have you done today?
Let's see.
I watched some Phineas and Ferb.
Took a nap. Had a snack.
I'm a little tired.
- Exactly.
- I just wanna beat Lassie and Gus.
- And... catch the killer.
- Sure, if that's what it takes.
As long as we get to do
our thing, chop it up,
pound the pavement,
walk the bzzz-neat.
Catch me up
on what we're dealing with.
I really am exhausted.
I'm having a vision that the technician
lied about not having another partner.
Then, let's call her in
and see what she's hiding.
Sorry.
- What are you two doing here?
- We're interviewing a witness.
- And you?
Are you two working together now?
What happened,
they bust you down to the minors?
You go where you're appreciated.
I got two different calls
asking me to come in for questioning.
- Who called you first, us or them?
- Who'd you meet first, us or them?
Would you two stop it?
We have reason to believe
you lied to us
when you told us
that you worked alone.
Which, if true,
could land you an obstruction charge.
I'm sorry.
I was trying to protect
my partner Ben.
Protect him from what?
Desiree was Ben's girlfriend.
He was supplying her
with fertility pills under the table
because their insurance wouldn't cover
the thousands of dollars in treatments.
Wait. They were trying
to have a baby?
But they weren't even married.
- Get with the times. It's 2008!
- It's 2010.
Nice try. That would mean we're at war
with the machines.
- How much did you know about this Ben?
- Ben Stephens.
He's not a lawbreaker.
He's a very decent guy.
He was only trying
to be a good boyfriend.
I lied to keep him out of trouble,
but I certainly don't think he's capable
- of something like this.
- Neither do we.
Guster, would you care
to get a cup of coffee,
- maybe take a little break?
- Sure thing.
Aren't we due for a break?
How would you feel about
a little heavy petting?
Just a little over the clothes
third base action?
- Maybe get some coffee?
- Sure.
What are you doing?
- Me? What are you doing?
- You pinned me in!
- This is my and Guster's lead.
- No, it's my and Shawn's lead.
- You should leave.
- What are you smoking?
I am head Detective.
All leads go through me.
Right. Like I haven't heard
that one before. I know your tricks.
O'Hara, I am ordering you
to get back in that vehicle
- and drive away.
- That's gonna be tricky, Lassie.
Give me those!
- Nice senior officiating there.
- Shut it!
You are letting your lead get away.
You just let your lead
slip through your fingers.
Will someone explain to me
how the four of you let him get away?
Someone else.
We were about
to question the suspect
when we got sidetracked
by a disagreement.
Disagreement.
Your little disagreement
has led to a state-wide manhunt.
He likes to use
your own words against you.
This reflects poorly on me too,
I'd like to keep my job.
Now, I want the four of you
to get your acts together and find him!
You can't yell at me.
You're just a consultant.
I know what happened
to your neighbor's squirrels.
Carry on.
I take my job very seriously, Guster,
and I don't like being reprimanded.
All right, we've gotta figure out
where Ben fled to.
All we have to go on
is that he was last spotted
heading west on highway 101.
- What are you doing?
- It helped you last time.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Just follow my lead.
Did you notice anything
when we were at Ben's house?
It all happened too fast.
First thing I know, we were arguing,
next thing I know,
he was crashing through the garage.
The DMV report
that came out today...
It said that the car that Desiree's body
was found in belonged to Ben.
Right. They shared it.
They were living in sin
and driving in sin.
So whose car did Ben
crash through the garage in?
Good question.
Maybe a loaner?
A rental.
We should have McNab check
all the local rental companies.
Nice!
I gotta tell you, I can't believe
this stuff actually works!
Even though I look like
a total moron doing it.
Crap.
Look at that.
Christmas came early.
So that's what the two of you
have been doing together...
- Tap dancing?
- Okay, the truth is...
Lassiter happens to be
in my tap class.
You've been taking
tap classes together!
How sweet! What's next,
singing into hair brushes?
Beachside pilates?
Quick, Jules, chime in
while I think of more zingers.
- What's next... bridge?
- Yeah, bridge... what?
Thanks for killing the bit.
Tapis something we both enjoy.
While you two are sneaking
around and spying on people,
we have a new lead.
You finishing each other's sentences?
But we have a lead too.
- Well, ours is more of a hunch...
- Hamburger!
Shawn, why in the world would I have
been about to say hamburger?
Let's roll, Guster.
- That doesn't even make any sense.
- I just heard you make an "h" sound.
So you go to hamburger?
We have to figure out
how Ben is involved,
but I don't think they're going
to be cooperative, without a warrant.
Jules, don't be Canada.
I'll handle this.
- Hello. How can I help you?
- I want to sell my body to science.
- Well, I'd like to make the first bid.
- Is this a... Silent auction?
What? She started it.
We would like to sign up
to be human Guinea pigs for money.
Our study pays 20 bucks.
- I'll do it.
- Uh, sorry. Women only.
- She'll do it.
- What?
Don't act like you can't use 20 bucks.
I've seen your place.
If you're interested,
go sign the consent forms.
You'll be put under anesthesia, and
the hormones may make your feet grow.
She's interested.
What's up?
What is anyone doing
in the grand scheme of things?
Your negativity is...
is clogging up my psychic signals.
Do you mind keeping her busy
- while I attempt to unclog them?
- how am I supposed to do that?
Gus would turn into smooth
Gus and try to pick her up.
- I'm not hitting on a girl.
- Does that scare you?
Or does that not scare you?
And does that scare you?
- What?
- Tthis girl could be dangerous.
make sure of that before you enter
into a relationship with her,
'cause she probably won't change.
Right this way.
- I'll be back to get your information.
- I'll be right here.
All right, put the time of death down
yesterday on the 12th.
I turns out I am taking
all of the medications
that Tonya here says disqualifies
somebody from being a part of the study.
That's... no.
A bummer.
Oh, well. We tried.
I guess we should roll?
And if they ever
discover a drug here
that makes me as strong as an ox...
But only when I'm fighting another ox...
You let me know.
- I will.
- All right.
- We are gonna nail this guy, Guster.
- Are you sure Ben's guilty?
100%.
Okay, here's the rental agreement.
\Mr. Stephens' car was due back
yesterday. Do you think he stole it?
Your chances of seeing that vehicle
again are about as good
as your chances of turning this job
into a viable career.
Hey, this antitheft tracking device.
- That a lojack?
- Yeah.
We're gonna need that tracking I.D.
We've got clear motive.
They've been together for a while.
She's been pressuring him,
putting the squeeze on him to have kids.
They're maried.
She'd get half of everything
if he left her. So he killed her.
I don't know. Who helps his
girlfriend obtain fertility pills If
he don't want to with her?
- This doesn't feel like murder.
- Guster, grow up.
People have sex,
and kill each other.
That's the real world.
Not some magical feelings place.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Let's go get a warrant.
- We're gonna eat first, right?
- We'll eat on the way.
- I got sunflower seeds.
We're so sorry
for your loss, miss Blake.
This must be very difficult for you,
so we won't take up a lot of your time.
I wish I could help, but I don't know
where he is. If I knew, I would tell.
Was there animosity
between the two of you?
He was a cheating bastard.
Desiree found out,
and they had this huge fight
right before she disappeared.
What she did to make him cheat.
- Shawn.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- You will thank me later.
Mrs. Blake...
I'm sensing that Ben felt
great remorse for his actions,
tried to reach out
to you personally.
The flowers he kept sending? Too little
too late. I never trusted that man.
- When did you last see Ben?
- Right after they found Desiree's body.
He came by to offer condolences.
I... promptly kicked him out.
I'm not so sure he's not
the reason she's dead.
Well... we have taken up
enough of your time, miss Blake.
- Thank you.
- We're just gonna...
- Shawn!
- Let's go.
Ben's looking more and more guilty
the more we learn about him.
I don't know.
Who kills someone's daughter
and then sends her flowers the next day?
A crafty killer.
Back to the station
and start putting pieces together.
Back to the station? Can't we
do this over a jamba juice?
My graph paper and colored pencils are
at the station to chart what we know
- and extrapolate.
- What was that word?
- Extrapolate.
- Doesn't sound very fun.
- Who said work was supposed to be fun?
- Ron Jeremy, for starters.
You go back to the office
and put all that boring stuff together
that... I already forgot what it was,
and I'll see you there in half an hour.
Okay.
Half an hour.
Sweet.
Good work, Gus.
You found Ben.
Shawn, what are you doing here?
Dude, I know you're not psychic.
Sorry, buddy. It's hard
to keep track of who knows what.
I broke away from Juliet,
tracked you on your little thingy.
How'd you find him?
Lassiter used the lojack
tracking system on his car.
I saw the location, snuck away while
Lassiter was working on the warrant.
Figured you guys were close.
And like me, you broke away...
- because you thought Ben was innocent.
- You're doing it again.
Am I? It's ridiculous.
- That's why you broke away from Juliet?
- Yep.
Needed to check it out for myself.
Well... Since we're both here,
we might as well do it together.
Sure. Whatever.
Ben.
No, wait, no!
Ben, we don't...
wait!
Whatever the police think I did,
I didn't do it.
I'm a psychic with the police dept.
This is my partner, Santonio Holmes.
- We don't think you did it.
- Really?
You were more distraught than anyone
to hear that Desiree was dead.
Of course I was.
Just thinking about it makes me sick.
I want to find the person
who did this more than anything.
I've loved Desiree like... forever. We'd
been living together since we graduated.
- When did you graduate?
- 2005.
Lassiter's theory that he killed Desiree
to protect his money doesn't make sense.
They weren't common law
husband and wife.
Those rights don't kick in until
a couple has been together for 7 years.
And they moved in together in 2005,
- which was only three years ago.
- Five.
I should start carrying
a pocket calendar.
Ben, why did you run from the cops?
Desiree's mom, she practically
accused me of causing Desiree's death.
I thought she was the one who called
the cops on me, so... I panicked.
Ben, listen to me.
But also hear me.
You didn't do yourself
any favors by hiding.
I can convince the cops that you're
innocent, but only if you trust us.
- And you're sure...
- I'll do the touching.
- Sure they'll believe I'm innocent?
- I can guarantee it.
Freeze, you murderous dirt bag!
Ish.
I can guarantee it "ish."
Guys, please help me out here.
- Hang in there, Ben.
- Shawn... Santonio?
Can I at least get my phone call?
- If it wasn't a common law marriage?
- Innocents don't run from the police.
I have a hunch
that he's not our killer.
- We don't deal in hunches.
- "We"?
I'm sorry, Shawn, but it's over.
I understand.
- It was fun while it lasted.
- It wasn't.
- We made a great team.
- We didn't.
It was a disaster!
Partners don't lie to one another,
and partners don't run off
mid-investigation,
and partners do not
go through my purse,
find my phone,
and text photos of my dog
to every guy in my address book
with the caption, "this is you."
- Partners support each other.
- We never support each other.
Yeah. We're constantly lying.
And running.
- I miss that.
- Me too. What!
We're still hired on this case, Gus.
Let's work.
But first can we get something to eat?
I'm kind of hungry. All I've had all day
are sunflower seeds.
Are you kidding me?
I haven't eaten in almost two hours.
Hamburgers!
- And then we try to free Ben.
- And then... Japa dogs.
What!
Well, 1 thing's for sure from all this.
It's nice to have you back.
Thanks. I'm sorry you got stuck with
an extra caseload while I was gone.
That's okay.
Besides, it's your extra caseload now.
It's good to be back.
- Woodrow, my good man.
- Shawn!
Always nice to see you
walk through that door.
Well, let's hope you never
see me rolled in on a gurney.
I'd be honored to saw through your chest
and remove your heart from its cavity.
I'm touched. Woody, in your professional
opinion, how do I die?
Murder. Gangland execution.
We never find your head.
- That's a shame.
- You slip in a tub.
We need you to tell us
everything you can about,
the death of Desiree Blake.
Cause of death in our victim...
Is confirmed to be drowning
Evidenced by the presence
of fluid in the lungs.
- What about this mark on her ankle?
- Yeah. Interesting, isn't it?
- Almost looks like freezer burn.
- Freezer burn?
How would she get freezer burn
in 70-degree water?
Question is why would a drowning victim
show no signs of struggle?
- What do you mean?
- Well, there's no bruising on the body
Or... or cuts
or any kind of struggle.
Hey. It's Ben's lab partner.
When Ben been arrested, I rushed right
over. There's no way that he did this.
- We don't think so either.
- Yeah, but we need proof.
You know, Gus and I...
Discovered something
pretty interesting.
Did you two know that when
a tech enters Ben's lab,
they have to swipe a security
card to gain entrance?
I wish there was some kind of record of
exactly what time he entered and exited
- on the day of the murder.
- Some kind of log.
- Or a registry.
- Ledger.
- Duckit.
- Docket.
- I've heard it...
- I haven't.
Hey, what is that behind your ear?
Will you look at that?
It's the entrance record!
According to this, Ben works
at the time of the murder.
What?
No way he could have killed Desiree.
- And now we revel.
- Alien-style.
Congratulations.
But you two are forgetting something.
- What's that, officer dad?
- Part-time officer dad.
There's still a killer out there.
Get to work.
All right, what do we know
about this case?
One... there's a woman who's dead.
Two, Ben didn't kill her.
- Three, these japa dogs are delicious.
- I hear that.
You gotta give it to the Japanese. And
not because they invented the Chinese.
I almost took Lassiter to the japa dog
cart, but I felt like I was cheating.
Oh. That's so sweet, buddy.
He was a cheating bastard.
Desiree found out, and they had this
huge fight right before she disappeared.
Wait a minute.
Ben... cheated... on Desiree.
- Yes, he did.
- We never figured out with who.
He didn't say.
She would have motive
to kill Desiree. Bingo!
We gotta get that out of Ben. How come
you're allowed to say bingo and I'm not?
Idem you're not
allowed to say "true DAT."
- True that.
- Exactly.
Buzz!
- What's going on?
- They pulled a dead surfer out.
Dead surfer...
Oh, no.
He... he's dead, Shawn.
- Oh, man.
- Once again...
No sign of struggle.
Fluid in the lungs.
Once, I wouldn't think as much of it.
But twice in one week with two victims
ho knew each other? That's suspicious.
What would be really awesome
is if it happened a third time.
You're saying that both drowned,
but neither of them died in the water.
How's that possible?
- They were dry drowned.
- Come on.
You're putting words next to other that
sound like things we're talking about.
No! Actually...
He's right.
Dry drowning can give
all the appearances of actual drowning.
It would have to be caused
by something like a methane gas leak
or an overdose of anesthesia.
If you're interested,
you'll have to sign the consent forms.
You'll be put under anesthesia.
Gus, we gotta get back to the lab.
You.
All right, we came down here
ya asked. Now what?
Let's be honest.
We need you, and you need us.
Let us all work together.
Watch it and feel it.
I refuse to watch, and I'm sure
not gonna feel it.
- Feel what, Shawn?
- We're about to get a confession.
Tonya. Got bad news.
These are cops, this is Dion Richmond...
No, I'm a psychic.
I see things, and I feel things.
- Do you wanna feel what you see?
- I can't lose.
- Have you no shame?
- I'm not here to play!
with a cold-blooded killer.
You had an affair with Ben.
Don't deny.
- Guilty as charged.
- Boom... Shaka!
- That's gotta be a new record.
- Cuff her, Lassie.
What? It's not like
he croaked while we were doing it.
You wanted Ben all for yourself.
No, I didn't.
We hooked up once,
and he totally freaked out.
He loved his girl.
Whatever. The beat goes on.
Not Ben's.
Likely story. You had access to the
anesthesia that dry drowned him.
I'm a part-time assistant.
I mean, do you think they
actually let me near that stuff?
My security badge gets me in and out
of the front door and into the bathroom.
I don't get anywhere near
the actual experiments.
You'd have to go to Devry
or something for that.
Yes. Interesting, indeed.
Looks like freezer burn.
I'm calling an audible.
I'm sensing something very strong.
I'm getting a strong,
jealous, spiteful...
spirit vibe here.
Right... In here.
It's strong here, but mostly here.
Yes. You. Lillian.
You were jealous of Ben
and Desiree's relationship.
Ridiculous.
Miss, a second. Spencer, what's the
deal? Am I cuffing Charlotte the Harlot?
No. Sorry.
You and I are back on dirty.
Lillian killed Desiree Blake because
she wanted Ben all for herself.
- That's crazy.
- Maybenot.
In your statement to us, you did refer
to Ben as a great boyfriend,
and yougot him out of jail
before we'd finished processing him.
Come on.
Of course you fell for him.
He was your partner.
He...
He shared with you.
He confided in you, trusted you.
But Ben never referred to her
as anything other than a coworker.
Come on, it's obvious
why he'd go for that one... She's easy.
I was more than a coworker.
I cared for him.
Everyone knew that Ben and
Desiree were getting married.
Ben made a mistake
and cheated on Desiree.
She moved out, and you saw that
as your opportunity.
Who are you calling a mistake?
- Isn't it obvious?
- How did I miss this?
- What is he doing?
- It gives him clarity.
Yeah, Lassie, I don't think we have time
to give the savion glover treatment.
Even after Ben cheated, He still pined
for Desiree. He wanted her back,
and you realized you would have to
get rid of her for good.
So you brought her to this lab and
gave her a high dose of anesthesia that
caused her to dry drown!
- I taught him that.
- We know.
You just had to get rid of the body.
So you put Desiree behind the wheel
of her car and drove it into the lake,
weighing down the accelerator with one
of those blocks of frozen water
that you use
for freezing lab samples.
Dry ice is not frozen water.
It's carbon dioxide.
- They do share the same...
- Not now.
I can't do this with you now.
The point is, the evidence melted.
Very clever.
All you had to do was be there for Ben,
and he would fall for you like you had.
Except he didn't feel
the same way about you.
I wanna find the person
who did this more than anything.
You were so delusional, you thought he
would be touched by your murderous act.
Of course, he was not,
because you are a crazy dry drowner.
And in the heat of the moment, it
was either you or him.
- And you chose you!
- Nice, Lassie.
Way to tap your way
back to the party.
A 2d review of the body
will trace the anesthesia
used to kill them back to your lab.
He should have been with me.
This is all her fault.
Hands behind your back, please.
- Well played, Shawn.
- Well played, everybody.
Way to roll with the punches. You never
know which way it's gonna come and go.
Psychically speaking.
- Thank you for agreeing to meet me.
- Sure.
Let's hope this goes better
than the last couple of days.
- Not that they were that bad.
- They were horrific.
- All right?
- OK.
Again, from the top.
That's my partner up there!
- Black guy's my partner.
- They're both black.
I know who the West Side rapist is.
And that's... my partner.
Kids, come on, freestyle.
One, two, three, four.