Shawn, we shouldn't left our troop.
Dude, this is a chance
to put our skills to a real test.
What was that?
It was nothing.
Your little lil'chief senses are off.
Okay, tell me you didn't hear that.
Probably just a giant beaver.
A giant beaver?
Dagnabbit, what is it?
Run!
Wandering off is about the dumbest thing
you've ever done.
Do you know
how dense this forest is?
Dense enough for a werewolf to run amok
and swallow me like a rollo.
- Werewolves, huh?
- Yeah, didn't you hear them?
The mind can convince itself of almost
anything when fear is involved.
But fear does not exist
in this dojo, does it, boys?
Help me.
We're out of here.
The following is the royal rumble!
"Hacksaw" Jim Duggan.
Winner of the first-ever rumble
in 1988.
- Old school.
- You even got the 2x4. All right.
Look at you.
We both went retro.
Although he should have
a vast and unruly beard.
I didn't want to draw on his face.
But don't worry,
the most important component
is still intact.
What?
Sylvester Ritter, aka Junkyard Dog.
The most prolific
and electrifying wrestler of his time.
May he rest in peace.
Amen.
Is it a little weird
that we still...
This might have to be the last year
for the dolls.
Kinda creepy.
Let's cover them with something.
Hurry.
Please say
you're the psychic detectives... please.
I'm the psychic detective.
He just has a magic 8-ball head.
Okay, terrific.
Okay, this is good.
Stewart Gimbley.
I need you to lock me up
and observe my behavior overnight.
You're my last hope.
- Dude!
- No, it's for your own protection.
Are those silver bullets?
I went to the cops,
and I told them to put me in a cell.
And the detective said,
"jail is for criminals,
not delusional whackadoos."
He said "whackadoos"?
And then he pinched himself
and told me to come see you guys.
And what, exactly,
does this detective look like?
Imagine Robert Goulet
dressed like Mr. Bean
playing the scarecrow in a summer stock
production of the Wizard of oz,
dedicated to Tony Randall.
So, Stewart, why do you feel
you need to be locked up and observed?
I'm almost positive I'm a lycan.
Lichen? Like seaweed?
No, a lycan.
You mean a lychee.
- Like sheep's wool.
- Lychee is a drupe fruit.
A lycan. Lycanthrope.
Werewolf?
What?
"Dee's nuts."
I don't get it.
I think I did that last night.
You think you killed a little lamb?
Tonight could be much worse.
I was gonna ask my sister to watch me,
but I love her
and clearly fear for her safety.
- Rumble's about to start any second.
- It's on.
- I don't really feel like...
- I can pay you thrice your normal rate.
I'm not doing it for half price,
I'll tell you that.
That's three times the amount.
- I've heard it both ways.
- No, you haven't.
It's starting.
- The rumble's on.
- We can throw him in the corner.
- It's a lot of money.
- It's not like he's really a werewolf.
House rules are as follows.
One...
- No talking during the rumble.
- Two...
You leave here at sunrise, never ever,
ever come back again. And three...
Touch the quatro queso dos fritos
and I will take you down using basic,
traditional beginner's karate.
Deal.
You are truly lifesavers.
Now, please,
bind my extremities as best you can.
Proving time and again here tonight.
Hacksaw is just hammering away.
He's hitting everybody in sight.
- You sure you guys can handle this?
- Please, Stew, we're professionals.
Psych 408
"Let's Get Hairy"
Timing: Psych Team
www.sous-titres.eu
I got something.
Right there.
Let's send Bambi back to ma.
On my word.
Ready...
Now!
Red?
What the...
Who's there?
I will blow you to kingdom come.
You hear me?
You are messing
with the wrong son of a b...
Damn it,
I told you to stop doing that.
It's like watching someone
while they sleep.
Why were you reading that file
like Mr. Peanut?
I was curious.
Several distinguished military
strategists throughout history...
But you know what, I don't need
to explain myself to the likes of you.
"Dee's nuts"?
Stewart Gimbley. Ring any bells?
Yay high,
yellow eyes,
howls at the moon.
This guy spent last night chained up
in our office
until he escaped and jumped
through our double-paned window.
- It's not even sort of double-paned.
- Wait.
He broke through his chains?
Figuratively, yes. Literally,
it was duct tape and kite string.
He chewed his way out with his big, bad
teeth, all the better to eat you with.
We were sleeping, so we can't confirm
how pointy his ears were.
- I didn't say ears.
- That's what I heard.
Me too. And now we have a broken window
that you should pay for.
Fat chance.
Here.
Why don't you go look for your lost pet
at his place of business.
"Occultopuss"?
Even though I wouldn't lock him up
because he was from the planet Wolfen,
he still told me to come down and have
my palm read by his sister... Willow.
You're saying you've worn that shirt
for at least two days in a row.
- Remove yourself from this place.
- You sure you don't want to tag along?
I would rather adopt a child.
Copy that.
- Occultopuss?
- Yes. But first... Jules?
Sorry, no time
for your tomfoolery and silliness.
That goes for your nonsense,
malarkey, and shenanigans.
We need a favor, it's legit,
and we promise to owe you big.
Make it quick.
I didn't have
anything else sanitary.
I used to have one of these
with wonder woman's face on it.
- Me too.
- It's a hair.
- We need to know where it came from.
- More specifically,
whether it came
from a wolf or a were-hybrid.
- Were-hybrid.
- Please,
this could be a matter
of life and death. Or mange.
Sweet!
Use the bat phone.
Book of shadows.
Hey there.
My name is Shawn Spencer.
My associate Ron Davis,
aka Bob Adams.
Known to his coven simply
as rich fingerlind.
You're a warlock?
No, but Halle Berry
calls me "Black Magic".
- You're never met her.
- Yes, I have.
On the set of Gothika.
That's right, I always forget.
He directed Gothika.
- May I help you?
- That depends. Are you Willow Gimbley?
- I am.
- Great.
We just spent the evening with Stewart
at our psychic detective agency.
And it turns out
that he might be a lycan.
Not the drupe fruit. Rather,
the hairy biped that hunts and mauls.
I was afraid that could be the case.
Ever since he was bitten, he's been
acting peculiar and blacking out.
All signs point directly
to the mark of the beast.
Did you just say "bitten"?
We were on a mystical march
in the Dick Smith Wilderness
in Santa Ynez a few weeks ago.
We got lost, and he went off-trail
to make water in the darkness...
- That's when it happened.
- Sure hope he finished his business.
He said he saw teeth, fur, and a snout.
Not necessarily in that order.
He's been so elusive this past week.
He won't let me or any other
of the shamans in our rhombus help him
because he doesn't want
to put us in danger.
It's really starting to sink in.
My big bro.
Any idea where he might be now?
We're fearless, we're trying to help,
and one of us is single.
And clearly goth-curious.
Trust us, you don't want the cops
to find him before we do.
I suspect he's hiding
and scared to death,
what with the third
and final full moon.
Which isn't exactly full,
just especially gibbous.
His need to feed tonight
will be more intense than anything
you can possibly imagine.
I see. Who are those people,
and why?
Friends, and a couple of the others
from Stewart's therapy group.
They're very close.
Stew's birthday last year.
- Is that shangri-lala's?
- Stew knows someone who works there.
We got half off the party package,
we got to bring our own vampire geisha.
Now, that's a party.
Please call us if Stewart shows up.
Our number's on the back, in pencil.
But feel free to use my work cell
on the front.
Please find my brother
before he eats an innocent.
"Bitten"? If she's telling the truth,
the man was bitten by a beast.
This may be above our pay grade.
Don't be the third Thompson twin
with the dreads.
This is exactly at our pay grade.
Plus, we're his only hope.
Imagine being him right now?
Then you wouldn't be able
to get jiggy with his sister.
Don't you talk about her like that.
She's clearly in emotional peril,
and her heart is heavy.
And all that weird,
sexy makeup is just a cry for help
from a strong man with a solid job.
Look at you crushing on Vampira.
Who is this?
I need you to come to leadbetter beach
and bring me a 36-hour survival basket.
Look, dad,
I'm a little tied up right now.
This is a challenge
that involves a former nemesis
and something I deserve.
Do you understand?
- Not even sort of.
- Bring me
two ham sandwiches
on stone ground wheat...
Mustard, no mayo.
Plenty of electrolyte liquids,
and a flashlight.
- Asap.
- Okay, folks, here we go.
Keep your hands
on this brand new beautiful truck
and see how long you can last.
Last man standing drives it home.
No mercy, Spencer.
Hot off the wire,
another possible animal attack.
About 6 miles from where that poor lamb
was ripped apart two nights ago.
- Hunters?
- Must've been lousy shots.
Son of a bitch.
- What is it?
- My worst nightmare.
Spencer's gonna be calling me
any second. Let's go.
Right behind you. I'm just gonna
stop off at the ladies' room first.
Unbelievable.
- This is getting serious.
- Dude,
- he completely forgot about his bag.
- What are you doing?
Preparing to playhot cross
bunson the recorder.
What it look like.
You can't go rifling
through another man's stuff.
Sure the privacy barrier was broken
when you duct-taped his thighs together.
It helped restrict the flexibility
in his hips.
"One capsule before bedtime."
What is Haloperidol prescribed for?
Schizophrenia. It also reduces
aggression towards others.
And used with chlorpromazine,
can control hiccups.
- What do you know about Dr. Ken Tucker?
- Psychiatrist. He's not on my route.
But he's doing well for himself.
He moved his practice
into new digs on Arthur avenue.
No kidding.
This is the first time
we've had a case with a doctor
- who wasn't on your route.
- All streaks are made to be broken.
If this guy thinks stew needs
help controlling his aggression,
we should probably pay him a visit.
You weren't kidding. This guy's
feeling good about himself, huh?
His office is this way, Shawn.
Look at that.
Right on the door there.
Hello there, Myrtle.
My name is R.P. McMurphy.
This is my partner Cheswicke.
We both have some faulty
wiring up in our noggins,
and we're gonna
have to talk to the doc.
No can do, sailor.
Push on!
- She totally shot me down.
- I got it.
Myrtle, when is
Dr. Tucker's next available session?
April 25, 2011.
Now hit the bricks, Woodpecker.
Is there a standby option
for extra-crazy people
who very well may pose
a threat to others?
You have ten seconds to make
like my third husband and disappear.
I don't think we can hang
with this old bird.
Heavens to Betsy!
I'll be right there.
- Don't touch me!
- Polexia, calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down.
Myrtle, give me some help here.
Oh, dear.
What are you doing, Shawn?
Get from behind that desk.
- That woman is gonna kill you.
- Patient info.
- Your phone. I'll take a few pictures.
- Use your own phone.
- I left it in the car.
- Too bad for you.
- Just gimme your phone!
- She's gonna break it.
- Gimme the phone one time!
- Hurry up.
Dude, am I seeing what my brain
is telling my eyes that they're seeing?
That's me and Ruiz the koala.
I make a yearly donation
to the "bear with me" foundation
to help protect the lives
of these precious and unique creatures.
- You're cuddling the animal?
- We're nuzzling.
And Ruiz made the first move.
She comes.
Oh, this is so embarrassing.
Those boys are dumb as rain.
See you next week.
Actually,
you won't.
I have to go.
I'm late for work.
Don't do anything
you might regret, girly.
Remember why you came to us
in the first place.
Excuse us.
Would it be possible for us
to speak with the doctor
in a non-therapy capacity?
You know, like gentlemen.
Beat it.
- That was a disaster.
- I wouldn't go that far.
So if I was to nuzzle
with a non-domesticated zoo dweller,
- I think I'd go with a giraffe.
- Giraffes are chronic spitters.
I'd climb up and risk it.
They've got those giant doughnut lips.
Like two Christmas hams
kissing under mistletoe.
Did that smokin' hot mess
look familiar to you?
No, I would have remembered that.
All right. Fine.
I deserve this one.
Let's hear it.
For who? The boy?
That's on Gus' iPod.
- It's back at the office.
- Who?
Don't say a word
about Denise Williams.
Who?
There was another animal attack
last night.
And it wasn't a poor little lamb.
Seems your delusional little buddy's
upgraded to hunters.
Look who's suddenly
on the black and tan express.
No, I don't think we're chasing
a werewolf, Spencer.
Just another cuckoo
who's seen too many movies.
Update: we don't have
any actual proof that Stewart...
He pretty much confessed to both of us,
and he has no alibi, remember?
Good luck getting by Dr. Tucker's
pit bull of a receptionist.
Maybe you just didn't have
the right tools.
The monocle isn't gonna help you
in this situation.
I'm talking about one of these.
Idiot.
- Anything back yet on the follicle?
- No,
but keep your phones on,
and proceed with caution.
This is our case now too.
Maybe we should
let them take it from here.
If we turn away every werewolf case
that comes through our doors,
people are gonna start talking.
Besides, do you really think Stew
is sprouting hair and fangs,
unable to resist
some sort of blood lust
when the moon is full?
If he isn't, then he's some crazy dude
who thinks he is.
But what difference
if he's out there killing people
and precious wooly animals?
None, I guess.
I have to go.
I'm late for work.
Hold on.
- What is it?
- Check out those pictures.
Dude, I knew
I'd seen that chick before!
She's a bartender at shangri-lala's.
Tell me I'm right.
Am I right?
She sure is.
Her name is Polexia.
Wasn't that Anna Paquin's name
in Almost Famous?
Anna Paquin was in Almost Famous?
Let's get a drink.
I'm gonna need to speak
with Dr. Ken tucker immediately.
Well, if it ain't little dorothy
and her pal scarecrow.
Where's the tin man
and the cowardly lion?
Well, here's the tin man...
And here's toto.
Follow me.
Obviously this is very troubling.
Does this look like the sort of thing
gimbley's capable of,
in your professional opinion?
Stewart has a very active
imagination.
- That's not what I asked.
- I heard what you asked.
What would you have me say?
I took an oath.
My job is to help people
like stewart
to overcome
the psychological hurdles
that impair their desire
to lead what we consider
to be normal, everyday lives.
Take a look around.
My success rate in this area speaks
for itself. Wouldn't you agree?
We're just trying to figure out
what we're dealing with here.
Two men are dead,
and tonight's another full moon.
I can't believe I just said that.
My opinion is that you're dealing
with a very troubled young man.
No kidding.
A few weeks ago, stewart took
a turn for the worse.
It is possible
he is blurring the lines
between reality
and a much darker fantasy.
At the end of our last session,
he even became emotional
and, uh... gave me a hug.
- Why would he do that?
- In the event he never saw me again.
Yeah, do you have any idea
where he might be?
I wish I knew.
Someone needs to save him
from himself.
Hello, gentlemen.
What'll it be?
Well, he would like a roy rogers.
That much we know for certain.
What?
You look really familiar to me.
Yeah, I've just got
one of those faces, I guess.
Nope, I don't...
I don't think so.
I'm almost positive
I've seen you before.
Wait a second.
Are you a patient of Dr. Ken tucker?
I knew it! I totally knew it.
We were just there earlier today.
I'm trying to get my buddy here
an appointment.
He's absolutely stir crazy.
Yeah, and skip here
has romantic dreams
about firemen who look like
dolph lundgren.
What?
You cheeky screwball.
What'd I tell you, he's wacko.
It was late, you were in a firehouse,
and you slid down this large pole...
- Why?
- You started it.
Okay, fine.
Have you enjoyed your experience
with Dr. Tucker?
He comes highly recommended by
a fellow named stewart gimbley.
Stewart gimbley.
Yeah, I know that little weirdo.
I dialed him up with a great deal
on our birthday package last year.
God, what a freak.
You know, he told me once
that his father is some sort
of demon rabbi.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
But as far as the doc goes, I mean,
if we really wanted an appointment...
Look, I'm probably not the best
person to ask about Dr. Tucker.
And why is that?
'Cause I don't think
i'll be seeing him anymore.
I'm not sure anyone will,
actually. Capiche?
No, I... not really. No.
Could you elaborate?
I shouldn't say anything else.
Look, there are plenty
of shrinks in this town.
Trust me.
Did you decide
on something to drink or what?
Yes, I have.
I'd like a sloe gin fizz, please.
Hold the gin, extra fizz.
I'll have more cherries.
Help me. Please.
Help me.
Okay, this is really, really...
- Really not good.
- Of course it's not.
I woke up next to a pair of dead
hunters who were torn to shreds.
I'm sorry, I can't focus until
we handle this wardrobe issue.
Agreed.
You know what, you can use
my halloween costume from last year,
which is in storage here.
- Really?
- There's a banker's box
with a hand-drawn
jack-o-lantern on it.
Costume's inside.
We need to call lassiter and juliet
and make a citizen's arrest now,
while he's docile.
Since when do we make
citizen's arrests?
Since a guy showed up naked,
covering his junk with balloons,
saying he woke up smack
next to the victims.
- Something feels off.
- What feels off?
I don't know yet.
That was impossibly fast.
You even put on the glasses.
- Who am I supposed to be?
- Are you kidding?
- You didn't watch television as a kid?
- Not after poltergeist.
You are none other than dwayne
cleophus wayne ofa different world.
A ladies' man with a plan.
What?
Stew, you know you've put us
in a tough spot coming back here.
I know.
I'll turn myself in.
I don't know what else I could
have done. I warned everyone.
I can't live like this.
I've never hurt anybody
my whole life.
Stew, look at yourself, man.
I mean, you're you.
I can't believe
you're doing these things.
I know, but there isn't
a single shred of evidence
to suggest that I'm not.
Can you think of anything you haven't
told us? Nothing can hurt your cause.
Willow disagrees,
but I have long since suspected
that our father, rabbi gimbley,
is actually a dybbuk,
and that we might be the spawn
of demon seed.
Keeping in mind, of course,
that not all demons are bad.
Take hellboy, for instance.
He's nice.
- Polexia wasn't kidding.
- Polexia? What-you...
Talked with the black widow?
- You call her the "black widow"?
- Not just me.
All of us in the group.
She was married to a guy
without hair...
- What's that called?
- Bald.
- Alopecia.
- That's the fear of beans.
So one day, polexia
ties him up to the bed
and gags him and all that, you know,
she was into
some very kinky business.
- Sure.
- Go on.
He had a heart attack and croaked.
But also, she used to
totally dominate our sessions,
like her problems are
more important than ours.
But we put up with it
because she has voluptuous buttocks.
What do you mean "used to
dominate" your sessions?
Well, she once threatened dr. Tucker
during a neo-jungian sharing exercise,
and ever since then, she only
does one-on-ones with him.
Really?
We're taking you
to your sister at occultopuss.
We are?
The man is wanted for a double homicide
and first-degree lamb slaughter.
I know this.
You think I don't know this?
Look, I'm taking a huge
leap of faith here, okay?
You are to stay put at occultopus until
you hear from us... Do you understand?
I can't put willow
in harm's way... it's unbrotherly.
Listen, I don't think
you're gonna turn
into a giant dog head tonight, okay?
I'm getting serious vibes that you are
part of someone else's nefarious plan.
- Why?
- You're vulnerable.
And you look like that.
And you believe in weird things.
Willow locks you in the bathroom,
just to be safe.
We're gonna get
to the bottom of this.
It all ends nice.
- You really think so?
- I do.
You're still a weird little dude,
you'll probably be single for some time.
But I think we can keep you
out of jail. Deal?
- Deal.
- My man.
- Be careful.
- Don't worry, I got it.
You drop that cooler in your backseat
off at the beach to my dad,
then we lay low until
dr. Tucker's office closes.
- Then what?
- We finesse our way in.
We find some evidence that
stew's not a hairy monster,
and that it's actually polexia
that's behind all this nefariousness.
It's wolf hair. Authentic wolf hair.
And we spoke to Dr. Ken tucker.
He said stewart is
a very troubled young man.
No problem.
I hope you're right about this.
- Who was that?
- It was a wrong number.
Two hours till sundown.
Only ten of you left.
Who's gonna win this baby?
Shawn, where have you been?
Gus and I are working on a case,
the likes of which we've never seen.
That's every week.
What's truly extraordinary is
this test of endurance.
Both mind and body have
to be very strong.
Very strong.
Here you go, dad. It's everything you
asked for. Plus a couple extras...
Daddy got a care package.
- You're wasting your breath, Zielinski.
- Must be your boy.
Keep an eye on your chakras,
everybody.
He's a 5'10" psychic detective,
which is more than I can say for
that mean-spirited daughter of yours.
- My height?
- She's an uncompromising chef.
She makes sandwiches at sub-zero,
and she refuses to hear me
when I say "no mayo."
That's my girl.
Dad, am I sensing
a bitter history between you
and sam elliott's
younger brother harland?
He's my old nemesis.
Butch Zielinski.
I told you all about him. He used to
step on my toes, steal my thunder.
- You could take him.
- Thank you, guster.
Agreed.
Now, the guy we're working for
thinks he's a werewolf.
- Whip garlic at him. That's all I got.
- That's for vampires.
Look, I simply cannot afford
any distractions.
Today is all about me, me, me...
And that hemi v-8, which,
i'll have you know,
churns out an astonishing
390 horsepower, guster.
Can't you smell it?
I drive an echo.
All right...
Here's a few freebies.
Casey kasem here with the manicure,
clearly not a truck guy.
You know he's early-exit fodder.
Woman by the side mirror
is a germaphobe.
Sneeze in her direction,
she's out of here.
And the young buck staring across
the bed at mounds mcclintock there
would like nothing more than
to take his hands off the hard body,
and put it on the soft one.
I'll be damned.
I didn't clock the germaphobe.
You're welcome.
High five.
Just kidding. Focus.
Go get 'em, pop.
Wait for it.
You took a picture of his schedule.
There's nothing impressive about knowing
when he's exiting the building.
Wait for it...
- Let's do this.
- Do what?
We still don't have a plan yet.
Would you stop being a baby?
We just have to stash ourselves
until Myrtle leaves.
What's wrong
with the men's bathroom?
We're men.
How's that not obvious?
Myrtle is a woman.
If she has to use the bathroom,
she's coming in here.
Think you're ready for this night train,
Johnny Murdock?
Think again.
You wish you were Johnny Murdock.
Shut up, Shawn!
Never underestimate the swiss!
I was underestimating you, Shawn.
What are we looking for, exactly?
Polexia's file.
And any snacks you can find.
Let's just pretend
that didn't happen.
For the record, I'm only doing this
because Stewart might be innocent.
Might.
That and you want to have a half-black
Fairuza Balk baby with his sister.
Question is,
whatever will you name it?
Well, if it's a girl,
Lavender, of course.
If it's a boy,
Deandre Pride Guster.
- Dude.
- What?
- Polexia's file is gone.
- What do you mean "gone"?
There's a tab that says "Polexia Li",
but the file is gone.
That's a major bummer.
Gimme the swiss.
See if you can find Stew's file.
Okay, here we go.
Here it is.
Let's see...
"I fear that Stewart's condition
is worsening.
"He's completely ravaged by delusions
and uncontrollable homicidal impulses."
I don't think
she was wearing underwear.
"He may pose a grave danger
to himself and others.
"I'm afraid
there's only one recourse.
"He must be committed
to a psychiatric facility."
Shawn, are you hearing this?
Dr. Tucker wrote this
at Stewart's last session.
- We have to go. Willow's in danger.
- Wait.
What?
Do these look right to you?
- The label says Haloperidol, but...
- I knew it!
Only for the last 11 seconds,
but still...
- What's actually in the bottle?
- I don't know.
- Horse tranquilizers, maybe.
- Horse tranquilizers?
- What do you know about taxidermy?
- What don't I know about it?
I'm a part of the largest campaign
to abolish the practice completely.
- That owl cost five grand?
- No way.
- What about the beaver?
- No beaver is worth that much.
It would take a larger game.
A moose head, or possibly a cougar.
Or a gray wolf.
- It's neither Stewart nor Polexia.
- Exactly.
We gotta get back to Occultopuss.
Black Magic.
Is everything okay?
Please tell us Stew is still here.
Okay, I know that you said
to wait for you guys to get back,
but Dr. Ken Tucker came by,
and he was very grim.
He said that Stewart might try
to harm himself, and/or me,
and that he was the only one
who can help him.
You let Dr. Ken Tucker
take your brother?
Sorry.
Dr. Tucker has been looking
after Stew for over a year.
- I just met you guys today!
- What does this mean, Shawn?
It means somebody's about to die.
Personal address...
I know. I said I've got it.
Well, find it.
What the hell is going on here?
119 Lincolnwood Place.
Sweet. Juliet, write that down.
This woman, Polexia Li,
is tonight's unlucky victim.
I know her.
Wasn't that Anna Paquin's name
in Almost Famous?
She was in Almost Famous?
'Cause I don't think
I'll be seeing him anymore.
I'm not sure anyone will,
actually. Capiche?
Yes! And she was having
an affair with Dr. Ken Tucker.
Not Anna Paquin, Polexia.
She was his patient.
He tried to end it,
she went ballistic.
She's gonna spill the beans
and cost him his marriage.
And more importantly,
his thriving practice,
and he can't have that.
Worst of all,
he's methodically set up Stewart
to take the fall.
- How?
- It'll sound ridiculous.
It makes more sense to catch him,
and then let me do my thing.
- Where is she now?
- You wrote down where she lives.
She tends bar at Shangri-Lala's.
A 15-block radius.
She could be at either place
or anywhere in between because...
the buses stopped running
an hour ago, so...
I'm getting a vibe
that she walks from work.
Fine, you two hit Shangri-Lala's,
and we'll take care of the rest.
- I'm coming too.
- I'm riding shotgun!
We are down to two.
It is down to Butch and Henry,
mano a mano.
Excuse me.
Where's Polexia?
She felt sick, I let her go.
Strike two, then.
She's definitely not here.
Yes, I have the right address.
It's the one you divined!
Hello, is someone there?
Hey, I have mace!
You just about gave me a heart attack,
you son of a bitch!
What are you doing here?
I wanted to apologize
for being so insensitive.
It's too late for that.
No, it's not too late.
We can work it out.
I love my wife,
but I really do enjoy
having sex with you.
That's the best you've got?
Pretty soon, everyone will know
just how pathetic you really are.
I'm afraid I can't let that happen.
It didn't have to end this way.
Freeze!
SBPD. Hands in the air!
You don't understand.
She's very sick, I was trying to help.
I don't think so.
And woman to woman,
it's time to ixnay this shortcut.
Way to be, partner!
Put your hands behind your back.
Check up there.
Great work from the whole team!
He's bound to have Stew
stashed up there somewhere.
I haven't seen Stewart
in over a week.
I've got Stew!
That was impossibly fast.
What the hell kind of sick charade
were you planning out here?
You see...
He couldn't just kill Polexia
in cold blood.
She was bound to have told someone.
He needed a patsy,
and in walks Stew.
Over the edge and convinced
he'd been bitten by a werewolf.
Evil black light bulb goes off.
First, Dr. Ken Tucker
gave Stew the wrong drugs
to ensure that he'd be passed out.
The next night,
he waltzed into our office,
where we slept under what we thought
was the blanket of protection
- a double-bolt lock provides.
- You never lock the door.
He smashed our window, stole Stew,
and killed two grizzled hunters
with an injection
of something I presume
is untraceable.
Then he actually proceed
to wolf them up,
using the tastelessly
mummified claws
of the beastly pelt
that I now wear on my head
as a tribute to its power and grace.
It's an awful act...
Taxidermy!
And, of course,
the murder thing too.
And finally,
he branded Stew with a pentagram,
and left him unconscious.
All leading to tonight,
when he would kill Polexia
and let poor Stewart confess.
For what it's worth,
I went into the woods to kill a deer.
The hunters were
a mere crime of opportunity.
A happy accident.
That's worth absolutely nothing.
You're the sickest of us all.
Well, Spencer,
I guess I should have listened to you.
- No one else would have either, so...
- You're gonna pay for our window?
Yeah, right.
That's rich.
Gus gave them to me.
Just in case.
Of course he did.
- Good thinking.
- You can never be too safe.
Where am I?
I feel like a baby.
That's because
you're wearing a diaper.
But you're gonna be okay, big bro.
Thanks to these guys.
How can we possibly repay you?
Maybe you and Black Magic here
could get together and do some
cauldron stirring sometime.
I'd love to.
Sounds good.
I think we should celebrate.
As soon as I am not naked anymore.
Agreed.
You're ruthless, Henry.
You are strong of mind,
but mean of heart.
We reap what we sow,
Zielinski.
Time to pay the piper.
My plight is noble, Henry.
This vehicle's not for me,
but for the children of St. Thomas
of the Apostles Orphanage of Goleta.
Come on.
Where did...
Look.
It's like
Pippi Longstocking's little sister,
Patches Longstocking.
You don't look
much like the orphan type.
As an infant,
after I was abandoned and left lakeside,
only to be found by big-fly fishermen,
it was the fine sisters
of St. Thomas of the Apostles
that raised the man
you see before you today.
And when
that old station wagon caught fire
and the kids didn't have new wheels
to take 'em on their field trips,
I said, "Butch...
"You know what you gotta do."
So here I am.
It's bigger than us, Henry.
And don't worry, I'm gonna have
this thing fitted with a custom camper
so the kids can't fall off the back
onto the freeway at high speeds.
Are you okay?
You gave up your dream machine
to a guy you punched in a bowling alley.
He brought a nun! Sometimes
you gotta give one up for the team.
You have to admit,
those were some cute kids.
No doubt.
You know what, that's actually
a really nice thing you just did.
- You ought to be proud of yourself.
- I'm tired. I want waffles.
- I could eat some waffles.
- I'm buying.
Which means I'm buying.
You know that's right.