We got a fire
offcounty road D-7
two miles west of
the Canyon Ridge intersection.
Suggest we dispatch
fire crews. Over.
(static)
This is DeputyWright.
Doyou copy?
Son ofa...
Sir?
Sorry to disturbyou, sir
but we've picked up
an unidentified bogey.
l thinkyou should see
the replay foryourself.
lt tripped the fence
at 231 7
offConnecticut's coast.
lnitial trajectory,
north by northwest.
then it went crazy.
Any other aircraft in the area?
No known aircraft
can maneuver like this.
Well,
whatever it was
dropped offthe screen
at 241 8, sir.
Hit ground west
of Lake Michigan
outside
Townsend, Wisconsin.
The tracking
prediction team
calculated impact
at over 800
miles per hour.
l've instructed Chief Koretz
to start
her report...
Negative.
She tracked
a meteor.
lt's aberrant movement
was due
to instrument malfunction.
But, sir...
Your report
will refect these facts.
ls that clear?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Code lndigo-Delta-Echo-Niner.
l have a confirmed fallen angel
in sector 87.
Mobilize Operation Falcon
immediately.
Wright:
Hello?
(screaming)
Reporter:
Theywill have no comment
until the government
investigation now underway
is completed.
Government officials
remain vague
about the toxic cargo that has
caused the immediate evacuation
ofTownsend, Wisconsin's,
1 2,000 residents.
Speculation here
has centered on
a shipment oftoxic waste.
Mulder:
Then what happened out there
if wasn't a train wreck?
Man:
Mr. Mulder, the continental
United States is surrounded
by an electronic fence
that reaches 1 5,000 miles
into space.
We use it
to track and monitor
the 7,087 man-made objects
that orbit the earth.
Last night at 231 7
that fence was breached.
This morning at 01 00
Operation Falcon
went into effect
led by Colonel Calvin Henderson
the Air Force's
reclamations expert.
Reclamations?
During the Cold War,
hisjob
was to prevent technologies
from downed U.S. aircraft
from getting
into Soviet hands.
He's part
ofa crash retrieval unit.
Mm-hmm.
Quick response.
l'd sayyou have
24 hours
before the entire area
is sanitized.
After that, it would be
like nothing ever happened.
Man:
Alright, get the trucks rolling.
Keep 'emgoing!
(chattering)
(soldiers chattering)
(helicopter whirring)
Thankyou, sir.
Thankyou.
Get 'er rolling.
Let's go! Let's go!
Soldier:
Alright, clear the road!
You're late, lieutenant.
lt will be dark
in a halfhour.
We had a fat, sir.
There's a briefing
at 2200 hours.
Go to headquarters
for live rounds.
Live rounds, sir?
You got a problem
with that?
We were told
this was a drill.
They told you wrong.
Sir.
Okay, everyone out!
Come on, people,
light a fire!
(indistinctchattering)
Man: Uh, roger,
this is Charley-Delta-SevenSquad.
We're continuing thesearch,
butat this time, it'snegative.
(men yelling)
(whooshing noises)
(shutter clicking)
(shutter clicking rapidly)
Youjust made
the worst mistake
ofyour life,
Agent Mulder.
l thinkyou knocked out
a filling.
You'll pay the price
for putting my men
at risk.
Since when does taking pictures
put lives at risk?
You violated
a U.S. Government quarantine
and that's a federal crime.
A quarantine?
That's whatyou call this?
We're trying to contain
an ecological disaster.
That's a lot offirepower
to protect Mother Nature.
l have my orders
and the license to execute them
as l see fit.
l suggest
you forget whatyou saw
orwhatyou thinkyou saw
foryour own well-being.
You've got a downed craft
in those woods, sir
and troops
carrying live rounds.
We both know what's out there!
Areyou MUFON or KUFOS?
Doyou mind ifl sit down?
Let me guess.
You're wh that new group,
CSlCOP, right?
Say no more.
You're a cautious man.
Trust no one-- verywise.
Afterwhat happened toJ.F.K.,
l understand completely.
Let me
introduce myself.
My name is Max Fenig.
l'm with the National
lnvestigative Committee
ofAerial Phenomenon--
NlCAP.
Pleased... pleased
to makeyour acquaintance.
l wish we could shake on it,
you know.
Firm grip,
look right in the eye--
you learn a lot
about a guy that way.
Can l, um..?
Can l askyou a question?
Go ahead.
Did you
see anything?
Did you get close?
Me, l saw nothing.
l didn't see anything!
Nada, zip.
A hundred yards
past the roadblock
they nailed me.
l have no idea
how they did it.
l'm telling you
it's like the Roswell cover-up
all over again.
What makes you so sure
there's something out there?
Same thing
that makes you so sure?
l didn't order room service.
This isn't funny,
Mulder.
Did you meet Max?
Who?
Max from NlCAP.
Oh. They must have released him.
Another intrepid soul
in search ofa close encounter.
ls that what this is about?
What else?
Try explaining that
to Section Chief McGrath.
He's ordering
a full inquiry
with a recommendation...
Mulder, he wants to shut down
the X-Files
and he wants you
out ofthe Bureau.
What else is new?
l don't understand you, Mulder--
whyyou're always
defying protocol
ignoringjurisdiction.
Because l know
what l saw, Scully.
There weren't train tracks
anywhere near that site.
So how could it have been
a derailed container?
Because it wasn't.
Whatyou saw
was not a toxic spill.
But it wasn't
a U.F.O., either.
Okay, l'm all ears.
what was it?
lt was a downed Libyanjet
with a nuclearwarhead.
(chuckling)
Over U.S. airspace?
They've been
picking up radiation
indicating
that the plutonium casing
may have cracked.
So to avoid mass panic...
You really believe that story?
That story happens to be
highly classified.
A highly classified lie.
(helicopterwhirring)
They're searching
for someone, Scully.
Probably the pilot.
You think they'd roll out
all this material
for one Libyan fighterjock?
Besides, no human pilot
walked away from that wreckage.
Well, maybe he ejected.
Maybe.
Scully:
You can't be serious.
As long as we're here
in Townsend, why not?
The hearing
is tomorrow morning.
That gives us 24 hours
to investigate.
My assignment
is to bring you back--
not to helpyou
dig yourselfin deeper.
The LastDetail
starring Dana Scully.
(phone offthe hook)
What's going on?
Looks like housekeeping
hasn't been hereyet.
Who would..?
(banging)
Shh.
Max?
Getyour hands up!
Whoa, don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Max?
Ahem.
My apologies.
Forgive me.
l'm a curious man.
l had to know.
Know what?
lfit was reallyyou.
You don't know me.
Wejust met last night.
We at NlCAP have been
following your career closely
sinceyour involvement
with X-Files.
Following my career? How?
The Freedom oflnformation Act.
Your travel expenses
are a matter
ofpublic record.
So this must be
the enigmatic Agent Scully.
How did you
recognize me?
l sawyour picture
in a trade publication once
and l read your article in Omni
about the Gulf Breeze Sightings.
l published that
under a pseudonym.
M.F. Luder. l know.
lt's an anagram for F. Mulder.
You really didn't think
that would fool us, did you?
l didn't think anybody
was paying attention.
Somebody is always
paying attention, Mr. Mulder.
Amazing.
Amazing? Hardly.
You want to see
something amazing
come with me.
Enigmatic Dr. Scully.
This is my, uh...
Right this way.
Excuse the mess.
Okay.
Where's those, uh...
Let me turn this off.
Theywere right here.
Oh, here they are.
The latest crop circle photos
from Project Argus. Huh?
Your opinion--
fact or fraud?
Mulder:
Fraud.
Max:
Explain the anomalous blisters
on the plants.
Mulder:
Some unreported weathering
effect common to wheat
or a systematic reaction
by the plant tissue
to being lodged
in one position.
Max:
You've read the literature.
Mulder:
l try to keep up.
You said you had
something to show us.
Oh, yeah.
The Wolfs Ear 2000.
Ever hear ofthis?
Yeah. Wolfindustries
supplies the C.l.A.
with all ofits
surveillance equipment.
State-of-the-art
search and intercept--
up to 1 00 channels
per second.
l'm jacked into local
fire and police departments
cellular phone pathways
and when the weather's right
air traffic control
from Whitmarsh air force base.
What haveyou got, Max?
Mobile unit broadcast
in scan mode
Townsend Sheriffs Department
two nights ago.
We got a fire
offcounty road D-7
two miles west
ofthe Canyon Ridge
intersection.
Suggest we dispatch
fire crews. Over.
This is DeputyWright.
Doyou copy?
And then this, 35 minutes later
presumably from the fire crew.
Reception got wiggy
for some reason.
This is Unit 53.
Man down. Request medevac.
l said request medevac.
You're breaking up.
Barely... bad...
Very bad. Wait a second.
What the hell?
Charlie, we got
a situation here.
We put up a tight net.
Yes, sir, every inch
ofground is being covered
dug up, squeezed, and sifted.
No, sir.
lt will not get away.
Not this time.
Mrs. Wright?
Hi. l'm Fox Mulder.
This is Dana Scully.
We're from the F.B.l.
We'd like to askyou
aboutyour husband.
He's dead.
What else is there
to know?
l'm sorry
aboutyour husband.
Oh, please.
Mrs. Wright,
we want to helpyou.
Then leave me alone.
Let us helpyou.
l don't know anything.
Don'tyou understand?
Theywon't even release the body
so l can give him
a proper burial, okay?
The government
can't do that.
l'm sure
ifwe appealed...
No! You can't.
You're entitled
to the truth.
l can't afford the truth.
They said ifl
spoke to anyone
theywould withhold
my husband's pension
and l have a child
to take care of.
(static screeching)
Picking up extremely high
frequency signal--
200,000 megahertz.
Sir, target
on the northeast side.
foot speed--
seven miles per hour, sir.
Beta team...
Copy.
Target entering your section
from the southwest.
Search and destroy.
Repeat-- search and destroy.
Yes, sir.
jackson?
Nothing.
Must have been an animal.
l'm sorry, but unless
you have a subpoena
l can't discuss
patient information.
Does that meanJason Wright
was your patient?
lt means l have
nothing more to say.
What about to his wife
and child, Doctor?
Would you have anything
to say to them?
Because whoever got toyou
also got to her.
They must have made
some pretty big threats.
What did they hold
overyour head--
your medical license,
the l.R.S.?
l hate fascists.
Excuse me?
The men who came in here--
The way they
pushed us all around.
Dr. Oppenheim, tell us
about the deputy.
You saw him that night
didn'tyou?
Yes.
And three others
from a fire crew.
Theywere all D.O.A. with
fifth- and sixth-degree burns
over 90% oftheir bodies.
But theyweren't like
any burns l've ever seen.
They took the bodies away
before we could perform
any pathology.
Did you note any cadaveric
heat rigor or stiffening?
Quite a bit offexion
in the limbs.
How doyou know
so much about it?
l did my residency
in forensic medicine.
ln your opinion
could those burns have been
caused by ionizing radiation?
Well, l hadn't thought.
l suppose it's possible
ifthe exposure
was sufficiently intense.
Let's say those men died
from radiation exposure.
Couldn't it have been
from the cracked core
ofa nuclearwarhead?
l've read about
these kinds ofburns.
So have l--
in Hiroshima at ground zero.
l'm talking about
close encounter mortalities.
l have a stack ofX-Files
reporting the same results.
l don't claim to know
all the answers
but ifwe don't make
the O.P.R. inquest
by tomorrow morning
there may not be
any more X-Files.
(moaning)
Start an l.V. here, stat.
Mulder:
Tell us what happened.
Whatever happened
has nothing to do with you.
Wrong, Colonel.
We want the same thing,
onlyyou want it dead.
Can'tyou see that
chasing it down
leaves it no choice
but to defend itself?
How many more have to die before
you rethinkyour approach?
Listen to me
'cause l'm not wasting
another breath on this.
lfyou and your partner
aren't out ofhere
in 30 seconds...
Agent Scully stays here.
We're undermanned,
she's a doctor-- she stays.
lfthat's okay.
Ofcourse.
lfyou don't mind
youjust take care ofmy men
and let me do mywork.
Outside this emergency room
you can do whateveryou want
but in here l call the shots--
assuming, ofcourse
you want me to take care
ofyour men.
Get this man
out ofmy sight.
Where do l scrub up?
Max.
Hey, Max.
Hey... Max.
Who are... who areyou?
Max, it's me, Fox Mulder.
You okay?
What areyou doing here?
You were having
some kind ofseizure.
Seizure?
That's impossible.
You were lying on the foor
unconscious, convulsing.
That's odd.
l haven't had an episode
in seven years--
not since l went on medication.
Let's getyou to the hospital.
No.
l mean, l mean
it's not necessary.
You sure?
Yeah. l lived with epilepsy
all my life.
l'm not in any danger.
Yeah, it started
in South Dakota
when l was ten.
The doctor said l must
have incurred a head injury.
l don't remember
ever hitting my head.
You have no memory
ofyour seizures?
As a kid l used to wake up
in strange places
with no idea where l was
or how l got there.
(sighs)
Sorry. l...
l got to,
l got to go to sleep.
All right.
(sighing)
Rough night, huh?
lt was terrible.
We lost all but two
and they're still
in critical condition
on theirway
to the burn unit
atJohns Hopkins.
So what doyou think, Scully?
What's going on out there?
l don't know, and under
other circumstances
l would like to find out
but we have a plane to catch
injust over an hour.
l wantyou to take
a look at something first.
What?
Max.
There's an unusual incision
behind his left ear.
l've seen this incision
twice before.
Two women--
a thousand miles apart
no way ofknowing each other,
no relation.
both claim to have been
abducted by aliens.
areyou saying Max Fenig
is an abductee?
Mulder
the man is taking
powerful antipsychotic drugs.
l saw them in his R.V.
They're for his epilepsy.
Dilantin is an anti-convulsant
but Mellaril is used exclusively
to treat schizophrenia.
More than likely,
Max is delusional.
You don't seem
to understand, Scully.
Max doesn't believe
he was abducted by aliens.
l believe he was.
Now, could you at least
take a look at the scar
and give meyour
medical opinion?
Okay.
You pack.
l'll take a look at Max
on the way to the airport.
Sir, l have fash traffic
at 24-1 8.
Repeated calls for l.D.
go unanswered
and it's not in the orbital
or sub-orbital inventory.
24-1 8--
isn't that where..?
Same exact spot, sir
though l am reading
a much larger craft.
Meteor, Ms. Koretz.
A much larger meteor, sir.
Hold on a second.
We have a confirm.
Whitmarsh Air Force Base
is tracking.
Where is it?
Well, sir, the meteor
seems to be hovering
over a small town
in eastern Wisconsin.
Come on, Mulder,
let's get this overwith.
Hey, Max.
Max.
Max?
Hey, Max.
Mulder, look at this.
Mulder:
What is that? Blood?
Man:Falcon Patrol
reporting unidentifiedtrespass.
Repeat. Falcon Patrolreporting
unidentifiedtrespass
at the waterfront
Mulder!
Come on.
Where doyou think
you're going?
lfwe go to the airport now,
we might make the plane
which would giveyou
halfa chance
ofdefending yourself.
Think about it.
Max is a gypsy,
nomad, right?
Yes. So what?
He intercepted
Wright's last call
to his dispatcher
which means he was here
in Townsend, Wisconsin
the night ofthe crash.
Ofall the places he could
have been, he was here.
lf Max
was abducted
that would go
a long way
to explaining
his obsessions.
lfwe figure that out, you
can be sure Henderson has.
Doyou have the keys?
(panting)
Don't do this.
Sir, we've apprehended
the target, a civilian.
Negative, Falcon patrol.
Take him
with extreme caution.
They're dead.
(Max groaning)
Max:
lt hurts. Stop.
Why? Why? Why?
lt hurts.
Max?
Stop. lt hurts.
lt hurts. lt hurts.
lt's all right.
Stop it!
...lt hurts.
No, no, it's me they...
They're coming for me.
No, l know that...
that's why they're here.
They're coming for me.
(helicopterwhirring)
lt hurts.
(moaning)
Alpha team, secure the roof.
Hold it right there!
Putyour hands up
and come with us!
Alpha team, ready on the roof.
Roger, Alpha.
Delta team, report.
Delta team in position, sir.
What areyou doing?
You have a very sick man
in there.
We're not in the hospital now,
Dr. Scully.
Omega team, report.
He's a delusional
schizophrenic.
Keep her clear.
Sir, this is Alpha team leader.
l'm picking up three forms
inside the structure.
Henderson:
Did you say
three forms?
That's affirmative.
Two are proximate
the third approaching
from 40 meters.
All teams prepare for go
in 30 seconds.
Come on. Come on, Max.
Why... stop. Why...
l'm here to helpyou.
l'm scared.
l know.
Don't let them take me.
Mulder:
l won't let them takeyou.
Come on, Max.
Come with me.
No!
Max!
Sir, this is Alpha team leader.
Except for our men
l'm only picking up
one figure inside.
l do not copy that.
We indicate only one figure
inside the building.
What?
Soldier:
Blow the door!
Take him!
(soldiers chattering)
That's your unit, sir.
Where is he?
He's gone.
They got to him first.
They beat us, Colonel.
Arrest him.
And keep looking.
Agent Scully
to the best ofyour knowledge,
was Agent Mulder ever assigned
to investigate matters
related to the evacuation
ofTownsend, Wisconsin?
No, sir.
At any time
wereyou aware ofhis
submitting a Form 302
requesting said assignment
or travel expenses?
No, sir.
While in Wisconsin
did Agent Mulder drive
a blue Ford Taurus
registered to
the State Car rental agency?
Yes, sir.
Thankyou,
Agent Scully.
Sir, request permission
to make a statement.
Request denied.
Sir, it's unfair tojudge Mulder
by the same criteria...
You're dismissed.
But, sir...
That will be all.
You hear that noise,
Scully?
Hammer and nails.
They're building a gallows
in the town square.
Don't worry.
lt was
only a matter oftime.
l'm surprised
l lasted this long.
Good luck.
l'll break a leg.
McGrath: ...as well as
insubordination and misconduct.
How doyou respond to
these allegations, Agent Mulder?
Over a dozen men
lost their lives
and you want me to respond
to issues ofprotocol?
You failed to obtain proper
authorization foryour actions.
l knew it wouldn't
be forthcoming.
You also violated
a Federal quarant...
A cover-up was underway...
Exposing yourself
and possibly others
to toxic contamination!
Oh, toxic contamination.
Are we back in that?
You read my report.
Explain Max Fenig's
disappearance.
Your report is not the subject
ofthis inquiry.
X rays taken while Mr. Fenig
was institutionalized
showed an object
lodged in his cerebellum.
That is irrelevant,
Agent Mulder.
The man was abducted.
Everybody in this room knows it.
Colonel Henderson's
written testimony states
that Fenig's body
was found two hours later
in a cargo container.
Then what can l say?
How can l disprove lies
that are stamped
with an official seal?
That will be all,
Mr. Mulder.
(sighing)
You can deny all the things
l've seen
all the things l've discovered,
but not for much longer
'cause too many know
what's happening out there
and no one,
no government agency
hasjurisdiction
over the truth.
Why did you countermand
our decision?
Mulder's conduct
was in clearviolation
not only of Bureau procedures,
but of Federal Law.
Yes.
l don't understand.
The committee's case
was airtight.
You've ruined the last
best chance we had
to get rid ofhim.
l appreciate
your frustration
butyou and l both know
that Mulder's work--
his, uh... singular passion--
poses a most unique dilemma
but his occasional
insubordination
is in the end
far less dangerous.
With respect, sir--
less dangerous than what?
Than having him exposed
to the wrong people--
what he knows...
what he thinks he knows.
(sighing)
Always keepyour friends
close, Mr. McGrath
but keepyour enemies closer.