Woman: What's she doing
there by herself?
Man:
Teena?
Honey?
You're freezing.
Where's yourjacket?
Where's your daddy?
In theyard.
He told me he needed
some time to himself.
I'd say his time's up.
Come on, honey.
I'm sure he wouldn't
wantyou to catch cold.
joel?
Hey,Joel,
the swing set's supposed to be
foryour daughter, not foryou.
( screams )
I'll call 91 1 .
Daddy?
Death by hypovolemia
75% blood loss.
That's over four liters
ofblood.
You could say
the man was running on empty.
The man's daughter,
eightyears old
was away from his side
no more than ten minutes.
She doesn't remember anything.
No trace evidence
at the scene.
Any evidence would have been
washed away byyesterday's rain.
There were two small
puncture wounds
in thejugular.
Areyou at all familiar
with the phenomenon
ofcattle mutilations?
Hmm?
Since 1 967, over 34 states
have reported unsolved cases
ofcattle mutilations.
( projectorhumming )
The trace evidence
is remarkably similar.
Incision marks
ofsurgical precision.
The area around the mouth,
and, often, the sexual organs
has been removed.
There's a substantial degree
ofblood loss
without a trace
ofblood.
How can that be?
Exsanguination.
Ifyou stick a needle
in thejugular
ofany living creature
the heart itselfacts as a pump.
These animals
had theirjugulars punctured
the same as that man,
only this is the first time
i've seen it on a human being.
But there was no struggle.
How can a manjust sit through
a bloodletting?
The M.E. found
traces ofdigitalis--
a South American plant that can
be used as a paralytic drug.
These X Files indicate this
is a U.F.O.-related phenomena.
Often, there are sightings
in the sky near the incident,
surface burns...
Witnesses often report
time loss.
We've seen this
in abduction cases.
That might explain why
she can't remember anything.
Mulder, whywould alien beings
travel light-years to earth
in order to play doctor
on cattle?
For the same reason
we cut up frogs and monkeys.
Besides...
they seem to have stepped up
their interest.
Her mother passed away from
ovarian cancer twoyears ago.
There's no other family.
We'll keep Teena here until we can
place herwith a foster family.
Has she spoken about it?
No, not a word.
Any nightmares?
No. At least,
not that I know of.
Can we talk to her now?
Yes.
Teena?
These are the people
we talked about.
This is Miss Scully
and Mr. Mulder.
Doyou think
you can talk to them?
Okay.
Hi.
I knowyou must
be feeling
very sad right now
and scared
but we want to find out
what happened
so we can help stop
whoever hurt
your daddy, okay?
Did you ever see
any strangers
with your daddy at home?
Did you ever see anyone
yell atyour daddy
oryour daddyyell at them?
No.
Can you think ofanyone
who might want
to hurtyour daddy?
No.
That's a nice bunny, Teena.
Can we talk about
what happened that day?
About what happened
in the backyard?
You remember any strange sounds
or lights
or anything like that?
There was red lightning.
Can you
tell me more
about the red lightning?
I can't remember.
It all went dark.
Haveyou ever seen
anything like that before?
You have?
When?
The men from the clouds.
Theywere after my dad.
( telephonerings )
Scully.
Whywere these men
afteryour dad?
Theywanted to exsanguinate him.
Mulder.
What?
There's been another one.
It's like looking
at a mirror image.
The victim, Reardon,
was married with one daughter.
Cause ofdeath: hypovolemia.
Mulder, this is uncanny.
They also found traces
ofthe poison, digitalis.
Puncture wound?
Uh... yes.
On thejugular.
The time ofdeath was estimated
at 2:30 p.m.
Same day,
only three hours earlier
than the Simmons murder.
That's Pacific Standard Time.
That makes it
the exact same moment.
It appears as ifwe
have two serial killers
working in tandem.
No, serial killers
rarelywork in pairs
and when they do
they kill together,
not separately.
Mulder, nothing beyond
your leading questions
to Teena Simmons
substantiates
a U.F.O. mutilation theory.
Was Reardon's daughter
here when he was murdered?
Uh... yes.
The police report states
that she remembers nothing.
She's with her mother
and family in Sacramento.
When will they be back?
Tomorrow.
Even money, she'll
remember red lightning.
( footsteps approaching )
( screaming )
Teena?
Teena!
She was kidnapped from
the social services home
around 1 1 :00 p.m.
Iast night.
Looks like someone
was afraid
she might remember too much.
Someone
or something, Scully.
Connecticut state troopers
set up roadblocks
within a halfan hour.
Nothing.
Maybe theyweren't looking
in the right direction.
I told them to contact us
in case they find her.
Teena?
No.
What's your name?
Cindy Reardon.
Doyou live here, Cindy?
Ever since I was born,
eightyears ago.
Help!
( whimpers )
(yelling )
Whew!
This is the ceremonial signing
ofthe bill
which is now known as...
and forever forward
from this point on, known as...
Cindy really is
a beautiful little girl,
Mrs. Reardon.
Doug and I wanted
to spoil her.
We wanted to protect her
from everything horrible
in the world.
She was Daddy's
little girl.
Is she an only child?
May I ask... was Cindy adopted?
No.
I gave birth to her
at San Rafael General.
So I assumeyou have
all the proper
documentation--
birth certificate...
Ofcourse I do.
Was she the only child
delivered at that birth?
What the hell kind
ofquestion is that?
Look, I have told the police
everything I know.
Mrs. Reardon, haveyou ever
seen this man before?
Is this
your suspect?
No.
Did he do something
to Cindy?
No, he...
No, Mrs. Reardon.
This is notyour daughter.
That girl's name
is Teena Simmons.
She lives in Greenwich,
Connecticut.
That man-- her father--
was killed in the same
manner as your husband.
Cindy is my daughter.
I can showyou videos
ofher birth.
We tried for sixyears
to become pregnant.
In vitro fertilization?
At which clinic?
The Luther Stapes Center
down in San Francisco.
Mulder:
Thanks.
Scully: Doyoustillbelieve
this is U.F. O.-related?
Cindy Reardon didn't see
red lightning.
The only thing similar
about these girls
does seem to be
their appearance.
There is
the random possibility
that two people can have
an unrelated likeness.
Who bothjust happen to see
their fathers exsanguinated.
I'd like to get the odds on that
in Vegas.
The girls are
the one and only link
between identical murders.
And one girl wasjust abducted.
Kidnapped.
* Po-ta-to, po-tah-to... *
Where areyou going?
Ifthe murders were committed
by the same person
part ofthe pattern involves
kidnapping the daughter.
You'd expect
the pattern to continue.
I'm going to watch the girl.
You check out the clinic.
See ifthe Simmons
were enrolled.
I'll call
the San Francisco bureau
and get someone
to relieveyou.
Okay.
Dr. Katz:
During vitro fertilization
we canimplementfertilization
andimplantation
ofthe embryo
in the uterus.
Could a patient believe
she was receiving her own egg
but actually receive another
without her knowledge?
Not here.
We have very strict
controls.
Areyou aware ofever
having patients
named Claudia
andJoel Simmons?
That's confidential.
It's our policy.
Both the Simmons are dead
and their daughter
has been kidnapped.
I'd say any information you have
that could help
would overrideyour policy.
You had copies
oftheir records transferred
to Greenwich, Connecticut
in 1 991 .
They came here nineyears ago
under the supervision
ofa Dr. Sally Kendrick?
Is there a problem?
Dr. Kendrickwas nothing
but a problem.
Hello, and welcome
to the Luther Stapes Center
for reproductive medicine.
I'm Dr. Sally Kendrick
a specialist
in the exciting field
ofin vitro fertilization...
She was a resident here in 1 985.
Brilliant.
First in her class at Yale Med
where she got her M.D.
after completing
her doctorate in biogenetics.
Oh, we were thrilled to get her.
And nowyou don't sound
so thrilled.
We have reason to believe
that Dr. Kendrick
was tampering
with genetic material
offertilized ova in the lab
prior to implant--
experimenting
with eugenics.
Did you report this
to the A.M.A.?
Ofcourse.
I fired her
and requested an investigation
from the health department.
And what happened?
The A.M.A. censured her.
My request for
an investigation was denied.
...atLutherStapes...
Dr. Kendrick... disappeared.
Weknowthepain ofinfertility,
andweare readytohelp.
In the next halfhour
I'll guideyou
through our l.V.F. program...
Scully: Kendrick supervised
the Reardons'
and Simmons' l.V.F. program.
It seems she experimented
at the clinic.
Mulder: And maybe now she's
trying to erase the results?
I wish that we could guarantee
everyone success
but with
our scientific advances
a little luck,
and a lot ofhope
miracles can happen.
Well, she must have
had an accomplice
in order to have done
both murders.
Soyou think this is a vendetta
that she and a colleague have
against
the Stapes Center?
Haveyou abandoned
your U.F.O. connection?
( phonerings )
Hello?
just a couple clicks.
Must be
the wrong number.
I'll tell you what...
I'm going to sleep on it
and we'll talk about it
in the morning.
Mulder, you're rushing me
out ofthe room.
No, I'm not.
Doyou have a girl
coming over?
What's a girl?
I got a movie
to watch on TV.
Sleep tight.
Seeyou in the morning.
Areyou certain
she hasn't followed you?
What areyou doing here?
Well, I thought we might
take in a Warriors game.
No. Actually, I was
just in the neighborhood
and, uh...
wondered if
I had ever told you
about the Litchfield
experiments.
Hmm... no, you haven't.
Well, it was a most...
interesting project.
Highest level
ofclassification.
All records have since
been destroyed.
And those who knew ofit
will deny knowledge
ofits existence.
In the early '50s
during the height
ofthe Cold War
we got wind
that the Russians
were fooling around
with eugenics--
rather primitively,
I might add--
trying to crossbreed
their top scientists,
athletes--
you name it--
to come up with
the superior soldier.
Naturally, wejumped
on thebandwagon.
Mulder:
the Litchfieldexperiment.
Deep Throat: A group of
geneticallycontrolledchildren
who were raisedandmonitored
ona compoundin Litchfield.
Theboys were called 'Adam"
andthegirls
were called "Eve. "
There'sa woman
youshouldsee
andl'llmakesure
thatyoucangetin.
Agents Mulder and Scully here
to see Eve 6.
Deposityour firearms.
Sign for these.
What are those?
Panic buttons.
Can't letyou inside
without one.
Thankyou.
Why the fashlight?
She screams and screams
ifwe turn the overheads on.
No one's ever got
a real good look at her.
We'll be right outside.
Mulder:
Hello?
So I guess you found
whatyou're looking for.
One ofus, at least.
Sally Kendrick.
Unlock the chains,
and then we'll talk.
They're probably there
for a good reason.
No. A bad reason.
I paid too much attention
to a guard.
I bit into his eyeball.
I meant it
as a sign ofaffection.
( laughs )
Areyou here to give me
an l.Q test, by any chance?
I think I can top 265.
We're very bright,
we Eves.
It runs
in the family.
Where are the others,
the Adams and the Eves?
We're prone to suicide.
All that's left is me...
and Eve 7.
She escaped early on.
And Eve 8.
She escaped ten years later.
Areyou Sally Kendrick?
That's not my name, but...
she is me, and I am her, and...
we are all together.
Scully:
Did you work
for the Luther Stapes Center for
reproductive medicine in 1 985?
In 1 985, I had been tied up
like this for twoyears
and forwhat reason?
No reason. I did nothing.
I'm just me.
They made me...
but did they suffer?
No. No, I suffer.
I suffer!
They keep me alive
for the Litchfield project.
They come in and they test me.
They poke me
to see what went wrong.
Sally knows what went wrong.
You and you--
you have 46 chromosomes.
The Adams, me, the Eves--
we have 56.
We have extra chromosomes.
Number four, five,
1 2, 1 6, and 22.
This replication ofchromosomes
also produces additional genes.
Heightened strength,
heightened intelligence...
Heightened psychosis.
Saved the best for last.
You don't believe me.
I have proof.
Look on mywall.
My family album.
Scully:
My God. It's the girls.
Eve 6: We were close.
We were very close.
Sally Kendrick
was using the clinic
to carry on
the Litchfield experiment.
She was cloning herself.
Cindy:
" Now I lay me down to sleep
"I pray the Lord my soul to keep
"ifl should die before I wake
I pray the Lord
my soul to take."
God bless
Grandma and Grampa Stenner
Irma and lrmapop
and God bless Mom
and please take care of Daddy
up in heaven.
You're such a special
little girl, Cindy.
Good night, honey.
If Eve 6 is right
then there are
two other Eves out there.
That could account for
the two identical murders
occurring at exactly
the same time.
Sally Kendrick does have
an accomplice. Herself.
Until I heard that,
I suspected the girls.
No, no. It seems
the two remaining Eves
are doing awaywith the parents
in order to keep Teena and Cindy
in the family.
Scully: Doyou suppose the girls
have any idea ofwhat they are?
I hope not.
Mulder, let's go!
I'll take the back.
( knocking )
There's someone upstairs.
Wait outside.
F.B.I.!
I'm armed!
Which one areyou?
Eve 7 or Eve 8?
Drop it.
You know I'm capable.
Slow. Very slow.
The suspect's name
is Sally Kendrick
early 40s, 5' 8",
1 35 pounds.
Now, she may have
an accomplice
similar in appearance.
Kendrick is driving
a light blue '93 Corolla.
She has exceptional strength
for her size.
Soyou must consider her
armed and dangerous.
Quite possibly she'll display
severe psychotic behavior.
The Oakland bureau is here
to orchestrate the search
across the bridge.
What if..?
What ifshe kills her?
First Doug, now Cindy?
The fact that Kendrick
and her accomplice
murdered the fathers
and abducted the girls
tells us that they
want them alive.
I'm sure Cindy's alive
and we'll find her.
And then what do we do?
I'm sorryyou have
to meet this way
but it's the best
for all concerned.
Teena Simmons,
meet Cindy Reardon.
Agent Scully? They found
the light blue Corolla
in the parking lot
ofSan Francisco
lnternational.
Start a check
on every single passenger list
for every fight
that left the terminal
within the past 1 2 hours.
Check every terminal
and make sure
she's not hiding out
for a later fight.
Remember, she may have
an accomplice.
A motel manager in Pt. Reyes
has a guest matching
Sally Kendrick's description.
We found the car
at the airport.
She might have ditched it.
The manager said this woman
checked in with a little girl
that she leaves in the afternoon
by herself, is gone all night
and returns with the girl.
The area is a place
full ofvacationing
families with kids.
This kid said to use chlorine
to eradicate the dinofagellates
in the swimming pool.
Sound like someoneyou know?
That's it.
I've always kept a close eye
on your behavior
no matterwhere I was.
The last fewyears
I spent in search
ofthe remaining Eve.
That, however, was cut short
byyour... activity.
I'd hoped mywork
at the Stapes Center
had corrected
the Litchfield faws.
Psychotic behavior
didn't develop
in the Adams and Eves
until age 1 6,
homicidal behavior at 20.
Imagine my... disappointment
when I learned
ofyour accelerated development.
How did you learn
ofeach other's existence?
Wejust knew.
Did you discuss
howyou would orchestrate
your little... prank?
Wejust knew.
Why murderyour fathers?
They weren't our fathers.
We have no parents.
We weren't born.
We were created.
You... You
cannot think that way.
You're human beings...
different, special...
butyou cannot give in
to genetic destiny.
That's why I've taken you.
I was raised by a man
who knew what I was.
He was a genetic engineer
on the project.
With the proper environment
and a program
oflong-term medication...
you can become like me.
And not
the other Eves.
( rattling )
Wh-What..? What haveyou done?
Your soda--
Four ounces offoxglove.
Extracted
from a digitalis plant.
This much is
a lethal dose.
We cultivated them
ourselves.
Wh-Why?
You tell us.
You made us.
Cindy:
We'reyour mistake.
I-l'll...
correct... that mistake.
Well, I waited
likeyou told me.
No one's come in or out
that I could tell.
( glassbreaking )
Get the back!
We were all supposed
to drink
but we only
pretended to drink it.
They tried to poison us.
Who's they?
She and another lady.
What did
the other lady look like?
Eve 8.
Theywere working together.
It's all right.
We'll take care ofyou.
You're safe with us.
It looks like
the Eves mixed
about four ounces
ofdigitalis
in each glass.
Their own mini-Jonestown.
Eve 6 said theywere prone
to suicide.
It has a sweet favor.
It's probably not even
perceptible in soda.
So far, there's no sign
ofthe other suspect.
We'll have an officer
take the girls back.
No, maybe it would be best
if we take responsibility
for the girls.
We can get them
checked out by a doctor.
Okay, whatever.
Okay.
Come on, girls.
We're going
to takeyou back.
Backwhere?
What's going
to happen to Teena?
We'll talk about it
in the car, okay?
They've already grown
so attached.
It will be hard
when Teena's placed
in foster care.
Agent Mulder, I have to
go to the bathroom.
Me too.
Can you hold it?
I really need to go.
I could use some caffeine.
Mulder:
Hi.
Where's your bathroom?
In the back. You'll need a key.
Thanks.
Oh, can I get four diet sodas?
- Regular.
All right. Two diet
and two regular. To go, please.
Thanks.
Tina:
AgentScully, my door'sstuck.
Scully:
Justasecond.
just a minute.
It's okay.
My dad will pay for them
when he gets out
ofthe bathroom.
Okay.
Those are the diet?
I think these are.
Areyou sure? It's really sweet.
Try it.
It's diet.
I saw her pour it.
Okay.
Scully:
Let's go.
Come on.
Don't forget the drinks.
Ah, the drinks.
How much?
Five dollars.
Okay.
Want to pay?
Sure.
Thereyou go.
You got those?
Thanks.
Mmm, tastes syrupy.
Cindy,
you didn't pick up my keys
offthe counter, did you?
No.
No? All right.
I'll be right back.
Scully!
What?
Scully...
just wanted to open
the car door foryou.
Mulder!
It's them. They poisoned it.
Let'sjust get them
in the car.
Okay.
I only had a sip.
We didn't drink enough
to make us sick.
Stop it!
Scully! I got them!
Leave me alone!
I got them!
Scully!
Hey!
What the hell areyou doing?
I'm a federal agent.
And these are
America's Most Wanted?
Hands in front.
Leave me alone!
Now let the girls go.
Get in the truck, girls.
I'll call the police.
We are the police!
Theywent that way.
You seen the twins we were with?
No, l...
There's a bunch ofschoolkids
just left
on that bus.
Forgetyour sodas?
We didn't do
anything wrong.
We'rejust
little girls.
That's the last thingyou are.
They said they have
an excellent program.
Mulder:
They can't hide
behind a bureaucracy,
Mrs. Reardon.
You have every right to know
what happened--
a right to know
aboutyour daughter.
All I need to know is
she was not my daughter.
She neverwas.
Hello, girls.
It's so nice to have company.
Sign for this.
Hello, Eve 8.
We've been waiting.
How did you know
I'd come foryou?
Wejust knew.