(Growls)
(Dull Pop)
(Slow, Heavy Breathing)
(Snapping And Cracking)
Eugene?
Eugene, it's Dr. Monte.
Eugene, areyou asleep?
- No.
- I was on myway out
and I wanted
to see howyou were feeling.
Fine.
Good.
You nervous about tomorrow?
Don't be.
I knowyou think
theywon't letyou out
so I snuck a peek
at the reports ofthe doctors
that will testify
atyour review tomorrow
and they concurwith my opinion that
you're ready to be released from here
and rejoin the community.
So...
why don't we get some sleep
and relax
and I'll seeyou tomorrow
at the review, okay?
Let'sjust keep
our fingers crossed.
Agent Scully.
We have reviewed your reports,
and frankly, we are quite displeased.
Irregular procedure,
untenable evidence
inconclusive findings
aggravated byvague opinion.
But, sir, the very nature
ofthe X-files cases
often precludes
orthodox investigation.
Areyou suggesting the Bureau adopt
separate standards foryou and Mulder?
- No, sir.
- You suggesting Mulder obstructs
you from proper procedure?
No, sir. Ifanything,
I'm suggesting
that these cases be reviewed
with... an open mind.
Maybeyour mind
has become too open.
On X-files cases investigated by
Agent Mulder and myselfto date
we have a conviction
or case solution of75%.
That's well above
current Bureau standard.
And that is
your only saving grace.
May I ask, sir,
what moreyou require?
What I require
is increased frequency
ofreports
conventional investigation.
In short, Agent Scully,
it is your responsibility
to see that these cases
are by the book.
I understand. However...
conventional investigation
ofthese cases
may decrease rate ofsuccess.
(Gavel Pounding)
judge:
By order ofthe State of Maryland
the Court shall review
the psychological status
of Eugene VictorTooms.
We'll begin with the court-appointed
expert witnesses.
Court calls
Dr. Pamela Karetzky.
I performed several
diagnostic procedures on Mr. Tooms
in order to determine any
organic physiological dysfunction--
an electroencephalogram,
chromosomal analysis
a computerized axial tomograph.
All ofthese were negative.
" Mr. Tooms
had recently lost hisjob.
" Parenthesis: Baltimore animal
regulation/dog catcher.
Close parenthesis.
"Aggravated by a false arrest
incident with the F.B.I.,
"his assault on Agent Scullywas
'frustration directed
at the wrong person."'
I'm reading
from a recent interview
I did with Mr. Tooms
at the Druid Hill Sanitarium.
"Question: lfyou are released
"what is the first thing
you would do?
"Answer: I'd like my oldjob back.
"Question: Why?
"Answer: The animal shelter
"made me feel
I was helping everyone--
people and animals."
So, you see, what is occurring here
is that Mr. Tooms has learned
to articulate his feelings
and invest his emotional energy
towards creative
and constructive activity...
(No Audio)
...in himself.
It is my opinion that Mr. Tooms
has had a very excellent response
to the months
oftreatment and therapy.
I would see no reason
why he would be considered
ofany danger
to himselfor society.
Woman: ...is the truth, the
whole truth and nothing but the truth?
I do.
Mr. Mulder, as an expert witness
for the State of Maryland,
can you listyour qualifications?
I'm a special agent
with the F.B.I.
I worked for threeyears
at the F.B.I.'s behavioral science unit
profiling serial killers.
Your Honor, I know where
he's going with this.
May I remind the Court Mr. Tooms
was placed in psychiatric care
solely for the assault
on Agent Scully.
He has never been charged, nor has any
evidence linked him to any other crime.
judge:
Proceed... with caution.
Myers:
Agent Mulder, I understand
thatyou've developed
a profile on Mr. Tooms.
- Yes, I have.
- Please.
These murders
span nearly a century.
1 9 homicides-- five occurring
every 30 years since 1 903
all in the Baltimore area.
In each case,
the liverwas extracted
and presumably eaten.
A trophywas taken from each victim,
many ofwhich were found
in the living quarters of Eugene Tooms
at 66 Exeter Street.
Records show that a Eugene Tooms
has resided
at that same address
since 1 903--
the sameyear a man was murdered
in that building.
The most notable element
connecting these cases
is the undetermined
point ofentry.
Manyvictims were found
with theirwindows and doors
locked from the inside.
These fingerprints found
at seven ofthe 1 9 crime scenes
match Eugene VictorTooms.
Agent Mulder,
look at his fingers.
- Look at him. 1 00 years old?
- I contend that perhaps
through a genetic mutation
Tooms is capable ofcontorting
and elongating his body
to gain access to victims
so he may extract the livers
which provide him sustenance
for the hibernation period
of30 years.
He needs one more victim
to complete this cycle.
A preliminary exam
revealed abnormalities
in his stride, muscles,
and axial bones.
His attorney
blocked further study.
- I askyou to place the safety...
- No further questions.
This is a rare and abnormal human
creature who should not be released.
- You may step down.
- Ifyou release Eugene Tooms,
he will kill again.
It's in his genetic makeup.
Would they have taken me more seriously
ifl wore the grey suit?
Mulder, your testimony--
you sounded--
I don't care how it sounded,
as long as it was the truth.
And where wereyou?
Your testimonywas important.
I was called into a meeting
byAssistant Director Skinner.
What did he want?
just wanted to reel me in.
They're ready.
It is the opinion ofthis Court
that Eugene VictorTooms
shall on this day be released
from the Druid Hill Sanitarium.
Court also attaches
these conditions:
One, that he remain in counseling
under the care of Dr. Aaron Monte--
that he may retain hisjob at the
Baltimore Regulations Animal Shelter
and last, he take residence
in the house of Mr. and Mrs. Arlan Green
trained in a program to assist
patients released from Druid Hill
in their transition to society.
Mr. Tooms?
Doyou understand
and accept these conditions?
Yes, Your Honor.
Verywell. You're free to go.
I'm not taking
my eyes offhim.
He'll kill again first chance he can,
but he won't kill the old couple.
Tooms didn't remain a secret
for 1 00 years by not being careful.
Think ofhim as an animal. He kills
out ofnecessity or self-defense.
Ifhe makes an attempt,
I'll be there.
I'll keep surveillance with you.
Ifhe can't be tied
to recent evidence
go to the earlier murders
to prove it was him.
That was 30 or 60 years ago.
There's no statute oflimitation
on murder.
That's going to entail
unorthodox methods
ofinvestigation.
Ifyou're resistant
becauseyou don't believe
I'll respect that,
but ifyou're resistant
because ofbureaucratic pressure,
they've not only reeled you in
they've skinned you.
(Door Opening)
Arlan:
I hopeyou'll be comfortable, Eugene.
The room in
the back is small
but I'm sureyou'll
be able to squeeze in.
Tooms:
I'm sure.
(Growling And Snarling)
Excuse me.
Could you help me find my dog?
He's a Norwegian elkhound.
His name is Heinrich.
I use him to hunt moose.
IfTooms gets away now
then the next time
he takes a life
you'll be nearly my age.
Detective Briggs,
you helped us so much before.
Now we have to prove
that Tooms was involved
in the killings
you investigated 30 years ago.
You've lived with this case
halfyour life.
There must be something.
Maybe a connection
between the victims.
Now, I know that we've seen
all ofthe evidence
but is there anything,
anything at all
amongst the evidence
that does not fit?
There was something
that never did sit
quite right with me.
All ofthe victims
that I investigated in '63
were found at the crime scene,
liver extracted.
All five.
As were the four
most recent murders.
When I was a sheriff
during the Powhatan Mills
killings of 1 933
only four ofthe victims
were found at the crime scene.
However,
there was a fifth person
who was missing
and never found
but this--
this was discovered
at the Ruxton Chemical Plant
when it was under construction.
But it doesn't belong
to the othervictims.
That doesn't prove it belongs
to a person murdered byTooms.
I'm positive
Tooms hid this one victim
because something about the body
could prove he was the killer.
- What makes you positive?
- A hunch.
An old-fashioned hunch.
You've got to trust
your instincts.
And what does your instinct say
about where Tooms
buried the body?
In the cement where
they poured the foundation
ofthe chemical plant.
(MachineryWhirring)
Scully:
Ground-penetrating radar.
It bounces signals off
ofobjects or cavities.
Tells you
where the body is.
Well, it signals ifsomething
inordinate is present.
An experienced operator
attempts to differentiate
ifthe signal is a body
or a stone or a hole in the ground.
- Differentiate.
- Mm-hmm.
You mean he guesses.
Well, it's an educated guess.
Mm-hmm.
How are we doing?
Well, it's really
hard to tell.
It's here.
Here!
What is it?
It's here!
It's right here!
(Deep Breath)
(Jackhammer Hammering)
Agent Scully!
Look at this.
(Computer Keyboard Clicking)
Woman:
Robotoddler's finally sleeping.
I'm gonna watch TV in bed.
Okay.
(Vehicle Approaching)
(Baby Crying)
I'm coming, honey.
Mommy's right here.
Shh, shh.
Screw it.
(Grunts)
(Knocking)
Christine:
Honey, would you go down and get that?
(Sighs)
F.B.I.
- I suspect an intruder in your house.
- What?
Someone opened mywindow.
I suspect theyear ofdeath
to be in the mid-1 930s.
Anterior surface
ofthe right femurwas green
indicating a long-term exposure
to copper
so we concentrated on the area
and we found several pennies.
1 933, '31 , 1 933.
Can you determine
cause ofdeath?
My instinct says
that burial in cement is murder.
Uh, no. At the moment
I have found
no definite proofofmurder.
There are gnawing marks
near the ribs.
However, I suspect that's
the result ofrodent activity
prior to the body
being set in the cement.
We need to see much more ofthe remains
to determine cause ofdeath.
As you know, it's a slow,
but necessary process.
I did try
a little something.
It's a little premature
ifwe're going by the book.
Well, we'll keep it
offthe record.
Good. Thankyou.
The old man, Mr. Briggs,
he gave me a photo
ofthe missing person in '33
suspected ofbeing a murdervictim.
I ran a computer-assisted
photographic superimposition
on what we have ofthe skull.
This is not official
but that skeleton
was that person.
It's not enough.
It doesn't tie it to Tooms.
Well, it's a start.
Mulder, it's getting a bit ripe
in here, don'tyou think?
(Sniffs)
(Plastic Wrapper Crinkling)
Pine scented.
(Sniffs)
Whew!
Better?
Tooms hasn't come out
ofthe house all day.
I sat through a Phillies game,
an Orioles game and four hours
of Ba-Ba-Booey.
When it got dark,
I took a walk around the block.
Doyou have that sandwich
I asked you to bring?
It's liverwurst.
Ha-ha.
Mulder, you know
that proper surveillance
requires two pairs ofagents-- one pair
relieving the other after 1 2 hours.
Article 30, paragraph 8.7?
This isn't about doing it
by the book.
This is aboutyou
not having slept for three days.
You're going to get sloppy
and you're going to get hurt.
A request for other agents
to stake out Tooms would be denied.
Well, then I'll stay here.
You go home.
(Sighs)
They're out to put an end
to the X-files, Scully.
I don't know why,
but any excuse will do.
I don't really care
about my record
butyou'd be in trouble
just sitting in this car
and I'd hate to seeyou carry
an official reprimand
in your career file
because ofme.
- Fox.
- (Chuckles)
And l... I even made my parents
call me Mulder.
So... Mulder.
Mulder, I wouldn't put myself
on the line for anybody butyou.
Ifthere's an iced tea
in that bag, could be love.
Must be fate, Mulder.
Root beer.
You're delirious.
Go home and get some sleep.
Here. Take my sandwich.
I only had one bite.
You're going to want it later.
And call me ifanything happens,
immediately. I'll be here.
Oh, and 1 1 :30,
station 790--
Pete Rose Late Night
Sports Talk radio show.
Wouldn't miss it
for the world.
(Car Starts)
It has worked, hasn't it?
You'll be all right now.
I know it's worked!
(Screams)
Yeah, they found him
out cold in the street.
He's been beaten up
pretty badly.
Contusions,
multiple lacerations.
Shoulder's been pulled
right out ofjoint.
Let's get him prepped
for some blood work and X rays.
Orderly:
Yes, Doctor.
He's been kicked
in thejaw
and it may be fractured.
Look, there's
a partial shoe print.
I want to get a photo ofthat.
We might be able to find
the shoe that matches it later.
Doyou know
who did this toyou?
(Whispering)
We'll be right back,
Mr. Tooms.
Says it was an F.B.I. agent
named Mulder.
So would you say he's delusional
orjust schizophrenic?
Well, it'sjust a cursory exam,
but there's nothing to indicate that.
(Grunts)
(Knocking)
(Sighs)
- Agent Mulder?
- Yeah.
What's going on?
What's this about?
Agent Mulder, getyour things.
You're in some trouble.
These are serious allegations.
The evidence is incriminating.
A good forensic scientist would know
there is not only a shoe print
but also an impact point
ofa foot from inside the shoe.
An analysis ofTooms' injurywould show
that my foot was not inside the shoe.
Areyou suggesting
Tooms is framing you?
- Ofcourse.
- Ifyou were engaged in an unauthorized
surveillance ofTooms
how could he gain access
toyour shoe withoutyou seeing him?
Sir? I was engaged
in the unauthorized surveillance
as well
and Agent Mulder
was orienting me
on the situation at the time
Tooms was admitted into the hospital.
Agent Mulder could not have done it
because he was with me.
Agent Scully, you wouldn't
be lying to me, would you?
Sir, I would expectyou
to place the same trust
in me as I do in you.
Agent Scully, may I have a word
with Agent Mulder, please?
Fox...
you are one ofthe finest,
most unique agents
in the nearly 60-year history
ofthis institution.
I mean, we were talking aboutyou
when you were in the academy.
Now, most ofus feel thatyour talents
are wasted on the X-files
but we respect thatyou're
deeply invested in those areas.
But ifthese cases
are creating such stress
as to cause not onlyyou
to act inappropriately
but those agents
close toyou as well
then may I adviseyou
to step away... for a while?
Clearyour head,
take an extended vacation.
That's a good idea.
Thanks foryour concern.
You're forbidden
to go near Eugene Tooms.
Mulder...
this was close.
Any closer and a thousand friends at
the capitol won't be able to helpyou.
Scully:
These are Eugene Tooms' dental X rays
obtained from
the Druid Hills Sanitarium.
Your sandwich
gave me an idea.
Dr. Plith mentioned
he found gnawing
on the rib cage
near the location ofthe liver.
Further excavation revealed
more pronounced bite marks--
human teeth marks.
Tooms will nevervoluntarily submit
to a dental cast.
This software can create
an exact three-dimensional model
ofTooms' mouth
from the dental radiograph.
We've also mapped out
the bite marks
on the skeleton's rib,
there.
They match.
(Knocking)
- Eugene, Dr. Monte.
- Hi, Eugene.
I wanted to see
how everything was going.
Arlan: Susan and I
are going out for the evening.
Thanks.
Great place.
Wonderful place.
How areyou feeling?
Why the newspapers strips,
Eugene?
Areyou making
some paper-mache?
- Yes.
- That's terrific.
Wonderful. I had no idea
you were interested in art.
I like art.
I do too,
and I'm very proud ofyou.
You know, art can provide a window
toyour thoughts and your feelings.
What areyou doing,
Eugene?
Eugene, areyou all right?
(Dr. Monte Screaming)
That makes five.
- He's building his nest.
A 30-year hibernation.
- Where would he go?
Where he's gone for the last 90 years:
66 Exeter Street.
- No, they tore down that
apartment building he lived in.
- What's there now?
Mulder:
Thanks.
He's got to be here.
Ifhe is drawn to this location
for some reason
maybe this nest is in the approximate
location ofthe previous nest.
This is the area.
There's a storage facility
on the second foor.
What?
Scully:
There's only room for one.
You can get
the next mutant.
Mulder!
(Growling)
Here. Take my hand!
Come on.
You can reach it! Mulder!
Mulder, what's happening?
Quick!
(Growling)
(Screaming)
You read this report?
Doyou believe them?
Ofcourse I do.
Okay. Let's go.
It's amazing how
things change, isn't it?
The caterpillar?
No. A change for us.
It's coming.
How doyou know?
A hunch.