( loudrumbling )
The kids.
Boy:
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Kevin.
( Yelling )
( KevinScreaming )
Mom! Ruby's gone!
Ruby?
Ruby!
Blevins:
AgentMulder's latest302
requesting assignment
and travel expenses
for the both ofyou.
Sioux City, lowa.
That's the first
l've heard ofit.
lt came up through channels
from Mulder's ASAC
to the district G-1 4
and onto my desk.
l don't understand.
ln essence, Mulder
is petitioning the bureau
to assign a case number
to a tabloid headline.
He must have
more evidence than...
Not according to his 302.
l admit, that is strange...
even for Mulder.
Perhaps it has something
to do with this.
Take a look.
An X file?
Has he shared
any ofthis with you?
There's no need
to protect him.
He's the agent ofrecord.
He initiated the file himself.
She was his sister.
She disappeared 21 years ago.
He was 1 2 and she was eight.
He claims that he was
in the room when it happened.
He recalls a bright light
outside the window
and, uh... and a presence
in the room.
ln your opinion
has Agent Mulder's
personal agenda
clouded
his professional judgment?
ln my opinion, no.
Butyou can see how
it might appear that way.
As you know,
Agent Mulder's preoccupation
with fringe matters
has been a big source
offriction in the Bureau.
This is another case in point.
l'm going to disallow the 302.
With respect, sir,
at least let me talkwith him
and make a recommendation.
ltjust doesn't seem...
substantial enough
to warrant an investigation.
Okay, Scully, so we disagree.
lt's not the first time,
and it won't be the last.
At least ifwe had
a legitimate source...
This is the essence
ofscience.
You ask an impertinent question
and you're on yourway
to a pertinent answer.
What makes this case
any more credible
than the hundred-year-old mother
with the lizard baby?
Because the lizard baby
wasn't born anywhere near
Lake Okobogee.
- Oko-what?
- Bogee.
Okobogee.
ls that supposed
to mean something to me?
lfyou know anything
about trout fishing
or U.F.O. hot spots.
Define hot spot.
Four sightings
in 1 967, August
including one by a National
Weather Service plane.
This is a light-blasted,
digitally enhanced enlargement.
The pilot took that photograph?
Try a Girl Scout
with an lnstamatic.
Four ofthe nine girls in the troop
claim to have seen something.
Five, ifyou include
the den mother.
The air force said it was a weather
balloon caught in a wind shear
but there wasn't
a weather balloon
launched that day
within 700 miles.
Read me the names of
those Girl Scouts from 1 967.
Lisa Terrel, Bonnie Winston,
Doreen Mccallister, Darlene Mor--
lt's the same
Darlene Morris.
Ms. Darlene Morris?
l'm Agent Scully,
and this is Agent Fox Mulder.
We talked with you
on the phone last night.
Please, come in.
Well, l knew that ifl screamed
loud and long enough
that someone
would listen
but l never expected
the F.B.l.
Uh, this is Kevin.
Kevin, say hi.
Would you like
some coffee?
Mmm.
Some days, l can't even...
get myselfup out ofbed
and... Kevin has been acting
so strange.
l don't know what to do anymore.
l just want her back again.
Ms. Morris
during the divorce,
was there a custody battle?
Charles had nothing
to do with this.
How can you be so sure?
Because l know what happened.
lt'sjust like it was before.
Summer of 1 967?
The Girl Scout troop?
- How did you know?
- Your name's on record
at the Center For U.F.O. Studies
in Evanston, lllinois.
Really?
Yeah, a pilot
for the National Weather Service
made a sighting over
the same area on the same day.
They took her,
didn't they, Mr. Mulder?
You said that Kevin was there
the night it happened?
He didn't see anything.
He was asleep.
Doyou think l might
talk to him anyway?
- Mmm.
- Thanks.
You know...
l've told the story
so many times now...
Oh, to the newspapers
and the police...
And every time l tell it
people get this look
in their eye
just like the look
thatyou've got
right now.
Hey, buddy.
You mind ifl sit down?
Thanks.
Your mom tells me
you've been having nightmares.
l guess so.
- You want to tell me about them?
- No.
All right.
What areyou doing?
You making something?
Can l take a look at it?
Thanks.
lt's coming from there.
The TV?
l don't know what it is.
May be a binary sequence ofsome kind.
Could be anything,
could be nothing.
l knowyou're busy.
Look, l know a friend
who knows a friend
who can getyou a ticket
to a Redskins game.
You got it. All right.
You know where to find me?
Thanks, Danny.
As l was telling your partner,
we found no evidence ofkidnap.
No phone call, no ransom note
and since we didn't
turn up a body...
You assumed
she ran away.
Well, it wouldn't be the first time
Ruby Morris ran away from home.
How doyou explain
what her mother saw?
l think that Darlene
has a very active imagination.
l've been listening to those
stories since the first grade.
So, basically,
you ignored her statement.
l included it in my report.
Butyou didn't bother
to check it out.
We went out to the campsite.
We didn't find anything.
Darlene's little girl
was no prom queen.
l can't count the number oftimes
l pulled her out ofparked cars
or found her puking her guts out
by the side ofthe road.
lt wasjust
a matter oftime before...
Before what?
Before something bad
happened to her
and if Darlene needs to make up
crazy stories to get past that, fine,
but don't tell me
to treat it as the truth.
l'm not going to waste my time.
l just think
it's a good idea
not to antagonize
local law enforcement.
Who? Me?
l'm Mr. Congeniality.
You never know. We might need
his help one ofthese days.
l'll send him a bundt cake.
You're looking
for Ruby, right?
That's right.
Who areyou?
lt doesn't matter.
Areyou a friend of Ruby's?
Ruby didn't have friends.
Shejust had people
she liked to hang with.
And she liked
to hang out with you?
l guess we had some times.
Like the night she disappeared?
lt was Greg. She was
supposed to see him that night.
Who's Greg?
Her boyfriend,
Greg Randall.
Theywere supposed to meet
up at the lake.
They had stuffto talk about.
What kind ofstuff?
Greg got Ruby pregnant.
l don't know, whatever,
she got herselfpregnant.
Doyou know what they
were planning to do about it?
Theywere going to leave town.
At least, that's what Ruby told me.
You know Greg from school?
Greg? School?
l don't think so.
All he ever did
since we met him
was pour beer
at the Pennsylvania Pub.
Excuse me.
- Doyou know where
we could find Greg Randall?
- Who's asking?
What kind oftrouble's
he got himselfinto now?
Actually, we were hoping
you could tell us.
Greg called in sick
three weeks ago, man.
l haven't seen
or heard from him since.
Any ideas where
he might have gone?
No, but ifyou find him,
tell him he's fired.
This is the hotel we'll be staying at
ifyou hear ofanything.
That's a nice tattoo.
What is that?
What's it look like?
A fying saucer.
You don't really believe
in that stuff, doyou?
l take ityou don't?
No, l think it's all
just a bunch ofcrazy people
howling at the moon.
So, you haven't been out
to Lake Okobogee, haveyou?
No, l haven't. Why?
You should ride with us
sometime.
You might see some things
that will changeyour mind.
Get a killer sunburn
in the middle ofthe night.
Where's Mulder?
Where did you get
the document?
lfyou explain whatyou're talking
about, maybe l can helpyou out.
This is a document?
just looks like a bunch
ofones and zeroes to me.
- Tell me whereyou got it.
- Tell me what it is.
Keep playing games
l'll haul your ass
up in front ofthe D-6.
You can explain to them
whatyou're doing obstructingjustice.
lt's your call, Holtzman.
Unless they tell me
otherwise
l'm not accountable to anybody
outside my subcommittee.
l don't care ifit's the N.S.A.
or the Vatican Police.
lt's a defense satellite
transmission.
You're kidding.
just a fragment,
but highly classified.
We need to know
where it came from.
Well, sure, l'll letyou know
as soon as l find out.
That's it, Mulder.
Youjust boughtyourself
a one-way back to Washington.
We got it.
Great.
What?
You shouldn't have told them.
They have nojurisdiction.
Mulder, they're N.S.A.
They think the boy may be
a threat to national security.
How can an eight-year-old boy
who can barely multiply
be a threat
to national security?
People call me paranoid.
How did Kevin obtain
top-secret information?
Where doyou think
he got it from?
lt's okay, baby.
Don't worry.
- lt will be okay.
- Agent: Come with me, son.
Mom!
lt will be all right, baby.
You guys do
really delicate work.
- Let's get this to Cryptography.
- Let's go.
Thinkwe got what we needed.
Thankyou.
What is it?
l'm not sure.
We scanned all 77 pages
through the mainframe.
And none ofthe information
is actionable.
Other than
the satellite transmission
nothing can be construed
as a security risk.
The boy's being released
this afternoon.
So it wasjust a random set
ofones and zeroes?
On the contrary,
there was nothing random about it.
l don't understand.
All information
can be rendered digitally
in a series ofones and zeroes.
When we downloaded the data,
we found an amazing range...
Well, see foryourself.
Da Vinci's UniversalMan.
A DNA double helix.
There's lots more.
( ClassicalMusic Playing )
- That's from the Brandenberg Concertos.
- But they'rejust fragments.
A few notes here and there
some lines from the Koran,
a Shakespearian sonnet...
Almost like someone
switching channels, huh?
- Mrs. Morris...
- l have nothing to say toyou.
Mrs. Morris, please,
give me a minute to explain.
Would you pleasejust wait
right over there for Mama?
l'll be right there.
l thoughtyou were both
here to help us.
Scully:
This has been a terrible mistake
and l assureyou
that the government
will pay for all damages.
l don't wantyour money.
l want my daughter back
and l wantyou
to leave us alone.
Butyour son has seen something.
You stay away from me,
and you stay away from my child.
Come on, honey.
lt's okay.
Let's go now.
l thought we were
headed back into town.
Where are we going?
The boy's the key, Scully.
l know it.
The key to what?
Finding Ruby.
Think about it
for a minute.
This is a boywho is
receiving digitized data
from a television screen.
Agent Atsumi said it was
a statistical aberration.
- No.
- Okay, l admit it's not much
ofan explanation...
Kevin is a conduit
ofsome kind.
A conduit.
A link or a connection
to whoever...
orwhatever took Ruby
that night.
But how?
lfthere was an abduction
it's likely that Kevin
was touched in some way.
Mulder, l know
whatyou're thinking.
l know why
this is so important toyou.
l know.
But there is no evidence
indicating an abduction.
That's whywe're going
to Lake Okobogee.
According
to the police photos
Ruby and Kevin
were sleeping right here.
just a stone's throw
from the forest wall.
Meaning what?
Meaning anybody could have
come out ofthe forest to grab her.
Haveyou noticed
the tree line?
Evidence ofextreme heat.
Or an electrical storm.
Besides which,
there's nothing
to connect it to the night
of Ruby's disappearance.
That's true.
Doyou think a lightning strike
could have caused this?
Doyou have any idea at what temperature
sand solidifies into glass?
2,500 degrees fahrenheit.
Something was out here,
Scully--
something hot enough
to turn sand into glass
to singe those trees
and to blister the roof
ofthat camper.
( Whispering: )
Mulder...
look.
What is it?
lt's a grave.
Shallow, by the smell ofit.
Mulder, what areyou doing?
Mulder, you are disturbing
a crime scene.
Stop!
What ifit's her?
l need to know.
You okay, Mulder?
l'm fine.
Looks like a male caucasian.
Sir.
Victim's name
was Greg Randall.
Ruby's boyfriend.
Ruby had a lot ofboyfriends.
Beforeyou put that away,
can l look at it?
Go right ahead.
Look at that.
That's her--
the girl from the library.
Who?
We didn't get her name, but she claimed
Greg and Ruby had run offtogether.
Doc Fowler's
a buddy ofmine.
Delivered both my kids.
l can find out
who had that appointment.
Scully:
Have a seat, Tessa.
We know thatyou lied to us
the other day.
We know thatyou
had the appointment
with Dr. Fowler
on August 7.
We know thatyou're the one
that's pregnant, not Ruby.
You don't know nothing, doyou?
We can prove it, Tessa
and we can prove
that Greg was the father.
So what ifhe was the father?
This is very serious.
Doyou understand
how serious this is?
Now, you've waived
the right to an attorney.
So ifyou lie to us here today
you could be charged
with perjury.
He promised me we'd be in L.A.
by Christmas.
He had
a friend there.
And l'd never seen the ocean.
You said that he and Ruby
were seeing each other.
You said that theywere planning
to meet at the lake.
ls that true?
l was nowhere near
the lake that night, okay?
Sureyou were, Tessa.
You knew theywere meeting, soyou
sat there and you waited for them.
You were angry
and you werejealous.
- l wasn't.
- You sat there and you waited.
When they showed, you killed him first.
lsn't that how it went?
- No.
- You snuck up from behind him
and you shot him in the back.
Bam!
And then you killed Ruby.
What was she doing right
before she died, Tessa?
Was she pleading
for her life?
Was she running away?
- l didn't kill her!
- Where's she buried?
- l don't know!
- You don't know where
you buried her, Tessa?
- l didn't kill her!
- You didn't?
She wasn't even there
that night!
Well, how would you
know that, Tessa
ifyou weren't
thereyourself?
Mulder, you're not seeing
the whole picture.
- Which is?
- ln all likelihood, Ruby is dead.
ls thatyour conclusion
or the conclusion
ofthe Sioux City
Sheriffs Department?
They're searching
the national park
and a rescue dive team is coming in
from Des Moines to drag the lake.
They're wasting their time.
Doyou really thinkTessa Sears
is telling the truth?
Why not? What if Ruby
never did show up that night?
She lied to us in the library
and about her pregnancy.
What makes you think she wouldn't
lie to us about killing Ruby?
Because something was
out there in those woods.
We have a suspect in custody.
We have a confession
to one murder
and we have a statement which speaks
to the intent to commit another.
lt's over, Mulder.
lt's time to go home and turn this
over to local law enforcement.
l can't do that.
- Mulder, where areyou going?
- To talk to the boy.
Darlene won't even
letyou in the door.
Well, l've got to see him.
They don't want to have
anything to do with us.
Stop running afteryour sister.
This won't bring her back.
Come with me,
or don't come with me
but until they find a body,
l'm not giving up on that girl.
- ( Knocking )
- Hello?
Mrs. Morris?
Kevin?
( Teapot Whistling )
Mulder?
What does it mean?
l don't know.
l'm going to check upstairs.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
just come up here.
Look.
lt's her.
lt's Ruby.
This is a long shot.
They could be anywhere.
You know, when l was a kid
l had this ritual.
l'd close my eyes
before l walked into my room
because l thought that, one day, when
l opened them my sisterwould be there
just lying in bed,
like nothing ever happened.
You know, l'm still
walking into that room...
every day ofmy life.
Scully!
Darlene!
Look. There's
a trail head.
( WomanScreaming )
( Panting )
- Areyou okay?
- lt's here.
- l saw it.
- Where's Kevin?
- l couldn't keep up with him.
- Go ahead.
Kevin!
- Areyou okay?
- She's back.
Kevin, l'm sorry, but...
She's here.
l know it.
Kevin, l don't
think she is.
l know how much you
wanted it to be her.
- l did too.
- Scully: Mulder!
Come on.
Scully!
Ruby!
She's unconscious,
but she's still alive.
l'll get help.
The nurse says she's been awake
for almost an hour.
Any ideas
what caused the coma?
There's no sign
ofhead trauma.
No narcotic traces,
or electrolyte abnormalities
except herwhite blood cell
count was sky-high.
Was there a reduction
in the lymphocyte population
or release
ofglucocorticoids?
Um...
Actually, both.
How did you know that?
They're symptoms ofprolonged
weightlessness.
Shuttle astronauts have reported
similar imbalances.
Hi, Ruby.
Who areyou?
We're with the F.B.l.
l'm Special Agent Dana Scully,
and this is Fox Mulder.
My mom said you might
be coming by.
How areyou feeling?
( Sighing )
Fine, l guess.
Where were
you, Ruby?
Can you tell us?
Kevin:
lt's okay, Ruby.
He knows.
l'm not supposed to tell.
They told me not to say.
Who told you?
Ruby, who told you?
Darlene:
Sweetheart,
you don't have
to say anything.
You're right.
We should wait till
Ruby gets a little stronger.
Could we speak outside
for a moment?
l think that it's best that
we put all ofthis behind us.
Hasn't Ruby been through
enough already?
l know how disoriented
she must seem right now
but in a couple ofweeks,
maybe even a few days...
l don't want her
talking toyou or anyone.
She should be encouraged
to tell her story.
lt's important thatyou let her.
lmportant to who?
l have my daughter back.
l don't want any more trouble.
Besides,
she hardly remembers anything.
She will remember one day,
even ifit's only in dreams.
And when she does, she's going
to need to talk about it.
Like l did?
Listen to me.
All ofmy life
l have been ridiculed
for speaking my mind.
But it was the truth, Darlene.
The truth has caused me
nothing but heartache.
l don't want
the same thing for her.
lt doesn't have to be
that way for Ruby.
As far as l'm concerned
she spent the last month on
the back ofa Harley-Davidson.
ls that whatyou're going
to tell Kevin?
l'm sorry.
Werber:
Butyour eyes are open?
Mulder:
Yeah, they're open.
But it's like nothing's
happening.
Try turning your head.
l can't.
Why not?
l don't know.
l can't move.
So l don't.
l just lie there in bed.
Can you seeyour sister?
No, but l can hear her.
What is she saying?
She's calling my name
over and over again.
She's crying out for help
but l can't help her.
l can't move.
Areyou scared?
l know l should be,
but l'm not.
Doyou know why?
Because ofthe voice.
- The voice?
- The voice in my head.
What's it telling you?
Not to be afraid.
lt's telling me that no harm
will come to her
and that, one day,
she'll return.
Doyou believe the voice?
l want to believe.