You all right?
Everything okay?
Allison,
everything okay?
It's so quiet.
Joe, say something.
Oh, my G, I can't hear.
Oh, my God,
I can't hear!
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
片名:Medium 第4季第4集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：卡萨
What are they saying?
We're not sure why.
She just woke up,
and, and she couldn't hear.
No, not a thing.
What are the]rsaying?
Wait.
No, never before.
Uh... no, no viral infection
that we're aware of.o.
No-no, no head trauma,
nothing like that.
It-it just... I don't know.
It just happened.
BRIDGETT
What's going on?
Why does it feel like
the middle of the night?
Paon me. Can you hold on
just one second?
It ithe middle of the night,
Brid,
and I'm on the phone
with the emergency room
and I really need you
to get back to bed.
Why's Daddy
Bed, bed.
Oh, really?
That would be great.
9:00 a.m.?
Absolutely.
We'll be there.
Thank you.
What did they say?
"...tests."
???
Oh, good.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, I don't think
we should say anythi
?wGto the girls
until we know more.
I love you.
I don't hear anything.
Your wife's hearg loss
is rather profound.
Let's go speak
in my office.
What is  saying?
I cahear anything!
Shh, shh, shh.
Okay.
DOCTOR:
I believe your wife
is suffering from something
called SSHL:
suddenensorineural
hearing loss.
It can be caused
by any number of things.
About, uh, 30% of the time,
people just wake up with it.
w, the good news is,
for most people,
the condition simply
goes away on its own.
But you're reasonably confident
that whatever it is,
whatever is causing it
is not a permanent condition?
(ringtone playing)
Sorry, that's my wife's phone.
Hello?
CYNTHIA:
Forgive meI'm looking
for Allison Dubois.
Have I dialed the wrong number?
No, no.
This is her husband Joe.
Can I ask who's calling?
My name is Cynthia Keener.
Your wife and I have been
doing some work together.
I wondered if I might
have a word with her, please.
To be honest, Cynta,
she woke up this morning
not feeling terribly well.
In fact, we're at the doctor's
right now.
Can I have her call you back?
One of us call you back?
Of course. Uh, please tell her
I hope she feels better.???
Sorry. You were saying?
You asked me
if this sort of hearing loss
is ever permanent.
And is it?
It can be.
But... we're a long way
from even thinking about that.
JOE: What's going on?
BRIDGETTE: What's all
the hollering about?
Hey, hey, are you
all right?
Mom, was that yo
This silence is so...
It's like somebody just put
a blanket over your head.
I felt like
I was going to forget
how to breathe.
And I thought maybe if I just...
scream!
Maybe I'll hear it.
Maybe it'll start something,
and I'll be okay,
but it didn't work.
Please don't
be scared, guys.
It's okay, Mom.
I know you're going
to get better.
What?!
Feel better, Mom.
Just don't scream.
It's scary.
Oh, I love you, too, babe.
???
What's that?
What are you doing?
I don't want to look
at anything on the computer.
THE GIRLS ARE IN BED
Cool!
Tell me something else.
KEENER CALLED NEED TO CALL HER BACK WHAT DO I SAY
I don't want her to know.
I don't want anyone to know.
Maybe you should just tell her
I have the flu.
How are you doing?
MAYBE A LITTLE LONELY
(moaning passionately):
Mmm...
Yeah.
Who are you talking to?
Hold on. Sorry.
Hold on one seco.
Cynthia Keener.
Who?
(shouting):
Kee-ner!
Yeah.
Okay, Miss Keener,
I'll, I'll pass everything
along to her.
Yeah, any information
that she gets,
I'll give it to you
right away.
Okay.
Okay. Hey.
(whistles)
Come...
"She has a case for you."
I thought you told her
I the flu.
"Kidnapping night before last.
12-year-old girl."
COMPLETELY DEAF.
???
JOE:
Nicole...
Swenson
is the
daughter of...
Of Laura and Darrin Swenson.
Daughter of
Laura and Darrin
Swenson.
Got it.
Laura's late husband
founded the Lyndhurst
Land and Lease Company.
You may have seen
thbillboards.
Okay.
She really can't hear
anything we're saying?
No.
No, she really can't.
Okay, well,
the, uh, Swensons'
family attorney
is an old friend of mine,
and he's hired me
to work the point
and negotiate
any and all discussions
with the kidnappers
as we work to get Nicole back.
What about the police?
We don't want
the police involved.
The family
was given very strict
instructions by the kidnappers.
Listen, I-I can't
do this anymore.
I've got to get back
to the Swensons.
How about I talk to you,
and you talk to her?
Okay.
So Allison says she saw the men
wearing masks.
That's what
she said, yeah.
Tell her
that's good.
that's very good.
That if, in fact, they're
purposely hiding their identity
from the girl,
it means they probably
don't want to kill her,
that they're ready
to hand her back alive
as soon as theget their money.
Okay.
Tell her also
that it's very useful
to know that they're
communicating in sign language.
Th would suggest
that it wasn't really
a crime of opportunity.
It was very
well planned.
They don't want to hurt r.
They, they just
want their money.
Okay.
All of this
will be very important
once we start our negotiations
with the
Thank you.
Mr. Dubois, uh, would you
please l me know
if Allison gets any more...
particulars?
Absolutely.
I've got to go
to the house now.
What did she say?
I feel a really bad case
of carpal tunnel coming on.
Testing.
Testing, testing.
But I don't understand.
I'm, I'm asking you
a simple question.
Well, please connect me
with somebody who can.
Watch your tone. Just...
Who's he talking to?
I'm on hold.
It's the insurance company.
Mr. Swenson, wou you
please hang up that phone.
When I'm finished.
We have a kidnapping
and ransom policy.
Now they're telling me
they won't give us theoney.
Well, of course not.
That not how insurance works.
They only reimburse after
the ransom has been paid.
Now, please, Mr. Swenson,
will you hang up that phone?
They can't help you.
The fewer people who knoabout
your daughter's kidnapping,
the better right now.
Come on.
Let's... Let's sit down.
I don't understand.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna do
whatever we need to do.
Now, I know this is difficult,
but you have to think about this
as a business
negotiation.
You haveomething
they want.
They have something
you want.
We want to resolve this
as quickly as possible
without anyone getting hurt.
But that's what I mean.
What they want, I don't have.
I don't have five
million dollars.
Not just lying around waing
to get thrown into a duffel bag.
We will find it.
We're, we're talking
to the banks.
We'll remortgage the house.
That's why we have Cyrus.
That is what he's
good at. Tell him.
Unfortunately, Darrin
has already given you
a fairly accurate assessment
of our situation.
With the banks...
With the mortgage...
I think the st cas
we can put together
before day's end
is somewhere in the neighborhood
of three to three
and a half million.
I mean, if I had more time...
We'll offer them three million.
Weren't you on the same
phone call that I was?
They want five.
We have three.
I don't believe
they're gonna find
a buyer who has more.
How can you be sure?
How can you be sure
that they won't do something...
awful?
???
I mean, there wouldn't
be an upside to it.
There's no profit
to be made from it.
For the men who took Nicole,
this is just a business venture.
They don't want this
thing to drag out,
and three million dollarC..
is an ful lot of money.
Now, when they call,
I'm gonna talk
to them.
Trust me.
This will work out.
MARIE:
Mommy.
Mommy. Mommy, Mommy, Mommy.
She can't hear you.
Come on. I'll
read you the book.
I want Mommy to read it.
But she can't. I'll
do it though, okay?
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Hey.
"Is your mama a llama?"
ARIEL:There we go.
MARIE:
Okay.
??? ALLISON:
Can I do that?
Okay.
"Is your mama a llama?"
You guys
are reading.
I can do that.
"'Is your mama a llama?'
"I asked my friend Dave.
"'No, she is not,' is
the answer Dave gave."
What are you doing?
You're calling Cindy?
You can't call anybody.
You're not gonna be
able to hear them.
Cynthia Keen. We have
to call Cynthia Keener.
Why?
It's the middle
of the night.
All ri Nev ???
The place where
the video was shot,
it had a very rustic
feeling to it.
like a... like a cabin
in the mountains.
AnI also saw
a glass, a water glass,
and on it was printed
the name of a local diner.
Well, I saw a video
about an hour ago,
but I didn'tsee any
Well, I'm not sure it was
actually in the video.
I think they realized...
you could see it.
One of the kidnappers
pulled it off the table
before they started cording.
It sd "Mano's Diner."
We looked it up online.
A Mano's Diner is in
the White Tank Mountains,
just outside of Phoenix.
The White Tank Mountains.
Hmm.
Well, that's the first
real clue we've had
since this whole
thing began.
Well, I mean, the glass
doesn't actually guarantee
that they're somewhere
near the diner.
ll, still,
it's a's a good start.
She's quite amazing.
(loudly):
Would you-- would you like
to stay with me today?
???
I would like for you
to stay with me today.
CYNTHIA:
Laura,
Darrin.
This is Allison.
Allison's an investigator
I work with.
She, uh, has reviewed
the ransom tape
and has some
pretty strong ideas
about where it might
have been shot.
Oh, my goodness.
Well,
it's, uh, it's not a certainty,
but Allison feels
that your daughter might be
in the White Tank Mountains
not far
from here.
Excellent.
So, uh, what do we do?
Well, I'm about to sqd
some people up there right now.
Uh, we're going to work
as many angles as possible,
gather as much
information as we can,
and continue to negotiate.
Thank you. It's, it's,
it's just such
a comfort...
Um, Allison is profoundly deaf.
It's one of the reasons she
feels such a strong connection
to Nicole
and why she's been working so
hard on this particular case.
I know we forfeit interest
by cashing in now,
but I need access
to those funds.
That could be them.
Is everyone ready?
Swenson resince.
(electronically altered):
Who is this?
Gentlemen,
this is Cynthia Keener,
just like the last time.
I need to talk to the Swensons.
I'm sorry.
Uh, I thought
I'd already
explained to you
that that's just
not going to happen.
We very much
want Nicole back
and, uh, we're very anxious
to get this whole thing moving,
but you are going to
have to deal with me.
And how can we be sure
you're not the police?
You're jusgoing to have
to take my word for it.
Again, all I'm interested in
is getting you your money
and getting the Swensons
their daughter bk.
Now, uh, we've seen your tape.
We believe you have her.
How do we move
this thing along?
You have the money?
We do.
$5 million?
Three, we have $3 million.
But the price is five.
Well, I understand
the price is five
and I'm lling you
all we have is three.
You justive us
Nicole back
and we'll give you
$3 million.
(whispering):
Tell them we'll give them
the money.
W-We'll figure out a way.
We just need a few more days.
No, no.
Gentlemen?
Gentlemen,
we-we're not hearing anything.
Gentlemen?
Five.
Three.
I'm offering you
what the Swensons have
and what they have
is $3 million.
Cash.
(phone clicks)
Hello?
ial tone)
They're gone.
You're fired.
Excuse me?
I told you.
We can get them
their money.
But we have no more time.
Every second that you
alw your daughter
to spend with
these people,
you put her further
and further in peril
Now, truste, they
want to make a deal.
They want to give you
your daughter back
and they want their money.
They want the
same thing you do.
$3 million or $5 million,
they want what you want:
they want this to be over.
Did you get
anything?
No.
They're going to call back.
How can you be so sure?
Well, like I told you before,
it's not as if there's
another buyer out there.
They're going to call back.
Well, I hope you're right.
I hope you know
what you're doing
because if anything happens
to our Nicole...
???
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN DEAF VERY LONG, HAVE YOU?
Swenson residence.
MAN (voice distorted):
We'll take the $3 million.
Get it ready.
(sighs)
(sobs)
It is ready.
Where do I meet you?
Not you. Have the father
bring us the money.
I'm sorry.
He's not available to do that.
I'll, uh,
I'll be bringing the money.
Well, then I'm sorry,
but his little girl won't be
available to be returned.
Either the father brings the
money or there's no exchange.
Listen tme...
No, listen to me.
I'll be calling back
with final instructions shortly.
At that time, I need
the father to bring the money.
I will be watching.
If the father is followed
by police, by you,
there'll be no exchange.
You'll find nothing.
You'll find no one
just the corpse.
Cyrus,
get the money ready.
I'm going to need an armed team
to follow Mr. Swenson
to the drop.
Lady, you follow me,
you order anybody
to follow me,
I'll come back here
and I'll kill you.
Mr. Swenson...
Or shall I kill
you now?!
Cyrus, where are we
with that money?
MR. SWENSON:
It's two hours.
What could be taking them
so long?
GIRLS IN BED LUV U GOODNIGHT
Mmm.
Oh, I'm not sure
if you've actually answered
the phone yet or not.
Actually, I'm not even sure
if the phone's finished ringing
yet or not.
I miss your voice.
I miss the girls' voices.
The sound of the house
in the morning.
The way that you sigh
when you roll over in bed.
Sorry I'm not there.
Honestly, I'm not really sure
what good I'm doing here.
???
I know that I am not easy.
But I do love you
and I hope you still love me.
Anyway, if you're there...
sweet dreams.
Sleep tight.
And know that I love you.
And if you're not there...
...sweet dreams.
Sleep tight.
And know that love you.
Hi.
Allison.
She saw one of them.
One of the kidnappers.
She can identify him
and he knows it.
They're going to have
to kill her now, aren't they?
Mrs. Swenson...
I need your help.
I need you to convince
your husband
to let me call
the police.
What, what are you
talking about?
They said no police.
That's...
that's what we agreed on.
That's what we promised.
I have new information.
???
It's her, isn't it?
You, you told us
her first name,
but you never told us
helast.
It's Dubois, isn't it?
What does she know?
She thinks your daughter
may be in serious danger.
Now, we havepeople
the White Tank area
for this cabin.
But with police help,
we have a much
better chance
of finding her.
??? changing the plan.
Are you insane?
We're almost there.
We're one call away
and now you want
to double-cross them?
Now u want to give
them a reason
to kill our little girl?
I fear they already
have a reason.
What are you talking about?
What is she talking about?
That's it.
I'm going to the bedroom.
I'm going to try and sleep.
And when
that phone rings,
I'm doing whatever
those people tell .
I'm going wherever
they want me to.
And I am bringing
my daughter ba.
Mrs. Swenson,
I beg of you.
Please let us
call the police.
Otherwise, I fear
we're compromising
your daughter's
safe return.
How dareou?
This is not your child.
This is our child.
Darrin, Darrin...
Mrs. Swenson,
ishis what
you want?
She's my baby.
I... I d... I don't know you.
I don't know
this woman.
They said no police.
And we'll be...
We're almost there, right?
We're almost there, honey.
Come on.
Let's go to bed.
They'll come for us
when the phone rings.
I heard...
u had a dream.
Maybe saw some,
some bad guys?
Want to go look
at some pictures
Maybe see if you
recognize anyone?
CYRUS:
Exactly three million.
One million a bag.
Thank you, Cyrus.
I don't understand
why it is taking them so long
to call back.
They like this.
Right.
They like
that wre anxious.
Mr. and Mrs.
Swenson...
omething I'd like
to propose to you.
I just got a phone call
from my office.
They have a small, electroc
portable beacon
that they can have
over here in ten minutes.
It's tiny.
It fits in the wheel well
of your car and...
it can give us your location
if anything should go wrong.
I can't risk it.
I won't risk it.
But, Mr. Swenson,
they'll never know it's there.
Looks like
it's a moot point.
I'll handle this from here.
Thank you.
Hello, this
is Nicole's father.
MAN (voice distorted):
Is the money ready?
Yes. It's ready.
It's completely ready.
Then it looks like you're going
to get your daughter back today.
Oh, thank God.
I need you to follow
my instructions precisely.
Do you have a pen and paper?
Yes. Yes, I'm ready.
Drive to Deer Valley Park.
At the corr of 19th and
Landale, y'll find a trash can
nearhe southernmost swing set
on the playground.
Okay.
Right on top will be
a white paper bag,
and in the white paper bag
you'll find a cell phone.
Okay. What then?
Mr. Swenson.
When you
retrieve
the white paper bag--
I'll give you gloves.
???
It may contain
forensic evidence
that will help us find
the men who did this.
Don't you understand?
I don't care
about the men who did this.
None of us care
I'm not going to that
garbage can wearing gloves.
What if they're
watching me?
No.
I just want my daughter back.
Oh... bring her back to me.
You bring her back to me.
You know I will.
It's almost over.
I can feel it.
Mrs. Swenson...
I'm so sorry
if me and my people
have made this
harder for you.
But, uh, quite
honestly,
I've never worked
with a man as...
determined
as your husband.
He just wants it over.
We... We just want it over.
I guess now
we just wait.
I'm going
for some air.
Keener.
We got a winner.
Pardon me?
She's looked through
six books of mug sho5v
and she finally found the guy.
If you've got a computer there,
I can e-mail him over to you.
That's terrific.
Is she sure?
Is she really sure?
You want to know she's sure,
hold on a second.
Cynthia, it's him.
CYNTHIA:
Do either of you
recognize this man?
No.
There is something
familiar about him.
His name is David Barrington.
???
Coincidentally,
Mrs. Swenson,
he worked for your husband
for several months last year.
Oh, my gosh.
Wait aute,
What...
What a you saying?
Are you saying
this is an inside job?
That someone who worked
fo husband betrayed him?
Maybe.
Maybe he still works for him.
Cynthia, I'm the one who
brought you in on this.
I've always been in
your corner, but now...
My husband was right about you.
What you're saying,
it doesn't make any sense.
Why? Whyould he hire someone
to kidnap his own stepdaughter?
I don't know.
Maybe he's planning
to use the ransom money--
minus what he's giving
to the kidnappers--
to cover all
the shortfalls at work.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
What-What shortfalls?
The coany is doing fine.
That's not what Cyrus told me
when he hired me.
He didn't want
you to know.
Since Darrin's been
running things,
he's taken a lot
more risks.
The company's accumulated
a grt deal of debt.
It-It still...
It doesn't make any sense.
???
For the moment.
Until you're reimbursed
through that insurance policy
he made sure you had.
My, uh...
My dad had a...
a hunting cabin...
in the mountains.
No one's
used it in...
in years.
He won't be there.
(sobbing):
You're-You're wrong.
You are so wrong.
Give me the address.
Let me prove you right.
Well, well.
The man with the plan.
Where is she?
She's in the other room.
She can't hear anything.
Yeah, let's get
this over with.
As promised,
one million dollars.
It's all there.
Hey, come on, man.
You know where I live.
Listen,
if I were you two?
I would get the hell
out of here now.
In fact,
I'll tell you what.
I'll wait ten minutes
before I go in and get Nicole.
That way there's absolutely
no chance she'll see you two.
Yeah, well, I wouldn't
worry about that.
She already has.
What are you talking about?
Well, it was a bit
of an accident.
Yo daughter hurt herself.
She screamed.
I ran inside, but...
I wasn't wearing my mask.
She saw your face?
Wait a second.
What are we going to do?
???
I told her aut you.
I told her how this
was all your doing.
Your idea.
Well, I didn't tell her.
Wrote it out.
How can you do this to me?
Do you know what this means?
This means I can't
take her home.
We dug you a hole out back.
Nicole...
I am so sorry.
Come on.
(screams)
(screaming)
Come on, Nicole.
Nicole! Stop it!
Just so you know...
it would give me
enormous pleasure
to put one of these
right between your eyes
and another through
the center of your chest.
Fine. Deny a woman
a little happiness.
NTHIA:
Mrs. Swenson?
There's someone here
who'd really like to see you.
Mom!
I love you.
(sobbing)
ARIEL:
No... Is Your Mama A Llama?
Can we read
about a giraffe?
MARIE:
No.
ARIEL:
Or... uh, the girl
in the forest?
MARIE:
No.
ARIEL:
Is your mama a llama?
Is my mama
a llama?
(gasps)
Is your mama
a llama?
(sighs)
Is your mam...is
your mama a llama?
No? Come here.
"'Is your mama
a llama?'"...
BOTH:
..."I asked my friend Dave."
"'No, she is not,' is
the answer Dave gave.
"She hangs
by her feet
"and she lives
in a cave.
I do not belie
that'sow llamas behave."
Mm.
Mom, can you hear?
Yeah.
Welcome back.
It's good to be back.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入