They say 40 is t new 3
And I say they're right.
I look young,I feel young,
and I act young, and frankly,
most men my age can't begin to keep up.
So where does a girl go?
Where does she go to
find suitable playmates?
Come on. I'm gonna show you.
Amy and I were suppose||to get
married right after graduation.
She'd already picked out
the dress,reserved the hall.
Everybody says that it
must have been her time...
but maybe it was the
drunk who hit her's time.
It's been five months.
I still can't sleep.
Don't really eat.
Don't really want to be with anybody.
Other than this group, I mean.
Five months without anybody?
This is actually too simple.
I hope that answers your question.
Completely.
Fold-down rear seats--
I'm gonna get some.
I think I forgot how
amazing that can be.
You want to do it again?
Now,this is the tough part.
Remember,the goal here is to love 'em
and leave 'em, not keep loving 'em.
I mean,how you going to move on
to your next young lover if...
you're still with the last?
So now that you got him where you want
him, the trick is to move in for the kill.
See,that's what really separates
the cougars from the pussycats.
You want to do it again?
- How about that?
- That's nice.
- Like this?
- Oh,yeah.
- That feels good.
- You like that?
- Yeah,that's good.
That's nice. Yeah,that's good.
Bad dream?
It was weird.
Just weird dream. Weird.
This woman, she was behaving like...
well,I don't know what
she was behaving like.
She kept trying to get
these young guys into bed,
and then when she was
through with them...
Actually,she was
behaving just like a man.
Okay. Sorry I asked.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Medium
Season04 Episode11
Girls,let's go. Breakfast time.
Ariel?
Don't do that. You do that too hard and
it'll go right through to your brain.
My ear's itchy.
I need your credit card for gas.
I've got a meeting with
Devalos this morning.
Police have not yet released
the name of the young man,
whose body was found early this
morning in the back of his SUV,
- which was in a downtown church parking lot.
- I'll be right back.I got to make a call.
Coroner's figuring he died
last night around 11:00.
You were right about his fiancÈe.
She was killed by a drunk
driver six months ago.
In fact,he was attending some kind of a
grief support meeting here at the church.
Well,did anyone see him leave with the woman
I described: tall, very beautiful,early 40s?
According to the others at the meeting,
no one there really fits that description.
I saw her as plain as day.
That's the thing,Allison.
Whoever did this,there's
nothing womanly about her.
It's pretty savage, kind
of bordering on butchery,
and it's hard to imagine a
woman of any age with the anger,
not to mention the strength, necessary
to hack this fellow up the way he was.
Come in.
Oh,sorry I'm late.
Hey,come on in,Allison.
You remember Ben, my campaign manager?
Ben Salzberg. Allison Dubois.
- We've met.
- I remember.
"Manuel Devalos. An
Instinct for Justice."
Well,you have my vote, Mr. Devalos.
There's one. Okay Here,I
want to show you something.
Mr. District Attorney, polls show Manuel Devalos is closing the gap on yourseven
- point lead.
Do you have any comment about what's
being called the "Manuel Momentum"?
The only person calling it the "Manuel
Momentum" is former District Attorney Devalos.
Now,I'll admit his numbers look impressive,
given his late entrance into the race,
but the citizens of Phoenix have
had enough of Manuel Devalos.
They know what baggage
he brings with him.
They know that when it comes to the
trying of fact in a court of law,
you don't go to a witch doctor or
a fortune-teller for legal counsel.
My intuition says the
voters aren't buying it.
Thank you very much. Excuse me.
Talk about "going negative."
I didn't bring you here to upset you.
Well,I appreciate that,sir.
Mutual admiration aside,we've
called you here,Mrs. Dubois,
because Manny has a very
important fund-raiser tomorrow.
Say no more.
I'll book a bus ticket
out of town if it'll help.
I thought you said she was a psychic.
You're misunderstanding, Allison.
I don't want you to stay away.
I want you there. Prominently.
I don't understand.
Manny's biggest problem and Van Dyke's
biggest asset is "the Allison question."
Who is Allison Dubois? Where is she?
If she's the real deal,
why is Manny hiding her?
We've come to the conclusion that the best answer
for the Allison question is Allison herself.
It's time for you to come
out of hiding,Mrs. Dubois.
"The answer to the Allison
question is Allison herself"?
He actually said that?
So what? So now we got
to go to this thing?
Well,what was I supposed to say?
I don't know. Tell
him we got a sick kid.
What?
What are kids for if not to be used as excuses
to get out of things that you don't want to do?
That's not funny.
That's not even a little funny.
If one of our girls gets sick now...
Oh,please,one of our kids
is not going to get sick now.
And it is too funny.
Be quiet. I'm not listening.I'm asleep.
No,you're laughing. You're
laughing on the inside.
I can't hear you. I'm in dreamland.
You want to keep your laughter
down,please? I'm trying to sleep.
You going to want something
else? It's last call.
No,thanks.
I guess I've been stood up.
Happens to the best of us.
You know,he may still show.
You got 20 minutes till closing.
There's no one coming here to meet me.
Fundamental truth: Hardworking young men
like the idea of seducing rich,older women.
They think it's easy.
They think we're desperate-- so desperate
we'll do whatever it takes to keep them happy.
Little does he know I only
want him for the night.
Glass ring,fake pearls.
He's a man.
He won't know the difference.
How's that treating you?
Good. Thanks.
It's my fault,you know, that he
thinks he can treat me this way.
I should never have bought him
that little sports car he wanted.
Now he thinks he can just leave me here sitting,
waiting for him all night in a restaurant.
He sounds like a fool.
A blind fool.
You're right. He is.
Look,I got to ask you something.
Well,go ahead. Hurry up.
Only got 19 minutes before closing.
How does a guy get to be
with a woman like you anyway?
He asks.
You're pretty amazing.
Pretty and amazing, yeah.
God did okay by you,too.
Hey,I'm gonna,uh, pour myself
a drink. You want something?
Whatever you're having,sure.
This one actually makes me a little sad.
He's so cute.
I could see myself spending more
than just one night with him.
But that would never work.
He thinks I actually have money.
Don't look so surprised.
Any cougar worth her salt knows
a thing or two about nails.
Hey,lover, you ever had your back
scratched by a woman who really knows how?
Oh,come on. Don't be such a baby.
You'll love it.
Careful.She just fell asleep.
I don't want to wake her.
Okay. Don't blame me.
Blame Dr. Friedman.
He's the one who's leaving town and told us
we've got to get to his office in half an hour.
Hey,how many times you
think we've made this trip?
I don't know,what?
The early morning ear
infection/antibiotic run? I don't know.
Together or separate...
Hey,what street was that?
24th,I think.
Let me use your phone. I've
got to call Detective Scanlon.
Detective Lee Scanlon, Phoenix PD.
I,uh,I got an anonymous tip|| there might have
been some trouble here in the restaurant last night.
Well,looks okay to me.
Okay,I give up.
Come on,Allison.
Hello? Lee,is that you?Hello?
Uh,I'm gonna... I'm
gonna call you back,okay?
What's going on?
**********
Victim's name is Ryan
Haas, 26 years old.
Been working at this restaurant
for four years as a bartender.
The manager said,uh, Ryan offered to
close up last night after his shift ended.
Didn't say anything about
him,uh,having a date.
Anyone remember the woman at the bar?
This place is kind of a pickup joint.
Ryan was a flirt.
The manager says there's always girls hanging
around the bar till closing, but no one they noticed.
Well,that doesn't make sense.
This woman is beautiful.
She was,uh... sexy.
She's not the kind of woman
who would go unnoticed.
Well,she did last night,
if she even exists.
What does that mean?
Allison,this guy was
killed with a nail gun.
So?
So how many women you
know have a nail gun?
Much less the strength to overpower
a 26-year-old man long enough
to drive a couple hundred six-penny
nails into his head, his neck,his chest...
This isn't about strength.
It's just like that guy that got
lured into the back of his van
and stabbed to death the other night.
She seduces them, she has sex with them,
and then when their defenses are down
and they're vulnerable, then she strikes.
I want to see that movie.
You know,I'm not even convinced
these two murders are related.
Well,they are.
So you're telling me that there's
a female serial killer out there,
picking up men and then murdering them.
That's what I'm saying.
I guess I should be grateful I'm
not out there on the prowl anymore.
Relax,stud. You're about ten
years too old for this black widow.
You look pretty.
Thanks,sugar. So do you.
Mama has to go out.
I don't want to, but I promised
someone I'd do something for them.
How do you feel?
It still hurts.
You know Daddy and Ariel and Bridgette are
all going to be here to take care of you,
and I'll be back home
before you know it,okay?
"I" before "E," except after "C."
Can't you just tell me how to spell it?
Uh,Dad,I think you're in trouble, 'cause
Mom's all dressed up and you're not.
No,honey. Daddy's staying home with you.
It's okay. You can take him if you want.
He's being kind of grouchy anyways.
You know,the whole point of "the kid is
sick" excuse is to get us both out of going.
Yeah,I'll remember that next time.
Hey,don't forget to wake her up at
9:30 for her last dose of medicine,okay?
Come on,grouchy.
Allison.
It's so great you're here.
Don't be silly. What a terrific turnout.
It's going very well, lots
of press,lots of donors,
a few big fish we still need to haul
into the boa|| And here comes Shamu now.
How are you?
Constance,I'm so pleased
you could make it.
Mr. District Attorney.
I don't see Richard.
Oh,he's running late.
Some business thing.
Constance,have you met Mrs. Dubois?
Allison Dubois,this is Constance Madsen.
Nice to meet you.
Oh,my... the famous Allison Dubois.
So tell me,what is my
fortune? What's in my future?
Oh,I feel strongly you and your husband are going to
make a significant contribution to Mr. Devalos' campaign.
Very clever,Mrs. Dubois.
Allison, Constance's husband, Richard,owns a
very successful construction firm here in Phoenix,
and they have been very
supportive over the years.
But then,I'm sure you knew that.
Oh,yes. I know everything.
Well,tell me, do you happen to know when
my husband is actually going to show up?
But the truth is, I did
not do it all myself.
I was privileged to work with a
dedicated group of police detectives,
and some of the most
talented ADAs in the country.
And as most of you now
know, I had a secret weapon.
Her name is Allison Dubois.
Allison worked for me as an investigator,
as a jury consultant and as a paralegal.
And it was her dedicated
service to the city of Phoenix
that was invaluable in helping to convict
and incarcerate a number of violent criminals.
So what does your crystal ball say?
Is he going to win this election?
I wish I knew.
I'm afraid I'm as much in the
dark as anybody on this subject.
Really? That doesn't seem fair.
I think it's the universe's
way of evening the score.
Connie!
There you are.
Sorry I'm late. What did I miss?
The speeches,the food, the champagne...
but let me introduce you to the
very best part of the evening.
Richard,this is Allison Dubois.
She's the psychic who was working
with Manuel all those years.
A-ha,how do you do?
Is this honestly the only way?
It's the only way for you.
You don't look happy,Richard.
You should be happy.
I know I'm happy.
Now,go.
Go to your little party for
Manuel Devalos and enjoy yourself.
And please write him a generous check.
She looked into the future and said that you
are going to write a big check for this campaign.
Well... we don't want to
make a liar out her,now do we?
Hey,stranger.
What time did you get in?
A little before midnight.
You two were dead to the world.
Yeah,well,this little one
was exhausted from screaming.
And me,I was exhausted from
trying to calm her down.
Poor thing.
Oh,I'm okay.
So what did I miss?
How was the fundraiser?
Did we raise a lot of funds?
Did we fund a lot of raises?
It was fine.
Well,actually, it was a little strange.
I was introduced to this friend
of Devalos',this big donor.
And the second I met him...
I knew something was wrong.
What do you mean "wrong"? Was he ill?
Something going to happen to him?
Not him,Devalos.
Something bad was going
to happen to Devalos.
What do you mean "bad"?
I don't know.
His friend was in cahoots with Van Dyke.
They were plotting against Devalos.
What do you mean?
Plotting against him how?
I don't know.
So you met this guy, and you
got a bad feeling about him.
Then what happened?
Well,then he wrote Devalos a big check.
Well,I'm no politico, but there must be a better
way to crush a campaign than by funding it.
So did you say something to him?
Well,say wh||?
The night seemed to be
going so well for him.
I didn't want to be the one to ruin it.
Especially since I don't know
what, if anything,is going on.
All right,we have 45 minutes
before the girls get up.
Oh,did you happen to see the note that
I left for you in the kitchen last night?
The message from Scanlon?
You know,I don't get it. I'm usually
persona non grata around here.
You know,you're sneaking
around to meet me, but today,
you're waiting for me by the front
door, escorting me up the elevator.
What can I tell you?
If I had my way,we'd pick you up in a limo,
offer you champagne and caviar for lunch.
You know,don't you worry if you lie
like that, your nose is going to grow?
Or God's going to
smite you or something?
Look,the honest to God truth is,
I got two dead 20-something guys who were
found exactly where you said they'd be,
murdered exactly the
way you said they'd be.
I need to get you with a sketch artist.
I know it sounds like a lot of nothing.
I just kind of felt funny
keeping it to myself.
Well,I don't know what
to tell you,Allison.
The man's check cleared.
Well,at the end of the day, I guess
that's all that really matters.
I'm being summoned.
Oh,well,then don't let me keep you.
You know,it meant a lot to me
that you were there last night,
and for what it's worth, your name
was mentioned in this morning's paper.
Well,then I guess it's
mission accomplished.
Mission accomplished.
I'll talk to you soon.
You know,it just doesn't make much
sense what she's saying, Mr. Devalos.
It just... doesn't.
Well,I grant you,it doesn't
make much sense to us.
No,it doesn't make much sense,period.
Why would Richard Madsen be having secret
meetings with District Attorney Van Dyke?
The man just donated a
truckload of money to you.
Well,then, you tell me.
What kind of deal could
they have been making?
Manny,listen to yourself.
You're becoming completely preoccupied
because some woman told you ...
Not some woman.
Allison Dubois. Do me a favor.
Just... keep your ear to the ground.
Okay.
Got your message.
Dispatch said you think you
may have spotted my suspect.
My partner and I got a call to
break up a fight in the parking lot.
We were finishing up in here with the owner,
and I saw someone that looked like your sketch.
She even has the coat.
Hello.
Sorry.
- Hello?
- Am I waking you?
No. It's okay.
I think I may have spotted your exterminating
angel, that woman you keep dreaming about?
She's here at a bar trolling
for guys half her age.
You're kidding.
No,Allison. It's 11:45.
I never kid after 10:00 on a weeknight.
So here's what I'm calling to find out.
You had any more dreams?
I mean,is this chick gonna pull a chainsaw out
of her purse or a jackhammer out of her underwear?
Is there anything I should
be on the lookout for?
I'm sorry. I don't know.
I haven't had a dreamt about
her in the last couple days.
Okay,well,I'm gonna take that as a good sign,
maybe introduce myself to this little lady,
see if I can get to the
bottom of this thing.
Okay.
- All right.
- Bye.
I no,uh, speaka da English
so... so good,yeah,no.
You speaka da English just fine.
Oh,pretty. Oh,yeah.Yeah.
Maybe,um, I-I teach
you Italiano later,huh?
Excuse me? Excuse me!Phoenix PD.
Ma'am,if I could ask you to please
step away from the gentleman.
Keep your hands where I can see them.
What's this all abou|| What's going on?
It's about her,sir. It's not about you.
If you could stand still and stay calm.
I am not from here. Are you policia?
Yeah. That's me.Policia.
Tell you what. Why don't
you hand me the purse?
Hand me the purse. Turn around.
Put your hands on the car. Turn around.
Put your hands on the car.
Uh,scuzi? Scuzi?
Says here,you're
Michelle Todd of Tucson.
Okay.
So,uh,is trying to impress a guy
in a bar against the law,Officer?
Maybe.
I think you're going to have
to come with me,Ms. Todd.
What? I'm just a girl
looking to have some fun.
- What's the crime?
- Murder.
Well,wait a second.
- What are you talking about?
- You ever had any contact with a Ryan Haas or Mr. Sean Covey?
Who?
Maybe you never asked them their names.
A support group widower in
need of a little comfort?
A bartender I suspect
you may have nailed?
- You have the right to remain silent...
- Wait.
Wait,wait. Wait a second.Wait a second!
A bartender? Support group widowers?
It sounds like you're talking
about my book. I have a...
Ma'am,let's not make
this difficult,okay?
No,no,look,look! Open my trunk.
It sounds like my book!
Open my trunk, and I'll show you!
All right,all right,all right.
If you take her for a second?
A Cougar's Guide to the Hunt: Bagging a
Man in the Urban Jungle by Charisma Kennedy.
Be nice. That's my pen name.
Look,flip it over.
Look,see?That's my picture.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
See,in there...in there... Under
the chapter headings-- look,see?
It's all there.
"Making the Connection
at a Support Group."
"Leaving More than a
Tip for the Bartender."
Nothing in here about cops,huh?
No. Why?
Tonight's your lucky night.
I'm going to take you downtown.
I hate you. It's barely
7:00 in the morning.
Hey,early bird,I thought you
wanted to catch this worm.
Well,where is she? I've
been here since 6:00.
Hold your horses. The
show is about to begin.
Here comes your dream girl now.
What do you think?
Well,that's her.
At least it looks like her.
What's the hesitation about?
I don't know. She looks so frightened.
Well,being charged with
murder will do that to you.
Hey,when you get a chance, if you have some
time, this is actually a pretty good read.
Every seduction you ever
dreamed of is in here.
The support group, the bartender.
It's quite uncanny.
What is this, a how-to
book for killing men?
Not killing them,
Allison. Seducing them.
Oh,you mean, there's no chapter in here
about the best way to nail-gun your man
after he's flambÈed you in the kitchen?
Maybe she's saving that for the sequel.
Let's go have a little chat.
You both understand how absurd this is.
I... Look at me!I-I...
I don't even know how to
use a knife or a nail gun.
I like men. In fact,I love them.
I've made a lot of money loving them.
How do you mean?
Well, as Charisma
Kennedy, I have the books.
I've written 12.
That one came out four months ago.
In fact,I'm still
doing the book signings.
Then there's Charisma
Kennedy, the column and blog.
Then as Michelle,I have The Single
Girl's Guide to Financial Independence.
And then as John Todd,I have The Single
Guy's Guide to Financial Independence.
I'm a busy little girl,
but I am no murderer.
Then why don't you just tell us where
you were on the nights in question?
Look,I don't mind
waiting for a couple hours
until your lawyer gets into his
office and we can get him down here.
No,really.
I don't have anything to hide. I...
It's just you're not
going to believe my alibi.
What do you mean?
Do you not remember what you were
doing on the nights in question?
I remember exactly what I was doing.
I was at home...
alone... reading.
I don't know.Based on
what I saw last night,
you don't strike me as the
"home alone reading" type.
Well,I am.
For the most part.
Sure,yeah,sometimes I have to go
out and see what's really going on.
Hear the latest lines.
Try a new technique.
Is there a law against a single
girl looking to have some fun?
You say that,but the fact
remains two men are dead.
Well,I had nothing to do with it!
I'm no killer.
Like I said,I love men!
But the fact remains two men have been murdered
using techniques eerily similar to not one,
but two chapters in your book.
Yeah,well,then, maybe it means
that your killer can read.
Look,I'm going to make this
simple for you,Ms. Todd.
If you can't provide us with an
alibi for the nights in question,
then I'm gonna have to exercise
my right to hold you for 24 hours
while I obtain a warrant
to search your apartment.
But that's not right!
Yeah,well... that's the law.
But don't worry.
I'll be sending a hot,young thing in
here in a minute to,uh,show you to a cell.
Come in.
Richard.
Come on in. Take a seat.
I'll just leave and
let you two catch up.
So,you want to tell me about it?
What... What are you
talking about,Manny?
I got a message to come
see you, and here I am.
It's your meeting. You want
an answer?Ask a question.
Okay,here's a question.
Did you know when I
was District Attorney,
that some concerns surfaced about
corruption in the construction sector?
No. I...I didn't know that.
Didn't get very far before I was
asked to take a permanent vacation.
But as it turns out, I still have some
friends in the District Attorney's office,
and recently, they've brought
some information to my attention.
Paying off city inspectors?
Bribing council members?
Van Dyke must have really
put the screws to you.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but this is a strange way to thank
a major contributor to your campaign.
Yeah. Right.
Thanks. So,how is that supposed to work?
I cash the check, and then Van Dyke
announces that he's indicting you?
And,oh,yes, isn't it funny that former
DA Manuel Devalos is taking money
from a city contractor under
investigation for corruption and fraud?
What did he promise you?
A suspended sentence, some kind of fine?
You're my friend,Manny.
Y-You've always been my friend. I...
I had no choice. I,uh...
I can't go to jail.
It was very strange.
On one hand I had these very vivid
dreams, in which she was always the one.
And then sitting across from her
today, my instincts told me I was wrong.
Well,for God's sake,
listen to your instincts.
Don't listen to your instincts.
Well,she's in jail tonight.
So,I guess it's up to the police
and the justice system now.
Why are you scratching your ear?
I don't know.
I'm hoping it's just a case
of the power of suggestion.
Hanging out with Marie all this
time, watching her scratch her ear.
Well,I hope you're right.
I will be very upset if I have to wake up early
in the morning and rush you to the pediatrician.
Right back at you.
Where you going?
I told you. I have a transport at 0800.
I'm shipping out to Germany for
a satellite operations assignment.
So... last night was it?
You turn me out and then you just leave?
Honey,we agreed.
No strings attached.
No seeing each other again.
Yeah,but that was before.
I mean,this is kind of new to me,but...
I don't want you to go.
I'll tell you what.
I'll give you something
special before I leave.
Something to remember me by.
Come here.
What are you doing?
You'll see. Give me your hand.
There you go.
Now the other.
Now close your eyes.
Lift your head.
They're bringing her up right now.
How is she?
Relieved. Upset.
Thrilled that she's starting
to look like she's not guilty.
Horrified that somebody's doing this.
I don't know what to tell you,Lee.
In my dreams,I saw her.
I saw her kill that man last night.
I saw her kill all those men.
Well,she definitely didn't kill
the guy you called about last night.
She's been under lock and
key for the past 24 hours.
Ms. Todd, I want to tell you that the Phoenix
Police Department extends its sincerest apologies.
So,that's it?
************
********
*********you are free to go.
You know, my book has sold
upwards of 60,000 copies.
Okay.
Well,it seems to me that means there are at
least 60,000 people who could be doing this.
Who could be using my book, my...
techniques, the scenarios I've
written to lure young men into bed.
Yeah,actually,I thought
about that myself.
Except I couldn't find the setup for
last night's killing anywhere in here.
- Really?
- Really.Here.
We know that the killer was
dressed up as a naval officer.
And there isn't any, anything
like that in the book.
A naval officer?
Oh,they told me they hated that one.
I'm sorry. Who told you they hated what?
My publisher.
It was one of the scenarios
that was cut from my book.
Uh,"Patriot Games" I think I called it.
Female naval officer.It's her
last night before shipping off
and she is going to spend it
sharing her bedroom secrets *******
Um,are there any others?
Sure.
I remember they couldn't wait to get
rid of "Naughty Nun with a Bad Habit."
It was like,who has a
nun's habit hanging around?
Oh,and then there's "The Extra Ticket."
Simple,but effective.
Very few men can resist the,the temptation of
accepting that extra ticket to "tonight's big game."
Of course,it's after the game
that the fun really begins.
And these techniques, these chapters that
were cut, who else might have seen them?
Sandra Marshall, my publisher,
and-and-and her staff. Yeah.
*******
Can I have the remote,please?
Thank you.
I'm here to speak with you today on behalf
of my client and friend,Richard Madsen.
Many of you know Richard.
- He built our new hospital downtown.
- What the hell is this?
He's currently hard at work
on our new arts complex.
His firm is also involved in the
upkeep of our bridges and roadways.
Also,Mr. Madsen is a major financial
supporter of my run for District Attorney,
which is why it saddened me earlier today
to learn that for the past several months,
Mr. Madsen's firm has been involved in
a series of payoffs to city officials
in order to secure contracts and approvals
his company might not otherwise have enjoyed.
Oh,my God.
My conscience...
it's been weighing on me.
So, I decided to talk
to my friend Manuel here,
who has advised me to throw
myself on the mercy of the court.
No! No,no,no,no,no!
Corruption in city government
is an insidious problem.
It cannot happen if it
is not allowed to happen.
Ladies,my name is Detective Lee Scanlon.
I'm sure you're all familiar with the recent series
of killings here in Phoenix targeting young,single men.
Well,we have reason to believe that these killings may
have been inspired by a book that you published here,
a book that all of you women worked on.
It's called A Cougar's Guide to the
Hunt: Bagging a Man in the Urban Jungle.
I'm sure you're all
familiar with it. Yeah?
Well,as part of our investigation,uh,
I'm going to need to know where each of you were on
the nights that each of these killings took place.
Then put it right five
times,Bridge, but...
Hello?
Allison. It's Lee.
I'm over here at Michelle's
publishing company.
I gotta tell you, it's
a complete strikeout.
Every single one of the women who worked
on this book has a rock-solid alibi.
Allison?
I don't know what to tell
you,Lee. I'm stumped,too.
Well,that's two of us.
Except I'm stumped and hungry.
Uh,I'm going to get out of
here.Call me if you need me.
Okay.
You work here?
No. Just visiting.
Are you an author?
Elliot Davis. This is my company.
Nice to meet you.
Are you from out of town?
You got that slightly dazed, "I'm
from out of town" look in your eye.
Do I?
You know what?If you're free,
I've got a couple of tickets
to the big game tonight.
I was supposed to go with a buddy
of mine, but he just cancelled.
We could grab some dinner.
Catch the game.Whatever.
Where should I pick you up?
What? You've never been
approached by a man before?
At my age,I don't get
approached much by anybody.
No,I don't believe that.
I mean,who doesn't appreciate
the company of young people?
But every now and then, it's nice to spend some
time with somebody who can carry on a conversation.
Ah,you'd be amazed at the number of
people, who otherwise would never...
yeah,they're at a vulnerable moment.
They're lonely. They're bored.
In a strange city.
It's just a basketball game.
I've been told I'm terrific company.
I promise you, I'm discreet.
In fact,I think I can safely say that no one who's
ever spent time with me has ever lived to regret it.
City detectives announced this
afternoon that publisher Elliot Davis
has been arrested and charged
with three counts of murder.
The 49-year-old Davis reportedly confessed
to luring three local men to their deaths,
using a book his company published that
advises older women how to seduce young men.
Michelle Todd,who goes by
the name Charisma Kennedy,
the author of A Cougar's
Guide to the Hunt,
was shocked to learn how her book
played a role in the murder spree...
Okay,quit moving.
I can't get this medicine in your ear.
Naturally,I'm shocked and
saddened that a book that
I wrote with the intention
of bringing pleasure
and-and hope to women of a certain age
would be used in such a perverse way.
I mean,it's obviously
a very effective book...
maybe too effective.
And what's next for you?
Well,ironically,this tragedy has brought
a lot of attention to the Cougar books.
I've gotten a number of calls from cable
networks about a Cougar reality show,
and maybe a Cougar Web site or a social
networking,uh,page like My Cougar.
And you know... I'm open to anything.
What is she saying? I can't hear.
I can't hear anything with all
this, this medicine in my ear.
Don't worry. You didn't miss a thing.