Distributor cap?
I wouldn't know a distributor
cap from a baseball cap.
Mom,a freaking mechanic!
It'sand my piece-of-crap
car won't start,
and all I want to know is
can I please use ur Tmber?
Without the lecture.
You know what,Mother? Never mind.
Someone's here. Someone more
useful than you right now.
bye.
Thank you for stopping.
You work at the yogurt place?
Car trouble?
Yeah. All I know is it won't start.
I don't know if it needs
a jump or a tow or...
Or a screw.
Excuse me?
Maybe you just need a screw tightened.
Sometimes,the rain,you
know,it loosens things.
Let me take a look at it.
Let cables.
********
******
but I don't thinkI'vebefore.
I just start
*******
well...********
All ri
Look,uh... why don't you get in
and see if it can get started?
You rule,man!
You totally saved me.
My mom. Pain in the ass.Thank you so...
Suzie!
Had a nightmare.
I thought you day with me ********
I had a real nightmare
about Cynthia Keener hare.
What could possibly give
that woman nightmares?
Other than somebody named
Dorothy dropping a house on her.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Medium
Season04 Episode09
We are running mind-bogglingly late,so
I need you to wolf this down double-time.
That means you,too.
And if I choke because
I'm eating too fast?
will Heimlich maneuver
on the way to the car.
What's this?
I don't know. Mom's
underwear catalogue?Let's go.
But it's addressed to you,Dad.
it's orts like it says on the cover.
What sport is she doing?
Look,I don't publish the magazine.
I didn't edit the magazine.
You know,your mom gets lots
of magazines,too,you know?
Yeah,but Mom's magazines ********
Swim!
no. Dad's still reading that.
Chew!
YOUNG WOMAN ABDUCTED
FROM MALL PARKING LOT
Cynthia Keener had a daughter named
Suzie who went missing in 1998.
*****with her cell phone,her
wallet,her credit cards still inside.
"to the victim found inside the vehicle
"led Phoenix police to conclude that MneHer
was forcibly abducted from the scene."
God.
You're taking this pretty hard.
I work with this woman practically
every da dn't even know she was a mother,
let alone a victim
of a horrible tragedy.
I can't believe she anything.
that you bring up in
casual conversation.
My conversations with her aren't casual.
I help her find missing people.
Her daughter is a missing person.
You'd think that would com I'm
supposed tet wh hein less than an h
What the hell do I say to her?
Why... why are you
going to say anything?
I methis is clearly something
that't want to talk about.
I dreamt it for a reason,for a purpose.
is to open up Cynthia Keener's
year and pour salt in it.
Of course not. But.
I don't think there's a "but" here.
It seems to me that everything you saw
is right there in that news article.
Did you see the kidnapper's face or his.
- No.
- I don't know.
Maybe the universe just wants you to
know at tWitch isn't so wicked after all.
Melanie Louise Linder,age 18.
Lives with her parents
Marjorie and Clarence Linder.
Hasn't called home in 72 hours.
Did you get to the
she's done this before?
Yeah. Ran off to Baja with her
friends for two wee she was 16.
that she used her ATM card
that cost about as muc
e in the last quarter,
leads me to believe that
young Melanie decided to
at to escape her ovotects.
Still,her mother must be devastated.
They usually are.
I know you don't normally dream
aboung girls on shopping sprees,
but I'd like you to listen to these.
What are these?
They're some interviews I
did with Melanie's friends.
I'd like you to listen to them and tell
me whether you get a feeling or whatever,
********
What's wrong
Nothing. I...
I just feel bad for her mother.
Not knowing be
Yobe a how much the human
constitution can withstand,Allison.
I just wanted to,I don't
know,give her a hug.
It's amazing how finding out this one new
thing about her makes the rest of it make sense.
I don't know what I
would do if I were her.
Well,**
Instead,you are someone who's going to
figure out how to make this meal edible.
I'm an engineer. You're a psychic.
Why can't we follow this recipe?
GETTE: This is stupid!
What you got there,Bridge?
What's stupid?
Science. Science is stupid.
That's a pretty bold statement.
What's all this about?
We're supposed to take this stupid solar
cell,make it turn on this light bulb.
olar cells are not stupid.
Th becomnergand then the energy
turns on the Christmas tree light.
But th stuIf it's sunny
outside,what's the pointng on a light b
Shgota point there
The point is toze yourself with other ways to
energize things an plugging them into a wall socket.
But why a light bulb?
Well,it doe have be a light b
You're right.Ituldnbe a light b at mb e
What do you want it to do?
I don't know.
Play music?
Okay,an d
I'm pretty sure Ariel's gotm box
he We could try and power that.
That might be fun.
Hey,where you going?
To get the boom box!
Don't scream. Doscre Don't
scream l kill you,okay?
Just calm down. Calm down.
It's okay.
*******
Good
No,don't cry.
Don't cry. He hates it when you cry.
an you... can you please untie me?
*******
at t going on?
Where the hell is this place?
Middle of nowhere,as far as I can tell.
The last girl tried
screaming,but no one hears.
No one but him.
The last girl?
It seems like there's always two of us.
One of us out he one in there.
Onpsycho to play with,and
the other to watch
Oh,God! Oh,God!Oh,God!Oh,God!Oh,God!
It'll be okay.
g to get out of this. Somehow.
My... my name is Suzie.
Johanna.
So,how many days in the last
month woy you sought employment
or engaged in activities designed to bring
yo to the attentional emplo eseapredse
or a forms of employment outside of
your current field or specialization?
I would thatged one the above le second
of every single day just like last month.
And have you turned down any
offers of employment in tnth?
No,I haven't torn up
any ing ckets either.
d boch of money from my mother,though.
at was particularly pleasant.
The state doesn't have
m with that,does it?
Man humiliating himself by
asking his mother for money?
That's not gonna screw
up my $240 a week,is it?
Sorry,yere Go ahead.
Ask me the next one. The
one about the prospects.
That's my favorite. That's
the one I look forward to.
We have to ask theuest Mr. Dubois,in
the event that answactually chang
Isn't that the definition of crazy,doing the same thing over
and over again with the expectation of a different result?
Could I not say the
same thing back to you?
Mr. Dubois,you're a highly educated man.
he things you're doing
to find employment king.
are only two companies in Phoenix
that do work in your field,
and that in the near term,neither
one is going to hire you.
Why are you waiting for someone to
give you permission to earn a living?
I beg your pardon?
Never mind.
Take this to the last windowight.
Weu next month.
How come the voices sound so funny?
lay at normal speed.
You might need a couple more of these.
But I don't have any more.
Maybe if you...
if we ask your teacher for more.
Bu tea we can only use what
she gave us for the project.
Well,maybe if we talked to her.
That's the assignment!
Where goin
*******
That desert wind's really
picking up out there.
*******
Leave it. It'll be fine.
Hey,how'd that Bridgette thing go?
Fine.
She now has a solar-powered
Christmas tree bulb,
a perfectly handy device of you're
okay Christmas tree being outdoors
and only illuminated during the day.
********
omeone's giving my invitation.
I feel like I let her down.
I got her all excited en I didn'tough.
*******
I know.
I feel like maybe if better maybe
if I were a better engineer...
Or w get Ariel's boom
box to play? Come on.
Wow,who died and made you the
sheriff in charge of self-pity n
listening to these teen
angst tapes all day. Nothing.
Not a twinge,t a not an inkling.
You want to know why?
My mind's completely
preoccupied I got top out
God,I know I should
have brought in that fur
Aren't you the girl from that magazine?
*******
You don't mind,do you?
It's the middle of the night.
How are you gonna tan in
the middle of the night?
Wedon'.
I'm gonna use this
special chaise you invente
This is so great,
and amplifies it enough
a lito give me a tan.
You're a genius,Joe.
And an amazing engineer.
********
It's okay,Joe.
It's only a dream.
And no one's going to understand
that better than Allison. Please?
You want to hear somey?
What if we're already dead?
What if this is death
and someonst f to tell us?
What?
- What?
- Listen.
Do you hear that?
- 's got the TV on or a radio.
- No,no.
No,I know what that is. That's...
that's St. John the Divine.
What do you mean,the apostle?
No,the church.
It's two blocks from my house.
I've heard them ring
every day of my life.
ust be within blocks of my house.
Are you sure?
Every day of my life.
You're right.
a die. No way.
****Not if I'm this close to home.
t if I'm this close to my mom.
Allison?
Why didn't you say something?
I never say anything to anyone.
It's mine.
I own it.
's tnowior w...
who did it...
what they did.
******
*********
Sometimes I think it's
God laughing at me.
I think I ere he took
h e he k and the others.
The others?
There was at least one other.
Her name was Johanna.
my G
I believe with a little bit of legwork,we
can figure out where he kept them.
something your daughter said.
She heard church bells.
It was underground,
but it wasn't a basement or
it wasn't just a basement.
And it looked like it was set up
like some kind of a fallout shelter,
which makes sens 'cause we
don'allyavesements here in P
I still don't understand
how that telanyt
Well,I was hoping that we could
go down to City Hall,save records,
permits and *******
if we make a list of all the addresses
that are half a awafrom that churc
*******
to come to Phoenix.
I look for some reason,some...
unsolved case that I can attach myself
to without expending too much effort.
excuse I can give compy here
I keep thinking I'm
gonna find something,
some clue,some stone
nobody's turned over.
every year,I leave with nothing.
Until now.
415 Natchez.
Well,it's the last address on our list.
*********
How long have you lived here,Ms
Um,six years.
******
He talks about making this a
game room f those home theaters,
but the grandkids have pretty
mucfor when they're here.
What about before
you,say,eight or nine years ago?
Do you have aneaved here then?
No,I'm sorry.
*********
He rented it out,which is why it was
in such bad shape when we bought it.
Nice man.
Passed away June before last.
Uh,I need to grab that.
This is the place.
Tell me everything.
They kept them...
shackled to the wall over here...
with just enough chain so
that they could reach the...
the wash basin here.
And here.
This is where first kept her...
bound and gagged.
**********
She was here the whole time.
st six b.
Here's where you can reach me,
um,if you do fi numfor the former
Oh,fin I've got it here somewhere.
Thanks.
Hi,Mom. What's going on?
What's all this for?
For me.
Where is everybody?
Follow the obnoxiously loud music.
It's all about the mirrors.
that your father rented
to back in, uh, June 1988.
Weuh, ld call me with any
information or-or fax me,
that w beally great.
I hope to hearfrom you.
I keep waiting for it to
fail,but it just won't fail.
I'm sorry. The topic of
the conversation is what?
My little solar-cell amplifion
I just hooked it upto the garage
door clicker,and it worked.
It powered that, too.
Excellent, Mr. Edison.
A clock radio that only works un
is t or you shine a lamp on it.
Hey, just 'cause your world isn't sunny,
that doesn't mean you
get to rain all over mine.
I'm sorry I wasn't listening.
I was watching the clock radio stop
working whenyou click the light off.
You're in a dark place,aren't you?
I still have my pi y decorations.
You want to borrow some?
Do you have any idea how to do this?
God,no.
Where did you get that?
I saw it upstairs,and I...
You know.
I thought maybe I could use it...
to pick the lock or...
But I don't know what I'm doing.
Do you think your mom
might really find us?
She's an investigator.
ally good at this stuff.
nice.
Itt beeling.
I'm sure your mom is
worried about you,too.
I'm sure she's out there looking.
My mom?
My mom is...
home right now and...
knitting me a sweater.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
momto knit. She's.he'sitting.
Yeah,she even opened a yarn
store in Buxley,two towns over.
Any minute now,she's gonna...
burst in the door with a knitting needle and
threaten to stab our host in the heart with it.
No. No,no,no,no,no,no!
Get off her!
No! Don't! Let her
go!Let her go!Let her go!
Stop! Don't you...Oh,my
God...Stop it,please!
No! Stop!
Well,I went down to police headquarters.
lookthe mug books all
the way back to '95.
dn't see his picture.
But I have his face burned in my memory.
So this is the man you
saw kill this girl Johanna?
The same girl who-who was
trying to help my daughter?
She d in Or her mother lived in Buxley.
At least she owned a shop
there,a yarn store or something.
me to The Complicated Yarn.
What can I do for you?
CYNTHIA: Marion Wheeler?
Are you the owner of this store?
**
Actually,we're here to talk to you
about your daughter,Mrs. Wheeler.
Okay.
Again,who-who are you?
We're investigators working
on a missing persons case,
anthat happened nine years
ago. aughter's name came up.
I don't understand.
Johanna.
We're talking about Johanna.
We think we know what
might have happened to her.
M-My Johanna?
We thought yight filed
a police report,...
I have...
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Johanna.
Her disappearance.
In 1998.
Okay,I'm sorry. There's...
Th-there's obviously someriblhere.
My dn't missing. She's
never been missing.
She never disappeared.
I mean,I was with her
yesterday here,and...
and-and I spoke to her
this morning. She's...
she's fine.
She's fine?
Uh,par-pardon me. Forgive me.
Do you have a picture of her?
If I could just look at her...
Uh,yes,I-right over here.
We took a trip to ndogether a couple
Oh,my goodness,that's her.
That's... that's who?
Thatdaughter. That's my Johanna.
And-and really,for
the life of me,I c...
I cannot figure out what
you people want with her.
Um,yo rigMr. We've obviously made
some sort of horrible mistake.
But she exists.
The fallout shelter exists.
It must mean something.
It means you're wrong.
It means I'm actually...
I'm actually angry that
that woman's daughter isn'
because she couldn't have been
there for my daughterinal moments
if,in fact,she was ever
even in that basement.
Cynthia!
I think we've come to the of Allison.
What does that mean?
It means...
I don't want to have anything
further to do with you.
I no longer want any
association with you.
ns you're fired!
Where can I drop you off?
INSPIRATION
Uh,I don't understand.
We're talking about Ariel's old toy?
Here's the thing: it isn't just a toy.
I actually think that
it might havel-woations.
I mean,there are problems on top of problems
but if I could lick even just a few of them...
Wait,slow down.
Are you telling me you think you...
you actually invented something?
I've a lot of things.
This... this would be
mine.This could be ours.
I mean,think about it: own *****
I mean,I'm actually starting to
think that everyg thhappened wit that
it was supposed to happen so that I
could be t this idea,have this new future.
I don't understand. w
dork?What do we do next?
We just put gnoutside the
house,"solar-cell amplifiers for sale"?
Well,that's what I've been trying to
figure out since 3:00 in the morning.
First thing I got to do is file a bunch
of legal papers,patents and things.
Then I got to get a working model built,ybe
pay for some testing,some studies s
o that I can show people
that it acly dwhat I say it
And then the key to thing
Wait a second.Wait a second
All that sounds expensive.
Well,that's why you meet
with the venture capitalists:
to get the money to start the business.
Yeah,but...
all the stuff before that
all the stuff foreit to them--
the lawyers and the
model and the studies.
Yeah,I figure all that's
gonna cost about 30,000.
Joe,come on.
$30,000? We don't even have $3,000.
I mean,Cynthia Keener
fired me yesterday.
We're getting $240 a week loyment.
We don't have money for
this kind of thing right now.
But we do.
Don't get that.
*****
We're in the middle of a conversation.
It's Cynthia.
Cynthia?
Allison.
I think I owe you another apology.
Uh,Cynthia,I don't know
what you're talking about.
Where are you?
You close to a television?
Turn on the news.
am I watching?
A man who's holding two girls against
their will was just killed by one of them.
Deputies sto the Turns out he kept them chained
up for days,assaulting them,beating them.
Any of this sound familiar?
Yeah,okay.
was just like your dream...
except it wasn't my daughter.
lanithe girl you were hired to find?
That's right.
Except she didn't run away.
She was abducted...
along with another girl.
Oh,my God.
And you're never going to
guess who the other girl is.
****
She was being wit Now,in the present?
Allison,let's take
our good news e we I...
lik you wanted to help me so
badly that,uh,people,places,
they just all got shuffled around,
but you were more right than
wrong sorry I snapped at you.
I hope you'll give some thought to the
idea of our continuing to work together.
I...
I'm sorry I dragged you out of bed.
Go back to sleep.
They found Melanie Linder with Johanna,the
girl I thought wathia's daughter.
The good news is everybody's alive.
No,I see that.
Well,here's to you.
Congratulations.
Case closed. It must feel good.
I can't figure out why I keep
dreaming about Cynthia's daughter
Okay,well,this is good.
You feel disturbed. I feel disturbed.
feel disturbed?
Why do you feel disturbed?
Aren't you the guy who
just had the big epiphany?
Yeah,I am.
trying to talk to my wife about it
and then the darnedest thing happened.
Yeah,the phone rang.
And you said you needed
$30,000 on't have $30,000.
But we do.********
There's almost $32,000
just sitting there.
You can't be serious.
Oh,I've never been more serious
about anything in my life.
I think this idea cobe wons.
That could pay for a lot of college.
What if it's worth nothing?
What if someone thought tre you did?
Where does that leave the girls?
You know I can't do this.
t to get that money,I have to sign
for it,too,and I can't do that.
God,isn't life funny?
I mean,this whole marriage has
always been about me believing in you.
Now the one time,the one time,the
shoe ends up up on the other foot...
Thise sath It's exactly the same thing.
Exactly.
Where are you going?
- What does it matter?
- Joe...
Joe.
Police say the perpetrator
*****According to police,
- Draper was shot and killed by one of his captives after...
- *******
whadoing?
Where are you going? It's not even 7:00.
I'm going tome coffee,some
breakfast o be by myself.
Wh I wouldn't let you raid
the girls' college fund?
When are you going to be back?
Read my mind. Figure it out.
Keener
Cynthia,it's Allison.
Hey,Allison.
I'y to the hospital.
Melanie's about to give
her statement to the police.
girit shaken up,t thg fine.
****
I just got a fax from the daughter of
the man who used to450 reet,the house
where I thought your daughter...
Yes,I know the house,but
it was a false lead.
Yeahw I'm not so sure.
The man who rented that house back in
1998,the year that your daughter went missing?
the same man I've been dreaming about.
He's real.
His name is Peter Connolly.
t,he's the same youeamed killed Johanna
Yes.
******and about to be
reunited with her parents.
Come on,for God's sake,Allison.
The man who heldn is dead.
w,can we stop torturiring
each other with it?
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
Please! Stop!.
Oh,God! Oh,God!
Oh,God!
The look on your face.
as all,it was all worth itjustlook.
******
You didn't think that Petes sth to
leave all the,the doors unlocked,did you?
- What?
- Didn't you?
You really thought that... Oh,Suzie.
You sure can pick 'em,Johanna.
I sure can.
But now the play's over.
It's time to take a bow,Suzie.
I... I don't understand why...
Mom? Dad?You guys up?
to be continued