-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
oh, my god...
this is good.
I mean... really good.
It's delicious.
What did you say this was again?
I didn't, actually.
It's just an old recipe.
I'm sorry, I...
haven't seen you in...
well, gosh,
it seems like forever.
All I can talk about is
the food.
How have you been?
Well.
Very well, as a
matter of fact.
And what about you?
I see you went and
got yourself inked up.
Oh... (quiet laugh)
yeah.
Me and the boys had a little bit
too much to drink one night.
When I woke up,
I had this tattoo.
I'm sorry.
I really hate to nag, but, uh,
this is the best thing
I've ever tasted.
Please, you have to tell me
what it is.
Sometimes it's better
not to know.
Come on, what is it?
Filet? Tenderloin?
You're sure you want
me to tell you?
Oh, I'm sure.
Okay. But I'm
surprised
you haven't figured
it out yet.
That meat you're
enjoying so much?
The secret
ingredient...
is you.
we're eating you.
Your right leg,
to be exact.
Look for yourself.
You'll see.
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：卢  斌
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
灵媒缉凶  第4季 第6集
Well, there was definitely
nothing literal about my dream.
But the guy in it,
he, he was young.
He was like 20, 21, uh...
oh, he had dark, shaggy hair.
Oh, he also had a, uh, a tattoo
on his arm.
It was like an eight ball
with fire all around it.
I don't know what to tell you,
allison.
No one matching that description
has been reported missing.
Or turned up dead.
lee, can you hold on a second?
I'm getting another call. Sorry.
Hello?
Hello. Is this allison dubois?
Yes?
This is mrs. Desai from
the ubient credit corporation.
I'm calling to inform you
that your accois more
than 90 days past due.
Well, I appreciate
your heads up, mrs. Desai.
But you know what?
We already know that.
Someone from your company has
been nice enough
to call us every single day
to remind us.
Now, if you can't arrange to
make the minimum payment soon,
I'm afraid your credit cards are
going to be frozen.
Yeah, you know what?
We know that, too.
we want to pay you.
We really do.
And we will, as soon as we can.
I'm sorry,
I have to get off now.
'Cause I have another call.
Lee, sorry about that.
Uh, no problem.
I'll keep an eye out, okay?
Thanks.
So, you're fairly confident
that cassandra baldwin would
make a good juror?
She's perfect for you.
I think thatilhe wl
vote to acquit.
Sir?
Hm...?
I'm sorry, allison.
The truth is,
my mind isn't really
on this jury at the moment.
actually, there's something else
I would like to discuss
with you.
I had dinner last night with an
old colleague-- jed garrity.
He was a judge
when I was a junior prosecutor.
He's served
as a state senator for...
more than a decade now.
It was quite
an interesting evening.
Apparently,
there's some dissatisfaction
with the way tom van dyke is
handling himself
as district attorney.
Imagine that.
Van dyke is up
for reelection soon.
There are some people
who are disappointed
that he's running unopposed.
Senator garrity among them.
Last night, garrity asked me
if I'd be interested
in throwing my hat
into the ring.
So what did you say?
Oh, I told him
that I was, uh, content
to languish in a rented office
on the edge of downtown.
I also told him that I...
always imagined spending
the autumn of my career
picking up cases on a
catch-as-catch-can basis.
What do you think
I said?
I imld h I'm excited.
I told him that I miss serving
the city of phoenix.
I, uh, that I'd be thrilled
to stand for the job.
Oh, that's great news.
I'm so happy for you.
I have to admit
I'm happy for me, too.
But I'm trying to keep it
in check.
This isn't going to be easy.
The logistics of getting
a campaign up and running
at this late date-- frankly,
they're... daunting.
And... (sighs heavily)
the senator's support
is conditional.
Before he's willing
to endorse me,
he has concerns
that need to be addressed,
and chief among them is you.
Hey, if it helps you
get your job back,
I will happily crawl
under a rock
until after the election.
well, I appreciate the offer,
but I don't think that's
a realistic possibility.
Reporters are quite good
at looking under rocks.
Yeah.
Senator garrity
would like to meet you.
Tonight, as a matter of fact.
If you're willing, the three
of us could have dinner.
The senator could ask you
his questions,
and, hopefully...
that'll be that.
Dad.
Yeah?
I need to call hannah back,
and bridgette won't get off
the phone.
Well, I'm in the middle
of something, ariel.
Just be patient.
Yeah, but she's been on the
phone for, like, ten minutes.
Who's she talking to?
I don't know--
some weird guy-- but she won't
say when she'll be done.
well, just hold on for
a couple minutes, okay?
I'm sure she'll be off soon.
Really? You got to call somebody
in niagara falls?
How many times?
Bridgette,
who are you talking to?
Can you hold on a
second, please?
Mr. Reshmi.
Have you ever talked
to anybody in alaska?
Bridgette,
who is mr. Reshmi?
He's the credit
card man.
You're talking to somebody
from the credit card company?
Give me the phone.
But we were in
the middle of talking.
Mr. Reshmi...
hi.
Yeah, my name is
joseph dubois.
I wonder if your supervisor
would be interested in learning
you've spent
the last ten minutes
chatting with a nine year old.
That's right, nine.
Well, all right,
let me be really clear
about something,
I don't want you
calling here again.
harassing my family.
And if it continues,
then I'm going to call
the authorities.
Good-bye.
A hiker's dog sniffed him
out of a shallow grave
in boyce park
this morning.
Somebody stabbed him
a couple dozen times,
then they dissected him
with a chain saw.
The best bet is
your friend here died
somewhere close
to midnight.
That's the same tattoo
from my dream.
Now, what would really
be helpful would be
if you could give me a complete
description of this guy.
A little something
more than, uh,
four feet tall, no arms,
no legs, no head.
You know, I could probably
also give you the description
of the guy who did
this to him.
What are you talking about?
You saw the murder?
You never mentioned that.
Well, not exactly.
It wasn't realistic.
But there was a man
in the dream
who was definitely
interested in his limbs.
He wanted them...
for food.
Hubba, hubba.
A hubba from the hubba.
Well, that's good.
But it's not too hubba, right?
Mm, why do you ask?
Well, devalos is too polite
to say anything,
but I'm getting the feeling that
this endorsement hangs
on whether or not
this garrity guy
thinks I'm a complete nut job.
I want to look nice...
but sane.
Well, you look very nice.
Very sane.
But I do have to ask:
Are you sure that you are okay
with devalos campaigning
for his old job?
What are you talking about?
Well, campaigns mean publicity.
And publicity means reporters.
Lots and lots of reporters.
Asking questions,
writing things about you.
It wasn't exactly a party
the first time around.
Well, I don't feel like
I have a choice.
Devalos isn't asking for my
permission to run for office.
He's asking for my help.
I know he's not thrilled
of what he's doing right now.
And I feel partially responsible
for that.
I'd really like help him get
back the one job in the world
that makes him truly happy.
Allison.
You look lovely.
Thank you.
Jed...
the secret ingredient
is you.
Allison dubois,
I'd like you to meet
senator jed garrity.
Hey.Hi.
Are the girls in bed?
Uh, ariel'sdoing homework.
Bridgette and marieare asleep.
How'd dinner go?Oh...
I passed musterwith the senator.
He's going to endorse devalos.
They're scheduling a pressconference for friday.
Oh, so that's a win, right?
Yeah, it's great.
I even managed to getthrough the meal
without accusing garrityof murder.
You know, I spentthe whole afternoon
with a policesketch artist,
giving hima perfect description
of an arizonastate senator.
what if they distributethat sketch?
who are you calling?
Scanlon.
I got to stop them
before they putthat sketch out.
Hi, this is detective...
(sighing): Ah, it'sgoing to voice mail.
Lee.
It's allison.
Uh, listen, uh,
that sketch that I did
with your artistthis afternoon?
Um, do me a favor anddon't distribute it
until I talk to you.
Okay, I guess I'll talkto you in the morning.
your mom's going to betied up most of the day,
so I'll be picking you upthis afternoon, okay?
Okay, daddy.
All right, kiddo.Give me a kiss.
ByE.
Daddy, how can we tellmr. Reshmi
that he needsto lock his back door?
Tell who what?
Mr. Reshmi.
I had a dream that somebody
broke into the placewhere he lives.
Mr. Reshmi?
What, the credit card guy?
You had a dreamabout the credit card guy?
I saw his nameon the apartment door.
These robbers, they came in
from the sliding doorin the back.
I think they took a ring.
Uh-huh, okay.
Well, look, bridge,
like you said,it was just a dream.
And even though you dreamt it,doesn't necessarily mean
that it's going to happen.
But I don't thinkit was just a dream.
I think we need to warn him.
Warn him? Bridge...
okay, even if it was one of,you know, those dreams...
there's no way of knowingwhether this is something that's
going to happen or somethingthat's already happened.
But either way, it couldn't hurtto warn him, could it?
Bridge, I wouldn't have any ideahow to begin finding this guy.
I mean, these credit cardcompanies
have thousands of employees.
Most of the call centersare in india now.
Well, we could call information.
Okay.
All right, when I gohome, I'll, um...
I'll call the companyand I'll, you know,
we'll try and give mr. Reshmia heads up, okay?
Thanks, daddy.
I think mr. Reshmi will bereally glad you called.
Oh, and daddy,
make sure he knowsthat it's the back door, okay?
Okay.
Manuel devalos,an instinct for justice.
The campaign should
keep the public focusedon mr. Devalos' record.
Minimize anyquestions about
how he achieved it.
You can help us do that,mrs. Dubois, by being
very clearwhen you talk to the media.
When the word "psychic" comesup, you should say that
you've never been comfortablewith that term.
In fact, you don'tconsider yourself psychic.
You've always beenhighly intuitive,
and you've used that "intuition"
to solvea number of cases.
Well, the newspaperswere very definite
about what it was I didfor the district attorney.
You really thinkwe can get away
with pretendingI'm not what I am?
To be blunt, allison,
I don't believe you arewhat you say you are.
Not exactly.
Now, that's not to saythat I think you're a fraud...
but if I were to accept
everythingI hear about you,
well, that would make mequestion
too many of my dearly heldassumptions about the world.
And the last thing we wantto do is make people
question theirassumptions.
So, we're tryingto find language
that fits what you dointo the way most people think.
People like the word"intuitive."
They're comfortable with it.
I'm comfortable with it.
To me, it describessomeone who might
use unconventional techniques...
in your case, someone who mightmake leaps in logic
that might elude otherinvestigators.
Occasionally, one of thoseleaps in logic
might come to you in a dream.
Is that a pretty fairdescription of what you do?
Actually, that'san excellent description.
And I don'thave a problemwith it, either.
That, to me, sounds like someone
I would want to haveworking for the good guys.
Good.
man: I'm surrendering!
I'm surrendering!
my name's jed garrity.
I'm a captain in the 101st
infantry unit.
I expect allrights due to me...
allison,  are you all right?
I'm fine.
Sorry, sir, did you saysomething to me?
Garrity:I did.
I said I think we accomplished
a great deal here this morning,don't you?
Definitely.
I wanted to thank youfor making me 86
those wanted postersdepicting our own
senator garrityas a murder suspect.
We got a dna match for the body.
I assume this guydoesn't look familiar.
No, he does not.
This is the murder victim?
Turns outhe's from corpus christi.
Name is gordon laroche.
And seeing
as he was 59instead of 20 like
the guy you dreamed about,I figured that
maybe you were wrongabout everything.
Well, I guess I was.
This guy laroche must've had
the same tattoo as theman I dreamt about.
Well, this is great news.
Thank you.
Okay, so I never reached outto mr. Reshmi.
Would you have spentthe afternoon dialing india?
No, probably not, but I wouldn'thave told our daughter
I was going to do itin the first place.
Well, I'm pretty
sure this falls underthe category of white lie.
As far as she's concerned,mr. Reshmi is buying a lock
for his back door right now.
And I'm fine with that.
What?
Nothing.You're proably right.
She'll probably never know.
Unless, of course, she hasanother dream about him.
And if she does and she sees hisapartment's been broken into,
well, then she'll be positiveher father lied to her.
I'm not sure that ournine year old is really clear
on the difference betweena white lie and a regular one.
I guess I'm calling india.
looks like the welcome committeegot to you.
You got a name,soldier?
Jed garrity.
I'm a captain.
Welcome to hell,captain garrity.
I'm from corpus christi.
The name's laroche.
Gordon laroche.
Senator garrityand gordon laroche
knew each other.
They spent four years in aprisoner of war camp together.
They even marched side by side
in a memorial day paradein 2002.
I can prove it:I found this
on the internetthis morning.
There isa connectionbetween these two men.
I know.
I found outthey knew each other yesterday.
Turns out laroche hadquite the gambling problem.
Owed moneyto bookies in four states.
I looked at his bankstatements yesterday--
even when larochewasn't working,
he still had chunks of moneycoming in every so often.
$8,500 here, ten grand there.
A lot of that money camein the form of personal checks
from jed garrity.
As a matter of fact,
he sent larochea check for 15 grand
just last christmas.
So you thinkingwhat I'm thinking?
What's that?
Isn't it obvious?
Garrity was making down paymentson laroche's limbs.
It's kind of an expensivemeal, but, hey,
when you've got a ravenousappetite for human flesh,
I guess you have to expectto pay through the nose.
(Laughs)great, it's comedy.
It's cop comedy,the best kind.
What do you want, allison?
It looks to melike every so often
senator garrity would
try to bail his old warbuddy out of trouble.
Should I send a squad carover to his place?
Charge himwith being a nice guy?
You don't thinkit's a strange coincidence?
Laroche turns up murderedin garrity'sometown?
Not really.
Especially sincelaroche owed money
to at least two loan sharksin phoenix.
Tell you what.
I'm going to spend my morningworking the whole
"shady guys larocheowed money to" thing.
I might even follow upon the fact that,
at 10:00 on the nighthe was killed,
laroche's hotel manager
saw him get intothe passenger side
of a silver sedan and drive off.
But, hey, if you want to,uh, pursue your
"senator cannibal" theory,by all means,
feel free.Be sure and let me
know if anything breaks.
Garrity:Allison?
Hello.
Are you headed upto manny's office?
Yeah, I am.
Are you leaving?
I thought you two were workingtogether this morning.
We were, but ihad to reschedule.
A friend of mine died.
I've got to fly out to texas
pay my respectsto his family.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Were you close?
Once upon a time.
We were in the service together.
Well, I have to admit, sir,
I know a little bitabout your background.
About the thingsthat you've lived through.
I imagine that the bonds thatyou develop
during war are very strong.
You have my condolences.
That's very kind of you.
But the truth is,I've been out of touch
with gordon for, oh...
it must be almost 15 years now.
Really? You didn't haveany contact at all?
I'd think that people who sharedthose kinds of experiences
would keep in touch.
Unfortunately, my friend and i
became very different people.
We just drifted apart.
gordon and I saweach other at a funeral.
Must've been,oh, '91 or so.
We haven't evenspoken since then.
Allison, are you all right?
You look a little pale.
I'm fine, sir.
Suprabhaat, ubient credit,
bangalore.
Hi. Do you speak english?
Yes, sir.
How can I help you?
Hi, I'm looking for an employeeof ubient credit.
I don't have a first name,but his last name is reshmi.
Your office in bombay said thatthey thought that
he might work at this branch.
That's right, sir.
Maneck reshmi.
Let me see if he's started
his shift.
Hello, this is mr. Reshmi.
Hello, mr. Reshmi.
My name is joe dubois.
I live in phoenix, arizona.
Uh, you may recallyou had a conversation
with my daughter the other day.
Uh, she's nine.
You spoke of all the interestingplaces that you get to call.
Yes, sir.
I... think I remember.
How can I help you?
Would you like
to arrange a payment?
No, no, actually,uh, I am, uh...
I'm callingto talk to you about...
home security.
I don't think I understand.
I'm calling to ask youto buy a lock
for your back door.
Uh, you know,the kind that-that, uh...
that makes it impossibleto slide open?
you know whatI'm talking about, right?
You-you have a sliding door?
I do.
And you're calling me because
you'd like meto buy a lock for it?
That's right, I would.
Uh, I know this sounds, uh, odd.
I'm afraidI don't understand, sir.
Are you tryingto sell me a product?
No, uh, I just want youto tell me
that you're going to buy a lock.
I'll tell you what.
I'll pay for it.
Okay?
Uh, those locks are cheap,right?
What, uh, what,about... about $25?
I'll send you a personal check.
If you are going
to send a check,
why don't you let me credit it
to your account?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, it's for the lock.
You got to buy the lock.
Uh, I'm still confused,
mr. Dubois.
Why exactly are you so concerned
with my home security?
Uh, look, it's, uh...
it's my daughter.
Um... my daughter liked you.
actually, she's worriedabout you,
and-and... I promised
that I would try
to get ahold of you.
So what do you say, huh?
It's not every day
that a strangerfrom another continent offers
to buy you a free lock.
so, you sent hima check anyway?
Yeah, I sent hima check anyway.
You know, I thinkI need to talk to devalos
to warn him about garrity.
Warn him about what exactly?
I don't know.
All of it-- the things I'vebeen seeing in my dreams.
Two days from now,
devalos is supposedto stand shoulder-to-shoulder
with garrity in frontof every reporter in phoenix.
Can you imaginewhat would happen
if garrity becomes a suspectin a murder investigation?
It would be the endof devalos's political career.
Well, maybe,but there's nothing
that indicates garrity'sgoing to become a suspect.
What about this?
The night of the murder,
someone picked up larochefrom his hotel
in a silver sedan.
Garrity drives a silver sedan.
That's not exactlya smoking gun.
Every malein the developed world
has owned a silver sedanat some point in his life.
Uh, that's pretty muchwhat scanlon said to me
when I called himthis afternoon.
All right, then whydo I keep seeing things
that tell methat garrity's a bad guy?
Why did he look me straightin the face and lie to me?
He told me he hadn't beenin touch with laroche for years.
He sent him $15,000last christmas.
The two of them were in a paradeless than five years ago.
What is he trying to hide?
rhoades has dysentery.
He's dying.
He's not going tolast more than a week.
Now, we can just let it happen,
and who knowshow many of us are going
to starve to deathbefore he dies.
or his death can mean something.
It can help us live.
What are you talking about,captain garrity?
If rhoades dies,how does that help us live?
Are you sayingwhat I think you're saying?
We don't have any food.
Rhoades is dying anyway,so we just...
...help him along.
Then we get to live.
Man:No.
No way.
I can't do that.
We all have to be in on this.
We all have to agree.
And we all have to eat.
God, I'm so hungry.
fine.
But which of us is goingto do it?
Who's going to kill rhoades?
We'll draw for it.
Thank god.
two straws left,captain garrity.
Looks likeit's between me and you.
Let's just dothis, laroche.
where am I?
am I home,captain garrity?
Not yet.
but you will be soon.
Let me be sureI understand you.
A young man namedmichael rhoades
died in a vietnameseprisoner-of-war camp
more than 30 years ago,
and it's your beliefthat jed garrity murdered him
then... ate him.
Garrity didn't want to do it.
He was starving to death.
All the prisoners were.
He did it so the rest of themcould survive.
And you think that all of thisis somehow connected
to a murder that occurredfour days ago?
Gordon laroche was in that campwith garrity.
He was in the room
when garrity killedmichael rhoades.
His gambling debtsare out of control.
Senator garritywas giving laroche money,
and lots of it.
What if they wereblackmail payments?
What if laroche said to garrity
he was goingto expose their little secret
if garrity didn't paid him off?
Don't you thinkit's possible
garrity killed larocheto protect himself, his career?
No.
Actually, allison, I don'T.
Even if I were willingto concede that,
many years ago, in some of thedirest circumstances imaginable,
jed garrity did a terrible thingso that he could survive,
I refuse to believethat he had anything to do
with the murderof that man scanlon found
the other night.
This is a man that I've knownfor more than 20 years.
Someone who has been decoratedwith the highest medal
the military has to give.
And if you're goingto come to my house
and accuse him of murder,I need something
more than dreams abouta prisoner of war camp.
There is more.
10:00, the night of the murder,
someone drove larochefrom his hotel
in a silver sedan.
Garrity drives
a silver sedan.
Now, I think I'm going to haveto bring this to scanlon.
And I really thinkyou should distance yourself
from that man before I do.
And you say this all happenedon sunday night?
Senator garrity was with meat 10:00 P.M. On sunday night,
sitting right in this very room,
as a matter of fact.
That was the nighthe came to see me
about running fordistrict attorney.
We sat right here,
drinking whiskey and talkinguntil just before midnight.
I'm sorry to deflate
your theory, allison,
but the silver sedanyou're referring to was parked
in my drivewaythe entire evening.
ariel:Dad?
Do you know some guynamed mr. Reshmi?
He called when I wason the other line.
Thanks. Hello?
Hello, mr. Dubois.
I... I hope I'm not reaching youat a bad time.
Uh, no, no, I can talk
for a couple minutes.
What's up?
Thieves broke into my apartmentlast night.
They came inthrough the back door.
I'm afraid they took everything
they could carry.
They even found a ring I had
been saving for my engagement.
I have to know, mr. Dubois:
How exactly did you think
to advise me to buy a lock
on the very day
I was about to be robbed?
Um, well, uh...
it really has nothingto do with me.
Uh, like I told you,it's my daughter.
Um, she... uh,she worries about people,
and at times, it-it...
seems like she's very...
prescient.
Do you know what I mean by that?
I think I can guess.
Will you please tell her
I appreciate her effortson my behalf?
I will.
I-I wishI had been more convincing.
And I wish
that I had listened to you.
I also thoughtyou'd like to know
that your family's statuswith the company has changed.
Your account was previously
classified as urgent.
Someone was meant
to call your home every day
until we received payment.
Based on the conversations
we had,
I have reclassified your file
as payment pending.
It should be quite some time
before it's reclassified
as urgent.
Perhaps 90 days.
You're telling me
that nobody's going to call usfor three months?
Thatis right, sir.
Wow. Well, I appreciate that.
Um, are you sureyou're comfortable doing that?
It is a large company.
Errors are made.
Good day, mr. Dubois.
uh, bridgettewants to know
if, uh, we can contributea little something
to mr. Reshmi'sengagement ring fund.
I mean, you got tohand it to the girl.
She's reallybuilt a bridge
between the dubois familyand its creditors.
Well, I'm glad one of usis seeing something useful.
You know whatI can't stop thinking about?
Is that poor soldier,michael rhoades.
Just a boy, really.
And he died half a world away.
Al...
it was horrible, and now,
nobody's ever going to knowwhat really happened to him.
Well, maybe that'sa good thing, too.
Even if you could provethat this guy died
at the hands of hisfellow prisoners,
what possibly could begained by exposing it?
I mean, imagine the horrorhis family would feel
if they found outthat this kid was eaten.
And the menwho killed him,
I know that they dida terrible thing,
but they were in akind of living hell.
And it doesn't soundlike they went on
to become career criminals.
I know. You're right,of course your right.
this is whatI keep thinking:
If I can't tell the truthabout michael rhoades,
and if I can'tp the policesolve la roche's murder,
then why am I seeingthese things?
Why do I have such horriblethings stuck in my head?
Man: I don't think I can do this.
I'm serious-- I can'T.
We've beenover this, evan.
None of us wants to do it.
Gordon's been out of controlfor a long time.
His debts are getting bigger.
He keeps coming to usfor more money.
Now he's threatening to takehis story to the networks.
I know, but you're talkingabout murdering someone.
I haven't held a gun in my handsfor over 30 years.
I'm a doctor now.
We've all built lives forourselves-- that's the point.
If la roche comes outand tells the truth
about what we did to rhoades,that's it-- we're ruined.
I didn't fly out hereto have a debate.
Draw.
Sorry, evan.
Look, I know we needto do this...
correction: Youneed to do this.
Why should I bethe only one at risk?
We'll all do it.
Together.
If everybody takes part...then no one can back out later.
No one can becomeanother laroche.
We can't blackmaileach other
or threaten to goto the authorities.
Because we'll allbe murderers.
Each one of us will be justas guilty as everybody else.
It's the way we should've donethis in the first place.
If we all did rhoades together,
then laroche would've hadhis own skin in the game,
and we wouldn't be havingthis conversation right now.
Tomorrow night.
Evan, you tell laroche you needto talk to him.
He can come to your housefor a drink.
Put some sleeping pillsin his whiskey.
We'll all come over later.
Midnight.
We'll kill him together.
And then each of us will get ridof a piece of him.
Evan, you have to burywhat's left of him.
Do you thinkyou can handle that?
Now let me askyou something.
Do you own a chainsaw?
Scanlon:Evan sabow?
Yes?
My name's lee scanlon.
I'm with the phoenixpolice department.
I have few questionsfor you about, uh,
about the murderof gordon laroche.
You knew him, right?
Of course.Gordon and I go way back.
We were in the army together.
Did you happen to see himthis past sunday?
Sunday?I don't think so; no.
You sure? Can you rememberwhere you were that night?
I was here.I was home all night.
Are you asking me to accountfor my whereabouts, detective?
Hope you're not implying
I had anything to dowith gordon's death.
Nah, I'm just checking.
Can anybody confirm that youwere here-- wife, kids?
No, I'm divorced.
I was watching televisionall night, by myself.
I like that tattoo.
Gordon laroche hadone just like it.
Yeah, I know.We, uh, we got 'em together.
A group of guys from our unitgot drunk one night
when we were on leave;
we all had thesewhen we woke up.
Wish to god that we hadn'T.
We were justunchof stupid kids.
What's in the bag?
Oh, just some tools, old stuffI was going to get rid of.
You mind openingit up for me?
You don't have to.
We could just waithere together
while somebody drivesover a search warrant.
That's a nice-looking chain saw.
You shouldn't keep your toolsall mixed up like that, though.
They're I was going to get rid of them.
Hmm...(sniffs)that smells like bleach.
No wonder you're lookingto dump that thing.
It's not going to last very longif you use bleach to clean it.
I really don't see that that'sany of your business, detective.
Funny thing aboutchain saws, though.
They're almost impossibleto get completely clean.
There's just too manynooks and crannies.
So, dr. Sabow...
if I take a real closelook at that thing,
you think I'll find some ofgordon laroche's blood on it?
hello?
Evan sabow just confessed
to the murder of gordon laroche.
Lee, that's great.
Have you arrested garrityand the others?
No. And right now, it doesn't
look like we're going to.
What do you mean?Why not?
Sabow confessed but he'ssaying it was all him.
He says he killed larochewithout any help.
Well, that's not right.
Laroche was blackmailingall of them.
All four of them killed him.
Not according to sabow.
He says laroche borrowed moneyfrom him,
the two of them had an argumentabout when laroche was
going to pay him backand it turned physical.
He's lying. He's tryingto protect the others.
I believe you,
but we searched his house.
There's no evidence that tiesanyone else to the murder.
None of the neighborssaw anybody
coming or going from the houseon the night laroche died.
We'll keep working it, but, uh,
it looks like sabow's taking
the truth to jail with him.
So that's it?
So garrity and the rest of themjust get away with it?
I hope not, allison, but at this
point, that's a possibility.
Evan sabow may bea bad murderer, but, uh,
I have to admithe's a good soldier.
senator garrity?
I'd like to talk to youabout gordon laroche.
I'm afraid I don't have timefor a conversation right now.
Senator...
you really shouldn't be here,mrs. Dubois.
I'm sure you're aware that mannyand I have a press conference
starting in just a few minutes.
I would hate for any reportersto see you hanging around.
You don't want to hearabout laroche.
Why don't we talk aboutprivate michael rhoades?
Would you all excuse usa moment?
It's been a long time
since anyone mentionedthat name to me.
I know what happenedin that camp.
I know that gordon laroche wasblackmailing
all of you about it.
And you killed him.
That's quite a story, especiallysince evan sabow just confessed
to gordon's murder.
From what I'm told, they werehavin argument over money.
But we know better, don't we?
And don't think that youand you're friends are
just going to walk awayfrom this.
I am going to find a wayto prove that you did it.
That sounds like a tall order.
The killer's in jail;he freely admits to his crime.
And I must say,I don't understand why a woman
of your obvious talentswould waste her time
on a piece of businesslike this one.
The four of you killed someone.
Fair enough.
But let me make sureI've got your story right.
A long time ago, a soldier died
so that the men he served withcould survive.
My guess is, they were probablyaware of the burden
that the death of michaelrhoades placed on them.
Who knows? Maybe they even madeanonymous contributions
to the family ofthat poor, dead soldier.
Seems like the leastthey could do.
If these men had anykind of decency at all,
it seems to me that theywould live their lives
in a way that honoredthe sacrifice
that made them possible.
Don't expect me to sympathizewith you.
You gave up your rightto understanding
when you murderedgordon laroche.
Right. Gordon laroche.
He's the sticking point here,isn't he?
If you're right aboutany of this,
he's the only one who made itout of that camp
who didn't understand the legacythat rhoades left behind.
The only one who didn't holdhimself to a higher standard.
If fact it sounds like youthink laroche tried to exploit
that terrible timefor his personal gain,
and he tried to drag the restof those survivors down
into the mess he had madefor himself.
Would I be sorry that someonelike that was gone?
Not at all.
He wasn't worthy of the lifeanother man gave him.
Now, if you'll excuse me,allison,
I have to go help put your bossback in office.
A man I happen to believewill do a lot of good.
A man I believe will help you doa lot of good.
And that's all mostof us want, isn't it?
A chance to do something goodwith the time we have.
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入