Your aspirin, mademoiselle.
I was starting to think
you'd forgotten about me.
I was just looking for
a store that was still
open, that's all.
Must be some headache.
Can't even kiss your husband
in the most beautiful city
on Earth.
This isn't right, Kent.
It's springtime in Paris.
We're in the same room
we honeymooned in.
Come on, maybe
a little Chardonnay
will put you in
a better mood.
To us.
JOE (groggily):
You all right?
What's going on?
Were you dreaming again?
An American couple in Paris...
The wife ended up
stabbing the husband through
the hand with a corkscrew.
I don't know what to tell you.
I don't think 'em up.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：观海卫
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
片名Medium 第4季第3集
BRIDGETTE:
Three tenths...
Two twelfths, whic
really one sixth.
Um...
Can you give me a clue?
It's a math problem, doofus.
So?
So, there are
no clues in math.
You either know
the answer or you don't.
Mommy, I don't like doing
flash cards with Ariel.
I'd rather do them with Daddy.
Sorry, kiddo.
Your dad is getting ready
for a big job interview.
It's your sister
or nothing this morning.
You ready for
a good luck kiss?
Why don't you tell me,
do I look ready?
Let's see.
Ooh, you look good.
Highly employable.
Oh, yeah?
Absolutely.
If I was the president of
a big aerospace company,
I would definitely
hire you-- definitely.
All right. Okay.
From your lips.
Don't be such
a fatalist.
I'm not a fatalist,
I'm a realist.
I mean, aside from Aerodytech,
aside from the company
that fired me,
there are only two
other firms in Phoenix
that do anything
even remotely related
to the kind of work
that I do.
And one of them
is laying people off.
This may literally be the
last engineering job in town.
That's okay.
You only need one.
You're a brilliant man,
Mr. Dubois.
I've been following your career
for some time.
We'd be lucky to have you.
And that would be that,
except that, for some reason,
at this particular
moment in time,
there are also two or three
other engineers
who I expect we'd be
lucky to have
and I've yet to meet with them.
So I'm going
to have to ask you
to be patient,
bear with me.
May take me a week or two
to identify just who it is
I'm going to ask to join us.
Of course.
I understand completely.
It's a big decision.
For both of us.
Now that we got that
out of the way,
I have to ask you, um...
kind of a peculiar question.
Okay.
Your wife-- she wouldn't,
by any chance,
be the Dubois woman who was
on the news earlier this year?
Why? Is that going
to be a problem?
Depends what you
consider a problem.
My wife followed
that story very closely.
When I told her I was meeting
with you this morning
she made me promise
I'd find out.
Well, please tell your wife
I am married to Allison Dubois.
And she is the woman that
they were writing about.
Frankly, I take issue
with a lot of the things
that were said, a lot of
the things that were implied.
Well, it can't be easy.
For you or her.
For what it's worth,
my wife is a big believer.
And her husband?
Well, I'm a big believer
in my wife.
Which brings me to
my next peculiar question.
What are the two of you
doing this evening?
JOE:
Hey.
Hey. How'd it go?
Honestly, it's a little
hard to say.
But I need a favor.
So let me get
this straight--
they're having a party
at their house.
It's kind of
a charity thing.
Tonight.
I know, it's a
little bit odd.
And your new boss?
He's not
my boss yet.
Right, not your boss yet--
wants us to come
to this party
because his wife
thinks I'm interesting.
Uh, you make that sound
like it's a bad thing.
Well, just so you know,
it feels like a bad thing.
I'm not a freak,
I'm not an oddity,
I'm not a science experiment.
I don't even know what you're
talking about now.
What is going to be
expected of us
when we go to this party?
What is she expecting
me to do?
Do? I don't know-- eat,
drink, maybe be merry.
And you're fairly sure
her idea of merriment
doesn't include me sitting
in the corner reading tea leaves
or telling a fortune or two?
Allison, this man that I met
today, Pet Peter Barrister--
he strikes me as a fairly
sophisticated man.
I've got to believe that if he's
looking for party entertainers
he has the means
and the wherewithal
to find them on his own.
I honestly think
that his wife
is legitimately
interested in you.
Which is another way of saying
that you are someone
that she would love
to meet, period.
Now, if you don't want
to go to this party,
I guess we won't go
to this party.
But I got to
tell you, finally,
you doing what you do
and you being who you are,
has the potential of
giving us-- giving me--
a leg up in a situation
where I could use it.
Now, he's interviewing
two other people.
I'm betting neither of them
are married to a famous psychic.
I'll tell Ariel that
she's babysitting.
We need a signal.
Hmm? What do you mean?
Well, what if we do if
Mrs. Barrister corners me
tries to get me, you know,
to guess people's birthdays
or the future...
I don't know.
Hmm, let me see...
Why don't you just give me
that look you always give me
and then I'll, uh, interject
myself in the situation.
I'll know what to do.
What are you talking
about? What look?
I don't know what look
you're talking about.
You know, I think you're
intentionally being vague
because you actually
find this situation amusing.
Well, it's not amusing.
Not to me.
Yeah, that's the one.
Oh, hi.
Hi. Hello.
Hi, um...
I'm Joe...
Joe Dubois. Yeah, I recognize
your wife
from the newspaper.
You must get that
all the time.
Allison.
I'm Bonnie Barrister.
I'm so excited that you're here.
Come on in.
We're thrilled
to be here.
Oh, please, come in,
make yourself at home.
JOE:
Thank you.
There's a bar in the next room,
and there's food as well.
Peter is around
here somewhere.
I have to iron out
a few wrinkles
with the caterer, but after
I'm through
I plan on finding you.
I'll be here.
Wonderful.
You're not fooling me.
That's not the look.
I see you've been abandoned.
Uh, no, he's just...
hunting and gathering.
(laughing):
Oh, my.
Does that make my
husband his prey?
(laughing)
I hope Chardonnay's okay.
Thank you.
For what it's worth,
ow Peter's very taken
with your husband.
Not just because
I'm taken with you.
I have to be honest
with you, Allison.
I don't know how
you can live with it.
I'm sorry. Live with what?
With this city
and the people in it.
The way they treated you,
the way they treated
the district attorney.
I followed that story
like a hawk.
You said that that man,
Walter Paxton,
murdered his wife and he did.
You said that the reporter,
P.D. McCall,
would get killed,
and she was.
And you found the evidence
to put Paxton away, you did.
And then it was as if
it never happened.
The district attorney was gone,
and you were treated
in the press
like some kind of pariah.
Or worse--
some kind of nut.
But you were right
about everything.
Thank you.
Oh, there's Melissa.
Have you met
my daughter Melissa?
No, I don't believe I have.
Oh, I would love for her
to meet you.
She's listened to me
talk about you
for quite a while now.
And besides, she's getting
married next month.
Oh, congratulations.
She is gonna get such
a kick out of this.
Just let me know
if you have any
premonitions.
Oh, what do you mean?
Oh, wedding-day disasters, um,
how many grandkids I can expect,
that kind of thing.
Bonnie, I need to let you know
it doesn't really work that way.
I'm joking, Allison.
I know she's here somewhere.
Oh, here's Melissa,
right over there.
Don't do this.
Oh, my God, how do I not?
How do you not?
Al, come on! You're talking
about something that,
if it happens at all,
probably won't happen for years.
I mean, look at her.
She's fine now.
JOE:
She's happy now.
She's not in Paris.
She's nowhere near
a corkscrew.
Hell, she's not even
married yet.
What's the harm
in just letting her
enjoy this party?
Are we in agreement?
Are we in agreement
about what?
About not saying anything--
not tonight.
'Cause I really don't think
that's gonna help my cause.
BONNIE:
Allison,
you took off so suddenly.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Uh, no.
I get headaches
sometimes.
Well, if you'd like,
I'm sure we have some aspirin
upstairs.
Oh, no, no.
I'm fine.
Bonnie, who...
who's that man
with Melissa?
Oh, that?
That's Steven,
Melissa's fiance.
That's her fiance?
This isn't right, Kent.
Okay, wait, wait.
Who's Kent?
I overheard somebody earlier
mention a Kent.
Oh, Kent. God, no. Kent was
Melissa's first husband.
She was married before?
Three years.
Three horrible years.
They didn't happen,
by any chance,
to have honeymooned
in Paris?
That's very good.
Isn't she something?
(chuckles)
Come on,
admit it.
That was the most fun
you've had with your clothes on
in a very long time.
Don't push your luck, buster.
You don't fool me,
uh-uh.
I saw smiles.
I saw phone numbers
being exchanged
and I saw
a kiss good-bye.
All right.
I was just trying
to help my deadbeat
husband get a job.
Yeah? Well, all right.
Methinks she doth
protest too much.
Okay, I admit it.
I liked her.
She wasn't
what I expected.
She was smart
and she was nice
and she liked me.
Bingo.
Isn't that every one
of your minimum
requirements for
friendship?
Yeah, I'm pretty easy,
aren't I?
I liked
the husband, too.
In fact, I even
like the daughter.
I know. She seemed
rather pleasant
for somebody given
to impaling her exes.
Whatever she was going through,
whatever drove her to do that
to her first husband,
it seemed like she put it
all behind her.
It seemed like it was
ancient history.
Yeah.
Thank you.
For what?
For going.
Peter took me aside
and he said that he wants
to have a second interview
with me tomorrow.
You're kidding!
When were you gonna tell me?
I don't know. I think I was
afraid to say it out loud.
I think I was afraid to jinx it.
I think I want this job
very badly.
I think
you're gonna get this job.
Do you mean you know
that I'm gonna get this job?
I don't know anything.
I just think that there's
nobody who deserves it
more than you do.
Bingo.
You just met every one
of my minimum requirements
for friendship.
Hmm, cool.
Hmm.
Mm...
I didn't want to
hurt you, Kent...
...but I'm not gonna
pretend anymore.
I'm not gonna keep
playing this game with you.
This whole thing
was a mistake.
Yeah?
I'm starting to sense that.
Paris was a bad idea.
Maybe I should have gone
with the cabin--
our secret hideaway--
but I know how much
you love that place.
I'm not mad, Melissa,
I swear.
I just want you
to put that down
before you hurt yourself,
all right?
It's okay, honey.
It's okay.
We made it through
so much before.
We're gonna make it
through this, too.
I still love you.
Ooh!
You okay?
Is everything
all right?
Oh, yeah, yeah...
No, no, it's nothing.
I'm fine.
Just more ancient history.
It's... nothing.
Hello.
Dad, it's for you!
Hi, Peter.
We have three kids.
There's no such thing
as too early.
"Family crisis,"
that's all he said?
That's it.
That and "Is there any
way that you and Allison
can come up
to the house?"
Oh, Allison, Joe, I can't
thank you enough for coming.
It's been
a rough morning.
PETER:
My daughter and future
son-in-law live in Los Angeles.
As it happens,
Steven had to fly back
after the party
last night.
Some kind of a
emergency meeting
with one of his clients
this morning.
Melissa was going to spend
a few more nights,
finalize all the wedding
plans with me, but...
PETER:
When we went out
to the guest house to get
Melissa for breakfast,
the guest house was empty.
Her things were gone,
so was she.
And I found
this message
on my phone: "Mom,
I hate to do this to you,
"but I need some time
to think.
"I'm just not sure
that I can go through
with the wedding.
"Please, don't try
to find me.
I'll keep in touch
en I can."
Does her fiance know?
I called him right before
I called you.
He's a mess.
I called the police.
Of course, she's an adult.
She's allowed to come and go
as she pleases.
Allison, I...
I don't mean to put you
on the spot, but...
I know from all the articles
I've read
that you've helped the police
find missing people before.
You dream about them, right?
Yes, but...
I thought
if you found her,
I could talk some sense
into her,
convince her that she's making
a terrible mistake.
She's done this before--
run away when
there's a lot
of pressure.
Bonnie, but what I need you
to understand is the impressions
I get, the things that I see,
I can't count on them to
point me toward your daughter
just because I want them to.
Look, uh, true confession time.
I'm fundamentally a skeptic
about these sorts of things.
I've already been
on the phone
with a number of
private investigators.
Having said that,
we obviouslyant
to make sure
we've left no
stone unturned.
Allison, I promise you,
if you come up empty,
if you come up dry,
I'll understand.
I mean, you only
just met her last night,
and briefly at that.
I really do understand.
I mean, it's not like
you've been dreaming
about her.
(voice breaking):
It's not like she's on
your wavelength
or anything.
Well, I guess
you're helping
the Barristers.
I mean, what else could I say?
She's desperate, and so nice.
I have been dreaming
about her daughter. I have.
And you're trying to get
a job from her husband.
And I just... I... I didn't feel
like there was anything else
I could say.
I mean, it's true.
All the dreams
I've had about her
have been about her past.
But still, I mean,
what else could I say?
You said the only
thing you could say.
Thank you.
And, just remember,
if we ever hope
to send our three
girls to college,
you damn well
better find her.
Okay. How about this?
Is it possible
that you've dreaming about Paris
because that's
where Melissa's run off to?
That makes no sense.
Makes sense to me.
Oh, come on.
What woman in her right mind
would go to the place where
her first marriage fell apart
to figure out whether or not
to get married a second time?
Moving on.
What else do you remember
from that first dream?
Well, she was upset.
She didn't want to be there--
Paris, I mean.
That's it?
That's it.
He poured her a glass of wine,
she stabbed him through
the hand with a corkscrew.
Those are the highlights.
What?
That's all right.
I didn't want
to work there, anyway.
All right, that's not fair.
It's not my fault
that the dreams I'm having
have nothing to do
with where she is now.
The second one
same as the first?
Yes. Second one
same as the first.
Corkscrew through hand.
Smashed bottle against wall.
Sounds romantic.
She said that Paris
had been a mistake.
He said they should
have gone to the cabin.
What?
He called it
their secret hideaway.
The cabin.
That's what he called it.
Did either of them happen
to mention where it was?
I'm going to call Peter.
He's not going to
know where it is.
It's a secret hideaway.
Yeah, well, maybe he can
help us find his ex-son-in-law.
He's got to know where it is.
It was his secret.
I hate these foreground trees.
I hated them yesterday,
ill hate them today.
Mr. Henley?
Hi. My name's Allison Dubois.
I spoke with your receptionist
about an hour ago.
Oh, right, uh... yeah.
Bonnie and Peter's friend.
Have we met before?
Maybe one
of their parties?
You look
awfully familiar.
Mrs. Dubois?
Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
Bonnie tried to tell me
what exactly it was
you did for a living,
and I didn't get it.
This is it.
This and six other buildings
like it.
We design and create exhibits
for museums and exhibitions
all over the world.
That's very
impressive.
Thank you.
This is one of those days
where I feel like an
overpaid window dresser.
So thank you.
Now, what can
I do for you?
Are you shopping
for a life-sized,
historical diorama
of your very own?
Or is there something else
I can help you with today?
Mr. Henley, actually,
I was hoping
to talk to you
about your ex-wife.
She's missing.
"Missing" may be overstating it.
Uh, she ran away.
Her parents are very
concerned about her.
Sounds like my Melissa.
So what scared her off
this time?
I don't know how
much you know.
I don't know how much the two
of you have kept in contact.
She's planning on getting
married next month.
Mel and I haven't spoken
in years.
I needed to do some healing
after our marriage ended.
And for my own peace of mind
I just had to cut off contact
for a little while.
I understand.
I'm sorry-- I didn't mean to
stir up any painful memories.
Just no one else seems to know
where she might be.
So you thought you'd come
to the last guy
that Melissa ran out on,
and see if he could
shed any light.
I know the two of
you had a cabin.
Now I know where
I know you from.
You were in the papers
a while back.
You worked with that
district attorney, right?
The one who messed up
the serial killer thing?
Well, same old Bonnie.
Leave it to her
to find someone like you
to help her
with Melissa.
Now what did you say?
That we had a cabin?
No. We didn't
have a cabin.
There was a cabin
that we rented,
that Melissa really liked.
It was on Lake Mead.
And I think
she liked it so much
because her parents
didn't know about it.
It was kind of
our secret hideaway.
Is that where you think
she might be?
I'm not sure.
I'm just trying to help.
We went there maybe
three or four times,
but Melissa handled
all the arrangements,
so I don't even remember
the address.
I'm sorry.
The owner's first name
was Chuck, I think.
Sorry.
I know Peter and Bonnie are
probably beside themselves.
But she'll turn up.
She always does.
Say hi to them for me,
will you?
Yeah. Thank you.
JOE:
Yeah, Lake Mead.
Well, we hope it helps.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
Bye.
I take it no one has heard
from Melissa yet?
Not yet.
They're going to call the
Lake Mead Tourist Board
first thing in
the morning.
See if they know of any
locals named Chuck
who have cabins for rent.
It would be
completely wrong
during ts
periodcrisis
to wonder when...
and if he's ever going
to offer you that job,
wouldn't it?
Yes.
It would be
completely wrong.
But I can't help but
wonder either.
Is there some
particular reason
you don't want to take
this to the Barristers?
Allison, this is not an
easy call to make.
"Hey, sorry to wake you up
"in the middle of the night,
Peter,
"but my wife
thinks your daughter
is in the clutches
of some maniac."
You don't get
to pick and choose
Hey...
which dreams you want
to believe in.
Listen, I'm not asking
to pick and choose.
I'm just saying that
if we're going to deliver
this horrific news,
can we at least serve it up
with a side order of hope?
Just tell me that
you saw the,
the make and model
of the car
or the license plate.
That you have some clue as
to where all this happened.
This was just supposed to be
so simple.
Dream the dream.
Find the girl.
Get the job.
Do we have to wake them up
in the middle of the night?
Do you think it'll hold
till morning?
It's like you said...
I don't have any clues,
just bad news.
Yeah, I think
it'll hold till morning.
The trunk of someone's car?
Allison, um...
our daughter left us a message.
She needed time to think.
She wasn't abducted.
She wasn't kidnapped.
Yes, we asked you to
help us find her
but, uh...
I don't think what you're saying
makes much sense.
I know how strange
this sounds.
The dream was very clear.
Your daughter is
in danger.
I think you need
to call the police.
I think you need to file
a missing persons report.
I think you need
to launch a search for her.
We launch this search
on the basis of nothing other
than this woman's dreams
and it turns out she's fine?
Turns out she's
doing exactly
what she said she
was going to do?
Thinking?
She's going to be furious
with us.
Peter, this woman is
trying to help us.
She's trying
to warn us.
She was right
about Lake Mead.
I was?
Partially.
We called there first thing
this morning.
There is a cabin owner
named Chuck.
I don't remember his last name.
He knew exactly
who Melissa was.
He rented a place to her
several times before.
But he hasn't heard from her
in years.
And she certainly
isn't up there now.
Fine, Peter. You win.
She's only half right.
Look,
all I'm saying is we have three
different private investigators
out there looking for her.
Why don't
we take a step back.
You take a step back.
Someone I trust is telling me
my daughter is being
held against her will.
I know what I
have to do.
I'm calling
the police.
PETER:
She's changed a lot
since that
time but...
Peter does not look happy.
What other choice
do we have, Joe?
Well, how seriously are the
police going to take all this
once they hear
that you're involved?
No one's going to mention me.
Oh, excuse me.
Steven, hi.
Uh, come in.
Come, come in.
My plane got in
a little early.
My favorite
son-in-law to be.
I'm glad you're here.
What...
What is all this?
Steven...
I can't give you
specifics just now,
but suffice it to say that
we have reason to believe
that someone may be holding
Melissa somewhere
against her will.
You're kidding me,
right?
But that's not possible.
I don't want to believe
it either...
No. You don't understand.
It's actually not possible.
She just left me a message
an hour ago.
(on voicemail):
Hey. It's me.
I know I'm being a coward,
leaving a message, but...
I just didn't think
I could handle talking to you.
Not yet.
I'm not going to tell you
where I am,
but I wanted you to know
that I was safe.
That I'm thinking about you.
About us.
I just need little more time
to figure it all out.
When I do, I'll be in touch.
I promise.
BONNIE:
Oh...
I turned my phone back on
when the plane landed,
there it was.
She knew I was flying back
from L.A. today.
I figured she did it
on purpose.
Called my cell when
she knew it'd be off,
so she could
avoid speaking to me.
Oh, thank God
she's okay.
Thank God.
I'd, uh...
I'd better explain
to the detectives
why we won't be needing
their assistance after all.
As for the two of you,
I suggest you slip out
of here quietly,
before I ask these police
officers to find something
to charge you with.
Hey.
???
Kids down?
Yep.
And out.
All except Ariel.
What you doing?
I'm looking for a job.
How's it going?
Well, that depends.
How you feel
about Oregon?
I'm so sorry.
I know how badly
you wanted that job.
I know how badly we needed
that job.
I just...
(sighs):
I don't know.
Okay.
Guess I'll go to bed.
Co here.
REPORTER:
A federal jury in Chicago
found reputed Mob boss
Joseph Binale Nardiello
guilty on all charges today
after a five-month trial
in federal court.
A racketeering conspiracy charge
included in the indictment
carries a maximum sentence
of 20 years in federal prison.
Sentencing will be set
on February 28.
You ?
See? Someone had
a day worse than ours.
(on TV):
And...
(remote clicks):
Morning paper! Read all about...
Big news out of Chicago today
as Joseph Binale Nardiello
was found guilty
on all charges,
after a five-month trial.
You okay?
Everything all right?
Yeah.
I think so.
You remember
when I told you
that Melissa would never
have gone back to Paris
to figure out whether or not
she wanted to marry Steven?
I think I must
have been wrong.
Oh, Mr. Henley.
Ah, thank goodness.
I was afraid
I might've missed you.
You have so many buildings here,
I wasn't sure
this was the right one.
Mrs. Dubois,
did you call?
Was somebody
in my organization
supposed to let me know
that you wanted to see me?
No, it all happened
spontaneously.
You said that you
had read about me.
Yeah.
I had a dream
last night...
a dream about Melissa,
about where she may be.
I know this sounds crazy,
but I think that
she may be in Paris.
I think she may be
in the hotel
that the two of you
honeymooned in.
What?!
It doesn't make a lot
of sense to me either,
but there you go.
Anyway, I spent
most of my day
trying to figure out
which hotel in Paris.
And it's a long story,
but I can't really ask
Bonnie and Peter.
And then I realized...
I could ask you.
I know it
sounds crazy.
Let me get this straight--
you... you saw Melissa...
in the same hotel that
she and I honeymooned in...
in a dream?
Okay, um...
Residence de Bastille.
???
Yeah.
But I'm afraid you're
not gonna find her there.
Why do you say that?
It was torn down in 2003.
No, are you sure?
Positive. I tried to book
a room there last year.
Look...
I don't mean to tell you
your business, but...
it sounds to me like...
your dream was just a dream.
You okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
WOMAN:
Phoenix Police Department,
may I help you?
(hushed):
What are you doing here?
Do you have any
idea how much trouble
I'll be in if
anybody saw you?
What if Van Dyke
walked in?
Wait a second.
I'm confused.
How could anything
you've seen
possibly have
happened in the present,
in Paris, no less,
if that hotel room
doesn't exist anymore?
I think he built it.
The hotel room--
He recreated it
down to the titiniest detail.
I think he even
duplicated the view.
You're serious?
Look, I know how it sounds.
I tossed and turned
about this all last night.
But this is what this guy does.
He builds dioramas.
He builds environments.
So you're saying you think
that Melissa Barrister
is being held captive
in some fake Paris hotel room
that this guy built
over there at his business?
But why?
I don't know.
She's about to marry again.
Maybe the idea
of losing her forever...
I think he thought
he could win her back.
All right, look,
even if I could
wrap my mind around
the idea of this lovesick guy
building an elaborate
stage set
to woo his ex-wife...
...there's no way
I can get a warrant
to search that complex
on the basis of a dream.
It's not gonna happen.
I know that.
I'm just worried.
He knows who I am.
He knows I'm looking.
He knows I know
about that hotel room.
I think I may have
rattled his cage.
I am concerned
about what he may do to her.
No, no, no, I hear that.
But I still can't
legally go in there.
I mean, it's not like somebody
called in a fire alarm
or a chemical spill
or a bomb threat.
What are you saying?
I mean, I'm going to be in that
area around 10:30 this morning.
About an hour
and fifteen from now.
And you know,
if somebody did call in,
like a fire or a bomb threat,
something like that,
then being in the area,
I'd actually be legally obliged
to assist the emergency crews--
walk through every building,
each and every room
in that complex to make sure
that everyone was evacuated.
But failing that...
Oh...
In any case, I'm sorry
I couldn't have been more help.
Somebody please
let me out of here!
Please let me out!
Please!
Somebody, please!
Somebody...
(door opening)
NEWSCASTER:
Melissa Barrister was released
from Casa Valley Memorial
Hospital this morning
where she was held for 24-hour
observation after spending
four nights a captive of her
ex-husband, Kent Henley.
Mr. Henley, who abducted
his former wife at gunpoint,
went to great lengths
to give her family
the impression
that she had run away,
even going so far as to force
Ms. Barrister to leave a message
on her fiance's cell phone
that indicated she was
safe and would come home soon.
In other news...
BRIDGETTE:
This is so not fair.
They didn't even mention
how Mommy helped.
Here, hon.
Well, it's okay, honey.
Mommy's had more than enough
attention the last few months.
Mr. Barrister knows,
though, right?
Now he'll give you the job?
Uh, well, he would
give Daddy the job,
except he doesn't own
the company anymore.
He called us last night
to let us know
that he was selling it.
He wanted to stay home
with his daughter,
help her get better after
everything she'd been through.
Okay, but doesn't
the new owner
still need an engineer?
Uh... I'm pretty sure
that Aerodytech
has all the engineers
they can handle.
Aerodytech?
Your old company
is the new owner?
Mm-hmm.
That's so not fair.
What are you doing?
Still looking for a job.
Any luck?
Um, that depends.
How do you feel about Oregon?
You mean building it
or actually living there?
Come here.
???
??
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入