Previously on 24.
As soon as I get the recording, we're
going to have to involve your father.
You know I don't like
to be kept in the dark.
Tell me what this is all about.
I will. I just need a minute.
I decide what needs to be done,
Mr. Anderson.
I never authorized you
to kill David Palmer.
President Logan?
And a man named
Christopher Henderson.
I know what you did.
I know what you're doing.
And I'm going to
put an end to it.
You asked to see me,
Mr. President?
Hal, I'm asking Secretary Heller
to tender his resignation
and I wanted you
here as a witness.
What?!
He came here to accuse me of being
complicit in today's terrorist attacks.
- Miles set me up.
- Please come with us, Ms. O'Brian.
We traced your call to a public
phone at Van Nuys Airport.
If Audrey Raines is at that location,
you're in a lot of trouble.
You're supposed
to be in custody.
You helped Audrey Raines
break surveillance.
You're sick and you need help
and if you try to stop me,
I will recommend you for
psychiatric evaluation.
Get in here.
I haven't been able to
contact Jack or Audrey.
I haven't talked
to them either.
Whatever you tell me will remain
between the two of us. I promise you.
Not here.
Outside the south stable.
- Is Bauer dead?
- Not yet, Mr. President.
- He has the recording.
- Yes, sir.
That evidence directly implicates
me in David Palmer's death.
- Son of a bitch.
- What the hell's going on?!
They've come for the recording.
- Audrey!
- I have her, Jack!
What have you done to her?
The left brachial artery.
She has about three minutes
before she bleeds to death.
- Now throw me that recording.
- Jack, don't do it.
She's running out of time.
- Don't give it up.
- Here it is.
Easy, easy.
- Stay with me.
- Jack!
Stay with me.
I need to loosen
the tourniquet.
Good. The bleeding's stopped,
which means he didn't
sever the brachial artery.
I need to get you to a doctor.
Jack, I can wait.
Do what you have to do.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Keep your arm elevated.
Chloe O'Brian is not available.
Chloe's not picking
up her phone.
Is there someone else who
can help you track Henderson?
No one who has the same access
to the CTU satellite network.
Jack, I'm so sorry.
This is my fault.
Audrey, stop it.
I'll be right back.
- This is Jack Bauer.
- Jack?
Why are you answering
Wexler's phone?
Wexler's dead.
Henderson and a commando unit
attacked us 15 minutes ago.
They killed all your men
and took the recording back.
- Is Audrey all right?
- She's fine.
Did you cut your
deal with Logan?
Logan accepted my terms.
Then he took a call,
and suddenly changed his mind.
That call must have
come from Henderson.
Jack, we have to get
the recording back.
If there's anything I can do to help,
let me know.
With all due respect,
Mr. Secretary,
I asked you for your help,
and you betrayed me.
Jack, I did what I thought
was best for this country.
I made a mistake.
Please forgive me.
I need to go, sir.
Come on.
- Hello?
- Bill, it's Jack.
Jack, we've been waiting
to hear from you.
Did you get the recording
to Secretary Heller?
I don't have time to explain.
Henderson's got the recording.
I need Chloe to help me find him,
but I can't reach her.
Chloe's here with me, Jack.
She was arrested by Homeland
Security for helping you,
- but she managed to get away.
- Put her on speaker.
- Jack, where are you?
- I'm at Van Nuys Airfield.
Chloe, listen to me.
Henderson left here ten minutes ago
with a recording that
implicates President Logan.
I need you to access CTU's satellite
data streams so that we can find him.
If I log onto their system, they're
gonna find me eventually, no matter what
I do.
I don't need you to track him for long.
Do you think you can do it?
I guess I can try to slip
in through the subnets.
Get back to me when you're in.
I'll set up a VPN pathway,
so that they can't trace our call,
but it will only work with
the phone you're using.
Okay. I got a hold of Chloe.
We need to go. Can you get up?
- Yeah.
- Slowly.
If we're going to do
extensive satellite tracking,
I need more than my laptop. I'm gonna
have to network onto your computer,
even though it's
kind of pathetic,
and I need you to get that
screen to work for me.
All right.
I hope you don't mind
me bossing you around,
but  technically,
I don't work for you anymore.
- That's all right, Chloe.
- Good.
Bauer.
Jack, I'm pulling up satellite footage
of the airfield from 15 minutes ago.
Look for an explosion in
the northwest corner.
Okay, I see it.
About  five minutes after that,
a vehicle leaves the airfield.
That'll be Henderson.
He went south on the service drive,
and east on Menders,
then I lose him on the grid.
Use another satellite, traffic cams,
whatever you have to, just find him.
It's gonna take
us a few minutes.
We're just setting up,
but we're on it.
Copy that. Get back to me as soon
as you got him on a live feed.
What makes you think that
Henderson hasn't already
destroyed the recording?
He would have done it immediately,
in front of me.
Given me less of a reason
to come after him.
- Why would he keep it?
- It's his insurance.
- Yes.
- Is Bauer dead?
No.
What happened?
All that matters is that
I have the recording.
- Have you destroyed it?
- No, sir, I have not.
Why, what's the problem?
Actually, I'm making sure
they're won't be any problems.
I don't understand.
I may need protection.
That recording gives it to me.
- Protection?
- Yes, sir.
Do you mean from me?
That's absurd.
With all due respect,
Mr. President,
it isn't absurd,
as evidenced by Walt Cummings suicide.
That was different.
You told me yourself
that was necessary.
And I'm assuming that one day,
others will tell you the
very same thing about me.
Chris, you and I have been
in this from the beginning.
Destroying that recording
protects both of us.
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
I give you my word it will be
kept in a very place safe,
and will only be made public should
I meet with some... accident.
Chris, this is
completely unnecessary.
I'm sure it is, sir.
Then again, I am a very cautious man.
Chloe, have you
got Henderson yet?
Yes, his car is three quarters
of a mile in front of you.
He had a head start.
He should be farther along than that.
I don't know what to tell you.
It's definitely the car
he left the airport in.
How long until
I've got a visual?
The road curves up ahead, Jack.
You should be able to see
him once it straightens out.
Hold on.
Got him.
Get down.
Damn!
It's over, Christopher.
Turn around!
Put the gun down and keep
your hands where I can them.
Do it or I will kill you!
You kill me, Jack,
Secretary Heller dies, too.
What are you talking about?
There's always a contingency plan, Jack.
You know that.
My men have been tracking Heller from a
chopper ever since he left
Logan's Retreat.
Now, if I can't contact them
every 15 minutes on the dot,
they have orders to
kill Secretary Heller.
Which means, you got about
three minutes to save his life.
Jack?
Audrey, please get
back in the car.
Is he lying about my father?
Slowly walk towards me.
Put your hands
behind your head.
Get on your knees.
Cuff yourself.
Yeah, Jack.
Chloe, patch me through to
Secretary Heller's cell phone.
See if you can get a satellite
to lock on his signal.
I need you to download a visual
of his vehicle on my PDA.
He was leaving Logan's
retreat just before 1:00.
On it. Open up the parallel
channel on the NSA's landsats,
can radial slices in three mile
increments, emanating from the
Retreat... sir.
Okay, Jack,
I'm pulling up the DOD database.
Here it is,
I'm patching you through.
Copy that.
- Heller.
- Mr. Secretary, it's Jack.
I need you to confirm for me if a
helicopter's been tracking your vehicle?
- What's going on, Jack?
- Sir, time is critical.
Is there a helicopter
above you or not?
Yeah, there's a chopper above me.
Who are they?
Henderson's men.
He claims he's given them orders
to kill you if I don't let him go.
Is he bluffing?
He doesn't do that, sir.
Jack, I've got Heller's car.
I'm patching it through to your PDA.
Copy that.
Jack...  they have a laser
sight trained on me.
Get up.
You give me the recording, I let you go:
that's the deal.
No.
Come on, Jack,
you're wasting time.
We both know you're not
going to let Heller die.
I  can hear him, Jack;
don't let him do this.
I'm going to walk
out of here, Jack,
and you're not gonna stop me,
so uncuff me.
Jack, don't let him go.
- I don't have a choice, sir.
- Yes, you do.
If I had listened to
you in the first place,
none of this would be happening.
This is my responsibility,
I will not allow Logan and
Henderson to use me as a pawn.
Sir?
Do not let them
get away with this.
Make sure that the recording
gets to the right people.
Tell Audrey I love her.
Mr. Secretary,
what are you doing?!
No.
Chloe, are you
still on the line?!
Can you confirm that Heller just
drove his car into the lake?
- Yes.
- Damn you!
Oh, my God, no.
How could you do this?
This isn't about what you
think is best for the country.
This is about your
greed for power.
Today, you have been responsible for
killing an ex-president, David Palmer,
and the secretary of defense,
two real patriots.
Damn you!
What happened to you?
- Give me the recording.
- I don't have it.
Where is it?!
I'm not going to tell you, Jack, and you
know that-- no matter what you do
to me.
Do it.
Kill him, Jack. Do it!
Yeah.
- Graham?
- Yes.
You need to cancel the action
against Henderson immediately.
Why?
He has the recording,
but he's made arrangements
to have it released if
anything happens to him.
You should have exercised
more control over him.
There's a limit to
how much I can do.
- Apparently.
- Don't.
Don't you use that tone with me.
We've both made mistakes today.
You're right, Mr. President,
my apologies, but the fact is,
I think we have a bigger
problem than Henderson.
What? What are
you talking about?
At least he can be trusted to act
rationally, in his own interest.
Unfortunately, the same
is not true of your wife.
My wife.
Apparently, there's a secret
service agent named Aaron Pierce
who knows a little
more than he should.
He intends to share
that with Martha.
I'm well aware of that, and I've
taken steps to deal with Agent Pierce.
But the real problem
is Mrs. Logan.
She continues to talk, to ask questions,
talk about her suspicions.
People don't take her seriously.
They think she's unstable.
There are too many
loose ends lying around.
We cannot afford to have her pull
on one and unravel everything.
You think I don't realize that?
I think you're in a
very difficult position
and that you have been hoping the
situation with Martha would
resolve itself,
but it hasn't.
You must silence her.
- I know.
- But I'll handle this myself.
Mrs.  Logan,
Agent Pierce was transferred.
That's what you keep saying,
but it doesn't make any sense,
not at 1:00 in the morning.
We work around
the clock, ma'am.
It's quite common for agents to get
pulled off details at odd hours.
Right when they're supposed to have a
meeting with the First Lady of the US?
I don't know anything
about a meeting.
Well, I do! I found Aaron's
phone laying on the ground,
right where we were
supposed to meet.
Now, I want you to
find Agent Pierce,
and I want you to get him back here,
right now!
There's a glitch in the
scheduling software,
I can not pull that
record up right now.
And are these glitches quite common,
as well?
- Actually, no, but...
- Mrs. Logan.
I'm Agent Adams.
I think I can explain everything.
Well?
This is a sensitive
issue, ma'am.
President Logan would
like you to come with me.
Ma'am.
What is this
"sensitive" information?
Is it about Agent Pierce?
I'm sorry-- you need to talk
to the president about that.
I'm asking you.
Do you know where
Aaron Pierce is?
No, ma'am, I don't.
Is this where my husband is?
I want to talk to him.
Charles?
Hello?
Yeah.
Henderson wasn't lying.
He doesn't have the recording on him.
Could it be in his car?
No, he wouldn't have
left it behind.
There must have been some kind
of a hand-off. What do you mean?
Well, that would explain why he
wasn't any farther ahead of me
when I left Van Nuys Airfield. He must
have stopped and given it to someone.
Okay, I'll back trace the
route with the satellite,
see if I can spot anything.
Yeah.
Jack, we're getting that
recording and exposing Logan.
I don't care how far I have to go or
what I have to do, do you
understand, Jack?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Jack, you were right,
I found the hand-off.
Henderson stopped and
rendezvoused with another car.
I'm sorry I didn't
see it before.
Can you track the other car?
We're tracking it now, Jack.
It headed back to Van Nuys.
Looks like the civilian
side of the airfield.
Pulled onto the tarmac.
Whoever was in it got out and
got directly onto the plane.
Isn't air traffic
still grounded?
Yeah, this is not a
commercial flight.
I'll find out what
I can about it.
Jack, the plane is servicing.
It's about to take off.
Has Curtis been relieved of his duty,
or is he still attached to CTU?
He's at CTU,
taking orders from Homeland Security,
but I think we can
trust him, Jack.
- Where is he?
- According to the deployment grid,
he's 25 miles northwest of you,
with a tac team.
Bill, I want you to call him.
Get him to this location
as soon as possible.
I want him to transfer Henderson
and Audrey back to CTU.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Logan's in control at CTU.
Curtis will be able
to protect them.
Right now,
it's our best chance to secure Henderson
and get Audrey the medical
attention she needs.
- Calling Curtis now, Jack.
- Thanks.
What's happening?
The person Henderson
gave the recording to
just boarded a plane
at Van Nuys Airfield.
Why aren't you going now?
I'll go as soon as Curtis gets here--
he's not far.
- Jack, I'll be fine until then.
- I'm not leaving you here alone.
Jack,  if you don't get that recording,
my father will have died for nothing.
Jack... for me.
Henderson is secure.
When he regains consciousness, I don't
want you going anywhere near him.
You don't even talk to him.
You understand me?
I understand.
We have to assume his people
are still looking for him.
They're gonna be monitoring
all non-VPN cell traffic,
which means, you can't make or receive
any calls unless they come from me.
Here's Wexler's cell.
I've got the number.
All right.
Audrey, I don't feel
right about this.
I'm going to be all right.
I'm so sorry.
Jack, you have to go now.
Jack?
Make sure you get
that recording.
I will.
Let me know as soon
as you're done.
Vladimir Bierko has
regained consciousness.
But we're still waiting
for the medical assessment
to be finished before we
can begin the interrogation.
Let me know when they
give us the go ahead.
Final protocol shifts.
You can tell Washington
the transfer of authority from CTU
to Homeland is officially complete.
Okay.
Two hours ahead of schedule, Karen.
That is remarkable.
I'm sorry,
my head is somewhere else.
Where?
We gave the President Bauer's
location over an hour ago.
We should have heard
something by now.
The military authority
is handling Bauer.
Yes, I know,
but this doesn't make any sense.
The President insisted we redirect
our focus from Henderson to Bauer.
We find Bauer, and then he hands
the mission over to the military.
Karen, we're out of that loop.
- Karen Hayes.
- Ma'am, we have a problem.
Chloe O'Brian got
out of holding,
and as far as I can tell,
she's not in the building.
Not in the building?
How's that possible?
I'm still gathering the details.
But I reviewed the surveillance tape,
and it looks like Shari had a
conversation with her, and Shari let
her go.
Shari didn't try
to stop her? Why?
I don't know. She won't tell me.
I had security take her into custody.
Good. Bring her up
here right now.
We need to focus on
how we find Chloe now.
My guess is she'll
try to contact Bauer.
I agree, but how?
She was using CTU resources
before to help Bauer.
Maybe she'll try that again.
Which means she could try to
access our system remotely.
- All she needs is a laptop.
- That's right.
- She'll disguise her traffic.
- Can you get through that?
I can trace her physical location
by looking at the binaries.
Do it.
Wait outside.
Why did you let Chloe escape?
- She intimidated me.
- She intimidated you? Sit down.
You are in a great deal trouble,
Miss Rothenberg.
You had better start
talking to me now.
She said she'd recommend me
for psychiatric evaluation.
I'd lose my job.
I'm sorry, Miss Hayes.
There's something wrong with me,
I know that. Shari...
And I should probably
see someone...
Shari!
Did Chloe tell you why she was
helping Audrey Raines and Bauer?
- She thinks Jack is innocent.
- Based on what?
Based on some absurd idea that
President Logan framed Bauer.
She even said something about
President Logan being involved
in the assassination of David Palmer.
I mean, can you believe her?
And people think I'm crazy.
Damn it, open this door!
I don't know what you think you're
doing, but you'd better think again!
Unlock it.
Open it!
Charles.
I want that man arrested!
And I want know where
Aaron Pierce is.
Shh.
Martha, calm down.
All right? Aaron's fine.
I just transferred him back
to Washington, that's all.
In the middle of the night?
Doesn't make any sense.
And why am I locked in this room?
'Cause we need to talk.
About what?
Martha, I've been
wanting to tell you this,
but I told myself that you
were too fragile to handle it.
But that's not the truth.
The truth is, I've kept this
from you because it's horrible
and because it's ugly.
What are you talking about?
What happened to David Palmer
wasn't supposed to happen.
He put himself in harm's way,
and he got involved with
something that he shouldn't have.
What are you saying?
That I never
authorized his death.
You... mean...
you know who killed David?
Yes.
How do you know that?
- He works for me.
- What?
- Martha, it's very complicated.
- What?!
- There's an explanation.
- What?! An explanation?! Oh, my God!
- Stop!
- Go to hell!
Stop! You don't understand!
Oh, my God!
You're involved in David's murder.
Martha...
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Why are you telling me this?
Because you're on your way to
finding out the truth on your own.
And because you need to stop.
Stop what?
You have to stop
asking questions,
you have to stop talking about
this to everyone. Never again.
Martha, do you realize how traumatic
this would be for the country
if people were to find out?
Oh, yes,
we're worried about the country.
Damn it, Martha!
That's the most important part of this!
This scandal would destroy the American
people's faith in their government.
It would destroy our
credibility all over the world.
You lied to me.
Everything.
This whole day has
been one giant lie.
What you've done makes me sick!
Martha, enough!
I know that what I did,
what I allowed to happen, was a mistake.
It was a terrible mistake.
But it's done.
Right now, I need you to swear to
me that you will do as I ask...
for the country, Martha.
I've forgiven you many things,
Charles, but not this.
You've broken my heart.
I'm looking at you...
I hate you.
But I will keep my mouth shut.
Because the people of this
country don't deserve to suffer.
You do, Charles. You do.
Are you sure we're going to get
through this the way we planned?
What does that mean?
There's too many loose ends.
What operation doesn't
have loose ends?
Of course we're not going to get
through this the way we planned.
No one ever does.
I have never made
a deal in my life
that didn't feel like it was going
to fall apart in the 11th hour.
Now, if you don't have the
stomach to deal with a few bumps,
then this is not the
room where you belong.
And that goes for all of you.
You're starting to have doubts.
I can smell it,
and I don't like it.
You need to remember the strength we had
18 months ago when we started
this thing.
We okay, Ron?
Yeah.
Think about your kids.
That's what I do when
I need to get focused.
Yeah?
The situation with
Martha is taken care of.
- I spoke to her.
- And?
And I made it very clear that if
she continues with this behavior,
I will send her back to
the hospital in Vermont.
Well, you were going to have
her committed earlier today.
But you changed your mind?
It's because she
found out the truth.
And I decided I should
keep her close.
What if she finds
out the truth again?
She won't.
And if she does, I will handle it,
just like I have all day.
Okay. Fair enough.
You have done a remarkable job today,
Mr. President. I will admit that.
Thank you.
It's about time I heard
some words of appreciation.
Oh, listen to me,
we were just talking about
how you've had to be on the
front line through this,
how you've had to
get your hands dirty,
while we could just sit back
and watch from a safe distance.
You've earned our trust.
And I am sure...
that you will do whatever it
takes to keep your wife in line.
Audrey.
Where's Jack?
I'm sorry about your father.
I never intended your father
to get in the middle of this.
I've known Secretary Heller a very
long time. He's an honorable man.
What time is it?
It's ten to 12 minutes since...
If those windows didn't collapse
when that car hit the water,
it could have created an
air pocket or something.
20, 30 minutes in a submerged car, even
at 100 feet, if there was an air pocket.
Stop it.
Your father could be alive.
Secretary... Secretary Heller
could be alive inside that car.
If he's alive,
you got to do something about it.
I mean, if there's a
possibility that he's living,
you got to call military authority or
the emergency services or something.
I mean, for God's sake,
he's your father.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop talking!
What, do you think I'm stupid?
You want me to make that phone call
so that your people can find me.
Audrey, my people are
going to find us anyway.
And Jack's not going
to stop all this.
I'm trying to help your father.
Your father's drowning in a car,
and you're not doing anything about it.
You're gonna live with that
the rest of your life.
Shut up.
He is dying, and you are doing nothing,
Audrey. You are doing nothing.
I swear to God,
not another word.
- Yeah?
- Jack.
I've got a visual on the plane.
It must be some kind
of diplomatic flight.
There's a lot of
security on the ground.
- We have a problem.
- What?
I've been tracking the helicopter that
Henderson's men used to shadow
Secretary Heller.
And?
It changed course, it's heading towards
where Audrey's holding Henderson.
How could they find them?
I don't know-- maybe they're
using satellite imagery, too.
The point is,
they're going to be there any second.
Where's Curtis?
Based on the speed
of the chopper,
he might not make it there
before Henderson's men, Jack.
Upload your visual to my PDA.
Advise Curtis of the situation,
I'll get back to you.
- Jack?
- Audrey, listen to me.
Henderson's men have zeroed
in on your location,
they're heading
back towards you.
You've got to get
out of there now.
- And just leave him?
- We don't have a choice.
Yes, we do, Jack.
I have the gun and I can kill him.
Audrey, we need him alive.
Curtis's team is almost there,
they'll track him down
and they will secure him.
You've got to get out of there.
Jack, he's responsible for the
death of my father's death.
I can't just leave him here!
Audrey, please,
listen to what I'm telling you.
You've got to start moving now.
Audrey!
Stipes, get over and get
these handcuffs off me.
Heller's daughter's somewhere
in this building-- kill her.
Then get back here,
we'll deal with Bauer.
Audrey, it's Curtis.
Stay behind me.
Secure him for
transport back to CTU.
Yes, sir.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Hostiles are down and we
have Henderson in custody.
- Yeah?
- It's me.
What's happening?
Curtis's team killed Henderson's men and
they're taking Henderson into custody.
Jack, I tried to shoot him,
but I couldn't.
The only thing that matters
is that you're safe.
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
Yeah. Okay, good.
Let me speak to Curtis.
Curtis? It's Jack.
Go ahead.
Yeah, Jack?
Curtis, I want you to transport Audrey
back to CTU as quickly as possible.
And get her over to Medical.
And I want you to
tell Karen Hayes
that no one is have access
to Christopher Henderson.
She'll be taken care of.
But as far as Henderson goes,
CTU is more interested in apprehending
you than taking your advice.
Just do what you can.
I'll get back to you.
Jack, is Audrey all right?
Yeah, she's gonna be fine.
Curtis is in control of the situation.
Chloe, what have you
got on the plane?
The details just came in.
You were right,
it is a chartered diplomatic flight,
security-level eight, scheduled
to leave at 2:00 A.M. or sooner.
Okay, we need to find out who's
onboard so we can try and figure out
who Henderson passed
off the recording to.
I'll try-- it's not going to be easy
getting past the State
Department's firewall.
I understand.
Bill, see if you could slow down
the departure of this flight
so I can figure out
a way to get on it.
All right, Jack.
There's a maintenance gate on the
northwest side of the airfield.
You should be able to get
close to the plane there.
I know, I'm there.
Just get back to me as soon as
you've got the passenger list.
Copy that.
- All clear.
- Go ahead.
Yeah?
Jack, we've tried everything we can,
there's no way to delay the plane.
It's taking off in
less than ten minutes.
Okay. Has Chloe got
the passenger list yet?
I still can't get
past the firewall.
- Chloe, I need that list.
- Jack, I'm trying.
There you are.
- Yeah?
- I got O'Brian.
Did you find her on our system?
Yes, she's using
one of our nodes
to try to log-in to the
State Department network.
Do we know why?
No, but she was using a work
around I'd never seen before.
So I machine-coded a
matrix to get through...
Miles, we just need to find her.
Where she is?
I'm running a physical trace.
It's a private house.
Cross-referencing with
property records.
Karen... she's working out
of Bill Buchanan's house.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
We have a Tac Team not far away.
I'll dispatch them now.
What's their ETA?
I'm showing less
then seven minutes.
Good, keep me posted.
Novick.
Mike, it's Karen Hayes.
Karen. How are things
going over there?
It's a rough transition from CTU to
Homeland, but we're getting through it.
That's good to hear.
What do you need?
I need some clarification.
We were sent over here on a
directive from the White House,
but we've been dealing exclusively
with Vice President Gardner
until about two hours ago.
What happened two hours ago?
The president called me himself
and ordered me to arrest Jack Bauer
on evidence he was
unwilling to share with me.
Yes. I know about that.
Have you seen the evidence?
No, actually, I haven't.
Mike... Who has seen it?
I don't have a good
answer for that.
Are you telling me
you're not in the loop?
Actually...
I don't even think
there is a loop.
The president is keeping his
own counsel at the moment.
- That's a first.
- Yes. It is.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
Uh, nothing that I can
say with any authority.
All I know is that...
it's been a strange night.
I see.
I wish I could be more helpful.
No, Mike, actually,
you've been very helpful. Thank you.
- Hello?
- This is Karen Hayes.
You have less than seven minutes
to get Chloe out of there.
Karen, I don't know what you're
talking about, Chloe's not here.
Bill, stop. Miles traced Chloe
through a remote node she's accessing.
And if you don't believe me,
tell her he used a machine-coded
matrix to find her.
Karen, why are you warning us?
Because I may have made
a mistake earlier.
A lot of things have
not made sense today,
until Shari told me
what Chloe said.
About President Logan
being... involved.
I've got to go.
Just get out of there, now.
Chloe, we have to go.
I can't leave yet.
Jack needs the passenger list.
Chloe, if they find you here,
you'll be arrested.
- You have to go now!
- Not yet.
It's the last one! Let's get this
thing out of here. Let's go!
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: team FRM
www.forom.com