AUDREY:
I'm on the phone with a man
who claims to James Nathanson.
He was Walt Cummings' contact.
He says he has information
about the terrorists,
but he will only talk to you.
JACK:
What do you want with me?
CUMMINGS:
Protection.
The terrorists you're after
are trying to kill me.
What makes you think
I'm not gonna kill you myself?
Because you want to stop
the Sentox gas from being
released on American soil.
So do I.
Nathanson, stay down!
Stay down!
What's on the chip?
Please, what's on the chip!
O'Brian.
I have a thumb drive that's
gonna help us find the Sentox.
CHLOE:
The decryption element
kicked out a company
called Omicron International.
Pull up their
senior executive roster,
See if a man named Christopher
Henderson's on the list.
Okay, here it is.
Senior Vice President
of Research and Development.
Send me the decrypted files
over to my PDA.
That's gonna be a little bit
hard to do right now, Jack.
The two of you are up
to something, and I'm
not gonna stand for it.
This is a deliberate attempt
to circumvent my authority.
Lynn, we're all
on the same side.
If you're father wasn't
the Secretary of
Defense, I'd have you
thrown out of here.
I don't have that problem
with you.
I spent a year securing a weapon
that would bring Moscow
to its knees.
And you waste it.
We were betrayed, Bierko.
Someone must pay.
I agree.
( grunts )
This is President Logan.
What is it you want?
I want the route
of Suvarov's motorcade.
If you refuse to cooperate,
I will have no choice
but to release
all the Sentox nerve gas.
He wants to assassinate Suvarov.
Don't negotiate with them!
Isn't that the point of the
treaty you just signed?
Mr. President, I'm glad
that we have this opportunity
to thank you
and Mrs. Logan
for your hospitality.
The motorcade will take
service roads to the 118...
Mrs. Logan...
Aaron,
I've decided to drive to
the airport with the Suvarovs.
I'll ride up front.
No, that's not necessary.
Yes, it is.
( phone rings )
Yes?
Where is the motorcade now?
Just getting on the 118.
How long before they reach
the ambush point?
About 40 minutes.
Good. We'll be waiting.
Get everything ready.
Mr. President,
I asked Secret Service
to sent a threat assessment
for President
Suvarov's route.
The most vulnerable point
is here,
the downtown corridor.
This is the most likely
point of attack.
If an ambush were to occur.
It's going to happen, Mike.
We gave the terrorists
Suvarov's route.
I need to come up
with a public response.
I need to convince
the world that
Suvarov's death
only underscores the importance
of this antiterrorism treaty
that we just signed.
I'll, uh, begin working
on a statement, sir.
Yes?
Thank you. I'll...
let the president know.
What? What is it, Mike?
What's going on?
Who was that?
( exhales )
Agent Pierce. Um,
I don't know how
to tell you this.
Just tell me.
Mrs. Logan is riding
with the Suvarovs.
What are you talking about?
Sir, she got into
that limousine.
Oh, my God.
Didn't-didn't the
Secret Service
try to stop her?!
There was no reason to stop her.
The motorcade is under
Secret Service escort.
As far as they're concerned,
she's not in any danger.
She wants me to call back
the motorcade-- she's trying
to save the Suvarovs.
Should I alert them?
Yes!
No, stop, wait.
( exhales )
If we warn them, the terrorists
are going to set off the gas.
Where are they now?
They're still on the 118.
Get my wife on the phone.
( exhales )
MRS. SUVAROV:
My aunt visited Los Angeles
in the 1950s.
She told me this area
was filled with orange groves,
but I haven't seen any.
I suppose it's all been
built over, no?
Martha?
Yes. I-I...
I was just trying to remember.
Um, I think your aunt's memory
is better than mine.
I visited here when
I was a child,
but I don't recall
the orange groves.
( phone rings )
Yeah, this is Pierce.
Mrs. Logan,
it's the president
for you on line one.
Thank you, Aaron.
Hello, Charles.
Listen to me carefully.
I want you...
Yes, I think they had
a wonderful visit.
And they would very much like
for us to come to Moscow.
Wouldn't that be lovely?
I want you to tell the Suvarovs
that I need you back here.
I'm gonna have one of the
follow cars bring you back.
I don't think so, Charles.
Tell them now, while
I'm on the phone.
Martha,
I know that you want me to call
the motorcade back, but...
the terrorists were
very specific:
if-if I don't allow them
to attack the motorcade,
they're gonna release
canisters of nerve gas
in multiple locations.
Well, I... guess we'll just have
to figure something out
before that happens.
We're trying! We're trying,
but we haven't found them yet.
You need to get out of the car.
Okay, I should go now,
but you'll call me
Martha...
if there's any change of plans?
Damn it, Martha!
Okay, bye-bye.
I'll-I'll talk to you soon.
She won't get out
of the limousine.
My God.
We got to do something, Mike; we
got to get her out of the car.
I could have, uh, one
of the trail cars
stop them and force her out,
say that I need her back here.
You could, but... if Martha
is desperate to save
the Suvarovs,
she might feel that
the only remaining option
is to tell them the truth.
And Suvarov will know that
I gave him up for assassination.
Sir,
do you want me to recall
the motorcade or not?
Edgar, meet me
in the server room
in a few minutes.
Am I in trouble?
No, but there's
something
very important
that we need to discuss.
Okay.
And, Edgar,
don't tell anyone
where you're going.
This needs to stay
between us.
Sure.
What did Audrey Raines want?
She was just going over
some DOD protocols.
I thought you were supposed
to be monitoring chatter.
We are.
Why isn't it on
my screen, Carrie?
I didn't think
you wanted us to mirror
everything
to your system.
I thought you wanted
to save time.
I do want to save time.
It saves me time by not having
to clean up more mistakes.
Mirror everything until
we've secured this nerve gas.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
The thumb drive data
Jack sent us checks
out as authentic.
It's time-stamped
by DOD and CIA.
So Omicron International
did make Sentox gas
for the military.
Yeah, and some terrorists
found out about it.
Or worse-- they were in contact
with Omicron.
Who is this Henderson?
CHLOE:
Christopher Henderson,
Senior Vice President, R&D.
Jack said he knew him,
but he wouldn't talk about it.
Is he connected with the Sentox?
Doesn't say;
it just said he was a senior VP.
All right.
( phone rings )
Yeah?
Jack, we've authenticated
the thumb drive data.
Omicron definitely made the
Sentox for the military.
Okay, I'm almost there--
look, I need you
to work something up
that gets me through
the front door
without them knowing I'm CTU.
Do you think it's necessary
to go in covertly?
Yeah. There's someone
I need to talk to.
I don't want him
to see me coming.
Christopher Henderson?
Yeah.
Who is he?
Someone I used to work for.
Where?
CTU. He was the man
who recruited me.
You've never mentioned him.
I know.
Things ended badly between us.
What happened?
I was part of an investigation
that uncovered evidence
that implicated him in the sale
of classified intelligence
to defense contractors.
We never had enough evidence
to indict him,
but he lost his job,
his command.
Even as he was walking
out the door,
he maintained his innocence.
He never forgave me for being
part of the investigation.
Are you convinced he did it?
I was at the time.
Jack, Chloe can't find
a direct connection
between the Sentox
and Henderson.
Trust me,
if Omicron was making Sentox,
legally or illegally,
Henderson knew about it.
Get back to me as soon
as you got my cover.
All right,
I'm on it.
What are you doing
here, Chloe?
Same thing you're doing here.
Edgar, thank you for coming.
Look, whatever this
is about, I don't
have a lot of time.
We don't have a single active
lead on this nerve gas.
That's not exactly true.
Jack is following a lead
out in the field.
How do you know?
I just spoke with him.
Everyone's looking for him.
Lynn issued an arrest warrant.
That's why we wanted
to talk to you, Edgar.
Lynn is losing it--
first he went after Jack,
and then he took Bill Buchanan
out of play.
Lynn is incapable of leading us
through this crisis.
So you're both working
behind his back?
We're afraid that if
we bring him into this,
he might derail the only
good lead that we have.
We have to help Jack
locate the nerve gas
before it's too late.
What do you want from me?
Cover for Chloe until
Jack reports back.
Please.
Okay.
Thank you.
Okay, fine. Yeah.
That was Secret Service.
As you can see,
the motorcade continues
to make its way to the airport
without incident.
There won't be
any warning, Mike.
When these people
attack,
they will be fast
and they will be merciless.
You can count on that.
I have to talk to this man.
M-Maybe I can convince him
to hold off.
Hold off?
Just until Martha
gets out of the car.
She wasn't supposed to be a part
of this in the first place.
Sir, I don't think that would
change his plan.
He has to know that my wife's
in the car!
I can't lose her, Mike.
The only way
to keep Martha safe
is for me to call Secret Service
and tell them to turn
the motorcade around.
What about...
what about CTU?
Do they have any active leads
on the nerve gas?
As of five minutes ago,
they don't...
nothing that would help
our situation.
What am I missing, Mike?!
There's got to be some way out,
something
that I'm not seeing.
You're not missing anything.
Any action we take
to save Martha
would also save
the Suvarovs,
and if that happens,
the terrorists
will release the gas.
Unfortunately,
it's that simple.
Then there's nothing more
we can do, Mike.
Unless I warn them.
Martha's going to die
with the Suvarovs.
Aaron...
have there been any changes?
Excuse me?
Changes to what,
Mrs. Logan?
I-I was just wondering
if there had been any changes
to our route.
We haven't gotten
any revised
instructions, ma'am.
Thank you.
You sure you're all right,
Martha?
Yes, yes.
I just wanted to make sure
we don't run into
any heavy traffic.
Understood.
Those protocols should be
coming over shortly.
Who were you
on the phone with?
Homeland Security.
I gave you specific orders
to have everyone's systems
mirrored to mine.
I've been doing that.
But you're not finished,
yet somehow you have time
to chat with Homeland Security.
They needed us to give them
updated code sets.
It'll just take
another minute.
No, it won't.
Stiles, finish her task.
Carrie, you're done.
What do you... mean, done?
Fired. You don't
work here anymore.
STILES:
Mr. McGill,
it's not her fault.
She just...
Edgar, one more word out of you,
you walk out with her.
What's it gonna be?
( scoffs quietly )
Where's Agent O'Brian?
She had to step away
for a minute.
Where?
I don't know.
Jack, I'm still trying
to get your credentials
into Omicron's system.
You can't get into
the building without them.
What's the problem?
Omicron's systems
don't refresh
often enough.
We need to push
this page in manually.
Okay, I'm in.
You're going in under the name
of John Barrie.
B-A-R-R-I-E.
You're with a company called
Eclipse LLC.
John Barrie, Eclipse LLC.
I got it.
Hold on a second;
she hasn't
planted it yet.
Chloe. What are you
doing in here?
I asked her to help me.
She doesn't work for you,
Ms. Raines; she works for me.
But I don't,
and DOD has assignment
priority
over CTU.
We're in the middle of a
real-time investigation,
and we're understaffed.
Chloe's a department head--
you can't just take her
away from me.
AUDREY:
I'm not taking her from you.
We needed a system patch
on a server,
and Chloe's the only one
who could fix it.
Well, then you come to me
and you ask me.
Everything in this office
runs through me!
Lynn, we are all trying
to do the same thing.
Can we please
just get past this?
Yeah, I'm past it.
I want Chloe back.
Okay, I'm finished here.
Sorry, Mr. McGill,
it won't happen again.
Good afternoon.
John Barrie
with Eclipse.
I've got a 4:30
with R&D.
( typing )
Thumb print, please.
Go on in.
Thank you.
MAN ( over intercom ):
Well, I'll tell you what you do.
You kick the McAvoy meeting
to next week on Thursday,
but you keep everything else.
What about your trip
to Washington?
That's right. Okay.
Well, I got to talk to Kagan
tomorrow morning.
I'll get back to you then.
Can I help you, sir?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm a little lost. I was looking
for the men's room.
Over there, second door.
Thank you.
( line ringing )
Audrey Raines.
It's Jack. I need you
to lose the secretary.
Her name is Joanna Tandy.
All right, I'll take care of it.
Thanks.
( phone rings )
Christopher Henderson's office.
Ms. Tandy?
Yes?
Jane Espenson
from accounting.
We need you
to come down now
and double-check some
of these invoices.
What invoices?
It's a little difficult
to explain over the phone.
Would you mind popping down
just for a minute?
Fine.
Thank you.
Mr. Henderson, there's a problem
down in accounting.
I'll be right back.
( electronic buzzing )
Jack? Jack?
( gasps )
( Jack groans )
( panting )
Just for the record,
I never believed you were dead.
What are you doing here?
Earlier this morning,
terrorists gained control
of a large quantity
of Sentox VX
nerve gas.
Omicron
manufactured it.
When I pulled up
the executive list,
your name was on it.
Sure my name's on it--
I work here.
Omicron had
the contract.
We manufacture
this stuff.
But every single gram of it
went to the Department
of Defense.
It's all been accounted for.
Well, that can't be true,
now, can it?
We have confirmation
that terrorists
are in control
of 19 canisters of Sentox!
What are you accusing me
now of, Jack?
Being in bed with terrorists?
I'm following
the leads!
Well, the leads are wrong.
DOD destroyed
the entire stockpile.
Sentox was responsible
for the death of the people
in the Sunrise Hills Mall
less than two hours ago.
The news said it
was chlorine gas.
That was a cover story
to stop
a widespread panic!
Come on, Christopher,
you know how this works!
The terrorists have threatened
to release the rest of the gas.
( quietly ):
Good God.
Well, whoever's implicating me
in this
knows my history with CTU.
I mean, I'm
an easy target.
This is not
a coincidence.
Look, Jack, I know
there's dirt between us,
but I swear to you,
I got nothing
to do with this.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry.
I can't afford to take
your word
on this.
Well, you're gonna have
to take my word.
11 people died in that mall!
Hundreds of thousands of others
will if they release
the rest
of the Sentox.
You're not hearing me, Jack!
I had nothing to do with this!
Then prove it to me.
I need complete access
to Omicron's Sentox program.
I'm doing it now.
The entire operation
was run from a bunker
across the campus.
Let me see the bunker.
NSA chatter analysis
just came in.
I decoded some
words and phrases.
What were they saying?
It's too scrambled to make
any complete sentences,
but number strings
keep coming up.
5, 110, 10.
Freeways?
Those are the routes
President Suvarov's
taking to the airport.
The only other phrase
I could decode
refers to the downtown corridor.
How long ago did
this chatter start?
About 30 minutes ago.
Come on.
Can we expand the search area?
I've got CTU air surveillance
on everything east of Glendale.
What about the north?
Edwards Air Force Base
is giving us
support there.
We're still at a dead end
on finding new leads
with the nerve gas.
Excuse me, Mr. McGill, we think
there might be an attack
on President Suvarov's
motorcade.
What?
Edgar just monitored
some chatter from
NSA and ran a threat assessment.
What are you doing
analyzing chatter
that isn't related to finding
the nerve gas?
It came through
on one of my filters.
The point is, sir,
we found something.
Don't you want to alert
Secret Service
considering that Suvarov
is on his way to the airport?
Based on
an unsubstantiated theory
from a couple of analysts?
I think I've been embarrassed
enough for one day.
Can we at least devote
some limited resources
to try to confirm this threat?
I'm sorry.
Maybe I wasn't clear. No.
Now go downstairs
and focus on what
you're supposed
to be doing.
I don't think it would be
a bad idea
to pass along
the intel.
Well, I do.
I don't want to hear
another word about it.
Yes?
Our men are in place.
How far out are they?
The motorcade will be there
in less than 20 minutes.
Are you sure no one is going
to interfere with us?
I don't think so.
Logan knows the consequences
if that happens.
But be alert.
Make sure they haven't
placed any of their
people near you.
If police show up,
we'll deal with them.
Good.
I'll call you when it's over.
Let's go, let's go.
Keep them out.
If things don't go as planned,
I'll use them here.
I'm busy, Ms. Raines.
Lynn, I just looked
at this chatter report
and I definitely think
that we need
to let Secret Service know
of the threat.
I'm not going to repeat
my orders
to every person
in this office individually.
My people are not going
to chase that white elephant.
They're busy trying
to locate 19 canisters
of Sentox nerve gas.
Has it occurred to you
that if this threat is real,
then it's likely
that the terrorists who have
the Sentox nerve gas
are the same ones
that are planning this attack?
This is an unverified threat!
If you want to hand
it off to NSA, be my guest.
NSA can't recall the motorcade
without going through
a time-consuming
approval process.
Good.
That process helps eliminate
false threats.
Look, we don't have that time.
According...
Ms. Raines, Ms. Raines,
this office has
made enough mistakes
for one day, and I intend
to stop the bleeding.
Now let my people
focus on their work
or I will have you
escorted out of here.
Thank you.
( beep )
I need to call this in
to Secret Service,
but they won't act on it
unless Lynn verifies it.
He's never going
to back you up on that.
Yes, he is.
I need you to hack
into Lynn's account for me.
I'll forge a message
to Secret Service
and make it look like
it came from him.
That's illegal.
Fine.
Edgar, I need you to put
a blanket on my sub-net
to make it look like
I'm doing something else.
We could all
end up in jail.
Think about it
for a second.
The Russian president,
his wife,
about 35 Secret Service,
all dead in a few minutes.
All right, but for the record,
this is not a good idea.
All right, I'll
compose a message.
As soon as you have the forged
verification file, call me.
Curtis.
Excuse me.
We need to talk.
What is it?
We've got a problem
with Lynn.
Yeah, I know.
He's not listening
to anybody.
Well, it's going to start
costing lives.
Just give him some time.
He'll come around.
Curtis, we don't have time.
We've got to get Bill
back out here.
That's not going
to happen, Audrey.
We need to make it happen.
What are you suggesting?
Section 112.
On what grounds?
Lynn is mentally incapable
of running CTU.
I may not agree
with all his choices,
but going from there
to mentally unfit?
That's a stretch.
No, it's not and you know it.
You've seen him.
With Bill in custody,
you are the ranking agent.
You are the only one
that can invoke it.
I don't know, Audrey...
Yes, you do.
Curtis, CTU is barely
functional.
You are the one
that can turn it around.
Even if I agreed, Section 112
requires documentation,
testimony, a lot
of groundwork.
The record of what is going on
right now
is documentation enough.
Curtis...
please.
Think about it.
I will.
Good. Thank you.
( knocking )
Mr. President.
Come in, Mike.
The motorcade
is only 15 minutes
away from the airport.
Yeah.
My father always told me that
life was about problem solving.
That every problem
had a solution.
You tell me where
the solution is
on this one.
I don't have an answer,
Mr. President.
But if you want
the Suvarov motorcade
to turn back,
I need to do it now.
We know the terrorists are
willing to kill civilians.
And the low... the low end
of the casualty range
on this one is...
100,000 lives.
Yes, sir.
I decided before that I couldn't
risk all those lives
to save one man--
the Russian president.
I can't risk those lives now...
( voice breaking ):
even to save my own wife.
Damn you, Martha,
for putting me in this position.
You brought it on yourself.
Mike...
Pray with me, Mike.
Uh, Mr. President,
with all due respect,
this is a personal matter.
I don't...
Please, Mike.
How much longer
until we can send this out?
A couple of minutes.
I've almost hacked in.
We don't have
a couple of minutes.
EDGAR:
I'm almost there.
Oh, no.
Lynn cut us off.
What do I do?
I think it's too late
to do anything.
Mr. Stiles,
did you really think
I wouldn't notice
that you were trying
to access my com?
Lynn, listen, we need to talk...
Shut up!
These people are working
against CTU protocols.
That means they're
working against me.
Lynn, what is this?
We were trying to warn
Secret Service
on an attack
on Suvarov's
motorcade.
Curtis, take Mr. Stiles
and Ms. O'Brian--
put them in holding.
And then escort Audrey Raines
out of CTU.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can, Curtis.
It's a direct order.
Now do it.
You forced them
to work covertly.
They had no choice.
You're not behaving
rationally, Lynn.
LYNN:
You and you,
take them all into custody
including Mr. Manning.
CURTIS:
If you try to carry out
that command,
I will draw my weapon.
If he draws his weapon,
shoot him.
CURTIS:
This situation is already
getting out of control.
Don't make it worse.
McGILL:
Why are you hesitating?!
I gave you an order.
Now do it!
What would you like me to do,
Mr. Manning?
What?!
Lynn McGill, I'm relieving you
of your command
under the incapacity clause
of Section 112.
You'll do no such thing.
Take him away.
You can't do that.
He can't do this.
Don't touch me.
This is an unjustified
usurpation of my authority.
Do you hear me?
We're in the middle
of a crisis.
There are going to be
repercussions.
Everyone involved in this
is going to face prosecution.
This is Curtis Manning.
Release Bill Buchanan
from holding
and inform Division that
he's been reinstated
as director of CTU
under Section 112 provisions.
Everyone, get back
to your stations.
Fill me in.
Chloe and Edgar
detected chatter
indicating a possible attack on
President Suvarov's motorcade
en route to the airport.
How'd they get
Suvarov's route?
We don't know, but
the most likely
point of intercept
is the downtown corridor.
Has Secret Service
been notified?
Lynn refused to do so.
Notify Secret Service now.
I need your
level one access
code to override the
firewall Lynn put up.
Here.
I need Carrie back.
He fired her for no reason.
Have security reinstate her.
Edgar, pull up satellite and all
possible intercept points,
and call the president.
Yes, sir.
Where are we on
the location of the
nerve gas canisters?
No substantial progress.
What about the lead
Jack was following?
He traced the Sentox
back to Omicron International
where it was manufactured.
Is that where Jack is now?
Yes.
EDGAR:
Mr. Buchanan,
president's on the line.
Mr. President,
we have intelligence
that indicates
President Suvarov's motorcade
may be attacked
in the next few minutes.
Is that so?
Yes, sir.
We are in the process
of notifying Secret Service.
What we can tell you is that
if the attack happens
it will occur
in or around the downtown area.
The motorcade is approaching
that area now, sir.
Mr. President?
Bill. Mike Novick.
The president is at a loss
for words.
His wife is
in the Suvarov's limousine.
( clears throat softly )
Thank you.
You've done a good job.
What do we do?
There's nothing we can do, sir.
CTU is informing
the Secret Service.
They'll no doubt take
defensive measures,
which makes the attack
substantially less likely
to succeed.
AARON:
Yes, sir.
Protocol red.
Hold on tight.
We're turning around--
we just received intelligence
about a threat
to the motorcade.
They're turning around!
( gunfire )
We're under attack!
We need backup now!
( gasping )
( yells )
It's a missile fire.
The motorcade's been hit.
A-Aaron?
Aaron?
Oh, my God...
( gasping )
( two gunshots )
( sirens wail in distance )
( gunshot )
( garbled radio transmission )
( softly ):
Aaron... Aaron...
It's okay.
Are you okay?
( phone rings )
( ringing continues )
Novick.
Yeah, Frank.
How badly?
And what about
Mrs. Logan?
I will. Thank you.
Your wife survived
the attack.
CTU intervened in time.
Thank God.
What about the Suvarovs?
They were shaken up,
but, uh, they'll be okay.
He's going to think
I tipped off CTU.
It won't matter to him
that I tried to keep
my end of the bargain.
I agree.
All the work
on the Sentox project
was run out of here.
How restricted
was the access?
Extremely. For security reasons,
each defense contract
was run out of its own
separate dedicated bunker,
each bunker's a completely
sealed environment.
Nothing gets in
and nothing gets out.
This is gonna
take some time.
I've got to merge some files,
find out who's working
on this project.
You're Senior Vice President
and you don't know?
Give me a break, Jack--
there's 8,000 people
that work for this company.
I got to run a sort--
it's gonna take me a minute.
So who's the honcho
over at CTU now?
Bill Buchanan.
( chuckles ):
Buchanan. What a stiff.
No wonder everything's
going to hell over there.
You guys keep getting rid
of everybody
who can do their job.
You made your own bed.
You accused
the wrong man, Jack.
I wasn't the lead investigator;
I showed them what I found.
I was framed.
By who?
Nina Myers, George Mason...
Who knows?
But I'll tell you, the one thing
that just hangs on me,
I'll tell you,
the one thing that just...
hurts me is that
you didn't believe me.
You made it impossible
to believe you.
How could I possibly defend you?
You wouldn't even
defend yourself.
No one gave me the chance.
Okay, we got
something here.
Lead scientist,
head of Project Sentox--
Alan Burkett, PhD.
I'm gonna need
to speak to him.
Well, you're gonna
have a problem.
Died in a helicopter crash
in Geneva two years ago.
Let's see what else we got.
This is bizarre.
Two other senior
scientists
on the Sentox project--
one drowned on a diving trip
in the Bahamas,
the other burned to death
in a car accident
two weeks later.
What the hell is going on?
CTU's gonna have
to break it down.
How do I upload the files
and get them ready to transfer?
We need I.T.
They're next-door.
I'll get somebody to help us.
I'll CTU know that
we're sending the files over.
Hello?
Damn it.
( mechanical clicking )
( grunts )
Oh, my God.
How could I be so stupid?
WOMAN ( over phone ):
Yes?
Yeah, it's me.
I listened to everything
Bauer had to say
about the thumb drive--
CTU does not have
enough information to hurt us.
What about Bauer?
Well, in about one minute,
he'll be dead.
( panting )
( loud grunt )
Tell the media we don't know how
the terrorists found out
about the Suvarovs' route.
We're looking
into it now.
( hangs up phone )
Mike, I've been thinking that...
diplomatically, we should
play up the fact that Martha
was in the vehicle.
Why is that, sir?
It will get rid of any suspicion
that we might have been...
( phone rings )
shortchanging
Suvarov's security.
There he is.
( ringing continues )
Hello.
I thought we had
an understanding.
I had nothing
to do with this.
You have to believe me.
It was your job
to make sure no
one interfered
with the attack
on the Suvarovs.
It happened outside
of my authority.
I told no one.
If Russia isn't going to pay
with the life of its president,
then its new ally,
the United States,
will pay with the lives
of its citizens.
Mr. President,
this is our final conversation.
Good-bye.
No. Wait!