-=THE LAST FANTASY=-
Proudly Presents
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
EngSub by snowmoon
Sync by not-young-anymore
Have you got it yet?
Told you I'd call you
as soon as I have everything.
I'm paying you a lot of money,
Collette.
And if you could've gotten
the detailed specs of a facility
this secure
from someone else, you would've.
CTU is no longer
an obstacle.
MAN:
This facility
has been contaminated
with Sentox VX1 nerve gas.
Repeat: this facility
has been contaminated.
Everybody, leave
the situation room.
Move! Now!
Seal it.
Lynn, it's Jack.
We found a computer interrupt
in the AC control unit.
Now if we can
shut that down in the next few
minutes, we can stop the gas
from permeating the safe zones.
The problem is
you're the only person
close enough to get to it.
Lynn, the truth is
if I could get there,
I would do this myself,
but I'm not close enough.
And I'm going to have
to ask you to do it
without any protection.
He did it.
Oh, my God.
( groans )
CTU is protecting
this city.
Are you saying
they're no longer
capable of doing that?
I'm saying they've been
seriously compromised here.
We've got terrorists with nerve
gas canisters out there.
Who is going to stop them?
Mr. President, I suggest
an emergency restructuring.
CTU is no longer
an operational entity.
It's a building with workers
who will report to us.
I can see
no other option right now
but to impose marshal law
on the city of Los Angeles.
What I will not do
is stand by and watch
Hal Gardner use you
to promote his own agenda.
You killed my wife
Michelle Dessler this morning.
She was my life.
And you took her.
My God, he's got a gun.
You can't do this.
We have to get him talking.
He's our only lead to Bierko
and the Sentox gas canisters.
You've had your chance.
He's mine now.
Tony!
Oh, my God!
Jack, I am so sorry.
Security find Henderson yet?
No, he got
out of the building
before the lockdown.
An external cam got a shot
of him as he was leaving.
And the car that he was using
was found a block away.
But I think that we might've
got what we needed from him.
What are you talking about?
Chloe was able to decrypt
a file from his computer.
She got a name of someone
connected to Bierko.
Who's Collette Stenger?
She's an international
intelligence broker.
State secrets,
intellectual property.
What's her connection
to Bierko?
Interpol claims
that she and Bierko
met at least twice over
the last eight months.
And we think she helped
broker the deal.
Is she still in Los Angeles?
She gave a name of
a hotel to customs.
But nothing's to say
that she's actually there.
Curtis is prepping
a tactical team
to try to bring her in.
Okay.
Good work.
( cell phone rings )
Manning.
Curtis, it's Jack.
When is the tac team
leaving?
Right now.
I'm going with you.
All right.
I have no intention...
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen,
member of the press corps...
Just so you're aware,
there will be no Q&A
following
the president's statement.
But you can submit questions
to my office...
You're having
second thoughts?
Putting soldiers
on the streets of L.A.,
this will not be
a popular announcement.
Maybe not.
But it's the right move.
Hal, would you
excuse us, please?
Mrs. Logan, the president's
about to go on the air.
I'll be brief.
I would like a moment
alone with my husband.
BROWN:
Now, before we begin,
I want to take a second to
address an issue of security.
I understand that many of you
have been here since early...
I've made up
my mind, Martha.
I'm not debating
this anymore.
Just listen, listen please.
Mike Novick spoke
to someone at CTU.
They think they have
a lead on this man,
this man Bierko.
They think they may
find him before he launches
another attack.
CTU was just hit.
40% of their people
are either dead
or unable to work.
To think that they
would be able
to stop this attack, that's
just wishful thinking.
Maybe not.
( sighs )
Bringing the military in
is the best way
to maintain order.
The Vice President's
right about that.
Of course he is.
What's that mean?
Hasn't it ever occurred to you
that he proposed this whole
thing to set you up for a fall?
So he gets the nomination
next year.
That's insane.
Hal's only motivation
is what's best for the country.
There's going to be fallout.
Hal knows it.
And you know it.
I have to go.
Charles...
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of
the United States.
As you all know,
America has been hit today
by a series
of terrorist strikes,
beginning with the assassination
of former President David Palmer
and the murder of innocent
Americans at Ontario Airport,
followed by
the attempted assassination
of Russian President
Yuri Suvarov.
These events
are being orchestrated
by terrorists
operating within our borders.
Our most recent intelligence
suggests
that they will strike again
and soon.
I can and will
do my sworn duty
to ensure the safety
of the American people.
Therefore I am issuing
an executive order
imposing a curfew
on all civilians
in the Los Angeles
metropolitan area.
This curfew will be effective
immediately and will be
enforced by the military.
As disruptive and distasteful as
I know this is for many of you,
I would ask that you remember
that we are at war.
Bracing ourselves
against future attacks...
D.O.D. is asking for a list
of our casualties.
I don't want any
names released
until the next of kin
have been notified.
Let me know when that happens.
This place is
a sinking ship.
We should be
taking over now,
not going through the
charade of an assessment.
Until we're ready to transition,
we need everyone here
functioning.
Once the remaining canisters
of nerve gas have been found
and the terrorists captured,
then we'll assume full control.
Karen.
Hello, Bill.
Bill Buchanan,
Miles Papazian from my office.
I appreciate your coming,
but that wasn't necessary.
We just need to replace
some key personnel.
We're all sorry
about the loss of lives here,
but the White House feels
you may need more than that.
They want an assessment
of how Homeland
may best assist CTU.
I'll brief you in my office.
Fine.
Miles, familiarize yourself
with the networks,
and then start the survey.
Let's go.
Upstairs.
Chloe O'Brian?
Who are you?
Homeland Security.
I asked your name,
not who you work for.
I need a vacant station set up.
I'm kind of busy right now.
I'm seeing Edgar Stiles
listed on my report
as a casualty.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Then his station
should be available.
I'll set up over there.
I'll be reinstalling
operating protocols
for everyone in your group,
so I'll need your keycard.
No.
I'm sorry?
You can't have my keycard.
We're here with a priority
admin directive.
You can confirm that with your
supervisor on your own time.
REPORTER:
We're live in Los Angeles,
where just a few minutes ago,
Army units
stationed in L.A. County
began moving in force
across city limits.
This is the first time a
military presence of this scale
has been activated
in a major metropolitan area.
While White House officials
have stopped short
of officially declaring
full-scale martial law...
Where are you going?
I just need some fresh air.
These mobile Army divisions
were activated
shortly after
the President's press conference
in which he declared
an enforced curfew.
Officials are hoping
the curfew will prevent
further acts of terror.
I do not trust him.
Ma'am?
The Vice President.
( cell phone ringing )
This is Aaron Pierce.
Aaron, it's Wayne Palmer.
Sir, I am so sorry
about President Palmer,
more sorry than I can describe.
Aaron, I know how close
you were to my brother.
You must have known
he felt the same way about you.
Thank you for saying that.
Actually, Aaron,
he's the reason I'm calling.
There's something
from my brother
I need to give you
personally.
I should be there
within the hour.
You're coming here?
Yeah, I know
it sounds impulsive, Aaron.
But I'd rather see you
sooner than later.
There's a curfew in effect, sir.
I know, I know.
I left before it was declared.
If I may say so, this
is an odd request.
Aaron, my brother
trusted you with his life.
I am asking you to trust me.
All right.
I'd also appreciate it if
you would keep this between us.
I'm hoping there's somewhere
we can meet discreetly.
I'll find a place.
Thank you, Aaron.
I'll call you when I'm close.
REPORTER:
The effects of this action
will no doubt
ripple across the country, as
other cities begin to take note.
So while legislators debate
the legality
of President Logan's action,
martial law is already a fact...
Mike, turn it off.
...on the ground,
here in Los Angeles.
( TV turns off )
"Debate the legality
of President Logan's action."
Did you hear that?
They're talking about this
like it's
an illegal action.
Don't worry, Mr. President.
I'm in control of the situation.
Our legal people are
working on it right now.
Do we have
anything more from CTU?
They're still following
up on this Bierko lead.
As soon as they have
something to report,
we'll be the first to hear.
Give me details of the current
threat assessment.
There's a high probability
that Bierko is
planning an attack
on a much larger scale
than anything we've seen today.
That's why he
targeted CTU--
to cripple our ability
to stop him.
And the question is:
Was he successful?
When you look
at the numbers,
you were harder hit
than you thought, Bill.
We're still functioning.
Maybe not at a 100%,
but when you install
the people I've asked for...
we'll be back
to fighting strength.
Have you made any progress
finding Bierko?
We've identified a woman
we believe might lead us to him.
Collette Stenger.
We've just sent a tac team
to bring her in.
Good.
I enjoy watching
you get dressed
almost as much as I enjoy
watching you get undressed.
You should get dressed yourself
and send
the bags down.
This deal you're working on,
I hope you're getting
a lot of money for it.
I never talk about my business,
you know that.
I know...
but Maria called about
this villa in Positano.
She said when you see it,
you'll love it.
We'll call her later.
I'll see you at
the airport, okay?
In 45 minutes.
I'll be there.
( cell phone ringing )
Yes.
I'm on my way.
And you have
everything I asked for?
Of course.
Good.
Do you have
the money?
As soon as I verify
the merchandise,
I'll have it transferred
to your account.
I'll be there soon.
Does she have the schematics
and the access codes?
Yes.
Everything we need.
The Distribution Center is
a difficult target.
It would be much easier
to hit a less secure location.
No, Mikhail, this is the place.
Release
the Sentox here...
and 200,000 people die.
And we need a second satellite
repositioned as
soon as possible.
Good. Thank you.
I saw a request
for proficiency evaluations
for all CTU personnel
on my secondary
screen.
That's a formality.
The fact is, we don't have time
for evaluations
right now.
Then why was it put
in the pipeline?
Like I said, it's a formality.
You're here to shut
this place down, aren't you?
And the evaluations
will be filled in later
as a matter of protocol.
I told you before,
the White House...
I know what you told me before.
Now tell me the truth.
The truth is, CTU is being
absorbed by Homeland.
Which means,
from now on,
every operational decision
needs to go through me.
Bill, what
did you expect?
You've been infiltrated.
56 of your people
have been killed.
The others are
demoralized...
They're not demoralized,
they're angry!
They want to fight back.
They're willing
to lay down their lives.
Some already
have...
It's done, Bill.
The decision's been made.
And I know
neither one of us
wants this transition
to interfere
with ongoing protocol,
so let's just
keep it between us.
At least until
this crisis plays out.
There.
Bill?
Homeland is being overly
aggressive with their survey.
What is going on?
Nothing.
It's just a formality.
They'll be gone as soon as
they finish their evaluation.
Where are we on
the military mobilization?
Martial law is in effect
in nine of the
15 L.A. districts.
I'm setting up checkpoints for
the rest of the county now.
I hope the president's
doing the right thing.
CURTIS:
Alpha Team,
we're approaching
Collette Stenger's
apartment
and we're ready to move.
Are you in position?
AGENT ( over radio ):
Affirmative.
We've got the lobby covered.
CURTIS:
Copy.
I think she went for the roof.
Cover the stairs.
Let's go.
We're going up top.
JACK:
Drop the gun!
Stand down or he dies!
I said stand down!
Our people are all around you.
They will drop you before
you could pull that trigger.
Put the gun down!
What do you mean
your "people?"
Who are you?
Counter Terrorist Unit,
Los Angeles.
Show me identification.
I'm with the German Federal
Intelligence Service.
My name's Theo Stoller.
What are you doing
in this country?
I'm here on
special assignment...
by agreement between
our governments.
Now you can get
the hell out of here
before you
destroy my cover.
That's not going to happen.
CHLOE ( over phone ):
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
I want you to check
on a foreign agent
on the SA list.
"Theo Stoller."
Okay.
Got it:
"Theo Stoller,
height, 5'll",
brown hair, brown eyes."
He's a German operative,
but trained in England
at MI-6.
There's even contact
information: cell phone...
That's all right,
Chloe.
That's enough,
thanks.
I told you,
you have to get
out of here now.
We can't do that.
You were with
Collette Stenger.
We need her to help us
find Vladimir Bierko.
I don't know him.
Bierko's responsible
for the terrorist attacks
that took place
in the city earlier today.
He's preparing to mount
another one as we speak.
Collette Stenger is the only way
we can find him.
Where is she?
I can't help you.
Why not?
Giving you Collette
jeopardizes my operation.
What operation?
I've been undercover
for the last six months
gathering intel
on Collette's clientele.
We've identified cells
in three countries,
but she's connected
to a dozen more.
She's too valuable to give up.
If we don't find Bierko,
hundreds of thousands
of innocent people
will die here today.
That is more important than
your preemptive operation.
It's not a question
of importance,
it's a question
of different agendas.
Your job is to save
American lives.
Mine to save German lives.
You're asking me
to betray
my duty to my country.
Ask yourself what you
would do in my position.
You better start
asking yourself
what you would do
in mine.
Now, let's go.
I'm here by permission
of your government--
you can't touch me.
Right.
We'll see about that.
Well, make sure that
your superior understands
that if this attack happens,
my government will hold
your country accountable.
Jack, it's Buchanan.
Audrey will be joining us
momentarily.
You're also on the line
with Karen Hayes
from Homeland Security.
She's been providing support
to CTU, and she's also
been in contact
with the White House.
Did President Logan get in touch
with the German Chancellor?
He's tried;
the chancellor's
unreachable for
another hour.
We don't have
They're stalling, there's
nothing we can do about that.
Jack, this is Audrey.
I was just speaking
with German Intelligence.
They're refusing
to order their agent
to cooperate with us.
Maybe you can get
a deal with him.
Okay, I'll talk
to Stoller again.
Good. Call me
if you get him
to change his mind.
Yeah.
Curtis?
Let me have a moment
with him alone.
Jack, what are you doing?
It's all right.
All right.
Your intelligence service
denied our request
for cooperation.
So has your government.
I'm not surprised.
Collette Stenger
is a golden goose.
There's no upside
in giving her up.
Maybe I could provide you
with one.
Meaning?
I will give you something
that is more valuable
than Collette Stenger.
It's hard to know
what that might be.
Our roster of all known
terror suspects
working around the world,
our WET list.
As allies, we've requested
this WET list
many times before.
But the NSA has always said,
giving us the
list would
jeopardize their operations.
It will.
I don't work for the NSA,
I don't work for CTU.
This is personal.
And right now, you're not
giving me another choice.
All right.
I'll give you Collette
in exchange for the WET list.
Okay.
Let's see what we can do.
Agent Bauer.
I'm aware of several names
that should be on that list.
Don't try and pass me a fake.
( phone ringing )
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Do we still have a back door
into NSA's
secured mainframe?
I can't really talk
right now, Jack.
Okay, fine. Then, listen.
I need you to log on to their
server, download the WET list,
and send it to my
PDA immediately.
Why?
The WET list is what
we're gonna have to pay
to get Collette Stenger.
Jack, that list is
as top secret as it gets.
Homeland Security
sent a team over here.
You're gonna have
to clear it with them.
We can't afford
to take the chance
of them saying no.
I'm not saying I won't do it
without their approval.
I'm saying I can't.
They took my keycard.
I can't get into the NSA
mainframe without it.
Just do what you have to.
It's our only way
to get Bierko.
Fine. I'll call you back.
Excuse me, Miles.
Oh!
( gasps ):
My God!
What is the
matter with you?
Sorry.
What's wrong with you?
I'll pay for the dry cleaning.
JACK:
Yeah?
Jack, I got on the NSA server.
Did you get the file?
Not yet. They put
an extra layer
of authentication
in place.
Can you get around it?
Hold on.
Okay, I got it.
I hope you know
what you're doing.
I'm uploading it now.
Thanks.
I got it.
Well, that appears legitimate.
It is.
Give me back the memory card.
You can't upload the WET list
to your people
until I have Collette Stenger
in custody.
Well, fair enough.
We have to go now.
I'm supposed to meet her
at the Van Nuys airport
in less than 20 minutes.
What kind of a car
is she driving?
I don't know.
I'm supposed to
park in car Lot C
and wait for her.
She'll probably
recon the area before
she makes contact.
She's, uh, cautious by habit.
Curtis, we're on the move--
Van Nuys Airport.
We'll give you the details
when we're on the way.
When you receive the funds,
transfer them immediately
into the Caymans account.
In Euros.
My bank is ready
to accept the transfer.
The file is encrypted.
What is the decryption key?
Transfer the funds.
It's been sent.
Thank you.
E-mail me confirmation
of the transfer.
The decryption key is
Charlie alpha three nine
alpha.
It worked.
This is what you wanted.
Of course it is.
Until next time, gentlemen.
Are the men ready?
Yes.
Torch this place.
We're moving out.
Governor, I'm not trying
to co-opt your authority,
but we are in the middle
of a crisis here.
Now, you can either transmit
my orders word for word
to the National Guard,
or I can federalize them,
and give them
my orders
directly, your choice.
Excellent.
Thank you, Governor.
I look forward
to your cooperation.
Sir, we have a situation
at one of the roadblocks
that the region three commander
needs your call on.
Tell me.
Wayne Palmer is insisting
he be let through one
of our roadblocks.
He claims he still has
his clearance and that he's on
official business.
And where exactly is that?
He was stopped trying
to get on the access road
coming towards
the retreat.
He's on his way here?
To do what?
He wouldn't give
the officer in charge
of the roadblock
any information.
What should I tell
the roadblock, sir?
Captain, all I'm asking you
to do is call and confirm
I have a grade two clearance,
that's it.
Sir, regardless
of your clearance,
authorization to let you through
must come down through the
appropriate chain of command.
And just who would that be,
huh, Captain?
Who's in charge
of the military's role in this?
( phone ringing )
Riggs.
Understood.
Thank you, sir.
You can go on through
now, sir.
Let him through.
Thank you, Captain.
CURTIS:
All teams are in position, Jack.
No one moves in
until I confirm that it's her.
Copy that.
Collette won't show herself
if she senses anything's wrong.
Make sure he stays hidden.
Don't worry. He will.
What will happen to her?
To Collette.
I don't know yet. Why?
Uh, just curious.
You've been in
my situation?
I've been undercover for long
stretches of time, yeah.
And been involved with a woman
during that time?
There's no question we are doing
what has to be done
for our countries,
but sometimes it's
harder than others.
Chloe, could you join us in
the Situation Room, please?
Sure.
What's going on?
Why don't you tell us,
Ms. O'Brian?
I don't know.
We've got you hacking
into a top secret NSA archive.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
MILES:
I pulled a mirrored archive
of your web traffic.
Whatever you took from NSA
was uploaded to Jack Bauer's
remote node.
Ms. O'Brian, tell us exactly
what document
you passed to Jack Bauer.
BUCHANAN:
Chloe,
this is going to get much worse
if you force me
to have NSA run a back trace.
What is it?
Jack needed the WET List.
What?!
Why on earth
would you give him that?
Theo Stoller wouldn't lead us
to Collette Stenger without it.
Chloe, giving that list
to another intelligence
agency could be disastrous.
Years of work could
be rendered useless,
our own agents could be exposed.
Jack needed it, okay?
No! No, it's not okay.
And you expected us
to give your agents a chance?
Get me Bauer.
( phone ringing )
Put it on speaker phone, or
I'm getting out of this car.
Fine.
This is Bauer.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, it's Bill.
Karen Hayes is here, as well.
If you're with
Theo Stoller,
get some place you
can talk privately.
I can't. We're in the middle
of an operation.
If I move,
I'll jeopardize our position.
Then you'll have to have this
conversation in front of him.
Have you given him
the WET List yet?
Yes.
Has he given it
to German Intelligence?
No.
Then get it back. Now.
I can't.
If I do that,
Stoller won't cooperate.
And then
we'll lose Collette Stenger.
Bill, will you explain this
to her?
It's not his decision.
Retrieve the WET list now,
or I will order Agent Manning
and his team to do it.
Right now, Collette Stenger is
our only connection to Bierko.
If you blow this operation,
you will be responsible
for every life lost
in his next attack.
I don't like to be threatened,
Mr. Bauer.
Ms. Hayes, that's not a threat,
that's a fact.
HAYES:
German Intelligence
will move preemptively
on people
that we have been
watching for years.
Our ability to prevent
terrorist attacks
will be severely threatened.
Then that's a risk
we'll have to take.
Right now, we have to deal
with this situation.
It's not your call.
It's not mine, either.
We need authorization
from the President.
Then get it.
CURTIS:
Jack, one of our forward teams
I.D.'d a woman fitting
Stenger's description
driving a red Lexus making its
second circuit around the lot.
This could be her.
We have a possible suspect
approaching.
Ms. Hayes, are you
telling me that I have
to abort this operation?
Yes or no?
Ms. Hayes, this is your call.
You don't know for certain
that this woman
will lead us to Bierko.
No, not for certain.
But, right now,
she's our only lead.
Are you willing
to take this chance?
You've left me no choice.
Proceed.
But you have severely
compromised this situation
and I promise you there
will be repercussions.
Fine.
Are we all right?
We're fine.
CURTIS:
Red Lexus turning the corner.
A hundred yards away
and approaching.
No one move until I give a go.
The red Lexus is parked.
Move the center mirror,
so that I can see the car.
There.
Now get her out of the car.
Hi.
Hello.
JACK:
I have a positive I.D.
All teams move in.
All teams move, move, move!
Let's go!
Put your hands
where I can see them!
Theo, get in the car, now.
Let me see your hands!
What are you doing?
Now!
Let me go.
Theo, get out of there.
I'm sorry.
Theo, who are you?
Move!
Letting him go.
He's given us
what we want!
Put your hands up!
Turn and face the car!
Put your hands on the roof!
Do it!
Where is Bierko?
We know you're
working with Bierko.
Where is he?
Fine.
Take her back to staging.
I want a team
searching this car.
Take everything back
to the staging area.
Now!
It's Theo.
I'm en route to the hotel.
Tell Heinrich
I'm uploading something
he's been wanting
for a long time.
( phone rings )
Stoller.
Theo, it's Jack.
I'm sorry.
I thought we had a deal.
When this is over,
I promise you,
I will help you rebuild
your investigation.
I give you my word.
I had your word.
What have you got?
Nothing.
She's covered
her tracks.
There's no sign
of what she sold to Bierko.
Come with me.
Collette Stenger,
my name is Jack Bauer.
Who is Theo really?
German Intelligence.
Then he sold me for a price.
German and American Intelligence
don't work together often.
Where is Bierko?
The fact is, I actually
had feelings for Theo.
I never once suspected.
He was very good.
I always thought that there
were some things
that you cannot fake.
Bierko.
Tell them to leave.
Jack?
It's all right.
Curtis, have your men
move back.
Just give us a second.
Let's go.
Theo had a price.
What's yours?
I'm not for sale.
Everyone is for sale.
This isn't a game, lady.
We're running out of time.
You better tell me
what you want.
All right.
Full immunity.
No holdbacks.
Signed by your president
and transmitted to lawyers
in Zurich and Tripoli.
But I can't tell you
where Bierko is.
Why not?
Because he's already gone.
I met him at a safehouse,
but he was already on his way
to carry out the attack.
What were you selling him?
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
I mean I don't know.
It was a schematic.
What kind of
a schematic?
I'm paid to broker
the information,
not dwell on the details.
I make it my firm policy.
You expect me to believe
that you acquired information
for a terrorist group and you
didn't know the specifics?
You can believe
whatever you want.
The fact is, I got the
schematics from a source
and they were
digitally encrypted.
That source can tell you
what they mean.
Give me immunity and
I'll give you my source.
Those are my terms.
You haven't offered us
very much.
I'll see what I can do.
( phone rings )
Buchanan.
Yeah, it's Jack.
She wants full immunity
signed by the president.
She claims that she doesn't know
where Bierko is.
That she just brokered a deal
for a set of schematics,
and then delivered them.
She doesn't know
what building they're for,
but she can provide us with
the source of the schematics.
She doesn't know
what she sold him?
She said it was
digitally encrypted.
Do you believe her?
She's an independent contractor.
In her line of work,
sometimes
what you don't know
will save your life.
Either way,
if she's telling the truth,
we don't have a lot of time.
She said Bierko already left
to set off his next attack.
Miles, call Mike Novick,
let's get this started.
Jack, this better work.
And for the record,
I don't like it.
We've paid a steep price.
There'll be fallout
on the WET List.
No, there won't be.
The fallout will be from
German Intelligence.
I programmed the memory card
to self-destruct.
Why didn't you tell us this
before?
I told you, I was in the car
with Stoller.
Get back to me as soon as this
is done, we need to move fast.
I think it's clear.
CTU was hit,
but we're still doing our job.
I believe
that's an argument
to maintain our autonomy.
Well, I'll withhold
judgment on that.
We're giving a free pass
to a terrorist collaborator,
and I have yet to see
what we're getting from it.
( tires screeching )
( panting )
Has the document been received
in Tripoli as well?
And it meets with
your approval?
So, there's no way
that they can fail
to live up to the terms?
Merci, Herve. Au revoir.
The safehouse
is a manufacturing facility
at 12451 Saticoy Boulevard.
As for the data
I sold to Bierko,
it's something that I
received from a contact
at the Department
of Defense.
What's his name?
Her name.
Audrey Raines.
You are lying to me.
She sold me the information, Mr.
Bauer.
Apparently she had a price.
Put her in the car.
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
http://tlfsub.eastgame.net