Looks pretty tempting, doesn't it?
But what if I told you that each one
of these delicious little morsels
has almost a thousand calories?
Would it make you want one any less?
Me, neither.
And that's normal.
We all want things
that we know are bad for us.
Everyone has dangerous fascinations
and unhealthy fixations.
Some of them are a little harder
to explain than others.
But most us know how to keep
our impulses in check.
We use willpower to fight off
our darker instincts.
Unfortunately, for others,
willpower just isn't enough.
The siren call of
one's own obsessions
is simply too strong to resist.
The thing we used to want...
... becomes the thing we now need.
Our obsession
becomes our compulsion.
Until eventually we realize
pursuing the one thing
we want most in life
has left us without
much of a life at all.
But in the end,
our compulsions are still there.
Even after they've pushed
us to the brink of death,
or guided us
into places of unimaginable horror.
Okay. Don't be mad.
I know, I know they're for
that bake sale at Bridgette's school,
but what can I say?
I couldn't resist.
- You want some?
- God, no.
I'm going to bed.
What?
It was a cupcake.
Okay. Now you try.
What are you doing?
What's she doing?
What are you making her do?
I'm not making her do anything.
She likes it.
Don't you like it?
Don't just stand there.
You know, fold some more.
Bridgette, that's your job.
You're supposed to fold the laundry.
That's why you have an allowance.
It's not my job.
It's my responsibility.
And I'm keeping that responsibility.
I'm just outsourcing, that's all.
It's no big deal.
Everybody's doing it.
Mom!
Sorry. Not Mom.
Feel free to continue fighting
till she gets here.
Dad, Bridgette's making Marie
do her work folding the laundry.
She asked me how to fold socks.
That's all. And underwear.
And towels, and how
to put them in drawers.
You are such a liar.
Okay, well, maybe she didn't ask
about the drawers.
Hey, Marie, did you ask
Bridgette any of that?
You are never moving out of
that bottom bunk!
Hey, what is all the noise about?
Why isn't anybody eating?
Why is all this laundry
still not folded?
And Bridgette, why are
your books not in your bag?
What is this?
I don't know.
It's a week old,
and it's marked urgent.
Well, then I guess it wasn't
really very urgent, was it?
Tomorrow's Parent-Teacher conference
has been rescheduled.
You're kidding!
I rearranged a meeting
so I could make that.
I already told Mr. Sacks I can't make
rehearsal 'cause I have to baby-sit.
It's not even 7:00, and I'm already
having a bad feeling about today.
I don't care.
Dad's got to go to work.
I just got a text.
I got to meet Scanlon downtown.
We're gonna talk about punishment later.
We've got to get breakfast going.
Nice work, doofus.
Well, I suppose there's
a bright side to all this.
We all have a free night.
Every single one of us
all here at the same time.
No meetings, no rehearsal.
You're right, Dad!
That's great news!
It's not that great.
Security guard stumbled
across the body.
We're thinking
it happened last night.
Looks like they used
a baseball bat or a pipe.
Normally, I'd start by asking his family
and friends if he had any enemies.
Of course, to do that, I'd have to have
the first clue who this guy is.
No wallet?
Actually, it was right there
in his pocket.
Only problem is, every piece
of ID he's carrying is fake.
Check out his fingers.
No fingerprints.
Who do you think did this?
I'm guessing since
he's carrying all that fake ID,
that his very severe mani
is just part of the package.
This is a guy who clearly didn't want
anyone to know who he really was,
- which is why I called you.
- Coming through, Detective.
I was hoping maybe you'd see him
and, you know,
get some feeling,
have some instinct about who...
... who he is, where he came from.
Who might have done this.
Allison, you with me?
Yeah. Of course. If I see anything,
I'll call you.
You see this old microwave over
here? You think it's okay if I just,
you know, dig it out of the trash,
take it home with me?
Tell you what.
You help me figure out who
played percussion on this guy's noggin,
I'll even buy you a new one.
Mr. Brewer?
What you doing?
You gunning for my job?
You trying to be an early bird
or something?
I don't like it.
Ambition.
Initiative.
Makes me nervous.
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
I couldn't sleep.
I kept thinking about the problem
with the contact grid.
I know we've been going around and
around this for the past three weeks,
but...
you know, suddenly at 3:00
this morning, I...
I had a...
This just came to you?
Well, the concept. I got in here
about an hour and a half ago,
and I started working on
the engineering.
Well...
This-This is amazing.
Okay. Now I'm officially
threatened by your intellect.
Hey, what are you and Debbie
doing for dinner tomorrow night?
I mean, are you busy?
Do you have plans?
I've been talking to my wife about
having you guys over since you got here.
Hello!
Gooey red stuff.
What did I miss? Spaghetti?
Ketchup for take-out.
- Okay. Where is everybody?
- Where?
It's late, Dad.
I put Bridgette and Marie down,
and Mom went out
to work in the garage.
Work in the garage?
Al?
Back here!
Hi.
Ariel said you were in here.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
What are you working on?
I don't know.
You're gonna think it's silly.
Looks like you're trying
to take apart an old microwave.
That's exactly what I'm doing.
I'm taking apart anoldmicrowave.
I found this thing in the trash
at the crime scene this morning,
and I suddenly got really curious
about the way these things work.
What do you mean? Just ask me.
They use radio waves
to create a radiation that creates
excitement in the molecules in the food
and that heats it up and makes it cook.
We have one of these in the kitchen.
Well, not an old one like this.
You know, I just want to look inside,
see how it does it.
How you put food inside, it comes out
hot, but then the oven stays cool.
Did you eat?
David and I ordered in.
That reminds me.
Hey, don't be mad.
I invited he and his wife Debbie
over tomorrow night for dinner.
It's time, Allison. The guy relocated
here with his family
- almost two months ago.
- Yeah, fine.
I'll make a roast.
Do they eat meat?
Yeah, he sure does. I mean, boy,
can he engineer. I mean, what a find.
Couldn't you find a less
gross-looking microwave?
I mean, it looks like you can
catch a disease from that thing.
I'll be in in a minute.
All right, fine. I've been kicked
out of bed nicer than that.
- I'll see you in a couple of minutes.
- See you in a couple of minutes.
Do you know that it's almost
3:00 in the morning?
Do you have any idea how much heat
this thing can generate?
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I do.
I would say roughly enough to bake
a big potato in about seven minutes.
Can we go to bed?
Allison, you've been out here
for almost six hours now.
I don't know what this fascination
is with small appliances,
but you've got a big day tomorrow.
We both have big days.
We have people
coming over for dinner.
Oh, my God.
- What time did you say it was?
- It's 3:00 in the morning.
I don't even...
I don't even know what to say.
I just suddenly got so fascinated
with that thing, I...
I kind of got lost in it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
But only a single step
is the beginning of a new dialogue
between the United States...
The search continues
for Justice Heath Clemens,
a federal judge
on the 12th Circuit Court,
who was reported missing
yesterday afternoon.
Anyone with information
on his whereabouts is urged to
- contact the authorities immediately.
- Arlo! You in there?!
Arlo, quit tinkering
with that idiot box and come outside.
I got something I want to show you.
Dad, I just saw this man
on the news.
They're looking for him.
- His name's...
- He doesn't have a name!
He surrendered his right
to an identity
on the day he was sworn
onto that court.
The day he agree
to become another cog
in the machine
that is systematically destroying
everything and anything
that was ever good about this country!
He's an extension of them.
A diseased limb.
You're a smart boy, Arlo.
You know what a doctor would do
with a diseased limb, don't you?
Dad, please don't...
You want to know what
this robot does with his life?
He sits behind a bench
all day issuing rulings
that take away the rights
of free citizens like you and me.
He gets paid to harass us,
to decide how we get
to live our lives.
Now, tell me, does that sound
like the kind of government you want?
Is that the way you want
your country run?
Dad, he's not the government.
He's just a man.
He's just a man trying to do his job.
I'm sorry.
What was that last bit you said?
'Cause I think
you were describing me.
- How are we supposed to eat this?
- With a fork.
It's not what I mean.
You forgot the syrup.
It's all hard without the syrup.
- Here.
- Ketchup?
All right, knock yourself out
and help your sister, too.
More, more!
All right, all right,
I'm giving you more.
- How are we doing over there?
- Never better.
No urge to take apart
the central air?
Figure out how it is the air
comes in so hot, but comes out so cold?
Is something going on?
Everything's fine.
I just... Mommy didn't get
a lot of sleep last night,
and Daddy didn't get much either.
But everything's fine.
We still okay for tonight?
It's not too late to call it off.
I'll be fine.
I got to go down to City Hall,
show Scanlon something.
Then I'm heading right
to the store to go shopping.
Hey, girls,
when Ariel comes in, can you be sure
to tell her she's got to clean her room?
We have company coming tonight.
I will be in the bathroom
taking apart the shower.
I'm just kidding.
Just kidding.
His name was Heath Clemens.
He was a federal judge.
The police think someone abducted him
from his house in Needles, California.
June of'85. So, what does any
of this have to do with me?
Did you see the part where
it said they discovered his body
a few weeks later in the desert, and no
one was ever arrested for the murder?
Yeah, I can read, Allison.
The man who killed him,
the man I saw slit his throat
was the same man
we discovered the other day,
laying in all that trash,
the one with no fingerprints.
When you say "saw,"
what you really mean was...
Dreamt.
What I really meant was dreamt.
Don't... don't start on me today.
I had three hours of sleep last night.
Okay, easy.
So what have we got?
We got a dead guy... no name.
Now, we got another dead guy from
a long time ago who you say he killed.
I guess that might explain
why he burned his own fingertips off.
Needles,
I guess we could make a few calls,
send them a picture of our friend in
the morgue. See if anybody recalls him.
He sounded like one of those,
those rightwing conspiracy
nuts who thinks
the government is out to get them,
take away all their personal freedom.
And he had a son.
Well, he sounds like a pretty
unique character.
Maybe someone will remember him.
I'm home!
What in God's...?
Did the dishwasher break?
What's going on?
Nope, it didn't break.
Mom insisted she needed
some sheet metal screws
and the ones in the back of
the dishwasher were perfect.
Need?
Need for what?
Where is Mom?
Where is dinner?
People are coming over.
They're going to be here any minute.
Yeah, I know.
I kept telling her.
- What did she say?
- She didn't say anything.
She just announced that she'd be
in the garage, working.
Allison?!
I'm back here!
What the hell is going on?
I'm soldering.
And I'm getting
pretty good at it, too.
No, that's not what I mean, Allison.
People are on their way over.
There's nothing cooking in the oven.
The dishwasher is in the middle
of the kitchen.
You're and the kids aren't dressed.
Come on, what the hell are you doing?!
You know, I'm not quite sure,
but I was kind of hoping
that you could tell me.
I think this thing really is
going to work, whatever it is.
You set the timer here and then
whenever that time runs out this thing
starts to get hot, really,
really hot,
but why and what that does,
I'm not...
What is that smell?
What are you talking about?
What smell?
It almost smells
like a plumbing problem.
Did you buy all this fertilizer?
I sure did. It took me
five trips to get it here.
Can you tell me why?
I'm not quite sure. I know it's got
something to do with this thing.
It wasn't something I planned to do.
It came into my head,
and I knew I had to have it.
Allison, I need you to step away
from that thing right now.
- All right, give me one second, honey.
- No, no, time's up.
I need you to step away from
that thing and come with me.
You know, if this is about
this whole dinner thing,
I'm starting to think maybe
we should reschedule.
- What are you doing?
- Put that down.
Get the hell away from that thing.
Get away from it and go in the house.
- What the hell is your problem?
- My problem? You want to know?
This thing you've been working on, this
is some kind of a timer, a detonator.
And these hundreds of pounds of
fertilizer you brought into our house,
our house where we live,
where our children live.
These would be your explosives.
Now, I may be crazy,
but I think you're minutes away
from having an uncontrollable urge
to rent a panel truck,
fill it with all this stuff
and drive it to a federal
building somewhere!
Oh, God.
You know what. On second thought,
why don't you just continue doing
exactly what you're doing, okay?
Because, you know, if we're all
dead then maybe no one will notice
that there's no dinner!
Sorry.
David, hi.
Debbie. Hello, Joe.
God. This is so embarrassing...
Is everything okay?
Yes. No, no.
It's, um...
We've had a...
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault.
Well, maybe "fault"
isn't the right word.
It's me. I have food poisoning.
That's Debbie, that's David.
Yeah, I'm Allison.
It's nice to meet you.
I... It's nice that I'm...
we just met.
No, please.
You don't have to do that.
I've been living in the bathroom
for the last...
the last 45 minutes.
Which is you know, why...
that's why I'm not dressed.
And, you know,
I've been in there cooking all day.
We would ask you in, but...
Yeah, it's like a bomb
went off in there.
Or we would ask you to go
to a restaurant, or something...
Oh. I feel terrible for you.
Hey, I've been looking
all over for you guys.
This is our middle
daughter Bridgette.
- Say hi to the Brewers.
- Hi.
Do you guys know that it smells
like a barn out in the garage?
Hey, we're going to take off...
but we brought this.
- Oh, no, no. You don't have to do that.
- I... I insist.
I just... maybe
wouldn't drink it tonight.
Right.
All right, Dave.
So long. I'm sorry.
It's nice to meet you, Debbie.
Okay, Bridgette, would you go
and get ready for bed?
Daddy needs to talk to Mommy.
What are you doing?
I called the store.
They're open till 10:00.
So I'm loading up both cars.
We're taking all this back,
'cause I don't want it in the house.
I don't want it anywhere near the house.
Ariel can watch the girls.
You follow me in your car.
We'll get it done in a couple trips.
- I can do this tomorrow.
- Yeah...
Right.
- Well, what does that mean?
- That means that you built a bomb...
in our house, Allison.
In my children's house.
Now get in the car, please.
It's getting late.
Are you still awake?
You're kidding, right?
I think it's over.
I took apart that thing that I was
building. I threw all the pieces away.
Not even a twinge of regret.
And for what it's worth,
when we went back to that store,
nothing, nothing glowed.
I'm sorry, but that's not
reassuring enough.
I need you to promise me,
if these urges,
if these compulsions to...
to build things to acquire things,
if they come back,
you have to call me...
you have to find me.
I'll come home.
I'll hold you down.
I might call you just to test that.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry about tonight.
So you got all this from
the Needles Police Department?
The sheriff recognized the photo
of our John Doe as soon as he saw it.
Turns out this guy
is actually Mitchell Slocumb.
Mitchell Slocumb...
I know that name.
Well, I would hope so.
He certainly made enough news.
Back in 1985,
he detonated a fertilizer bomb
in a parking garage beneath the federal
courthouse in Sacramento, California.
It was one of the first cases of
domestic terrorism in this country.
Seventeen people died.
Mitchell Slocumb wrote a letter
claiming credit for the bombing.
Then he just disappeared.
That is, until now.
You okay?
Yeah, no, yeah.
I'm just...
I'm surprised.
Anyway, this man's death
is gonna be big news,
so before I talk to the media,
I just wanted to make sure you...
didn't have any new insights
into who might have killed him.
Although, to be perfectly frank,
I'm not sure if I prefer to prosecute
his murderer or recommend
the guy for a commendation.
So nothing?
- You feeling better today?
- Yeah, thank you.
Can I have a word with you?
I started building that bomb two days
ago, just hours after I saw his body.
I have to believe that's more
than just a coincidence.
So you think maybe that
he was using you to take care of
some unfinished business?
He blew up a federal courthouse
in 1985.
I work in a courthouse. I drive my car
into a courthouse garage every day.
But you haven't called me, so I'm
assuming you haven't felt the need to
buy anything, build anything,
collect anything.
- What are you doing?
- If we can't be absolutely positive
that Mitchell Slocumb won't get
into your head again,
at least we can make sure
you don't have the means
to buy any more fertilizer for him.
A gallon of gas?
You all right?
I'm fine.
It's a bad habit.
Debbie thinks I quit.
If she knew, she'd kill me.
You sure you're okay?
No, I'm okay.
It's family stuff.
It's just...
Explain.
Don't lie to me.
Don't lie to me!
Don't tell me it wasn't you. You'll just
make it twice as bad if you lie to me.
I thought he deserved
a decent burial...
I gave him what he deserved, Arlo.
I tried so hard to raise you right.
Look at me!
All you do is disappoint.
The problem with you, son,
is you keep forgetting
we're at war here.
Me... I got this to remind me.
I see it in the mirror every day
and I remember.
Crawling through the mud
and the puke at Khe Sanh.
I remember my boots
filling with the blood
of young American boys,
whose daddies either
weren't rich or white enough
to keep them out of a racist,
classist draft.
I remember the stink
of their corpses...
knowing that they died
for nothing.
- Dad, what are you doing?
- Like I said, Arlo,
we're at war.
Now you'll have something
to remind you.
Dad... Dad!
It was nice seeing you again,
Allison.
I hope the next time you meet Debbie,
you'll keep my secret.
Somebody's been
awfully quiet all night.
Well, somebody's in a real quandary.
Oh, really? You think so?
Have you not heard
anything that I've said?
Yeah, I got it.
He's a smoker.
Me? I'm willing to look past it.
You know that's not
what I'm talking about.
Seriously? Because I don't think
the other matters.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
Let's say that you're right.
Let's say that...
Mitchell Slocumb really is
David's father. So what?
Does that change who he is?
Am I supposed to think less of him
for something that his father did?
Changing your name
so people won't hold
what your father did against you,
is that a crime?
- Boy, you really don't get it.
- No, Allison, I think I do.
As psychic dilemmas go,
this one's pretty cut-and-dry.
If David Brewer doesn't want
anyone to know who he is,
then that's fine,
that's his business.
I get it.
We don't h he doesn't have to tell.
But, Joe, I think I have to ask.
I know that Slocumb was a monster, but
it's my job to find out who killed him.
- You think it might have been David?
- Well, I don't know.
But if what I'm seeing is true, in
addition to killing all of these people,
Mitchell Slocumb was
an incredibly abusive parent.
That doesn't make David a killer.
And, look, let's not forget,
we're not absolutely certain
they're father and son.
You should have seen him
outside of your office.
It was right after the news hit
that we identified Slocumb.
David was trembling. When I asked what's
wrong, he said it was a family thing.
Well, maybe it was. How do you know?
Maybe he had a fight with his wife.
I am sorry.
I know that you really like him.
But I need to tell Devalos
what I know.
And he's going to question him.
Allison, we're not talking about
somebody that I... that I like here.
We're talking about the only person
that I've hired so far.
He's like half the company.
- It took me three months to find him.
- I know.
I want to be the one
to talk to him first.
If he's going to get hauled into
the DA's office
because he has the bad luck
to work for me,
then I want to be the one
to explain it to him.
- David, thank you so much for coming.
- Yeah. Like I have a choice.
I was born Arlo Slocumb.
Mitchell Slocumb's my father.
Was my father.
So what do you want to know?
I'm not going to be able to tell you
very much. I moved out before I was 17.
As soon as I turned 21,
I changed my name.
I, I don't think
I have any light to shed.
Be that as it may, I do need
to ask you some questions,
the most important being can you account
for your whereabouts Monday night?
You mean the night
that my father was killed?
Yeah...
but no. I mean...
I was at home, but there was
no one there with me.
What about Debbie?
Your kids?
They were visiting with
her sister in Flagstaff.
Is that the working theory?
You think I spent 20 years
hiding that I was his son
so I could come back and kill him
and become notorious for it?
I don't know how to prove it,
but I didn't even know
he was in Phoenix
until I saw the online report
that he was dead.
I'm afraid that's not good enough,
Mr. Brewer.
I've got to find a way
to substantiate your alibi.
Even in death
the man is complicating my life.
So what's next?
How do we do this?
It's pretty straightforward stuff.
We fingerprint you.
Look around your house
for a murder weapon.
- Talk to some people who know you.
- Oh, man.
Look.
I get it.
I understand what you have to do.
I get it. I...
All I'm saying is just...
please be sensitive to my situation.
Be discreet.
I've spent a long time
building a life as David Brewer.
I have a wife, I have two kids
who have no idea that their grandfather
was a mass murderer.
I have a professional
reputation to protect.
We understand, Mr. Brewer.
We'll do our best.
Mom! Daddy's on the TV!
Daddy's on the TV!
I was trying to find cartoons. But all
the channels had Daddy on them instead.
Mr. Slocumb, is it true you've been
living under an assumed name
- since the 1980s?
- I have nothing to say about that.
- Seen the news?
- Seen it?
Lee, my God, this is terrible.
This man's a friend. He works for
my husband. We gave him our word.
- How did the press find out?
- Someone must have seen my report,
made a call.
I'm guessing money changed hands.
That poor man.
All he did was ask us
to protect his privacy.
You ready for the punch line?
It was all for naught.
We found the man
who actually killed Slocumb.
Name is Donald Wright.
He ran with the same rightwing
nut jobs that Slocumb did.
Turns out the two of them
had a fight over money.
Ended with Wright taking a pipe
to his "buddy's" skull.
David's completely innocent?
We questioned him for nothing.
I'm afraid so. I wonder
if it'll be any consolation to him
while the media's picking
his life apart.
No, okay.
No, I, yeah, I understand.
Look, if there's ever anything
that I can do for you...
I'm so sorry.
I really am, David.
What? What now?
He just quit.
They're moving.
Oh, God, no.
Somebody threw a rock
through their window.
He's been getting threatening
phone calls all night.
The police have a car parked
outside of his house,
but it's not like they can stay
there forever.
He just wants out of here...
and I can't blame him.
I don't understand.
What is all this?
If he's innocent, why am I being shown
all these things?
So I can ruin the life
of a good man?
You got me, Al.
Dad?
I have something I want to show you.
What the hell is that?
I found one of those new microwave
ovens over at the dump.
It was pretty smashed up,
but the inside still worked.
It gave me an idea.
See, this is a timer.
You just set it for however long
you need to get away.
And this, this thing
gets really, really hot.
You take all this,
you put it in a vehicle filled
with gas and-and an oxidizer...
Oxidizer?
What's an oxidizer?
Fertilizer.
You take 20 or 30 bags
- of fertilizer...
- And what?
Well, I think you could
blow up a building.
That's...
beautiful, son.
I could never build
something like that.
Not in a million years.
You always said you wanted
to change the world, Dad.
Now you can.
Oh, my God, what are you up to now?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm not building anything.
I'm not blowing anything up.
I'm just trying to find...
Here it is.
From a 20-year-old microwave.
I completely missed the point.
I have no idea what you're
talking about. The point of what?
The dreams, the compulsions. They had
nothing to do with Mitchell Slocumb
trying to get me to blow up
another courthouse.
It had to do with seeing
how the bomb really got made
so I could understand
who really made it.
What do you mean,
"who really made it"?
Mitchell Slocumb
didn't build that bomb, Joe.
His son did.
Remember that night he came over?
He handed me that bottle of wine?
As soon as I touched it,
I saw these images.
These flashes of...
pictures. Faces.
I really didn't understand it at the
time, but now I'm starting to think...
There they are.
There's 17 of them.
I'm starting to think that I saw them
'cause they're always in his head.
He's haunted by them.
Okay, so let's say
that you're right.
What are you gonna do?
It's 23 years now.
The only other person
who was there is dead.
How exactly do you go
about proving any of this?
I mean, what do you do with it?
I don't know.
How do you do it?
How do you live with yourself?
How do you live with it
day in and day out?
With 17 people's lives
on your conscience?
I don't know what you're talking about.
They aren't on my conscience.
My father detonated that bomb.
My father killed those people.
Your father figured out how to use
microwave oven parts
to build a detonator?
You father knew to use
gasoline and fertilizer ten years
before Timothy McVeigh
and the Oklahoma City bombing?
Your father, who dropped out of high
school and went right into the army?
I think I'd like you to leave now.
I know you built it.
I know you made it.
I know you gave it to your father.
And he drove it to California
and he murdered
17 people.
17 people whose pictures you saw
in the newspaper the next morning.
17 people whose faces
are etched in your mind.
Whatever you say.
But seeing as how there are no police
cars flooding this driveway,
I don't see how you are actually
able to prove that.
Well, you're right.
I can't prove it.
But the 17 people
who died that day...
the people who loved them...
they really deserve to know
what really happened.
They-they know what happened.
A misguided fool with mental
problems set off a bomb.
And if it hadn't been that bomb,
it might have been another.
Dynamite stolen
from a construction site,
or a war-surplus hand grenade.
Is that how you excuse what you did?
By the way,
I think your math's a little off.
18 people died that day.
A badly damaged
boy named Arlo Slocumb...
he died in that blast, too.
And out of his ashes...
David Brewer was born.
And while David Brewer
may sometimes think about
some of the things
that Arlo Slocumb did,
it'd be an unspeakable tragedy
for him to go to jail
for that boy's crimes.
I mean...
what would be the point of
destroying one more family?
- Sweetie. We really need to get going.
- I'll be right there.
I'm sorry that we're not gonna able
to have that dinner, Allison.
I really think you'd like me.
It's always there,
isn't it?
Give Joe my best.