We can cast off the shackles
of our daily lives.
We can go anywhere we want to go.
We can be any version of ourselves
That we want to be.
I'm not saying that isn't true.
Who am I to contradict
a college textbook?
But any schoolkid can tell you
That there is one thing
you can't do in your dreams.
You can't die.
According to just about every schoolkid
Who's ever lived--
If you actually die in your dream,
You'll die in real life, too.
We laugh at that idea
as we get older.
But I wonder sometimes:
Can we ever be absolutely sure
That those kids are wrong?
I mean, if your dream
does kill you,
You're not around to talk
about it, right?
They'll call it a heart attack.
They'll say you died
in your sleep.
They'll never know
what actually happened
Is that your worst nightmare
finally caught up with you.
You okay?
You all right?
Actually, I'm dead.
Get some more sleep.
You'll feel better.
S06E06
Bite me
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
Stop it.
You're ignorant.
They're coming for you, Barbara.
Look! There comes one of them now.
Cool.
They really were coming for her.
- I'm getting out of here.
- Johnny!
Johnny!
Help me!
Hey, where you goin' ?
You're not afraid, are you ?
Hey, what're you watching over there ?
It sounds pretty scary
for a Sunday morning.
It's some old movie called
Night of the living dead.
It's part of a zombie movie marathon
That's going to be on until Halloween.
They're not running the one
Where everyone gets trapped in the mall,
Are they ?
Bridgette! I am going to kill you!
Mom!
Make her come and get this thing
Out of here!
Bridgette, I mean it!
Get in here
before I flush this thing!
That thing has a name.
Miss Scarlet.
I don't care what your
stupid science class
Decided to call their stupid pet.
Get it out of here. Now!
Bridgette, I thought you told me
You were going to keep
miss Scarlet in your room.
I know, but miss Colletto
said tarantulas do better
In humid environments
Like a bathroom or a basement.
And it's not like I was
going to keep her in here.
Humid,huh?
How do you think she'll feel
at the bottom of the toilet?
Ariel, relax. Bridgette, hey.
Bring miss Scarlet back into your room.
You can bring her in here when
it's your turn to take a bath.
Scanlon.
He does know it's Sunday, right?
Hey. What's going on?
Hey, I know it's the weekend,
but I was wondering
If there's any way you could
give me a hand with something.
I got kind of a situation.
What kind of situation?
You're damn right, I'm upset.
Something bad has happened to him,
And you people don't seem to care.
This is a man who has given discounts
To the policemen and firemen
For as long as he's been in business.
He's even buried a few men for free
When he realized that
the families couldn't afford it.
And now that he needs you,
All I hear is, it's too soon
To file a missing persons report.
The person who answered
your call obviously wasn't aware
Of your father's special relationship
With the department.
Which is why we're here to assure you
That this is being taken seriously.
We're doing everything
we can to find your father.
Now, do you think it's possible
Thanks.
That he may have just slipped
away without telling you?
Maybe taken some time off?
You haven't heard a word
I've said, have you?
He's not taking time off.
He doesn't take time off.
"time off" is not in my father's dna.
This is a man who lives to work.
Period.
He's been running
this place for 40 years.
And as far as I know,
The only time he's taken time off
Was the morning that I was born.
And that was only because my mother
Threatened to kill him if he didn't.
Okay, well...
Along those same lines,
did he have any enemies?
Anyone who may have wished him harm?
Ten, twelve years ago,
I would've said "no."
He was always a very loved man.
He was the president of
the chamber of commerce three times.
He always sponsored a little league team.
He loved this neighborhood.
I think that's why he was so upset
When he started to see it change
with the drugs
And the crime and the dealers...
The gangs.
You know, daddy's never been shy
about his opinion
With regard to the state
of things around here.
And on more than one occasion,
He's had words with
The drug dealers.
Maybe...
One of them, finally just...
Just got rid of him.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have two funerals this morning.
The dead don't like
to be kept waiting.
Yikes.
Okay, here's the plan.
I put miss Scarlet on the tip
of Ariel's toothbrush
and you take a picture.
And then, once Ariel's done
brushing her teeth,
we show her the picture.
Your spider looks funny
when he's sleeping.
First of all, it's not a spider,
it's a tarantula.
Second of all, it's not a he, it's a she.
And third of all,
tarantulas don't sleep.
Well, this one does.
What?
What did miss Colletto say ?
Was she mad?
No, sweetie, she wasn't mad.
Nobody's mad.
She was just sorry it took
her so long to call us back.
She wanted to make sure that
you don't worry about it.
She said there's no way
of knowing how old miss Scarlet was,
And it was probably just her time.
That isn't your fault.
I think I'm just going to go to bed.
I thought we were going
to finish this together.
You can finish it without me.
I'm just not in the mood
anymore.
Did miss Colletto happen to mention
what we were supposed to do with
the spectacular spider remains?
Apparently,
miss Scarlet is flushable.
Burial at sea.
Excellent.
What about the terrarium?
She said if we
don't have any use for it,
We can just throw it away.
Seems that she has more than
she needs in her classroom.
Dead tarantulas,
Flesh-eating zombies,
And a missing funeral parlor director.
Halloween isn't exactly
being subtle this year.
Hey, come on, barb.
Church was this morning, huh?
I'm sorry.
Was that you who just
said something to me?
And did you say it in black and white?
I mean, praying's for church, huh
Come on.
Wait, back up.
Did you just call me "Barb"?
My name's Allison.
And I'm not sure I like
What this black and white
is doing to my skin.
Do you remember one time,
when we were small,
We were out here?
It was from right over there.
I jumped out at you from behind a tree,
And grandpa got all excited
and he shook his fist at me
And he said, "boy,
you'll be damned to hell."
You used to really be scared here.
This is really freaky.
You're still afraid.
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
You've got to stop calling me Barbara!
My name is Allison!
Even though this is a dream,
my name is Allison!
They're coming for you, Barbara.
Look!
There comes one of them now.
Don't worry.
You're going to wake up soon.
Hey, is that your house?
I need to get inside!
We both really
Need to get inside...
Hey, what's going on?
You all right ?
Yeah, nothing.
It's a nightmare.
It's just a nightmare.
Sorry, honey.
Go back to sleep.
What? Allison?!
What did you do to your arm?
Oh, my god.
I just don't understand
how this happened.
I was having a dream,
A weird, old zombie movie dream.
Well, I mean...
If you were dreaming,
you weren't, like, in control.
You just, like, grabbed yourself--
You grabbed your arm,
and you scratched yourself up.
Really ripped the skin.
But, you know, it's not that unusual.
Had a roommate in college
Who used to throw punches in his sleep.
I sometimes grind my teeth.
I mean, it's not like
you went in the garage
And, like, started up the skill saw.
I mean, you scratched yourself.
You scratched the crap out of yourself,
But still...
Okay.
Voilà .
Groundskeeper found Bobbi Catalano's dad
A little over an hour ago.
Forensics thinks he was killed
out there by those graves,
Then dragged in here and out of sight.
Wallet and watch are gone.
Car is still parked in the parking lot.
Do we have any idea
what he was doing out here ?
Given his profession, you'd think
It might have been work-related,
But apparently,
One of those headstones over
there belongs to his wife.
Best guess is, he was visiting her
When someone jumped him.
Smashed his head in with a
stone and emptied his pockets.
It's kind of a strange place
for a mugging, don't you think?
Well, yes and no.
It's quiet, isolated.
If you yell for help,
there's no one around to hear
Except for a bunch of dead people.
Feel free to take a look around
And see if you get anything.
I'm going to go call ms. Catalano
And let her know we found her dad.
Sir?
Sir.
Sir, are you all right?
What the hell is going on?
Allison, go for help.
Get them to call an ambulance.
The mesozoic era is often called
the age of the reptiles.
Reptiles were the dominant form
of life on earth
For the entire era, which lasted...
...Almost 200 million years.
The mesozoic era is divided
into three distinct periods.
Bridgette?
Are you all right?
Hi, kiddo.
No hello?
Is everything okay?
I think miss Scarlet's mad at me.
Miss Scarlet?
The spider ?
I don't think that's
possible, honey.
I was there when
miss Scarlet was fl...
Laid to rest,
and I don't think she can be mad
At anyone or anything at this point.
I think she can.
And I think she is.
And I deserve it.
Why?
Because I gave her some candy.
What?
I fed her some candy.
I put some candy in her cage,
Just to see if she'd like it.
I think that's why she died.
Paging dr. Stateman.
His name's Edgar Kripke.
According to social services,
he's a drug addict
And a paranoid schizophrenic.
When he couldn't get a bed at
the local homeless shelter,
He'd sleep in that cemetery.
Bobbi Catalano told me that kripke
Had actually had words
with her father before.
I guess her dad wasn't
too happy that this guy
Was crashing a few hundred
yards from his wife's grave.
Carl actually called
the police on him once.
Had him arrested for vagrancy.
But that doesn't prove that he...
We searched the cardboard
box that Kripke calls home.
Found Carl's wallet
in there and his watch.
What about the blood around his mouth?
And the groaning?
Drug overdose.
He must have just gotten
high when you spotted him.
His doctor says it caused
some serious brain damage.
What kind of drug does that?
You ever heard of something called "wet"?
Cigarettes soaked in methanol,
formaldehyde and ethanol.
It's a hallucinogen. Believe it or not,
There's actually demand for this stuff.
The government's been
trying to make it harder
For the people who cook this stuff up
To get their hands on the ingredients,
But we just keep seeing
more and more of it.
So, what, this guy just fried his brain?
We're never going to get him
to admit what he did.
It's okay.
I think we got enough
to pin this murder on Kripke,
Whether he ever talks again or not.
I don't know exactly what it was
That drew your attention
to this deadbeat, but
I'm glad it happened.
At least now we got some
answers for Carl's daughter.
So, Bridgette thinks she's being haunted
By that dead spider?
Yes, indeedy.
So, what did you tell her?
I suggested she talk to her teacher
And tell her that she fed
candy to the class pet.
Well, how is that going to help?
She's obviously got a guilty conscience,
Not to mention an overactive imagination,
So I just figured if she confessed, then...
Okay, I get that.
You've been at this for a while.
Have you ever communed
with any dead insects?
Now that you mention it,
I'm going to have to add
that to my to-do list.
...Reports, incredible as they seem,
Are not the results of mass hysteria.
A wave of murder, which is sweeping
The eastern third of the nation,
is being committed by creatures
Who feast upon the flesh
of their victims.
I think we have some late word
just arriving.
This is the latest disclosure
in a report
From national civil defense
headquarters in washington.
"it has been established that
persons who have recently died
Have been returning to life
and committing acts of murder."
"widespread investigation
of reports from funeral homes,
"morgues and hospitals has concluded
"that the unburied dead
are coming back to life
And seeking human victims."
Hello?
Joe.
Oh, my god.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry. My name's not Joe.
It's Dale. It's Dale Cosgrove.
Don't you remember?
I saved you from that creature
Who was trying to get in here.
You fell down, and you hit your head.
We put you on the couch
so you could sleep it off.
But now you're up,
I could use your help.
I mean, if you're feeling up to it.
And that creature who attacked you...
He's got a lot of friends.
Pretty sure they're coming back.
Hey.
I know what I'm talking about.
My family and I were on the interstate,
And we saw a whole bunch of them.
I slowed down.
It was dark.
I didn't realize what they were at first.
And before I knew what was happening...
One of them got my wife's door open,
And he... He pulled her out of the truck,
And they all began biting at her,
Ripping at her flesh with their teeth.
That's horrible.
So, we found your house,
And... Hope you don't mind
that we set up camp here.
It's fine with me.
It's not my house.
I don't know whose house it is.
Daddy?
My daughters.
That's Abigail, Mabel and Bella.
I'm sorry... I didn't catch your name.
I'm Allison.
I'm Allison Dubois.
Daddy, I know you told us
to stay in the basement,
But that man is getting worse.
There's a man?
What man?
Someone else is here?
We found him on the way.
We saved him from a pack
of those things.
They were
biting him and clawing at him,
So we brought him with us.
Girls, go to the kitchen.
Get him some water.
See if he'll take a drink.
We got to board this place up,
Wait it out until the police
Or the national guard can come get us.
I think, if we can make
it till morning...
- ...We'll be okay.
- They're back, daddy!
A whole bunch of them!
You can see them through the window!
Damn it.
We're going to need more wood.
And fast.
Look for old furniture.
Anything we can break into more boards.
Hey.
Come on.
What are you staring at?
We have work to do.
I'm sorry.
I know him.
We kind of come from the same place.
Oh, my god.
He's not breathing.
Hey, come on down there!
We need some wood!
Here.
Here, you take this.
I'll look for more.
No, no.
Yeah?
Al, what is it?
What's wrong?
Oh, my god.
Mr. Dubois?
Hi... Doctor.
How's my wife?
She'll be fine.
We dressed her wound,
But I'm not sure that's
what we should call it.
What do you mean?
Once we rinsed all the blood away...
You know, her skin is...
It's raw, it's inflamed.
There's clearly bruising.
And it certainly seems for all the world
Like she's been bitten.
The only thing is,
there's no broken skin,
No teeth marks, no actual trauma.
How's that possible?
Well, one possibility,
And the only possibility
I can think of is,
There's a phenomenon
known as psychosomatic bruising.
In very rare cases,
A patient sometimes can injure themselves.
I don't think
that's possible in this case
'cause the bite was on the back
of her calf, so I...
Oh, the wounds wouldn't have
been caused by physical trauma.
The belief is, they're generated
by the patient's mind.
The injuries are a subconscious
physiological response
To extreme stress.
The theory is that your emotional state
Can cause your blood vessels to engorge.
And if it's bad enough,
You could actually bleed
right through your pores.
Now, you know, your wife did say
That she's been having nightmares,
so I thought
Maybe all she needs is a couple nights
Of uninterrupted sleep.
So, here's a prescription
for sleeping pills,
And beyond that...
That doesn't make much sense.
She wants me to get more sleep?
Hey, look, I don't know, you know?
She seemed to think that, you know,
A night of uninterrupted sleep was...
Wait. I don't think she gets this.
I don't think I could survive
a night of uninterrupted sleep.
I mean, think about it.
Even if she's right, even if
I'm doing this to myself,
I'm still getting hurt.
I dream that I get hurt,
I wake up, and I'm hurt.
What if my next dream,
I dream that I break my leg,
Or what if I die in my dream?
Die? You don't think that
could happen, do you?
Honey, this is crazy.
How do you not sleep?
You have to sleep.
It's 6:15. The girls
are gonna be up in a minute.
I was hoping we'd get home before...
Okay, here's what we're going to do.
I'm going to stay awake tonight, okay?
I'll watch you sleep.
If it looks like you're
having a nightmare,
Then I'll wake you up.
And if you make it till midnight,
then we'll switch.
I'll sleep for a few hours,
and-and you stay awake.
And we'll keep doing
that until morning.
And that way, between the two of us,
We'll share a good night's sleep.
How's that sound?
Mrs. Dubois?
Mrs. Catalano, I didn't know
you were coming by.
I didn't know I was coming by.
The district attorney
called me late last night,
Invited me to be part
of a press conference
That they're having this morning.
Anyway, I saw you sitting over here,
and I wanted
To come over and say thank you.
They told me that you were the one
Who figured out who killed daddy.
Well, not me by myself,
But you're very welcome.
I am sure that you
hear this all the time,
But if there's anything
that I can do for you...
Oh, thank you.
I'm just glad they caught the guy.
Ooh, my.
I'd better get going.
Thank you.
What happened to your hand ?
It's really not that bad.
Actually, I did it to myself.
Really?
When I got the call
About dad, and they told me
That he was really dead, I must have
Just grabbed my hand and
started squeezing it.
Anything. Anything to keep
from screaming out loud,
And I guess that...
I didn't even realize
that I was doing that.
But...
Anyway, I'd better get going.
Again, thank you.
I'm really sorry, miss Colletto.
I shouldn't have given
miss Scarlet a piece of candy,
And I should have told you what I did.
Thanks for coming in
and telling me that, Bridgette.
That must have been a hard thing to do.
Can you keep a secret?
See mr. Nibbles back there?
No one else knows this,
But he's really mr. Nibbles two.
See, I took the first
mr. Nibbles home with me
One weekend,
and I forgot to shut the door
To the room where I was keeping him.
Turns out, my cat was able
to knock the top off his cage.
Long story short,
I spent most of my Sunday
Driving from pet store to pet store
Looking for a mr. Nibbles look-alike.
These things happen, Bridgette.
You probably shouldn't
have given miss Scarlet
A piece of candy,
but you can't even be sure
That that's what made her die.
Bridgette, what is it?
Are you okay?
She's got her sweatshirt like that
So the tarantula can't
get into her mouth.
You still sore?
Yeah. No.
You know what's weird?
Why don't we talk about
what isn't weird, huh?
That would be a much shorter conversation.
You know that man... the one
who owned the funeral home,
The man who was killed?
His daughter came into work today,
And she had the exact same cuts I have.
What do you mean?
I mean, exactly the same...
the same place, same everything.
Maybe she ran into
the same zombie you did.
They were exactly the same.
That can't be a coincidence, can it?
I don't know, Al.
And I'm happy to keep talking about it
For as long as you like,
but keep in mind,
You're cutting into
your first sleep shift.
Remember, you got to be up
to relieve me in three hours.
If I even snore weird,
you're gonna wake me up, right?
You go to sleep.
I got it covered.
I'm not going to let
anything happen to you.
No! No! No!
Joe, if you can hear me,
I'd really like to wake up now.
Joe!
Let us in!
Please! Dad's hurt.
You have to let us in.
Can you hear me?
You have to help us!
You promised !
No, I can't!
Please. I'm out of bullets.
For the love of god, let us in!
No!
No. I have to protect myself.
If I let you in, you might kill me.
I can't let myself die in a dream!
Let us in, please?
No, I can't.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, I don't want to die.
I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
I don't to die.
I don't want to die.
Allison.
I don't want to... die!
Easy.
It's okay. You're awake.
You're safe.
Hey, Al, it was just a dream,
that's all it was.
Okay? Nothing scratched you,
nothing bit you.
You're fine.
I know, you're right.
It's your turn.
This one is nice and fresh,
But if this was all brown,
you just simply want to...
And that's his first two.
Devon Gray, and there's...
...Harriet Banks are the lucky winners
Of this past weekend's
super lottery draw.
The pair came forward to claim
their $11 million prize...
Hello?
Careful. That's hot.
You already know that, don't you?
Why are you pointing that thing at me?
I'm not one of them.
We know exactly who you are, Barbara.
My name is not Barbara.
It's Allison.
Don't bother lying.
We already found
your lab over that hill.
We know all about the concoction
You cooked up in your tanks, Barbara.
What are you talking about?
We know that everything
that happened here
Last night was your fault.
I've never seen these things before.
Look.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What lab, what concoction?
You made all those people sick, Barbara.
You poisoned them.
No, you're wrong.
You know what?
I'm glad I was the one who found you.
No, where am I going?!
The pentagon wants us to keep
a few of the specimens alive.
Given their ravenous appetites,
I was worried the creatures
wouldn't make it
All the way to Washington.
I guess it's good we found them a snack.
No!
Get that door.
No.
No, please!
Let me out!
Please.
Hey, you never woke me.
I fell asleep.
And?
It was horrible.
I guess I survived it, though.
Scanlon and Devalos were there.
Really?
Any sign of the tin
man or the scarecrow?
They kept calling me Barbara,
and they said I was
responsible for all of it
And then they threw me
in the back of this truck,
And you were there and the girls.
Wait a second, I thought you said
that we were all dead.
You all ate me,
all of you feasted on me.
You don't look any worse for wear.
Seriously, wasn't this
exactly the kind of dream
That we were worried about?
I mean, if we did actually, you know,
Eat you in this dream,
It's pretty safe to
assume that you were dead
If not when the meal started,
Certainly by the time it ended.
You're not dreaming now and
you look pretty lively to me.
I guess you're right.
It's usually a series of four
treatment sessions to reduce...
What is that?
I guess I did sustain
an injury in that dream.
When I touched something hot,
it burned me.
Oh, god.
I guess if you dreamt
about being eaten alive
By the reanimated corpses
of your dead family,
And that's the only
wound you got, I guess
You could consider yourself lucky.
I'm sorry.
No one was in front, so I just
made my way around the back.
Oh, it's okay, mrs. Dubois.
What can I do for you?
I brought by your father's
personal effects.
I read in the paper that
the viewing was tomorrow,
and I wanted to make sure
that you had everything
you needed... his watch,
His wedding band.
You're very thoughtful.
Actually, our embalmer Steven's
On his way over with daddy's remains.
I was just getting... The room ready.
You all right?
Oh, I'm sorry, it's just...
Daddy always used to say,
"death never takes
the wise man by surprise ;
He is always ready to go or to let go."
I guess I'm not feeling
terribly wise right now.
Shoot.
Do you happen to have a pen?
If you wouldn't mind
signing this receipt
that you received your
father's personal effects...
Could you just give me one
moment to empty the autoclave?
I was just cleaning some instruments
For Steven.
Excuse me, what are those ?
Those?
They're the embalming tanks.
They hold the fluid the embalmer uses
to replace the blood in the dead body.
Ethanol, methanol,
Formaldehyde.
Sorry.
Burned myself.
Bobbi?
That wouldn't happen to be short
for Barbara, would it?
As a matter of fact, it is.
How did you know?
Okay, if you have something to tell me,
You're going to have
to figure out a way to tell me.
Miss Scarlet,
I'm serious.
Oh, eggs.
Thank you again for coming in,
ms. Catalano.
I realize how busy you must be
during this difficult time,
So I'll get right to the point.
There have been some recent developments
In the investigation into
your father's murder.
We now have reason to believe
that he bit his attacker
Before he died.
Really?
All right.
Well, forgive me, mr. Devalos,
But I don't see
how that really qualifies
As a new development.
I don't want to hear all the gory details
About the fight between
my father and that man.
That's the thing.
That man Edgar Kripke...
He doesn't have any bite
marks anywhere on his person,
And as a result,
we're no longer convinced
He's the one who murdered your father.
I don't understand.
He had my father's watch,
he had my father's wallet.
They had argued several times.
Edgar Kripke is an unmedicated
paranoid schizophrenic.
He argued with many people many times.
He never hurt anyone.
Now, as for your father's possessions,
If Kripke was the first person
to find the body,
Maybe he stole them
Or maybe they were planted.
Planted, really?
Who would have wanted
to do that and why?
We're not entirely sure,
But now that Kripke's
guilt is in question
And because there are no other suspects,
We are going to reopen the investigation.
If that's what you need to do...
Typically,
We begin with the last person
who saw the victim alive
So we can rule them out as a suspect.
In this case that person is you.
So, if you don't mind,
We'd like you to submit yourself
To a brief physical examination.
If the female officer doesn't
find any bite marks on you,
Then we can refocus our energy elsewhere.
You're joking.
I beg your pardon?
I loved my father.
I would never hurt him.
If he knew how you were treating
A member of his family,
After everything that he has
done for this department...
Are you aware that your business
has taken out
No less than five separate loans
From the bank over the past few years?
Do you read the papers, mr. Detective?
The economy is not what it used to be.
And yes, people are still dying,
But their survivors are
not spending the money.
Now, what is your point?
I also called a few of your suppliers.
If business is down,
Maybe you could explain to me why,
over the past year or so,
You ordered three times
more embalming fluid
Than in previous years.
Are you aware that
embalming fluid is a mixture
Of ethanol, methanol, and formaldehyde...
The ingredients in the drug wet?
I did not know that.
We've been curious how
our local drug dealers
Have been able to put
so much out on the street.
You care to venture any theories
I wouldn't know where to begin.
Your father figured out
what you were doing.
He confronted you.
There was a struggle.
He bit you
On your right calf.
I, for one, appreciate
everything your father did
To help the men and women
that serve this city.
That's why, provided
you enter a guilty plea
And make a full confession,
I'm prepared to discuss a deal
With whoever you hire to represent you,
Or if you insist on
doing it the hard way,
I'll simply have detective
Scanlon here arrest you,
And once your calf has been
examined for a bite mark,
Well, then... Then your fate will lie
In the hands of the jury.
He asked me to meet him
at my mother's grave.
And he told me that
he knew everything.
He said my mama
Would have been ashamed of me.
Those are all eggs ?
Yep.
Did you know that a tarantula can lay
Up to 2,000 eggs at a time?
They're not going
To hatch here, are they?
No, probably not.
I called miss Colletto
as soon as I found them,
And she says that she's going
To take 'em to the pet store tomorrow
And make sure they all get good homes.
It's what miss Scarlet
would have wanted.
You two ready
for a little trick-or-treating?
Okay, you're a witch,
I get that, but dad,
What are you supposed to be?
I'm a nerd.
Ariel, honey,
we're going to see you later.
We're taking off.
Hold on!
It was from right over there.
Just promise me we won't go anywhere
Where we might see someone I know.
We'll try not to.
Hey, are those my boots?
Did anyone remember
to turn off the tv?
You used to really get scared here.
You're still afraid.
Stop it now, I mean it.
They're coming to get you, Allison.
Stop it, you're ig...
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
Yeah, that's what I thought you said.
forom.com