Al? Hey, Allison?
Are you hearing this?
Ariel?
What the...?!
Whose baby is that?
And where's Ariel?
Joe, keep your voice down.
Where's our daughter?
She's right here.
Ariel's right here.
Oh, Joe.
My God, Joe, it's Bridgette and Marie.
It can't be.
How is that possible?
Allison.
Come on, Al, help me make sense of this.
I think maybe it's my fault.
I've been wishing for it secretly.
Okay. I get it.
You're upset. But don't you think
you're being a little bit immature?
So, listen...
What do you think about
having another baby?
S06E05
Baby Fever
forom.com
Bridgette!
That's nice.
She's practicing.
Make it stop!
I'm begging you to make it stop.
Hey, she's your sister,
she's been at this all of two weeks,
and this is important to her.
What she really needs
is your encouragement.
And she's got it.
I'm encouraging her to stop.
Great.
I was just getting the hang of it,
and the reed breaks.
Bridge, okay, come over here.
We'll get you another one.
Have some breakfast.
That really stinks.
I wanted Mommy to hear me play.
Don't worry about it.
Mommy isn't even here.
She got a ride with
Detective Scanlon this morning.
Do me a favor. Go get dressed.
I'll make you something
to eat in the car.
And you promise that we'll go down
to the music shop
and get me a new reed right after school?
Absolutely, I promise.
Oh, Lee,
she's so beautiful.
Thanks.
So, how's Lynn adjusting?
There was no adjusting. It was instant.
The second little Lee came
into the world, bam, she was a mom.
What is it with you women and kids?
It's like a drug.
It is pretty amazing.
I woke up this morning convinced
that I had to have another one.
Oh, I don't know what came over mere.
What did Joe have to say about that?
Nothing. He pretended he was asleep.
Yeah. Well, it's different for guys.
It's an adjustment.
A great adjustment ;
a fantastic adjustment;
but an adjustment.
Tomorrow night's date night.
I finally convinced her to get a sitter,
leave little Lee for a couple hours.
Ooh! Big step.
Are you excited?
I'm excited. She's terrified.
Detective, advise your 20.
I've got a Code Two in Fountain Hills.
So you woke up... what time?
6:45, give or take?
The baby's just gone?
Housekeeper's just vanished?
He's not in the nursery,
she's not in her room.
Her room? She has a room?
She stays here five nights a week
in case the baby fusses
or wakes up during the night.
And his name is Bryce?
Bryce, yes.
And that's a very recent photo-
last weekend.
Here's a picture of Elizabeth.
The housekeeper.
You said her last name was Torres.
Yes.
And during the night,
you didn't hear anything?
The baby didn't cry or anything, so,
you have no idea what time this happened?
No.
How about your wife?
Did she hear anything?
Obviously, no.
So, is this it?
Is it just you two?
A forensic team and some more
detectives are on their way.
We'll get these to every media
outlet in the area.
We'll get a description of the car
up on Amber Alert.
Can I speak with Mrs. Carlo?
Of course.
She was just... putting on some clothes.
She'll be... She'll be down in a minute.
Is the nursery upstairs?
Yes.
Do you mind if I take a look?
I'll be up in a bit.
I'm gonna talk to the mother,
and I want to be here when
the rest of the cavalry shows up.
Should I not be in here?
I see you're wearing gloves.
I shouldn't be in here, right?
I might ruin some clues or something?
Mrs. Carlo?
Dana.
You're with the police?
My name is Allison.
I'm with the District Attorney's Office.
We're gonna find him.
Wherever she went, wherever she took him,
w- we're gonna find him.
I'm not worried.
I mean, of course I'm worried, but...
I also know that there's
no one on the planet
that loves Bryce as much as I do,
except Elizabeth.
She worships him.
She lives for him, and that's how I know.
That's how I know he's okay.
But you do believe that she took him?
Well, maybe she did,
and maybe she didn't.
I mean, maybe this is all a dream,
a nightmare.
In a little while, I'll wake up,
and Elizabeth will be downstairs
holding Bryce,
and we'll sing songs and play games,
and it'll just be another day.
What do you think the chances are that
this address for Elizabeth Torres is good?
That we knock on the door, she opens it?
That the baby's there,
asleep peacefully in a laundry basket?
Ms. Torres, it's the police.
If you don't open up on
the count of three, we're coming in.
One...
two... three.
Okay, home before lunch.
Nice work if you can get it.
Allison, you okay?
Yeah.
No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
It's that little baby.
I can't get it out of my head.
Don't worry.
You know, something's got to give.
There's got to be a ransom demand.
Someone will spot this Elizabeth.
Something will break. It always does.
Hello.
Hi. You're at home?
I- I called your office,
I called your cell.
It's a long story.
Are you okay? You sound upset.
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
Nothing. I don't hear it now.
Hey, listen,
what music store did
you rent Bridgette's clarinet from?
I promised her that I'd get her
a new reed on the way home from school.
Marshall's. I got it at Marshall's.
There it is again. Do you hear it?
No.
Marshall's, huh?
Allison, are you all right?
Allison?
Yeah. Honey, I'm fine.
I'll see you when you get home.
Baby?
Shh, I'm here now, honey.
What do you want, honey?
Something you want in the garage?
It's the car.
You wanted to be in the car?
Oh, my God, I'm talking to a picture.
You want to go for a ride, don't you?
Okay.
Wait right here,
I'm gonna get my purse and my keys.
Bridge, what are you doing?
Put that back!
Don't play with that.
- That's not yours.
- Okay.
Come on, help me find a reed.
Okay, what size are we looking for?
One, one and a half?
She with you two?
How long has she been playing?
What are you talking about?
She can't play.
Which house is it?
What, did I pass it?
Hello?
Hello, is anybody home?
I hope you know what
you're getting us into.
Hello?
Is anybody home?
I'm with the District Attorney's Office.
I'd like to ask you
some questions about a missing baby.
What is it now?
Baby?
Keep crying, I'm gonna find you,
I'm here!
It's you, Bryce, isn't it?
Come on, you gotta tell me
how you did that.
I don't know how I did it.
Just leave me alone.
Okay, one half hour
of TV then homework, okay?
Hi, I gotta talk to you.
I need to talk to you, too.
Okay, you first.
No, no, no. You go. What's going on?
Okay, I took the kids to an early dinner,
like you suggested,
but something happened
in the music store.
Something that makes absolutely
no sense whatsoever.
Now I'm thinking maybe
you should go first.
What is that?
It's a baby!
Yeah, no, I sussed that part out.
What is it doing here?
Come on, little sweetie.
Oh, I don't even know
how to start explaining this.
Okay, well, any effort
you make will be much appreciated.
Right, well, the short version
is his name is Bryce Carlo.
His housekeeper kidnapped him
this morning and I found him.
Okay, and what?
We're, like, waiting
for the police to come get him?
Allison?
I haven't called the police.
Because...?
Because I'm not sure I'm supposed to.
Oh, okay, yeah,
I can help you with this.
You're supposed to.
No, you don't understand.
There's something about this little boy.
From the moment I heard that he was gone.
From the moment I saw his picture,
I knew I was supposed to look for him.
I was supposed to find him.
And now I think I'm supposed to keep him.
Allison, he has parents.
Yeah, I know, I met them.
But they're probably frantic.
Well, his father is concerned
but his mother is oddly calm.
What are you talking about, oddly calm?
She's probably in shock.
And what difference does that make?
It's her baby.
Just because you took him
from a kidnapper
doesn't make you any less of a kidnapper.
No, you're wrong!
You don't understand.
He's supposed to be here;
he's supposed to be with me.
Oh, look!
He's smiling! He knows I'm right!
He's smiling, that's your proof?
That's your answer, he's smiling?
He's a baby! They all smile.
That's standard equipment on a baby-
that's what they do.
Allison, people go to jail
for this for a very long time.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to protect you from yourself.
I'm gonna try and reach somebody-
a friend on the phone-
Scanlon or Devalos.
Somebody who can take this baby
back to its rightful parents.
- No!
- Hey, yes!
You already have children.
And they don't want to only
see you on visitor's day.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Sorry. I know I'm late,
but it was so hard to leave her.
She kept looking at me
like I was abandoning her.
I know it's tough,
but it's good practice for next week,
when you go back to work.
Okay, and I don't want
to think about that tonight.
A drink for madam?
Yeah. She will have a martini with...
No, no, no. Breastfeeding,
breastfeeding, breastfeeding.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
We will have a bottle
of your finest water.
Thank you.
So how'd she check out?
Sorry. Who?
The baby-sitter.
You were gonna run her license.
Lynn, she's 17. She's clean as a whistle.
- What are you doing?
- I'm texting her.
Baby's not used to getting
milk from a bottle from a stranger.
I just need to make sure
everything's going okay.
And would we like to hear
the specials for tonight?
Not me. I can't really eat anything.
What?
Well, I've got to get
this baby weight off.
Nothing fits me.
I hate the way I look.
You look fantastic,
and you have to eat something.
Could you give us a few minutes?
What are you doing?
She hasn't texted back.
You just texted her.
Besides, maybe she's taking
care of the baby.
She can't text you if
she's taking care of the baby.
And I also know that
the whole idea of tonight
is for the two of us
to have a good time,
to get your mind off the baby and relax.
All right?
What's going on?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I think I had my phone on vibrate.
Scanlon here.
Well, I'm just kind of
in the middle of something.
Yes, sir.
You got it.
I know that look.
The Carlo case-
there's been a breakthrough.
I'll see you at home ?
Yeah, I'll see you at home.
Obviously, the most important thing
is that Bryce is home safely.
We'll let you know more as it develops,
but that's all for now. Thank you.
It's okay. You did the right thing.
You know you did the right thing.
Okay, mission accomplished.
As far as the Carlos are concerned,
Allison led Lee to their son.
- Thanks.
I don't understand.
What was Bryce doing
in that strange house all alone ?
We don't know yet.
Yeah, the house is owned
by a woman named Maribella Gomez.
She freely admits that she's friends
with the housekeeper, Elizabeth Torres,
but has no idea what's going on.
She wasn't home when Elizabeth
came by to stash the baby.
Has no idea why she would have broken
into her house,
no idea where she is now.
Listen, Allison, if you're up to it,
the Carlos would like
to thank you personally.
I know it sounds crazy,
but if I can't hold him, protect him...
Maybe some other time.
Allison...
Oh, geez.
It's Bryce's.
I guess somehow we missed it.
Come on.
Give it to me.
Come on, I got to get rid of it.
And Allison, I'm not trying to be mean,
but that blanket is- it's evidence
that Bryce was here,
that he was in our house, so...
come on, I gotta have it.
I gotta burn it or something.
It's okay. I'll do it.
I will; I'll do it.
In the morning.
Oh, my goodness.
I am so thrilled that you stopped by.
I was so worried
I wouldn't get a chance to thank you.
I know I must have seemed
a little crazy yesterday,
talking about how much
I trusted Elizabeth,
even though she took my baby.
It's just,
sometimes things are so awful,
it's like your brain can't take them in.
No, I completely understand.
I can't imagine what I would do
if I woke up and one
of my babies was gone.
Well, speaking of which, where's Bryce?
I'd really love to see him.
I kind of miss that little guy.
Well, actually, you just missed him.
My husband Scott took him over to
his grandparents for a little while.
Oh, well, that's nice.
Maybe I could just hang out
till they get back.
well, that's probably Scott now.
Let me just see when
he plans on heading back.
Are you the lady
who brought my brother back?
I wish you hadn't done that.
He's not safe here.
I'm afraid Scott and Bryce
will be gone all... day.
it caught my eye.
That's Lucy.
She would've been six.
She fell ill last year
and died very suddenly.
I'm so sorry.
Be a year at Christmas.
I don't know if you heard me,
Scott and Bryce...
they'll be gone all day.
Well, give Bryce a- a hug for me.
And thank you for the tea.
No, thank you.
Thank you for everything.
Actually, Mrs. Lovett,
I wasn't calling about Bridgette.
I was calling about our six-year-old.
I was wondering if she could get
music lessons, too, you know?
Maybe we could- we could do them,
back-to-back or...?
You don't have any openings?
Oh, wow, that's too bad.
Could we
could we maybe get on a wait list or...?
She can have mine!
Sorry, hold on one second.
What's that, Bridge?
My lesson.
She can have it.
It's at 4:00 tomorrow.
I don't want it.
But that's your lesson, Bridge.
I... don't... want it.
She can have it!
Go away. I'm busy.
Sorry, coming in anyway.
Hi.
Look, I know you got homework,
but you have to clear
something up for me.
I thought I heard you say
you wanted to quit clarinet.
Yeah, so, what's the difference?
I stink at it, anyways.
What are you talking about?
You've only been at it for two weeks.
Yeah, and Marie's been playing for,
like, two minutes.
And she's already great.
Come on, you can't do that.
You can't compare yourself to Marie.
I mean, I don't know what
is going on there,
but that girl clearly has
a special aptitude for the clarinet.
But I don't.
you are already one of the most
special people in the whole wide world.
Really. Now, anybody who knows
you would say that.
No, you're wrong.
Nobody's ever said that.
Except you.
Just now.
And only because you're my Dad.
I don't believe that.
Yeah, well, it's true.
You know who I am?
I'm everybody's sister.
That's not true.
Yeah? Well, I'm Ariel's sister,
because she's smart and she's pretty,
and everybody likes her.
And she knows about
clothes and-and boys and dancing.
And... now, I guess
I'm Marie's sister, too.
'Cause she can play clarinet
without even trying.
Come here.
No, it absolutely it just broke
my heart, you know.
She just seemed so defeated by it.
Do you hear me?
Allison?
Hey, Allison?
I'm sorry, were you talking to me?
Where are you ?
What are you so busy thinking about?
Look, don't be mad.
I went to see him today.
I brought him his blanket.
I can't believe I'm hearing this.
I'm trying to talk to you
about your own child.
He had a sister.
Had.
She died a few months ago.
She said that Bryce
wasn't safe in that house.
That I shouldn't have
brought him back there.
What, the dead sister told you this?
Look, I checked her death records.
It said "unexplained illnesses,
natural causes. "
Apparently, they took her
to expert after expert.
No one could really put
their finger on it.
What are you saying?
Well, I'm saying something's
wrong in that house.
The sister said that Bryce
wasn't safe there.
The mother said the housekeeper
lived for him.
So, I'm starting to think
maybe she didn't kidnap him at all,
maybe she was trying to protect him.
Maybe someone or something
in that house killed the sister,
and now it's trying to harm Bryce.
What are you doing?
I can't do this.
I can't spend another
ounce of energy on this thing.
I spent last night running
all over hell's half acre.
- Hey, you asked me what was in my head.
- The little boy is home safe
- I'm telling you what's in my head.
- with his parents.
Our little girl is beside
herself in her room.
- Joe?
- Yeah? What?
You have a dream ?
What's going on, Allison?
That, do you hear that?
What? Hear what?
I listened for- Oh, Allison,
look, it's almost 1:30 in the morning.
No, that, that. That baby crying.
What are you -  there's no baby crying.
What are you talking about?
We don't have a baby.
It's him. It's Bryce.
He needs me. I'm going over there.
Going where?
To the Carlos'.
I need to make sure he's okay.
Hey! Are you listening to yourself?
It's the middle of the night.
I don't care! He's in trouble.
He needs me.
For crap's sake.
Help you?
Mr. Carlo...
We met the other day.
I was with Detective Scanlon.
This is my husband Joe.
Look, I know it's
the middle of the night;
I know this is really unusual,
but I was wondering
if I could just look in on Bryce.
Allison.
What going on?
What are you doing here?
This...
this... hard to explain.
I just- I need to see Bryce.
I need to know that he's okay.
Why wouldn't he be okay?
Oh, no, no.
Did we do that? The doorbell?
No, no, this is pretty much
par for the course.
Well, as long as that's the case.
I mean, if he's up,
is there any way that I can just see him?
Oh, he's such a beautiful boy.
Your little girl never got to meet him,
did she?
I got pregnant just before she passed.
I know Scott was worried
that I was so filled with grief
that I might lose him.
I can't imagine what
it would be like to go through that.
Well, the hardest part
was never getting any answers.
Never knowing what was wrong.
I mean, the only thing
everyone seemed to agree
on was that she was dying.
Did you ever consider getting an autopsy,
so you would know why?
Allison.
Lucy suffered too much.
We couldn't put her through that, too.
And, ultimately, an autopsy would've
just been for our benefit, not hers.
We just wanted her to rest in peace.
I just don't understand
why they wouldn't get an autopsy.
I mean, if one of our girls died...?
Allison, you have to stop.
That family opened their door
to us at 3:00 in the morning.
They're not evil.
If anything, they're saints.
Okay, I'm not saying they're not nice,
I just - I think it's strange... Strange?
Strange?
You want to talk about strange?
Look, I hate to break it to you,
but the only thing strange
about that house tonight
was the fact that we were in it.
Now, you have to leave that family alone.
I mean it.
Go away. I'm tired.
Yeah, well, too bad.
It's time to get up.
Well, I haven't even been to sleep yet.
What are you talking about?
It's morning.
You've been asleep all night.
Not really. I've been dreaming.
Dreaming about that stupid song.
What are you talking about?
You dream that song?
There's this old man and he
has a clarinet.
And all he does is play
that song over and over again.
Showed me how to do it.
I hate it.
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
Why are you even telling me all this?
Because you're my big sister.
Allison.
Sir, I was wanting to ask you
about Bryce Carlo.
When you brought him in,
did anyone run any blood work,
anything that could test
for toxins in his system?
Sure.
Blood tests are fairly routine
in child abduction cases.
We look for sedatives, tranquilizers.
The good news is, in Bryce's case,
everything came back completely normal.
Devalos.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
That was the morgue.
Seems a sanitation worker found a
corpse stuffed
in an abandoned refrigerator
in one of our municipal
landfills early this morning.
Matches the description of our missing
kidnapper, Elizabeth Torres.
Yes.
That's her.
That's my cousin.
Thank you for coming down
and making the identification.
I may have a few more questions.
If want to just wait outside?
M.E.'s calling cause of death
blunt-force trauma.
Looks like she took a couple
of hard blows to the head.
Hard enough to kill her.
Doesn't make a lot of sense.
This woman takes a baby boy,
you find the baby boy,
then someone kills the kidnapper?
Something's missing.
Like what?
To begin with, I still can't figure out
why this woman took that child,
only to abandon him
at the house where Allison found him.
Might make sense to have
forensics go back,
see if they can find any
of this woman's blood.
All right, girls.
Hey, girls, come on.
It's time to leave
for Marie's music lesson.
Hey, Dad?
Yeah.
Marie wanted me to tell you that
she doesn't want to go to her lesson.
What?! Why?
All right, sweetheart.
All good?
Okay, come on.
She okay?
Well, not yet, but eventually.
This is one of those things, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
This definitely appears
to be one of those things.
So, how do we fix it?
How do we make her stop
hearing that song?
I don't know, Bridge.
I honestly I don't know.
From my experience with mom
and with Ariel and even with you,
it's best to just let
these things run their course.
Hello?
Allison, I hope I didn't wake you.
I just called to let you know
that the police went back out to that
house where you found the Carlo boy.
They actually found a small spot of
blood on the underside of a doorknob.
The blood matched some blood that
we found on Elizabeth Torres's body-
blood that wasn't hers.
So, while we don't yet have a suspect,
the good news is, once we do,
we have enough forensic evidence
to nail him for murder.
Anyway, I'm...
I'm going to go home, go to bed.
You do that, sir.
Allison.
It's 1:00 a. m.
I know, I know.
I'm sorry to have wake you and Scott.
Scott's not here.
He's out of town on business.
Look, I'm sorry, Dana.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You're a nice person.
I need you to understand
everything that I am doing,
I am doing for Bryce.
What-what are you talking about?
What are you doing for Bryce?
I hope you're not going
to ask to see him again.
No, I don't need to just see him.
I need to take him.
Bryce needs to be with me!
Okay, Allison, you need to leave.
I'm serious.
You're not welcome here.
Bryce isn't going to be with you.
That's just never going to happen.
Hi. Hello.
Hey, it's me. I'm fine.
You're fine ? You're fine?
Allison, I'm calling you,
like, 35 times.
Did you turn off your cell phone?
I had to throw it away.
I knew they were going
to use it to try to track me down.
Look, I just want you to know
that I'm safe.
I can't tell you where we are,
but we're safe.
But you're not.
The whole state of Arizona
is looking for you.
They got AMBER alerts and APBs.
I beg you, turn yourself in.
Now!
If we're lucky,
all they're charge you with is assault.
I can't.
I can't explain it.
It's just... I know.
For now he's supposed to be with me.
But he's not.
Allison, please, tell me where you are.
Tell me at least you have a plan.
There's no plan.
He had to sleep, eat.
I need to sleep. Honey,
I have to get off the phone.
I know that they're probably
tracing our home number.
I love you. I love the girls.
I'll see you soon.
Mirabella !
It's Elizabeth.
Please. I'm in trouble.
I need help.
Mirabella? ?stas en casa?
?ola?
Elizabeth?
I know you're here !
- Elizabeth?
- Primo !
Primo, what are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
You know exactly what I'm doing here.
You think you could just
cut me out of my own plan?
No.
No, you're wrong. I would never...
You would never what?
What, you never what?
No, no, I did everything you asked.
I gave you the alarm code.
I took pictures.
Yes, you were a good cousin.
You did everything you were supposed to.
Maybe too much.
No.
- Yes.
- No.
Yes. How else do you explain it?
This morning when Martin and I
were supposed to kidnap the baby,
we find out he's already gone.
- Alberto...
- And then the TV.
They're saying the person
who took it was you.
I want that baby !
I'm sorry, Alberto, he's not here.
I don't have him anymore.
I gave him to Mirabella.
She's gone to the police.
She's going to tell them everything.
You're lying !
No !
It's the truth.
I don't lie.
Not like you lied to me.
Martin told me
he told me you were never going
to give that baby back,
even if they paid the ransom.
That you were going to sell him
for hundreds of thousands of dollars.
I could never be a part of that.
You cannot really be my cousin.
You are not even human.
Ma'am, you're under arrest.
I'm gonna need you to put your hands
on your head and surrender the child.
I'm so sorry that I sprayed you
in the eyes.
I just had a conversation
with the man you work for-
the district attorney.
He explained to me that I have
every right to prosecute you
for kidnapping Bryce, assaulting me.
Every right to send you
to prison for a very long time.
But...
...he also confessed
that he thought that would be
a huge mistake.
And then he talked to me
about you and your dreams.
He told me it was a dream of yours
that led police
to the man who killed our nanny.
That once they brought him in,
he confessed.
He told them that after you had brought
Bryce back to me and Scott,
Alberto and his partner realized
they still had the alarm code.
They still had everything they needed
to go through with the kidnapping.
They even had my husband's
travel schedule,
which is why last night,
shortly after you assaulted me
and took my son,
they came to my house.
Oh, my God.
If you hadn't taken Bryce,
it appears they would have.
They-They pulled up to our house
and found police cars in our driveway.
Police cars that were
there because of you, Mrs. Dubois;
because you'd taken my little boy.
Now maybe it was just a coincidence,
but I prefer to believe this...
this thing you have,
this gift...
it forced you to keep Bryce safe.
And that's what I prefer to believe.
You're not going to prosecute me?
I told your boss that my memory
of last night is faulty.
I'm not comfortable testifying
about what happened.
Oh, thank you.
Stay away from my house, Allison.
Stay away from my family.
If-If I ever see you again,
my memory may very well improve,
do you understand?
I understand.
But it's not going to be a problem.
I was there when Bryce needed me.
But I think for the rest of his life,
one mother is plenty.
Excuse me.
Can u tell me the name of that song?
It doesn't have a name, actually.
I wrote it.
Well, me and my dad anyway.
I'm Mr. Bronson, by the way.
And who are you?
Bridgette Dubois.
Nice to meet you, Bridgette Dubois.
Yeah, this song doesn't have a name-
'cause it doesn't have an ending.
We never finished it.
I was working on it
with my father when he...
he passed away suddenly.
Wait right here.
I think I know someone
you're gonna want to meet.