Season 13 Episode 3
"Margaritaville"
Do I really have to do this, dad?
Now more than ever
you need to understand
the importance of saving money.
But grandma said I could use
this money to buy whatever I want.
OK, next, please.
Go on, Stanley.
- How can I help you, young man?
- I got $100 check from my grandma.
And my dad said I need to put it in
the bank so it can grow over the years.
Well, that's fantastic.
A really smart decision, young man.
We can put that check in
a money market mutual fund,
then we'll reinvest the earnings
into foreign currency accounts
with come can pounding
interest and it's gone!
- What?
- It's gone. It's all gone.
- What's all gone?
- The money in your account.
It didn't do too well. It's gone.
- What do you mean? I have $100.
- Not anymore, you don't. Poof!
What can I do to get back my...
I'm sorry, sir, but this line
is for bank members only.
I just opened an account!
Do you have any money
invested with this bank?
No, you just lost it all.
Then please stand aside for people
who actually have money with us.
Next, please.
Hello, Mrs. Farnickle.
How are you today?
Making a deposit, are we?
Great. We can just put that
into your retirement account
and make it go to work
for you and it's gone.
- What?
- Sorry, That's gone. Please step aside
for people who actually
have money with the bank. Next, please.
Dad!
I'm trying to teach my son
the importance of savings.
- You already lost his money?
- Oh, Mr. Marsh! Don't worry.
We can just transfer money
from your account and into a portfolio
with your son's... and it's gone!
This line is for people
who have money with the bank only.
Please step aside.
This is a 9 News special report.
Recession: a nation in peril.
An economic crisis has hit South Park
and the nation like never before.
Another South Park bank closed down,
leaving thousands of people in debt.
It's just crazy, you know?
Everyone's affected by it.
It's like all
the money just vanished.
It's really terrifying. We've got
no money to pay our mortgage now.
- We could very easily lose our house.
- Hi, grandma!
First, the money started going and
now everyone's getting laid off work.
They took our jobs!
- They took our jobs!
- Took our jobs!
Just how far will the economy fall?
We asked economic reporter
Dan Banks for his assessment.
We'll have the rest of Dan's
interview tonight at 10:00.
All right, everyone, eat up.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Sliced hot dogs and tomato slices?
You said we had to be
careful with our money.
I've got nothing for a food budget!
Mom, dad, how come there's
suddenly no money?
I'll tell you what happened, son.
There's a bunch of idiot s out there
who weren't happy with what they had.
They wanted a bigger
house and materialistic
things that they didn't even need.
People with no money
who got loans to buy
frivolous things
they had no business buying.
These assholes just blindly
started buying any stupid thing
that looked appealing because
they thought money was endless.
... meaning less money coming in.
And the idiots couldn't see
that by doing all this
frivolous spending they were
mocking the economy.
And they made
the economy very angry.
We're all feeling
the economy's vengeance
because of materialistic heathens
who did stupid things with their money.
Do you understand, son?
Yeah. I think I get it.
And so why is
our economy failing us?
Because the government
kept interest rates
too low for too long!
The government took
our economy for granted
and now we are
all here paying the price!
How long will we sit and watch
our economy fall...
And so I say to you, do not listen
to the Wall Street brokers, for they...
are the ones who
put us in this situation!
Fat cats with corporate greed.
They are the ones who knowingly
drove us down this pathway of doom.
It must have gone somewhere!
The answer is obvious,
my friends. It is the Jews!
Covetous Jews, who have taken all our
money and hoarded it for themselves!
Hidden all the cash in some
secret Jew cave that they built,
probably back in the early '60s.
It is the Jews...
... people casting all different kinds
of blame from person to person.
But the fault lies in all of you.
You! Who bought that $300,000 house
when you only had
$20,000 to put down. You!
Who bought that third car even though
only two people in your home drive.
It is time to stop pointing fingers.
Finger-pointing
gets us nowhere. Steve!
We have mocked our economy
and now the economy has
cast its vengeance upon us all.
He's right.
This is the first guy
to actually make sense.
Yeah, it is an angry
and unforgiving economy.
To repent we must stop
frivolous spending.
Instead of paying for cable,
let us watch clouds!
Instead of buying clothes,
wear but sheets from thine beds!
Cut spending to only
the bare essentials...
Water and bread.
And margaritas, yeah!
Hello, young man. Welcome to
Sur La Table. Can I help you?
I wanna return this Margaritaville
my stupid dad bought.
Oh, that's all
we get anymore, returns.
Could you please put
the receipt here on this table?
Sorry, our computers are slow today.
We need a new Ethernet cable.
I'm sorry, sir. I'd like to give you
a refund, but I'm afraid
it's not doable.
- What?
- I said I'm not able, sir.
You see, this Margaritaville
was purchased with a payment plan.
So?
Well, an outside financing company
handles those payment plans.
Customers just pay
for some of the machine
and the finance company
pays for the rest.
Can't I just return it and get
the money my dad put in back?
That's improbable,
but not impossible.
I'm not really sure how it works.
You'll have to speak
with the people at the top.
I can give you the finance company's
address if that's agreeable with you.
We have become lovers of pleasure,
rather than lovers of the economy.
There are those who will say
that the economy has forsaken us.
Nay! You hath forsaken the economy!
And now you know
the economy's wrath.
Oh, thoust can shop
in a sporting goods store,
but knowest thou that the economy
will take away
thy broncos cap from thy head.
You mocked the economy without fear.
Thine own stockbrokers...
now lie dead by their own hand.
And thou knowest that thy
stockbrokers did not fear the economy!
Well, here we are, my friends.
You have brought the economy's
vengeance upon yourselves.
- What can we do, Randy?
- Yes, tell us!
- Tell us what to do!
- Tell us, Randy, what we should do!
We must all wear sheets instead of
buying clothes that need detergent.
Instead of cars that take gasoline,
we can get around
on lamas from Drakes Farm.
Instead of video games
that take batteries and software,
our kids will play with squirrels!
We must let the economy know
that we are capable of respecting it.
No more needless spending!
The economy is our shepherd.
We shalt not want!
- Morning, Ted.
- Morning, Al.
Well, this sucks.
Sure was better when
our parents were buying us stuff.
Of all the times for people
to decide to stop buying things,
it had to be the week that
GTA4 comes out for Nintendo DS!
You want something
new every week, fat ass.
Don't you fraternize me!
- This is all your fault, you know.
- My fault?
The Jews took all
the money away and they...
Don't even start!
Don't even start, Cartman!
Well, why are we wearing bed sheets
and playing with squirrels, Kyle?
Not because of the Jews, Butters!
Who told you that?
Well, Eric did!
Just tell us where
the cave is, Kyle.
Now, look!
The reason we're in this situation
is because people are being stupid!
The economy isn't some vengeful
being that takes things away from us.
The economy is just
made up of people.
And people have just
lost their faith in it.
What people really should
be doing is spending more.
Spending is fine!
We best speak with the council.
Tell them a young Jew is speaking
heresy towards the economy.
- Can I help you?
- I want to return this Margaritaville.
OK. Let me send you into Josh.
Hey, welcome to Big Orange
finance company!
Yeah, have a seat.
You want some Carmex?
No thanks.
I want to return this Margaritaville
and the guy at Sur La Table said
you are the company that financed it.
Oh, yeah. No. You know what?
- No, yeah.
- What?
Yeah, we can't give you
your money back for that. Yeah, no.
You'd have to talk to
the people on Wall Street. Yeah.
Wall Street?
Yeah, no, see what
I do is find Americans
who want a frozen beverage
machine but can't afford one.
And I hook them up with investors
who want to get into the Margaritaville
payment plan business, yeah.
So?
So the problem is your Margaritaville
payment plan has been combined,
with thousands of others into
one big Margaritaville security.
Yeah, no.
Yeah. No, yeah.
The entire town has given over
to your ways, Mr. Chairman.
Everyone has even
stopped using electricity
so as to stop
paying electrical bills.
You've really done
an amazing thing, Mr. Marsh.
People have learned
to hold on to their money
so as to not feel the sting
of the economy's mighty sword.
I am pretty smart, yeah.
But I have assembled
this economic committee
to make sure everyone
sticks to my new plan.
We've got guards posted
at the malls to make sure nobody
gets tempted to buy dumb stuff.
And Pat Saltzman
is doing house checks
to make sure nobody's
ordering anything stupid online.
Then perhaps soon
our economy will return to us.
Council, I bring news of discord!
A young Jew was in the town square
speaking blasphemy
about the economy.
- What?
- He was saying that
your ideas are false
and the economy is not vengeful!
He was rallying
people to spend more!
Spend more? What mockery is this?
Relax, Father Maxi.
What harm can
one Jew do against our...
economic recovery movement?
I had a dream last night.
I was in a field,
and I had GTA: Chinatown Wars
right next to me.
But then the sky went black and...
GTA: Chinatown Wars
just melted in my hands.
What's that?
Excuse me. We need
to borrow your squirrels!
- What?
- No! No, please!
You have sinned!
- Oh, Jesus, I'm sorry. Please!
- What's going on?
Garrison, you have brought your filth
to this town for the last time!
What did he do?
Your teacher was buying a kitchen aid
stand mixer at Bed Bath & Beyond.
Take thy punishment, heathen!
Hey, stop it! Stop!
Move aside, kid. He must
pay for his stand mixer.
Come on, this is ridiculous!
What's ridiculous
about hucking squirrels at a man
- who has angered the economy?
- Just have a little compassion, huh?
Everyone's gone out and bought
something stupid. It's not so bad.
Whichever of you guys has never
bought anything frivolous, go ahead
and huck the next squirrel.
Excuse me? Excuse me!
I'd like to return
this Margaritaville, please.
Margaritaville?
My dad bought it on a payment plan
that was set up by a finance company,
which got their principal
investors from somebody here.
- Oh, that makes sense.
- It does?
You see, son,
we lump thousands of these
Margaritaville
installment plans together
into Margaritaville
based securities,
then chopped those securities up in
a way that we could sell them to banks.
So I can return it to a bank?
Nope. Because people like you
are defaulting on their Margaritavilles
so the government had to buy the
Margaritaville assets from the banks.
What?
Just talk to the treasury
department. In D.C.
They're the ones who really
understand how all this works.
Oh, sell, sell, sell, sell!
Listen, this is
all you need to know.
The economy is not
a supernatural all-knowing entity.
The economy is just an idea
made up by people
thousands of years ago.
The economy is not real.
And yet, it is real.
Nowadays, they'll give credit cards to
practically anyone who applies for them.
I applied for this
yesterday to prove a point.
It is an American Express
platinum card.
It has no spending limit.
Do not be afraid!
This is only plastic.
It's just something
made up by people.
Truly meaningless
until we put our faith in it.
Faith is what makes
an economy exist.
Without faith, it is only
plastic cards and paper money.
By all reports, the young Jew
is not letting up.
He is still going around
convincing people to have
faith in the economy by shopping.
We've done everything we can
and yet the economy has not improved.
Worse, it has declined.
Poor Bart here just lost his
job at Little Caesar's pizza.
Our tireless work is obviously
being undermined by this one Jew.
Why does he go around pretending
to know the true will of the economy?
Perhaps he is the economy's
only son, sent to save us.
Are you retarded, Stotch!
The economy is omnipotent.
Which means it can do anything.
So saying it would be limited
to one son is fucking stupid!
That is stupid, yeah.
And going around telling
people to shop is dangerous.
Well, then there's only one option.
- We have to kill the Jew.
- Yep, I think we gotta kill the Jew.
I don't know.
He's got a lot of support.
It might be hard
to even catch this Jew.
Did somebody say "catch a Jew"?
The person you are after might be
hard to get, but I can bring him to you.
And all I want in return...
is GTA: Chinatown Wars
for handheld Nintendo DS.
How can we help you, young man?
I want to return
this Margaritaville.
My dad bought it on a payment
plan set up by a finance company
that got investors from Wall Street
who combined it into securities, sold
to banks who transfered it to you!
That makes sense.
No problem. We just need
to consult the chart.
We can determine your property's
value and we'll be done.
Really? Thank you.
Be right back.
Excellent news, sir.
We've determined the investment
value of your Margaritaville to be
$90 trillion!
What?
Hey, what's the matter, Kyle?
You seem... bummed out.
I just have a feeling this might
be the last time we get to do this.
Don't worry, Kyle. We're not
gonna let people kill you.
We'll keep you hidden forever!
I can't just hide
my whole life, Butters.
And besides,
I have this strange feeling that
one of you is gonna totally betray me.
All right, whoever is thinking
of betraying Kyle, that is not cool.
That's fricking lame, dude.
Kyle's trying to get
the economy going again.
If somebody is thinking of stabbing
him in the back, you're being a dick.
Go ahead, Kyle.
Whoever it might happen to be,
I'm not giving him the opportunity.
Tomorrow, I'm going to do something.
Something I've known I would have
to do to restore people's faith.
Kyle, please.
For... fuck's sake,
don't do anything drastic.
There's no choice anymore, guys.
Don't worry about me.
I've been preparing
for this for a while now.
No, no, no. Excuse me.
I don't understand.
How can this stupid thing
be worth $90 trillion?
- What, you think it's worth more?
- No! Dude, that doesn't make sense.
Well, you don't get $90 trillion, but
the chart says that's what it's worth.
- Oh, problem! Problem again!
- What is it now?
Another insurance company
is about to go under.
If they do,
people could lose millions.
OK. No problem.
We better consult the chart.
Sir, another insurance
company is going under.
Now determining most prudent
move for insurance company!
- Bailout!
- Most prudent move is a bailout!
Bailout the insurance company!
It's a miracle.
- Why would someone do this?
- What is this? What's going on?
There. Look.
It's the Jew.
Somehow he got a platinum
Amex with no spending limit.
What's he doing?
He's... paying for everyone's debts.
Hey, thanks, kid.
This is really nice of you.
But that's impossible.
Why would he do this?
So that people have money to spend.
Kyle! Kyle, you have to stop this!
It's OK, ma.
No, Kyle, you'll be in debt
for the rest of your life.
Please, somebody, get him to stop!
There's about $17,000 worth here.
He paid for our debts
so we could spend once more.
He's dead.
No, he's just passed out.
We should get him to bed.
For the first time in almost a year,
the economy in South Park
has taken a small,
but noticeable upturn.
Stores and shopping malls
are open again
as newly debt-free people feel
safe to make purchases.
The new Margaritaville!
With salsa dispenser!
Just pour your favorite salsa in the top
and it comes out the dispenser
at the bottom!
Oh, we need this!
Are we out of the woods yet?
Only time will tell.
But we must not forget the sacrifice
one person made
to restore our faith,
and make us believe
in the economy once again.
The person we must thank
every day for his amazing sacrifice...
Barack Obama.
Come on!
SouthParkNews.net