SouthParkNews.net
La Fabrique
Okay, kids.
Let's take our seats.
There has been a change
in school policy,
and so I am assigning you all
a book to read.
A book?
God, I hate those!
Now, kids,
this book is very controversial
and has just been taken
off the banned books list.
Really?
It's called Catcher in the Rye.
It has some very risqué parts.
All right!
- And strong, vulgar language.
- Awesome!
In fact, many schools
across the country still ban this book
because it's thought
to be so inappropriate.
Man, I can't wait!
Tonight, I want you to read
chapters one through five.
- Tomorrow, we'll discuss...
- Come on, let's read it now!
Didn't the guy who shot John Lennon
say it was because of this book?
Apparently, John Lennon's killer said
he was inspired by Catcher in the Rye.
But he was just a kook.
You're telling us
this book is filthy, inappropriate
and made a guy
shoot the king of hippies?
Can we please read this right now?
You will read it at home
and you will all be mature
about its adult themes and language!
Did you get to any dirty parts yet?
It's still some whiny annoying teenager
talking about how lame he is.
I don't get it.
What's so controversial about this?
All he's done
is said shit and fuck a few times.
I know.
I'm almost at the end and nothing.
Motherfucker!
The whole thing.
I read the whole fucking thing!
I kept thinking, all right,
the offensive stuff must be coming.
And after a hundred pages,
I was like,
all right,
all the dirty stuff is at the end.
Then I got to the last page
and I was all,
the fuck is this?
I just read a book!
For nothing!
Why the hell was this book banned?
They fucking tricked us!
Tricked us into reading a book
by promising us vulgarity.
What the fuck is so dirty
about this piece of shit?
We know, we were just saying that!
Why would anyone think
this book is obscene or dangerous?
Kill John Lennon!
Dad, where does John Lennon live?
John Lennon's dead.
Dangit.
Some people
really do consider this obscene!
It's not obscene.
I'll show them fucking obscene.
We should write our own banned book.
We could get a book banned
way more than this one.
- Sweet!
- Awesome!
The Tale of...
The Tale of Scrotie McDick'n'Ass.
No, Scrotie McBoogerballs.
That's good!
All right, Chapter One...
It was a warm spring morning...
The Tale of Scrotie McBoogerballs?
"It was a warm summer morning
"when Scrotie McBoogerballs
awoke to find his..."
"He took a..."
What?
My God!
"He then grabbed his dog's..."
"Walking out of his house,
he spotted a bloody, pus covered..."
You need to read this!
- Read what?
- This book!
Our son and his friends wrote it!
So?
It's really good.
I mean, it's disgusting.
It's the most disgusting thing
I've ever read,
but the plot is amazing!
And the characters are so vivid.
"It was a warm summer morning
"when Scrotie McBoogerballs
awoke to find his..."
- Gross!
- Just keep reading!
"He took a..."
"And..."
This is...
I know, but trust me,
you gotta push through to the end.
- That's just wrong!
- Please!
You've got to listen to me!
"Walking out of the house,
he found a bloody, pus filled..."
What?
"Which he immediately
stuck up his infected..."
"That was all long ago
in some brief lost spring,
"in a place that is no more.
"In that hour that vag frogs begin
"and the scent off Scrotie's
infected anus comes strongest."
- Man.
- Well?
It's awesome.
It's the best book I've ever read.
Right?
It's not just me!
The whole part about Amsterdam...
What do we do?
We can't support
our son talking like this, but...
I know...
People need to read this book...
This is Pulitzer Prize stuff.
You're dead, Kenny!
Guys!
We are totally fucked!
The book is gone from my drawer.
My parents must have found it!
Why we're all fucked?
They'll think you wrote it all.
I'm not taking the heat for this alone!
We all wrote it.
If I'm going down,
somebody must go down with me!
Cartman's going down!
And if I'm going down,
Kyle and Kenny are going down.
Dude!
Somebody has got to go down!
- What are you up to?
- Hey, fellas!
I'm just watching the Kardashians!
Today, my sisters and I
are going to have to wash something.
It's gonna blow!
Kim Kardashian is so sexy.
Her butt is like
a big mountain of pudding.
- Listen, you are in big trouble.
- I am?
You remember that book you wrote?
Stan's mom found it.
Which book was that?
The book you left with us
when you were sleepwalking last night!
I don't even remember!
But it all makes sense now.
Ever since I read Catcher in the Rye,
I've been having these...
blackouts,
crazy thoughts
of wanting to kill the phonies!
I must have channeled all my angst
into dark writings in my sleep!
All right, boys.
We need to get to the bottom of this.
We've all read the book now.
It's very shocking, to say the least.
Actually,
it was all written by Butters.
That's right.
Is that true?
I barely even remember it,
but I know I did.
We think...
that this is one of the best books
we've ever read!
- What?
- Really amazing.
Thanks!
We were actually
so moved by your book,
that we brought Mr. Nadelbaum
from Penguin Publishing to read it.
Mr. Butters,
we would like to offer you a deal
for first publishing rights
to your brilliant novel.
Wait a minute.
That's ours!
We wrote that!
Okay, boys.
You already told the truth.
We really did write it.
Tell them, Butters.
I wrote that.
- He's so young!
- Amazing!
What?
It is being called the most disgusting,
foul, sickening book ever written,
and it is also being called
literary genius.
The Tale of Scrotie McBoogerballs
hit the shelves this weekend,
and so far, no one
has been able to get through
the first paragraph without vomiting.
The book has already sold
millions of copies worldwide,
and has been translated
into 26 languages.
The book is changing
the literary world
and it is all thanks
to Leopold Butters Stotch.
Here he comes!
- Amazing book!
- Thank you!
- You changed my life, young man.
- That's nice!
What the fuck
do you think you're doing?
Just enjoying myself.
Why, Eric?
You know goddamn well
you didn't write that book!
But you told me I did!
That was when we thought
we'd get in trouble, asshole!
Leave Butters alone.
- He's a very fragile artist.
- He's so brooding and full of angst.
I'm brooding.
He doesn't deserve credit
for Scrotie McBoogerballs!
We deserve it all!
You guys are pathetic.
Get a life and stop mooching
off of others' success for once.
God dammit!
Do you really think
it's fair to lie like this?
- Let me tell you that if you don't...
- Let me tell you something, fellas!
You always take advantage of me,
and after reading Catcher in the Rye,
I've learned you're nothin' but phonies!
I'm not letting you
trick me this time!
So the four of you
can just suck on my wiener!
That inconsiderate jerk!
Today on Today.
We meet the author of the book
that has swept the nation
and has now spawned
TV's most popular game show!
How long can you listen
to Scrotie McBoogerballs
and not vomit?
The book is full
of disgusting words and acts,
including Sarah Jessica Parker,
who is mentioned 465 times.
Are you upset your wife
is made fun of so much in the book?
Obviously, it's wrong to make fun
of anybody's physical appearance.
My wife is a beautiful woman,
and most people agree with me.
And Matthew, how come a transvestite
donkey witch is standing next to you,
and why is it wearing a dress?
Joining us now is the author,
Leopold Stotch,
along with his parents.
- Hello, Matt!
- Hi, everyone!
You must be
pretty proud of your son.
We certainly are!
We're thrilled he's so talented.
We also understand
that your son is grounded, is he?
We had to ground him
for the language in the novel.
I come right to my room
after school.
But we are very proud nonetheless.
Now that you're a respected author,
- have you met any famous people?
- Not yet,
but as soon as I'm not grounded,
I'm hoping to meet Kim Kardashian!
I wanna jump on her belly.
All right.
My favorite part was
when Scrotie McBoogerballs
slid his head up into the horse's...
Sorry. Was that chapter
a slam on health care reform
as people have suggested?
Pretty much.
I think so.
Is that why the doctor character
pulls out all the stringy...
Are you ever worried
somebody might take your book wrong
and try to kill someone like
when that guy tried to shoot R. Reagan
after reading Catcher in the Rye?
Is that who the book
was telling me to kill?
Kill Ronald Reagan!
Ronald Reagan is dead now.
Really?
Gosh, dangit.
More and more of us
are against this book every day.
The author is cruel and offensive.
And for these reasons,
we demand this book be banned
from all schools, stores
and libraries.
This book is nothing, but smut
and vulgarity purely
for the sake of smut and vulgarity!
That's just because you're too young
to understand the underlying themes.
There are no underlying themes!
We know that for a fact!
You just failed to understand
what the author meant.
The author meant to be as gross
as possible, because it was funny!
That is such a simplistic view.
There is no deeper meaning.
Read it again!
So you're suggesting
that the author arbitrarily made fun
of Sarah Jessica Parker
for no reason?
But what would be the point?
There's is no point!
It's just because
Sarah Jessica Parker is fucking ugly!
No writer
would take the time
to make fun of Sarah Jessica Parker
just because they think she's ugly.
- Yes, they would!
- It is because
she is a metaphor in the book
for oppression
felt by the lower class.
What?
That is not in the book at all!
This book is an important look
at how liberals
are hurting this country...
Scrotie McBoogerballs
is the most conservative-hating
liberal in literature!
What did you read?
There's nothing about that!
Then why does
Jessica Parker's butt cheese
end up in Scrotie's milkshake?
Breaking news
from acclaimed author Leopold Stotch.
The artist has announced
that he is working on a second novel,
as a follow up
to his wildly successful best seller.
We got a statement from the writer,
who is still grounded in his room.
Can you give the public any idea
what the new book is about?
It's kind of
about love and betrayal.
The inner workings
of the human mind.
Will it be as sick and disgusting
as your first book?
It's raunchy all right!
I know what my readers want
and I'm going to deliver!
Away from the window!
You are being grounded!
Sorry, I was just bein'
the voice of a generation.
I can't believe
they won't ban our book!
I know! It's so much worse
than Catcher in the retarded Rye!
It's fucking disgusting!
All right,
I know what we have to do.
We've got to kill
Sarah Jessica Parker.
- What?
- Think about it!
If somebody kills her,
they'll assume somebody did it
because of what was in the book.
- Then the book will get banned.
- We're not killing her!
Be right with you!
We don't have to kill her.
We can just help her get killed.
Shut up!
Just face it.
We lost this one!
We only have to help her get killed
and we totally get back at Butters.
Okay.
Miss Jessica Parker!
Over here.
The day has finally arrived,
the eagerly-awaited second novel
from the author
of Scrotie McBoogerballs
hit the shelves this morning,
and apparently bookstores are jammed.
Al, how is it out there?
I don't know
if you can see this, guys,
but the line stretches
all the way around the block.
People waiting for their turn
to get inside the book store
and read the novel.
They've brought trash bags
and buckets to throw up in,
just a festive atmosphere here,
Matt and Meredith.
We've got
our vomit buckets ready too,
because coming up,
a very special in-studio treat.
That's right,
we are going to have a reading
of the first five chapters of the book
live in our studio!
We must warn you
that this is from the same author
who wrote the most graphic,
obscene novel of all time,
so brace yourselves
for some harsh language.
Take it away, Morgan Freeman!
The Poop that took a Pee.
"Chapter One."
"Douglas had to poop.
"His butt was all stinky
because he had to poop so badly.
"There was a gross woman
named Rebecca
"who was sunbathing all naked
and she was fat.
"Douglas walked up to her and said,
"I need to poop.
"Okay, Rebecca replied.
"I like poop.
"Douglas squatted down...
"over the fat sunbathing lady
"and went poop.
"The poop,
sat there on Rebecca's boobs,
"looking like a wiener."
"Chapter Two."
- See any hunters yet?
- Not yet.
Doing good Miss Jessica Parker,
just hang out right there.
Guys! Stop!
We don't have to do this!
- Butters wrote a second book!
- So what?
If he wrote a second book
they'll know
he couldn't have written the first one!
We can get people to believe us now.
Dude, sweet!
"Why are we here,
"Douglas cried,
"as poop came out his wiener
"in a long, thin strip.
"It was
"wiener poop.
"Which is the grossest poop of all."
"The pee pee got on the woman's leg
"and she screamed
"pooping out her boobs."
"And so, when the pee
got mixed with the poop
"it smelled like a butt."
This is even lamer than we thought!
People are gonna want Butters' head!
Are you reading this?
What do you think?
So far, I think it's incredible.
It might be better
than his first book.
I agree it wasn't as edgy,
but it's like
he's gone back to his roots.
- What?
- You can't be serious! You like this?
Some of the imagery is unbelievable.
A woman pooping out her boobs
is not good imagery!
Says you.
You must be a pro-life nut, huh?
Didn't like
what the book had to say?
What are you talking about?
This book is as pro-life as it gets.
- Come on!
- God dammit!
Will you people stop
reading into stuff that isn't there?
"And the poop and the pee
lived happily ever after.
"The end."
Kill the phonies!
Today my sisters and I
are going to shop for underwear!
Can I go with you girls?
Our nation is still reeling
from the tragic deaths
of the Kardashians.
The shooter claims he was driven
to commit the slaughter,
immediately after reading
The Poop that took a Pee
by Leopold Butters Stotch.
It's all over.
The Kardashians...
wiped out,
in the blink of an eye.
All because one little...
prick...
had to go and write a book.
Leopold Stotch.
I hope they bury you!
You evil fucker!
Dude, people are pissed off at you.
I know.
They're saying they're gonna ban
both your books, completely!
You're not making any more money!
You think I care about that?
My writing got the most
beautiful woman in the world killed!
I loved her!
And now she's gone
and it's because of me!
It'll be all right.
We've all learned
that people look for meaning in books.
And sometimes,
even if it isn't there,
they'll try and invent
their own meaning.
That's why we all need to avoid books
and stick to television.
Thanks, fellas.
I'll definitely never write again.
I think I can get over this.
That's good, because we need
to tell you something.
- What?
- You were sleepwalking again
and dressed
Jessica Parker up in a moose suit.
You left her in the forest
and she got shot by a hunter.
What?
Sorry. You're gonna have
to come down and admit it was you.
I got her killed too?
At least, she was ugly.