Season 13 Episode 10
"W.T.F."
Say that again, Edge.
You think you're better than me?
Cena, your mouth has gotten you
into trouble for the last time.
I'm gonna shut it up for you!
- Mess him up, Edge!
- Kick his ass!
I've got something else
to tell you, Edge!
I slept with Vanessa last night!
Cena slept with Edge's girlfriend!
- My God. This is so awesome!
- I am having the best time!
You cheated
and took my belt from me.
And now
I can't hardly get work wrestling!
You took my girl
and you took my job!
He took his job!
Sweet!
- Dude, awesome!
- This is so awesome!
- Dude, that was so badass!
- Wrestling is awesome!
This is it.
We know what are calling in life is.
Tomorrow we are signing up
for wrestling class!
- All right!
- Sweet!
The fuck is this?
Why did they have us
put on long underwear?
I guess we're supposed
to make your own outfit
and then wear it over this.
That makes sense.
Did everyone settle on their names?
I did.
I'm the Rad Russian.
I come from Russia
to crush your puny capitalist head!
All right!
Glad to see some new recruits
interested
in the fine sport of wrestling.
- Cool!
- Let's do this!
The first things we're gonna learn
are the fundamental wrestling holds.
Let's get some volunteers.
Come over here, young man.
What's your name?
- The Rad Russian.
- What?
You capitalist swine!
I crush you!
Just get on your hands and knees.
Just down on the floor.
Hands and knees.
And now how about you?
Your name is?
Triceratops!
All right.
Come on over here.
I'm gonna position you into the official
wrestling starting position.
Here we go...
The fuck is this?
Now just reach around him, here.
- Good.
- Dude! Dude!
The fuck are you doing?
Get back on the floor.
It's the starting position of wrestling!
That's not wrestling.
That's fucking gay!
Are you a child molester?
Where's the cool costumes
and jumping off ropes?
Not this again!
Let me guess, you went to that stupid
WWE show in Denver last night!
The WWE is not wrestling!
That's a bunch of fake bullcrap!
How stupid are you?
Real wrestling, boys, is this.
Well, this is fucking lame.
Let's get out of here.
He probably wants
to take pictures of us naked.
I got half a mind to report...
Report you to the police, sir!
The Wrestling Takedown Federation
has several matches planned today.
So here's how we'll do this.
I'll come out to the ring first,
then Jimmy tells me he'll kick my ass.{\*I'll come out to the ring first and then Jimmy you come in and tell me you're gonna kick my ass.}
I'll say you slept with my girlfriend,
and I'll do you a headslap.{\*Then I'm gonna say you slept with my girlfriend, and I'll charge you and do a headslap.}
- Sounds good.
- Butters comes in as the ref
like, "The fight hasn't started!"
That's when Jimmy sneaks up
and hits me with the foldaway chair.{\*And that's when Jimmy sneaks up from behind and hits me over the head with the foldaway chair.}
Okie-doke!
So is that when I tell you
your girlfriend is a whore?
Let's save it for after Stan headbutts
Butters for stopping the fight.{\*Let's save the girlfriend is a whore line until after Stan headbutts Butters for trying to stop the fight again.}
- Boy, wrestling sure is fun!
- All right. We ready to try this?
Let's start wrestling.
- I'm gonna kick your ass!
- You slept with my girl, Hammerclaw!
No, the fight hasn't started yet.
No! Bad!
He slept with my girl, referee!
In my country
we don't wait for a bell, mister...
Your girl is a whore.
- Wait for the whore line.
- Right. Sorry.
You're gonna get it, Hammerclaw!
- We'll see about that!
- Now hold on!
I am stopping the fight!
What's going on?
Apparently that crippled kid
slept with
that Russian kid's girlfriend.
Geez.
They're so young!
I'll kill you, Triceratops.
You made fun of my crippled mother!
That's because your mother
betrayed my mother, Juggernaut!
You don't come to this country
and make fun of it!
And just what do you care
about your pitiful country?
I served my country.
I fought for two years in Vietnam!
That kid was in Nam?
Man, that's incredible.
Good for you
for serving your country!
Guys, check this out!
There's this little kid from the Congo
who was raised by panthers!
Are you serious?
Just admit it, Congo.
Admit you lied about me to Irene!
I admit nothing.
Maybe Irene lied to you!
That kid in the hat
is having sex with two different girls?
No, that little kid from the Congo
lied about one of them to get the kid
in the hat in trouble with his wife.
They're married?
You will have to forfeit the fight,
Rad Russian!
You can't fight
until your test results come back!
I have to wait for my hepatitis test,
but in the meantime,
I have brought my comrade
from Mexico to wrestle against you!
That Russian kid's got hepatitis?
Here he comes now!
The cold blooded wrestler
from Mexico.
El Pollo Loco!
What are you doing here,
El Pollo Loco?
Your girlfriend doesn't even like you,
Stan the Man.
She likes me!
You don't know
what you're saying, Juggernaut!
Irene loves me
and I'm gonna marry her!
If she wants you,
how about
she tells all these people here?
Here some comes now.
It's Bad Irene!
Let me tell you something.
It's true I love Stan the Man
with all my heart.
- But I want to be with Juggernaut now.
- What?
No way!
What are you doing?
Stan the Man loves you!
Don't break his heart!
If you love Juggernaut, Irene,
then tell what you did two years ago.
How you killed his child!
It's true. I was pregnant
with your child and I aborted it.
Irene, no!
Why?
Do you know what it's like
to have an abortion at seven?
Do you?
I've had so many abortions.
I got addicted to them.
Did you hear that?
Irene, you said you loved me!
I don't love you.
I love abortions, don't you understand?
I'm telling you guys,
you got to see this.
These kids ain't more
than eight or nine years old
and they got more problems
than you can imagine.
There's this one kid,
he saw his father get murdered.
And yesterday he finds the killer
and it's this other kid
who's an ex-cop.
Needless to say,
he whooped his ass good.
And there's this little girl.
She's actually addicted
to getting abortions.
Got pregnant
by nearly every boy there.
You're shitting me.
No, we're telling you
these kids are fucking crazy.
You gotta check it out.
You can watch them
almost every afternoon.
It's some of the greatest wrestling
we ever seen.
It isn't real!
Don't you people understand?
That stuff isn't real.
None of it!
How stupid are you?
What do you mean it ain't real?
It's all made up.
Fiction.
Real wrestling is a serious
and respectable sport.
Why can't you understand
that kind of wrestling isn't real?
Mister,
there's a little girl out there
who's had fourteen abortions
and she ain't even ten yet.
But I guess
that's just not real to you.
Son a bitch.
Look!
This is wrestling!
Mister, you better take your gay porn
and walk right outta this bar.
Holy crap.
There's a huge turnout tonight!
Good thing we made
those changes to the seating.
You guys, let's bring it in.
We've done a great job.
Let's just keep the energy up,
have a good flow and have fun.
Let's do this!
One, two...
Backyard wrestling!
What a perfect night for fighting!
Low, the moon sets
upon the tips of the trees and I,
the man known as the Rad Russian,
start to stir
with the excitement of violence.
Only a country like yours
can breed men of such discontent!
But you don't know what real pain is.
Pain, like I've known.
Abandoned when I was
four years old by my parents.
Left to die in a cold
and dark sewage tunnel.
Geez, I didn't know
his parents did that.
I'm very sorry,
but I'm afraid we have to terminate
your employment here
at South Park Elementary.
You're firing me?
Why?
The school board has decided
to discontinue the wrestling program.
Wrestling simply involves
too much adult subject matter.
Like murder and abortion.
No!
This isn't wrestling!
Principal Victoria,
let me stay on and I can teach kids
what real wrestling is!
The board has made up their minds.
You can't fire me
for what these kids do!
That isn't the only reason.
What?
We found all the gay porn
on your iPhone, Mr. Conners.
So we do the part
about Jimmy's relationship
with his alcoholic father
after you smash Butters onto the table.
- Sure, that works.
- You guys!
Listen to this.
It's amazing!
- What, dude?
- We received a letter from the WWE.
- From the wrestlers we saw in Denver?
- No way!
"Gentlemen, we have heard
of your wrestling organization
"and are quite interested
in its popularity.
"The WWE is delighted to inform you
"that it will be sending a talent scout,
president Vince McMahon,
"to view your wrestling event
this Saturday, the 24th."
Vince McMahon is coming to see us?
This is our shot
at making it into the WWE,
to be real wrestlers!
- My God!
Guys, listen!
We seriously have to focus here.
We've exactly three days
before the scout see us wrestle.
We've got to step it up
and work it like never before!
Time for the second act.
Let's bring the crowd back
from intermission
and then improvise some stuff!
No, I think Congo
is a great wrestler.
I just think Rad Russian
has his number.
But Rad Russian
has a lot of abandonment issues.
Looks like intermission is over.
We better head back.
I left my wife today.
Walked out of the apartment
without saying a word.
I ran away from my responsibilities,
just I like always do.
And I, again,
am alone.
Here he is.
Hiding in the forest as I told you!
Juggernaut, there's to be
an ultimate Smackdown this Saturday.
Are you going
to run from that as well?
I'll fight anytime, anywhere!
He don't run from fights,
just from responsibilities.
What do I do?
Juggernaut is my long lost brother,
and yet Congo saved my life in Nam!
It's El Pollo Loco!
Thanks for coming.
I'm sure you're wondering
why I've called you to Sizzler.
What's this about?
We should be writing our monologues.
Kenny and I have been talking.
Smackdown might be our one shot
at making it into the WWE, right?
And it might never come again.
The way we see it,
we have three primary obstacles
in making Smackdown a great show.
What?
Let's face it.
They can't wrestle for crap.
Every time, they flub a line
or blow their monologue.
And Token,
he has no emotion, no timing.
He's the worst wrestler
I've ever seen.
- He's right.
- What?
It's hard to do your best wrestling
against Token.
- Right?
- Butters and Jimmy,
they're never gonna make it
as professional wrestlers.
So then WWE will recruit us
and not them.
They're gonna hurt our chances!
Because the new material
I've written is stuff they can't handle,
we'll suffer from it.
So what?
We gotta bring somebody else on
who can handle the more difficult roles.
Somebody who can do the harder stuff
so that Token, Butters and Jimmy
- can have smaller parts.
- How do we find this person?
It's simple.
We just gotta hold tryouts.
Number 17, step forward please.
You're wrestling a Muslim immigrant.
You suspect he could be a terrorist
and your parents died
in the 9/11 attacks. Go.
You dirty, Muslim bastard!
I don't trust you.
And I never will!
Do you know how it feels
to lose your parents.
No, you wouldn't, you smelly brown
middle eastern piece of...
Thank you.
Number 24.
You're wrestling for the right
to marry Mackenzie Phillips
but just learned that she had sex
with her father. Go.
Your father?
Your own father?
I don't care if you were on drugs,
you sick whore!
Thank you.
- That guy's a pretty good wrestler.
- Yeah, not bad.
Can we get number 37
to step forward again?
Want to get to know you better.
What can you tell us about you?
Not a whole lot to tell, really.
Was born in Fort Collins.
Started watching wrestling
when I was four years old.
My father, he liked it too...
until he died.
Sometimes I think it's because of him
I follow this dream.
All my life,
all I ever wanted was to be a wrestler.
Fighting in the ring,
winning that belt.
And so I dreamed every night
that I was the undertaker,
smashing skulls in,
breaking arms.
- Damn, that is some badass wrestling.
- Yeah, this guy crushes.
It isn't fair.
All my hard work.
{/$WRESTLING SMACKDOWN
BRINGS WWE PRESIDENT}
I'm not going to take it anymore.
That wrestling show is in
for a big surprise.
I'm putting an end to this
once and for all.
He's here!
Vince McMahon is here!
It's really him!
He's here.
My God!
All right.
Places everyone!
Welcome to this performance
of Wrestling Takedown Federation:
Smackdown.
- What's going on?
- You know what's going on.
It's Smackdown tonight.
We might have to fight each other.
You shouldn't be fighting anybody.
What about your cancer?
Wait a minute.
Who is that?
It's Triceratops,
and he's with Irene!
You aren't welcome here,
Triceratops!
Stay calm.
You know what you have to do
for the good of real wrestling.
No, Irene please, just this once,
do not abort this baby.
My body, my right.
In fact, I'm junking
for the rush so badly,
- I won't make to it the clinic.
- You can't possibly mean that...
Maybe I'll have another abortion
right here, right now.
There's someone here
to wrestle you, Irene.
A baby you aborted
many years ago survived.
And he's here now.
Mother!
Why did you abort me? Why?
He is alive!
You, get back in the trash condition
where you belong.
What do you think?
They are decent wrestlers.
We'll see how they develop
their through line in the second act.
I thought I would find you here,
Triceratops!
Stay out of my business,
Sgt. Hammerclaw!
Excuse me.
I'm sorry,
I'm afraid this area is off limits.
Don't mind me.
I was just about to...
What the fuck is this?
How I long
for the spring meadows of Russia.
The soft Russian sky.
When are you going
to face reality, Congo?
Just because you were raised
by panthers doesn't mean you are one!
He's closer to a panther
than you'll ever be!
Lies!
These are all a bunch of lies!
Now, you listen here, El Pollo Loco.
Your wife was killed,
but you can't keep Irene's aborted baby.{\*It doesn't matter if you wife was killed. You cannot keep Irene's aborted baby.}
Just let him crawl back Mexico,
Sgt. Hammerclaw.
Only one shot.
Maximum damage.
This is all your fault,
you WWE president asshole.
Your fault we all die here
right now.
For wrestling!
Shut up!
You idiots want wrestling?
This is wrestling.
We want some real wrestlers.
This is just a bunch of garbage.
And you're all ruining
the good name of wrestling.
Wrestling is from ancient Greece.
It's in the Olympics.
What the hell do you care?
Get off the wrestling mat.
Why do I care?
These kids made it so real,
wrestling is gone from schools.
It's practically gone
from the culture.
Damn it.
They took my job!
What?
- They took his job.
- I know.
You want to know pain?
Pain is dedicating
your entire life to a sport,
to a career,
and then having it all
ripped away from you
like a baby from its mother.
- Man, they took his job.
- They took his job.
Lost everything.
Couldn't even afford to pay
for my little retriever Rex anymore.
Animal control came and got him.
They took his dog!
I ended up on the streets stealing.
Got busted by the police
and had to spend the night in jail.
The other inmates, they beat me up
and fractured my jaw so I couldn't eat.
They broke his jaw!
So you see, I have nothing left.
Nothing!
Not even the will to live.
Sir, that was one
of the finest wrestling performances
- I have ever seen.
- What?
Will you not join
our wrestling organization?
I promise to make you
our leading act.
- You mean it?
- Come.
I want to get you in rehearsals
right away.
What?
What about us?
Our show?
Sorry, boys.
You are decent wrestlers,
but lack the raw wrestling talent
this man has.
This is your fault, Kyle.
You screwed up the second act.
Me?
It was your stupid ass writing.
Face it, Stan's crappy singing
is what who sunk us.
What the hell is this?
This is garbage fight.
Screw this.
This is just stupid.
Fake!
SouthParkNews.net (1.0)
La Fabrique