( theme music playing )
¶ oooh! ¶
¶ yeah yeah! ¶
¶ yeah yeah ¶
¶ yeah, my mind
has been enabled ¶
¶ in the memory
you overflow ¶
¶ i wanna be
your superhero ¶
¶ even if i
tumble, fall ¶
¶ i'm okay ¶
¶ but i need you
desperately ¶
¶ you know i need you
¶ i wanna be
your superhero ¶
¶ yeah, oh yeah ¶
¶ oh yeah. ¶
You guys were right.
i feel like a new man.
Tell us about it.
- i don't kiss and tell.
- come on, give us something.
- like what?
- like was she a squirter?
- you are disgusting.
- what's up, guys?
- yo, what's up?
- he's disgusting.
- turtle got laid last night.
- by the coed.
- really?
- is it that unbelievable?
No, i just thought
jamie, you know...
He's over her.
guy got back on the horse
and performed like a man.
- i'm impressed.
- how are things going
with you?
Well, sloan agreed
to have lunch with me.
Where evil will perform
like a woman.
- shut up.
- so what are you gonna say?
I'm gonna tell her i want
to get back together.
You've said that before,
haven't you?
- you don't think it'll work?
- no.
I don't really want
relationship advice from
you anyway, drama.
I'm not really giving you
relationship advice, e,
'cause you and sloan don't
really have a relationship.
But embrace it,
because freedom is
a beautiful thing.
- and now we all have it.
- yeah, well, i don't want it.
I didn't want it either.
it was forced upon me.
You guys are pathetic.
i'm leaving for italy tomorrow.
is anyone coming with?
- i don't know.
- maybe.
Free johnny is.
you really gonna
quit acting, drama?
Freedom, baby.
i might even have some
t-shirts made up.
- he's just taking
a little break.
- ( phone ringing )
Oh, miss u.c.l.a.
You go, girl.
- hey.
Look, this may be
a little direct,
But i'm feeling really insecure
that you didn't even try
and kiss me last night.
I didn't want
to be aggressive.
- i like aggressive, turtle.
- i can see that.
- come over.
- now?
yeah, unless you're busy.
No, i'm not busy.
it's just...
- jamie?
- yeah.
I will help you get
over jamie, turtle.
- you think?
- i know.
Even if we just talk.
All right.
I'm just saying no amount
of ivy gimlets
Is gonna make sloan
fall back in love with you.
- i'm out.
- round two on campus?
- something like that.
- love it.
- learn from it.
- later, boys.
- later.
- enjoy.
Look, e,
i agree with johnny.
What's a lunch
going to accomplish?
I'm gonna make it special.
How are you gonna
make lunch special?
i've got some ideas.
You're gonna need
some roofies, bro.
( stifled laugh )
So what are we here
to talk about?
Well, this is
extremely secretive.
Everything in here is.
I'm buying
a very big company.
Oh, congrats.
Which he said wouldn't
cost us anything.
This deal will make me
the head of the largest agency
In the entire
entertainment business.
You said it wouldn't
cost us anything.
Well, i didn't think
that it would.
He said the company
was gonna buy it.
i thought that
the company could.
But it's been a rough
year so, you know,
We're a little
strapped for cash.
But the bank has
asked me to personally
guarantee something.
$12 million.
I think it's great
that you two have
Such open communication
about your money.
It's not our money.
- it's her money.
- oh.
And i just put up
my money when we started
this new agency.
And that was over
two years ago,
And we still haven't gotten
all of that money back yet.
And that doesn't
concern you, ari?
No, because we're gonna
make it back 50 times
- on this one.
- ( laughs )
You don't see it this way?
Even if i did, i don't see
this as just about business.
Is it about ego, ari?
Well, i've always dreamed
about ruling the world.
But now that i'm getting
older i would settle for
ruling hollywood.
It goes much deeper than that.
he's got enemies at this
company he wants to buy.
- i have enemies everywhere.
- who are these enemies?
These are very
personal conflicts.
he wants payback.
- and i'm not sure
he's thinking clearly.
- what?
tell me about
these conflicts, ari.
- they don't matter.
- your wife seems
to think they do.
My wife doesn't know
how i do my business.
But you need her money
in order to buy this
business that you want.
- so why do you want it?
- for revenge.
- for a music department.
- for terrance.
For a book department
that i can pair with
filmmakers.
- and for lloyd.
- for spts stars.
Is it possible that
these people are the reason
you want to buy the agency?
Yes, he wants
to destroy them.
Tell her.
tell her.
Is it true?
do you want to destroy
these people, ari?
Okay, yes!
S!if i could gouge out
terrance mcquiewick's
eyeballs
And eat them for what
he did to me, i would.
And i would sell that
benedict arnold adam davies
Into white slavery
if we lived in a place
that had a market for it.
And lloyd,
that little queen
Who i welcomed
into my home
And allowed to
play with my children
and care for my dog,
And who left me
for those two scumbags,
I would tie him up
and allow the entire
Screen actors guild
to anally rape him
If not for the fact that
i know he would enjoy it.
I hate 'em all.
And yes, i want to see
them destroyed.
But that is not why
i want this company.
I want--
no no, i need
This company because
it's good business.
It's good
goddamn business.
And if i don't buy it,
someone else will
And that will be very
very bad for my business.
And my wife, of all people,
should know
That when it comes
to business, my judgment
is never clouded.
So please please,
Support me like you
always have
And i will deliver for us
Like i always have.
what do you think?
I think it was
a good speech.
Yeah.
Do what you need
to do, ari.
Really?
I love you.
Can we fuck in here?
Johnny, "melrose place"
will not stop calling me.
They like you.
like sally field,
they really really like you.
Well, i'm sorry you have
to deal with that, lloyd.
But i told you,
i'm passing.
Johnny, just go in
and read for them.
10 minutes of your life.
what do you have to lose?
What's left
of my soul, lloyd.
sorry, got to go.
Johnny, maybe you
should just test.
If you get it you can
turn it down if you
really don't want it.
I don't want it.
really.
Look at me.
Vince, i have
one pair left.
- oh, awesome. thanks.
- you're welcome.
- vince, what's up?
- hey, matty.
- how's it going?
- how you doing, buddy?
- good to see you, man.
- good to see you.
- hey, matt.
- hey.
Johnny.
Listen, man, did you
get the stuff that i
sent over to ari?
It's the foundation
i'm working with--
the one by one foundation.
- the kids' foundation.
- oh, yeah yeah.
It's at the house.
i haven't had a chance
to look at it.
You haven't looked
at it yet?
- no, i've been busy.
- with what?
I'm doing the new
darabont movie.
- don't be afraid
to get involved, vince.
- i'm not.
We're raising money for
children all over the world.
it's for kids.
- it sounds good.
- it is good.
- you should look at it.
- i will.
- you can look at it too.
- yeah, i will, matt.
- i'll see, you, man.
- see you later.
It's for kids.
Wow, he's intense.
¶ yeah ¶
¶ cruising on a grey snake
till my dying day ¶
¶ checking out your henhouses
all along the way... ¶
- where are we going?
- it's a surprise.
- how far is it?
I have to be back by 2:30.
You're not gonna be,
so surprise.
- no, i'm serious.
- me too.
Come on, eric.
no fooling around.
I have something
i have to do.
- really?
- yeah.
That's my fault.
i wasn't thinking.
- but this is really important.
- what is?
I can't tell you
till we're there.
( laughs, groans )
Come on, what is it?
I can't tell you
till we're there.
Anyway, you can change
your appointment.
( sighs )
Is this really important?
Yes it is.
Okay.
- thank you.
- you owe me.
Always.
¶ you're the only
one i need ¶
¶ ain't nobody
make me feel ¶
¶ the way you're
making me feel ¶
¶ and, girl, you know
this love is real... ¶
- wake up.
- i'm up.
- you're like kissing a corpse.
- i'm sorry.
You're not
attracted to me?
Are you kidding?
you're smoking.
- yeah?
- yeah.
Maybe you just need
to loosen up a little.
Relax.
Now you're
getting somewhere.
- yeah?
you like that?
- uh-huh.
You like that?
Yeah.
( sighs )
I can't believe i can't
get you to stop thinking
about her.
I'm sorry.
She hasn't called me
back in three days.
Maybe she doesn't
want to talk to you.
No, i think she's pissed
i didn't try to stop her
from going.
Or that i didn't go
with her, you know?
I don't know her,
turtle.
I should have
gone with her.
Well, maybe you
should go now.
I'm really sorry.
I'll live.
Yeah, but i got you
all worked up
And now i'm just
abandoning you.
that's not fair.
You want me to go down
on you or something?
( scoffs )
- lloyd. lloyd.
- yes?
Ari gold's on his way
up here again.
What?
why is this happening?
Why does ari gold
keep coming up here?
Adam, i gave up my life
to work with you.
You two make
a cute couple.
Adam, talk to me, please.
I think we're merging
or ari's buying us.
i don't know.
Oh my god.
what will that mean for me?
I know what
it'll mean for me.
You know what i'm looking
forward to, terrance?
No, what's that?
Walking through this place
terminator style
And eradicating
all the dead weight.
Unlike you,
i have a soft heart.
( laughs )
soft as a diamond.
Okay, can we dispense
with the pleasantries?
You know, my business
hasn't done too badly
over the years.
But it can be doing
so much better.
And it will be doing better
once we're done here.
so let's move on.
You were always so certain
that you knew better than i.
Barbara's right,
seeing is believing.
But when i trim
the fat off this shithole
And put it all under
the miller gold banner,
You will see what it
could have been if you
would have kept me around.
Oh, i look forward to that.
Except of course it won't be
under the miller gold banner.
I don't follow.
You obviously havet read
the addendum in the contract.
- what addendum?
- it was added in
this morning.
It's nothing really.
it's just i want assurances
That the 40-year-old
terrance mcquiewick agency,
Which i founded, doesn't
somehow lose its name.
Well, that's not really
for you to decide.
The addendum says it is.
Are you joking?
Ari, we've only had
our name for two years.
- how attached
to it can you be?
- i like gold, okay?
You can't pull this shit
last second.
I wouldn't have
thought i needed it.
My lawyers
didn't think i did.
They said, "what idiwoud
of a brand name
That is synonymous
with entertainment
And has been for nearly
four decades?"
But i woke up
in a terrible sweat
last night.
And i thought,
"my god.
I know what idiot
would want that-- him."
You got your price,
you have no other say.
- ari.
- i'm out of here.
Come on, ari.
don't let your
unchecked ego
Bring you
to your knees again.
Ari, come back and sign
the fucking papers.
Lloyd lee, you got
a new lease on life.
You too, scumbag.
- drama: lloyd. lloyd.
- yeah, johnny?
I said it doesn't matter
because it isn't about
the money.
Tell 'em i said thank you
but no thank you.
- okay.
- all right, i'll talk
to you later.
Okay.
What happened?
They're willing to push
my quote 10 gs.
You're making 'em want you.
what are you thinking?
I'm thinking about
you and me
Scouring the italian
countryside.
I can't think
of anything better.
You know i'm gonna be
working most of the time?
Yeah, you've still got to eat
and blow off some steam.
True. i just want to make
sure you're gonna be okay.
- i don't want you
to have any regrets.
- i'm great, bro. really.
I might even take up
as a cobbler like daniel day.
Now that would
be interesting.
( phone rings )
Ciao.
the chase residence.
hey, it's matt damon.
Hey, matt, it's johnny.
what can i do for you?
You can write a big check
to the one by one foundation.
I'd love to, but my future's
a little uncertain right now.
- i'm out of the business.
- were you in the business?
I was on a hit show
for three years.
- what happene  they fired ?
- no, i left by choice.
Well, listen, john,
there are millions
of helpless children
With much much
bigger problems.
Well, yeah,
of course.
Is vince there?
did he look at
the materials yet?
Hang on.
it's damon.
He wants to know about
that charity thing.
He must have slipped out.
But i can see the brochures
opened up here on the table.
Put him on the fucking
phone, john.
Okay.
Sorry, he jason bourned me.
( sighs )
hey, matt.
I was just looking
over the stuff.
- pretty moving shit,
isn't it?
- very.
Okay, so can i
count on you?
Just let me know
what i can do.
i'll tell you
what you can do.
we've got some trips coming
up to cleveland, ohio.
Feeding america, one of
our partners, is running
a food bank there.
I need a other celebrity
to go with me to draw
attention to the fact
That one out of six
american children--
One out of six,
are food insecur
Do you even know
what that means, vince?
It means they don't
know where their next
meal is coming from.
One out of six americans.
it's fucking shameful.
Yeah, i'm leaving
for italy tomorrow.
You know what?
fuck the american kids.
Let them starve.
have a good time
on your vacation.
No, it's not a vacation.
i'm working.
- get off your arse, vince.
- that's bono, vince.
Oh, hey, bono.
You know, it doesntake muchg
effect here, vince.
- yeah.
- matt: i'll tell you what--
When you're done with
your frank darabont movie,
- i'm gonna take you
on a trip, okay?
- yeah, for sure.
in the near term
i would like a check.
Okay.
for how much?
- do what's right, vince.
- don't be a cheapskate, man.
Do it today, okay?
don't make me wait.
i'm going to be waiting.
-we'll both be waiting.
- see you, vince.
( door shuts )
Yo, what's up?
I'm going to new zealand.
Hey, what happened
with the coed?
Nothing.
not today or last night.
You lied?
Sorry.  i love jamie.
i don't want to be with
anybody else.
I got a 6:00 p.m. flight.
Well...
I guess freedom is ours
and ours alone, johnny.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I may have been lying
to myself too, bro.
I'm an actor.
I've got to get
to that meeting.
Eric:
we got lucky today.
basically perfect weather.
Yeah.
God, it feels like forever
since we were last here.
It was only
a couple years ago.
More like three.
We spent two
nights at shutters.
that was a good weekend.
It was for me.
You got so sunburned you
couldn't breathe without pain.
Maybe i glorified it
a little bit.
No, it was amazing.
So what are we doing here?
Is vince thinking about buying
this place or something?
No.
So what then?
I just wanted to remind you
how good we could be together.
Wow.
You've got to be kidding me.
- sloan.
- eric, i canceled
on someone.
Was it really
that important?
It's the guy i'm seeing
and yes, i like him.
Well, i still love you.
- i want to go home.
- sloan.
Eric, we've been over this.
I want to go home now.
Hey, jame,
it's me.
I just wanted to let you know
i'm on my way to see you.
We need to talk
face to face.
I'm taking off in a little,
so please call me if
you get this.
- auckland. you traveling to?
- how long is the flight?
- about 14 and a half hours.
Sweet.
This lying scumbag
piece of shit.
What did you
expect from him?
I expected him to honor
the deal that he agreed to.
- he was never going to.
- he has never honored
anything.
But you still want this.
More than i want
my wife to crave pussy.
But i will not be controlled
by that rotting old douchebag.
- i was for too long.
- it's a fair deal though, ari.
For whatever reason,
he's being more than fair.
And you know that
if you drop this ball
The whole town
is gonna dive for this.
- what the hell?
- he's weak.
I don't know why, but he is.
just get the deal done.
- andrew.
- terrance.
Nice to see you.
didn't realize you were
still in the business.
- die.
- not for you.
Not for any tv agents.
hello, ari.
I should kick your ass
for wasting my time.
Remember when you first
came to work for me?
We used to go spar
at my gym.
I'd kick your ass.
You were my boss.
i let you win.
I could still kick
your ass and you know it.
Listen, you crawled
over here for a reason.
what is it?
I want to make
this deal work.
well, then i suggest
that you go find a buyer
Who will let you
push them around.
'cause it ain't
gonna be me.
I want you to buy it.
why?
Because you miss having some
sort of control over me?
Listen, i'm smart enough
to know that i never had
control over you.
No.  not while
i was working for you.
or shall i say with you?
I was your number-one asset.
We used to laugh at all
those other dickheads.
But you became one
when you threw me out
of the company
that i built.
Look, let's put
the past behind us.
The future is yours.
don't destroy my legacy
out of spite.
Admit that you destroyed
me out of spite,
Out of bitterness
and out of jealousy.
Is that what
all this is about?
you want me to apologize?
Poor hurt little boy
still pines for his
daddy's approval?
I became too big for you
and you couldn't handle it.
No, i couldn't handle
your rotten ego
Or your extraordinary
salary demands.
Bullshit.
So this is why you won't
let me keep my name?
If you don't like it,
you can go find someone else.
No, i don't want
anyone else.
You're the only one who
can take this company forward
for the next 50 years.
- well, then apologize.
- i just did.
It was a mistake
That i kicked you out,
ari, all right?
I was just
feeling unneeded.
Well, you were needed.
Well, you know you're
going to grow old
someday, ari.
Hopefully
you'll find someone
Who'll be able to help
you do it gracefully.
I'll let you
keep your name.
( chuckles )
make it last.
You've got a roomful of people
that are very excited
That you changed
your mind and decided
to come in, johnny.
Well, i'm just glad you guys
are still willing to see me.
Truth is, phil begged
us to see you again.
And i'm--
I'm questioning
the reluctance.
are you not
feeling this role?
- no no no.
- well, what then?
Well, for a minute there
i didn't think i wanted
this anymore.
But then it hit me.
What i don't want anymore
is the rejection.
18 years of it
has taken its toll.
I was on this show
once before.
And i was on another series
for the past 87 episodes.
I've done over 140 guest
spots on tv and other movies,
16 plays, 39 commercials--
Yet still you haven't
seen enough
To just offer me the part.
Still you make me
sing for my supper.
Hey, if you
don't want to...
No, it doesn't matter
if i want to.
I have to.
There you go.
that's the spirit.
Roll this.
do it, johnny.
( shouts )
here we go!
Yeah, they basically gave me
the part in the room, bro.
- yeah?
- yeah, yagota said
i was pitch perfect.
I even got a sincere thumbs up
from that jerkoff director.
You should have stopped caring
a long time ago, johnny.
no shit.
So i guess this means
i'm going to italy alone
then, huh?
Well, i don't have
an official offer and i don't
want to jinx it,
But sorry, bro.
looks like you're solo.
I'm proud of you, johnny.
Thanks, vince.
- later.
I don't know why
you're so angry.
I said i was sorry.
You rejected me,
i feel bad enough.
You should be
used to that by now.
Look, i was wrong,
all right?
The guys told me
you were over me
and i didn't believe them.
and you usually listen to
every word the guys say.
I know.
It's just that even though
we've been apart for
the last three years,
I always believed
that one day i'd have
you, a house, kids.
- you mean we.
- i don't follow.
We would have a house
and kids.
You're a selfish prick.
you follow that?
Why is it so selfish
because i'm trying to tell
you i want to be with you?
Because last time you
convinced me it was forever
And then took off with your
buddies five minutes later.
I'm sorry.
i was trying to get
my business going.
- you took me for granted.
- i know.
Eric, why are you
doing this to me?
Because i love you.
I will not get lured
back into this.
I can't trust you.
You love to have a girlfriend,
but on your terms.
You're never gonna
be able to commit,
not to anyone.
That is not true.
i will commit to you
right now.
- eric, stop.
- i swear to god.
- i'll marry you.
- you'll marry me?
Yes, i will get in that car
right now, drive to vegas
And commit to you
for the rest of my life.
Really?  have you even
thought about this?
Yeah, i have.
And this time
i swear on my life
It'll be forever.
Jesse.
how've you been?
I've been--
Great. i'm back
and you're fired.
- ( paintballs shooting )
- hello all.
No need to run.
your fates have already
been sealed.
- you're safe.
- oh my god.
You're safe,
for now.
Hello, nice to see you.
who's your best client?
Um...
Jesus!
I represent
"jon and kate plus 8."
Where are you, davies?
Ari, i'm already packing
to save myself the indignity.
That's too bad.
Ari, jesus christ!
- have you lost
your mind, ari?
- ( laughing )
Now where's lloyd lee?
Mr. lee knewhat you
were coming, mr. gold.
He decided not to wait
for your arrival.
Now why don't
i believe you?
( gun fires )
Now, lloyd, maybe
you're not here.
maybe you are.
Either way, you have
nothing to fear
Because i'm not
gonna kill you.
i love you.
you see, even though
you betrayed me,
you were the best slave
that i ever had.
I mean, who could
possibly replace
The way that you picked up
my dry-cleaning?
No one.
Who could better the way
you picked up my dog's shit?
And if i liked
short, fat men
Sucking on my dick,
I'm sure that no one could
do it better than you either.
So return to the king
Or exile yourself
From this town forever.
You have until the end
of the day tomorrow
To agree to be
rebranded mine.
( gun firing )
woman:
welcome aboard,
ladies and gentlemen.
Excuse me, ma'am.
If there's a seat left with
an open one next to it,
- i'd love to grab that.
- as would i.
I'm sorry, but i think
the flight is full.
- awesome.
- ( phone rings )
Jamie.  jesus, why
haven't you called me?
- turtle, where are you?
- i'm on my way to you.
I don't want you
to do that.
i don't want
to see other people.
- i can't believe you'd
think that i would.
- turtle.
Excuse me, sir.i'm sorry, ya
have to get off your phone.
- we're preparing
for takeoff, okay?
- just one minute.
- sir.
turtle, please
don't come here.
i know i said you should
see other people because i
don't want you to resent me.
- but i was just being weak.
- weak? how?
The truth is i don't want
to end up resenting you.
Why would you resent me?
Because i could be
gone for a year.
And if the show is successful
i could be gone for five.
So you want to see
other people?
I don't know what i want.
but i've done the long-
distance thing before
And i ended up getting
really really hurt.
and i would never want that
to happen to either of us.
It's not like
i won't come see you.
you've worked so hard this
year to get your life going.
You can't be flying
back and forth to new zealand.
- i can make it work.
- it wouldn't work.
And if we're ever gonna
have a chance in the future,
We shouldn't try.
Wow.
i didn't see this coming.
I really do love you.
Sir, you need to get off
the phone right now.
Okay then.
Turtle, i'm sorry.
Yeah.
( engines powering up )
I've got to get
off this plane.
I've got to get off
this plane.
I'm sorry,
that's not possible.
The door is closed
and we've already pulled
away from the gate.
I can't go to new zealand.
i've got to get off
this plane now.
Sit down.
put your seat belt on.
What if i yell bomb?
Then you can get off
the plane and you can
go straight to jail
And pay a $250,000 fine.
( sighs )
Thank you.
Hey, vince,
we got to roll.
You're gonna
miss your flight.
I'm flying private, johnny.
They won't leave
till i get there.
Oh yeah, i forgot.
- no word from e?
- or turtle.
( phone ringing )
It's phil yagota.
Hey, phil.
give me something
officially great.
John, you blew us all
away at the audition.
Yeah, i know.
you told me that yesterday.
i wanted to tell
you again.
So did i get it or not?
In my mind you did.
- whose other mind is there?
- the network's.
- they didn't like me?
- they did like you.
- but?
- they think you're
too old, john.
- but i'm not.
- well, they think you are.
I didn't shave yesterday.
i could cut my hair.
They're going
younger, john.
I guess they've got to do
what they've got to do.
I've got to tell you,
I thought you were gonna put
up a little more of a fight.
I got no fight
left in me, phil.
- i left it all in that room.
- i know you did, john.
- and so does the network.  -.
in fact, they said
that they think
that you are finally ready
to carry something.
Great.
let me know when
they got something.
They want to start developing
something for you now.
they want to give you
a holding deal and they
want to make sure
that nobody snags you up.
Really?
i've never had a holding
deal before.
Good times ahead, john.
- thanks, phil.
- you got it.
Bye.
They want to develop
something for me to star in.

- johnny, that's amazing.
- yeah.
And even more amazing,
i'm coming to italy.
- ( laughs )
- you got to pack.
I brought some bags
just in case.
A holding deal.
It sucks the guys
are gonna miss this.
It sucks for them.
Thanks for flying.
bye bye.
- thank you.
- any idea how quick
i can get to rome?
You just flew in
from l.a.
Oh yeah, i'm trying
to break the guinness record
For most miles in 24 hours.
what's it to you?
Wow, i didn't really
think you'd show.
- i didn't come for work.
- what did you come for?
I came to tell you
to go fuck yourself.
- watch it, lloyd.
- don't tell me what to do.
And don't you dare
let yourself be convinced
That i betrayed you.
You abused me.
and you won't ever again.
But i will work myself
to the bone
So that someday i will be
in a position to abuse you.
You're not so smart.
how could you be
If you actually believed
i would ever work for
you again?
So you wouldn't work for me
if you were an agent?
Oh, you think
i'll fall for this?
- and then you'll
laugh in my face.
- i'm serious, lloyd.
You just showed me balls
i didn't know you had.
So that speech made you
believe i should be an agent?
I believed it
before you got here.
Terrance apologized to me.
I...
I'm sorry, lloyd.
I still think
you're fucking with me.
Go check your office.
It's supposed to say agent.
( applauding )
Oh.
All right.
Get off.
Vince:
wow, turtle's gonna
meet us in italy.
- drama:
what happened with jamie?
- he didn't say.
What, is damon coming?
Oh, jesus.
what the hell?
- unbelievable.
- hey, matty.
What, are you following me?
No no, pure coincidence.
told you i was going
to cleveland.
You guys know lebron.
he gave up his vacation
for the kids.
Hey, lebron.
hey, big fan, man.
- hey.
- so did you get
the check i sent?
- yeah, i did.
- hope it was enough.
- it wasn't.
You guys are flying
a private to italy, huh?
- must be nice.
- yeah.
- good living.
- and what are you guys
doing here?
Saving the geese from
an untimely death?
We're on a charitable
mission, john.
The jet was donated by marquis
as well as the carbon offset.
- we're good.
- touché.
I want a big fucking
check from you, vince.
- how big?
- what are you making
this year, 20 million?
- ari told me 20 mil.
- yeah, give or take.
And you only gave 10 gs?
That is a little
light, bro.
I didn't know
what was appropriate.
What did you give, lebron?
i'll match it.
- i gave 1 million, vince.
- oh.
- send a buck 50.
- i was gonna say 200,
but that's good.
- that's good.
- yeah?
- it's for the kids.
- done.
- good.
- yo yo.
- hey, yo, e.
Call marvin.
have him write a check for
150 grand to matt's charity,
- okay. hey, guys.
- what's up?
Matty d, lebron,
let's hit it.
- all good?
- as good as always, kenny d.
- let's do it. jimmy edmonds.
let's go.
- later, fellas.
- have a safe flight.
- see you, vince.
- bye, lebron.
- 150 gs?
It's for the kids.
- hey, sloan.
- hey.
- hi, honey.
So where you been, kid?
- long lunch?
- lunch ended yesterday.
- and it was a disaster.
- and yet you have
no luggage?
Duh-duh-duh.
Great mother of god.
- you've got to be kidding me.
- we got engaged.
Wow!
Yeah, i was gonna
marry her but...
We knew you guys
and my dad would kill
us if you missed it.
- and we would have.
- congratulations.
- thanks.
Welcome to the gang.
i wish we could stay
and celebrate.
Audition some bridesmaids,
if you know what i mean.
I promise you will have
plenty of time for that.
So i'm assuming
you're not coming.
Well, no.
Wow, first trip no e.
- we're gonna come
visit though.
- mm-hmm.
You son of a bitch.
congratulations.
- i know you're
gonna kill it, vince.
- no doubt.
Hey, you take
care of that girl,
you lucky bastard.
If you don't,
johnny drama will.
¶ so sentimental... ¶
So are you
regretting this yet?
Not in the slightest.
I know i'm gonna
regret this,
But you if you want
to go with, i understand.
Really?
Yeah.
I love you.
Yo, guys.
wait up.
¶ lisztomania ¶
¶ think less
but see it grow... ¶
I'm kidding.
( laughs )
¶ lisztomania ¶
¶ think less
but see it grow ¶
¶ like a riot,
¶ i'm not easily offended ¶
¶ it's not hard
to let it go... ¶
Wow.
The guy's down
for the count.
Which one of us
do you think will be next?
I have no idea, johnny.
¶ in my lifetime ¶
¶ what's the meaning ¶
¶ what's the meaning
of life? ¶
¶ it's the thought of a ride
that make my eyes wide ¶
¶ i'm caught up,
i'm trying to make ¶
¶ all of my dreams
materialize ¶
¶ so i sorta say my goodbyes
to the straight and narrow ¶
¶ i found a new route,
you about to see my life
change ¶
¶ i make the means
justify the ends ¶
¶ i make the cream materialize
keys to a benz ¶
¶ and so i'm rolling
for now ¶
¶ holding down the fort,
who's controlling? ¶
¶ the grounds
gotta blow 'em ¶
¶ yup, you should've
told 'em ¶
¶ my first felony's
approaching, copped
my first key ¶
¶ took a freeze,
now i'm frozen ¶
¶ i bought a black mac,
i'm outta control ¶
¶ losing bankrolls
on blackjack ¶
¶ you gotta know it always
crossed my mind ¶
¶ that feds be tapping
the lines like gregory hines ¶
¶ still on the phone
discussing my biz like it
could never be mine ¶
¶ i know the price,
know the risk ¶
¶ know the wrongs
and the rights ¶
¶ still my blood flows ice,
it's just my life ¶
¶ what's the meaning ¶
¶ what's the meaning
of life? ¶
¶ in my lifetime ¶
¶ what's the meaning ¶
¶ what's the meaning
of life? ¶
¶ in my lifetime ¶
¶ what's the meaning? ¶
Vince, this is matt damon.
Listen, i just had a really
disturbing phone call
With the foundation.
it's been a week.
I'm in haiti at the moment.
i understand your check
has not come.
It has not come, vince.
don't you fucking
push me, vince.
Don't push me.
send the check.
You do what's right, vince.
You gave me your word.
you gave lebron your word.
Let me tell you something, man.
i never even thought you were
a fucking good actor.
I thought you were terrible.
everything i--
"aquaman,"
"queens boulevard"--
they stink.
They fucking stink.
I can't even believe
that you have money to give
to a foundation.
But the fact is
that you do
And you gave me your word
that you would.
So give me the fucking
check, vince!
I can't believe i have
a fucking academy award
And i am calling you back
Again and again and again,
you cocksucker!
Send me the check!
( sobbing )
Hey, vince.
it's matt.
I'm sorry.
i'm sorry, buddy.
Um, that was really
out of line.
And, um,
i didn't mean that.
I'm just--
i'm just--
I'm just
a little tired, man.
And, uh, i'm sorry.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com