John From Cincinnati Season 1 Episode 10
His Visit: Day Nine (Version NoTV)
Capture: Calamitydan.com
Synch: Gaillots and Toupack
www.Team-NCIS.com
www.All-about-Subs.fr
Haven’t I told you not to leave
your fucking machine on
to spew incomprehensibilities
at passers-by
like a roadside fucking bomb?
I turned it off last night.
Did you turn it off twice?
Which would be back on, because it is.
Did you touch the keyboard or anything?
while I ran my tongue
in and out of the little sockets
on the back of the fucking box.
That’s Butchie’s motel.
Sharp as a tack, you.
Holy shit.
Come on, we got to change you
out of your fucking fatigues…
... or whatever those things are.
Hey, you wait here, John.
Is Shaun all right?
Shaun’s all right.
Here, these won’t fit you
and they’re dirty, but…
… put these on.
Where were you coming
from off the water?
Cincinnati.
You’re up, buddy.
It’s alright, John, go with Butchie.
Take that wetsuit off
and put these on.
No-no-no, w-w-w-wait wait wait.
Shaunie, you ready?
Fine, hurry up man.
Hey chick.
It’s Cass, Kai.
They’re alright. They’re back.
Good. Good.
Thanks for taking care
of him all this time.
I gotta cook.
I’m here with the mother.
I’m here on spec.
Hi mom.
Are you OK?
I’m fine.
Ya I gotta take you
to your Gram’s and Gramp’s, Shaunie.
I wanna stay with John.
Ya well, I want a seal
that barks my name.
You coming?
You stay here, John.
I’ll keep an eye on him.
Thanks.
I’ll come back soon, John.
Yeah, yeah, let yourself in.
Let’s sit down, John.
Shaunie, Shaunie!
He came in
on the water, him and John.
Shaunie's not sure... from where.
Linc's talking to John
to find out what went on.
Linc is?
Hey, Freddy got squat when he tried.
Ya-know, maybe slick will work.
He’s probably
gonna sign him to a deal.
Where have you been, Gramps?
Haven’t you done enough?
Hey, what the hell did she do, Ma?
How much time have you got?
I’ll talk to you later, Shaunie.
I'm glad you're all right.
Thanks, mom.
Come on, I’ll drop you off.
Can you make me
a peanut butter-butter sandwich?
Not tuna?
So…
... I'm the guy that every time
you see, you tell the end is near.
You’re Linc Stark.
You should get in the game.
Like Mitch Yost?
Mitch Yost should get back in the game.
So I’ve never been in the game?
If my words are yours...
... can you hear my father?
Let’s say I can.
Let’s say...
... the zeros and ones in Cass’ camera
help you hear my father’s word.
Cass and I go back.
Let’s say you
and Cass go back, Linc Stark.
Let’s say, in my father’s word,
in Cass’ camera...
... the internet is big.
9/11 is big.
But not every towelhead is eradicated.
Let’s say I don’t follow.
Let’s say...
... without Cass’ camera...
... “big” and “huge” won’t mean dick.
Getting dusted won’t be an issue.
This is me grabbing
my balls and jumping here, John.
Grab your jump-balls, Linc.
You use my words...
... and when you speak them...
... if I listen right,
I can hear your father?
Yes Linc.
If you are the end, I am near you.
Without...
... Cass’ camera,
whatever the fuck that is...
... we’re all toast?
You’re all going to be toast.
We’re coming 9/11/14.
Fuck me, John.
Fuck you Linc.
Is there any special purpose
to us burning
our ass-cheeks off on this asphalt?
I don’t know Butchie instead.
Is my order ready?
Not today.
I order smoothies
for me and the dogs, every day.
And every other day they’re ready
and today they aren’t,
so either piss off
or go behind the counter
and make them yourself.
Technically...
... there’s no way
we can be seeing what we’re seeing.
Hey, ah, back off a sec, will you?
Don't leave town.
I’m staying, and I’m trying
not to give Cissy a heart attack.
I’m all over it, ya know,
what Shaunie was up to with John.
John’s not an asshole,
or he’d know how to take a dump.
Give the guy a tip.
Does your father have a father John?
My father has a father.
What’s your father’s father’s name?
“Father”.
Like George Forman and his kids.
Like George Forman.
Do you know your father’s father?
I know my father’s father’s words.
What are his words?
“Listen to your father.”
That’s what
your father’s father says to you?
That’s what my father’s father
says to my father.
You don’t talk,
you and your father’s father?
We don’t talk.
But he’s alive, your father’s father?
I listen to my father’s words.
Let me ask you something right
from left fucking field, John.
Right from left.
What am I supposed to do?
I mean, tell me
what to do, my brother.
Just spit it right the fuck out.
Five words, maximum,
right now… pow boom!
Maximum, right now, pow boom!
Give me a pound.
No, you give me a pound.
You got some “good ones”?
“They” want to sponsor you?
That does that mean, Shaunie?
Your grandmother’s right.
We deserve to know.
I’d like to move in
with John and Dad.
It's time for me to go.
What are you saying?
You don’t love us?
We did a horrible job?
What?
You know I have that pack
with the liner for wetsuits, out back.
That’s OK, Gramps. I’m good.
- Hey.
- What are you talking about?
I – you know
maybe it is time.
You’re sending Shaunie
to live with Butchie and
that asshole just ran off with him?
How can you be that fucking thick?
He should be here, for Christ’s sake,
where we can watch him.
He was here, Cissy,
he was here,
you were here. you had
Bill and Freddy out front.
I love you Gramps.
I love you Gram.
I’m gonna hop over the fence.
Get back down here!
Could you turn off the fan?
How’s Shaun, Butchie?
My mom and dad are pissing in his ear.
Do you have a mother, John?
My mother is my father.
My mother’s a cunt with earflaps.
Your mother has turned herself
into the worst ball-buster
known to man so no one
would be around her,
and she wouldn’t have to be afraid
she’d do something like that again.
That’s how ashamed of herself she was.
Mitch wipes out.
Mitch wipes out Cissy.
Cissy shows Butchie how to do that.
What the fuck, John?
Butchie hurts Barry’s head.
Mr Rollins comes in Barry’s face.
We are all frail vessels.
John is going all “psychic hotline
on us, huh?
Can I crash with you and John, Dad?
You can crash with me.
He keeps running his mouth,
John may be hospitalized by then.
What’s up with the flak suits,
my brother?
That’s what they came back wearing.
Showing up in camouflage?
John spouting,
“The end is near. 9/11 is big”
liable to push some
people’s buttons, Shaunie.
They want to sponsor us.
Who wants to sponsor you?
What the fuck’s going on, John?
Where the fuck did you guys go?
Hey, hey, hey, talk to Shaunie.
I’ll talk to John.
That sounds like a fucking plan.
Butchie hurt my tit.
It’s yours,
I picked it up by accident.
If it had rang, would you
have wanted me to answer it?
No.
It rang, I answered.
Moana’s coming, landed in San Diego.
Should I get the tools from the trunk?
He called ahead…
True…
Should I be strapped in my person,
on my room?
On the ear,
I can recognize the drift of things.
Let it play out.
Didn’t they used to have
bibles in these places?
Yeah, Gideons…
big distributor.
Don’t you understand, Shaunie?
This shit’s freaking me out.
You disappear with your mom…
- We went to SeaWorld.
- I know you went to SeaWorld
and mom brought you back.
But John told some people
that you were gonna be gone.
And before you came back,
everybody was already freaked out.
And then your mom brought you back,
and the next morning,
you’re fucking gone again.
I was with John.
It’s where you went with John, Shaunie,
that’s got everybody’s shorts in a bunch.
I don’t know.
So that has everyone worried that he half
hypnotized you or some fucking thing.
They had some pretty fun ones.
You remember that?
Sort of.
You remember they want to sponsor you.
I sort of remember.
What does “sort of” mean, Shaunie?
I remember to say it.
The waves were good.
Were the waves on water?
- I don’t know.
- Jesus Christ!
What did they do to you Shaunie?
Where the fuck did you go?
Cincinnati.
Cincinnati’s that way.
The sky’s up there.
Where’s your friend,
the fucking chemist?
At the Alternative Apothecary.
Who are you calling?
Bill Jacks.
You need to be watched, Mitch.
You always needed that.
Bill Jacks, can I help you?
Great news, Bill. Shaunie’s home.
Can you come over?
Thanks a lot.
Well, where are you going?
Errands.
Let’s say you’re not
from around here, John.
Let’s say I’m not, Linc.
Chocolate, vanilla…
Everyone’s from somewhere,
so you’re not from here.
On the other hand,
finding out you’re not from here
is a bit of a nut-nudge
for us earthlings.
I can’t imagine
your old man wouldn’t know that.
my old man wouldn’t know that.
So that’s your father’s point…
with the camo and stuff?
Scare our balls off?
You hear my father’s words.
You hear them better in Cass' camera.
Who’s supposed to see this, John?
You hear my father’s words, Linc.
Me?
Your fuckin’ father’s
on the fuckin’ ceiling.
Fine.
Come here, Shaunie.
Something’s fucked
at the house, I’ll check in.
Here, hook up!
Meet the Jetsons!
I wanna give you an address...
... you meet me here...
... and bring the tailor.
Why... why don’t
we just pull you down, Dad?
No!
What’s the difference if the ceiling
keeps you from flying off or we do?
Look, I want
as little complication as possible.
I need to know what this is about.
What about
the complications for us, Mitch?
Worrying you'll piss on our heads
every time we walk under you?
You could tell me about
where you went, Gramps.
Well, I can…
I can… I can do that from here.
Oh yeah? Then why aren’t you, Dad?
Just get out, get out.
Don’t look. Just…
Going to the restroom.
Men!
There’s a parade this afternoon
down at the pier for Shaun and John.
3:30, 4-o’clock.
Don’t be no-shows. You’re in it.
Our own celebratory barbeque, Ramon,
is thus somewhat impinged upon.
You guys!
You’re the island contingent!
We could take this stuff
to wherever the parade’s at.
No way to paint
this pattern on more wetsuits.
In the 2 hours, you mean,
before we put the play on in the barn?
The logo I could do.
Barbeque’s been 86’d, Dickstein.
The surf guy is having
a parade down by the pier, 3:30.
All right, Linc,
so as his personal manager now,
with Shaun back
from the dead and outer space too…
... and-and-and assuming
he’s signed you too?
I – I assume
you’ve signed “Ming of Mars”?
Your idea for the skit
in the barn is like,
"Stinkweed,
it's face on all this…"
“A miracle…"
"... half our base runs the other way.
Do we make that up selling at shrines?”
All right, so you tell him
something that I said to you
and I’m supposed to think, like,
“Whoa, he just came up with that.”
Then I’m supposed to like
wet my pants and OK the street fair?
“If I get you to Tijuana,
the kid can hear our confession.”
Something I didn’t say to him.
“Do you want me
to write you another check?”
Something I didn’t say to her
that he could have heard
on her tape recorder.
“What room is she in?”
- Do the t-shirts.
- Stinkweed logos on the wetsuits.
We need an El Camino.
Who’s logo is this?
“Mind your own fucking
business incorporated”.
I want to see that logo,
everywhere we set up.
In 2 hours?!
Amazing he can do
design work while up on a cross.
Whoever John is fronting for,
he calls him his father.
I’m guessing if his father wanted,
we’d all be good and fucked by now.
So you guess his old man’s
got plans for the Yosts?
He talked to me
before he talked to Mitch.
So his... father’s got
plans for you too?
I’m a salesman. I’m guessing
he wants me to sell the family.
Through Stinkweed?
Isn’t that how we built the brand...
seeing the winners early?
May I tell you
something about my bears?
Absolutely.
They were what my eyes
opened to this morning,
there on the floor beside my mattress
in my otherwise unappointed bedroom.
Nice.
They were just as I had situated them...
... before I laid my head to pillow.
Nothing untoward
had transpired in the darkness.
“My God”, I thought...
... “they’re just 2 bears
doing what bears do.”
I didn’t see Freddy’s teddy
and wonder how hard he may have violated
my Teddy the night before, or...
... how many times
he may have called Teddy “Faggot”,
or “cocksucker”, or “Sissy Mary”.
I chose to believe they played nicely…
Live and learn.
And I choose to do so still...
... even in their proximity
to the flame.
I’m standing
so they don’t get sparked on.
Tell the queer I don’t like
those bears sitting together.
That's your opener.
Then ask if him and the beaner
are wearing them clothes to the parade.
Go… go ahead.
We’re talking we’re talking.
You're listening, now you're listening.
Look at the bears for a second.
Look at the bear, look at the bear.
Hey? That’s good. Hey, you wearin’
them clothes to the parade?
I thought I would.
Fine.
Aren’t these parade-appropriate?
Dickstein had a life-changing
experience, why he’s been out of touch.
He’s wearing those.
We all right?
What did he say about the bears?
Segregated...
whenever they’re indoors.
Cherry Oldies, 8th and Palm.
Cherry Oldies, 8th and Palm, what?
Has an El Camino.
Then we better go check the fucker out.
Over there. Over there.
Miss, Miss, I told you once
about the Kodak.
Fuckin please... Not at us.
Stare me down. Stare me down!
You want a picture.
You want a picture?
Take a fuckin’ picture… of me, not him.
I'm taking a picture
of the entire scene, my brother.
All the zeros and ones...
That’s how I work.
Fuckin’ ball-buster.
Can we please get ready for Moana?
Kinda cute.
She just called you a zero.
I feel that you boys
are ready for this Camino.
Fuckin lug nuts on a T-Bird.
Between the two of us, we own
more cars than you have on this lot.
My guess
is your feeling’s probably right.
That’s not what I mean by ready...
number of vehicles owned.
What do you mean, pops?
We gots to boogie.
So I have to know
what I mean before I can have a feeling?
Do I have to know
that you’ll understand me?
Do you have to know
you’ll understand before you’ll listen?
25 cars between you?
You shoulda let me
sit down before you told me.
I’ve got that many dealerships
in each of that many sectors,
and brands on goddamn franchise.
I gotta boogie! Me!
He feels you’re ready for the Camino.
You’re off-line now, country.
I don’t know Butchie instead.
How’s he for high-performance?
And he ain’t who’s worst under-powered.
Intrusions, evanescences…
I’m a shepherd,
without crook or understanding!
Fits and stops and starts,
waves and ripples and ramifications!
Busted knee, mother-son handjobs.
Christ, Jesus Christ, Jesus Christ!
Crosses… and shoulders to bear ‘em.
El Camino! $15,000, as is!
Is it gassed?
Fuckin’-A right it’s gassed. Linc.
You and your 25 cars.
Circle and line on the wall,
and zeros and goddamn ones is
what to turn the both of your gifts to…
… and not one damn minute to waste!
Ragheads are gonna get
themselves eradicated.
Country...
... I took you off-line.
Manuel!
Get a cage on this thing!
So how was the flight?
It was good, you know, fair.
Got sick?
Small kind, not really.
What then?
Terrible fuckin' hurricane, tsunami?
What the fuck
you talkin’ about? Where?
Five days since we spoke,
maybe they had them at the airport.
Clear skies, brah.
Maybe you spent them
turning over and over,
“What’s he talking about,
this haole fuck..."
"... pretending to give me something?”
Maybe you spent them…
”He musta got old
fuckin’ fast over there,"
"thinks he gonna move on me,"
"confusing me for some other kanaka."
"Maybe handle his shit for him
before he handles mine for me.”
You know I got to think about that.
But you didn’t come in her blazing…
Come on, Freddy, you raised me up.
So I know you didn’t travel alone.
You cocksuckers always need
someone to work for.
Tell the Chinaman,
“Freddy’s got 17 safe deposits.”
Tell him, “He’ll take
a taste for three years,
but all he wants is out.”
But…
before you talk to him,
if you eat something strange
that puts a brain in
your fuckin’ head, Moana,
tell the Chinaman…
to go fuck himself,
and ask me for the keys on your own.
I got them, I got the fish.
Jake Ferris, Stinkweed.
Can anyone throw me a bone?
Who’s ride would this be now?
Has Shaun Yost been found or not?
There may be some news on that.
We’re putting something
together for you guys soon.
Is that Tina Blake?
Can I get some rhythm?
She’s part of my private life.
This ain’t the time
to break you’re his mother.
Think of a place we’re going.
There’s a fence around back,
we could climb over.
Brah,
try take your glasses off.
Having it where we can see,
that’s the Chinaman asking to negotiate.
They’re already in the car.
Askin’ to negotiate with me…
…volunteering to off Moana.
That kid better be more than half-smart.
So what’s the buggah bulai to you?
Brah,
I think the buggah like me take
over his turf in Hawaii.
What?
How come?
I don’t know. Maybe he had
a vision or something. I don’t know.
Fucking mahu.
So what?
He like give you his business?
So you can come and give ‘em back to me?
Brah,
I don’t give nothing to nobody.
If anything, I take.
Ah, Moana.
You remember small kid time?
I used to hang you over the roof
so you can break in to
the window and rob the house?
You trust me then, right?
Yeah, but that was hanabaddah days.
That was then, this is now.
And you know what?
I may be pupule,
but I ain’t no lolo.
I never say you was lolo.
So what?
What?
What you like me do now?
I don’t know, I think mo’ bettah
you hele back to Hawaii.
Let me figure out
what’s really going on.
How’s that sound?
OK brother,
I’ll go hele back,
but remember one thing:
we go back a long long way brother.
Remember,
you and I,
we ohana.
Yeah.
What, I can throw my glasses
back on or what?
Shoot.
All right.
Aloha.
Aloha no, brother.
Drove off.
The Chinaman.
Moana walked away on foot.
Let’s go to the parade.
You bring your cellphone
with you, definitely.
He won’t be using no cell phone.
One way or another, he’ll be comin’.
What do you want here?
This.
Times Square, new year’s eve…
only thing missing’s the ball…
which could be him in there.
This…
- Shaun…
- We sell it
as a Stinkweed drumroll,
hype for the Yost Family signing…
All the Yosts in Stinkweed gear,
tremendous coming-out party.
What about John?
He’s your student,
you made me sign him.
Fold him into the family package.
It lays down cover, Mitch,
for whatever’s going on,
as long as it’s going on.
None of those flesh-eaters
know about me yet.
You ever plan on going outside?
Do I assume no permits were secured?
Stinkweed’s a good citizen of I.B...
We’ve got one to set up in the park.
If you took your hat off indoors,
you might realize I was
I was referring to traffic control.
Form up adjacent to the surf shop
and I’ll lead your vehicles in.
Back in the game, Mitch Yost.
Stare me down!
I guess you’re back.
The staging area that
I had designated was closed.
I tried to get some citizens
to move their cars.
We got a report that you were
intimidating customers.
I wasn’t intimidating customers!
Ask her!
I have coffee in there every day.
And now I’m in cuffs,
for Christ’s sakes!
You want to make yourself useful?
Cite him!
Because those things cut
the legs out from under oldsters.
Just when you think things can’t
get worse, the man with the dog.
It’s the albatross around my neck.
Mr Mandatory retirement.
What the fuck is this circus?
I’m on my way to the vet…
This is obstruction of a peace officer.
We’re peace officers!
And you’re retired.
Look at the vehicles.
This situation is deteriorating
by the second.
Excuse us officers, we have a limited-use
permit for an event hear the pier.
They had a permit,
and my strategy was
to stage the vehicles here
Why stage the vehicles here
if the event is three blocks away?
Why now just go there?
Listen, gives these guys an escort,
get them off the fuckin’ street
and set up down there.
Because your poodle’s
late for his haircut?
Dog has a fulminating fungus on his pad.
Hey Tina,
I’m the guy that jerks off to your tapes!
Shut up, you perv!
How would you like to suck
her ex-husband’s dick?
Yeah, see if you can tell the world
what a useful life you’ve led
with that kind of mouthful!
You perv-dick-mouthful 24!
Go ahead, you’ll be lead through!
Follow the police officers!
You’ll be led through.
Lead them through!
Go on through, you’re being
led by the police officers,
the cocksuckers that forgot
to take my cuffs off!
Go on through,
go on. Here’s a drug casualty…
thinks this car’s normal.
Go ahead, it’s the homosexual
in the hybrid… go on!
You’re being led through.
Look at the breasts on these women!
This country is doomed!
But go ahead, have fun!
Low rent and half-assed…
hardcore Stinkweed.
But we always roll with
the lovely Stinkweed ladies!
We got some free t-shirts right here.
Ladies, throw them out!
Check out the new design.
Come to the booth.
Check out the new Stinkweed logo!
Hey press, don’t forget to take
these gift baskets on the way out.
If you don’t take ‘em,
Jake won’t be able to write them off.
Take a good look ma.
We’re them now.
If I look familiar,
probably some time in your life
you’ve seen Linc Stark’s car
getting detailed.
Link Stark,
founded Stinkweed!
Our C.E.O. and in-house visionary.
Linc’s got plans and
he’s here to tell you all about them.
And I guarantee you, they’re big!
Standing down here,
at surfhenge because they do not want
to be on the same stage as me…
Linc’s going to sell the family.
… ladies and gentlemen…
Cissy and Mitch Yost!
Tina Blake…
the name might be familiar
to some of you.
Butchie Yost!
Somebody check that man for a weapon.
Shaun Yost!
Butchie’s new surfing discovery,
Johnny Monad from Cincinnati!
Stinkweed,
a wing and a prayer
until we signed Butchie Yost
15 years ago.
Butchie Yost put Stinkweed on the map,
and we did all we could
to help Butchie crash and burn.
‘Cause business is business.
In our business,
we sell crash-and-burn
like Ford sells tough.
You got a hankie?
Time passes,
I see Butchie Yost’s son surfing.
Shaun Yost surfs like an angel,
and when I pitch it
to Mitch and Cissy Yost,
they agree to let Shaun sign with me
because it’s what he wants.
And maybe I make a promise
that I won’t do the same thing
with Shaun that I did with Butchie.
Huntington Beach,
Shaun goes down.
Sorry Cissy,
sorry Mitch.
Do not think for a second,
no matter what he says,
that the leopard will ever
change his spots.
Stinkweed markets Shaun’s sprained neck
as a miracle journey
back from death by surfing’s
new young superstar.
Shaun and John go AWOL surfing,
the leopard decides to sell it
as a disappearance.
He calls the grandparents,
gets them all freaked out.
They call the media,
tell ‘em Shaun’s missing.
Shaun and John come home.
Cissy and Mitch are down on the leopard.
Butchie wants to bust a cap in his ass.
Some people just will not see
the business angle.
Which is how and why
the leopard is here before you now.
The Yosts have thrown
a collar on the cat.
They’re making him climb in a cage.
They will stay with Stinkweed
only if I get out.
Stinkweed lays down cover for my father.
I’m out folks! Jake Ferris,
the new C.E.O.
Linc is El Camino.
We will never do bad again.
Linc Stark, ladies and gentlemen.
Get off my fucking foot
or I’ll kill you.
Look…
other side.
Talk or get the fuck out of here.
Brah,
give me the keys.
Check out the new wetsuits,
Stinkweed’s new design.
Dr Smith comes back 20 years
younger from Cincinnati.
Cissy gets knocked up.
She’s bigger than Leona Helmsley.
Earth puts Dickstein on retainer.
Daphne keeps his head straight.
Jerri meets a slew of new hairlips.
My father four-walls Barry’s bar.
Dr Smith trains Dwayne and Ramon.
My father freelances in Cass’ Camera.
Saying I’d not climb those stairs again
or come back in this room…
I guess now you know I’m a fibber.
Why I came up here, sweetheart…
that son of the Yost boy…
Butchie who helped you
with your groceries?
His son went missing.
The long and short of it, Shaun…
Butchie’s son…
safely returned.
Happy outcome.
On the downside,
the green one’s gone.
I was remiss,
trotting him places outside the house.
Although I’ll say,
first excursion out
I took him to the hospital.
It was a…
worthwhile visit.
See, this is why…
this is why I don’t come up here.
Where do you start and stop?
Every event and incident…
“Oh, if she could have only seen this!
Wouldn’t she have laughed
to have seen that?”
If I took the mouth-harp
to hand to come up with,
I’d have never made it up the stairs,
or I’d play to you.
Here I go down.
God love you, my Lo’,
and hold you tight.
Lois…
Lo’,
look at this!
Mother of god, Cass-Kai.
www.Team-NCIS.com
www.All-about-Subs.fr