capture:frm@maoren sync:frm@frm
Resynch : Team-NCIS.com
Hey, old man!
I didn't realize
I was this far down.
I kept catching
those really long rights.
Keep doing that and
you'll end up in rosarita.
I didn't mean to intrude.
It's a long walk back.
My car is here
if you want a ride.
You should watch your feet.
I stepped on a syringe here yesterday.
Yeah, welcome
to the slooze.
Who's that chick?
Is she a fan of yours?
All my fans are
in retirement homes.
Mitch Yost, you probably
don't remember me,
but I met you once.
Pipe masters.
I was 15,
and I got to tell you
I had a big crush.
- My name is cass.
- Give me a fucking break.
I didn't notice, huh?
I was still knock-kneed
with braces.
Well, everything changes.
Yeah, I make movies now.
Thanks anyways, pop. I'm
gonna walk and get some air.
- All right, Kal.
- Nice car, chick.
These are hard to find.
I like vintage. What can I say?
So, I'm doing this film.
It's called "legends".
i would love to shoot you for it.
I know this really isn't
your kind of thing,
but you know my name
and you've got my number.
Just think about it.
Bill jacks.
Why'd I hang up? I got
tired of being held on hold.
Good thing I'm not
being robbed here.
I'm looking into a nut job,
as certain if he's wanted or missing.
I got his prints here.
I want him lifted.
Why am I calling ahead?
Well, anderson, that's
to avoid standing there
like a mope with my hat in my
hand someplace I worked 16 years
while my request
is walked through channels.
What are the prints on?
You ask me that, I think maybe you haven't
tried the water fountain this morning.
Because being the nutjob drank
from the station house fountain
yesterday, anderson.
His prints are on the fucking handle
which I am in fucking possession of.
Hey, you know what?
Fuck you.
Where are you gonna drink?
Try the toilet.
And while you're in there,
go fuck yourself.
But you really ought to be doing is
updating the goddamn bulletin board!
Preparation for the celebration
of the millennium
was a goddamn disgrace.
16 fucking years.
How did you sleep?
I slept, you know?
You know, I do know that I'm
not feeling dope-sick right now.
What are you doing? You got
to take a horrendous dump too?
Because I got to take
a horrendous dump, pal.
I got to take
a horrendous dump.
Fuck.
Firsties on the can. I got the face.
Damn, but make it quick, all right?
Drop your pants. Ass on
that seat, baby, and push.
I gots to go.
Come on.
Oh, shit. Are you shy about
doing your business, John?
I'm shy about
doing my business.
Shit, I haven't seen you dump
or take leak since you got here.
Do you want me
to step outside?
I don't know Butchie instead.
Hey, we all have
our quirks and wrinkles, pal.
It is all good.
Jojo got through his heat.
Anyways.
Shaunie Yost.
I got your demo, man.
it rocks.
It's about Shaun, and the event
at huntington.
give me two minutes
to tell you what I can do.
Well, hurry up.
Mitch will be home
any minute.
What's shaking, Ramon?
Dickstein said
new owner's coming over.
Strapped like
he was yesterday?
Should be relevant to you, since
you're supposed to be gone now.
You dumped out, John?
I'm dumped out.
Stand up and pull your pants up.
The kid's turn
on the crapper.
There you go.
Come on.
Do that outside.
I got to go.
Here.
Park it right here, my man.
Good, well done.
A- plus on
the fume-control, pal.
Radio silence now, John
until further notification.
this is a dump that a
grown man can be proud of.
What the hell are you doing here?
You need to hear him.
Shaun's back in at huntington.
You muscled him in.
yeah, that's
the way it goes, Shaunie.
You miss your heat...
as long as you can hear the
money talk, you got no problem.
You just sign up with the man,
get the sponsor's push,
win yourself a Hummer.
Just this once, Mitch,
think what Shaun wants.
You know, I was a grom
just like you once.
always in the water.
totally stoked 24/7.
I felt like I was tapping
into something bigger.
and I'll tell you, a lot of people can
paddle out there and get that rush,
but to be able to give them a
taste of it just by watching...
No, that's something different.
And I never had that.
Not like you and your dad...
and your grandpa.
But I could see that people would pay
to see those who could do it.
And I made some money.
And I made some mistakes.
Your dad was one of them.
I was young, he was changing the sport.
All I could see was that him being
a bad boy was good for business.
I thought the image was the thing.
What I see now...
What's taken me
years to see...
Is the thing itself...
that's the thing.
And I don't have to show
them any more than that.
To get them to buy the thing
that you want to sell them.
Well what if I'm selling
them the thing for itself?
I think you're a fucking saint.
Well, I got all the money I need, Cissy.
Yeah, well, that makes
it a little easier.
It's the way
some of us need it.
Does that rule me off the team?
I'd like to compete.
I like it.
If you feel me going
off with Shaun, just tell me.
I would be grateful to hear it.
No image.
Just him and some really great waves.
So huntington's crossed-up swell.
What do you think?
You want to try the new stick.
I might try it.
A day like this,
if you can get the dealer's
ass out of bed,
the pier's a nice place to cop a fix.
Let's get the dealer's ass out of bed.
We're not here to score, my brother.
Although I can't say why
I'm not getting dope-sick.
Found your man, frat boy?
Comfy cozy, sweet pea.
How didn't I figure you two
would know each other?
We don't. I drove him over
to your place yesterday.
I never got high overseas
like I needed to get after that ride.
Did you come in through the slooze?
And don't go over the railing!
I came in from the slooze and
I won't go over the railing, Butchie.
Is that where you picked him up?
You think he may
be a mexican?
I'm trying to get
a line on him, joe.
Why do you think I needed
to fire up that fatty?
My old man levitated.
I'm not feeling sick. John,
what the hell is going on?
John, you can be honest
with me, man.
tell me what's going on.
John, tell me what
the fuck is going on.
What are you looking
at out there, John?
What do you see?
What do you want, Butchie?
Come on, Pal. We'll figure it all out.
Joe, smoke another fatty, baby.
So he said to meet here
in the office?
Specifically insidethe office.
Seemed in good spirits when he called.
Yesterday too until
he pulled out his gat.
- Buenos dias, Ramon.
-Buenos dias.
And a hearty shalom,
attorney dickstein.
Hot from the panaderia.
- Oh, thank you.
- Empanadas,
churros, coffee.
I see you drink tea.
Si, antioxidant.
Also, I bear news
that the motel will not be leveled.
Is that so?
It is so, Ramon.
I had a vision, gentlemen.
That how you got the numbers
for the jackt?
In fact, Ramon, yes.
I often get visions after my seizures.
Eventful days like yesterday
do tend to bring them on.
Teddy and I had quite the siege.
The next drawing is on tuesday.
I looked it up.
No numbers in last
night's vision, Ramon.
I am called, among other things,
to learn to surf.
I have the perfect board
for you to learn on.
Ain't you glad now you didn't
blow your brains out yesterday?
Motel is closed.
Change in ownership.
Butchie Yost.
He went out, Butchie.
He's in number F.
You could leave it on the door,
if you want to leave a message.
I'll give it to him
when he shows up.
Pastry while you wait?
Why raise a building
for what its walls have seen?
Why not imagine
it's shuttered saloon
as some homier place
of entertainment?
Renovate the guest rooms.
Upgrade,
liberate them.
Why not?
Room 24.
Excuse me.
It's his join.
He looks like the bowzer
guy from Sha Na Na.
It's okay.
No, no, no, no.
- Yeah.
- It's Shaun, Bill.
Hey, Shaun, come on in.
Give me a hand here. I'm just about
to clean these cages.
Guess what?
You found a dinosaur egg.
I'm back in the contest.
Is that so?
That contest at huntington
I missed yesterday.
This guy is getting me back in.
- My heat's in two hours.
- Jesus, that doesn't leave us much...
My gram and gramps are taking me.
- Is that so?
- This guy talked to them.
We left my dad a message.
Maybe he'll come too.
- Good, fine.
- You want to go up there with us?
- My gram and gramps are right outside.
- Right outside?
Jesus, Shaun.
No, I can't.
This is a family outing.
This is...
This is a family thing. I can't go.
No, you go ahead.
Bill's not coming.
- Well there's that.
- Thanks anyway.
- I'll cheer him on from down here.
- That's all right, Bill.
- We understand.
- I got to get after the accumulation.
They're crap machines.
My birds, they're crap machines.
You do good, Shaunie.
Drive safe.
Good for them.
Maybe Shaun's ne'er-do-well father
and his jerk-off sidekick
will go up there too.
That would be nice.
She's like the kid's second mother.
I can't believe she saw you
hit on Mitch this morning.
You know, linc,
I actually do make films.
That's the trick, that's what you're supposed
to make her think you're here for.
Arguably, it is what
I'm doing here.
Is it... Arguably?
I'll see you at huntington.
Yeah, you'll see me, but
you won't fucking talk to me.
Yeah, and for christmas, I was thinking
i could either run you over
in the street or enroll you in
a tony robbins seminar.
I guess you and young einstein are out.
Anyway, so Cissy just called,
and she must have spiked
Mitch's wheat germ.
He's letting Shaun surf
in the contest at huntington.
I bet Shaun would like it
if you went up there.
I'm not going. I'm hip-deep
in customers here.
Huntington, shit-for-brains.
Did you get Mitch
in your porsche?
you show him how
the gear box worked?
I make movies.
I want to make one about Mitch.
It's obvious that he respects you a lot,
although it's not as obvious
as you and I getting off on
the wrong foot this morning.
No sale, chick.
Mitch's wife just called Cissy.
Shaun's in an event at huntington.
First time Mitch
ever let him enter.
Well, maybe I'll go.
Yeah, maybeI'll go too.
You know, that family's got
enough of their own problems, but
can't we all still do our
little parts to make them worse?
I'll tell you something.
And I'm not a frightened
person by nature...
But I'm afraid
here suddenly.
I'm feeling a real...
Genuine frightened feeling.
Something's behind me or whatever
the hell might be going on.
I'm afraid here to even
turn around and look.
isn't that
something, zip?
Brother.
Is that you, Lois?
Is that you, honey?
I wish she'd
come to me.
She used to come
to me in dreams.
Barry:
the motel is haunted.
at least room 24
is haunted.
You had mentioned you had an
unpleasant experience there.
It was all one
in my mind.
Time flies when
you're having fun.
Mega millions are not the broom
to sweep
room 24 clean.
Must I say for me?
Isn't "for me" understood?
You're getting
a little hard to follow.
Not for Gilbert Rollins.
He can do it dead.
Well, you're with us now.
- you don't have to go in that room no more.
- fuck room 24.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- No, it's okay.
I woke up
this morning happy.
I mistook that freedom
for power.
Ghost showed you
what was what.
Yes.
Yes, Ramon.
Our visions are powerless
against our pasts.
Happiness is helpless
in passing.
Please, god.
Help me live.
I forgive gilbert rollins.
I forgive Butchie Yost.
Thank you for my friends.
- Amen.
Amen.
You don't think that's
going through, Marco,
because he's hanging with Butchie.
and if he's hanging with
Butchie, he ain't juiced.
He's juiced.
I am hanging
with a man of means.
This is my brother
from another mother
from the side of the family
with some cheese.
And if that doesn't
go through, this will.
And that ain't my cock!
You are in for
a big surprise, Marco.
That's right!
That's right, ladies.
The line forms to my left to blow me.
The line forms to Butchie's left.
Okay, just to see how much
fuel we have in this rocket,
I will take half of the...
No, I will take
the whole row of Chivas Regals.
Could we try my dad again?
Sure we can.
Can I call him?
Then why don't we
get out of the car
and bang our heads on that lamp
post until the light changes?
Do not fall in love with
the cardboard models, John.
Papercuts on the penis...
very painful.
Wait till the...
no no no no.
Jesus, John.
What the fuck?
Okay, follow my lead.
I say this from the bottom of my
heart, brother, and with all the love
but I'm picking up you don't do
too well with traffic, do you?
I don't do too well with traffic.
Which leads me to believe...
Come on, come on, come on.
Quick, follow me.
Leads me to believe that
you're not from around here.
- I'm not from around here, Butchie.
- Oh yeah, no?
Or any other metropolis
for that matter.
I'm feeling kind of a,
you know, small town.
Not a farm town, but a small town.
A small town like, you know,
I'm feeling a little Cincinnati.
- I am from Cincinnati!
- Get the fuck out.
- You get the fuck out.
The housing brain unit's
open 24 hours, baby.
Linc, this is bullshit.
My kid earned his spot in this round.
What is this?
What this is, Mr. Dolan,
is your son's main sponsor,
who is about to send him and
you on a mag trip to Sumatra,
is saying tommy had to take
one for the team.
Yeah, okay, team is one thing.
But Butchie Yost's kid,
that's something else.
You're not gonna let me be polite?
you do not get a vote
about Shaunie Yost.
You get to vote on whether
or not you pass on Sumatra.
That's the horn for the junior finals.
Remember it's 30 minutes
for each surfer.
The three highest
scoring waves count.
First to surf is in yellow.
Nice turn over the top.
That's Shaun Yost
picking one up on the outside.
Looks like a party wave out there.
Oh yeah, that could
be interference on red.
Watch this.
Yeah, Shaunie!
Your kid sticks one like that,
you come back and piss in my ear.
One thing for certain, these kids
definitely know how to handle them.
Nice turn, cut back.
And he's milking that one
all he can.
He's got it won.
Right? Hands down.
Unless they're completely fucking blind.
Here we go.
I could throw one down tonight.
Get off my girl, Johnny monad.
What the fuck?
Wait here, John. Wait here.
Hey, Freddy, did I get
teleported to fucking hawaii or...
Motherfucker!
What's that you say,
Butchie, huh?
You're gonna drown me
in a cop tsunami?
Or whatever faggot threat
you left on my machine?
That call was a mistake.
No, that call was
a fucking favor to me.
It reminded me of what
a fuckup you turned into,
instead who I watched surf rocky point.
I was pissed off you beat me
on the fucking buy.
You got no business
buying a lid of smack.
I got a fucking injury settlement.
I was looking to make a move.
It's not like I got many left.
Fuck your sad story, Butchie.
You'd have od'ed and died
before you sold your third bag.
What are you looking at, big eyes?
You want some of that?
- I want some.
- yeah?!
Freddy, he ain't all there!
Well, now he's there even less.
Don't fucking hit him anymore.
It's just an earthquake,
John. It happens all the time.
What do you want, Butchie Yost?
You'll remember, to expedite closing,
you had me waive
the physical inspections.
I absolve you if the walls tumble down.
Oh, boy.
Oh, what the hell is going on now?
Anderson, hey, Bill Jacks.
Hey, did you guys feel
a temblor over there just now?
No, because I felt like
i just felt a temblor.
All right, Anderson!
Oh, a socal tremor there.
Dude, I felt that.
Big fucking earthquaker !
Wave of the day, the judges
are doing the boogaloo
'cause of a little
fucking earthquake.
You had it won already, bro!
I think they missed it.
Well, if they didn't miss
the entire heat, he's fine.
He's not up.
He's not up. He didn't come up.
He never came up!
Shit!
Look at you swinging, Zip.
It was a temblor.
Seems minor.
Minor temblor.
And the old man's still got his marbles.
Do you find that your emotions
are getting the best of you?
I would say so.
I mean, when she pushed me...
We're closed.
Instead of what you want to see,
see what the fuck is
in front of you.
It's how you get 17 safe deposits.
Fuck you surfing rocky point!
Fuck watching you
from my fucking porch.
Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt.
- Phone call for Butchie.
- Yeah?
You piece of shit! What's
with your fucking phone?
The battery died.
- Yeah, what a shock.
- Uh, no hurry.
Whenever he's done...
Phone, just...
Is that what you called to talk
to me about, my fucking phone?!
Shaunie broke his neck at huntington.
- Is he gonna be all right?
- He broke his neck!
They're airlifting him
to mercy hospital.
Of course, if you gave
any kind of shit,
I wouldn't have to be telling you
this 'cause you would've been here.
What the fuck you talking about, he's at
huntington? Nobody fucking told me dick!
Your battery's dead.
What, you couldn't drive four
fucking blocks out of your way
- To come down here and tell me?
- Why,
'cause you've never been anywhe
for anybody? Why waste the gas?
So what are you saying, dad?
Is he gonna die?
Go ahead out for pizza.
I can leave word with
the manager.
What's going on?
Come on, John. We're gonna take a ride.
Garage door Tijuana, Freddy, to cop.
And you better not try and stop me
unless you're ready to fucking kill me.
Look, my kid got hurt.
He broke his neck.
- I can't handle it straight.
- I'm holding.
Get in the car.
Go get the dope and bring it back to me.
Get in the car
or I'll shoot you,
him and the three guys
in the fucking office.
What do you want ?
I didn't drop a dime on you,
if you're thinking about
killing me in that car.
Go ahead, go.
Well, they seem
to have worked it out.
His father said
his son had an accident...
Butchie.
They make these fucking
cars for midgets.
I hate coming to this fucking country.
Sunset beach, the kid you
used to put on your back
and paddling out to for
him to watch from the channel...
That's the one broke his neck now?
It's the only one
i know I got, Freddy.
Some fucked-up shit.
I thought of that on the way
to the airport this morning.
That is some fucked-up shit.
Then till now I hadn't
thought of it fucking once.
That mope in the back seat
keeps changing fucking shapes.
Who the fuck are they?
I want you to go in here, Butchie, and
I want you to act like a fucking man.
The business between us,
we'll deal with later.
Well, you didn't get me high,
but you didn't kill me either.
Just shut the fuck up and get out.
Take this shape-changing mope with you.
- I ain't afraid of you, Pal.
- I ain't afraid of you.
I don't give a fuck
what you are.
- I ain't afraid of you, Pal.
- I took more acid...
Than you ate cheerios
for fucking breakfast.
In a volcano.
The fucking hallaka-halama-vaka
fucking thing.
Haleakala, freddy.
If you move your seat back,
you wouldn't look like
such a fucking monkey.
Get out, before I blow
both your fucking heads off.
Thanks for not killing me.
Come on.
Motherfucking press.
Come here.
Leave the fucking door open.
Fucking seat belt.
I'd doubt the connection
with the minor area temblors
we've been reporting, bob,
have had much to do with this.
All we know at this point is that
the young surfer broke his neck
while competing
at huntington beach
and has en listed in grave
condition at mercy hospital.
And this is the famous
surfing Yost family?
That could be Shaun.
Who are they discussing?
Where is he?!
What's his condition for Christ's sake?
Oh my god!
Don't yell at me.
Anderson! Anderson, for God's
sake, don't hang up on me.
Please help me find an injured friend.
I won't intrude on them, but
if there's anything they need...
The family, errands
or whatever the hospital
doesn't provide,
I'm available to do that day or night.
Okay.
Well,
I have terrible news
to share with you.
Shaun has suffered devastating injuries.
The vertebrae at the base of his
skull was crushed when he fell,
and that left him paralyzed
and unable to breathe.
a machine is breathing for him now,
but the time he was without oxygen
underwater and later
did catastrophic damage.
Our tests show that there is
no electrical activity in Shaun's brain.
So you're saying he's brain-dead.
You're saying there's nothing you can do.
I'm sorry,
but I think
that's the case.
we'll run our test again
in the morning,
but I don't expect
to see a change.
Why put him through
the tests then?
We have to be absolutely certain
of Shaun's condition and prognosis
before later decisions can be made.
Yeah, but you're
absolutely certain now.
A protocol is developed
in these situations.
Your protocol's more
important than his suffering?
To take a patient off life support,
possibly making his organs
available for transplant,
those aren't cliffs you can reclimb.
Why don't you leave
the cliffs out of it?
I understand that you're
suffering terribly.
If it's any consolation, i assure you,
your grandson is not.
When it suits your protocols,
we take you at your word.
When it suits your protocols
before we can take you
at your word,
you get to crucify him with
another 12 hours of tests.
Mrs. Yost,
do you have anything
you want to ask me?
No. Doctor, go away.
I'll be with Shaun.
You take Shaunie
off that machine, Mitch,
you better never
get in our bed again.
Did you hear anything
that asshole said?
He needs it to breathe.
He stays on the machine.
I will murder you in your sleep.
Shaunie is brain-dead, Cissy.
- He's breathing and I can hold him.
- well, get a dog.
he's dead.
I want him off the machines.
You want to get back to
your clubhouse, go ahead.
get out, you coward!
get out and leave me
alone with my grandson.
You're afraid
of the hospital, not me.
i got used to it,
all the months I spent
listening to the asshole
I married whine about killing himself
'cause his knee was gone.
He couldn't be king of the waves.
Mitch Yost, the big realist.
"Let's face it, Cissy, he's gone.
Let's just put him
in the ground."
Well, when the time comes,
why don't you just sign
whatever papers it is
they need you to sign?
- Should I go in?
- I don't know.
Did he die?
Your mother will explain it.
- Did he die?
- No.
Cissy is in there.
How's it going?
Did you du out this morning?
You need to dump out?
Okay, come on.
He was going for a little
cover-up on the inside,
the water sucked out.
Was he doing good
before he ate it?
He had it won.
Can we go see him?
He's dumping out.
This is my son Mitchell junior.
Shaun's father.
How do you do?
- Can we go in?
- Please.
Is it okay if touch him?
I thought one day, a day with
no dog fights, I'd square things.
You know, surf some spots
with him in Indonesia, maybe.
I thought we'd have the time.
They asked about
donating Shaun's organs.
He gave his stick away that time
to that one-legged kook kid at trestles.
I surf.
You were great.
You know, I could introduce
you to him if you want.
or you could keep pretending
you don't know each other.
Hi, I'm Linc Stark.
Hi.
- Get with Mitch.
- Can you hold that, please?
Like my heart's beating in a cartoon.
Are you here to see Shaun?
Yes, I am.
Can I see him?
I don't have to decide now
about the organs, right?
I'd still have the 12 hours
to change my mind.
You've been more father
to him than I was.
Excuse me.
Okay, zip.
Now, don't hold back on me, pal.
I just took a dump a grown
man would be proud of.
Attaboy.
A- plus for fume control, Butchie?
A- plus, John.
The end is near.
That's it, zip. That's it.
And kiss Shaunie too as long
as we're being stupid.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
www.Team-NCIS.com
www.all-about-subs.fr