Previously on Prison Break...
Let me get this straight.
The brothers come back to a city
that's 15 miles from the prison
they escaped from. Why ?
Because the president
is in Chicago
to make a speech,
and they're up to something,
Legally speaking, this tape is useless.
So we blackmail her.
In exchange for what?
A presidential pardon.
Are we gonna keep crying about money
you've already got coming to you?
Or do you want to make some more?
- I'm listening.
- Ever been to Mexico?
When's the meal coming around?
I'm starved.
Freshen me up
when you get a chance, darlin'.
Tia, ella es Maricruz.
I'll check this bag for you, sir.
That's coming with me. Give it back.
Sir, I know that bag
is way over the weight limit.
Your bag will be safe.
They're watching you. But from where?
There.
President Reynolds ruined your life;
she ruined my life.
You want to take that bitch down?
You just found your inside man,
but it's got to be right now.
Have either of these men checked in?
Yeah. Room 1006.
Today,
you'll get a package in your cell.
It's gonna be from me.
I need you to use it. Okay?
Open on four!
I need a hand in here!
- I need a medic in B-4!
- Let me die.
Let me die.
A large crowd is gathering along
Beaumont Avenue here in
downtown Chicago,
anticipating the arrival
of President Caroline Reynolds,
who continues her speaking tour
with an appearance today
at the Grand Carlisle Hotel.
Inner Circle approaching
the south perimeter. Marker One.
Marker Two.
Marker Three.
I think you'd better go.
You sure?
Thank you for your help,
but, there's nothing more
- you can do for us.
- It doesn't feel right, just leaving.
I don't think you want any part of this.
Thank you.
- It's ten minutes away, right?
- At least.
Listen, if this doesn't work,
we're gonna need a way out. For good.
Well, that's on you.
What about Derek?
Derek Sweeney?
- You think he'll be up for this?
- Yeah.
All right.
This is your neck of the woods.
You want to meet at the park?
How's Third and Racine?
Third and Racine?
3:15, the corner.
I'll be there.
If anything happens...
I love you both.
Key.
Sit down.
Subtitles: swsub.com (V.1.00)
When were they here,
5 minutes, 10 minutes?
- They were never here.
- I know they were here.
Where did they go?
- I don't know.
- No, you do know.
He decided it was for the best,
and I couldn't take this anymore.
It's over just like that?
- Yeah.
- It's over like the time
you flew to New Mexico
on dead woman's ID to meet him?
Or it's over
like the time that you met up
and got back together
at the train station in Evansville?
Or maybe like the day, today,
when you checked into this hotel here
2 h ago?
- Which one is it like ?
- I don't care you believe me.
- I'm telling you the truth.
- He's not going to call you?
Don't lie to me.
You don't want to do that.
Can you tell me what the sign
means over there?
I'm just wondering.
No hablo granjero.
I need the phone.
Listen to me, man, it needs to be today.
My family is in trouble, all right?
There's man out there
who's trying to hurt my family.
Your family is fine.
There's nobody after your family.
No, look at me, man.
Look, I'm not crazy, okay?
I know the rules.
I wouldn't be asking you
if it wasn't an emergency.
Please, just let me use that phone.
- Agent Lang.
- I need to speak to Mahone, please.
Can I have him return?
Listen, this is Benjamin Miles Franklin,
and I need to speak
to Mahone right away.
- It's Franklin for Mahone.
- I'll take it.
Mr. Franklin? This is agent Wheeler.
- I don't believe we've met before.
- I need to speak to Mahone.
Something I can help you with?
Listen...
I want to leave a message for him.
You tell him...
You tell him that I'll do
what he wants me to do, okay?
I just need a little bit more time.
I'll do it.
Just don't hurt them.
You hear me?
Don't hurt them.
What's up?
Excuse me.
- What the hell are you doing here, man?
- Keep your voice down. Keep it down.
How you been?
- You all right?
- It's good to see you, man.
You, too, brother.
If some of the guys knew you were here,
they might not be too cool.
Well, I ain't hanging around;
I need a favor.
- You owe me.
-I do.
You know I do.
Look, it's just...
Look, it's just your situation
right now.
I mean, I just had a kid, a baby boy,
and I promised Marie...
I didn't come here to cause trouble.
I'm short on friends.
I need you to hook me up.
I know you can do it
without the green up front.
I'm serious about this, man.
Here. I need it.
I'll give it a shot.
- By when?
- ASAP.
- Tomorrow? The next day?
- Now.
Now.
All right, Linc.
Come with me.
Who saw him go down?
- Any press?
- We got him down pretty quick,
but you never know.
Some may have gotten a shot.
Check around.
Confiscate cameras if you need to.
Put out a statement
before rumors get started.
And get everyone out of here.
Now.
We're waiting for the response
from Counter...
You and I both know that this situation
requires us to abandon protocol.
I don't know what you need to tell them,
but I need your men to leave.
Now.
Yes, sir.
Where's your brother?
- I need to see the president.
- Really?
And you think that's a possibility?
She'll want to hear what I have to say.
Oh, I highly doubt that.
The only person you get to talk to...
...is me.
And the only way you're going
to live through the next hour
is if you tell me
where to find your brother.
Okay.
He's in a safe place.
Be more specific.
Specifically...
a place you will never find him.
I had the honor...
to attend Mountfort military academy.
whose mission it is
to ensure the greatness of this country
and his future leadership,
encouraging patriotism,
building a strong moral foundations
and providing the service of men
committed to the values of honor,
freedom and country.
But...
first and foremost,
they taught you this.
How do you say "cherries" again?
Cereza.
Looks like you have to get more cerezas.
I've just got you 100 pistachios,
with the right amount of salt, too.
Well, it's the combination.
I need both.
Why I am I a sucker for you, huh?
What? What's she saying?
That looks like T-Bag.
He said he was trying to steal luggage
from the airport,
He's got $5 million. Why would he...?
Unless he doesn't have it.
Unless he lost it there.
- Stop it, Fernando. - What?
Do you really believe
that that money is at the airport?
Forget it.
Look at what we have together.
Do you really want to risk that?
We have everything that we need.
- Except your cerezas.
- Right.
I'll be right back.
You got to know it's not real hard
for me to recognize a junkie.
I'm...
I'm saying
you don't look so good.
I'm fine.
Yeah.
You mind me asking what you're taking?
Here. You want one?
- No, that's okay.
- Here.
Save it for later.
Varatril.
Benzodiazepine's a hard-core
tranquilizer, man.
You take these every day?
20 milligrams.
You must feel like you're walking
underwater.
I do.
It's very quiet, down here.
That's why you started, right?
Peace and quiet.
That's not why you do it anymore,
though, is it?
Now it's the headaches, right?
And you probably don't sleep.
And you know you're gonna
destroy yourself, right?
I haven't ruled that out
as a possibility.
I hope we hear from your boyfriend.
There's one difference between me
and Agent Mahone.
He doesn't know the value
of a bird in the hand,
he just keeps beating and beating
around that bush.
But if you don't give up Burrows,
I don't care.
One down, one to go.
I need to talk to Mr. Scofield.
Alone.
Madam President...
could I...
have a word?
It wouldn't be prudent
- for me to leave you alone...
- My men...
are right outside this door.
I have a right to privacy.
Your rights
aren't my first concern.
Do I need to remind you
who you are talking to?
Step outside,
and close the door behind you.
The things you do for your brother.
It's impressive.
I could say the same for you.
But I won't.
Bear in mind,
your opinion means little to me.
This tape.
You have it with you?
But I can arrange for you to hear it.
You don't make arrangements
for me, Mr. Scofield.
I have people for that.
I'm not exactly sure
what is on this tape,
but I doubt it's of any interest to me.
It's a recorded conversation
between you and your brother.
Well, out of millions of conversations
that I had with my brother
during his lifetime...
I'll narrow it down for you.
It was recorded sometime...
after his death.
And this...
particular conversation...
you might want to keep in the family.
And where is it?
20 different copies
in 20 different locations.
I can call my brother right now.
He can play it for you.
Not on the phone.
Have him bring it here.
These are the terms.
You can hear it over the phone,
or you can hear it on the news.
It's up to you.
You know, it's why I started.
Started what?
Using.
Same reason as you.
Why, because you had to stay up
all night during residency?
Because the bass player dumped you
in front of the whole sorority?
Yeah, you and I got a lot in common.
I've seen people die, too.
I'm assuming you didn't make them die.
You need help.
Not what I'm looking for.
For your sake, I hope your boyfriend
calls back real soon.
Where the hell is everybody?
Mami!
Lookie here, good old Sucre.
What did you do to them?
Where are they? Maricruz!
Keep your cap on.
They're out picking apples
for the Snuffleupagus.
- If you ever...
- Calm down!
They're going to walk back in here
any minute...
which means trouble.
Now, unless you want to see me try out
the new T-20Z on your
bella muchacha, Mari-poon.
I think you'd better come with me.
I understand you have something for me.
You still there?
I'm here.
It's good to finally talk to you.
Wish I had the chance
one of those 242 nights
I spent on death row.
Please, just play the tape.
It's awful, I know.
But the choice was clear.
You need to be far away
from all of this.
I am.
I'm the Isle of Terrence,
far off to sea.
Look, I'm still here for you.
Now, listen to me.
Don't dwell on the negative.
Some people deserve to dwell, Caroline.
You know I'm only a phone call away.
And 3,000 miles.
Do you know
how cold it is here?
We talked about this, Terrence.
You knew that you would be
lonely, but it's only temporary.
His appeals process has started already.
This is gonna fly by
quicker than your 20s.
And soon the world
will forget all about him
and they'll forget about you, too.
I promise.
But...
it's killing me
not being able to see you,
sweet Caroline.
I want to see you, too.
But that can't happen right now.
This house is so big.
I just think of you...
lying in bed...
I know. Me, too.
Your warmth... your touch.
Was it quick
when he killed himself?
It was a lot quicker
than how my father died.
They shot him in the back.
He died in my arms.
I just want to know what happened.
Your brother apologized.
He said he was sorry,
and then he blew his brains out
all over the wall.
It was quick.
And it was his decision.
And now it's time for you to make yours.
You know, I can't do it.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
You don't get it, do you?
You can't stop this guy.
Not without your cooperation, I can't,
but if you talk to me,
if you tell me what's going on,
I can take care of you, okay?
You've got to trust me, Mr. Franklin.
I can help you.
C- Note, right?
Yeah. Whatever, man.
All I need you to do
is tell me exactly what
Agent Mahone told you.
If you give me Mahone,
I'll give you your life back.
God's been smiling down on me,
I can tell you that.
First, I caught up to
Haywire up in Algoma.
He did a swan dive off a grain elevator
before they could put him away,
but I still get the reward.
Wait, wait. He's dead?
Yep, like a gnat on a Peterbilt.
Hope you don't take
the same route, Sucre.
Oh, hell no, I got plenty reasons
to live.
I hope a few of them are in Fox River.
And maybe, if you play nice,
I'll throw your Maricruz a couple bills
after I turn you in.
How much are you getting for this?
A hundred grand.
I bet you never thought your
ass'd be worth all that.
Wait, wait.
What if I know where you
can get five million dollars?
You hear me?
Where is it?
I could take you there,
if you didn't have to take me
back to the States
and turn me back in.
Where is it?
T- Bag's in town.
I made my commitment a long time ago.
I agreed to put my country
ahead of myself,
like a mother does for a child.
And I thought
that what I was doing was noble
and that I would be rewarded.
You were wrong.
Don't you see that
I'm a pawn in this, too?
The power that has taken over
this country is like a cancer,
and it will stop at nothing.
It is out of my control.
So is this.
Tell me what you want from me.
Uncuff me.
I don't have the keys.
You'll get them.
Second, I want you to arrange
for me to walk away, alone.
No surveillance.
Okay.
And finally,
I want a presidential pardon for me
and my brother,
fully exonerating us of all our crimes.
And I want it today.
I can't just hand out pardons
to anyone I choose.
There is a process, rules.
This is no exception.
A document will be delivered
for your approval just like any pardon.
You'll sign it
and then file it
with the attorney general
who'll submit
to the presidential record.
Fine. I will sign
whatever you need me to sign.
That's very kind,
but we both know that's not enough.
What do you want from me?
I will unlock you myself,
walk you out of here.
What, you want me to drive you
to the airport?
I guess I'm not as trusting as I used
to be, especially with paperwork.
It's so easy to lose.
Now, I want you to go out there
in front of everyone and announce
our full pardon on live TV.
You're insane.
That is not the way things are done!
This is not a vacuum,
people will ask questions.
Pardon!
On stage!
Now!
And how do I know
that you won't release the tape
an hour later?
You don't.
You'll just have to take my word for it.
Well, I need more than that.
Well, you're not going to get it.
It's time.
Make your choice.
Adams, I need you to uncuff the detainee
and bring him here to be released.
What...
are you doing?
I am going to make an announcement
pardoning Mr. Scofield and his brother
and he will walk away unharmed.
Are you out of your mind?
He has brought
some indisputable evidence to light.
We could end this all.
Right now.
And you're gonna let them walk?
I am the commander in chief,
and you are a corporate lackey.
I am making the calls now.
You have no authority.
My men will see to it
that Mr. Scofield walks away
without the interference of you
and your pit bulls.
- You alone?
- Yeah.
How'd you do?
Three tickets, one cabin, one way.
Nice.
I owe you.
No, we're even.
- These are for you.
- Nice.
And this.
- What's this?
- Eddie,
when you broke out,
bet me a hundred bucks
you'd be caught in a week.
I said, "No way. Not the Linc I know."
Figured I'd split it with you.
So this is it ?
Yeah.
Good luck.
- You take care.
- You, too. All right.
You be safe.
Your neck of the woods.
Yeah, how's Third and Racine?
I'll be there.
I don't want to do this, I really don't.
What are you,
what are you talking about?
You can't say
that I didn't give you a choice
but you, you know,
you never take the easy way, you...
And I noticed that about you, you...
I should never expect it to be
any different, but I have a job to do,
a job that I'm being made to do.
Pick it up, Sara.
Sara, pick it up.
Pick up the phone!
Wait, wait!
Don't move.
Just...
I need the phone.
Give me the phone.
Stay right where you are, please.
You don't really want to do this.
You don't know the first thing
about what I want.
Get my message?
Yeah.
- I got her.
- She's on her way out.
Follow her;
she'll take you right to Scofield.
Sir...
we need to talk.
In just a few minutes,
the president
is going to announce a pardon
for Burrows and Scofield.
As you're well aware,
this is quite a departure.
She's always been willing to play ball,
but I think
we need to take some sort of action.
Sir...
I hate to disturb you,
but I'm not sure you realize the gravity
of what she's about to do.
Michael.
Sara, it worked.
The pardon?
She's announcing it any minute.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Michael, that's amazing.
Just get here, Okay ?
I'm on...
Highland.
It's a warehouse.
It runs right down to the water.
Yeah, I'm on my way.
We did it.
Yeah?
What happened to your face, man?
If you want to take the ride...
you got to buy the ticket.
Yeah, right.
Well, Derek hooked us up with a cabin
on one of those freighters.
South America via the Great Lakes.
We're not gonna need that, but,
this is appreciated.
One more time, bro.
We did it?
It's done.
We're done.
I...
I wish I could have seen
the look on her face.
No, you don't.
Oh, yeah, I do.
Unbelievable.
She's going to do it.
The president is now taking the stage
here at the Grand Carlisle Hotel.
The two-hour delay in her appearance
due to an investigation characterized
by Press Secretary Ryan Berg
as "an overzealous fan..."
You are not going to do this.
I'm afraid I am.
There are some developments
you need to be aware of.
I have made my decision.
And I would appreciate you
not second-guessing me.
I don't think you understand.
We know your secrets, too.
And we can reveal them just as easily.
You need to ask yourself
who you fear more,
Michael Scofield?
Or us?
You got 30 seconds.
I won't keep you.
The world is waiting.
Ten seconds.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the United States.
Nine, eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three,
two, one.
Thank you for waiting so patiently
all afternoon.
If it were not for the support
of this great state,
my home state of Illinois...
... I would not be here today.
Which is why I have chosen
today to make
this very important announcement.
A situation
has recently come to light,
and I feel that I must take action.
It is my job as president
of this great country,
to make rational decisions
when I am given facts.
Decisions that are best not for me,
but for the people.
And so,
after much consideration,
I regret to inform you
that I have been diagnosed
with a highly malignant form of cancer.
And because of that reason,
I am no longer fit
to serve as your commander in chief.
In the best interest of this country,
effective immediately,
I am stepping down as president
of the United States.
If she ain't the president,
the tape's useless.
She can't pardon anyone.
We got nothing.
There's only one thing we can do.
We got to disappear...
forever.