(woman) Once, when she was a girl,
a very little girl...
... Dana was in the woods.
It was autumn. She had always been
a tomboy, unlike her sister Melissa.
For her birthday, Dana's brothers gave her
a BB gun and were showing her how to use it.
Their father had told them
only to shoot at cans.
But in a patch of grass
Bill Junior found a garter snake.
And the boys began shooting.
Wanting to fit in with her brothers,
Dana also shot at the snake.
It squirmed wildly, fighting for life...
... but as the boys continued to shoot,
the snake began to bleed.
When she realised what she had done...
... Dana began to cry with irrevocable guilt.
Through her tears, she was saying that
something was missing from the snake.
She had taken something
that was not hers to take.
Although afraid of snakes,
Dana held the animal...
... as if sheer human will could keep it alive.
The snake, its blood on her hands, died.
Nothing she could do would bring it back.
(Mulder) It's too soon, Mrs Scully.
We can't give up.
That day in the woods, I felt for my daughter.
But at this moment...
...I know how my daughter felt.
(door opens)
LOVING DAUGHTER AND FRIEND
"The Spirit is the Truth." 1 John 5:07
PARANORMAL ACTIVITY
GOVERNMENT DENIES KNOWLEDGE
THE TRUTH IS OUT THERE
X-FILE
(tape rewinding)
(kissing sounds, moaning)
(female voice) We should stop.
(tape rewinding)
(phone rings)
NORTHEAST GEORGETOWN
MEDICAL CENTER WASHINGTON, DC
Sir... Sir, you can't go in there!
Who brought her here?
How did she get here?
- Would you...
- How did she get here!
Ms Scully was in this condition
when I arrived.
- If you step outside, Dr Daly...
- Is that Daly? Are you Dr Daly?
- What the hell is going on?
- Settle down...
Was it paramedics, FBI, military?
Answer me right now!
You saying she just appeared?!
Who did this to her?!
- Sir...
- I wanna see her admission forms!
I wanna see what tests were done!
If you're with them, if you're hiding anything,
I swear I will do anything!
Whatever it takes,
I'll find out what they did to her!
Dana is listed in critical condition. Comatose.
There is unawareness
of self or environment.
No evidence of language comprehension
or voluntary responses to external stimuli.
My apologies, but no one here can determine
how Dana arrived at the hospital...
...or how she was attended to
in such a critical condition.
Um...
Because of the absence of Dana's recent
medical history, I'm at a loss for a prognosis.
I can't determine with certainty
how long she's been in this state.
You haven't said why she's like this.
We just don't know, Mrs Scully. There are no
signs of injuries, traumatic or non-traumatic.
I can't find signs of
degenerative or metabolic disorders.
- We have conducted every test possible.
- I'd like her examined for trace evidence.
She's been bathed and cleaned
since her admittance.
Also there is a situation
which I don't know if you're aware of.
The FBI has notified us of
the terms of Dana's living will.
- What is it? What did she say?
- Well, Dana is a doctor.
Her criteria for terminating
life support is quite specific.
She states that if her
Glasgow Outcome Scale lists her...
She doesn't wanna live in this condition.
You signed the will as her witness.
I've been told not to call you Fox.
By who?
Dana. Just now.
Dana talked to you just now?
If she'd talked, the EEG would've moved.
Her soul is here.
Hi, Mom.
I'm glad you could come, Melissa.
You're Scully's sister?
Dana's choosing whether...
...whether to remain or move on.
You can feel her.
Here.
(Mulder) She's not here.
(Melissa) Your anger... your fear is blocking
any positive emotions she needs to feel.
I need to do more than
just wave my hands in the air.
(woman) May I help you?
Dana Scully, please.
Frohike?
Hey, Mulder! This is weird.
- Good work sneaking out these charts.
- Tucked 'em in my pants.
There's plenty of room down there.
You look down, Mulder.
You're welcome to come over on Saturday.
We're hoppin' on the Internet
to nit-pick inaccuracies of Earth 2.
- I'm doing my laundry.
- The chart shows abnormal protein chains.
The amino acid sequence
is in a combination I've never seen.
I downloaded Scully's data
to the newest Lone Gunman.
- He goes by the name "The Thinker".
- (Byers) This guy's a hacking genius.
What?
He reports the protein chains
are the by-products of branched DNA.
- Branched DNA?
- The cutting edge of genetic engineering.
Biological equivalent of a silicon microchip.
Way beyond cutting edge.
This is technology 50 years down the line.
- What's it used for?
- Could be a tracking system.
- Developmental stages of a marker.
- You mean a hi-tech identity card?
Or something as insidious as grafting
a human to something... inhuman.
Good theories, but all for naught.
This branched DNA is inactive.
It's waste product.
Whoever experimented on Scully is finished.
Now it's just a biological poison.
Will she live?
Um...
Her immune system has been decimated.
And, uh... I doubt even a healthy
human body has the ability to fight this.
Mulder, there's nothing you can do.
Dana?
Dana, honey? I know you can hear me.
This is Nurse Owens.
I'm here to take care of you, sweetheart.
Watch over you. Help you find the way home.
I know you're far away from home tonight...
...and that where you are is peaceful.
It would be nice to stay.
But, Dana, you must leave here
only when it's time.
I'll be here when you need me, dear.
Excuse me, sir. I have to take some blood.
(continuous beep)
- Code blue! Crash cart.
- Crash cart coming in.
Let's go!
- Let's get an airway in.
- She's asystolic.
- BP 80 over 60, dropping.
- Let's shock her. Paddles. 200 joules.
- Clear!
- Clear.
- What have we got?
- Got a catheter in. Dropping...
- Let's go again. Clear!
- Clear.
Hey!
HOSPITAL ELEVATORS
- I didn't expect you here.
- A man took Scully's blood.
- Forget him!
- Get that gun away!
This compact SigSauer
is pointed at your head...
...to stress my insistence that your search
for who hurt your partner desist now!
You ignore my call, then expect me
to do what you say? Go to hell!
You got him killed! You got her killed.
That's not going to happen to me.
You're my tool, understand?
I come to you when I need you.
You're heading in a direction
that can lead them here.
- What are you talking about?
- You can't know. That's the point.
I owe her more than just
sitting around doing nothing.
She was a good soldier, but there is
nothing you can do to bring her back!
She's not dead.
Listen to you.
Listen. You're a damn schoolboy, Mulder.
You have no idea. No idea.
OK, then tell me. Tell me!
I used to be you.
I was where you are now.
But you're not me, Mulder.
I don't think you have the heart.
Walk away, grieve for Scully
and then never look back.
You will be able to live
with yourself, Mulder...
...on the day you die.
(footsteps)
Federal agent!
(clatter)
(footsteps)
Federal agent. You know I'm armed.
Don't turn around.
Put your gun very slowly on the ground.
Put your hands behind your head,
interlock your fingers.
Turn right towards the machine
and put your head on it.
Face me.
Who wants this?
Who wants it?!
All right, let's go. This way.
(screams)
Stay there.
Wait!
You wanna see what it takes
to find the truth, Agent Mulder?
You wanna know the things I know?
I'll attend to this.
(Dr Daly) Discontinuing the respirator
does not necessarily mean ending her life.
Karen Ann Quinlan lived for nine years
after cessation of mechanical ventilation.
I do believe, however, this is not the case
with your daughter, Mrs Scully.
My guess is that she's been like this since
her disappearance, and she will not improve.
Is she below the criteria
established in her will?
It's possible branched DNA
can be treated with designer antibiotics.
I don't know where you got this diagnosis,
but you are in no position to continue...
You've never provided an answer as to
why she's here or what's wrong with her.
- We must study her.
- She's not a piece of evidence.
She's here because of
unnatural circumstances.
She's dying.
That's perfectly natural.
We hide people
because we don't wanna look at death.
We have machines prolong a life
that should... that should end.
That's a much more unnatural circumstance
than any cause of her death.
That's very politically correct.
That's very human.
I love her.
And this is right.
Dana... has made our decision.
Fox.
You and Dana had a friendship
built on respect.
Now, in the last year,
I have lost my husband...
...and God knows
I don't wanna lose my baby girl.
But, like you, I have always respected her.
Fox, this is a moment for the family.
But you can join us if you want.
Read it. It's all there.
If you're having trouble sitting on Mulder,
Assistant Director Skinner...
...I'm sure you know we'd have no trouble.
Uh-uh.
THANK YOU FOR NOT SMOKING
(knocking)
Yeah, come in.
Sit down.
I called you because of rumours
about an incident at the hospital.
Is this about the tooth
found in the cafeteria Jell-O?
The rumour has it
you were involved in the laundry room?
- No, sir.
- A man was executed.
- I was with Scully.
- Traces of her blood were found.
- May I see the police report?
- There is no report or body. You know that!
Since I am unfamiliar with the incident,
how would I know?
- Knock it off!
- How does it feel?
Constant denial of everything,
questions answered with a question.
- I wanna know what happened, dammit!
- Him! That's what happened.
Cancer Man is responsible
for what happened to Scully.
- How do you know that?
- It's a rumour.
- Who is he?
- It's not your...
You can have my badge, the X-Files.
Just tell me where he is.
And then what? He sleeps with the fishes?
We're not the Mafia, Mulder.
We work for the Department of Justice.
That's what I want.
Agent Scully was a fine officer.
More than that, I liked her. I respected her.
We all know the field we play in
and what can happen in a game.
If you were unprepared for all the potentials,
then you shouldn't step on the field.
What if I...
I knew the potential consequences...
...but I... I never told her?
Then you're as much to blame
for her condition as... the Cancer Man.
Hello, Starbuck.
It's Ahab.
People would say to me...
..."Life is short."
"Kids, they grow up fast.
Before you know it, it's over."
I never listened.
To me, life went at a proper pace.
There were many rewards.
Until the moment that... I knew...
...I understood that...
...I would never see you again.
My little girl.
Then my life felt as if it had been
the length of one breath.
One heartbeat.
I never knew how much I loved
my daughter until I could never tell her.
At that moment, I'd have traded every medal,
every commendation, every promotion...
...for just one more second with you.
We'll be together again, Starbuck.
But not now.
Soon.
Dana?
I know death is at arm's reach tonight.
But, Dana, your time is not over.
You know, Fox... Sorry, Mulder.
You could spend your life finding everyone
responsible and it still won't bring her back.
Whoever did this to her
has an equal horror coming to them.
Including myself?
Pardon me. Sir, do you have
change for the cigarette machine?
No. Sorry, I don't.
What do you mean, yourself?
There's a pack already here. Morleys.
Not my brand.
900 WEST GEORGIA STREET
(shouting on TV)
(man on TV)
Cigarette, Frank? How about a smoke?
(creaking)
Sit down!
- How'd you find me?
- Shut up!
Tonight I ask questions and you answer,
you son of a bitch!
Don't try and threaten me, Mulder.
I've watched presidents die.
Why her?
Why her and not me?
Answer me!
I like you.
I like her, too.
That's why she was returned to you.
You should be the one to die.
Why?
Look at me. No wife, no family.
Some power.
I'm in the game because
I believe what I'm doing is right.
Right?
Who are you to decide what's right?
Who are you?
If people were to know of the things
that I know, it would all fall apart.
I told Skinner you shot the man
in the hospital, but I didn't believe it.
And here you are with a gun to my head.
I have more respect for you, Mulder.
You're becoming a player.
You can kill me now,
but you'll never know the truth.
And that's why I'll win.
Don't worry. This'll be our secret.
We wouldn't want others to... start rumours.
(machine whirring)
To Assistant Director Walter S Skinner:
Please accept my resignation
from the FBI, effective immediately.
I WANT TO BELIEVE
When I started out,
this room was where they kept the copier.
At least back then
it wasn'tjust wasted space.
(ripping)
It's unacceptable.
I know you feel responsible for Agent Scully,
but I won't accept defeat as self-punishment.
All the forensics, the field investigations,
the eyewitness accounts...
...to still know nothing.
To lose myself...
...and Scully.
I hate what I've become.
When I was 18, I... uh... I went to Vietnam.
I wasn't drafted, Mulder. I... I enlisted in
the Marine Corps the day of my 18th birthday.
I did it on a blind faith.
I did it because I believed it was
the right thing to do. Maybe I still do.
Three months into my tour...
...a ten-year-old North Vietnamese boy
walked into camp, covered with grenades.
And I, uh...
I blew his head off
from a distance of ten yards.
I lost my faith. Not in my country
or in myself, but in everything.
There was just no point
to anything any more.
One night, on patrol, we were, uh... caught.
And everyone... everyone fell.
I mean everyone.
I looked down at my body...
...from outside of it.
I didn't recognise it at first. I watched the VC
strip my uniform, take my weapon.
And I remained in this thickjungle.
Peaceful...
...unafraid...
...watching my... my dead friends...
...watching myself.
In the morning the corpsmen put me in
a body bag until... I guess they found a pulse.
I awoke in a Saigon hospital two weeks later.
I'm afraid to look any further
beyond that experience.
You?
You are not.
Your resignation is unacceptable.
You...
You gave me Cancer Man's location.
You put your life in danger.
Agent Mulder,
every life, every day, is in danger.
That's just life.
Your plane ticket.
- But we barely know each other.
- I can't tell you why she was taken.
It's too close to me.
I'm giving you the men who took her.
- How?
- They believe you'll be out of town.
They believe you have information
about Scully in your desk in your apartment.
At 8.17 tonight they'll search your apartment.
They will be armed. You will be waiting.
- Waiting?
- To defend yourself with terminal intensity.
It's the only way, Mulder.
The law will not punish these people.
After tonight, we cannot
make contact for several weeks.
(knocking)
Mulder.
Sorry.
I came by. You weren't answering,
your machine wasn't on.
Can I come in?
For a second?
- Why is it so dark?
- Because the lights aren't on.
OK.
I just came from the hospital.
Dr Daly says... she's weakening.
It could be any time, so I figured
you'd wanna come down and see her.
Well, I can't.
- Well, I'd think that you would.
- Yeah, well, I would. I can't. Not right now.
Listen.
I don't have to be psychic
to see that you're in a very dark place.
Much darker than where my sister is.
Willingly walking deeper into darkness
cannot help her at all. Only the light will...
Enough with the harmonic convergence crap!
You're not saying anything to me.
Why don't you just drop
your cynicism, paranoia and defeat?
Just because it's positive and good
doesn't make it silly or trite.
Why is it easier for you to try to get even,
than just expressing to her how you feel?
I expect more from you. Dana expects more.
Even if it doesn't bring her back,
at least she'll know.
And so will you.
I feel, Scully, that...
...you believe you're not ready to go.
And you've always had
the strength of your beliefs.
I don't know if my being here...
...will help bring you back.
But I'm here.
(weeps)
(nurse) I'm afraid in this case...
Let me check the chart.
No, there doesn't seem to be any
significant changes since you were last here.
Call Dr Daly. Now!
This is ICU. Find Dr Daly, stat.
(phone rings)
Hello, this is Fox Mulder. Leave a message...
I'm here.
Hello, Fox.
Not Fox. Mulder.
How are you feeling?
Mulder, I don't remember anything.
After Duane Barry...
It doesn't... it doesn't matter.
I... brought you a present.
Superstars of the Super Bowls.
I knew there was a reason to live.
Now you wanna get some rest. I...
...just came by to see
how you're doing. Say hi.
Mulder?
I had the strength of your beliefs.
I was holding this for you.
(door opens)
Can I see Nurse Owens?
I've got something I'd like her to have.
Nurse who?
Owens.
Short, with straight, light-brown hair.
She watched over me in Intensive Care
and I'd like to thank her.
Dana, I've worked here for ten years
and there's no Nurse Owens at this hospital.
Visiontext subtitles: Natasha Cohn
(child) I made this!
ENGLISH HOH