******
I'm a banana. I'm in the fruit group.
To maintain a healthy and balanced diet,
you should have two, three,
or four servings of me per day.
I'm a chicken drumstick.
I'm from the Meat and Poultry group.
To maintain a healthy and balanced diet,
you should have two or three
servings of me each and every day.
I'm a pea pod. I'm...
You're a vegetable.
You're a vegetable!
I'm a veg... I'm in the...
Vegetable...
Three to five servings per day.
What?
Mommy, Mommy, wake up.
Oh, Marie, honey, you okay?
Did you have another
bad dream about the play?
Can I sleep with you?
Of course you can, sweetie.
Just as long as you
say your lines right.
Come on, honey. Let's hear them.
Marie, honey? We need
you to say those lines.
Come on, honey. We're serious.
If you don't say those lines right,
you're just going to have to stand by the
side of the bed for the rest of your life.
I'm a pea pod. I'm a part
of the vegetable group.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Medium Season05
Episode16 The Man in the Mirror
When I was in kindergarten,
I was the tomato.
And Scottie Collins, he was the peanut.
And he got so scared, he
peed right there on the stage.
And from that day on, we called
him "pee-nut." And we still do.
Okay, Bridgette, that is enough.
- Mom?
- You okay?
- Hey, you all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Let me give you a hand.
- No, no, I'm okay. Just let me sit.
Let me just sit down for a second.
Whoo, I was feeling a little bit faint.
For a second there.
Honey, honey, I'm okay. Just
probably drank too much coffee.
Are you sure? You want
me to call the doctor?
- No.
- Maybe we should run you by the emergency room.
No, I'm okay.
Okay, well, let me take
the girls to school.
That way you only have to worry
about getting yourself to work.
A-ha, my master plan worked.
I'll be fine, honey, but
that would be really nice.
Allison, I see you found me.
Went to the office. They told me you
wanted me out here. What's going on?
City Controller called me a
little after 8:00 this morning.
Department of Public Works is laying
some new underground power lines out here
and one of their crews came
across... Watch your step.
One of their crews came across
a body in a shallow grave.
Looks like the fellow was
shot sometime last night.
What are you doing out here?
I mean, until somebody's charged with the
murder, isn't this really a police matter?
Well, since the dead man met with foul play,
the whole area is now an active crime scene,
and that means that work has to stop until
investigation of the death is completed.
And that means that the city's
paying for all these contractors,
workers to stand around doing nothing.
So, I was asked to help expedite things.
Naturally, he has no ID.
I'm guessing that whoever
killed him saw to that.
We're running his prints and his
DNA, but that's gonna take a while.
Also, we found some hairs on
his body that don't belong to him
and that might point
to whoever did this,
but I was hoping that you would just take a
look at him and have one of your eureka moments.
Sorry. No eureka. No nothing.
Well, maybe this will help.
Ankle holster, but no gun.
- Was he on the force? -
Nope. Not police-issued.
All right, well, you'll let me know if
any bells go off in your head, won't you?
Of course, you'll be
the first person I call.
Allison! Hey, can you hear me?
Someone call an ambulance. Get a doctor!
Allison! Allison! Allison!
Where is she?
They took her in the back.
Excuse me. Can I help you?
My name is Dubois.
D-U-B-O-I-S.
My wife, Allison, was just brought
in here. I just wanted to see her.
Uh, maybe I could talk
to somebody about her.
The doctors are with your
wife right now, Mr. Dubois.
Somebody will come out and talk
to you just as soon as they can.
Yeah, I just want to
know what was going on.
You have to wait for the doctor
to come out and talk to you.
I'm sorry. That's all I can tell you.
- Okay, thank you.
- Come sit down, Joe.
Quiet. It's all right.
I live around here.
Mr. Dubois?
Yeah, hi.
Mr. Dubois, I'm Dr. Richards.
Hello. My... my wife? Can I see her?
I don't know what you know. I
don't know what you've heard.
Your wife arrived unconscious.
Unfortunately, she's still unconscious,
and frankly, we don't know why.
What do you mean you don't know why?
Well, there's no evidence
of physical trauma.
A bruise to the head or
any other kind of injury.
The CAT scan is negative, uh, no
evidence of scarring on the brain.
So, for the moment
we're a bit at a loss.
She's just not present.
I'm sorry. You have to give me
a better explanation than that.
I don't have a better
explanation than that.
We've called several neurospecialists.
Your wife will be examined by one of them
just as soon as we can get someone here.
Beyond that, I could tell you that when
something like this has happened in the past,
40 to 50% of the time, the patient
just comes out of it spontaneously.
Okay, what about the other,
uh, 50 or 60% of the time?
You just sit tight. Leave
your numbers at the desk.
And as soon as your wife can have
visitors, I'll make sure we find you.
Okay, well, thank
you, thank you, Doctor.
You all right?
Yeah, I gotta go pick
the girls up from school.
I can send a city car
for them if you'd like.
No, it's okay. Thank you, though.
Um, somebody's gotta, you know,
explain to them what's going on.
Um, excuse me. I have
to give them my numbers.
I don't understand.
She got sick at work?
I think that maybe she was starting to get sick
this morning when she fell down in the kitchen.
But, you know, in any event, she's in
the hospital right now and you know,
they're taking really great care of her.
Can we visit her?
Not today, sweetie. Not
right now, but soon maybe.
Well, can we talk to her on the phone?
Like I said, not today. Maybe tomorrow.
What's she sick with? I mean, you've gotta
be awfully sick to go to the hospital.
Not necessarily.
Well... who's that, Daddy?
Great. This is all I need.
All right, you kids wait here.
Ariel, lock the door after I get out.
Hey, no, no, no. You can't stand
here, man. This is private property.
Come on. Are you lost?
You need me to call someone for you?
Don't be frightened... Joe.
Excuse me? What did you call me?
Hey, listen to me. I got
kids in that car. My kids.
This is my house; you're preventing
me from getting my kids in my house.
What are you doing?
Don't wave to my children.
Come on, I'm gonna count to three.
And if you're not off this lawn by the
time I'm done, I'm calling the police, okay?
- Not necessary.
- One... two...
- Going, Joe.
- Come on. Come on.
Thank you. Three.
I don't know what to tell you, Mom.
By the time you get out here and get on
a plane, you know, she might just be fine.
I think I just want to wait
and hear from the doctors.
Daddy, he's back!
Mom, let me call you back.
What's going on?
What are you doing here in the
dark staring out the window?
The weird guy in the nightgown?
He's standing on the
sidewalk, staring at our house.
I'm sorry. That's just creepy.
Go to your room and do your homework.
- Well, what are you going to do?
- Go on.
- Call the police?
- I don't know. Go on. Maybe.
Oh, God.
Oh, Joe, I'm so... I'm so
glad you finally came back out.
Right, that's... that's
really nice of you.
Listen, man, you got to...
I don't know who you are or how
you know my name, but, uh, look,
we're going through some
stuff in our house, okay,
- some difficult, painful stuff.
- I kn... I know all about it.
And frankly, you're
upsetting my children.
Oh, please, please, you've got to tell
them everything's going to be okay.
Okay, you're upsetting me, too, okay?
So, um, this is the last time.
Is there somebody that
I can call for you?
Do you have somebody
who can pick you up?
Because, look, if you don't, I-I'm,
I'm going to have to call the police.
No? All right, well, I
got to call the police.
555-0126.
Ask for my husband. He'll... he'll come.
He'll, he'll, he'll pick me
up. He'll figure this out.
That's my number.
That's because I'm your wife.
Dad? It's the hospital. It's about Mom.
You stay here.
Where else would I go?
This is where I live.
I'm not so sure about that.
- Hi, this is Joe Dubois.
- Can you please hold?
Yeah, I'll hold.
Dad, why are you talking to that
strange man out there? He scares me.
- Wait, wait, wait a second.
- I'm connecting you now.
- Doctor?
- Mr. Dubois?
This is Joe Dubois. H-How is she?
I don't really have
anything new to report.
Still waiting to hear what
our tests today tell us.
Okay. But she's comfortable, right?
Very comfortable.
- And sh-she's there,
right? - Excuse me?
I mean, physically,
you know she's there.
I'm looking right at
her; I'm in her room.
Okay, good, good.
So if you'd still like to see her, today makes
no sense, but I'm sure you could come by tomorrow.
Okay, excellent. Well, th-that's
what I'll do, then. Thank you, Doctor.
So?
So yeah, uh... it's like I said.
She's comfortable. Everything's good.
Um, maybe she'll even
come home tomorrow.
- Did you speak to her?
- How do you mean?
Did you speak to her? Did
she want to speak to us?
No, I guess they gave her
something. She was asleep.
Well, do you want me to go get Bridgette
and Marie so that you can tell them?
'Cause I know that they're really concerned
and that would make them feel better.
Yeah, okay. Uh, let me just
talk to this guy out front first.
Okay, what did you mean by that?
What did I mean by what?
That thing you said before--
that you're my, uh...
- Your wife.
- Yeah.
That's because I am.
I'm Allison, Joe.
How dare you?
You are not my wife. How c...
My wife is in a... in
a coma in the hospital.
She's fighting for her life.
Well, no, not really.
I mean, my body is there, yes,
but y-you got to believe me.
- Joe, this is... this is me.
- Come here. Let me see this.
Okay, you are Todd Emory.
All right, here, Todd Emory, and you
are obviously, clearly, deeply disturbed.
I am disturbed...
but not how you think.
I am disturbed because every time
I pass a mirror or a store window,
- I see a reflection, but it isn't me.
- Oh, my God.
I am disturbed because I have walked
for miles and miles to get here
and you threw me off my own front lawn
this morning in front of my children,
and I am disturbed because the person
I am counting on to get me through this
is acting like he is disgusted by me.
I don't know who this Todd Emory is.
I don't know why he's on my wrist,
but I do know that's my home;
you're my husband;
those are my children.
I'm calling the police.
Good, call the police. Better yet,
call Scanlon. Better yet, call Devalos.
Get the...
No, no, no, come on.
Stop, stop, stop, please. I...
Come on, man. Hey, hey,
hey, sir, sir, please.
Sir, come on, Todd, Todd.
Please. I-I...
Al.
Oh, my Godthey're coming up t walk toge.
I'm locking the door.
- *******
- No!
rls, uh,s is.
Emory. Todd Emory. I'm...
it's very nice to meet the three of you.
I hope I not interrupting ur homework.
He's, uh.
he's sleeping here tonight.
In our house? In this house?
Well, he...he needs a place to stay,
d I don'want to go into all
the reasons why, but, uh...
I think it's the right
thing to do for tonight.
I can use the couch.
If there is one i-in, in
a room in that direction.
Are you serious?
That's crazy. This is
crazy. You're crazy.
You threw this man off
our lawn this afternoon.
Hey, hey, don't talk to
your father like that.
Don't talk to me like that.
Hold on, hold on a second, young lady.
You know, if Mom was here,
she would never allow this.
Yes, well, Mom is not here. I
am, and you need to trust me.
- Now, hopefully tomorrow, Mister...
- Emory.
Yes, Mr. Emory will go back where
he belongs and Mom will be back here
where she belongs and all
will be right with the world.
- Tomorrow.
- Right, if we live till then.
Well, I'm locking my door,
and I am locking their door,
and if you so much as walk
down this hall past our rooms...
He is not walking anywhere.
He is staying in the
living room on the couch.
He'd better.
That's your eldest daughter.
I think.
She makes me very proud.
What are you doing here?
How did you get in here?
That door was locked.
I used the key.
I know where the key i I
know where everything is.
Are you forgetting? I
live in this house, too.
Whatre you doing? What do you want?
Joe, I think I'm a murderer.
Okay, there we go.
Okay.
Okay, hold on. Hold
on. Okay. How's that?
A lot better.
Thanks, hon.
So start over.
Who is it that you think you killed?
Well, I don't really think
I killed anybody, but...
in my dream, Todd Emory-- the
guy who owns this body I'm in--
was burying a man, a dead man, the same dead body
I was looking at with Devalos when I collapsed.
Well, you know what we need to do.
We need to find out who
the hell this Todd Emory is.
According to this, you were
in theame hospital as my wife.
They thought he was in a coma, but then he
disappeared, and they can't figure out how.
******
"Last seen shortly after 11:00
A. M. lying comatose in his bed."
11:00 A.M.-- isn't that around the time
that you, um, that you went into your coma?
- Yes.
- Okay.
All right, our friend Todd got
hit by a car two nights ago.
I guess he ran out in the middle
of a dark road in the woods,
and that's what put him into his coma.
"At this point,Emory has been
officially declared" a missing person.
"Anyone who has information as to his
whereabouts is urged to contact" the authorities.
His family is said...
to be offering a sizable reward."
Wow, Joe, the whole city's
looking for this guy.
Whole city is looking for me.
I mean, I can't leave the house.
I can't go anywhere or do anything
to help myself get out of this.
What are you doing?
Devalos told me that they found
some hairs on that dead man's body
that weren't his, so
you give this to him.
You just ask him if they
match the hair they found.
No explanations, no back stories.
Just ask him to test, and if
he gets a match, then you can...
You tell him I'm here.
And all the rest of it.
Listen, if not, nothing
ventured, nothing gained.
Okay, I don't think
that's such a good idea.
What do you mean?
Well, because if I give
this to Devalos, ***
u know, this new you, in a***
Oh, well, we have to do something.
What if I woke up as Todd
Emory? Because I'm supposed to...
bring him to justice for
murdering that John Doe.
No. But the way it stands right now, you
wouldn't be bringing Todd Emory to justice.
- You'd be bringing yourself.
- No, I don't think so.
Yes. No, I-I-I
think that
if the police can prove that Todd
Emory murdered that man in the park,
everything's going to go
back to normal. I-I just...
I just have to believe that.
I mean, when the kids wake
up, take them out to breakfast.
I-I don't want them to have to look
at me across the breakfast table.
I frighten them.
You sure sound like Allison.
Going out for pancakes on a school day?
Just when you think there's
no such thing as miracles.
I don't understand it. We're just
letting that stranger stay in our house?
Oh, hey, it wasn't my id.
I mean, it was.
I don't know, sweetie. I just.
I got an instinct about this guy that
he's grateful for a place to stay,
that he won't do anything, that he
won't, you know, take anything or...
Yeah, well, I hope you're right.
Any chance that he'll be gone by
the time we get home from school?
Listen, Ariel, we all want
the same thing here, okay?
Marie, what's going
on with you, sweetie?
You're awfully quiet.
She's sad about Mommy.
She wants her to come home.
And she's worried that if
she doesn't come back in time,
then she won't have a
coste for the school play.
Hey, maybe, hopefully, Mommy
will come home today, huh?
And if she doesn't then,
you know what we'll do?
We'll find somebody else
to sew you a costume, okay?
We'll do something. All right, sweetie?
Hey, you. Don't you worry.
Everything's going to be
back to normal real soon.
Well, I don't know how to descre it.
I mean, she's in the room, but it's as
if she's not really in the room at all.
Well, I felt like I
had to come and visit.
I agree with you now, dear.
It was probably pretty silly.
I'll see you at dinner. Okay.
I called your office, and
they said you were here.
Uh, little visit.
Doctors arare completely baffled.
Listen, I'll... I'll
leave the two of you alone.
No, no. I-I need to give you something.
Um, you and Allison were examining
a murder vtim when she collapsed,
and I know that you found some
hairs on his body that weren't his.
Could you test and see
if these match those?
I'm sorry. I guess I missed it, but
where did you say you got these from?
And how do you know about
this murder investigation?
I didn't. What does it matter?
If those don't match, we
have nothing to talk about.
And if they do, I'll tl you
everything you need to know.
Don't look so confused.
You've known me and my
family for a long time.
You're quite right.
Well, if you need anything, just...
Todd Emory?
I'm talking to you.
We haven't met, but I'm the landlord.
And I'm serving you
with an eviction notice.
You've been warned.
- Dadd'm home!
- Daddy, I'm home!
Dad, I'm back. I have the keys.
I've got the girls, and
I've got Ashley with...
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make a pea pod for peanut.
Do you actually know what you're doing?
Well, let's see. Come
here, you vegetable.
Let's see what is looks like. Come on.
Let's try this... on. Yeah. There we go.
Now, was... was that
more like you had in mind?
That looks almost as good
as something Mom would do.
Well, I take that as a compliment.
- Do I know you?
- No.
None of us know him.
Come on. Let's get you changed,
and I'll get you a snack.
Go.
Thank you.
You're very welcome, sweetie.
If Mommy's still sick and can't
come to the play, will y come?
Marie! You know what? No. Come on.
You couldn't keep me away.
Bye now.
Bye.
Who is it?
- Hey, are you in there?
- Yes. Is there a problem?
Oh, I've been looking all ov for you.
Um, how did you get in there without the
girls seeing you coming down the hall?
I went through the sliding glass door
in the kitchen, and I to the ck way.
Well, why aryou-you talking
to me through the door?
Why don't you just come in here?
Ah, yeah, you know, if it's just
the same, I-I think I'd rather not.
Oh, come on, Joe. It's ridiculous.
There's nothing in here
that you haven't seen before.
Oh, I beg to differ.
Honestly.
Um, here's the thing.
Is, I-I think have to take the girls
to the hospital to visit you tonight.
Visit Allison. Visit you.
I-I dot think that I can keep this
thing under wraps for too ch longer.
I think that Iave to
tell them about the coma.
About you.
And I... And I just want to let you know,
because things might get weird when we get home.
Weirder.
You're worried about Ariel, aren't you?
Well, you think that she's angry now...
Oh, I don't know. Maybe
I should just leave.
And then all you have to explain
is the coma, and you just...
you just spare them the rest.
Well, you know, I thought
about that, but the thing is...
I don't think that I want you to leave.
Oh, my God.
Well, are-are you expecting someone?
No. Stay right here.
Don't let anyone see you.
- Joe.
- Mr. District Attorney.
I'm sorry to show up unannounced.
First of all, for what it's worth, those hairs
that you gave me this morning, they, um...
They don't match the hairs that were
found on the body of that man in the park.
So whoever's hairs those might have been, they
probably have nothing to fear from the police.
All right. Well, I-I'm sure
that's a relief to someone.
In the meantime, we have figured out just
whose body that is we found out there.
Dead man was a private
investigator named Porter Hayes.
Specialized in divorce work.
Yeah, I know. You're thinking, "What
does any of this have to do with me?"
Have you, um... have you
ever seen this man before?
Only in the newspapers.
The mother of one of your daughter's friends
called the reward hotline early this evening.
Her little girl swears that she
saw this man in your house today.
Like you said at that hospital this
morning, I've known you folks a long time.
That hair that you gave
me?I'm no psychic, but, um,
I have a very strong feeling that
it might belong to Todd Emory.
Joe, if Todd Emory were here, if he
was hiding in your house, you'd...
you'd tell me, right?
I'm asking you a direct question.
That man has been missing from the hospital for
two days now, and I think you know where he is.
Is he here?
Good evening, Mr. District Attorney.
I'm Todd Emory. I think you're
asking some questions about me.
He's gone.
They took him back to the hospital.
Okay, so, why do you look so sad?
I mean, you didn't even know him, so...
I think I convinced myself that
if I could help this guy, that...
that somehow that would help
your mom get better, too.
I know it doesn't make a lot of sse.
- No, it doesn't.
- No.
He took a picture of you
guys with himhen he left.
I'm sorry if this upset you.
Okay.
- Good night, Daddy.
- Good night, sweetie.
Todd?
Oh, you don't know who I am, do you?
It's me.
Sam.
Samantha, your wife?
Oh, God.
The doctors said there'd
be some memory loss, but...
I'm sorry. Oh, everything's just a...
It's a bit of a blank right now.
That's amazing.
Even me? I'm a blank?
We've been married for seven years.
I'm sure everything is good...
will come back soon.
Oh, Todd.
Todd... the night that you were hit...
why were you out there
in the middle of nowhere?
I'm sorry. I just... I
don't... I don't have any idea.
The police said that they found
you in some strange family's house.
I can't explain that.
You don't remember
anything? Anything at all?
Dead man was a private
investigator named Porter Hayes.
Specialized in divorce work.
Porter Hayes. I think he
was a private investigator.
Yeah, for some reason,
that stuck in my head.
Excuse me? Sorry to interrupt.
I have a little something
to help Mr. Emory sleep.
Doctor's orders.
You did that really well, Todd.
Maybe you missed your calling in life.
Physical labor really seems to suit you.
You didn't have to kill
him. And you don't have to...
You don't have to kill me.
Well, you didn't leave
me much wiggle room, Todd.
We could have had a wonderful
life together, you and me.
You and me, me and my flings, but no.
You had to go and hire a private
investigator, get him to follow me around town,
taking all of those pictures. Why?
So you could divorce me
and leave me with nothing?
I don't think you understand
how this game is played, dear.
Go on. Get in the hole.
Well, lie down. Make
yourself comfortable.
You're going to be in there a while.
So, what are you going to do?
Are you going to shoot
me in theack of my head?
Yeah.
But I am going to have beautiful
thoughts about you while I do it.
Oh, you...
You shot me!
I can't believe that you shot me!
Well, you were going to shoot me.
- In the back of my head.
- No! No!
Oh, goodness. What's gng on?
Something wake you, darling?
Oh, something's gone wrong.
Oh, please call for help.
Nothing's wrong. It'll all be over soon.
That pain that you're feeling?
That's just the air bubblehat
I've injected into your IV line.
In just a few moments, it will reach
your brain, and all the pain will be gone.
No! No! No! No, no, it'll all be done by t
time the nurses finish their shift change.
Don't fight it, Todd.
This is just the way that it has to be.
Please. Please don't do this. Please?
Page Dr. Ancheta at home.
His patient in 404 is coding.
404? What's the patient's name?
Emory. Todd Emory.
I don't know what happened.
He just started convulsing.
Charging at 260.
******
Oh, God. Allison.
Clear.********
Joe?
Allison.
No. Actually, I'm Todd.
I'm Todd Emory.
- What?
- I'm sorry. I wish I could explain.
I just woke up.
It's like I've been asleep for days.
The things that I've seen.
Oh, the things that I've dreamt.
I know what your wife has done for me.
And I know what my wife did to me.
Come on, Mr. Emory. Come back.
******
Clear!
- darling.
- Darling.
Shame on you!
Shame on you! You damn
near killed that man's wife!
Excuse me? Are you...
are you talking to me?
o is this? Who are you? And who are you?
He... He is a wonderful man.
And that-that... That is
his wonderful wife! And I...
I'm your husband.
The one you've been trying
to kill for the last two days.
Someone call security!
This woman is crazy! I want her
out of here! What is she doing here?
Mrs. Dubois, why don't
we get you to your room.
You waited all nig until the
nurses went on their shift change.
And then you injected an air
bubble into my I.V.Into his I.V.
And that was after she tried
to shoot me in the woods,
so she could bury me along with the
private investigator she'd already killed.
Clear!
I have no idea what this
woman is talking about.
Tell that district attorney fellow
who was at your house last night.
We have some new hair to test. Her hair.
Come on! Come on! Give
us some of your hair!
If no one is going to escort these
people out of here, then I am leaving.
She's aving. And she's
taking her hair with her.
Allison?
Todd?
Anybody?
He's coming back.
Take my wife. Please.
Take my wife.
Please.
Be my wife. Be my wife.
Please be my wife.
I would love to be your wife.
Wait a second. I already am.
Samantha Emory, the young woman arrested
at White Peaks Hospital earlier in the week
for the attempted murder of her husband,
was also charged today in the murder
of private investigator Porter Hayes,
as DNA tests place her at the locion.
Girls! Hurry up! We got to meet
your dad, and we're going to be late.
I'm just saying. I hope the school
play ends differentlyhis year.
I an, ybe this ar, it'll turn out that
vegetables are actually bad for you.
Yeah, I wouldn't count on that.
Well, where's Marie?
I'm a pea po I'm part
the vegetable group.
To maintain a healy diet, you should
have three to five servings of me per day.
Yes!
Honey, that was wonderful!
Oh, sweetie, great!
But we got to get going. We're going to
be late. We have to pick up Uncle Todd.
Mommy, Uncle Todd made me my costume.
I know. Wasn't that nice of him?
He did a really good job.
Almost as good as you.
You don't say.