ariel:
onomatopoeia.
bridgette:
what a dumb word.
i didn't ask you
to judge it.
I asked you
to spell it.
Well, that doesn't change
the fact that it's a dumb word.
I mean, you gotta wonder
what was going on in the room
The day they needed
to make up that word.
(chuckles)
Is there really a room
where they do that?
There's got to be. right?
Just spell it.
O-n...
There's more.
(air horn blares twice)
Thank you, mr. truck!
I don't understand.
What's he honking at me for?
(air horn blares twice)
It's a red light!
I don't control it.
I'll turn when it changes!
(air horn blares twice)
(truck engine revs,
car horn blares)
Ah, excellent.
(both horns blare)
(truck engine revving)
Hey! hey!
hey, what's going on?
Hey.
Stop! stop!
(tires screeching)
Ariel, do something!
Stop! stop!
(car horns honking)
(shrieks)
stop!
(horn blaring)
(gasps)
(sighs)
Talk to me.
I just hate it
that she can drive.
Ariel?
What are you talking about?
she's a really good driver.
I know.
She doesn't take any big streets
to school, does she?
I don't think she can take
any really big streets
On the way to school.
i don't think there are
any really big streets
On the way to school.
I don't think there's
even a stoplight
On the way to school.
Come on. allison, come on.
It's 4:00 in the morning.
You worked late.
You only got home
an hour and a half ago.
I'm sure it's just
a really bad dream.
Please. come on.
go back to sleep.
You're right.
She couldn't go faster
than 20 miles an hour
Even if she wanted to.
There's a stop sign
on every corner.
Exactly.
Come on. you need some rest.
we both do.
It's easy for you to say.
(phone rings)
Hello?
Man:
hello. i'm looking for
an allison dubois.
This is allison dubois.
May i ask who's calling?
I'm with the phoenix pd.
Are you the owner
Of a 1991 volvo station wagon,
dark cream?
Is something the matter?
Did you lend the vehicle
to anyone?
Is it possible it's been stolen?
My daughter.
my daughter has it.
Why are you asking
all these questions?
There's been an accident.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Ariel:
mom?!
They just came in the class
and told me what happened.
Joe:
hey.
I had to park
three blocks away.
Were you here when
this happened?
No. i had no idea.
They just, uh, they just
pulled me out of class.
You folks the owners
of the parked car?
The wagon, yeah?
The girl who was
doing the driving
Said she recognized
your daughter from school.
Oh, yeah, i've-i've
seen her around.
I think she's, um,
a year behind me.
Apparently, she has
her learner's permit,
So mom let her get behind
the wheel to drive to school.
She was driving
down this street
Looking for a place
to pull over
And a cat
crossed the road.
I guess she tried
to hit the brake,
Hit the gas instead, panicked,
jerked the steering wheel,
Went across the road
and plowed into your car.
It's pretty
cut-and-dry.
Nobody hurt.
really about tow trucks
And insurance companies
at this point.
Thank you.
Okay, thanks.
thank you.
Mr. and mrs. dubois,
I'm lauren portman.
i'm jamie's mom.
And i could not be
sorrier about this.
Uh, well, you know,
the good news is
That, you know, none
of the kids were hurt, so...
I'm joe dubois.
This is my wife allison.
this is ariel.
Hi.
Hi. and you're right,
That is the most
important thing.
She's actually a
good little driver.
I just think, you know,
being late for school
And that cat...
mom, it's okay.
So, um, i guess
this is the part
Where we exchange the
insurance information.
Right.
Of course, we are
completely at fault.
And i promise i
will make that clear
To the insurance company
when i call them.
My husband has his-- thanks--
His, uh, car here
if you need a ride somewhere.
Oh, no, we're fine.
you know how it is.
As long as the kids are
fine, everything's fine.
Okay, i'll ask.
What about any of this
is making you happy?
What makes you think
i'm happy?
Look at that.
You got that goofy
grin on your face.
You know that that
car of yours is
Pretty long
in the tooth.
I mean, i'm not
even sure
The insurance company is gonna
want to pay us to get it fixed.
They might just want
to write you a check
And, you know,
total the thing
And be done with it.
Well, they have to fix it,
don't they?
No, not if it costs more
than the car's worth.
Well, it's like
that lady said,
As long as the kids
are fine...
You love that car.
Yeah, i do,
but you know
About that horrible dream
i had last night.
The one where ariel and the kids
were killed in the car
On the way to school?
so, it can't happen now.
There's no car
for it to happen in.
Aha.
Ah, capisce. mm.
Well, we may be getting
ahead of ourselves.
We still gotta wait
To hear from the body
shop and the adjusters.
Oh, hey, by the way, was there
anything in that dream
About how we're supposed
to pay for whatever it is
We buy to replace the
car that you love
But that you're now
convinced is a death trap?
Take that as a no.
You sure you're okay with
me just dropping you off
At the car rental place?
You don't want me to
go in there with you?
Oh, please,
i know how to rent a car.
I can rent a car.
I'm not... okay.
(chuckles)
Sorry, ma'am,
but it's after 10:00.
I'm afraid your options
are gonna be pretty limited.
In fact, i'm showing
that we have nothing.
Are you serious?
(chuckles)
My husband just
dropped me off.
I've no way of
getting home.
You know what?
Let's go out there
and take a look.
That's it?
Kinda looks like
more than i need.
Rental agent:
wow. i don't even see
it on the manifest.
Must have just
come back in.
You want me to clean it up?
(cell phone rings)
Everything okay, ma'am?
I'm sorry.
somebody from work.
They want me
to meet them.
Do you know where
thunderhead pass is?
No, but that's okay.
this guy's got a nav system.
Hell, these terrains have
everything in them.
Do you want me to clean it up?
Actually, maybe i'll just
take it the way it is.
(horn honking)
Nice wheels.
It's a rental.
My car's in the shop.
don't ask.
Okay, i won't.
I appreciate you driving out
to the middle of nowhere.
I'm kind of dealing with
a head-scratcher here,
And i suddenly thought that
this might be up your alley.
A big telecommunications company
has cell phone towers out here.
And the guy in charge
of maintaining them
Was driving along the
access road this morning
When he noticed this.
Somebody set off
Some kind of explosive
device here last night.
The question is, what for?
Was it just a prank or could
it have been a dress rehearsal
For something to come?
I was out here all morning
with the forensics boys
And all we found were a
bunch of tiny shards.
Some metal,
some plastic.
I was hoping you could
help me figure out
Whether this was just someone
getting their jollies on
Or if it's actually something
we should be concerned about.
(police radio buzzes on)
Man (over radio):
hq to detective scanlon.
what's your 20?
They always call when
you're nowhere near the car.
(laughs)
man:
one, two,
Three, four, five, six,
Seven, eight, nine,
Ten, 11, 12, 13, 14,
15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20,
21, 22.
Twenty-two.
(beeping)
(beeping slowly)
(beeping rapidly)
(explosion echoes)
Scanlon:
you all right?
Yeah, i'm fine.
Well, i think i can tell you
what happened here.
I can't really explain it,
but i can describe it.
(ringing)
Uh...
Hello?
Joe:
i was just calling to see
How things went
at the rental place.
Well, it went fine.
Uh, i ended up with something
a little fancier
Than i'd normally go for,
but it was all they had.
This is kind of cool, though.
I'm talking to you
through the car speakers.
That's actually
called bluetooth, al.
It's been around for years.
Listen, um,
I don't want to freak you out,
But the buttons
on the car door--
They make the windows
go up and down.
You're very funny.
You're very comical.
Actually, there's all kinds
of gizmos in here,
And i'm going to have
to figure them out for myself.
Okay. i'll call you later?
Call you later.
(beep)
Woman (over radio):
this is satellite traffic
for boston.
We're looking
at bumper-to-bumper traf...
Man:
you're listening
to satellite traffic for denver.
Major...
(woman speaking over radio
in portuguese)
(song plays in foreign language)
(turns up volume)
Man (over radio):
are you sure?
I mean, really sure?
Like, we can call
my parents, sure?
Woman:
i can't be positive,
but i took four
Of those take-home tests,
and they all were.
(couple laughing excitedly)
Man:
we're having a baby?
We're having a baby.
(woman laughing)
(horn honking)
Oh!
(radio switches back to music)
(turns volume up)
(music cuts out,
couple argues in spanish)
(radio switches back to music)
(music cuts out)
Man (over radio):
don't kill me, okay?
Man 2:
you need to stop crying.
people can see.
You need to pull
yourself together.
The light's green. go.
(man whimpering)
I'm sorry.
i think it's the gun.
Uh...
Seeing it-it... it make...
It's making me shake.
I... i can barely hold
the steering wheel.
Look, if it's the car,
i'll give it to you.
(man panting)
I'll... i'll just get out,
And you can get behind the wheel
and drive away.
(man groaning)
(man whimpering)
That gun in my... my side...
Just please don't kill me.
Just don't...
My god, don't kill me, okay?
I beg... don't...
(radio switches back to music)
woman (over radio):
meanwhile, in washington
earlier today,
Congressional leaders...
Man:
and, over on the hardwood...
I'm telling you, i heard
someone being kidnapped.
It wasn't doing
that this morning.
This morning, i could hear
other people's conversations.
I could see them
talking in their car,
And i could hear
them in here.
(sighs)
well, it's not doing it now.
Well, i know it's
not doing it now.
Um, i don't know
what to tell you, al.
Maybe the
satellite radio
Was picking up
cell phone signals.
They weren't talking
on their cell phones.
They were talking to each
other-- i could see them.
Well, you called
detective scanlon,
And you described
the vehicle, right?
A blue pickup.
Well, i think it's out
of your hands, then.
I think you've done
all that you can.
I got to head inside, al.
You know, i promised
that woman whose, uh,
Daughter ran into your car
that i'd call her
The moment that we heard
from her insurance company.
Um, you're welcome
to come with me.
Or, if you'd rather just listen
to what we have to say,
You could always just
turn on your car radio.
Jerk.
woman:
good morning.
How may i help you today?
Man:
i need you to give me
all of your money.
Please, i don't have
a lot of time.
I need you
to fill these two bags.
I'm sorry--
i know i'm scaring you--
But i need you to do
exactly as i tell you,
Or everyone in this bank
is going to die.
(gasps)
you've reached the cell phone
of detective lee scanlon.
if this is an emergency,
dial 911.
If not, leave a message
after the beep.
(beep)
Hey, lee, it's allison again.
Look, i've been trying
to get a hold of you
Since 4:00 in the morning.
I'm on my way to the office.
Can you give me a call
when you get this?
(electronic chiming)
uh, uh...
Uh, lee, um, i think i'm getting
another call.
Uh, if i lose you, i'm sorry.
I'm just kind of new to this.
(beep)
hello?
Allison, it's lee.
You been trying
to get a hold of me?
Uh, yeah, i... i have.
Look, i had a dream last night
about a... a bank robbery.
Well, then, you just may
be batting two for two.
What are you talking about?
I'm standing outside the main
branch of mariposa national.
Some guy walked in here
45 minutes ago
And tried to rob the place.
Teller hit the silent alarm.
We think he's got 18 hostages
in there, and of course,
We've got every cop
in phoenix out here.
But here's the part
i thought you'd like.
Turns out our bank robber showed
up in a blue pickup truck.
Lee, he's got a bomb.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
say that again.
A bomb.
He's wearing a bomb.
You have to get everyone out
of that bank.
You've got to get someone
from the bomb squad over there.
Okay, i'm on it.
(siren wailing,
helicopter blades whirring)
Lieutenant wilkes,
this is that woman
I was telling you about.
Allison, this is
patrick wilkes,
The best bomb man
in the southwest.
So, you've seen it?
The bomb?
I think so. yeah.
It... it was strapped to
his body, kind of like a vest.
And it had, uh,
all those padlocks on it.
You see any wires?
Wires?
lots of wires.
And, uh, there were bricks--
like clay.
And for what it's worth,
he seemed genuinely scared.
Almost as if he...
he didn't want to be there.
Almost as if,
uh, it wasn't his idea.
What?
The bank robber's been
on the phone
With the hostage
negotiator.
He claims someone forced him
to do what he's doing.
Says a guy in a ski mask
climbed into his truck yesterday
And held him at gunpoint.
Made him drive to some kind
of trailer workshop,
Where he and another man
locked this bomb--
Which i guess is this vest thing
You're talking about--
onto his body.
Well, i think
he's telling the truth.
And that explosion
in the desert--
I think it's all part of this.
It must have been a test.
Whoever strapped that bomb
to that poor man...
He must have
been practicing.
Apparently,
it's a remote control rig.
He's telling
the hostage negotiators,
If we don't let him walk out
of there,
If he hasn't delivered the money
to the guy who abducted him
Within the next half hour,
The whole place
is going to blow.
You have to
let him go.
All-all those
people in there.
Actually, he's letting them out.
The hostage negotiator
convinced him that patrick here
Could defuse
that rig he's wearing,
But that we had to get
all the people out first.
Is that true?
can you do that?
Been doing it 15 years.
But the truth is,
I won't know until i get a look
at the thing.
I'm sorry.
i wish...
I wish i could
tell you more.
No, it all helps.
Really.
The, uh, detective here tells me
that you're a wife and a mother.
(sighs)
Do me a favor, then.
Get out of here.
As far as you can,
as fast as you can.
(school bell ringing)
Ariel:
looks like it hurts.
Oh. hey.
Uh, yeah, that seat belt
Really dug into
me yesterday.
Thought this shirt covered
it up more, but...
Um, i'm jamie.
Ariel.
I'm... i'm sorry
about yesterday.
I... it's really
embarrassing
And upsetting
And...
you know,
at this point, it's...
It's just an inconvenience.
Yeah, but, i mean, your
parents were so nice.
Do you  want to, you know,
borrow this?
To cover the, uh...
oh.
Sure. thank you.
yeah.
(chuckles)
Oh, no, no.
What did i
just do?
Jamie, are you
all right?
Yeah. yeah, i'm all right.
I'm a little sore,
but i'm all right.
Listen to me. we've got
to get out of the car
Right now before
anyone gets here.
And when people do get here,
you've got to tell them
That you were driving.
you understand?
What? no. why?
Sweetie, my record's
not perfect.
If the police find out
that i was driving,
They'd... they'll
give me tests.
Oh, i love you, baby.
Um...
Can i ask you a question?
If you were driving
yesterday morning,
Then how come
your seat belt bruises
Are on your right shoulder?
I mean, if you were driving,
they would be on your left.
You weren't driving,
were you?
Look, we already said the
accident was our fault,
So what does it matter
who was driving?
The insurance is
going to pay for it.
(school bell ringing)
I... i guess
we got to go.
(sighs)
Thanks for the scarf.
Yeah.
male newscaster:
once again, we're told
the bomb squad
Is on the scene
at the mariposa national bank.
And that an expert of some kind
Has been in the bank
for ten minutes now,
But beyond that, officials
are being tight-lipped.
We can tell you,
if you're driving in that area,
Traffic is at
a virtual standstill.
In sports, the national
hockey league featured a...
Man (over radio):
oh, god, god, god, god.
Wilkes:
i need you to
stop doing that.
And i need you to
stop shaking.
Okay.
(horn honking)
I think i've got this
wiring system clocked.
Okay.
(beeping)
Wait, what is that?
why is it doing that?
It's just acting up 'cause
i'm monkeying with it.
Doesn't mean it's
going to explode.
How do you know that?
You-you can't
be sure.
Yeah, actually, i can.
I've disarmed systems
a lot more complicated
Than this one.
Timer's still got about
ten minutes left on it.
Trust me-- it's not
even going to be close.
Now, listen.
This wire i'm looking
at right here?
yeah.
The yellow one?
mm-hmm.
I'm going to
cut it now.
Iafter i cut it,
we'll be in the clear.
You ready?
Just do it.
Okay.
Here we go.
(snipping)
Is that it?
Did... did it work?
Can you... can you get
this thing off me now?
Cut these locks off.
(rapid beeping)
Wait a second.
What is that?
is that... wait.
Hey. is it supposed
to be doing that?
(booming)
All right.
Lieutenant wilkes
is going to be okay.
Apparently, there was
some sort of delay
After the bomb
armed itself.
He had a couple of seconds
to run for cover.
The fire department found
him pinned under a desk.
That desk took the brunt
of the explosion.
Headgear and body armor
handled the rest.
What about the bank robber?
The man wearing the vest?
Yeah, not so lucky.
Crime scene boys found
a piece of a jawbone
And the tip of an
index finger.
That's it.
Everything else was
obliterated--
Including all the money
he was trying to steal.
Well, that's the thing.
i don't think he was
Trying to steal any money.
I think he was a victim
in all of this.
I think somebody forced him
to go into that bank.
Lee told me about
the thing you heard
Or overheard in your car?
Well, i can't, uh,
Shed much light on any of that,
but i can tell you this,
The man who tried
to rob that bank?
He's no stranger to robbery
And he's no stranger to banks.
Name's troy sanborn.
Did five years
Back in the late '90s
for walking into a bank
In denver with a hand grenade.
Wait a second.
if it was his bomb,
Why would he let the bomb squad
in to take look at it?
Why would he let anyone
take a look at it?
And why would
he let it go off?
They think he made it up.
the whole story.
They think he strapped
that bomb to himself
So that after he dumped
the cash that he stole,
He could claim he was
the victim all along.
But let's say
you're right.
Let's say there really is a
second man out there somewhere.
The only thing we know about him
Is that he was wearing
a ski mask
When this supposed abduction
took place.
The one person who could tell us
anything more than that--
Troy sanborn-- is dead.
Now, i know the crime
scene unit recovered
Some small pieces
of the bomb's casing.
Maybe, if we're lucky,
that'll lead us somewhere.
But if it doesn't?
If this mastermind
You believe you heard the other
day really does exist?
Well, he's going to be awfully
hard to track down.
no, that's
Very thoughtful of you
to call, mrs. portman.
Uh, but, no, honestly,
Everything has gone
really well
With your insurance
company so far.
And, uh, the truth is,
we still haven't gotten
An estimate back from the,
uh, from the body shop.
Uh-huh.
Oh, that is a very,
very generous offer,
But i'm-i'm sure that we...
We don't need to take you up
on that.
Okay.
Yeah.
You have a nice night, too, now.
Bye-bye.
It's, uh, lauren portman,
The, uh, saint lauren portman.
Um, she sends you her regards.
And she wants to thank you
again for your patience.
Well, if someone had
to hit my car,
I guess i'm glad
she's the one who did it.
I know, we should try
to schedule all
Of our future
wrecks with her.
She even offered to
drive ariel to school.
Who offered to drive
me to school?
Uh, jamie's mom.
She, uh... that was her
on the phone just now.
Yeah, well, i'm not getting
in a car with that woman.
Well, you don't have to.
It's just nice to know that,
you know, we have the option.
Okay, but that's not
an option for me.
(music playing)
(phone ringing)
(man humming along with music)
Man's voice:
leave a message.
Automated voice:
hello.
This is a message
for jesse reeder
Concerning the collection
of an unpaid debt.
If you are not jesse reeder,
Please contact
the ulterion credit agency
And calls to this number
will cease.
Thank you.
(machine beeps)
(man humming)
Jesse reeder.
(school bell ringing)
ashley:
check it out.
My article on the football team
Made the front page
of the school paper.
No way.
way way.
Mr. benevento said
I'm the first junior to do it
in seven years.
In particular
interest to you
Will be the fifth paragraph
in the second column,
Where i write about my good
friend ariel dubois
Totally wanting junior
sensation chad colburn.
Oh.
(laughs)
Uh, you know,
i was just kidding
About that last
part, right?
Huh?
I didn't actually write about
you wanting chad colburn.
Joe:
but why do you care?
What kind of question is that?
Oh, i don't know.
i'm just fascinated.
I mean, after all these years
I'm still trying to figure out
how your mind works.
I mean, this guy, he gets blown
up trying to rob a bank.
The guy who made his
living robbing banks.
The guy who once walked into
a bank full of people
with a hand grenade.
Me?
I-i kinda figure
good riddance.
But you-- you're
all worked up
That maybe somehow this
guy's a victim in all this.
Well, maybe it has
nothing to do with him.
I mean, it's more like...
It's like a thank you note
that you didn't write.
You wake up every morning
and you think,
"oh, gotta that note."
And you never get around to it.
And then one day
you finally do it.
You write it.
And then you feel better.
You feel... in balance.
I just know that this guy
Did not walk into that bank
of his own free will.
And until everybody else
knows it...
And you call that
thing a gift.
(groans)
(sighs)
(phone ringing)
Hello-hello?
Scanlon:
you were right and i was wrong.
You were right
and we were all wrong.
Really? what i was right about?
Well, jesse reeder, for one.
We found him.
We found that trailer
you dreamed about, too.
It's like bombs"r"us in here.
Wires, detonators,
blasting caps, you name it.
Even a mannequin rigged up
with one of his bomb vests.
Which makes me think maybe you
were right about troy sanborn.
Maybe he was a patsy.
Maybe reeder was the one
pulling the strings.
Really? did reeder confess?
No, but then he's not
in much of a position to.
Looks like he was gearing up
to rob another bank,
When something went off
in his face.
Truth is, there's just not
a whole lot left of him.
The way it stands,
Forensics is going to have
to scrape bits and pieces
Off the walls and ceiling
So we can make a dna match
and issue a death certificate.
Well, thanks for that visual.
I'm going to go back
to sleep now.
Well, i'm going to try, anyway.
Nighty-night.
There you go.
All your thank you
notes are done.
You feel better?
I don't know.
ask me in the morning.
(metallic rattling, siren wails)
(helicopter blades whirring)
(distant siren wailing)
(metallic rattling)
I'm going to die.
We're both going to die,
mr. sanborn.
Just not today.
(metallic rattling)
Mind if i ask why you're holding
those keys there?
Um, they open
the safe deposit boxes.
The man who put this vest on me
Told me to get them
from the bank manager.
He was very specific.
What do you say you let me hold
them for a little while?
That rattling's
kind of distracting.
Okay.
There you go.
We're about ready to get
down to business here.
I'm going to make a quick sweep,
Make sure nobody's here,
and then we'll get started.
Okay?
No, you're leaving me?
Just for a second,
i promise.
Now, you stand here
and try not to move,
And then i'll be right back.
Okay? in a jiffy.
Okay?
Nice and easy, troy.
Stay perfectly still.
(helicopter blades whirring,
siren wailing)
Okay, we're ready
to get started.
Try to stay calm,
mr. sanborn.
I think i've got this wiring
system all figured out.
(gasps)
I'm sorry, allison,
but you're telling me
That you think patrick wilkes,
The man who almost
got himself killed
Trying to defuse that bomb,
is the same man
Who strapped it on
to troy sanborn?
Not only that.
i'm telling you
He managed to steal
a little over $400,000
While he was at it.
that doesn't sense.
The bomb almost
killed wilkes.
no, it didn't.
After he triggered
the detonating device--
And make no mistake, he is
the one who triggered it--
He had a few seconds
to jump behind that desk.
And he knew
he would have those few seconds
'cause he's the one
who rigged that bomb.
I mean, think
about it.
How much sense does it make
To strap a bomb onto somebody
And ask them
to rob a bank for you?
I mean, how can you be sure
that the police aren't going
To follow him back
to where you're hiding?
Wouldn't you be better off
Figuring a way
to get into the bank yourself,
So you could hide the money
where no one would find it?
Patrick wilkes
knew that
He was gonna be called in
to defuse that bomb,
Just like he knew the police
were gonna cut the power
To that bank while they were
negotiating with troy sanborn.
He was counting on it.
With all
of the security cameras down,
He'd have
plenty of time
To-to stash the money
that he'd forced
Sanborn to steal,
and after that,
The bomb took care of the rest.
The one witness that he had
to the crime was dead,
And the money
That he took would be presumed
lost in the explosion.
No one would even bother
trying to look for it.
Allison,
We found a bomb
vest identical
To the one that
killed troy sanborn
In jesse reeder's home.
Jesse reeder's the
guy you told us to
go find, remember?
So, reeder built
and tested a bomb for wilkes.
And wilkes didn't need reeder
anymore. boom.
I bet you wilkes is
counting on the fact
That finding reeder's body
closes the case.
I don't know what to tell you,
allison.
Most people in this city think
that patrick wilkes is a hero.
They're even giving him a medal
This afternoon.
I can prove what wilkes did.
What's this?
serial numbers
On the deposit boxes
that wilkes used.
Open them up.
You'll find the money.
(school bell ringing)
Here's the thing.
You can't get in the car
with your mom again.
Not when she's driving.
Excuse me?
Look, i know
that you love her,
And i know that it's really hard
to wrap your brain around it,
But she's going to get you
killed if you let her,
So you can't let her.
I'm not guessing
About something
that might happen.
I am telling you about something
That is going to happen.
This is the thing
that people talk about
About you and your
mom, isn't it?
Yeah.
Well, you don't know
what you're saying.
I mean, you don't
know my mom.
She's a great mom.
She is a great mom,
But she's got a problem.
So, how do i get to school?
We'll walk.
I'll walk with you.
And after school, you can
practice driving with me
So that we can get you
your license,
So that you can drive,
really drive,
And not just take the blame
when she does.
So call her
And tell her that she doesn't
have to pick you up
Because you're gonna walk home
with a friend.
allison:
what do you mean,
the money wasn't there?
Scanlon:
i mean, we went to the bank,
And we opened up
the safe deposit boxes
You told us about,
and they were empty.
According to the manager,
The woman
who rented them came in
First thing in the morning,
and, uh, cleaned them out.
Woman? what woman?
And how did she get in there?
I thought the bank was closed
for repairs.
It is, except
for the safe deposit boxes.
They're downstairs, and there
wasn't any damage down there.
Now, as for who this woman was,
your guess is as good as mine.
The paperwork she filled out
was signed alma harrison.
Only thing
i can tell you for sure is
That that's not her real name.
What do you mean?
The driver's license,
credit card, social,
Home address she filled out
at the bank-- all that's bogus.
We don't even have
a good picture of her
On the bank security system.
I'm looking at the footage
that was recorded
On the day she rented the boxes,
And all i can tell you is
that she's caucasian,
Approximately five feet,
five inches,
And knows how to duck
Every time she gets close
to one of the cameras.
Well, obviously,
she's wilkes's accomplice.
He-he stashed the money,
and she went in to get it.
You got to bring wilkes in.
Based on what?
None of this proves anything.
A woman with a fake id rented
some boxes at a bank.
Now, would i like
to find her? sure.
Ask her some questions
about patrick wilkes?
Absolutely.
But i don't have a name,
and i don't have an address.
And unless you can tell me
where to locate her, i'm sorry,
But i just can't see us bringing
a case against this guy.
We still friends?
Not so sure about that.
You look happy.
Looks can be deceiving.
I got some good news
and some bad news.
Which do you want?
Give me some good news.
I could use some good news.
The good news is,
the insurance company wants
To write us a check for $2,300.
Well, actually,
that is good news.
So, what's the bad news?
The bad news is,
it's going to cost over $7,000
To repair your car,
which makes no sense.
I think we need to think
about getting a new car.
I don't want to think
about buying a new car.
I have other things
to think about.
You need a car,
And putting $7,000 into one
from the early '90s...
Hey, i heard you.
You know, most people kind of
like getting a new car.
They think it's fun,
they find it exciting.
Well, i'm not like most people.
You know my
dad gave me
That car as a present
for graduating college.
I know.
Well, did i
ever tell you
What i told him when
he gave it to me?
I said i hated it.
I said, "what kind of person
gives a 21-year-old girl
A station wagon?"
And he just looked at me,
and he said, "it's really safe."
And he died four days later.
So, don't push it.
I know what i have to do.
I've known what i had to do
Since i had that dream
of ariel and the girls
And-and that...
that wide road and that truck.
And i will deal with it
When it has to
be dealt with.
woman:
it's done.
Alma harrison is now
the proud renter
Of six large safe deposit boxes
at mariposa national.
Wilkes:
no trouble with the fake id,
the credit card?
None. but do you want
to hear something funny?
You gave alma the same birthday
as the bank manager.
Told him i'd send him a card
that day.
Aren't i an angel?
I'm headed back
to my place now.
Come by after work,
And i will give you the keys
to the boxes.
Female automated voice:
please enter an address.
Wilkes:
what was that?
Uh, it's nothing.
It's the nav system in my car.
I got a little turned around
on my way down from peoria, so
I thought i would try
to find a quicker way back.
(navigation system beeps,
horn honking)
You still there?
Baby, tell me you didn't just
say that you're in your car.
Tell me you took a taxi,
like we planned.
I didn't take a taxi, patrick.
How many times
did we go over this?
The bank has security cameras
outside, too.
If one of them recorded
your license plate...
I didn't come here
in my car, okay?
I'm not an idiot.
I thought i should test run
The id and credit cards
you gave me
Before i used them at the bank,
so i rented a car for myself.
If my license plate
got recorded, who cares?
They'll just trace it back
To the rental office
and alma harrison.
Damn it!
What's wrong?
I dropped my cd between
the seats, and i can't find it.
Screw it.
In a few days, i will be able
to buy all the music i want.
If the guy at the rental office
finds it, he can keep it.
(crickets chirping)
(laughs)
Female automated voice:
please enter an address.
(beeps)
Peoria.
(beep)
Thanks.
woman (on tv):
stunning turn of events
As lieutenant Patrick wilkes,
who only yesterday was honored
By the city
for his heroic effort
During the recent
mariposa national bank robbery,
Was arrested this morning
For masterminding
the robbery himself.
The nearly $400,000
That was thought destroyed
in the explosion
That rocked the downtown bank
earlier this week
Was recovered earlier today
at the home
Of wilkes's alleged accomplice,
erica duvall of peoria.
Peoria.
Joe:
okay.
Ready to go.
Where are the girls?
Uh, ariel already
took them to school.
Really?
(car horn toots twice)
(horn toots twice)
Come on.
Get in. we're not
walking today.
Wow. is this new?
Yeah. my mom
was renting it,
And then, she called
them this morning
And told them that
she wanted to buy it.
Nice.
yeah.
Okay. onomatopoeia.
What a dumb word.
I didn't ask
you to judge it.
I asked you
to spell it.
bridgette:
well, that doesn't change
the fact that it's a dumb word.
i mean, you got to wonder what
was going on in the room
the day they needed
to make up that word.
marie:
is there really a room
where they do that?
bridgette:
there's got to be. right?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com