Previously on Medium...
He's dying. The mayor,
the governer,
they all want me to step in.
They gave him his job back.
That's amazing.
- That means that you get your job back?
- As soon as I want.
- Who's that?
- Terry Cavanaugh.
The John D. Rockefeller
of solar energy.
You know I bought your company,
I bought your invention.
How'd you like to finish
what you start?
He said, "do it in Phoenix".
Find some space, hire some people.
Make me some money.
Tonight, on Ripley's
Believe It or Not,
you'll meet a hungry, young woman
with an appetite
for cold steel.
A music lover who has turned
his very extremities
into a sonorous instrument.
A contortionist
who's perfected a method
for examining his own spine.
But first, in 1848,
Phineas Gage was part of a workgang,
Blasting Rock
were clearing the roadbed
for a new railroad line.
On september 13th of that year,
Phineas' life
would be changed forever
by one simple spark.
He was tamping down
an explosive charge with an iron rod
when the gunpowder ignited early
and a three-foot iron rod
was blown clear
through Phineas' skull.
Miraculously, Phineas survived.
His body, it seemed,
had made a complete recovery.
His spirit, on the other hand...
Those who knew Phineas' best
said he was a changed man
after his accident.
Once even-keeled and hardworking,
he was now fitful, irreverent
and grossly profane.
But would it surprise you to learn
that Phineas,
after a long night of drinking,
once identified himself
to a fellow inebriate
as "Cyrus Ames"?
Who, you ask, was Cyrus Ames?
Cyrus Ames was a notorious
gunfighter and card cheat.
For a time, he was employed
by the railroads
to shoot any Indians who attempted
to interfere with the construction.
On the day of Phineas' accident,
Cyrus Ames lay dying of syphilis
in the very same doctor's office
where Phineas was treated.
Some believe
that an exchange of sorts
took place that day.
That the soul of a dying gunfighter
somehow slipped into the body
of an injured railroad worker.
Coincidence?
We may never know.
Unlikely? Yes.
Impossible?
You be the judge.
A man by the name of
Robert l. Ripley, after all,
would challenge you
to believe it or not!
Bad dream?
Bad rerun.
It was weird, I dreamt
about an old TV show.
You mean no one's in danger?
You don't have to call anyone?
We can just go back to sleep?
I don't believe it.
transcript: www.ragbear.com
www.sub-way.fr
www.seriessub.com
Allison, you're here. Good.
Once settled, join me and Lee
for a meeting, please?
With him?
With them.
Lee, Allison, this is Joel Tiernan.
And sitting beside him is my old
friend, his wife, Gabrielle.
Six months ago, Gabrielle's sister,
Robin, was found murdered
in a cottage she'd rented
on Saguaro Lake.
There were no witnesses
and as of now,
no suspects.
This all took place when D.A.
Van Dyke was running this office.
His people worked the case
but never solved it.
I believe it was...
August 16th
when I first realized that
the Phoenix police
department had given up
on trying to find
my sister's killer.
I had called district attorney
Van Dyke for an update,
and...
he told me there were
no new developments in the case.
When I asked him when I might
expect any new developments,
he was kind enough to explain to me
that good police work
depends on good leads.
And since there were
no new leads in the case...
Six months ago, there was nothing
I could do about that.
Now I can.
That's why I'm putting
my two best people on it.
I'm going to tell her everything.
What did you just say?
You heard me.
I'm going to tell her everything.
I think I saw his face.
- What are you talking about?
- The killer, I think I saw his face.
Put me together
with a sketch artist,
we might have something for you
to work with this afternoon.
Hey, kiddo.
How was school?
Why the long face?
I sort of got
in trouble in art class.
Oh, yeah?
What happened?
I kind of drew a funny picture
of my teacher,
Mr. Enright.
Did you apologize?
Well, yeah, but he wants you and mom
to look at the picture
anyways and sign it
- so he knows you saw it.
- Okay.
Bridgette, you drew this?
That man is naked.
He sure is.
This is the man you
believe murdered Robin Aaronson?
I think it's a pretty good likeness.
Tell me, is this the man you saw?
Yes. Absolutely.
- You know this man?
- I knew him.
Gabrielle's first husband, Nathan.
He was a very successful novelist,
and when he died, he left
Gabrielle a very wealthy woman.
He's dead?
Killed in a car crash two years ago,
driving home from a writers' retreat.
Struck head-on by another
vehicle, a stolen vehicle.
By the time the accident
site was discovered,
the other driver, the car thief,
had disappeared.
Skulked off into the night.
We never managed to identify him.
I'm sorry, Allison. I don't know
what you think you saw,
Nathan's dead for two years,
he couldn't have killed 6 months ago.
Look on the bright side. At least
this woman wasn't in the room
when you accused her dead
husband of murdering her sister.
Would you put that
thing away already?
I'm sorry.
It's just so...
Accurate?
Yeah, I mean I know
we've had the talk with Bridgette,
And I know she's seen all this stuff
in science class, but it's just...
But what?
You're acting like you never drew
a picture of a naked person before.
I'm sure that I scribbled
the occasional "bazoom" in my notebook,
but nothing like this.
What? A young boy's fascination
with "bazooms" is okay?
But a young girl's curiosity
about that, isn't?
I'm just going to turn off
the light now.
Yeah, you do that.
So, you're telling me
Joel Tiernan did this?
Joel Tiernan, Gabrielle Tiernan's
current husband,
is the hit-and-run driver
who killed her first husband,
Nathan Cafferty?
That is one very forgiving lady.
Obviously, I don't think she knows.
Obviously.
Look, I know how this sounds, Lee,
but I dreamt about it last night.
Joel Tiernan was the other driver
in that accident.
I think that's how he got
that big scar on his forehead.
What?!
I'm sorry, it's just Manny
puts us on one cold case,
and you start dreaming about
another that's even colder.
You may see
who took the Lindbergh baby.
What if i'm right? What if Joel
Tiernan is responsible for this?
If you're sure about what you saw,
and when I say "sure," I'm talking
in the neighborhood of 100 percent,
then I'll bring the guy in
for questioning,
ask him to account
for his whereabouts.
But if you're not...
Remember, these are Manny's friends.
At least the wife is.
If you're right about this Tiernan guy,
Gabrielle sure can pick them.
- What do you mean?
- I interviewed a few
of the dead sister's friends
yesterday.
One of them told me about a little
accident Robin had in '06.
She claimed she'd fallen, but the friend
spotted some bruising around her neck.
Got the feeling she may have
been covering for someone.
An abusive boyfriend, maybe.
Turns out she was.
And his name was Nathan Cafferty.
She was having an affair
with her sister's husband?
For about a year until Nathan decided
he was still in love with Gabrielle.
According to the friend,
Robin didn't take it well.
Threatened to tell her sister.
Nathan got physical.
Grabbed Robin by the neck,
threw her up against the wall.
It happened in the same cabin
she died in.
I saw it, Lee.
I saw it yesterday.
I just didn't understand.
So, so, wait...
so, if Robin was having
an affair with Nathan,
shouldn't we bring in Gabrielle for
questioning? She has the motive.
If she knew her sister was getting it on
with her husband, sure.
But according to the friend,
she never found out.
Besides, I did some checking. There are
photos of her at some charity event
in Flagstaff till the wee hours
on the night of the murder.
Plus, she's the one that came
to us for help, remember?
It wouldn't make much sense to
reheat a case that'd gone cold
if you were the killer,
now, would it?
Hey, it's me.
I got a call from Bridgette's school.
They want us to come in today at 3:00
to meet with her art teacher
and a school counselor.
I teach art, Mr. And Mrs. Dubois.
I'm not a prudish man,
and if I were teaching
a life drawing class
to a group of college students,
I might be inclined
to laugh this off,
but the fact is,
Bridgette is a ten-year-old
in a fourth grade art class,
and this is the second time
in two days she's drawn
a vivid portrait of me...
Her teacher.
I don't know what to say,
Mr. Enright.
This obviously is inappropriate,
and we're very sorry.
I appreciate that.
And please understand, she's one
of the most imaginative students
I've ever had the pleasure to teach.
I adore having her in the class,
but I'd be lying
if I said the last couple of days
haven't been disturbing to me.
So, that's why I asked
Mrs. Tharp to sit in with us.
Mr. Enright and I thought
that perhaps Bridgette
could use the benefit of
a few sessions with me.
You think that Bridgette
needs to see a psychologist?
- Because of this?
- The drawings are rather graphic.
We just wanted to find out where
Bridgette got the impulse to make them.
To see if she's been exposed
to anything that could have
caused this preoccupation
with the naked form.
Wait a second. She hasn't
been exposed to anything,
and this is not a preoccupation.
It's just a kid using her imagination.
Bridgette needs a lesson
in what's appropriate and not.
She doesn't need to go to therapy.
With all due respect,
you're not the subject
of the drawings, Mr. Dubois. I am.
I'm not sure
I agree with your assessment.
I'm not sure that you know my daughter
as well as you think, Mr. Enright.
Mrs. Tharp,
we do appreciate your offer, I think
we'll to speak with Bridgette ourselves
before we take you up on that.
Mr. Enright,
I am sorry
for any kind of discomfort
or embarrassment that our daughter
may have caused you.
We'll make sure we speak
with Bridgette and let her know
that these kinds of drawings
in school are not appropriate.
Absolutely.
And I promise you this
will never happen again.
Hi, kiddo.
How you doing?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's okay, sweetie.
We're not mad at you.
But you need to stop drawing
pictures of your teacher.
It's making him uncomfortable.
Well, I didn't want to draw
another picture of Mr. Enright.
I just felt like I had to.
- What do you mean, you had to?
- I don't know.
When I close my eyes,
I see him in my head.
And I just know that I have
to put it down on paper.
Maybe Vridgette's not
the problem here.
Maybe it's that teacher
we should be worried about.
What are you saying?
This is Mr. Enright's fault?
I don't know. All I know is
that she goes in his class,
and then she feels like she has to
draw him without his clothes on.
Why? What's going on
in this guy's head?
What kind of, I don't know,
energy is bridgette picking up on?
What are you saying? Mr. Enright's
putting in some kind of "naked energy"?
I don't know but we should talk
to the school,
and get her transferred
to another class.
Okay, good luck
with that conversation.
You'd better make sure that
you have your facts straight.
If you're going to accuse somebody
of putting out a "naked vibe,"
make sure you have
all your ducks in a row.
How you can just dismiss this?
I'm not. It'll pass, Joe.
I asked Bridgette specifically,
"did anything inappropriate happen?"
"Anything at all that made you feel
uncomfortable?" She said no.
It'll pass.
Whatever it is that's making her
want to draw these pictures,
It'll pass.
If we make a huge thing of this,
we're just going to make Bridgette
more confused than she already is.
All right, you got me thinking.
I just took a look at our files
on Nathan Cafferty's accident.
Unfortunately, it turns out
the city destroyed both cars
about a year ago.
We won't find any DNA to help us figure
out who was driving that other car,
but I did find one
interesting thing.
Turns out our friend
Joel has a record.
Arrested in '02 for car theft,
and again in '04 for check-kiting.
Although how that proves he killed
Nathan Cafferty, I've no idea.
What about the papers?
Maybe you should check the papers.
What papers?
The papers from the accident scene.
They were everywhere.
There were hundreds of them.
I saw Joel touch one of them.
If they're in the evidence locker,
we should check them for fingerprints.
I'm looking at the report right here,
and there's no mention of any papers.
It's just two cars
and one dead body.
I think you're focusing
on the wrong case.
Our boss asked us to help solve
the murder of his friend's sister,
you're trying to prove her husband
committed manslaughter.
You should just stick
to the case at hand.
Just a suggestion.
Tell me about the first time
we made love.
We were staying at
your parents' house.
You snuck into the guest room
to join me.
You were worried
about getting caught.
But then you fell asleep in my arms.
Your mom woke us up in the morning
but she didn't seem that mad.
How did we celebrate when
you sold your first novel?
We booked a presidential suite
at a resort we couldn't afford,
and we ordered room
service all weekend.
I was...
I had a difficult year.
I was going through something.
The miscarriage.
You were almost three months along.
No one knew but us.
We were just about to share
the good news with our parents.
We even had names picked out.
Courtney if it was a girl.
Peter if it was a boy.
When you called me, I just...
I just couldn't believe that anything
you were saying could be true,
that there was any chance you could
be who you said you were,
that there was any...
possibility that...
- we could be together again.
- It's me, Gabby.
It's Nathan.
I've come back to you,
and I promise,
I'm never going to leave you again.
Mrs. Dubois.
Hi, I'm sorry. I know it's early,
I didn't call first.
No, no, it's fine.
What's on your mind?
The night before I met you,
I had a dream that,
that I couldn't understand.
It was about a man
who died a long time ago.
Only instead of
his soul crossing over,
it made its way into this other man.
Well, I guess that's why i'm here.
The more I come to learn
about your family,
the more sense
this dream starts to make.
After Nathan's accident,
there were days
I didn't know how I'd carry on,
or if I even could carry on.
But then, just when
I was ready to give up...
Joel Tiernan appeared?
Imagine losing the love
of your life,
but then before you'd even begun
to start mourning the loss,
getting him back.
Being spared the lifetime it would've
taken to get over that loss.
It was...
it was a miracle.
Nothing short of a miracle,
surely you, of all people,
can appreciate that.
Did Nathan ever talk to you about what
happened the night of the accident?
He ever told you how exactly he might
have crossed paths with Joel Tiernan?
No, no. All he remembers was
the screeching of tires.
Nothing after that.
And in regards to Joel Tiernan, neither
one of us remembered ever meeting him.
We tried to investigate
his life after the switch,
but as it turned out, there wasn't
much of a life to investigate.
No family,
no friends to notice Joel
behaving differently.
I can only imagine what a comfort
it must've been to have your husband,
your real husband, by your side,
when you got the news
of Robin's death.
Actually, I was by myself
when I got the news.
I'd gone to an event that night.
Joel couldn't go,
and so we didn't see each other
until much later...
but it was difficult for Joel, too.
I think he loved her
as much as I did.
Bridge! I heard a rumor
you weren't dressed yet.
Just leave me alone!
Come on, come on.
It's getting late.
I'm sorry, daddy.
What are you sorry about, honey?
What's the matter?
I know I wasn't supposed to...
but I couldn't stop.
Joel Tiernan
is Nathan Cafferty.
That's what you're telling me?
I know how this sounds.
No, I don't think you do.
It sounds insane, Allison.
You are telling me that the essence
of my friend's dead husband somehow
found its way into the body of that man,
Joel Tiernan, and that therefore,
we should question Joel Tiernan
for the murder of Gabrielle's sister?
They were having an affair.
She threatened to tell.
With who? On whom
was she threatening to tell?
- They're one and the same.
- I think that's a tough sell to a jury.
Sir, I am telling you,
Joel tiernan was driving the car
that killed Nathan Cafferty
that night.
Joel and Nathan were
within yards of each other
when Nathan's soul left his body,
but instead of going wherever
it was supposed to go...
It did what?
It just made its way
to the nearest warm body
and took up residence.
- Is that really what you think?
- I know that's what his wife thinks.
Can't we just bring him in here
and ask him
where he was the night
his sister-in-law died?
- You mean no one asked him that?
- No one has asked him anything.
No one thought it mattered.
In the past 24 hours, a theory
of evidence has emerged.
It's unconventional, to be
sure, but I was just curious
as to whether you might
have a point of view about it.
Mrs. Tiernan, Gabrielle,
recently spoke
with Mrs. Dubois here and...
shared some very interesting things
about the nature of you and your
wife's... mutual attraction.
My wife...
my wife is very spiritual.
She has some rather romantic
ideas about life and death.
I'm not sure she's...
entirely over the loss
of her first husband.
I suppose, inevitably,
appearance aside,
I have some things,
some traits in common with Nathan,
and I'm sure Gabrielle...
interprets those similarities,
well, with a...
a romantic's heart,
a romantic's sensibility.
I hope you don't think
too badly of her.
It's one of the reasons
i love her so.
- Anything else?
- There is one more thing.
Do you happen to remember where you were
the night that Robin was murdered?
Of course. At home.
In bed sick.
Gabrielle had this...
charity thing, really wanted me
to go with her
and meet some of her friends,
but I just couldn't get out of bed.
Then she got that horrible news...
and we weren't even together,
and, I mean, we're always together.
Was anyone else home that night?
A cook, a maid?
Would that be a "no"?
Yes, that's a "no."
Are you heading where
I think you're heading?
I barely knew Robin.
I just barely married her sister.
Why in the world would I want
to do her any harm?
On the morning
after Robin was murdered,
the police found a...
a spot of blood
- At the crime scene that wasn't hers.
- Yes, I know.
It was in all the papers. So?
So we were wondering if you'd mind
giving us a blood sample.
It would enable us
to rule you out, Mr. Tiernan.
Actually, i'm embarrassed that
this wasn't attended to earlier.
It's a simple request
and I would infer nothing from it
other than it would allow us
to do our due diligence, and...
we could look your wife in the eye and
tell her we have left no stone unturned.
So, Mr. Tiernan, can detective
Scanlon take you downstairs?
Is that a "no"?
Yes, that's a "no."
I will not participate
in this farce.
I will not have my privacy invaded
so you people can grasp at straws,
and most importantly,
I will not put my wife
through the embarrassment
and the humiliation and the pain
of knowing that her please
for help in this matter
have yielded nothing but the most...
cynical and simple-minded ideas
about
who might be responsible
for her sister's death.
- Is that all?
- You know,
I can compel you
to give us that blood.
Well, by all means,
call the family lawyer.
Gabrielle will give you the number.
I'm leaving now.
I let go of the contractor that
we hired to...
I'm home! Anyone want chinese?
... build the floor
model for trade shows.
That sounds good. We'll take new bids
in next week. See you in the morning.
Hi. You're back early.
Actually, I worked from home today.
You were in meetings and I needed
to make an executive parental decision,
after I made it, I didn't see the point
of discussing it until you got home.
Discussing what?
She was upset, embarrassed, I couldn't
force her to go to school.
What, you couldn't bring yourself?
You weren't here. You didn't see her.
She said she couldn't help herself.
Now, I think we should just keep her
away from school 'til this thing passes.
- You want her to miss more school?
- As a matter of fact, I do.
I mean, people do it all the time.
Kids get sick, they stay home.
But she's not sick.
She's not sick, Joe.
This is happening for a reason. She's
drawing these pictures for a reason.
She can't just miss school
'cause we don't know what it is.
What if we never figure it out?
- Wait a second. What is this?
- What's what?
I don't know. This spot.
On Mr. Enright's chest.
I don't know. It's his,
you know, his nipple.
No, I don't think so.
Look, there's only one.
And look, it's on all these.
She drew it on every single picture.
Is it growing? It looks like
it's just changing shape.
Look, this one's like
a little circle,
and then here it looks like an x.
Maybe she's not just
drawing Mr. Enright.
Maybe she's diagnosing him.
The city of Phoenix mourned today
as one of its favorite sons,
renowned author Nathan Cafferty,
was laid to rest.
Mr. Cafferty, whose
net worth was estimated
at somewhere between
$15 and $20 million
was killed last week when his car
was struck head-on by another vehicle.
He is survived by his wife,
Gabrielle, who insists
that rumors that her husband
was working on a new book
at the time of his death were,
to the best of her knowledge, untrue.
"Our friends often commented
that we made an odd couple,
"Gabrielle and I.
"She believed with all her heart that
there was far more to this universe
"than the so-called "scientists"
would have us believe.
"I, of course, did not.
"To the casual observer,
it may have appeared
"we had little in common, but faith,
"as it has often been said,
is feminine.
"Even the cynic
who believes in nothing
"can find a girl
who believes in him."
I was wrong.
Tiernan isn't walking around with
the soul of Cafferty inside of him.
He's walking around
with Nathan Cafferty's autobiography.
- I beg your pardon?
- Remember I told you
that I saw pages raining down from
the sky the night of the car wreck?
I think that's what it was.
It was Nathan Cafferty's autobiography.
Joel stole it before
anyone else could read it.
That's how he knew so much about him.
That's how he could convince Gabrielle
that he was him.
He had a...
a virtual manual on how to be him.
I'm sorry. I know I told you
that Joel was Nathan.
I was wrong.
I fell for the same scam
Gabrielle did.
The only thing I don't know
is, if Joel Tiernan
was always Joel Tiernan,
Why would he kill Robin Aaronson?
Maybe because
he didn't kill her, Allison.
What?
Lee brought this in a few
minutes before you arrived.
- Wait a second. Who's this?
- Arthur Kolber.
Worked at the cottages where
Robin Aaronson was beaten to death.
I was doing my due diligence on
the hotel staff when I found out
Kolber sexually assaulted
a female friend two months ago.
I had the lab compare his blood
with the drop that we found
at the scene of Robin Aaronson's murder,
and... guess what.
A perfect match.
Kolber claims he cut his hand
doing repairs at the cottage,
but I don't buy it.
I'm pretty sure this is our guy.
Wait a second.
Even if he didn't kill Robin,
what about everything he's done
to Gabrielle. Can't we get him on that?
On what?
Gabrielle is a full-grown woman.
If she wants to believe she's married
to the ghost of her dead husband,
well, there's no law against that.
On the other hand,
I'd be lying if I said
that I didn't think that Joel
Tiernan was hiding something.
But here's the thing, I already owe
the man an apology for accusing him
of killing his sister-in-law.
I can't also accuse him of
perpetrating one of the cruelest
hoaxes I've ever heard of,
especially without proof.
You... don't have any proof, do you?
Yeah, well. Me neither.
I'm sorry. I don't get it.
Your daughter has done
maybe a dozen more
explicit drawings of me,
And you want to talk to me
about this dot?
I'm not so sure that it is just a dot.
I think that maybe it's a mole.
All right, a mole. So?
So... do you?
Do you have a mole on your chest?
One that's, you know,
in roughly the same spot as these?
You know what? I don't really know.
I've got quite a few. Most adults do.
I know,
but I'm talking about this one.
You see how it's changing
shape in the pictures?
See, it's, like, growing?
I don't mean to alarm you, but I think
that you might want to see a doctor.
Mr. Dubois, with all due respect
to your daughter, these are doodles.
Now, are you seriously suggesting
that I have myself
tested for skin cancer
because of your daughter's doodles?
Actually, I am.
Robin, you in there?
The door's open.
I got here as fast as I could.
So why'd you make me drive all
the way out here hust to talk to you?
What is this place?
This?
This is our place.
It's so good to see you again, baby.
Robin, what are you doing?
Why are you dressed like that?
Stop!
What's the matter?
I can't do this with you.
I mean, I'm flattered,
don't get me wrong.
But I could never betray
Gabrielle like that.
That's funny.
You never had a problem
with it before, Nathan.
What did you just call me?
"Nathan." That's who
you really are, isn't it?
Gabrielle told you.
Yeah, she told me.
She told me all about you.
Of course,
if you were really Nathan,
you'd know about our little secret,
wouldn't you?
You'd know that you bought me
this négligée,
and you'd know that this place
is where we used to meet
to make love,
to betray my sister.
But you don't remember
anything about us, do you?
Because you're not Nathan,
you're a fraud.
A parasite.
- Wait a minute. You have it wrong.
- Shut up!
Stop lying.
I don't know how you tricked my sister,
but i'll make sure she knows the truth.
I'm gonna tell her everything.
Your sister loves me, Robin.
She's happy.
You should have left us alone.
Mrs. Tiernan?
I was hoping I could speak with you.
I'm not sure we have much
to talk about.
Not unless you're here to apologize for
the way your office treated my husband.
No, that's not why I'm here.
Obviously, he didn't write
about the affair
in his autobiography.
That's why Joel didn't know
about it.
So when Robin threatened
to expose him,
He didn't really have a choice but to
kill her or he lose everything.
No, you're wrong. They found another
man's blood at the crime scene.
A man who worked at the hotel,
he told the police he cut his hand.
I can't prove it, but it think
he's being honest with us.
The truth is, I can't prove
any of this.
But you came to us,
you told us you wanted our help.
And I thought you deserved
to hear the truth
even if a jury never does.
Even if it hurts.
Gabrielle,
he's gone.
The man you loved is gone.
And this man...
isn't him.
Gabby, I'm back.
Welcome home, Nathan.
It's okay.
You don't have to pretend
in front of Mrs. Dubois.
She knows who you really are.
What's she doing here?
After all I've been through
with the D.A.'s office,
Why would you let that woman
in our house?
She came here to talk to me,
to tell me some things about you.
Some theories she has about you.
What kind of theories?
Why would you listen to her?
We've been together
nearly two years.
What could she possibly tell you
that we don't already know?
Well, that's a great question,
Nathan.
You don't mind if I call you
"Nathan," do you?
You know what?
I was just flipping through
a couple of your books this morning.
They're beautifully written,
Mr. Cafferty.
You really have a way with words
and a very particular style.
You're a wonderful writer.
Thank you.
Anyway, I know this is gonna
sound like a strange request,
but we were wondering if...
maybe we could get you
to sit here and write something,
right here, right now.
Now, why would i want to do that?
Well, why wouldn't you want
to do it?
You know, it's, it's funny.
In the two years since
you first walked in that door,
I haven't seen you do
a single stitch of work.
I haven't seen you write anything.
And Nathan, I mean...
the original Nathan,
he was forever writing things,
reading things to me,
showing me things.
So do it for me again, Nathan,
like you used to.
Can you even type?
I think I'd like you to leave
my house now, Mrs. Dubois.
Actually, this is my house...
and I'd like Allison to stay.
She's invited some of her colleagues
over. They should be here in a minute.
Mrs. Dubois seems to think that
if the police take a look around the...
the property, they may turn up
that manuscript
that she says you took
from Nathan's car.
We turned the place upside down.
So far, we found nothing.
I'll give it more minutes, but I think
it's just about time to pack it in.
So that's it?
He gets away with everything?
Everything except Gabrielle.
She asked if we'd escort her husband
from the premises after we're done.
We might not be able to prove
Joe Tiernan's a murderer,
but at least we got him
out of her life.
Are the girls down?
Two out of three.
Bridgette's still buzzing
about all the nice things
that Mr. Enright had to say
about her after class today,
how she should feel free
to draw what she wants
when she wants.
Call me crazy. I think somebody
got some good news
from their dermatologist.
What is this?
It's a little picture of us that
Bridgette drew before she went to bed.
I looked very closely.
There's no lumps,
growths or vestigial limbs
on either of us,
so I assume we're
in the pink of health.
She even gave us clothes.
Did I tell you that I took
a life-drawing class in college?
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
You ever done any modeling?
Get used to these boxers, babe,
because they're never coming off.
You have something against art?
I'm telling you.
You've got a little something.
I just need to get my crayons.