(Joe coughing)
Hey. You all right?
Need something cold.
Hey, how's that flu?
That cough doesn't sound good.
I don't know why not.
I've been practicing it
all night.
"You Give Me Fever"
No, no, no, no,
I understand.
I don't live in
your area, but I...
I've called all the clinics
around us, and, well,
they all seem to be out
of the flu vaccine.
N-no, I understand.
The very young
and the very old.
The thing is, my
husband's sick,
and I'm worried
that if I get sick,
there's not going
to be anyone
to take care of
our three kids.
You can?
(chuckles)
You will?
Oh.
11:45.
Um, is there any way you
could do that any earlier?
It's just that Chandler
is so far from where I work.
You know what, never mind.
Never mind.
11:45. I will be there.
Don't give anyone my shot.
Thanks.
Boy, you sure seem happy
for someone that's going
to get a shot.
Yeah, I am.
You guys are lucky
you got yours at school,
but I missed mine at work,
and with Daddy sick and all...
Mom, do you want me
to take that to Dad
so that you can, uh,
have some breakfast?
Would you?
Yeah.
Thanks.
BRIDGETTE:
Hey, Mom?
How's that detective
you work with doing?
Detective Scanlon?
He's good.
He's got a beautiful
little baby girl.
Yeah.
He's good. Definitely.
Why do you ask?
I just had this dream last night
that didn't make much sense.
What kind of dream?
It was nothing really.
I mean, he was just sitting
in a restaurant
with this pretty blonde lady,
and he was really sad.
He had
this little box,
and I think there
was a ring in it.
But the big thing is,
he was just really sad.
But, uh, that doesn't
make sense, right?
I mean, if he already
has a baby,
then why was he giving
this lady a ring?
And what would have to happen
to make him so sad?
I don't know, honey.
Those are all
really good questions.
Hmm. So, you don't think it
makes much sense, either, huh?
Cool.
(elevator bell dings)
(coughing)
(sniffing)
(man coughing)
SCANLON:
So, what do you think?
Good ring, nice ring?
It's very good.
It's very nice.
You think Lynn will like it?
Well, of course, she'll like it.
Who wouldn't?
(chuckles)
I was thinking maybe tonight.
Figure it's time.
I wait much longer,
little Leigh
will be old enough
to be the maid of honor.
(chuckles)
Boy, there's a lot of
strangers around here today.
What's going on?
SCANLON:
It's a big hush-hush briefing
with some guy from FEMA.
You're not going?
Not going.
Wasn't asked.
Damn glad about it, too.
I have somewhere to be at 11:45.
MAN:
This picture was taken in 1996.
The subject lived
in a small village
in the Democratic Republic
of the Congo.
He succumbed to a disease
called viral hemorrhagic fever.
It's very rare.
The strain responsible for this
man's death is called FV-39.
Ladies and gentlemen,
FV-39 is of
particular concern to us
because the virus holds up well
in transport and weaponization.
In fact, there are a few of us
who believe that it
would be an ideal agent
for a bioterrorist attack
against the United States.
(man coughs)
FEMA has been trying
to create an antiserum,
a cure that can be deployed
in the event of just such
a bioterrorist attack.
In fact, we've been working
very closely
with a company right here
in Phoenix
that is at the forefront
of that effort.
Dr. Erik Westphal heads up
the bio-pathology division
of United Southfield.
I'll let him take it
from here.
Doctor.
Um... (clears throat)
Our lab is a biosafety
level four lab.
That means we're handling some
of the deadliest microbes
on the planet.
Uh, naturally, both our company
and the federal government
spend extraordinary amounts
of time and money
monitoring our inventory.
When the government inspectors
gathered their data
and filed their latest reports,
there appeared
to be trace amounts
of FV-39 cultures missing
from some of our samples.
(murmuring)
This isn't
the kind of thing
that you would notice
on a day-to-day basis,
but over time...
There is a measurable amount
of this bug
that we simply
can't account for.
(murmuring)
MAN:
Worst case scenario,
ladies and gentlemen,
is that someone either sold
or gave these cultures
to someone
who intends to use them
as a weapon
of mass destruction.
We at FEMA
need to move forward
as though that were the case.
DINOVI:
So, what does this mean?
Is Homeland Security
issuing some kind of alert?
MAN:
Quite the contrary.
There will be no alert.
There will be no notification.
There will be no
public announcement
of any kind.
As a matter of fact,
the only people
who know anything about this
are sitting
in this room right now,
and that is the way
it's got to stay.
Dr. Westphal doesn't happen
to agree with that decision,
but the fact is, at this moment,
ladies and gentlemen,
we do not have
an effective antiserum
in sufficient quantities
to deal with this.
As a result,
the preventive measures
that we can take are limited.
Dr. Westphal,
if this virus--
this FV-39--
is out there,
how bad could it get?
How many people
would be affected?
It's hard to say.
It's not an
airborne virus.
It is spread by
people, to people,
and it carries a mortality
rate of about 85%,
which is what makes it
such an effective threat.
Again, depending
on how long it was out there
and how soon we were able
to contain it...
hundreds of dead?
Thousands, maybe.
It's just too hard
to say for sure.
JOE:
You did the right thing.
(coughing)
There's nothing to be gained
by telling a man
who's contemplating proposing
that it might not--
and I underline "might not"--
go exactly the way he hopes.
Yeah, I know.
But you should
have seen his face.
He looked so vulnerable.
I just... I hate the idea
of him getting
his feelings hurt.
Well, if Bridgette's right,
he's going to get
his feelings hurt
no matter what you do--
um, either by you or...
or at dinner tonight.
Huh.
Well, thanks.
That... that... that helps.
That feels better. Thanks.
Anything else?
Oh, uh, honey,
can you do me a favor?
I'm running late
for my flu shot,
and I left the number
of the clinic
in the kitchen on the counter.
Can you go read it to me
so I can let them know
that I'm still coming?
You want me to go
all the way back to the kitchen?
Honey, please.
(tires screeching)
I don't want them
to give away my flu shot.
You still there?
I think there's going
to be an accident.
What?
Honey, hang up the phone.
Call 911.
Tell them to send an ambulance
to North Beeline Highway,
just south of Shea Boulevard.
Tell them to send a fire truck.
There's a man
who's about to crash,
and he's got a backseat
full of gasoline.
Sir!
Sir! Wake up!
(coughs)
Sir, sir, wake up!
What are you doing?
Get out of the car now.
Your car's on fire.
You have to get out now.
No. Get away!
Get away from me!
Open the door!
Go away! Get away!
You have to get out now.
Your car's going to explode.
Get away!
No.
I want to die, damn it!
Go!
It's going
to explode!
Go! Go!
(explosion)
I just don't get it.
I mean, what
is the point
of dreaming about
something like this if...
if you can't stop
it from happening?
Well, I wish I had
an answer for you.
I'm just glad he
didn't take you with him.
Did, uh... did he
say anything to you
before the car
blew up?
No, he just kept saying
that he wasn't getting
out of the car.
He kept telling me to
go away over and over.
Look, uh, the driver
was determined to do
what he was determined to do.
He turned his car into a bomb.
Even if you had managed
to get him out of it,
don't you think that ultimately
he would have found
some other way
to get the job done?
(sighs)
Oh, God.
(gasps)
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, fine, I guess, I...
What time is it?
It's 1:45.
Why?
Damn it.
Is there anything
I can help you with?
I had an appointment
to go get a flu shot,
which is why I'm out here.
That was over two hours ago.
You know what?
It's fine.
I'm just going to call them,
I'm gonna apologize...
(sighs)
Suddenly I'm not
feeling so good anyway.
I think I might have
already caught Joe's bug.
Well, do me a favor
and don't sneeze on me, okay?
I have big plans
tonight, remember?
For she's
a jolly good fellow
For she's a jolly good
fellow
For she's
a jolly good fellow
Which nobody can deny.
(cheering)
Hey, sorry I'm late.
(sighing)
You okay?
Look at them.
They have no idea.
I can't help it.
I can't help wondering
how many of them are
going to survive...
if you're going
to survive...
if little Leigh is
going to survive.
No, you can't talk
that way.
You can't think that way.
We'll figure this out,
we always do.
Really?
Are we any further
along tonight
than we were
this morning?
Do we know anything now
that we didn't know then?
How do you do it?
How do you stop a
thing you can't see?
(distant laughter)
I think I just
want to go home.
I think I just want
to be with my baby.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What am I doing?
We didn't come here for this.
Uh, you said there was something
you wanted to talk to me about,
something
important.
You know what? It'll keep.
Let's just go home
and be with our baby.
ALLISON:
I don't know.
I saw this horrible thing
and then I just--
I got the shakes.
(beeping)
And then I felt kind of dizzy,
felt kind of achy.
99.6.
Huh?
You are one degree
above normal.
(sighing):
I feel like I'm dying.
Well, I'm
sorry, Allison.
I don't want to make
a liar out of you,
but people do not die
from one-degree fevers.
I know that's not
what you want to hear,
and it's no fun being
the bearer of bad news,
but I think you have
what everyone has
and I think you're
going to live.
Now...
(coughs)
Want to hear
some good news?
Now that we are both
sick with the flu,
I believe we can once
again share the same bed.
Wait a second,
what's the good news?
(chuckles)
Ariel can take the girls
to school tomorrow,
and maybe I'll actually
feel good enough
to go back to work.
(sighs)
Try to get this morning
out of my mind.
The smell of all that gasoline,
the smell of that man burning.
(engine accelerating)
(coughs)
(gasps)
Lee...
hi, sorry to call so late.
I-I know you had a big evening
and all, but...
SCANLON (quietly):
Oh, no, no, that's okay, I, uh,
I kind of called a flag
on the play.
Right idea, uh, wrong night.
Really?
What's up?
I don't know,
I-I just had the oddest dream
about that man who burned
himself alive today in that car.
I think he was sick, Lee,
really sick.
What do you mean?
I don't know,
I just had a dream, and in it
he was coughing,
he had these white, oozy things
on his face, and...
he was bleeding a little
around his eyes and his nose.
Oh, no.
What do you mean, "Oh, no"?
What people have you
been in contact with
since you were at the accident?
What do you mean,
"in contact with"?
Allison, think, what people
have you been around
since the accident?
You,
all the police and the medical
people who showed up, my family.
Why?
Lee, talk to me.
What's going on?
We may have a problem--
you, me...
all of us.
Stay put,
I'm gonna call you right back.
W-What do you mean, "Stay put"?
What's going on?
Lee... Lee.
It seems weird,
eating while it's still dark.
I know, I'm sorry, guys.
So are we going
to school today
or what?
I don't know,
honey, I don't know
what's going on.
They just told us
to wake everybody up
and make sure
that we don't go outside.
We can't open
any windows or doors.
They were going
to come over soon
and explain everything to us.
JOE:
There are trucks outside.
They don't have
their lights on,
but I can hear them,
and people are doing something
on the front lawn.
You sure I can't
just open the door?
No, Devalos was very specific.
ARIEL:
There's a man outside
my bedroom window.
He's putting up plastic
or something.
(phone rings)
Hello.
MAN:
May I speak
with Allison Dubois, please?
This is her husband.
Can I help you?
Is everyone awake?
We don't want to unnecessarily
frighten anyone.
What do you mean,
"Is everyone awake?"
Who am I speaking with?
This is Dr. Erik Westphal.
I'm with United Southfield
Laboratories.
I'm here with the FEMA people.
Is everyone awake?
Are you ready for us?
We'd love to get this over with
before the sun comes up
and your neighbors notice
what we're up to.
What is he saying?
Well, wait a second.
What are you up to?
Just open the front door,
Mr. Dubois.
We're right outside.
They're at the
front door.
(knocking on door)
WESTPHAL:
Mr. Dubois, this
is Dr. Westphal.
Mr. Dubois... are you there?
Could you open
the door, please?
We're, uh,
kind of racing
the clock.
Mrs. Dubois has had
direct contact.
I need her isolated
in a room by herself.
The father and
the children
can be examined
together somewhere.
Wait a minute.
Mrs. Dubois, I need
to examine you.
I need samples
of your blood, your saliva,
your hair, and your urine.
What are you talking about?
What is going on here?
Why do you need to examine me?
Why do you need to examine
my husband and my children?
I promise you I will
explain everything to you
at the earliest
opportunity,
but right now I need you
to show my colleagues
back into your bedroom.
Every moment we lose could
potentially compromise
your health and your
family's health.
(clanging)
(rustling)
(door opens)
Mrs. Dubois,
I'm, uh, I'm sorry
this has taken so long.
Where's my family?
I can't get
a hold of my family.
I keep texting them,
calling them.
They don't answer,
they don't write back.
Well, your husband is
in the living room,
getting an IV drip for his flu.
(clears throat)
Your kids were totally fine,
and your eldest daughter
took them to school.
As for you, do you sleep
on a feather pillow?
Well... What? Why?
You shouldn't.
You're allergic.
Other than that, you're fine.
Are you serious?
You show up at my house
looking like something
out of a science fiction movie,
and you tell me that I'm fine,
that everyone's fine,
that everything is fine?
Yeah, I am sorry,
but we had no choice.
Okay, the man that you saw
kill himself yesterday
was a biologist
who worked in my lab.
His name was Mitchell Lomis
and he was apparently infected
with a very, very dangerous
virus called FV-39.
You thought that I caught
this virus, whatever it is?
Yeah, you and all the other
people who rushed to help Mitch.
This virus...
There are organizations, uh,
movements
that would pay a fortune
for even a minute amount of it.
Y-You infect one person
and then expose him
to as many people as possible
before he succumbs
and you can decimate
a small city.
At our lab we were working
on this virus,
working on a cure.
How Mitch became infected,
we still don't know,
but I can't believe
that it was an accident.
There are just
too many safeguards,
too many checks and balances.
The fear is
that he was attempting
to steal some and sell it.
How well do you
know this person?
Uh, does he strike you
as the kind of person
who could do
something like that?
There's a time when I would
have said absolutely not.
But he went through
a pretty ugly divorce
a couple of years ago.
He had some financial struggles,
emotional struggles.
Just wrestling with depression.
I-I just keep hoping
that whatever he took...
it was incinerated
right when he was.
But what if it wasn't?
What if it's still out there?
Yeah, well...
let's just pray that
that's not the case.
Uh, it's not that we
don't have an antivirus,
by the way.
It's just that we don't have
enough funding
to produce it in meaningful
quantities.
It's about two cents a person,
actually.
I mean, if every U.S. citizen
paid two cents,
we'd have enough to inoculate
the entire city of Phoenix.
Or Philadelphia.
Or San Antonio.
Just astounding, right?
NEWSCASTER:
...with the new increase
and the mystery virus,
nobody knows very much about it.
A short time ago
it was completely unknown.
How are you feeling?
Hey.
Pretty amazing, actually.
They hydrated me,
they gave me some antibiotics.
Hell of a house call.
How about you?
I'm fine.
It-it's all gone.
The achiness. The dizziness.
He said it was all in my head.
I guess he was right.
Did anyone explain this to you,
what they were doing here?
No one had to.
It's all over the TV.
Representatives from FEMA
and a Phoenix biotech firm
began showing up
on the doorsteps
of police and rescue workers
before dawn this morning,
concerned that they may have
contracted a deadly virus.
So far none of the city workers
have tested positive
and officials remain
tight-lipped
about whether or not the virus
remains a threat
to the general populace.
So much for secrets.
(elevator bell dings)
(phones ringing)
DEVALOS:
You feeling left out?
You want one?
A mask, I mean.
I know a guy who knows a guy.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm holding out
for one of those full body suits
that those guys who came
to my house this morning had.
Lot of fear.
About 20% of the staff are
taking a personal day.
About to have a little briefing
in the conference room.
You want to come along?
Yeah.
As soon as we realized
that this Lomis fellow had been
infected with the missing virus
and the fact that he worked
for United Southfield,
we began investigating.
Dr. Westphal gave us access
to his office computers,
and we obtained a warrant
for his laptop as well.
We discovered that Mr. Lomis
had been using an alias
to log onto several
anti-American Web sites,
and that he had indeed contacted
a potential buyer for the virus.
Now the good news is,
the e-mails indicate that
the sale was never completed.
Our best guess is that Mr. Lomis
inadvertently infected himself
as he was attempting
to dispose of the virus
as soon he realized that the
sale was not going to happen.
We now believe
that everything that he had
was in that car.
We believe that everything
that he had burned up with him.
And so I'm pleased
to inform you this morning
that even as we're sitting here,
the mayor's office is announcing
to the general public
that there is no longer
any threat from the FV-39 virus.
And just when you think
that there is nothing good
that can come from something
potentially so frightening,
the folks on Capitol Hill
woke up this morning
and heard about the panic
that was slowly spreading
throughout the Southwest,
and I've been told that an
appropriation is in the works
to allocate $60 million
for the production
of FV-39 antiserum.
Looks like we're all
going to live.
Which means I'll get
another shot at this.
Oh, I'm sorry last night
didn't go the way
that you hoped.
Eh, it's okay.
If it was meant to be,
it would've been.
You know, it's funny.
One of my daughters told me
yesterday morning
that she had a dream
about you proposing.
So I kinda knew it wasn't going
to happen last night.
Why?
When did she have me proposing?
No.
It wasn't about when.
You know what? Never mind.
Forget that I said anything.
I promised myself I wouldn't.
Well, wait a minute. Don't
let me make a fool of myself.
If there's something
I should know...
No. There's nothing
you should know.
(sighs):
I mean...
you were sad last night, right?
We both were. We thought
the world was going to end.
Okay, well, that was it.
That was her dream.
That she saw you getting
ready to propose
but instead you were sad.
So, it already happened.
You have nothing to worry about.
DINOVI:
How you doing out there?
Just getting locked and loaded.
I hate to leave
you guys,
but I've had this
dinner on the books
with the head of the
Teacher's Union
for weeks.
Are you sure
you're going to be okay?
Mm-hmm. Better than okay.
Hi, cutes.
Hi.
So this woman I'm
meeting with?
She has a reputation for
being kind of long-winded.
I wouldn't wait up.
Hey, as soon
as she hits the hay,
I'm hitting the hay.
Uh, what else, what else?
Uh, I've got my cell,
the phone number for
the restaurant's
on the fridge,
and, uh...
You know what, Lynn?
We're good.
You just go do
what you gotta do.
Okay, okay.
I'm going.
Mmm.
Okay.
Oh, Mama.
Bye.
(laughs)
Bye, honey. Bye.
(whispers):
Bye.
I've been working
on the baby bottle
All the live long day
I've been working
on the baby bottle
Just to pass the time away
(phone rings)
Can't you hear
the phone a-ringing...
What do you think, little Leigh?
Should we let the answering
machine grab that?
(machine clicks, beeps)
I'm with you.
Hi, Lynn. It's Jenny.
I just left this message
on your cell
and I called your apartment and
then I found this number, too,
and thought maybe I'd catch you
here, but I guess not.
Anyway, uh,
Larry Birkbaum called.
He wanted to let you know
he's running a half hour late
for dinner tonight.
Oh, and, uh,
he can't wait to see you.
Okay. Thanks.
That's all.
(kissing)
What was that for?
That was for
"I'm feeling better."
That was for "I haven't been
able to kiss you in days."
(giggles)
That was for...
"nobody's going to get
a deadly virus
"and bleed from their
eyes and nose,
get things all over
their face and die."
Not tonight, anyway.
That's a good answer.
What a day.
Ugh.
How many
almost disasters are there
that we never hear about?
Government or big business
don't tell us
because they don't have to.
Makes you grateful there are
people like that doctor
who was here this morning.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
What was that one for?
That was to hold
me till morning.
Another good answer.
(knocking on door)
WESTPHAL:
Come on in.
Okay, Erik, I'm here.
What's so important you needed
to get me out of bed
at 11:30 and rush over?
Don't get mad at me...
but I hacked into your computer.
I read your e-mail.
It's not happening, is it?
I'm sorry.
They don't buy it.
They all think it's a setup.
That maybe I'm working
with the government.
So it's not happening.
Maybe you picked the wrong guy.
I think deep down,
I don't want to be the one who
sells this virus to some nuts.
Gets a lot of innocent
people hurt.
I mean...
I'd do it if I had to.
You think you don't have to?
You see Congress approving
production of our antiserum?
Neither do I. You know why?
Because they can't see microbes.
They can see planes flying
into buildings.
They can see suicide bombers.
But they can't see microbes.
(sniffling)
Are you crying?
Oh, God, don't... don't cry.
I'm sorry.
(sniffling)
Are we going to be all right?
Are you asking me if there'll be
money to pay for your alimony?
No.
I'm asking you if we're
going to be all right.
Come here.
We're going to be just fine.
Good.
Wait, don't go yet.
No, I want you
to see this.
See what?
Me.
Drinking the last
of the antiserum.
I don't understand.
Why are you doing that?
Well, it's the only way
I can survive.
I had to expose myself to the
virus in order to infect you.
And now that I'm sure
you have it...
Are you serious?
You got about 12 hours, Mitch.
Be a good guy.
Go out and infect
lots of people.
Or don't.
As long as they find your
body covered with lesions,
blood running from your eyes
and nose, what do I care?
Do me favor.
Close the door on your way out.
Mrs. Dubois.
Come on in.
Oh, uh,
we better not.
Little bit of a cold.
It's good to see you again.
(clears throat)
Hope you're feeling better.
Oh, physically,
much better.
Certainly busy here.
Oh, we have antiserum
to manufacture.
We're finally getting
to do the work
that we were meant to do.
Feels good.
So, um, what can I do for you?
Well, you can admit
that you murdered
your friend, Dr. Lomis,
and that this entire panic
about FV-39 virus is contrived.
Why would you say that?
Why would you even think that?
None of that is true.
None of it.
(coughing)
Please, Dr. Westphal.
We both know that it's true.
That you are a pompous,
self-consumed,
self-aggrandized man
who thinks he's smarter
and knows better
than everybody else.
You infected Dr. Lomis
with that virus,
and you didn't even care
who else he infected.
In fact, it was only due
to Dr. Lomis's own sense
of decency
that other people
didn't get sick and die.
Where is this coming from?
This... story?
It's not a story.
You know it's not a story.
Well, can you prove any of it?
You can't prove it
because it's not true.
Just 'cause I can't prove it
doesn't mean it's not so.
Fine.
Believe what you like.
I have work to do.
Lives to protect.
I'm going to go talk to my boss.
Then I'm going to go talk
to that man from FEMA,
and I'm going to tell
them what I know.
And you're right.
I might not be able to prove it,
but I might be able to get them
to take a second look
at those appropriations
for your antiserum.
I might be able to get them
to put the brakes
on all of this.
Why would you do that?
Why would you deny hundreds
of thousands of people
the chance to live in the face
of a potential catastrophe?
To prove what?
To gain what?
Talk about pompous.
Self-aggrandized, self-consumed.
(sighs)
(keys jangling)
DINOVI:
You're home.
I wanted to surprise you.
The baby's asleep.
I was going to change.
Something special?
Uh, just things we need
to talk about.
(sighs)
Talk.
I can't do it
like this.
Do you want
some wine?
No. Let's just talk.
You got something on your mind.
I got something on my mind.
I was asleep
when you got home last night.
You were asleep
when I got up this morning.
Let's just do it. Let's talk.
Okay, I'll start.
How is Larry Birkbaum?
Wow.
You know.
I'm a detective, Lynn.
Why is my...
Why are you having dinner
with a lawyer
who practices family law
when you told me you
were working?
I mean, this guy specializes
in child support,
custody issues.
Unless it's something else.
Maybe the two of you
are friends.
No.
What's this?
That's my divorce.
What?
You're married?
I was.
For a minute,
in my 20s.
Oh, and now is probably as good
a time as any to tell you...
I wasn't a virgin
when we first met.
I know I should
have just
told you about it,
but honestly,
it meant so little to me.
It lasted so briefly.
And it happened so long ago.
It was so inconsequential
to both of us
that we didn't
even bother
to get it taken care
of at the time.
And then, when you
and I first got together,
things were so on-again,
off-again.
But now, since
we're on again--
really on--
I just...
I hated...
I really hated keeping something
from you.
Also...
It's never going to fit
on my finger.
(chuckles)
Shut up.
I want the knee.
I want the whole thing.
Okay.
But before that happens...
you're going to have to tell me
what I'm supposed to do
with this.
Okay, you win.
But I still want the knee.
(sighs)
Um...
unaccustomed to public speaking
as I am...
God, this better get better.
(laughing)
(dog barking in distance)
Go to sleep.
How do you know
I'm not sleeping?
I'm just psychic.
Well, how am I
supposed to sleep
when I know...
I just...
I know that
that evil bastard
is just sitting
in his house
gloating to himself
about how he got away
with everything.
I mean, he killed a man.
He marshaled the resources
of an entire city--
the federal government, even--
to get what he wanted.
I don't know what to
tell you, Allison.
Sometimes, you just
have to give up.
Sometimes, you just have
to surrender to the idea
that everything works
out in the end.
That, one way
or another,
life has a way of eventually
evening everything out.
Even the gloating,
evil bastards
are going to
get theirs.
But it can
only happen
if we get a full
night's sleep.
Are you mocking me?
No, I'm begging you.
A grateful nation
salutes you.
Quiet.
I'm trying to sleep.
(monitor beeping rhythmically)
MAN:
Good thing you called
911 when you did.
(grunting)
(labored breathing)
(coughing)
Shh.
Just relax.
Dr. Westphal,
try not to speak.
I know you're afraid,
but there's no reason to be.
105 is a pretty good fever,
but we've seen more
than a few patients come
through our doors
with this very same flu
you have,
and everyone's pulled through.
We've just got
to keep you hydrated,
keep your electrolytes balanced,
and the medications
we're giving you...
I'm betting we're looking
at 102 by morning.
MAN:
Me?
I'm betting 107.
But then your physician
doesn't know you
as well as I do.
He doesn't know you had
an allergic reaction
to that antiserum.
Sure, it cured the disease,
kept you from dying
of viral hemorrhagic fever,
but we always knew
a tiny part of the populace
would react badly
to it.
Which is why, when you
felt that first itch
at the back
of your throat,
must have been
a surprise, huh?
You didn't wait.
You gave yourself
a massive dose of steroids
to halt the reaction.
Because you knew better.
You were one step ahead,
as always.
But you never counted
on the flu.
And now, with your immune system
completely compromised
by those steroids,
your body has no way
to fight it off.
You might as well have FV-39
or the black plague,
for all the immune response
you can muster.
There you go.
You go to sleep.
For the very last time.
That's right, Erik.
You are going to die.
You know,
I'd kiss you good night
if I could.
But, hey,
you can't have everything.
Whoa.
You okay?
Everything all right?
It's better
than all right.
Everything's great.
Don't worry about me.
I've totally surrendered.