JOE:
You think she got in?
ALLISON:
I don't know.
I mean, it's kind of thick.
Thick is good, right?
Thick is good.
You want to take a look?
What are you talking about?
We can't take a look.
It's addressed to Ariel.
Why not?
Come on, no one will know.
You just steam open
the envelope right here
and then you reseal it.
No.
Joe, come on.
Cornell's her dream school.
Ariel should be the one
to find out first if she got in.
(door opening)
(door closing)
ARIEL:
Mom?
Dad? Anybody home?
Home, yes, yes, we're
home. Here we are.
We're just waiting
in the kitchen.
Just growing older
by the minute.
Waiting for you...
ALLISON:
Oh, I didn't know
you were with somebody.
Um, Mom, Dad, this is
my friend Kyle Covington.
Ms. Dubois.
Hi. Nice to meet you, Kyle.
Mr. Dubois.
It's nice to
meet you, Kyle.
You're just in time.
Ariel's just about
to open a letter
that she got from
the admissions office
at Cornell University.
Or you could just
leave it there
and watch while your
father has a heart attack.
Your call.
Um... you know what,
it kind of doesn't matter.
What do you mean
it doesn't matter?
It's Cornell. It's
your dream school.
Um...
It doesn't matter
because I'm pregnant.
(gasps)
Bad dream.
The worst ever.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
So this mystery kid Kyle--
did he seem nice?
Was he nice?
Yeah, you're saying
that he's going to be
the father of my grandchild,
and that's like, you know,
it's like Christmases and
Thanksgivings and birthdays.
And I just want to know
if I was going to like the guy.
I can't believe you're
joking about all this.
She's giving up her future--
everything she's worked for.
And you're asking me if the kid
she's giving it up for is nice?
Do you really think that this
is one of those dreams?
I mean, even I've had
dreams like that.
Every parent with a daughter
has dreams like that.
What are you looking for anyway?
The camcorder.
I thought I had it
in the case.
I want to tape Bridgette at
the clarinet recital she's got.
I want to make sure
it's charged.
I think
I saw the girls
playing with it
the other day.
Have you taken
a look in there?
Aw...
Aha, here it is.
Why didn't I know that?
Okay, now one bar.
See? I'm glad I looked.
What's this?
(groans)
Really!
(yelling)
JOE:
Did you tape this?
BRIDGETTE:
Yeah.
Why, Bridge?
I don't know.
He's funny.
No, that is not right.
Just because you think
this man's funny,
doesn't mean
you can tape him
without telling him.
He's our neighbor and you
violated his privacy.
No, not really.
He doesn't even
know about it.
No, just because he
doesn't know about it
doesn't mean it's
not a violation.
What are we going
to do about this, huh?
You're not going to make me
apologize, are you?
Because then he would
know about it,
and that would just
make things worse, right?
The first thing I'm going to do
is I'm going to delete this,
and the second thing
I'm going to do
is I'm going to forbid you
from using this camera again.
Go to your room and finish
getting ready for school.
You too, Tonto.
Girls, come on.
Five minutes and
we're out of here.
Um...
So, um, I was wondering--
would it be okay if I came home
after dinner tonight?
What's going on?
Well, I have S.A.T. prep
this afternoon,
and then I was going to go over
to my friend Casey's house.
We have an A.P. chem test
this Wednesday
and we were going
to study together.
I guess so.
But who's Casey?
Do we know her?
No, you don't know her.
And don't get crazy, but...
Casey's not a her.
A boy?
Well, when were you going
to tell us this?
I don't know,
I'm telling you now.
So, uh, is this a boy
you study with, or...?
I mean, we like each other.
And then we hang out.
We haven't gone on a date
yet or anything.
So, is it okay?
Well, I guess I'm just
a little confused.
(nervous chuckle)
Um, did, um, did Casey's mom
invite you to dinner?
I mean, I don't know,
he mentioned it.
So I-I don't know if his mother
is, you know...
I'll tell you what, why don't
you guys go do the S.A.T. prep
and then you and Casey
come back here.
You-you want me
to bring him here?
Yeah. Sure, why not?
We got food, we got dinner.
You guys can study
in the living room.
Sounds good to me.
You think it over,
okay, honey?
And talk about it with Casey.
But either way, I want you
back here for dinner.
Great.
SCANLON:
The guy's name is
Earl Sanderson. 55.
Window was jimmied.
A couple things missing.
It kind of looks like
a robbery gone wrong, right?
I don't know.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not even sure
why you want me here.
The guy's facedown
in the fridge.
Facedown.
What's he doing, offering
the robber a beer?
Or did the petty thief break in,
realize that the guy was home
and shoot in the back
'cause he relished the idea
of turning his
breaking and entering
into a crime that
would get him either life
or the electric chair?
I don't know-- my Spidey sense
is telling me that all is
not what it appears to be,
and I was hoping that my
friend that sometimes sees
things that aren't there
might help to shed some light.
We got a partial
sneaker print
off the dirt outside
the window,
but other than that,
I got nothing.
(motor starting)
MAN:
No! No, please!
No, no, please!
Please, please,
please don't do this!
Please don't do this to me!
Someone help! Help!
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Someone, help!
Please, please don't do this!
Please, please...
Why are you doing
this to me?!
Please, please
don't do this!
No, no, no!
No!
You know what, I don't think
I'm going to be able to tell you
who killed this man.
But I might be able to tell you
about somebody this man killed.
(wheezing laugh)
(laughing continues)
I'm sorry, man, I'm sorry.
You got to come over
and see this thing
my buddy forwarded me.
This dude is freaking out.
Come here.
Look at this.
(yelling)
(laughing)
Your friend found this
on the Internet?
Yeah.
This guy's hilarious.
ALLISON:
Okay, who is this man?
Do we know his name?
I don't know.
He's just some guy.
Some guy that lives around here.
Some guy?
Bridgette, he's a person.
He has feelings.
Now you've exposed him
to public ridicule.
JOE:
Last time I looked
thousands of people
had clicked on the video,
and there are 60
or 70 comments, so...
After dinner, you and your dad
are taking those videos down.
And then you're banned
from the computer.
Until when?!
Until I say you're not.
ARIEL:
Mom, Dad?
Be nice to your
sister's friend.
In the kitchen.
Um, Mom, Dad, this
is my friend Casey.
Casey, this is
my family.
There's another sister
running around here somewhere.
I'm Kyle, Kyle Covington.
Everyone calls me Casey.
Mrs. Dubois.
I know that you dreamt that
this kid got Ariel pregnant,
and wrecked her future
and everything, but...
But?
But I don't know, but he
seemed kind of nice to me.
He did.
He was polite and respectful.
And he seemed kind of smart.
And he acted like he genuinely
cared for Ariel.
I mean, we can't lock her up
until she's 25.
So forgive me if I take
some comfort in the fact
that she's found someone
who's nice.
No, you're right,
I take it back. Lucky us.
Our daughter's going to be
impregnated by a boy who's nice.
All's right with the world.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do.
No, you don't
know that.
First of all,
you've told me yourself,
your intuition
about these things
is notoriously unreliable
when it comes to loved ones.
And second of all,
if Ariel really--
if she was like--
irresponsible in that way,
do you think that
she'd allow herself
to miss out on college?
Come on, not Ariel.
Not the Ariel I know.
Not if she was pregnant
with octuplets.
So how about we forget
about the kid
that we don't know,
and consider the
kid that we do.
'Cause I got to tell you,
that this dream you had,
it strikes me less
as a cautionary tale
about premarital sex,
and more like
the anxious fears
of a mother
who's a little bit nervous
about the first boy
who's ever come
home for dinner.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Sorry to call so late,
but you know that composite
you worked up this afternoon?
I had someone compare it
to our missing persons database.
I think
we may have found a match.
Name's Angelo Filipelli.
Small-time thief,
bunch of petty crimes.
But, uh, I got to tell you,
if Earl Sanderson really did
bury this guy in concrete,
I highly doubt
that's the reason
he got shot last night.
W-Why do you say that?
Because Angelo Filipelli
was reported missing in 1992,
and no one's seen the guy since.
(gasps)
You're sure it was Casey?
Yeah, I'm positive.
He was carrying a gun and he was
stalking that-that petty thief,
that dead man that I saw
yesterday-- Earl Sanderson.
I don't know.
That kid that we
met yesterday,
he doesn't seem like the
kind to stalk anybody.
Much less use a gun.
Well, I'm telling you,
it was him.
You didn't happen to notice
what kind of shoes
he was wearing, did you?
No. Why?
Well, because the police found
a sneaker print outside
Sanderson's window.
Well, don't worry about it.
I'll ask Casey myself
when we question him today.
When you what?
When we
question him.
A man was murdered, Joe,
shot in cold blood.
Yeah, I know that.
But this kid
that we're talking about,
this is, this is
our daughter's friend.
And truthfully,
the only reason that you think
that he might be involved
is 'cause you had a dream.
Isn't that reason enough?
Of course
it's reason enough.
I'm just asking you to consider
the possible repercussions of
what you're about to do here.
Like what?
You're going to
question this boy,
he's going to go to Ariel,
and she's going to be
really upset with you.
So what would you have me do?
I don't know, wait!
Wait for what?
More evidence.
So at least you're sure.
I am sure.
Well, I'm not.
Because this is our daughter's
first boyfriend.
And don't you think that maybe,
just maybe, this is about that?
You don't have
to be Freud to suspect
that there's something else
going on here.
That maybe you're finding
reasons not to like this boy
by inserting him into the case
you're working on.
You really think that?
I don't know what I think.
Just tread lightly, okay?
Tread lightly.
Well, I'm dropping off the girls
and I'm meeting Lee
at the high school.
To the high school?!
CASEY:
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to tell you.
I've never seen this man before.
Did something happen to him?
Someone, uh, shot him.
He's dead.
You sure you're okay
talking to us?
We'd be happy to wait for
your parents or a lawyer.
Yeah, there's no reason to wait.
I don't know anything
about any of this.
And, I mean, I know Mrs. Dubois.
I just really want
to get back to class.
Just give us a second, will you?
Uh, okay, I get that
you know this kid.
I get that, uh, you had
a dream, but, uh...
But what?
Question him.
About what?
He's a good, clean-cut
kid from the suburbs.
The dead man's a
small-time, lowlife punk.
Absent your dream,
this makes no sense.
Just... question him.
(sighs)
All right.
So, Casey...
I need you to tell me where
you were two nights ago, say
between 10:00 at night,
2:00 in the morning.
At home.
Doing homework
and then sleeping.
Look, am I in
some kind of trouble?
SCANLON:
Can anybody confirm that?
That, uh, you were home, I mean.
I don't know.
My dad's out of town
on business, and my mom
went out to dinner
with friends that night.
I went to sleep
before she got home.
I suppose if you ask her
what time she got home
and if she checked
to see if I was asleep.
But other than that...
Uh, you mind if I ask
what size shoe you wear?
Ten.
What does that matter?
ALLISON:
The police found
a shoe print outside
Earl Sanderson's--
the man who was shot.
It was the same brand and the
same size that you're wearing.
Wait a second.
Everyone has these.
Look, Mrs. Dubois,
you'd tell me
if I was in some kind
of trouble, right?
You'd help me?
(door opens)
Mom.
Casey, wait outside.
Mom, this is...
I know who they are.
Just pick up your things
and wait outside.
ALLISON,
Mrs. Covington,
my name is Allison Dubois.
My daughter and your son
are friends.
I know who you are.
I know who both
of you are.
The principal
called me.
Why are you questioning my son?
What's this about?
We received a tip
about a young man
matching your son's description
at the scene of a homicide
two nights ago.
This is a joke.
My son?
Mrs. Covington, no one's
accusing your son of anything.
We're just trying to ascertain
if he knew this man.
You come marching
into a public school,
question a 17-year-old
without notifying his parents,
without giving him the chance
to consult an attorney?
Honestly, we offered
to let him call you.
Excuse me,
Detective Whoever You Are,
this is still America, isn't it?
This boy is
an honor student.
a national scholar.
And you ambush him at school
to talk to him
about a homicide?
Like some kind of thug?
What is the name
of your supervisor?
You can just call
the chief of police, ma'am.
I think I will.
And I think I'll call
my attorney, too.
And if you still have
any questions for me or my son,
you should just feel free
to run them by him first.
Oh, and I'd appreciate it
if, in the future, you,
your daughter, your entire
family stay away from my son.
Just stay away.
(door slams)
Well, that was productive.
Lee, he's hiding something.
Didn't you see
the look on his face
when you asked him
about his shoes?
Allison, it's not like
it's a particularly
expensive or
unique shoe.
And size ten is like
saying I'm a righty.
He was there, Lee, I saw him.
Hey, wait, Lee, wait.
She's still out there.
Lee, look.
SCANLON:
What am I looking at?
Hmm?
No, nothing.
I'm sorry.
(doorbell rings)
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Mr. Dubois?
My name is Lloyd Darby.
You recognize me?
I'm betting
that you do.
A lot of people
recognize me these days.
I take it you're aware
that a young lady
who lives in this house
has been filming me,
putting the videos
on the Internet?
Yeah, that's my daughter.
Uh, I'm... I'm so sorry.
I-I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Darby.
Um, I can assure you,
the video is down, it's gone.
My wife and I just found out
about this last night.
And if there's anything
that we can do,
if there's any way that we can
make this up to you...
You know how many people
have watched that video?
My second cousin in
Maine sent me the link.
People point at me
in the supermarket.
They laugh at me
when I'm in my car.
Does your daughter have
some reason to dislike me?
No, no, no, no.
Absolutely not.
I mean, I know
I'm not the most
graceful man in the world.
I know I'm carrying
a few extra pounds.
But I don't think I deserve
to be reminded of that
every time I leave my house.
No, absolutely not.
I need you to understand,
if I ever find myself
on the Internet again,
if your daughter
ever violates my privacy,
I'll have no choice
but to sue you.
I've already been in touch
with a lawyer.
Please don't
give me a reason
to have to contact him again.
It just keeps going
right to voice mail.
Hey, Ashton Kutcher,
tomorrow's garbage day.
Cans are already out front.
(Bridgette sighs)
All right, that's it.
I'm calling the police.
Ariel's still not home.
It's after 8:30.
No, no, no, no.
Don't do that.
She's fine, really.
She's just mad, like
you said she would be.
It's my fault.
I-I dealt with this
whole thing so stupidly.
I should have spoken with her,
let her know what was going on.
Be that as it may, she's still
not home, it's a school night.
I'm worried.
Ariel is home.
She's outside in a car
with her boyfriend.
(door opens)
Ariel!
(door slams)
(knocking)
ALLISON:
Ariel.
Go away.
I only came home because I knew
that Daddy would be worried.
Bridgette and Marie
would be worried.
Okay.
The thing is, I...
I wanted to tell you,
I did something wrong.
You sure did.
No, I mean...
honey, I should have
spoken with you first,
let you know what was going
on-- that I had this dream,
that I had to question
your friend...
No, see, you didn't
have to do that.
Okay, you could have
come to me and asked me
if he was capable
of being involved
with something like that,
of knowing anyone like that.
I saw him following
that man that died.
I saw him
carrying a gun.
You didn't see it.
Okay, you dreamt it,
and you're wrong.
You don't know him, I do.
Well, that's
another thing.
I don't want you
seeing him anymore.
What?!
He had a gun, Ariel!
In your dream!
Okay, which isn't real!
And you can't make me
not see him.
Don't test me.
No, no, no!
Where are you going with that?!
You can have
this back
as soon as you agree
to take my calls.
(door closes)
(car door opens and closes)
WOMAN:
Casey.
(footsteps approaching)
Why didn't you
come home tonight?
Your father and I
have been worried sick.
He went looking for you
at school.
Look at me.
You promised me you
wouldn't come here anymore.
They knew I was lying.
Ariel's mom, that detective.
They could tell I knew
the man in the picture.
But you weren't... lying.
You don't know that man;
you only think you do.
Don't tell me what I know.
That man,
Earl Sanderson,
he kidnapped me,
he threw my in a hole,
he covered me in concrete.
Right here.
Right here 17 years ago.
Casey,
listen to me.
This thing you keep
telling yourself,
it's not real.
You're not
Angelo Filipelli.
I know you don't
believe me.
But I died, Mom.
I died here 17 years ago.
I died the day I was born.
(soft gasp)
What is that?
It's Angelo Filipelli.
It's you.
Those are X rays
generated by
ground radar.
I convinced the
police to use them
outside the old Sheridan's
Pharmacy in Glendale.
I was certain we
would find nothing.
(chuckles)
And then there it was.
A skeleton.
Someone is
buried in there.
What difference does it make?
Why do you care?
(sighs):
Well... I think that you did
something really horrible,
something you may have to pay
for for the rest of your life,
and I want to help you.
You really think I killed
that guy, don't you?
I've always known...
as long as I can remember,
my name is not Kyle Covington.
It's Angelo Filipelli.
And I don't know why.
Okay? It just is.
I know all about his life.
I can do the things he could do.
When I was five,
I could fix a car.
Okay? I just could.
Check it out.
Angelo Filipelli was a mechanic.
I know about
how he died, too.
He was killed...
I was killed...
by a tall guy with
a limp and a ponytail.
(sighs)
This doesn't surprise me at all.
I go there all the time.
I just stare at it.
One time, I'm there, and...
this man shows up.
I knew who he was.
He was still wearing
that stupid ponytail.
I followed him
back to his apartment.
You know, I kept wondering
if there was something
I was supposed to do.
Kill him, maybe?
But I'm no killer.
Okay? And Angelo Filipelli,
he's no killer.
Look, I'm telling you the truth.
Mrs. Dubois,
you have to believe me.
(knocking)
Does she know
about all this?
(quietly):
No.
Look, if it's okay,
we have a class together,
and I just don't want her
to get in any more trouble.
No, it's okay.
Tell her I said so.
So, what'd she want?
You know what she wanted.
They think
I killed that guy.
(sighs)
I hate this.
Okay? I'm not a murderer.
I didn't shoot
anybody, okay?
I couldn't have.
I don't have a gun.
I-I've never
even seen a gun.
I know.
Look, maybe your
parents were right.
Maybe we should
leave each other
alone for a while.
(exhales)
Casey...
Casey, I'm not my mother.
Okay? I know you...
and I know that you
could never hurt anybody.
Thanks for
believing in me.
We should get going.
Class started a
few minutes ago.
You coming?
(phone rings in distance)
Joseph Dubois?
Yeah, that's me.
Can I help you?
You've been served.
(aerosol spritzing)
(hornets buzzing, man yelling)
No! No!
(buzzing, yelling continue)
Hey.
(turns video off)
You defied us?
I wasn't going to,
but then I had this dream,
and...
everything that
happened in the video
pretty much happened
in the dream first.
Except that in the dream,
I saw myself taping everything,
even though you told me not to.
And in the dream,
after the hornets
chased the guy away,
he came back and thanked me
for putting it all on tape
and for getting it
on the Internet.
Wow, really?
Now, you expect us
to believe that?
It's the truth!
No, it's not the
truth, Bridgette,
because the man that
you taped, Mr. Darby,
is so upset with it
that he's suing us
for defamation
of character.
Is that bad?
It could end up
costing us a lot
of time and a lot
of money, darling.
Well, the one bright
spot in all this,
if there is a bright
spot, is that you only
taped him in public places.
So technically, his privacy
wasn't violated, I think.
So we may not be in any trouble?
No, no, no, no, this is
gonna cost us something
before this is all over.
None of it changes the
fact that we told you
not to do something,
and you did it anyway.
ARIEL:
Mom?
Ariel.
I-I need to talk to you.
(door opens)
She doing better?
(sighs):
Not really.
I... got her to stop crying
for a little while, at least.
Then she'd go over it
again, and she'd get...
sad that somebody she
cared about lied to her.
Maybe even
killed a man.
No.
I'm still hoping not.
I got an e-mail back
from the lawyer.
It's like I thought--
he says the guy
really has no case.
Well, that's good.
Yeah, but it still doesn't
get us out of having
to go to court, and
it still doesn't get us
out of paying the lawyers
and missing work.
So he suggested that we
should offer a settlement.
We're gonna meet with
Darby's lawyers tomorrow
and see if we can
work something out.
How much "working out"
are we talking here?
He suggested
we offer $5,000
and then go up to
$7,500 if we have to.
Doesn't this guy know
we just bought a new car?
(cell phone playing ringtones)
Hey, Lee.
What's going on?
Based on your tip,
we were able to get a warrant
to search
the Covington's residence.
Found the .38 revolver
right where you said it'd be.
Ballistics says it's a match
for the weapon that
killed Earl Sanderson.
(sighs):
And, uh..
we've just
filed charges.
Thought you'd
like to know.
(quietly):
Thanks, Lee.
(beep)
They just found the gun.
Casey's gun.
It was the one that was
used to kill Sanderson.
Should we tell Ariel?
No.
She's been through so much.
We'll tell her
in the morning.
(long sigh)
(sighs)
You look good, Nance.
Angelo.
You look good, too.
Sit down.
The guy you're with must be
taking good care of you.
You have to stop calling me.
(chuckles)
Says who?
Angelo, that girl
you're trying to charm...
she doesn't live here anymore.
I haven't touched drugs
for two years.
This is the last time
we're gonna see each other.
Maybe, maybe not.
That baby you're
carrying around...
we both know that it's
not your husband's.
You can't expect me
to just disappear.
That night was a mistake.
One mistake.
And I am not
gonna make another one.
I got a nice life for myself,
I got a nice life for my baby.
Nice things. Nice people.
And I am not going
to mess that up.
Look, you're not going to come
out of this empty-handed.
I can pay you some money,
but there is no way
you are going to be
a part of my son's life.
It's a boy?
Lunch is on me.
Don't call again.
What are you going
to name him?
Kyle.
It's Michael's
father's name.
(sighs)
He won't take the money.
He won't go away.
You need
to take care of it, Earl.
Tonight.
You waiting to see your son?
How dare you
sit next to me,
pretending to give a damn
about me or my son.
You're the reason
he's in jail.
Now, kindly
leave me in peace.
Okay, well...
Casey won't be
back there long.
At this point, we're pretty
certain that he didn't do it.
Are you serious?
We know who the
guilty party is.
We're just waiting to see if
we can get her to confess.
You know, it seems
that 17 years ago,
the killer hired a man
named Earl Sanderson
to murder a man named
Angelo Filipelli.
Angelo Filipelli
was her child's father,
but she didn't want
her husband to find out.
I have no idea
who you're talking about.
Oh, I think you do.
(chuckles)
I spent the whole morning
going through bank records.
Yours. Earl Sanderson's.
Hey, you want to hear
a funny coincidence?
Starting in 1992,
around the time Angelo
Filipelli went missing,
Earl Sanderson started
living off of cash
from a mysterious
benefactor.
The amounts of his deposits
and the amounts of
your withdrawals
match up pretty nicely.
Another funny thing?
The size of
Sanderson's deposits
got bigger and bigger
year after year.
So did the size of
your withdrawals.
Till one day,
Sanderson turns up dead
and you stop
making withdrawals.
So, what?
Was he asking for more money
than you could hide
from your husband?
How does this work?
They know I'm here.
Are they going
to call my name?
Casey told the police
that the gun used
was a family weapon,
although when we
questioned your husband,
he claimed he didn't
know anything about it.
It was your
gun, wasn't it?
(sighs)
(chuckles)
What? You find
this amusing?
I find it strange.
You're making all
kinds of accusations.
We're in a police station,
but no one is arresting me.
(chuckles)
You know what
I find strange?
You love your son.
You were even willing
to murder someone
to make sure that he
had a better life.
Now you're willing
to let him go to jail
for a crime he
didn't commit?
Let me tell you
something about my son.
Casey is a very disturbed boy.
Ever since he was a child,
he's believed he's someone
other than who he is.
I can't tell you
how many doctors he's seen.
How much testing,
consulting...
Perhaps now,
the court will see to it
that he gets
the treatment he needs.
(chuckles)
Wow. You are really
putting a lot of faith
in an insanity defense.
You seem to be suggesting
that I have some choice
in this matter,
that there are options here.
There are no options here.
Think about it.
Aren't there?
Oh, I think there are.
Right now, your son
is back there getting
a simple DNA test,
and I think we both know
that that test is going to show
that Casey is not
your husband's son.
I don't want to
do this to Casey.
I don't want to do
this to your husband.
But I will do it
if I have to.
And then what?
What? Everything that
you've worked for--
everything that
you've killed for--
it all goes away.
Along with your family.
Along with anyone
who loves you.
Or...
I will make sure that
that DNA is disposed of,
that it is never tested.
At least, in this way,
Casey will still
have a father.
Still have a family.
He will still
have a future.
And...
if I were to confess?
Maybe offer, um...
a different motive?
Well, I will
keep your secret.
I promise.
(elevator bell dings)
Mr. Dubois?
Yeah. Mr. Darby. Hi.
(both chuckling)
Uh, my attorney, actually,
he isn't here yet, so...
I just, I--
You know, I'd just like
to say again how sorry I am
about all this and how-how
terrible my whole family feels.
It's all right, Mr. Dubois.
No. No.
No, it's not.
Yes. Yes it is.
In fact,
um, maybe you should
call your attorney.
I actually don't think we're
going to be needing attorneys.
Uh, excuse me?
(laughing)
It's the funniest thing.
Uh, Anna and I
worked together
at a water park
in Minnesota
the summer after college.
Lost touch.
Years go by.
I always thought
about her.
Turns out,
she always
thought about me.
Then she saw your
daughter's video.
Oh.
Okay.
(both laughing)
Great. Well,
who'd have thunk it?
(laughing):
I know.
Oh, my lawyer
thinks I'm crazy.
He told me I should
have taken your money.
Squeezed you for a
little more, even.
But I don't know,
Mr. Dubois.
I mean, we are
neighbors, and...
(elevator bell dings)
today just doesn't feel
like a day for attorneys.
(chuckles, clears throat)
(both laughing)
(elevator bell dings)
How is she?
She's... amazing.
She wants to see him again.
I told her it was okay.
But he lied to her.
I know.
She knows.
He took his mother's gun.
He followed that man.
He stood outside his window
in his canvas high tops,
but at the end
of the day,
he couldn't do it.
He didn't have it in him.
(sighs heavily)
She just keeps saying how
confused he is, how sad.
His mother's in prison.
That he can't make
sense of it all.
How he knows
the things he knows,
how he knew where
Angelo Filipelli was buried.
But here's what I know.
I know he's a good kid.
And the rest of it,
I can't explain.
So you really can see me?
They told me you could.
The way I heard it, kids
can only see people like me
for a year, maybe
a year and a half.
We got a lot to pack
into that time.
But you have to be
patient with me.
'Cause I'm new at this.
Being a dad.
Being dead.
I'm gonna come see you
every night, okay?
Every night
till you can't see me anymore.
That's gonna be
our special time.
I'm gonna tell you
all about my life.
The good... and the bad.
All of it.
I'm gonna try
and teach you stuff, too.
But first things first.
We got to talk
about this name of yours.
Your mom
and that guy she's with...
(sniffles)
I know they named you
something different.
But when I'm around,
I'm gonna call you the name
I would have given you.
It's my granddad's name.
(sniffles)
My dad's name.
Your dad's name.
I'm gonna call
you Angelo.
Angelo Filipelli.
(gasps)
(sighs)
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com