You okay?
Everything all right?
I just had a dream.
Anything important?
I don't know.
I mean, a man did die,
but it was in the hospital.
I don't think there's anything
to do or anyone to call.
That's enough.
Not funny. Come on. Wake up.
Come on.
Joke over.
Please.
Open up your eyes.
I'm begging you...
just open... your eyes.
Come on.
Didn't we already do this?
Transcript: www.1001fr.com
Bridge, honey,
can you turn that down?
Lee, hi, this is Allison. Can you
give me a call when you get this?
I had a dream last night.
I saw a young woman get,
redrumed.
Maybe it's something, maybe nothing.
I don't know. Give me a call.
Yes, indeed, nothing like a little
redrum to get you going in the morning.
What is "redrum", mommy?
Come on, everybody knows that
"redrum" is just "murder" spelled...
Bridge, little ears.
That's why we use code words.
- Sorry.
- It's okay. Just be careful.
What's "redrum"?
It's a kind of ice cream
that the tooth fairy
gives you if you're good.
Thank you.
Today is an excellent day.
Really? How is that possible?
It's barely begun.
Today is the day I find out
who I'm having a baby with
in wellness class.
Please tell me
that's code for something.
You know what I mean.
All the sophomores have to do it.
You get paired
with a "marriage partner," and...
then Mr. Parks gives us a baby
we have to take care of for a week.
Really? A baby?
It's not a real baby,
it's this expensive doll,
but it's almost as real
as a real baby.
They cry and coo
and burp and wet themselves.
Sounds like fun.
It's serious.
It's ten percent of your grade,
and it'd be nice if I ended up with
somebody I kind of liked as a husband.
I've always found that
to be helpful.
Bridge, can you turn
that back a channel?
This was the scene this morning
as Finley Park rangers discovered
the bludgeoned body
of a young woman,
identified as Kimberly Weeks.
What happened?
Lady ate too much redrum.
Right, mom?
- What are you doing here?
- I saw you on the news.
I thought I'd come by,
maybe you'd give me an autograph.
Did you get my message?
I might have dreamt about this.
- Young woman, red cocktail dress?
- Don't suppose you saw who did it.
Male, Caucasian, 50s-ish, nice suit,
driving a luxury SUV.
- You got a good look at this guy.
- Front seat, 3:00 A.M. show.
But here's the best part.
The girl scratched her killer's face
before she died... deep gouges.
I'm sure you're going to find
a wealth of DNA
under that poor girl's fingernails.
I beg to differ.
I don't think we're going to find
much of anything under her fingernails.
Somebody removed her fingernails?
Ripped 'em right out.
Must have happened after he smashed her
in the head with the rock.
Must have happened after I woke up.
That's why I'm always hanging around
till the credits are over.
They're always putting in extra things
during the credits these days.
Will you excuse me a second?
Are you okay?
I saw what happened to you
last night at the hospital.
I'm so sorry.
I can see you.
I can see people like you.
I really need to talk to you
about what you witnessed...
here last night.
Meet me over there by the bathrooms
in about five minutes.
Cal Jacobs
and... let's see... Marissa Masters.
You are the proud parents
of a baby girl.
Hey, Ash, who's left other
than Adam and Marcos?
We're not out of the woods yet.
We've still got the Unabomber.
Jack White...
and Ashley Whitaker.
I am so sorry.
Adam Mankowicz and Ariel Dubois.
Thanks.
- Look what we made, Mrs. Mankowicz.
- Yeah.
So I'll take the first shift.
I got an away game on Tuesday. Can you
take her for the next two nights?
- Sure.
- Sweet.
I'll call you.
If you were anyone else, I'd have you
arrested for intent to solicit.
You've been standing outside
this men's room for the past 20 minutes.
What can I say?
Times are tough.
I saw someone in the crowd
that I knew,
and I thought we were going to meet up
here after I was done, but...
Well, we're about to wrap it up across
the street, so I'm gonna take off.
Meet me back at the station,
we could work up a sketch
of the killer you saw in your dream.
Unless you got other business here.
- Funny. You're funny, funny, funny.
- We aim to please.
Okay, girls are down.
Well, two out of three.
Who's the holdout?
The one busy writing
"Mrs. Ariel Mankowicz"
on every available inch
of her notebook.
The good news is
she's considering hyphenating.
I'm trying to steer her
towards Dubois-Mankowicz
over the less husband-friendly
Mankowicz-Dubois.
What you looking at?
Mug books.
Trying to see
if there's anyone in here
who even looks vaguely similar
to the man I saw
kill that girl last night.
Oh, yeah, any luck?
Nope, it was a long shot.
The man in my dream
wasn't a career criminal.
He looked like an executive
or a lawyer
or some successful businessman.
What I can't figure out is
why that ghost didn't help me.
He saw everything.
I know. Would it have killed him
to talk to you?
Not funny.
I put today's mail
on your desk, sir.
Fine. Hold all my calls.
Yes?
You make it to work okay
this morning?
Excuse me?
May I ask who's calling?
You were a busy boy last night.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Who am I talking to?
Someone who knows everything
about the last two minutes
of poor Kimberly Weeks' life.
That was her real name, you know.
Or maybe you didn't, but I do.
I know everything:
how it went from playful
to really, really rough.
- What do you want?
- $500,000.
I don't have that kind of money.
I bet you can get your hands on it.
And that's why I sent you
a little incentive.
Do you see a brown paper package
lying on your desk?
Go on. Open it.
Take a look inside.
Oh, my God.
First one's on the house...
So in addition
to looking for a killer,
we're now supposed to be looking for
someone who's blackmailing the killer?
One fingernail at a time.
If we can't keep the world
safe for murderers...
Any clue as to the identity
of this woman?
No. I didn't see her face.
I only heard her voice.
But she knew everything about
the killer. He knew nothing about her.
- Maybe it was someone she worked with.
- Worked?
I thought she was a student
at Mesa University.
Well, we have reason to believe
that what you witnessed
wasn't just the end
of a date gone wrong.
It appears Kimberly helped pay
her tuition by...
entertaining men.
Nights. Weekends.
We're following up some leads.
Looking at her computer and cell phone.
Trying to see if anybody matches
the description of that businessman.
Well, whoever this blackmailer is,
one thing seems pretty clear.
She was a witness
to Kimberly's murder. So,
if Allison's dream is accurate,
she knows how to contact the killer.
Sounds like if we find her,
we can find him.
Looks like you survived
your first night.
- Yeah. Sorry about all the phone calls.
- No. It's okay.
This baby should really come with a
Get Out of Trig Test Free or something.
I don't know how I gonna stay awake
for my next exam.
She woke me up
four times last night.
Well, I don't know.
You look pretty comfortable with her.
It's kind of like
holding a football.
Well, you can pass her to me now.
Are you all right?
I feel really great.
Just a little dizzy.
But maybe you can
just put her in here.
Yeah, all right.
You should have seen the look
on their faces when I told them
we needed to be looking
for a blackmailer and a killer.
Oh, that brings back memories.
- Ariel, tend to your child.
- She can't hear you.
I can't hear me. Ariel?!
I sang to her,
I told her some jokes,
- but she's still crying.
- Don't play with that.
That's Ariel's wellness project.
But I'm baby-sitting.
Ariel's paying me a dollar an hour.
She's paying you to do her homework?
You take that baby back to Ariel,
and tell her that your shift is over.
And if she can't stop
her child from crying,
I'm gonna call
social services on her.
But I still got my dollar, right?
Who am I talking to?
Someone who knows
about the last two minutes
of poor Kimberly Weeks' life.
That was her real name, you know.
Or maybe you didn't, but I do.
I know everything
where you took her;
how it went from playful to rough
to really, really rough.
- What do you want?
- $500,000.
I don't have that kind of money.
I bet you can get your hands on it.
That's why I sent you
a little incentive.
Do you see a brown paper package
lying on your desk?
- Yes.
- Go on. Open it.
Take a look inside.
Oh. Oh, my God.
First one's on the house.
The other nine are gonna cost you.
Ariel?!
Suddenly, I'm not looking
forward to being a grandfather.
Nope. I'm not there.
I somehow managed to survive the night.
What are you doing up?
It's barely 6:30. You're all dressed,
you're ready for work.
I couldn't sleep. I decided I'd come out
here and try to find my ghost.
The one I keep seeing in my dreams.
First he's on hand
to witness a murder.
The next day,
he's at the crime scene.
Now, according to my dream last night,
he's spending time with the blackmailer,
listening in on her phone calls.
What are you saying? That he's following
the same case you are?
It seems that way. All the more reason
for me to try to find him.
Clearly, this guy knows more
about this whole thing than I do.
So, what are you looking at? I mean,
how do you track a ghost, exactly?
Is there some kind of
secret website?
Look, according to my dream, he died
the same night that girl Kimberly did.
So I've been looking through
the obituaries for last night and today,
but I'm not finding anything.
Maybe you're going at it
from the other direction.
Meaning?
Well, you know, when old Mrs.
What's-Her-Name down the street died...
... it took her husband, like,
three weeks after the funeral
to get around to putting
an obit in the paper.
The obituary writer is, like,
the last guy to know when someone dies.
You need to find the first guy.
You're right.
White Peaks Regional Hospital. May I
put you on hold for just one moment?
I'm sorry. We can't release
a patient's personal health
- information without a court order.
- I understand. Really.
I do, and as I told you, I work
for the District Attorney's office,
and I'm not asking for
any personal information.
I just wanted to know if a man matching
the description I gave you died here,
and if he did, what his name is.
Please. It pertains to the murder
of a young woman.
You say he was Caucasian?
Around 30?
If I could tell you
what you want me to tell you,
I wouldn't have anything
to tell you.
Mind if I have a seat?
Is that your wife and daughter?
They must miss you terribly.
Listen, who... who are you,
and what do you want?
I told you what I wanted
that day in the park.
I want to know what you know
about the murder of Kimberly Weeks.
I know you saw the whole thing.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
You were there the night she died
and the next day at the crime scene.
And then you listened in while a woman
tried to blackmail the murderer.
Listen, I know you are going
through a terribly difficult time,
trying to deal with your mortality,
to make peace with the fact
that your life is over.
It's a huge adjustment.
But I really need your help.
- Did you see me, Daddy?
- Yeah.
Yes, I saw you, sweetheart.
Now, come on. Go grab Mommy.
It's almost time to go.
Look, I don't know who you are
or what you think you know,
but I have surgery in 20 minutes,
so I'd appreciate it if you let me
and my family finish our lunch.
So let me see if I understand this.
This looks exactly
like the woman you saw
blackmailing Kimberly Weeks' killer,
but you don't want us
to distribute it?
That's right.
Any particular reason?
I guess I'm just not certain
of the accuracy
of my dreams
pertaining to this case.
The description of that woman,
I'm not sure I can stand behind it.
Am I allowed to ask what triggered
this crisis in confidence?
It's a long story.
In my dreams, I saw someone,
a ghost, who witnessed both
the murder and the blackmail.
- A ghost?
- He died of cardiac arrest
a few minutes before Kimberly found
herself in the car with her killer.
And I've been searching for him,
this ghost, ever since that night
to see what he knows,
to see what he saw.
And I actually found him this morning.
The problem is,
he's about as far from dead
as you can possibly get.
He's actually alive and well
and living in Scottsdale.
- The ghost?
- His name is Dr. Brian Seward.
He's a surgeon at White Peaks
Regional Hospital.
Obviously, he's not dead.
Obviously, he didn't see anything.
Which makes me wonder
if any of the things I saw,
or any of the things
that I dreamt actually
happened the way that I saw them.
Ariel, I'm on a work call here.
Can you please take care of that baby?
Mitch, hold on one second, will you?
Allison?!
- I'm giving Marie a bath.
- Ariel?!
- Bridgette!
- I don't have it.
And Ariel's in her room
with the door shut.
Look, sorry, Mitch.
Can I call you right back?
Thanks.
Yeah, Dad?
Do you not hear this?
- Sorry, Dad.
- "Sorry, Dad"?
Is that the best you can do?
Do a better job of taking care of
that baby. That is your assignment.
That's not your mother's,
not your sister's, not mine. It's yours.
No. I know.
I just, uh, I don't know.
I don't really want to move.
I don't want to think. I just...
want to lay down
and listen to music.
What's going on with you?
You feeling all right?
I feel really good.
I just... kinda hungry.
But really good.
Sorry about the crying.
Do you think Mom bought chips?
If she weren't our daughter,
I would have sworn
she was high as a kite.
- Don't say that.
- I'm just telling you what I saw.
She even went looking for munchies.
- Did somebody scream?
- You all right? What's going on?
There was a man in the house.
He was standing right there.
What are you talking about?
I was feeding the baby,
and I got hungry so I went
for a snack and then I came back
and saw him standing right there,
listening to what you guys were saying.
He was outside our door?
- Sweetie, there's no one here.
- I screamed and he disappeared.
- Where did he go?
- I don't know!
He was there, and then he was gone.
Okay, I'm going to go check the house.
You, you stand over there.
Be careful, Joe. Here.
I don't understand.
Did he say anything?
What did he look like?
He didn't look like anything.
He was just standing there
listening to what you
and Daddy were saying.
I don't know. He had...
sandy hair and wearing a white coat.
Wait, wait, a white coat
like a doctor's coat?
I checked inside.
I checked outside. Nothing.
This house is sealed up
tight as a drum.
I don't know what to tell you.
Thought this bed would be wall-to-wall
girls I climbed back into it already.
Everyone's in their rooms.
Everyone's in their beds.
I'm concerned about Ariel.
I'm telling you something's not right.
She's acting very strangely.
All this snacking? Now she's seeing
people who aren't there.
I don't know about that seeing people
that aren't there part.
I mean, the man that she described
sounded an awful lot like
that Dr. Brian Seward
I spoke with today.
The living dead guy?
Allison, come on, I just checked
every window and every door.
- No human being could get in here.
- Well, what about a ghost?
Honestly, honey, he's not a ghost.
Come on, you just said yourself
you saw him today,
interacting with his kid.
Didn't you say he's like a registered
surgeon at that hospital?
So either he's alive and running around
playing with his kids,
or he's dead and... and scaring
the heck out of mine,
but he can't be both. Right?
Right.
Just do me a favor.
Just keep an eye on Ariel tomorrow. Then
when I get home, we'll compare notes.
Of course.
Okay, Victoria. It's time.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
That was a close one.
Just tell me you saw something good.
Someone really rich doing
something really bad?
Actually,
I didn't just see something good.
I saw a gold mine.
You were at my house
last night, weren't you?
Don't even bother denying it.
I think I know
what you're up to, Dr. Seward,
and I'm not going
to let you get away with it.
Exactly what have I been up to?
I don't know what kind of weird
adrenaline junkie you are.
I don't know how you
figured out how to do it,
but you're killing yourself
a little bit,
making yourself into a ghost
so you can see people's secrets,
and then you bring yourself
back to life
so you and your partner
can blackmail them.
You actually said that
out loud in front of an adult.
I admire your courage.
But you must know
how absurd that sounds.
Don't worry about it.
I don't have to prove the "absurd" part.
I just have to prove
that you're a blackmailer.
And it's only a matter
of time until I do.
And in the meantime,
stay away from my house.
Stay away from my family.
Stay away from me.
You know, it's not what you think.
I'm not some greedy,
thrill-seeking bastard.
I'm dying.
You see this oval here?
That's a tumor.
Apparently, it's been growing
in my brain for at least five years.
Yeah, I had no idea.
I mean, I used to get headaches,
but who doesn't?
And then, one day last September,
I just collapsed.
I was clinically dead
for almost three minutes.
And I remembered
every moment of it.
I could choose to be anywhere,
watch anything,
anyone I wanted to see,
and they couldn't see me.
And just as I was getting
the hang of it, I was back.
They shocked my heart,
and I was back.
That's when I got the good news.
18 months to live.
Two years tops.
- I'm so sorry.
- Yeah, you and me both.
Look...
I'm only a resident.
Okay, I drop dead tomorrow,
no medical bills,
I will still leave my wife
with a hundred thousand dollars
of med school tuition I owe,
not to mention the mortgage,
my daughter's school.
I mean, come on.
It's kind of genius.
You stop the heart
with a few ccs of diazepam.
You get a whole three minutes
before brain damage sets in.
After that, it's just CPR 101.
Every ambulance driver
in the country
is trained on how to bring
the dead back to life.
You think it's depraved, don't you?
I think there has to be another way.
What you're doing is illegal.
And it's dangerous.
What if you don't come back next time?
Where does that leave your family?
You don't understand.
I don't have a choice.
No, you don't understand.
There is no choice.
I will bring a case against you.
Even if you're right,
even if I can't prove it,
is that really how you want to spend
this little bit of time you have left?
Putting your family through the stress
and the expense of a trial?
- So what exactly is it that you want?
- I want you to stop.
I want you to give me the name of
the man who murdered Kimberly Weeks.
- And in return?
- In return, this conversation
will stay in this room.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
I'll throw in the nine bloody
fingernails that will prove that
the man whose name I'm going to give you
is the one who killed her in exchange
- for your word.
- My word?
That the man isn't arrested
until after 5:00 today.
Why? Are you and your partner
getting paid off at 4:59?
Do we have a deal?
What if I say no?
I might just forget the man's name.
I might just lose those fingernails.
I have something at stake.
You have something at stake.
That's why they call it a deal.
Sorry. I don't know
what happened to me yesterday.
I was like a dead person.
Yeah, I noticed.
Totally spaced. I couldn't do
a thing but lay on my bed.
And then when I saw
the dead guy, I couldn't sleep.
So I had to wake up this morning
at 4:30 to do my homework.
But you're feeling all right now?
No, I'm fine.
I'm just a little tired, but fine.
Look, there's Adam.
Great. I can... it's his turn.
So I can give him the baby now.
Okay.
Good driving, sweetie.
Now you have a great day.
Mom will pick you up this afternoon.
You okay?
No, I just... everything's kind
of starting to spin.
I could really go for a cookie.
Ariel, look at you.
I don't really think I can do that.
Give me that doll.
That was weird.
You feel okay now?
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
When the doll was in the back seat,
you were fine,
and then as soon as you got close
to it... But I don't smell anything.
Give me the doll. I'll give it
to Adam before the bell rings.
Hey, you know what? You go ahead
to class. I'll give the doll to Adam.
But... Dad, I mean,
what if the teacher sees?
The teacher's not going to see.
You go to class.
Let me give the doll to Adam.
Ariel, I'll give the doll to Adam.
Hey, Adam, Adam Mankowicz?
Hi. It's nice to meet you.
I guess you could say that
I'm your father-in-law. Joe Dubois.
Ariel's father.
Nice to meet you, sir.
- Special delivery.
- Thank you.
You gonna be okay looking after her?
Your eyes look a little red.
No, sir. I'm fine. I have allergies.
Really?
How often
do you get these allergies?
I mean, are we talking every night?
After school? Before school?
How about at night,
when your parents aren't home?
I really need to go.
Do your parents even know
about these allergies?
No, I didn't think so.
So let me ask you something.
The other night,
when it was your turn
to take care of the baby,
did you have allergies then?
I might have.
Well, guess what, son?
You're getting a divorce.
- What?
- That's right.
And you've won sole custody
of that baby.
You're gonna raise her on your own from
now until the end of the assignment.
That's not fair,
because me and Ariel are supposed
to finish this project together.
Adam, you wouldn't want
me to have to tell your parents
about these allergies of yours,
would you?
- You can't do that, that's blackmail.
- Maybe you'd like to take this up
with your ex mother-in-law,
who works for Phoenix Police Department?
- No, sir.
- Then we understand each other?
If I ever get the sense that
you've given my daughter your allergies,
I know where to find you.
Local attorney Patrick Davidson
was arrested today
for the murder of Mesa University
student Kimberly Weeks.
Police say that an anonymous tip
led them to the discovery
of nine of the victims' fingernails,
which were apparently removed
shortly after the murder.
The fingernails, all of them
covered with the lawyer's DNA,
- helped seal the case against Davidson.
- Good.
Good for you.
- Well, good for everybody, I hope.
- What is that supposed to mean?
I don't know. I just don't feel right
about Dr. Seward
just walking away from this whole thing
with $500,000 of ill-gotten gains.
It's for his family.
I know, that's what I keep
telling myself.
But we can't stop. Not now.
I don't know what to tell you, Vic.
Tell me, you'll do it again.
At least one more time. After that,
if you want to walk away...
Think of your family, Brian.
A quarter of a million dollars
is nothing.
Once you're gone, what do you suppose
they're going to live on?
You don't understand;
I don't have a choice. Okay?
- That woman from the DA's office...
- What about her?
Does she have a badge?
A gun?
She's just a fortune-teller, Brian.
She can't tell anyone about us.
No one would believe her.
We ended up on her radar
because the man we were blackmailing
was the #1 suspect
in a murder investigation.
From now on,
we just pick someone who is
of no interest to the DA's office,
some rich guy, cheating on his wife.
She'll never even know.
10:17...
Mrs. James Richardson,
do you know
where your beloved husband is?
I'm betting you don't.
Good thing you're a banker, pal.
It's going to cost you.
Okay, Victoria,
hit me with the paddles.
I'm running out of time.
Hello?
Anybody here?
Hi. I'm Allison.
I'm Allison Dubois.
I don't think we've officially met,
but I think you know about me.
I'm the fortune-teller,
the one with no badge or no gun.
Please, have a seat.
I ordered you something.
You ordered me something?
I didn't even know I was going
to stop in here until a minute ago.
But Brian did, he's the one who told me
you'd be coming. Please, sit.
Well,
he wanted me to say "hi" to you.
Brian, I mean.
We had a little talk
right after you murdered him.
I'm sorry...
I have no idea
what you're talking about,
and if you mean Dr. Brian Seward,
I understand
that he committed suicide.
You went to a lot of trouble to make it
look like a suicide. And you know what?
You did a great job.
The truth is, the police, the D.A.,
they're never gonna be able
to get you for his murder.
You're not drinking your ice tea.
Want me to order you something else?
I'm fine.
Anyway, put your mind at ease. The whole
murder thing, it isn't gonna happen.
You completely outsmarted us.
Okay?
Anyway, that's not what you need
to be concerned about.
What you need to be concerned about
is... now that Brian is dead, I mean...
full-time dead, you would be shocked
by the things he can actually
see where he is.
I mean, for instance,
not only did he know
you were gonna stop
in this little diner,
but he knew you were making
your way over the border,
to take that $500,000 you stole
and put it in a Mexican bank.
He also knew that you had the money
in the trunk of your car...
in cash,
under an old Indian blanket,
and that you kept a spare key
in a magnetized box in your wheel well.
You know, I went and had a little visit
with Brian's wife today.
It was a pretty tricky conversation,
but it really helped to have Brian
right there, by my side,
while I explained everything to her.
She was really interested
in what I had to say.
And it took a little doing,
but eventually I convinced her
to leave Katie with the baby sitter
and take a little drive out here.
No, she's not here now.
That was probably her just leaving.
You know, what you're doing
is a really good thing.
Now Brian's wife
is gonna have the money
to bury the father of her child.
She'll be able to pay off
his medical school bills,
put their little girl
through college...
live a better life.
If you get any ideas
about trying to get that money back,
you should just swallow them.
Brian wanted me
to let you know that...
he'll be watching you, always.
And he's got my number.
I know you're a little tight
on cash right now, so...
that ice tea, it's on me.