My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice on you.
You're blacklisted.
When you're burned, you've got nothing.
No cash, no credit, no job history.
You're stuck in whatever city
they decide to dump you in.
- Where am I?
- Miami.
You do whatever work comes your way.
You rely on anyone
who's still talking to you.
- A trigger-happy ex-girlfriend...
- Should we shoot them?
An old friend who used to
inform on you to the FBI...
You know spies...
A bunch of bitchy little girls.
Family, too...
Is that your mom again?
If you're desperate.
Someone needs your help.
Bottom line...
Until you figure out who burned you,
you're not going anywhere.
Previously on "Burn Notice"
Why go back to work for the people
who've put you through all this?
I want to clear my name.
I want to know who did this to me.
- You think I burned you?
- I know you did.
You're on the edge of something
much, much bigger than us, my friend.
People I work for...
They have plans for you.
Nate, I need you to pick me up.
Fi and Sam are on a job
dealing with some heroin dealers.
Out of the car!
They took Sam.
Yeah, that was pretty painful.
How was that for you?
- Uh, Mike, it's for you.
- Yello?
Come out,come out, wherever you are.
- Nate, I'm gonna pull over and get out.
- You said they were following us.
Yeah, they want me.
When I get out, you go.
You don't stop for anything,you got it?
I have a job to do. I need 12 hours.
If you even come near me before that,
I will put a bullet in my head.
I believe we have a deal.
At least this time
we get to say goodbye.
Thank you, Fi.
- Time to get some questions answered.
- Burn notice, huh?
We need to talk, Michael.
We've been trying to bring you in.
We're so looking forward to meeting you.
As a spy, you get to spend
a lot of time alone.
Whether you're in an indonesian prison,
a cave in the afghan mountains,
or the back of a cargo truck,
it comes with the job.
You're trained to make the most of it,
plan your next move,
go over your intel,
review your training.
But when you've cleaned
your gun 30 times
and reviewed the past tense
of every verb in five languages,
you start itching to make a move.
- Hello?
- Hello, Michael.
Sounds like you're having
quite a party out there.
Indeed we are.
And you're the guest of honor.
No need for that, Michael.
The shooting's all over.
I hope you're not too disappointed.
You can see me?
Oh, I wish I could see you.
I thought we were gonna meet.
We will. First some business.
Yeah, sweetie. I thought
we were gonna discuss why you burned me.
We've had our eye on you
for a while, Michael.
I'm sorry. I didn't catch your name.
No, you didn't.
Why don't you call me "Carla"?
Go over to the car.
We have something
we want you to take care of for us.
A job?
Don't call it a job. Call it a favor.
I assume it has to do with the guy
you've got gift-wrapped and duct-taped.
His name is Jimmy.
He's someone else we asked for a favor.
See, he decided to skip town instead.
Oh, so this is
your employee-retention program.
You... could call it that.
He needs to go back to Miami
and do as he's told.
You need to help him.
- I do? And why is that?
- We have his wife and daughter.
If you don't help, what happens to them?
Oh, and one more thing.
Jimmy called 911 when he saw our team.
You probably want to move along.
I do this and then we meet.
I keep my promises.
I'll see what I can do.
Don't move.
JIMMY THE CLIENT
Air bags are great
for surviving crashes,
but they make
some evasive maneuvers tough.
Gone are the days when
you could run through a stand of trees
without a face full of nylon.
Of course, anything you used
to do head-on, you can still do.
But it's a little hard on anyone
who's stuffed in the trunk.
-=bbs.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Burn Notice
Season02 Episode01
Security measures can
sometimes seem a little cruel.
Just like parents sometimes
twist their kid's arm
yanking them out of a busy street,
sometimes the safest thing
isn't the most comfortable.
Sorry about the trunk, but I had to
keep you out of sight for a few counties
until we got clear of the police.
Jimmy, what are you doing?
We don't have time for
this! I'm here to help you!
Now, the people who did this
are putting the screws to me, too.
I don't want to be here
any more than you do.
Now, do you want your family back?
I'm gonna work on that. Can you be good?
We have a long drive back to Miami.
If you can be good,
you get to ride upfront.
A couple months ago,
I got a call from this lady.
Smokey voice, lots of attitude?
Wait a minute. You know her?
Not as well as I'd like.
Anyway, she wanted me to break
into this place where I did a job.
A job? What is it you do, jimmy?
Look, I-I'm -- I'm
in computer systems, okay?
I did a gig about a year ago for
this company called Security Associates.
Security Associates...
Is that private military?
Yeah, sure, something like that.
I don't know, okay?
They were corporate guys,
but really scary.
And the lady on the phone, she told me
I had to break into there, okay?
And get a memory dump off
their hard drive and get it back to her.
What did you say?
I said she was freakin' insane!
I'm a computer tech, man.
I'm not -- I'm not a break-in guy.
So I was like, "no way!"
And this led to you
being hog-tied on an airstrip.
The lady on the phone threatened
my family, so we decided to bail.
We hired this guy with a private plane,
and then we went upstate.
And we were about to leave,
and these guys with guns...
they came out of this helicopter.
And then they just...
They took my wife and my kid.
Please, I don't even know
who you are, but...
you got to help me.
We'll figure something out.
Mike, easy.
Just me and a couple of
slicesof wonder bread.
Hey, you okay?
I got to say, I didn't expect you back.
Yeah, I didn't expect
o be back, either.
Making yourself comfortable,I see.
Uh, comfortable? I wouldn't go that far.
Mike, how do you fit into
these little shirts?
They're like doll clothes.
Anyway, after you got meout of the boat,
I didn't want to scare veronica,
You know, with all this, so I thought
I'd lay low at your place for a while.
Wait a minute.
What happened with the big meeting?
It didn't go as well as I'd hoped.
It seems the people that burned me
want me for a job.
- For now, that's all I got.
- A job? Does it pay?
More of a "we'll kill you
if you don't doit" type of thing.
Never liked those.
So, what is it?
Help some computer tech
steal some data.
I figure if I find out
what they want stolen,
I might get an idea
of who they are.
The guy's outside
in the, uh, in the caddy.
The caddy. You brought back the caddy.
Oh, Mike, that's great. I was afraid
to ask, you know, 'cause Veronica,
she was getting on my case, and I...
Yeah, about that.
It's gonna need a little work.
So we're safe here?
Safe would be a stretch,
but let's just say we could do worse.
- Okay, well, I need my phone, 'cause...
- No, Jimmy, you don't need your phone.
You called 911 on a double homicide.
The police are now tracking it.
You just need to go on in
and clean yourself up.
Go ahead.
I can't believe you, michael.
48 hours ago, we said goodbye...
possibly forever.
And then I get a message
from you on my cell
that I should come right over
because you got a job.
Fi, there's a lot going on, so...
you couldn't start with "I'm alive"?
I thought the fact that
I was calling covered that.
That's not the point.
Fi, I called you because
I need your help.
Sorry. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hello.
Yeah, mom, I'm fine. I told you
not to make calls on that phone.
Well, I know that, but I'm stuck
in a motel in Fort Lauderdale.
And I've been worried sick.
And if the phone's being bugged
by those spy people,
I guess now they know it, too.
I'm worried about my son.
Besides, calls from
a motel phone cost a dollar.
Oh, that's terrible.
So, when can I start making calls again?
Just come on home.
You can make all the calls you want.
What about those men with the guns?
Are you okay?
Yeah, more or less.
I'm so glad.
I'm glad too, mom.
Bye, michael.
You hadn't called your mom yet?
I was going... to wait a bit.
Thanks for coming, Fi.
So, this woman on the phone...
Did you ever see her in person?
Did she give you a name, anything?
No, I told you, I never met her.
She said her name was Carla. That's it.
Besides that, it was just, you know,
"Go steal the stuff for us or else."
What is this data? What's on
these computers that they want so badly?
I don't know. I mean, they don't pay me
to look at the files.
They pay me to keep people
from stealing them.
Why do they even need us?
I mean, if they're blowing up a plane,
they've got guys.
The people behind this, they
don't want to gettheir hands dirty,
so they get others to do
their work for them
like making us break
into Security Associates.
I checked that place out.
Guy who runs it is Ryder Stehl.
Guy's been in all the hot spots,
usually has corporate clients
who want some heavy firepower.
basically any place where
more guns equal more money.
Yeah, that's the guy. Yeah.
I'm gonna need you
to make an introduction.
Talk to ryder? Face-to-face?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Private security companies don't have
a lot of walk-in business, Jimmy.
So we're gonna need an introduction,
and you're the best we've got.
If I'm gonna do this, I need
to lookat their security setup.
It'll be fine.
Sam and Fi will back us up
if anything goes wrong, right?
Yeah, right. Right, we got you covered.
Absolutely no problem.
- Calm down. You'll be fine.
- Right.
- Can we just go over itone more time?
- Sure.
We go in, you introduce me, you leave.
Private military companies are
best known for their bodyguard work.
For a big enough check,
they'll rain hot lead down
wherever you want.
It's not work that attracts
"service with a smile" types.
Thanks for, um...
this is the guy that I told you about.
You wanted to talk to me?
Terry Millar. I heard a lot of
great things about your operation.
Ryder Stehl. Jimmy here
tells me you're in mining.
My boy jimmy here,
he says that you're the folks
to look for when we need a mercenary.
We're security consultants,
not mercenaries.
RYDER STAHL MERCENARY
Right. I think what he meant was...
I can speak for myself, mate.
Piss off, then. We've got business.
You call yourself what you like.
I got serious business to be handled.
Now can we go upstairs
and talk in private?
I've got mining interests up around
the northern border of Kenya.
Locals are my problem.
I need 'em dealt with.
"Dealt with"
What does that mean?
You know what it means.
Enough with the word games.
I'm willing to pay good money
for a permanent solution to my problem.
Mr. Millar,
you just solicited an illegal act,
and my security tells me
you've got a backup team
sitting on the roof
of the parking garage across the street.
Are you a cop?
Is this a joke?
No joke. Two-person team watching.
We do regular security sweeps.
I don't know who these blokes are,
but they're not backup.
I've got an operation that looks
to prove out in the low nine figures.
I got enemies, mate.
- So they're not yours.
- Not mine.
I guess we'll just have to find out.
Take him out the back.
You're being too hard on Mike.
You know, he damn near got
himself killed saving me.
Yeah, and I damn near got myself
killed saving the both of you.
And then he comes back
and acts like nothing happened.
I'm just saying, I can count on one hand
the number of buddies I got
who would stage an armed assault
to save my butt, okay?
You got Mike.
You got...
When you're claiming
to be someone you're not,
the key is commitment.
You've got to sell it like
your life depends on it.
Because sometimes it does.
The point is, Mike is
the kind of guy who's got your back.
Gun!
One reason to work with the same people
is you know each other's moves,
So if you shoot at your team
in the middle of an operation,
they know to go with it.
What the hell is he doing?
I think we just got recruited
into Michael's cover I.D.
Get down! Get down!
It takes a good marksman to shoot you
at 50 feet from a moving car.
But it takes a great marksman to miss...
while making it look like
they're trying to hit you.
Or "markswoman," as the case may be.
- So, you're saying that that went well?
- He doesn't think I'm a cop anymore.
It's true.
I got him backstopped
with a job history, bank accounts,
even got a british mining company
to hire him as a contractor retroactively.
Point is, Ryder's boys have been
calling around, checking him out.
Now we just go back to him,
sell him on the deal,
and check out his security layout.
Listen, even if we pull this thing off,
I'm the only guy that can get that data,
and they know that, okay?
If we do this,I'm a dead man.
Never let that happen, jimmy.
One problem at a time.
That's easy for you to say.
- Yo, Jimbo.
- What?
Come on. Let's go upstairs,
set you up with a beer,maybe a yogurt.
Got this great card game
we used to play
back in the S.E.A.L. Teams
when we were feeling crappy.
I'll teach you. You're gonna love it.
Yeah, ma,you're back in town.
Michael, you have to come
over here now. It's a disaster.
On my way.
What are you doing?
Put the shotgun down.
What am i supposed to do?
There were men in suits with guns
out there after me.
They were after me.
Well, you're here,
so maybe i should have a shotgun.
What's the disaster?
It's the coffee maker.
You had me rush out of here on such
short notice, the damn thing burned out!
It blew a fuse in the kitchen,
and it spoiled a fridge full of food.
This is the disaster?
A coffee maker built in 1967?
And the food.
I've been cleaningfor hours.
I got your phone
in the glove compartment of the charger.
My phone in the charger?
I assumed it was one of yours.
You go through those things
like toothpicks.
Car's in the garage.
Excuse me a sec, mom.
Hello there, Michael.
Good to hear from you.
Glad I could brightenyour day.
Looks like you owe my mom
a new coffee maker.
Care to tell me why
you're breaking into her house?
Just letting you know we can.
I'd like to remind you that
there's a clock on this operation of ours.
I want you to speak to someone.
Daddy?
No, it's not your daddy.
I'm a friend of your dad's.
Can I talk to him?
He's not here right now,
but he wants me to tell you
that he misses you.
I don't like it here.
When is he coming?
Can you tell me where you are?
No, she can't.
Leave her alone.
You're not really
gonna hurta little girl.
Maybe. Maybe not.
If I get what I want,
you don't need to find out.
They said you weren't in, so I waited.
You got a lot of balls coming here.
It seems to me if anyone
should be upset, mate, it's me.
I'm the one who got shot at.
I'm the one who needs a job done.
If you're not interested,
I'll leave Miami.
If you are interested, we talk now.
Come on. Let's try it again.
Every thief knows that
the best way to scout
a place you want to rob
is as a customer.
Who gets to see the
vault at the local bank?
The rich guy with something to protect.
Who gets to see the security
at a private military company?
A guy who wants to start
his own little war.
There's unoxidized kimberlite
in this region here.
It's called blue ground.
It means diamonds.
My problem is the village.
We can handle the problem area.
Eliminate the civilians and burn it...
You'll never know it was there.
Let's get to the details and the deal.
Not so fast, mate.
There's a hundred mil U.S.
People'd kill for this deal,
not just those people from the other day.
I need to know my information is secure.
Building security is 24-7.
We have biometric security
in all the key areas.
Key-card access
through out the building.
A great way to get people
talking about their security
is to put them on the defensive.
Accuse a guy of having bad locks,
and before you know it,
he's telling you
where his motion detectors are.
Right. That's a nice toy.
But what about this door?
Hollow-core veneer.
You can cut through that with a handsaw.
That may be, but what do you do then?
The door's alarmed.
Building security is here in
under a minute, police under five.
Here...
the computer is kept in a sealed room
with a burn vault.
Someone breaks in,
it melts the drives to slag.
It takes some practice,
but counting your steps
can be extremely useful
if you need to reproduce
a floor plan from memory.
Not bad. Could be better.
I'll come back tuesday.
We'll talk terms.
Once you've memorized the floor plan,
you want to get it down on paper
as quickly as you can.
Combine that with the technical specs
of the security devices in the room,
and you'll know where
the holes in the security are.
Then it's just a matter of slipping
through one of those holes.
That is a terrible 2.
So let's do the math.
- How many 2s in a deck?
- Four.
Right. So those are your cards
you can play... 2s or 4s.
Or, 2 plus 4 is what?
6. You can play an 8.
2 times 4 is what?
8. You can play a 4, an 8, a 2...
Sam!
I appreciate you trying
to distract him, but
could you take it outside?
Sure. Come on, jimbo.
Let's go out on the balcony,
get some fresh air so you can concentrate.
Figuring out a time when
we can have our conversation?
Fi, I'm planning a heist.
Um, c-can you just...
I mean, I-I got to do the job...
first.
Right.
So, what can i do for the job?
I need you to get us into iso-gene labs.
It's a dna-testing facility
one floor above Security Associates.
I need to get in there
for an hour at night alone, and...
we're gonna be making a lot of noise.
You have a high estimation
of my skills, Michael.
You've earned every bit of it, Fi.
So, once I'm in,
how do I get the data?
It's complicated. You have to, um...
I have to come with you.
I don't think
this is your kind of operation.
I know. None of this is.
But those computersand hard drives
are completely secure,okay?
I made them that way.
So to steal the data, we have to tap
into the hardwiring in the wall.
And we'll only have
one chance to do that.
Well,that's gonna be dangerous.
Doesn't matter.
This is for my wife and my daughter.
Get me in and I'll get the data.
Hold on a sec.
What's the matter?
Oh, bum knee. I got to, you know,
stretch it once in...
badly done surveillance
that is surveillance you notice,
can mean a lot of things.
Some organizations need intelligence
but can't afford to pay for training.
Some organizations just
want you to know they're watching.
- Who are you? Who sent you?
- I don't know. I answered an ad.
100 bucks to watch and take notes.
Some woman.
- She give you anything?
- Yeah.
She told me not to open this.
HURRY UP
WE'RE WAITING
I was wondering when you'd call.
Oh, that was some operative you sent.
A freelancer. I don't think he'll be
answering newspaper adsfor a while.
Jimmy got our message?
We thought you could use a little
reminder of what's at stake here.
We head in tonight.
Is that soon enough?
That will be fine,thank you.
Now...
I need something from you.
What is that?
The guns your guys used to kill
those men at the airstrip. You have them?
They could probably be located.
Whatever for?
I want them.
If I'm gonna work for you,
I want tactical support.
I confess, I'm curious.
Fine, you'll have your guns.
And Jimmy's family.
I will give you a date and location.
You will deliver them
when and where I say.
Of course, Michael. We want this
to be a good experience for everyone.
I am so sorry.
We called as soon as
we realized the problem.
Apparently the engineer missed
the defect in the architectural plans.
We're dealing with all the floors.
We'd start with
Security Associates below you,
but you're up first 'cause
you've got all the heavy equipment.
Well, lucky us.
I'm just glad you guys caught it
before someone fell through he floor.
Getting into a secure facility
is as simple as giving yourself
a good reason to be there.
- Here we are.
- Uh, yeah.
- It's so stiff.
- I'll pull it out.
Right here.
Our guys will need a few hours.
The defect's in the beam,
so they'll be cutting.
We just need you to notify the building
and let the workers in.
The next morning, it will be like we were
never here, and I'll be out of your hair.
Hey, you come back anytime you'd like.
They'll be by tonight.
Please don't forget to call
building security,
or I will get into so much trouble.
We can't have that. I'll call now.
Talk to our rep?
- She told me you were coming, yes.
- How 'bout her, huh?
We're gonna be
in the back lab over here.
We're gonna be making some noise.
Should only take a couple of hours.
There's some B.S.
about the chemicals we use.
Now, you can come back,
but it's got to be on your insurance.
I'm, uh... I'm fine here, thanks.
The typical floor is concrete
slab over 20-gauge steel pan
with steel trusses spaced
30 inches for support.
When you cut through a floor,
the thing you have
to worry about is wiring.
Cut into the wrong wire, and
you'll set off the building alarms,
electrocute yourself, or both.
If you don't want a chunk of concrete
crashing through to the floor below,
you need to drill a hole
and anchor the slab.
A concrete saw cuts it like butter.
If you've done your planning right,
you'll be dropping into a blind spot
for the security system,
usually behind an interior wall.
Motion detectors bounce sound off objects
and analyze the reflection.
If something changes,
the alarm goes off.
Move slow enough,
and a wool comforter absorbs
enough sound to keep it from triggering.
A thermal blanket, meanwhile,
shields your body from heat sensors.
- How do you think he's doing in there?
- It's michael.
So, look, Fi...
I got to go back to Veronica,
explain where I've been,
why I'm all beat to hell,
and what happened to the caddy.
- I'd pay to watch that.
- Oh, come on. Fi, you're a girl.
What do I say?
I'm your girl consultant now?
When did I sign up for that job?
Fine. Forget it.
You know, I got lots of other friends
with ovaries. I got you...
Tell her you got beaten up
defending a helpless man from a gang
of ex lowlife soldiers.
- It's true enough.
- Okay.
- So I'm the hero.
- And the helpless man.
Somebody's working late.
Better let Mike know.
Evening, mr. Stehl.
Hey, Stevie. Thanks for the call.
- What's going on?
- It's, uh,probably nothing,
but you said you wanted us
to call you any time
if something unusual
was going on in the building.
Ryder is back
- How long?
I don't know.
It's supposed to be backing up now.
The data runs along the cable
of the backup drives.
Well, what's the problem?
'Cause we don't have time.
I set the backupf or 11:30.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, it's coming, it's coming.
Oh, god. Oh, god.
- That's not good.
- Give them a minute.
- Oh, god, I'm so sorry. What do we do?
- Plan "B."
Quadrangle buckshot
is a specialized round
designed to destroy
the inside of anything delicate
a computer, for example.
Get back!
Take the rope and tie it off.
- We're going out the window?
- Unless you want to wait around.
For hardened security glass,
I prefer frag-12,
a military round
with an explosive projectile.
Ohh, I think I sprained my body.
You want another beer?
- Telling you,did wonders for my ribs.
- You're fine.
I just want my family back.
- We're working on it.
- Yeah, how?
Those guys at Security Associates,
they're gonna kill me
as soon as they get a chance.
Exactly, and that
makes them predictable,
and that's how
we're gonna solve your problem.
Can you get me a
boat,something disposable?
Disposable?
Oh, I see where you're going.
I know a guy.
Yeah. It's a decent boat,
once upon a time.
It's got mold, but...
it doesn't sound like it's gonna be
around long enoughto bother us.
How is this gonna solve y problem?
These guys from Security Associates
want to kill you.
We need to give them
the opportunity to do just that.
Trust me.The heat that's on you,
everyone thinking that you're dead
is gonna be the best thing
that ever happened to you.
Yeah, Fi?
Michael, I got a delivery today.
Someone was kind enough
to break into the trunk of my car.
Yeah, what was it?
A present from your friends.
Be careful with those, Fi.
They're very hot.
Oh, I'll take good careof them.
Michael, your mother keeps calling me.
These last few days have been
a lot for her to handle.
I know the feeling.
Go see her, Michael.
I got to go visit my mom.
- Sam, get on that boat.
- Aye, aye, skipper.
You might want to slow down, mom.
How, Michael?
You tell me.
I'm not sleeping.
This business with the coffee maker.
- This is about a coffee maker?
- It isn't just that.
Your brother's still up
in Fort Lauderdale, you know.
I mean, he believes it's not safe here.
Uh, Nate has disappeared
for years before, mom.
He's been in Fort Lauderdale
for a few days.
What about me, Michael?
All these years,
and finally I see what you do.
You tell me I have to leave town
at a minute's notice.
I can't talk on the phone.
We're being chased by men with guns!
How am I supposed to deal with this?
All these years, you wondered why
I didn't come home, why I didn't call.
This is why, mom.
I never wanted thisfor you.
I'm sorry.
Well, it still doesn't explain
why you didn't write.
You want this big, right?
Just enough for the boat, Fi.
Try not to break all the windows
in South Beach.
- Call Ryder.
- Are you sure?
You said the cops
will be listening on this phone,
and that's
--that's the point.
We talked about this,and we practiced it,
so if you could do thatnow.
Security associates.
Uh, I need --I need to speak to Ryder.
T-tell him that it's jimmy.
Hold, please.
Did a hell of a jobin my office, kid.
Do you really think
you're gonna get away with this, huh?
Do you have any idea
who you just took on?
Please, just listen, okay?
It was... it was the guy, the one...
the one that I introduced you to?
Look, I want to make this right, okay?
If we can just meet,
then I can explain everything.
I don't need explanations, Jimmy.
I need my data back.
I want to give it back to you.
That's good. Just tell me where you are.
Once the cops pick up a call
on a flagged cell,
they triangulate its location.
From there, they organize
and deploy units,
a process that can take 10 minutes,
give or take.
Bad guys don't have
that chain of command.
They can be anywhere as fast as
their wheels can take them.
Get in position. Stay out of sight.
Going down to the boat.
What do we do if he comes out?
Do you want us to pop him?
No, I need to figure out
what the hell's going on first.
Then you pop him.
Get going.
You want to talk,
we do it face-to-face.
So you coming out,
or do I come down to the boat?
How do I know you're not armed?
I don't want to shoot you, Jimmy.
I just want to get my data back.
Hold him off.
Tell him to prove he's unarmed.
I don't believe you. Okay? Show me.
Show me that you don't havea gun.
What do you want me to do?
Here. Here. See?
Unarmed.
I-I don't believe you.
Jimmy, I'm not messing around.
I'm coming down.
Okay, just wait a second.
He's gonna figure this out.
How much longer do I have to do this?
If he finds out you're not on that boat
before the ATF gets here,
he will track you down.
He will go after you and your family
for the rest of your life.
Now, you will do this now.
Do it.
Stay back.
You don't want your data
all over the internet, do you?
Now don't take another step.
All right.
Take off your clothes, the jacket
and the pants, and then you can come.
- I'm not taking my pants off.
- I'm not messing around.
Neither am I.
I lied, jimmy.
Want to see my gun?
Here it is.
Now, want to know
what I'm gonna do to you
if you don't come out right now?
Yeah. Tell me.
Tell me what you're gonna do.
Drop it and show me your hands.
On your stomach... now!
Get your butt off this deck.
Move!
Nice hardware.
It's not mine. It's a setup.
Put him in the truck.
It's going to be hard for them to explain
why they have guns linked
to a double homicide.
Still, probably best to make sure
no one ever knows you're alive.
And my family?
Sam has a friend who's gonna take you
on a boat to Haiti tonight.
Should be fine.
Coast guard doesn't pay much attention
to boats going to Haiti.
From there, you'll fly to Argentina
and meet your family at the airport.
- You really think they'll be there?
- Well, Carla needs me for other things.
If she doesn't keep her promises to you,
she loses me as an asset.
Man, I-I don't know how to thank you.
Do you want my car?
I mean, it's at my work.
I don't really need it anymore.
It's a Saab.
Convertible.
Yeah. Love convertibles.
There you go.
I got to leave the country,
and you're stuck working for them.
I don't know who has it better.
You do, Jimmy. Believe me.
You do.
In intelligence gathering,
too little information
is obviously a problem,
but too much information is just
as bad in some ways.
500 files.
And every op looks pretty nasty.
The question is,
why does she want this stuff?
No clue,
but it's a start.
Time to talk.
I lost youthe other day.
- I came back, Fi.
- But you left...
You had a choice to make,
and you made it.
I always thought...
maybe
when it came down to it that...
but you didn'T.
What are you saying, Fi?
That I'll always care about you.
And I'll still help you with your thing,
and you'll still help me with mine.
But we can't be together.
I know.
I said that for a long time.
Yes, you have.
When you work as a spy
it's easy to think of people as assets,
resources to accomplish a goal...
because you don't have
a personal relationship with an asset.
You don't care about an asset.
You don't miss the scent of an asset
when she leaves the room.
I think 4 across is "beets."
- That looks like a tough one.
- A little.
But I'm getting through it.
Well, if you need any help,
I'm right over there.
I was just leaving, actually.
Next time?
It's a good thing
I'm patching things up with Veronica,
'cause if I wasn't,that's
a real firecracker there.
Hey, what about you?
You're a free man now that
you and Fi are, well, you know.
- We weren't together, Sam.
- Okay.
- How'd it go with Jimmy?
- Great.
He gave a call.
He's with his family. He's safe.
Looks happy enough.
Hold on a sec.
- Hello?
- Hello, Michael.
Just wanted to call now that
you're done with our little project.
See how that worked out?
He's happy. We're happy. You're happy.
We want to make this arrangement work.
Or you'll kill me.
See? Now you're catching on.
Yeah, just one thing.
You said we'd meet.
You promised, I believe.
But we did meet, michael.
Tell sam thanks for the help
with the crossword.
What's up?
ENJOY THE PUZZLE. I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
Arrangement : S@lomon