My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice.
You're blacklisted.
When you're burned,
You've got nothing...
no cash,no credit,
No job history.
You're stuck in whatever city
They decide to dump you in.
- Where am I?
- Miami.
you do whatever work
Comes your way.
you rely on anyone
Who's still talking to you.
a trigger-happy
Ex-girlfriend...
Should we shoot them?
... an old friend who's
Informing on you to the FBI...
You know spies...
A bunch of bitchy little girls.
... Family,too...
Is that your mom again?
... If you're desperate.
someone needs your help.
bottom line... Until
You figure out who burned you,
you're not going anywhere.
there's a good reason covert
Operatives keep their work
a secret from their families.
once your family knows what
You do,you've got problems.
best case... they're scared.
worst case... They figure
They can get into trouble
and you'll get them out of it.
Yeah. Mike,it's your brother.
Listen,uh,
I'm out at opa-locka airport,
And I got a situation.
I need you to come out and meet me.
I got to go.
Come on,man.
First you told me to leave,
And now you're gonna kill me?
That doesn't even
Make sense,all right?
I mean,it's gonna take you
Hours to deal with my body,
And then there's the cops.
Come on,man.
Come back,I shoot you in the face.
What the hell were you doing?
Working.
You're always on my ass
To get a job,so here...
I'm working.
Lying in a heap in an airport
Parking lot... How's that pay?
My buddy got into some
Trouble with some guys
And needed someone to talk to them.
I said I'd do it for a grand.
"some guys?" what guys?
Guys. I don't know.
Look,I'm just trying
To make a living here.
Besides,you have
No business giving me crap,bro.
You're driving around in my car.
your car?
Yeah,I busted ass for an entire
Summer working on this car.
Mom had no right
To give it to you.
She said that dad wanted me
To have it.
Oh,okay.
So you bailed,
I take a double dose
Of dad's crap for years,
And you get the car... Yeah,that's fair.
Nate,is this your way
Of asking me
To help you with this job?
Is that what this is?
It's like you read minds,bro.
We work on this together,
You clean up your act.
Http://www.ragbear.com
If I don't help him with this job,
He's gonna get himself killed.
Oh,now he's decided
That the car is his.
I've never seen you this
Attached to anything,Michael.
If my dad left me this car,
It was for a good reason.
He wasn't the sort of guy
Who would just leave me this
Because he was feeling generous.
I almost lost a finger putting
In that air-filter case.
I don't think he did you any favors.
Yeah. Well,that was more his style.
Try it now.
Uh,check the ignition.
You know,you've got a bug in there.
A bug?
Under the dash.
Looks like Sam's work.
Fi,you don't know it's Sam.
I know Sam's style.
I thought you had an arrangement...
He tells the feds what you're up to,
Tells you what the feds are up to?
I'll handle it.
No,no,no,no.
I'd be happy to take care of it.
There's nothing like
A smashed kneecap
To remind Sam
Who his friends are.
Don't say anything.
I know it's there.
They'll only hear
What I want them to hear.
Is that tradecraft,Michael?
Or just protecting your friend?
It's both,fi.
I got to get cleaned up.
Could you put this back
together and don't...
I'll... I'll behave.
Maybe.
I've worked airport
security for a year.
Log planes in and out,
deal with the cargo manifests.
So there's this family...
Lebanese,I think... the Zamars.
They're two brothers and a dad.
They run some kind of
import-export business.
So the thing is,
we became kind of friends.
They gave me some stuff.
Stuff? What kind of stuff?
Basketball tickets,some nice tequila,
Loaned me money a few times.
My... my wife's pregnant.
We're trying to get ready for the baby.
It's been hard.
I get it. You needed the money. Go on.
Anyway,I-I did them some favors.
I'd change the arrival
times on planes in the log.
It's against the rules,
but it seemed like little stuff.
Then,last week,they told me
They wanted me to leave
a flight off the log entirely,
And that's serious.
I-I didn't want to do it.
And I remembered... Nate told me
That you two had this kind
of business helping people.
Nate said we had
a business together...
The two of us,like a team?
Yeah.
Yeah,he said he was gonna
talk to the guys
And get them off my back.
I saw how well that went.
They came to my house.
They threatened me,
threatened my wife.
I-I said I was gonna quit my job.
They said they were gonna
hurt me if I did.
I just want to give
the money back and walk away.
Can you just talk to them and...
It's a little late for that,jake.
I know I screwed up,okay?
I just don't want
my family to pay for it.
And my wife,she...
I'm barely hanging
on to her as it is,man.
I don't know what else to do.
Please.
I'll look into it.
Thanks.
I told your friend
I'd help him out. You happy?
You should be,too.
I'm hustling you work.
Yeah,it's almost like we're a team.
You want to get in the car?
Hey,about the car...
did mom show you dad's Will?
No,all I saw was an old pack of kools
And an unfinished to-do list.
Come on. You hated him.
I put up with his crap.
I rebuilt the car's engine.
I'll give you the distributor cap
If you agree we should find dad's Will.
Deal?
Mike,you been doing some
work on the charger?
There's enough grease
in here to lube a semi.
You know,these pants are new.
Yeah,Fi and I have been
doing a little work on it...
Exhaust,electrical.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What's wrong with it?
Just glitchy.
Glitchy? Yeah.
Well,glitchy i
s my specialty,Mike.
Really? Your specialty? Yeah.
Might take you up on that.
Thanks,Sam.
Here we go.
I've looked into these guys
a little bit for you.
That's Eli Zamar.
He runs the company.
Ari and Ilan are the sons.
Eli's the one that beat up Nate.
The name sounds Israeli,
But jake said they were lebanese.
Yeah,the business is registered there.
They got an office here,
And they got a hangar out
at the airport.
Now,this guy... Eli...  Mike,
I think he's had some training.
Every time he comes outside,
he does a perimeter scan.
You see that?
in gathering intel,little
things can tell you a lot...
a topflight alarm system,
well-placed cameras
without blind spots,
paying attention
to strangers in the area.
Uh-oh. Time to go.
more aggressive
intelligence gathering
is more delicate.
but someone who knows what
to look for can find out a lot.
Hey.
Is this hangar 12?
What you looking for?
Hangar 12. I think.
I met this guy at a club,
And he told me that
he had a private plane
And that he would take me up in it.
And I-I get here,
And it's nothing like
a regular airport.
No,this is a private airport.
I mean,this is hangar 12,
But it's not your friend's hangar 12.
God,what a jerk.
What's the problem?
No problem. Relax.
You have to leave.
You guys are working,huh?
You know,before I go,
do you guys have a bathroom?
I mean,I drove all the way out
here from south beach
And it looks like I have to go
all the way back and...
I'm sorry. You have to leave.
Hey.
You're the,uh,boss?
That's right.
I-I was just looking for a bathroom.
No bathroom.
Out.
Okay. Unh. God,I just need to pee.
if you know what to look for,
a bunch of little things
can tell you everything
you need to know.
Arms dealers. Great.
Heavy stuff,too.
That plane had new engines.
It could probably carry a few
.50-caliber machine guns,
Maybe even a small tank.
Probably shipping off
to some african war
Off limits to legit dealers.
You're sure? I mean,you saw guns?
Didn't need to.
know a gunrunner when I see one.
They're my people.
They ship in a special lubricant,
And the whole hangar smells like it.
Mmm! There it is!
No wonder I got my ass kicked.
Oh,you were lucky.
The old guy had a desert eagle
9 millimeter with combat grip.
Ex-mossad.
What do you mean?
Like Israeli spies?
Sure.
Every other retired
spook is an arms dealer.
Not a bad gig,
if you can stand the ex-spooks.
You should probably call your client.
So... so,what do I do,huh?
I mean,Inever saw anything
like that there.
No,of course not.
They're too smart
to keep anything around
That would get them busted.
Listen,jake,now that we know
what we're dealing with,
We can try to do something.
I should call the police.
I-I know I'm gonna get busted.
No,if you call the police,
The only crimes they'll find are yours,
And the zamars will know
you turned on them.
That's not good,jake.
Take a look at this.
This is how your job opened up.
The old security manager
died in a car accident.
All of his brakes just happened
to fail at the same time.
Jesus.
I can't believe this.
I went to a goddamn basketball
game with these people.
The seats weren't even that good.
Well,next time you accept a bribe,
I'd hold out for courtside seats.
Jake,focus.
We need to deal with the problem.
I'm sorry. I don't... what do I do?
Cooperate.
We need to get them busted
with the guns,
And they need to go down
in a way that's unrelated to you
So it looks like you had
nothing to do with it.
Get them busted with the guns.
But where are the guns?
That's what we're gonna go find out.
Mike,um,there's something
I want to talk to you about.
Yeah,Sam? What is it?
I know you've been pushing
hard on this burn notice,
Trying to get yourself off
the blacklist and all,
And I understand that,
But I'm getting a lot of pressure.
Pressure? What kind of pressure?
Well,you know,they...
they want me to give them more.
It's always more,but the thing is that...
Yeah,Sam?
Oh,hey,there they go.
Talk about this later.
one cheap and effective
security measure
is working in an area
with low or no traffic.
anyone is a car is too obvious,
so you force any would-be
followers to get out and walk.
They're in there somewhere.
Oh,Mikey,come on.
It's 10 square blocks.
My cardiovascular fitness
isn't what it used to be.
You never said
we were gonna be walking.
Rest frequently.
Drink plenty of fluids.
You'll be fine,Sam.
Okay. Where do I find fluids?
I'm telling you,
there's no one here.
Dad thought he saw someone.
This is stupid. There's no one.
But we have to check.
I'm getting my shoes dirty.
fighting is something
you want to avoid.
once you fight someone,
he knows your face.
There's nobody here.
Shut up.
you kind of blow your cover
when you hit a guy
with a piece of rebar.
but when you have no choice...
rebar it is.
Send that to china,you sons of bitches!
Go ahead and offshore that!
You know,they used
to have 30 union welders here
and a foreman.
What are you doing?
What the hell does
it look like I'm doing,Pal?
I'm throwing crap at a warehouse!
Oh,you got a gun.
What are you... security?
Hey,go ahead,come on.
Shoot me. I'd thank you for it.
There's no jobs around here anyway.
You want to shoot him? Shoot him.
Let's go.
Oh,you don't want to shoot him?
Yeah,lovely.
Huh? Yeah,batter up,huh?
Oh,strike three!
You're laid off!
Yeah!
They're careful.
If we're gonna get them caught
on anything serious,
It's gonna take some more time.
Then I want melody out of here.
I mean,this was my mistake.
She shouldn't have to pay for it.
When the zamars ask
why your wife left town,
What are you gonna say?
They came to see me yesterday.
They got another shipment
going out soon.
They gave me more basketball tickets.
They're expecting my answer today.
What do I say?
Since they're probably
planning on killing you
If you say anything else,I'd suggest "yes."
Mike,I save your ass at the warehouse.
The least you could do is have
some decent beer in the fridge.
Next time you plan on saving my ass,
Tell me before I go to the store.
We still have to find out
where they keep their guns.
I think you're gonna have
to do the spy thing,Mike.
Make a new friend.
But I can't get an angle on this father.
I mean,his security drill is airtight.
What about the brothers?
The older brother's the same.
He goes to work. He goes home.
There's no way in.
Younger?
I talked to him in the hangar.
He's not so bright.
I could check him out.
Maybe you should bug his car.
Yeah,maybe I should.
I'll do the recon.
I'll see you guys around.
when you want to turn
someone into an asset,
get him to betray
the people he loves,
you have to get to know him.
This wine is warm.
This is very good wine.
You're supposed
to drink it a little warm.
Well,I like it colder.
Why did you spend $300
on a bottle of warm wine?
Did you speak to
your dad about that trip?
Yes. He said not this year.
How are we supposed to have a life
If he barely lets you do anything?
you need to know
his frustrations.
Who's coming?
you need to know how
he spends his time and money.
Paulie? What? He sucks.
you need to understand
his hopes and dreams.
Cover up a little bit.
Everybody is looking,okay?
Uh-huh.
Okay. Well,call me.
tonight,
we'll go to the club.
we'll have a nice time
and no more talk about work.
okay,and then
we have to be home by 2:00
because you're
a 30-year-old guy with a curfew.
oh,come on.
Don't be like that.
Ouch.
Ari,I don't understand you.
Hey,Mikey.
You read this guy's profile,
you're gonna kiss me.
I am not gonna kiss you,Sam.
Look,I'm not saying
I'm gonna like it.
I'm just saying
you're gonna kiss me.
It is that good.
All right.
Let's make you into an arms dealer.
c-4 has a plastic sheen
and a putty like consistency.
if you need to counterfeit it,
the best thing
I've found is cake icing,
or fondant,as it is known
in the baking trade.
Hey,how's the rest of the cover i.d.?
Pretty good. Got you a fake rolex.
Got a buddy who can rent us
an Aston Martin pretty cheap.
There's your business card.
"steve remington"? That's my name?
Yeah. I got to have some fun,Mike.
Oh,here we go.
Got you a list of Ari's favorite wines,
His position in the family business,
Favorite clubs,even
where he likes to vacation.
Nice work.
Are you done making
the fake plastic explosive?
Can I lick that?
Knock yourself out.
if you need a moldable
explosive that makes a bang,
someone with fiona's skills can
make homemade c-4
with spackle,petroleum jelly,
and a bunch of other things I
don't even want to know about.
How's it coming, fi?
Dangerous.
Unstable.
Remind you of anyone?
Pack it up,
Put a detonator on it,
And make it look pretty.
We have to put
Our best foot forward.
I'll wrap it in a bow.
All right, I got to go
To my mom's place.
Sam.
Mike.
Fi, be good.
Hello, Michael.
Mom. Nate, you find
Dad's will yet?
No, not yet.
I didn't know you were arrested
So many times.
You know that dad kept notes?
Not surprised.
On paper, you're a bigger
Screw-up than me.
You stole more cars
By the time you were 12
Than I did my entire life.
Dad was never around.
You ever wonder how we got
To the store to get groceries
When dad was on a tear?
I'm gonna get
Some more files.
Mom, I need to borrow
Dad's cuff links
And his cigarette case.
Nate is tearing up
This house
Trying to find
Your dad's will.
This is gonna be
One more thing
You two
Are gonna fight about.
I'll give them back
In a few days.
I just need it
For the job, mom.
He's so angry about the car.
Why is it so important?
I think he just wants to know
What it means,
Why dad gave it to me.
Because he loved you.
He wanted you to have something
To remember him by.
Now, why is that
So complicated?
It's not complicated.
It just...
Doesn't sound like dad.
Excuse me.
Do you have the 2003
Fisher vineyards coach insignia
By the glass?
Not by the glass.
By the bottle.
What the hell?
I'll take the whole bottle.
Okay.
It's a good bottle.
For $300, it better be
A very good glass.
You know your wine.
A little.
Thank you.
Try this?
I'd love to.
A glass, please.
What's your name?
Steve Remington.
Steve, Ari Zamar.
Mmm.
I love it.
You want to join me?
I have a table.
Who are you with?
I'm with my girlfriend,
Debbie.
I don't want to impose.
No, no, no. Please.
Beautiful wine.
You can come join us
At the table. Come on.
Another glass, please.
Let's go.
Follow me.
you ever meet someone, and it
Just seems to click instantly?
you like the same things,
Share the same opinions.
it seems like you've known them
All your life.
it could be fate,
or it could be that you have
A listening device
planted in the air-conditioning
Vent of your car.
So there I am,
In the mountains of afghanistan,
And I don't speak a word
Of the dialect.
I got all this training,
I'm sent over there,
And I'm stuck
With a bunch of guys
From the wrong side
Of the country.
I love it.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Ah, it's just my brother.
So, what did you do?
Well, I tried like hell
To learn the language,
And I ate goat for a month.
Oh, I love it.
Afghanistan?
Are you serious?
That's crazy.
Why were you over here?
Business... this and that.
To miami.
Where the beautiful women
Are allowed to go outside.
you'd be surprised
How often covert operatives
pose as international men
Of mystery.
fantasies about glamorous
Covert ops
can be extremely useful
To exploit,
though some secret-agent
Fantasies
are more useful than others.
Now that we know each other,
I have a confession to make.
It's not a coincidence
That we met tonight.
I want to talk to you
About something, about work.
I do import-export...
Furniture, regional food,
Import the cigarettes.
Ari, we're adults here.
The fact is,
The people in my business know
About your family's operations,
And we respect it.
I'm listening.
We also know
That your father does not work
With anyone
Outside of the family.
Still,
Your name gets around.
We also hear about your brother.
He's a hard-ass.
Yeah, he's been
Calling me all night.
He's probably
On his way here now.
That's why I want to talk to you
About an opportunity.
What opportunity?
Why don't you mind
Your own business?
I don't want
To cause problems.
If you're not allowed
To talk about your family's...
No, no, no. I'm allowed
To do whatever I want.
It's just that my father
Is a little, you know...
Jesus.
Your father again?
I don't want to get
In the middle of this.
God, it's my brother.
Ari, where you been?
I called you
Three, four times.
I've been here.
What do you want?
Let's go.
I'm having fun.
Now.
Nice car.
I'm a little tired
Of it, actually.
I want to upgrade
To the new model.
Sorry about earlier.
My, uh, family
Is a little paranoid.
Comes with the territory.
So, tell me about the deal.
I was in town to do a deal
With some plastique...
Good stuff,
Military-grade...
But the contact fell through.
anybody in the arms trade knows
that the mark of a pro
Is the blow and burn.
it's a detonator
On whatever you're selling
in case the deal goes bad.
This is very high grade --
40% cheaper than what
You can get commercially
With all the same kick,
Of course.
I just need a distributor.
You get the buyers,
You could double
Your profits, Ari.
How do I know this is good?
Oh, it's very good stuff.
You want
A little demonstration?
Please.
Are we in business?
So, you gonna go see
Your new girlfriend?
Debbie?
She's not coming, no,
Which is good,
Because I think Ari
Is the jealous type.
Well, I can see
Why she likes you.
You look like
A secret agent.
Listen, Fi,
I just need Ari to show me
Where daddy keeps his guns.
We bring in the cops.
Everyone goes home happy
Except debbie.
Well, maybe you shouldn't
Be so hasty.
Imagine some south beach model
Hanging on your every word.
How many times
She call you?
Five.
Maybe she wants Ari
To do the deal.
She wants to trade up.
Admit it.
* you are tempted
Not for a minute, fi.
If I need a beautiful woman
To mess up my life...
I could do a lot better
Than debbie.
Oh, you know
Your chardonnay.
A little.
Don't be modest.
You should come to my place
In france.
They call it a château,
But really,
It's just a big house.
So about this deal...
I think we should start
With something small.
Okay.
In addition to the c-4,
I can get you...
Military-grade
.50-caliber machine guns.
.50-caliber?
Wow.
And then we can go bigger.
I just need to see
Your operation.
Oh, no, operation...
No, I can't do that.
My father would kill me.
Are you kidding me?
Ari, this is about trust.
I can't just give you a
.50-caliber machine gun to sell
Without knowing
What warehouse it's going to,
What transport
It's getting on.
I can't.
It's impossible.
You know what?
Forget it.
I'm going out on a limb here,
And you don't trust me.
No, I get that.
I understand, and that's fine.
It's just not
How I do business.
So thank you for your time.
I'll get the check.
Ah, sit, sit,
Sit, sit, sit.
I like you.
Okay,
Meet me tomorrow night.
We'll see.
Okay?
Are you happy?
Very happy.
I can do the deal
And then talk to Ilan and dad.
you can make
A lot of money.
Okay, sounds like
He's gonna go for it.
Just goes to show you...
A car is a bad place
To have a conversation.
Mike, you know
I was gonna tell you.
What's that, Sam?
Don't treat me like I'm stupid.
The bug in your car.
I thought
We had a deal, Sam.
Mike, we do.
I help you out.
I tell you what I know.
But they know
You got something.
They wanted me to bust
Into your place and search it.
I told them
I wouldn't do it,
So they made me plant a bug
And said if I told you,
They'd be all over us.
At least I tried
To make it obvious.
I mean, I practically signed
My name on the goddamn thing.
Oh, that you did, Sam.
Mikey, I'm with you,
But this FBI crap...
I'm grinding my teeth
At night.
It's bad
For my blood pressure.
So break into my place.
Yeah?
Search it.
These FBI guys
Don't know anything.
It might get the attention
Of someone useful.
I got to go.
Jake's meeting
With the zamars tonight,
So you should have
A couple of hours.
I would search
In the kitchen area.
Cabinets?
Sink.
Behind?
Under.
Don't break anything.
All right, then.
So, tomorrow,
You'll do this, huh?
You'll talk
To the customs people, yes?
Yeah.
Is there a problem?
N-no, there's no problem.
You need
Some motivation, huh?
Huh? Huh?
Ow!
Hey!
I'm sick and tired
Of waiting.
I have to be somewhere,
And this...
Get up.
Get up!
It's me.
You never answer my calls.
Where's Ari?
He's coming.
He's getting bitched out
By his dad or something.
I wanted to talk
To you alone.
How long are you in town?
Aren't you and Ari engaged?
Whatever.
Come on.
Can you have a little fun?
You've been
Around the world,
But you never talk
About a girlfriend.
I want to see...
Your gun.
Okay, that's not my gun.
Not my gun.
Debbie.
Get out of here.
Now I know your secret,
You son of a bitch.
Get in there!
Ari, calm down.
I don't know
What you think you know.
You lied to me!
dealing with a blown cover
Is about stalling for time.
stay alive long enough
To figure out what they know
and tell a bigger lie
To save yourself.
You lied to me
Since day one!
What is this secret
You're talking about?
You wanted debbie, huh?
You wanted debbie
From the beginning.
Debbie?
That's what you thought?
You were watching me
The whole time, weren't you?
You sent her over
To test me.
You wanted to see
How I handled the pressure.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, you are good.
So, what... did I pass?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, your father
Trained you well, Ari.
Yeah.
So, I see the operation?
Yeah, okay.
riding in a car
With a blindfold on
takes some getting used to.
the good news is,
If the driver's busy
making sure
You can't see anything,
he's not paying attention
To whether he's being followed.
I'll take you to the warehouse,
But if you screw me...
Why would I want to
Screw you?
I've got merchandise to sell.
You've got buyers.
It's that simple.
I just want to know
What I'm getting into.
Okay.
Security is airtight.
The warehouse
Is not connected to us.
We keep the weapons there
Till we ship.
If the cops come,
They can't arrest anybody.
A dead drop.
So what if someone tries
To steal your merchandise?
Nobody knows where it is --
Just the family.
Out.
There.
Now you see the operation.
Not bad...
On the warehouse front.
What about security?
We have no problems
With cops.
We have cops
On the payroll.
They let us know
If there's a problem.
Great.
M1a .308.
Nicely balanced.
Special forces.
Airport security?
We have a guy.
Reliable?
Yeah.
If not, we, uh --
How do they say? --
We liquidate him.
Fn p90 with halo sight.
State of the art... Very nice.
Looks like you have things
Wired here.
So, are we gonna do
Some business?
After we send out the shipment,
We'll make a deal.
You and I...
We put it together,
And then I take the deal
To my father.
Trust me.
You're doing him a favor.
Shall we?
You want me
To talk to them again?
They'll kill me.
You see what they did.
I thought the plan was to find
The guns and call the cops.
That plan
Won't work anymore.
They've got cops
On the payroll, jake.
If you want to get out of this,
It's your best chance.
For your family.
What do I do?
I think it's about time
The zamar family learned
About Ari's new friend.
any good operative is going to
Be a bit of a control freak.
above all,
They don't want to hear
that the people
They think they own
really belong to someone
Who can destroy them.
Look, I said
I would help you.
I got to help
Your friends now?
I can't do this...
What are you talking about?
What friend?
Steve something.
He said he worked with Ari.
He checked out the logs,
Had me show him the airport.
He said
I belong to him now.
What the hell
Is that supposed to mean --
I belong to him?
He had
My social security number,
My passport information.
He had all kinds of stuff
About you guys, too... pictures.
What are you
Talking about?
I don't know
What's happening to me.
I want my life back.
Give me my life back.
Shut up!
Hey.
Who is this person?
Who is he?
I don't know.
Okay, that's what I'm saying.
He said
He was friends with Ari.
I don't know anything.
Get out.
Get out!
Ari, what did you do?
I've told you
Never to talk to anyone!
No, no.
This is my deal.
I did this on my own.
A deal?
Who asked you to do this deal?
Who is this friend, huh?
What... what... he has documents
About us, pictures.
Met him at a club.
He came to me.
What does he know?
Did you tell him anything?
Did you
Show him anything?!
I showed him
The warehouse.
We took a little tour.
But... but it's okay.
He was blindfolded.
He just wanted to see
The operation and --
Ilan,
Go to the warehouse now.
Come, you fool!
Was that okay?
Fiona: perfect.
Michael trained you well.
They're on their way,
Michael.
I am telling you,
He was the real deal, okay?
He had the trunk
Full of c-4 --
Stop!
Someone's there.
It's all gone...
...everything.
there's nothing worse
for anyone who spent time
In intelligence work
than being up against a ghost.
you can deal
With an enemy you know,
but an enemy you don't know?
he could be a competitor
who knows all about
Your operation...
...could be law enforcement
Getting ready to bust you...
could be a foreign agent
setting you up
In some deep spy game.
your only option
Is to disappear.
Steve remington --
He said he was special forces.
Try again. He could be
Using a different name.
Enough, Ari!
Let's go.
As long as they think
Steve remington owns you,
You're safe.
As far as they know,
There's a mystery man out there
Who can destroy them,
And you're his property.
Thank you.
Yeah. I'm not here
Fishing for thanks.
You need to understand
The situation.
Eli will have his ear
To the ground forever.
If word gets out he got conned,
You're dead.
You guys look so serious.
Come on.
It's not that hard, man.
I mean, secrets are what keep
A family strong, right?
Something like that.
I'm just glad
That you guys are finally happy.
I got to tell you, though,
When I busted into Mike's place,
I didn't know
If I was gonna find anything,
And then I find
This document here
In a hidey-hole
Under the sink.
I don't know. Maybe he's as bad
As you guys say.
We sent this
Up the ladder, Sam.
This document's classified.
Westen shouldn't have
Had this.
They're looking for leaks.
Well, that's nice.
But the point here, Fellas, is,
I brought home the bacon.
You got prime goods
On my buddy Mike right there.
We're off the case, Sam.
This thing's serious enough
Washington's sending
Someone else down.
Westen's
Someone else's problem now.
Yeah?
New surveillance?
What... what department?
Don't know.
Don't care.
Enjoy your lunch, Sam.
See you around.
Yeah.
Huh.
Thanks, Fellas.
I'm gonna miss you guys,
You know?
Mike.
Hey, Sam.
Yeah, good news
And bad news.
Good news is,
Your FBI tail got pulled.
Bad news is, they're sending
Someone new down.
Sounds heavy.
Thanks, Sam.
Who's the new surveillance?
Hell if I know.
Oh, uh, there's more good news.
They were so eager
To get rid of you,
They dropped three $20s
On a 10-buck tab.
Lucky you.
All right,
Check you later.
Hi there.
My frien
Just abandoned me.
Any chance I could get you
To keep me company?
Maybe.
I'm Sam.
Hi.
I'm Veronica.
What are we drinking?
I knew it wasn't gonna be
In there.
Well, she said
It was in here.
Of course she --
Well, it's not.
So, will you
Stop arguing now?
Ma, it doesn't mention the car
In the will.
I know.
You know?
I wanted Michael to know
That his father remembered him
In the end,
And, Nate,
You spent more time with him.
You lied.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
You know what, Nate?
Fine.
I'll flip you for it.
All right.
Heads.
Yeah.
Of course.
You know what?
You won it fair and square, bro.
Now, you see, Michael,
You're too hard on him.
I mean,
He can be so sweet.
I just want us
To be family.
I know, mom.
I know.
He just stole my wallet.
Nate!
Http://www.ragbear.com