My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice on you.
You're blacklisted.
When you're burned,
you've got nothing.
No cash, no credit, no job history.
You're stuck in whatever city
they decide to dump you in.
- Where am I?
- Miami.
You do whatever work comes your way.
You rely on anyone
who's still talking to you.
- A trigger-happy ex-girlfriend.
- Should we shoot them?
An old friend who used
to inform on you to the FBI.
You know spies...
A bunch of bitchy little girls.
- Family, too...
- Hey, is that your mom again?
- If you're desperate.
- Someone needs your help.
Bottom line...
Until you figure out who burned you,
you're not going anywhere.
As a spy, you have a lot of ways
to get information.
You can get it with a gun, a lockpick.
You can get it with a listening device.
But most often,
more than all the other
information-gathering
techniques combined,
you get information
with a free lunch.
How come you never invite me to lunch
at places like this?
There's no need, Sam.
You'll do almost anything for a $3 beer.
Yeah, sure.
Barry tracks down a Cayman Island
bank-account number,
and he gets lunch at the Chadwick?
That number leads to whoever
was trying to kill me,
so, yes, the Chadwick.
He's been complaining
about the job for days.
Yeah, and the squeaky wheel gets
the surf and turf. I see how this works.
Well, at least I can get
a good mojito here.
- We're on a budget, Sam.
- Okay, Mike, you know,
this cancels out one of the times
you saved my life, maybe two.
So, Michael...
How did you get
this mysterious bank-account number?
You probably don't want to know.
I do.
We don't have a lot of information.
That's why I'm coming to you.
I just need a name.
Yeah, no...
I understand why you hired me,
Michael Westen.
But you're having me break a lot of laws
with this job I'm doing for you.
When someone starts acting like
there's an extra person
in the conversation,
it's a pretty good bet
that they're wearing a wire.
This job you're doing for me?
The question, then,
is who's taping you...
The police, the Feds...
I think we should talk later,
maybe some place louder.
Michael, Michael, I missed you.
Or a government agent
you blackmailed a while back
and were hoping to never see again?
Sam Axe, you're living well
off a government pension, I see.
- Not that good. This is iced tea.
- Remember the file I have on you, Bly?
I think the idea was, you were never
to set foot in Miami again.
I know, I know,
but the sunshine, the beaches,
those little Cuban pastries...
Come on.
I just couldn't let a blackmail threat
keep me out of...
Paradise. Hi.
Actually, at this point,
blackmail ceases to be a threat.
At this point, I believe
I ruin your life.
How about I give your boss a call?
I'll be honest, Michael.
That file?
It kept me up nights,
so imagine my joy
when your friend showed up on my radar
investigating some highly suspicious
accounts for my old pal Michael Westen.
Barry is the brick
that I will tie around your neck
before I throw you into
that beautiful blue ocean over there.
Now, how deep you sink depends on
how quickly I get that blackmail file.
Welcome to Miami.
Season 2, Episode 13:
Bad Breaks.
Synchro VO: S@lomon
www.subbers-in-black.com
So, pull the trigger.
There's enough in that file
to reduce Bly's career
to a smoldering crater.
He can link me to Barry,
and Barry's broken a law library's
worth of financial regulations
looking into this account number.
If Bly goes after me with that,
I can throw the rest of my life
into that crater, too.
Government agents
have to stay within the law,
but they still have plenty of options
to hit you below the belt.
Sometimes, a bullet to the head
is a lot easier than a slow death
drowning in red tape.
- Sorry. For your own safety.
- Don't touch me, for your own safety.
According to the board of health,
this loft is unfit for human habitation.
And here I thought
it was just a dump.
Fiona Glenanne, you're wearing
more clothes than usual.
You know, I was on the fence
about that chair.
Thanks for making up my mind for me.
I hope you're on the fence
about everything that you own,
because toxic mold
could be anywhere.
There's been reports of spores spreading
to places you wouldn't believe.
Nope. No mold in that one.
Try the lamp.
I was always iffy on it.
You know what?
Thanks for watching out for me, Bly.
I'm gonna grab some clothes.
Call me when you're done.
Michael, don't worry.
I packed you a bag...
with some clothes to wear.
I have to say, for a tough guy,
you sure dress like an easter egg.
I hope you're not bringing
toxic mold into my house.
Ma, there's no mold.
I'm glad you're out of there.
The place didn't sound healthy.
My friend Paula is here.
She heard you were coming,
and she wanted to talk.
You advised her last week
about the guy she met on the internet.
Michael.
I am so sorry to bother you again.
This guy, Prescott...
I did what you said,
ignored his e-mails.
Then he called my house.
I think he's a stalker.
He's asking all these
personal questions. It's...
like he's obsessed with me.
Would it make you feel better
if I talked to him?
Really?
You could do that?
- Sure. Let me put my bag away.
- All right.
I'll put it in the guest room.
Michael will take care
of everything.
He lives at the Del Mar apartments.
I have his online dating profile.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
No Prescott in this building.
How about yours?
Not unless he's disguised
as an 80-year-old retiree.
I mean, this little manhunt
could take a while, Mike.
Whatever. Better this than sitting
in my mom's kitchen watching her smoke.
Likes fixing up old cars.
He's a mechanic, maybe?
I mean, I can check
his ASE certifications,
but, of course, that's if anything
on this page is true.
Check out the IP address
on his dating-service account,
- see what we're dealing with.
- Speaking of love, I got to get going.
I have a very big date.
She made millions as a beer distributor.
- The woman of my dreams.
- You have many women in your dreams.
So, I'm a romantic,
but this one, Mike...
I mean, she's got a beach house
in Antigua with a quad kegerator.
That's four kegs of beer
at 33 degrees, baby.
Sounds like love.
Hello.
Michael, it's Paula.
Prescott's outside my work.
I'll be right there.
I saw his car drive
past three times.
He walked by, looking in.
I'm the assistant manager.
I can't have him in here making a scene.
This is a private bank.
We're an appointment-only
private bank and safe-deposit company.
Very exclusive, very private.
You can understand
why I can't have him...
Has Prescott been asking you
about your work,
your schedule?
All of it.
I'm just afraid
he's some kind of maniac.
- Who's that?
- Just an old friend.
Did you get bored
redecorating my place?
I'll redecorate your life
if I have to.
- You find that file?
- Not yet. Let's talk later.
Actually, later is bad for me.
Now is good.
I want every piece of paper you own
that mentions me.
Files, phone records,
the page in your diary where you drew
little hearts around my name.
All of it.
You wanna do this, Bly?
You really wanna go nuclear?
I'd love to.
You really think
you have nothing to lose?
He's here.
The stalker.
He's not a stalker.
This is a robbery.
Stay quiet,
follow our orders,
or people die.
You'll find your cellphones
are now useless.
We've blocked them,
so leave them on the floor
and head into the conference room.
Now!
Go! Go! Go!
Conference room!
There are a number of different choices
when you take over a building by force.
Up! Move into the conference room.
Do you keep the hostages
facedown on the floor,
or do you move them
into a room together?
Let me see your hands.
Move. Move.
How do you cut all the lines
of communication out?
Give me that cellphone!
Get in that conference room.
And how do you deal
with the place's security method?
Whatever your style,
hostile takeovers are about one thing...
- Total dominance.
- Silent alarm is dead.
Now get into the conference room
or you will be, too.
We got the bank manager.
If we both grab guns,
we can level the playing field.
The playing field
is covered with hostages.
Make a move now,
and somebody could get shot.
If we don't make a move,
we may not get a chance.
Just wait, all right?
Shut up. Move back with the others.
It's all right. Just stay calm.
Stay calm. It's gonna be all r...
Bly.
That's quite enough of that.
Welcome to my retirement party.
I want you all
to have a good time, so...
let's down a few ground rules,
shall we?
No attacking the hosts.
No leaving early.
No calling the police.
I see one cop, I kill three of you.
I see two cops, six people die.
You can do the math.
Now, mess up my party
by breaking one of my rules, and...
You can expect me to overreact.
A wounded hostage is a good measure
of how far a criminal's willing to go.
They either want to keep
the hostage alive...
Get away from him.
I'm a doctor.
If I don't stop the bleeding, he'll die.
Then let him die.
Or they don't, which means
more people are getting hurt.
You have 20 hostages
in an unstable psychological state.
If they think they're going to die,
they will panic,
and they will fight back.
I'm just trying to make sure
that you get what you want
and these people stay alive.
Will you please allow me
to attend to this man's wound?
- Knock yourself out.
- Thank you.
Let's go take a tour of the vault.
Come on.
You son of a bitch.
I only need one person alive
to get me the vault-access cards.
Please don't make me choose.
Told you someone would get shot.
Yeah, I overestimated you.
I figured you'd back me up.
You know, it's not a good idea
to insult your doctor.
Okay, this wound doesn't look good.
I'm going to need to...
- Remove the round?
- Yeah.
- Go ahead.
- Come here.
I need you to apply direct,
steady pressure to this.
Hold this up. Hold it up.
There you go.
In a hostage situation, any idiot
can steal a gun and start shooting.
It's a great way to get
a bunch of innocent people killed.
Keeping people alive
means fighting like a spy.
Where is your data server?
It's by the elevator, but they cut
the power to the computers, so...
I'm using it for something else.
We need to cut through there
and get into the next room.
From there, we can get out.
There's no way out.
That's just an office.
There'll be a way out.
I'm working on that part.
You don't think the guards outside
will see us going through a wall?
- I'll take care of the guards.
- Yeah. No. Wait. You heard him.
If you attack his guys,
he's gonna start shooting people.
I'm not going to attack them.
They're just gonna have
some very bad luck.
Where are you going?
- I need medical supplies.
- Wait. Wait. Stop right there.
- No one leaves the conference room.
- Your boss said stop the bleeding.
- He didn't say you could leave.
- You wanna go downstairs and ask him?
The man in there is going to die
unless I remove the bullet from his arm.
To do that, I need tools, so...
help me find tweezers and propoxyphene
or shoot me in the face. Your call.
- You've got two minutes.
- We got less than that.
Fighting like a spy means
disguising attacks as attempts to help.
It means making acts of man
seem like acts of god.
- We have to go through here?
- That's the plan.
Does anybody have a razor
or a letter opener?
Here. I grabbed these.
Good. Here.
We're gonna trust your friend?
He is not my friend, but he might
be able to get us out of here.
- Sir, watch the door.
- Start cutting at the outlet.
Cutting through a wall with scissors
isn't as hard as it sounds.
Start at an electrical socket
and saw through the hard surface
of the drywall,
and the lower layers
are a lot easier.
Gauze,
aspirin.
This kit is terrible.
We're gonna need to search desks
and purses for some real pain meds.
You can do it with that.
With gauze?
Right.
Where'd you get your medical degree?
Wait for the water.
I'll look through these desks and
meet you back at the conference room.
What?
You got armed guards
at the only exit.
You think I'm gonna fight my way out
with a stapler?
Water's ready.
And look around for some towels.
In an enclosed space,
getting around a cellphone jammer is
a game of who's got the stronger signal.
A cellphone jammer broadcasts
a powerful signal
over a range of frequencies,
but it can't compete
with an entire ethernet
wired to serve as one big antenna.
So, I said no more stress,
no more work,
and no more getting married.
Life is too short.
How many beach houses
do I even need?
- How many do you have?
- Six.
Seven? It doesn't matter.
I'm always on vacation.
To me, true relaxation
is a state of mind.
- Do you have to get that?
- No. No.
You know, I like to relax, too.
You would love my place in Antigua.
Hammock on the white sand beach.
Clothes are optional.
Excuse me.
This better be good, Mikey.
I'm at Broward Private Trust
trapped in a bank heist.
It's Prescott. He's a pro.
His guys have killed the landlines
and brought a cell jammer.
Any cops, any resistance,
and it gets bloody.
- Just tell me what you need, Mike.
- I need you and Fi
to blast a door to the outside.
Alleyside wall,
20 feet in from the north.
Alleyside wall, 20 feet in.
You got it. I'm on my way.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Well, not really, no.
My buddy's being held hostage at a bank,
and I got to bust him out.
- It's true.
- We should call the police.
No. No. No. You can't do that.
It's complicated,
but there's nothing to worry about,
and I'll call you later.
- These are for the doc.
- Where is he?
Go find him.
The massive air pressure
that makes air hammers effective
also makes them dangerous.
Tamper in any way
with the locking collar
that holds the bit in place,
and the air hammer
becomes a very inaccurate gun
with a single bullet.
Not here.
Keep looking.
Mixing medications
is always a bad idea,
especially when one's an upper
and one's a downer.
Anxiety and allergy meds together
are a scary combination,
and that's before you add the caffeine
of an energy drink.
There you are.
What took you so long?
I was just...
This is for the pain.
- Who said I was in pain?
- If you're not now, you will be.
By the way, that green chair in my loft,
it was my favorite.
Let's go, Fi.
You're just annoyed 'cause
Mike called me first and not you.
He's in the middle of a bank heist.
- He's not thinking clearly.
- I'm the one who should be annoyed.
I was having lunch with the woman
of my dreams and had to leave.
What are you gonna do?
You know, being Mike's first call
is a big responsibility.
In case you're wondering,
you'd be my 19th call.
I'd call Madeline
before I called you.
Experience with battlefield medicine
may not make you as precise
as an ER surgeon...
Oh, come on.
But after you've stitched up
a few people under artillery fire,
you can handle outside pressure.
Almost.
Got it.
Oh, god.
We're making some progress on the wall,
but they're checking on us.
- We need maybe 20 minutes.
- You've got to go faster.
Keep working.
They're emptying
the vault downstairs.
- They're taking everything.
- How long before they clear it all out?
I don't know. There's hundreds
of safe-deposit boxes down there.
And he wasn't lying
about the silent alarm.
No call went out.
- No help is coming.
- Hide the hole.
Prescott wants you downstairs.
Let's go.
Thanks.
Michael said 20 feet in
from the street?
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
Well, what's the signal?
How are we timing this?
He didn't say.
- He didn't say?
- He's Mike. He's improvising.
Michael called you to tell you
to blow a hole in the wall of a bank,
- and you didn't think to ask when?
- Look, it was a brief conversation.
We didn't talk about shoes
or movies either.
Could you just place
the explosives already?
- Fix him.
- What happened?
The air hammer broke,
and the piston came off in his leg.
Keep him alive.
I'm gonna give you
something for the pain.
People are too trusting
when it comes to pills.
They'll take whatever
a doctor hands them.
I need to cauterize the wound.
I need to use your liquid-nitrogen gun.
You need to use something else.
Like what? Did you bring
an electrosurgical generator?
Liquid nitrogen can cool
a wound to 150 below,
freezing the cells
and cutting off blood flow.
Tie this around his leg, tight.
Either help me
or get me someone who will.
Up here?
Supercooling also damages metal.
Freeze the inside of a gun,
and the next time it gets hot,
it'll rip apart as if it's loaded
with the wrong ammo.
Prescott, get up here.
We've got trouble
in the conference room.
- Where's the knife?
- There's no knife. There isn't a knife.
This guy was trying to cut
into the office next door.
Come here.
What did I tell you
about the rules, huh?
Please, I...
I have a wife. I have kids.
They need their father.
I'm begging you.
Look, if I make an exception, I mean,
what kind of message does it send?
Wait. Wait.
You got the wrong guy.
It was me.
Just can't stop causing trouble,
can you, huh?
Should've done this the first time.
God!
Shoot him!
Move!
You got shards in your hand.
You're gushing arterial blood.
I'm the only guy here who can save
your hand, probably your life.
Tell your man to back off
or find another doctor.
Come with me.
Get the rest of them downstairs.
Four more. Let's go.
We're running about 20 minutes late.
Should I call the boat?
Get downstairs.
- I still need to...
- Get downstairs.
How's your plan going?
We're not getting out.
I'm working on plan B.
- I need your help. Do you trust me?
- Yeah, what do you need?
I need you to collapse in that doorway.
Sell it. Buy me time.
- What's going on?
- I think he's going into shock.
I can't move him.
I'll need a couple of minutes.
You got one.
Mike, let's get this done.
I got a beer-drinking angel
to get back to.
- You ready to rock?
- Forget the escape plan.
Prescott's moving
everybody downstairs.
These guys are calling
a getaway boat on walkies.
If you can listen in, locate the signal.
Maybe we can get some leverage.
I'll try to keep people
from getting hurt in here.
Come on. Downstairs.
Let's go. Now.
- All right.
- Elevators have so many safety devices
that they're easy to sabotage.
Disable any part,
and the entire system shuts down.
Hurry up. Move it!
Locate the getaway boat.
That's our plan.
This is Miami.
Look, we just need to find the frequency
that Prescott's walkies are on.
I think we should
set off the charges,
blow a hole in the wall, rush in.
- Beats waiting out here.
- Yeah, that's great.
Let's get Mike
and the hostages killed
because you have
the attention span of a 3-year-old.
Elevator's busted.
You're lucky.
I don't see any shrapnel,
and no bones look damaged.
Use the word lucky again,
I'm gonna put a bullet in your head.
Hold still.
I need to sterilize the wound.
This bank!
It's cursed.
That's it, isn't it?
My gun,
the air hammer, the elevator.
- What's wrong with this place?
- I'm gonna need more tape
and a splint.
I think there's something
I can use upstairs.
Do you need any meds?
What do you think, huh?
Let me blow your hand off and find out
if you need something for the pain.
Angela, hey, it's Sam.
How you doing?
Is your friend okay?
Well, he's still trapped inside,
but it's kind of a quiet time,
so I thought I would just call
and say hi. So...
Hi.
Hi?
I was thinking later,
we could get some drinks.
I know this quiet spot
that makes great a mojito.
Well, I was meeting a friend, but...
Playtime's over.
Angela, I got to run. Hey, don't make
any plans. I'll call you back.
Sounds encrypted.
So I was wasting my time
while you were buttering up your bimbo?
Look, we got the frequency.
There can't be that many marinas
around here in range of their walkies.
Okay, that's not good.
Those cops start asking questions
about that truck out front,
hostages are gonna die.
One of us needs to distract the cop,
and the other one needs
to track down the getaway boat.
And here I forgot to shave my legs.
Delivery trucks.
- Hey, stop! Give me that!
- No!
She is stealing my tip jar!
This is compensation
for you leering at me.
You should arrest her.
Es una ladrona!
- Arrest him for sexual harassment.
- We're not arresting anyone.
You're gonna stand there
while I'm objectified?
I say we go to the station,
hash this out... You, me... him.
- What do you say?
- Unit 204, dispatch.
Got a domestic disturbance
at Ocean and 4th. You close?
10-4. I'm on my way.
If you'd like to file a report,
you should go down
to the police station, okay?
Una cortadito, por favor.
We win yet?
I'm working on it.
I need some meds.
- Things okay?
- Yeah, hey, it's Miami.
The sun, the girls...
What's not to love?
If something bad starts happening,
make your move.
These should do the trick.
Life with a hypochondriac mother
gives you a useful knowledge
of pharmaceuticals.
Those are for pain?
In low doses,
pilocarpine cures dry mouth.
I'll take them after you do.
In high doses,
it has roughly the same effect
as a sarin gas attack.
Satisfied?
See what happens to you first.
- Still want that splint for your hand?
- Sure.
We're going upstairs.
You, keep an eye on the hostages.
Back in a minute.
What's it mean
if my fingers are feeling numb
and I'm getting sort of nauseous?
Do you have a headache,
any palpitations,
any tingling,
been drinking caffeine?
Yeah. Why?
Is that bad?
Sounds pretty serious.
I should check you out.
I'm just gonna take your pulse.
I'm just taking your pulse.
That's it. I'm just taking it.
In a weakened state, you want to avoid
pressure on your carotid artery.
Block the blood flow to your brain,
and you black out in four seconds.
The coating on tablets and medicine
keeps them from dissolving
in your stomach right away,
which buys you a little time
to find some privacy
and do the only safe thing.
Get them out of your system.
Hey, buddy.
I'm supposed to repair a radio
in a guy's boat,
but I'm late,
and I forgot the slip number.
Is there somebody hanging around
looking pissed?
End of the pier.
Thanks.
You have a good one.
Prescott.
- Vault's cleared out.
- It's about time.
Let's put everyone in the vault
and get the hell out of here.
Everyone in the vault now.
They've seen our face. They die.
Let's go.
Everybody into the vault.
There isn't much air in the vault.
We're all gonna suffocate.
- Should we attack them?
- No, not yet.
- I don't know how long we can wait.
- Just trust me.
Hey, Mike, I'm at the marina
looking at the getaway boat.
We got any moves here?
Prescott's shoving
everyone into the fault,
and no one's walking out.
You want to ask Prescott if he'll trade
his hostages for the boat driver?
Not likely.
- What about an operation Quicksilver?
- Quicksilver. You mean like WW II?
You're talking about a bunch of tanks
and the whole Normandy invasion force.
Yeah, but instead
of the Normandy invasion force,
I have a Walther with one bullet.
You got to sell this, Sam.
You got to sell it
like you've never sold it before.
That's the kind of pep talk I like.
I'm on it.
Angela, hi.
Hi. I was calling
to leave a message.
I think your life is...
is a little too...
fast-paced for me.
No, no, no.
That's not true at all.
Why are you whispering?
Are you still outside the bank?
No, I'm at a marina.
Just taking a stress-free walk
along the ocean,
the breeze blowing in my hair.
I might even get a tropical drink.
Hands in the air.
A stress-free walk.
Well, as much as I hate to admit it,
Angela, you're probably right.
We're just not meant to be.
Enjoy one of those beers
in Antigua for me.
You bastard.
You ruined something special.
If you have one bullet
and you need to take down
three armed guys in close quarters,
you're betting your life
on a lot of lucky breaks.
It's the kind of bet
you don't want to make
unless you have to.
There you are.
Your guy had a stroke
in the kitchen.
He needs immediate
medical attention.
You want me to put him in the vault
or just take care of him right here?
You're not listening to me.
Either you get your friend
into an ambulance with the proper meds,
- or he's not gonna make it.
- Well, I guess he's not gonna make it,
and neither are you.
Prescott.
- What's going on?
- Prescott,
they're at the boat.
They shot me.
Why didn't you tell us?
- Why didn't I tell you what?
- Who we were robbing.
Why didn't you tell us
who owned the bank?
Oh, my god.
You didn't know, did you?
We're dead.
Oh, my god.
They're coming back.
We're all dead!
Tom Prescott?
Was it dumb luck
that you chose my bank,
or did you and your buddies decide
that today was a good day
to make the worst mistake
of your lives?
- Who is this?
- That's not important.
What's important is that you
and your friends are robbing my bank,
and no one, I mean no one,
does that to me.
You think you got yourself a good plan
with your getaway truck and your boat?
Well, I got a plan, too.
If there is a scratch
on anyone in my bank,
you will all die.
If there is a single dollar
missing from my vault,
you all die.
You hearing this?
If there is a single hostage taken,
you will all die.
In fact, if you do anything
other than walking
out of my bank alone right now,
you will all know such pain
as you have never imagined.
So, who the hell is that guy?
He owns this bank?
He's lying.
I looked up everything about this bank.
Well, you obviously
didn't look up enough.
What did you get us into?
How does he even know we're here?
Shut up.
It's not important!
One evening, a patient was brought into
my clinic in the middle of the night.
He was tortured so badly I couldn't
believe he was still breathing.
A man was with him.
It was the man on your radio.
I'll never forget the voice.
He put a gun to my head and explained
that my patient had robbed him
and that he wanted me to save him
so the pain would last longer.
I did what I could.
He said to come here for my money,
my blood money.
There's a place
between life and death.
Amazing how long a man
can linger there.
That's enough, all right?
Bring everything upstairs.
We're getting out of here.
Tony?
Tony, can you hear me?
What the hell is going on?
I know this guy.
He'll have people outside the bank,
in your truck, and on your boat.
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
Shut your mouth.
We've got the money.
That's just some voice on the radio.
Yeah, but he's a voice on our radio.
He's on our boat!
How does that happen?
I mean, what happened
to the guys in the vault, huh?
- He's talking about our truck!
- There's nothing wrong with our truck!
Let's just get outta here.
Nothing's wrong with the truck?
Does that look like nothing?
Pick up the bag.
No way. I am gonna...
Unbelievable.
Just not your day, I guess.
Drop it! Drop it!
Hands on your head!
So, where were we?
I think we were deciding whether
we were going to destroy each other.
Well, you've already had
enough opportunities to let me die.
Maybe I just like the challenge.
I'm gonna go pass out at the local ER,
and when I wake up,
I'll take care of the loft
and the thing with Barry.
As long as you're in a helpful mood,
you think I could add
one more favor to the list?
And then they moved us
into the vault.
We knew there wasn't much time.
I mean, I really thought
it was the end,
but your son and Mr. Bly
were so brave, Madeline.
- Michael, what are you doing?
- I left something in here.
You just assumed
I was never gonna broil anything?
Well, so far I've been right.
Prescott will be leaving you alone
from now on.
You might want to select your dates
a little more carefully in the future.
I will.
Thank you so much.
- Bye, honey.
- Bye.
I'm off, too.
What? You... you're going?
You didn't even spend the night.
I resolved my toxic-mold issue.
Board of health says
my place is safe again.
I was thinking of ordering takeout,
but if you're going...
Actually, I don't have
to leave right away.
Takeout sounds good.
Bly says you're off the hook.
He was just using you
to get under my skin anyway.
Listen, Michael, I feel really bad about
the whole tacky business with the wire.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I love how I look with a shaved chest,
- but rolling over on you...
- I ask you to take risks.
It comes with the territory.
But next time, we'll have a signal.
If you're wired, tip me off
by offering to pay for lunch.
Perfect.
You know, I think I'm gonna get out
of town for a bit. I got to decompress.
- Sounds good. Stay safe.
- All right, man.
I had to take the guy
on the boat down,
get him to say the right things
at the right time.
While you were putting on a show,
I got rid of the cops,
and I wired a truck to blow.
Mike, back me up.
I think it's pretty clear
my tactical maneuverings
pretty much saved the day here.
- You feeling underappreciated?
- Oh, no. He appreciates himself plenty.
He's been insufferable ever since
you called him first yesterday.
Fi, look, don't be insulted.
You're good with the hands-on stuff.
- The simple mechanical things.
- Simple?
Like wiring a truck to blow?
An important task, yes,
but one a very intelligent monkey
could perform.
I'm just saying there's a reason why
I'm number one on the speed dial.
Sam, for your information,
I called Fi first.
You didn't pick up,
so in the future,
I'm gonna call Sam first.
It's all the originals,
everything I had on you.
I love your attention
to detail, Michael.
This would have been quite
the career-ender.
Well, I know
a little something about that...
Although I wasn't expecting you
to counter with even better leverage.
Well-played.
This would be a good
Michael Westen story
if people were allowed
to tell Michael Westen stories.
- So.
- So...
Any luck trucking down
that Cayman Islands account?
I don't have to tell you,
we have ways of investigating
that most people don't know about.
No one has the reach that we do,
but this...
I found the bank
and I even found the banker,
but the account...
It's just a number.
- No name? No organization?
- Nothing.
It gets worse.
That account was being monitored.
An electronic trip wire of sorts.
And you think you tripped it?
Might have been me.
It might have been Barry.
Look, whoever you're looking for,
they know you're coming.
Good luck.