Previously on Dexter...
I just got the sheriff's department.
They've confirmed their skinning victim
is related to ours.
That gives us 3 victims.
I've got units bringing in
a 15-year-old kid, Wendell Owens.
He was Freebo's doorman.
If things get really bad,
you use that card and call me, okay?
You think I cut this kid loose
to make you look bad?
I'm not sure anymore...
Partner.
You know a Joey Quinn?
Cooperation with I.A.
has its upside.
Yuki, that's not gonna happen.
Ramon's obsessed.
He's not going
to stop looking for Oscar's killer
until it takes him all the way down.
- Is there a problem here?
- Yeah, sergeant.
Your people don't know
what the fuck they're doing.
That guy is wound way too tight.
Where ya been, Dexter?
How are you, Camilla?
I've been better.
Are you, looking for
anything special tonight?
Might be more than an hour.
Take a pass...
Sergeant.
Anton, open up. It's me.
The Chicky Hines conviction.
My people have come across evidence
that could get the case reopened.
Prado know you're
coming to me with this?
Don't you see what happened today?
I gave you the chance
to avenge two women
whom the system failed,
and just like I hoped,
you seized that opportunity.
I see who you are. I am with you.
Behind you.
I respect you.
He's tired. Keep on reeling.
You got him.
Here he comes!
Come here!
Oh, shit!
Go ahead.
That's gonna be
some mighty fine eating.
Man, on the grill
with Syl's mango and lime salsa.
Our house tomorrow night.
Check with the little woman...
Who's getting bigger as we speak.
I could get used to the simple
joys of male bonding.
Hey, how 'bout a... Brewski?
Ah, that looks good.
So Dex...
What was it like?
In Bimini.
- Flat, mostly. Lots of mangroves.
- Talking about Ethan Turner.
- What about him?
- What did it feel like to...
Take him out?
To end his life.
So much for the simple joys
of male bonding.
Like I could explain
or Miguel could understand.
You put people on death row.
You must know what it's like.
No, but there's like
an ocean of bureaucracy
of briefs and appeals between me
and that bad guy taking his last breath.
I'm asking you what did it feel like
to use your hands, to...
To make this a better place?
It felt...
right.
Felt like justice.
I've got five floors of prosecutors
and the whole police department at my
fingertips, and you did what I couldn't.
You came through for me.
I been sleeping like
a baby ever since.
It was hot today.
Like I said the other night,
I know you, Dexter.
I see who you are.
We're like-minded.
Together, we can make a difference.
We?
Miguel, my amigo,
claims to know me.
On some level,
I suppose maybe that's true.
Who are you kidding?
He knows about Freebo.
He detailed me
to the Ethan Turner kill.
He's seen me with blood
on my hands and hasn't blinked.
Miguel's got no clue
what's really going on inside you.
The urge, the ritual.
Miguel has really gone out of his way
to understand who I am...
Which is more than you ever did.
Well, I understood.
I just couldn't accept it.
And Miguel won't either.
You didn't want me
to have any friends.
You think Miguel's a pal?
Your wingman?
You might wanna put
that notion to the test...
See how like-minded
you and Miguel really are.
Every time you let
someone get close,
it ends badly.
I do need to consider
my spotty record connecting
with others.
But Miguel's not going away.
I need to make him
understand the risks.
When he does, he'll wanna
rethink the like-minded thing.
Just because he can gut a fish
doesn't qualify him
to hang with me while I...
Do what I do best.
You need a jump? I have cables.
Skinner struck again.
Super-hard this time.
The victim's name was Wendell Owen.
He was 15 years old.
It's more collateral damage
in our search for fucking Freebo.
Wendell Owens?
I brought him in
for questioning the other day.
I remembered
hearing his name somewhere.
He might have been mixed up with some
lowlifes, but he was a decent kid.
Go do your thing.
I just need a min.
Body's still warm.
Putting time of death about 3 h ago.
Unlike the two previous victims,
this one died
- from the skinning process itself.
- Jesus Christ.
Freebo's probably in another galaxy
and the skinner doesn't even know it.
Meanwhile, he's
stepping up his game.
Maybe we let the press
know Freebo got outta dodge,
might get this guy
to put down his Ginzu knife.
Or he'll keep looking,
take his horror show on the road,
become somebody else's nightmare.
No, I wanna nail
whoever's doing this.
He's definitely not learning to do this
on the fly. He's had plenty of practice.
Run this through
the national database,
see if a similar MO
comes up anywhere else.
What I need to find right now
is a target to present to Miguel
with a high degree
of difficulty and jeopardy.
So that he truly understands
that he's in way over his head.
I have a question.
It's serious.
I can't ask any of the other cops.
I'm all yours.
It's about the skinner.
His last two victims,
Wendell and Javier,
they were both killed after
I was done questioning them.
Do you think the skinner's
drafting off my investigation?
- Anything's possible.
- Because I'm freaking out
that whoever's looking for Freebo
is using me to attract him.
Who else knows
you brought Wendell in?
His mom...
All the cops in the station.
Anton.
Ramon Prado.
Miguel's brother.
The law and order hard ass sheriff
who's been obsessed
about finding Freebo
for killing his little brother.
There's your motive.
Do we seriously think
that Ramon, a fellow cop,
could do something this sick?
Like a career in law enforcement
precludes violent behavior?
Can you imagine the shit storm
this is gonna create if I'm wrong?
It'll create a worse
shit storm if you're right.
Keep me in the loop.
Ramon's got anger issues.
I don't want you getting hurt.
You do care about me.
Wait till you see
the wine cellar at The Forge.
It is legendary!
They even have a bottle
of Chateau d'Yquem...
belonged to Thomas Jefferson.
I'm kind of a cuba libre
kinda girl myself.
Ellen, it's me. Nicely done.
Handing Miguel Prado
his head on a pike today,
make the Hines motion stick,
he could be disbarred.
Bravissimo.
I was gonna talk to you about this,
if and when my motion's upheld.
How 'bout we talk about it now?
Miguel's been playing fast and loose
for a long time with legal ethics.
The Chicky Hines case
is just one example
on a very long list
of prosecutorial misconduct.
I came to you with information
to help your client,
not for you to trump up some witch hunt
against my friend and colleague.
You can't possibly believe
he's either of those things
- if you really knew Miguel...
- Believe me, I know Miguel.
I will explain everything
over dinner.
No, thanks.
I'm not feeling especially
social right now.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
No, I'm alone. Come on in.
Taking the night off?
So, um... beer?
- Sure.
- Pot?
Fuck you.
Sounded kind of upset on the phone.
I'm kind of upset in person too.
You didn't talk to anyone
about me bringing Wendell in
for questioning?
No. I don't talk to anybody
about anything.
I try to keep the whole C.I.
Thing under wraps, you know?
Then how the hell did it get out?
Well, it's a pretty safe bet
Wendell didn't tell anybody.
You should have seen
what this sicko did to him.
I'm glad I didn't.
What would make anyone go that hard
on a street kid, for Christ's sakes?
There's this guy I'm looking at...
He's a cop
who had a beef with Freebo.
He saw me in the station
when I was questioning Wendell.
Wouldn't be the first time the boys in
blue handled their own business, right?
I can't rule out that I put
Wendell in the crosshairs.
He trusted me
enough to cooperate, and...
Look what happened to him.
Hey, look...
Even if you're right,
you couldn't have known,
right?
Don't beat yourself up.
It's what I do best, huh?
I should go.
All right.
Hey, look, um...
That girl from
the other night was...
Was nothing serious.
It's none of my business anyway.
Yeah, right.
Right.
Jenna Kendrick.
One of the first crime scenes
I worked blood spatter.
This is somebody's daughter.
And that was done to her
by this animal.
Clemson Galt.
Aryan affiliated.
Took a claw hammer to her
for getting pregnant.
He was arrested for murder,
even confessed to his cellmate.
He called it "hammer time."
They get a conviction?
Galt's Aryan affiliates
either got witnesses to recant
or made them disappear.
Verdict came back not guilty.
That type of stuff
happens way too often.
Galt's doing 15 to 20 for armed robbery
in a supermax upstate.
That's something.
Get him off the streets.
Only he's still running things
from his prison cell.
The wife and three kids
of an Aryan defector,
killed with a claw hammer.
While you're sleeping like a baby,
this is who's keeping me up nights.
Justice comes at a price,
one that Miguel is about
to discover he can't afford.
This asshole doesn't
deserve to breathe, OK?
You're not gonna get any
argument with me about that.
But he's in custody.
In a supermax, no less.
That's always been the problem.
You're the big deal law enforcement guy.
I bet you could get us access.
That's beyond dangerous, Dexter.
That's crazy!
I knew if I appealed to reason,
Miguel would eventually
understand the downside.
Never mind that my fingerprints
will be all over this!
Reason leads to self-preservation,
a potent force.
We both would be seriously
exposed here.
I just need to sit back.
He'll see the pros are heavily
outweighed by the cons,
and we'll be back to mojitos
and barbecues.
When you get right down to it,
I guess Ethan Turner
was an accident of opportunity,
a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
What about Freebo?
Another accident of opportunity?
Well, that situation
just sort of... unfolded.
You're right.
We both have too much to lose.
Hey, we took out
the garbage... twice.
We should quit while we're ahead.
I owe you this one, Dexter.
You stuck your neck
out for me twice now.
- You don't owe me.
- Fair is fair. I won't let you down.
But we need to come up
with a real plan.
Again...
"we".
Miguel surprised me last night.
I expected him to say no and he gave me
a definite maybe instead.
Hey! No doughnuts today?
Not today, Vince.
Talk about your passive aggressive.
Clemson Galt has been
on my Top 10 list for years,
and Miguel could be a big help.
But the goal here
isn't to satisfy my need.
It's to get Miguel
to find some other hobby.
Got a minute?
- Who's sick?
- Remember Camilla from records?
She's in the hospital.
It's not looking good,
- so I got everyone to sign.
- Camilla's sick?
Sorry, I thought you knew.
Lung cancer. It's terminal.
Just like Gene.
Camilla's husband.
My folks used to play cards with them
when Deb and I were growing up.
He died just last year.
Lung cancer too.
- Smokers?
- Chimneys.
Life catches up.
Yeah.
So does death.
It's a shame. She's a good person.
It sounds like she was a friend.
A good friend.
Those are in short
supply these days.
Camilla's at Good Samaritan.
You could drop that off,
let her know she's in our prayers.
- I'll do that.
- Thanks.
Detective Gianna, Sergeant Batista,
Miami-Metro Homicide.
- How can I help you, sergeant?
- I was...
wondering, Detective...
maybe we could...
See each other.
As in a... date?
Well, yeah.
You could call it that.
Look,
Sergeant, let's be clear,
'cause being clear
will save us both a lot of agita.
I don't date.
Ever.
Do you eat... ever?
Sometimes.
Good nutrition's important.
I'll tell you what, sergeant.
I get hungry enough,
I will call you.
- What?
- Can I throw something at you
- that might sound a little crazy?
- Crazy? From you?
- Ramon Prado.
- What about him?
Do we like him for the skinner?
- Okay, that's not a little crazy.
- He has access to all of our records,
so he knows exactly
who I've been talking to.
And we've all seen him up close,
he's not a stable guy.
- He's a fucking whack job.
- I looked into his work schedule.
He was off duty when
the last two murders went down.
You seriously wanna look
at Ramon Prado
for multiple homicide?
If only to rule him out.
Not only have we not found the perp
who killed M. Prado's little brother,
now you wanna investigate
his other brother for murder?
In a nutshell.
Can't ignore something
just 'cause it's messy.
- If I'm right, this is huge.
- And if you're wrong,
everyone involved
will be shitting blood
- due to acts I'd rather not describe.
- Thanks for that, Sarge.
I've got a gut feeling.
You wanna go to the lieutenant
with this?
I can't go to LaGuerta with this.
You follow up...
off the grid, and it's on you.
Thank you, Sarge.
Ramon's off duty tonight and tomorrow.
I'll set up on him,
see what shakes loose.
- If you need company...
- I've got it covered.
And try to be discreet, will you?
For a change?
You came.
I also brought you these.
But it looks like
somebody beat me to it.
Oh, well...
That new mom in maternity
donated them to terminal care.
Talk about irony.
You know, Dexter,
my whole life
I've been searching for...
The meaning of life?
The perfect...
Key lime pie.
And what do I get
when I'm about to croak?
Fucking pie crust,
reddi wip,
and green Jell-O.
I'll see what I can do about finding you
the perfect key lime pie.
You'd better do it fast.
Next thing to go is the appetite.
Gene always
had this thing
about lighting my cigarette.
And he'd pass it to me...
before he lit his own.
Sweet, sweet man.
Then it all caught up to him.
I watched him wither to a skeleton.
My six foot tall,
two hundred pound husband,
shitting all over himself.
His last breath was a mercy.
Dying I can do.
Hell, I'm doing it.
The pain sure is a bear, though.
How bad?
The worst part
of the whole damn thing...
not losing my life...
My time on this earth...
Is losing my...
Dignity.
That fish was great.
- You don't think Miguel overcooked it?
- A bit,
but the mango salsa saved the day.
So do you like what you do?
I mean, real estate.
I can't imagine doing anything else.
Yeah, I decided that losing my job
at the motel is not
a bad thing but a good thing.
So I'm looking around.
With your people skills,
you'd be great at real estate.
You think?
How about you start work tomorrow?
- I'm sorry, what?
- I need an assistant.
Having someone I can trust
is everything.
Salud.
Look, I've been giving a lot of thought
to this Clemson Galt thing.
Good.
Dígame.
What if we were to travel upstate
and arrange an interview with him?
About?
A career criminal
with a record like his,
he's gotta be an encyclopedia of intel
on tons of other cases.
We would just need
to get Galt alone long enough to make it
look like another prisoner did the deed.
Last week,
an inmate is found in a prison hallway
drowned in a bucket of water.
This stuff
happens all day long
in places like that.
An inmate is found dead
in custody, Dexter,
be a lot of inquiries
and investigations.
You got the bleeding hearts coming out
of the woodwork
whining about prison reform.
It doesn't sound like
much of a plan.
That is the plan...
So that Miguel finally
includes himself out.
But...
I'm in the middle of trying
a racketeering case right now.
Money laundering.
The Aryans, they're masters
at moving cash around.
I subpoena Galt
as an expert witness,
corrections transports him
down here to testify.
Then Galt is within our reach.
And on my turf.
Guessing it would take a long time
to set something like that up.
It would.
But I've already issued
the subpoena.
Galt'll be here tomorrow night.
Only...
he's gonna be a no-show on
the witness stand the next morning.
Swing by the courthouse tomorrow,
I'll walk you through
all the details.
Say thank you, Dexter.
Miguel seems to have
way more aptitude
and appetite for this
than I ever imagined.
Just calling to check in.
Just having a look-see
in Ramon Prado's car.
- You really need to...
- Relax.
He's scarfing down his 2nd
plate of arroz con póllo
at a restaurant up the block.
He's got a wife and kids
at home, got the night off,
so why is he eating alone?
Well, maybe the wife's
arroz con póllo isn't póllo enough.
- You find anything interesting?
- A set of German steel filet knives,
a couple of straight razors,
and like 12 pounds of human skin.
Just be careful
out there, will you?
Yes, sir.
Deb's got her mission.
I've got mine.
I can get out and give you a great,
big hug so everyone can see
what good friends we are...
Or you can talk to me.
You know, after 12 hours
on surveillance detail,
- how about you blow me instead?
- I've been given the directive
to either step up my investigation
of Quinn or close it.
Because you haven't found dick.
If you weren't such a fuckwad,
I'd almost feel sorry for you
for working for IA.
- Where careers go to die.
- You need to get next to Quinn,
be his go-to girl.
You'll be wearing a wire.
Are you on crack? How many times
have I told you to eat shit?
What the fuck makes you think
I'm suddenly willing to play now?
Because if you don't,
I'll put the word out
that you've been cooperating
all along.
Everyone'll think
you're a rat anyway.
Hard to believe even you
would sink that low.
So that door right over there?
Check this out.
That's supposed to be kept locked,
and it never is.
The smokers use it
as a shortcut to get outside.
Shortcut to a shorter life.
You know, statistically, most escapes
happen out of a courthouse.
Security's a little bit more lax,
the defendant's wearing
a suit and a tie.
It makes it easy for him
to just walk away.
Easier for us to cover our tracks.
That too.
Must be good to be you.
Sometimes.
Thanks for helping out.
Real reason she's blindfolded,
so she doesn't have to watch everything
she stands for get pissed on
by someone like Ellen Wolf.
She had this client once who threw
a 5-year-old into an industrial washer
for talking dirty. She got him off
with 6 months in a mental hospital.
Diminished fucking capacity.
Hey.
She probably got paid more that
than you took home in a year.
I gotta say I'm very disappointed
with your boss over there.
I never thought that she,
of all people,
would hurt me like this and throw in
with these fucking bottom-feeders.
My dad used to say be careful
what you think you know
about someone.
You're probably wrong.
Smart man.
Well, sometimes.
I appreciate your...
cooperation in the deposition.
I've never had a problem
telling the truth.
We've got
more than enough to get
the Hines conviction set aside.
And you've set the stage
for your smear campaign
against a stand-up guy.
Nice.
You ever wanna hear
the unexpurgated version of your guy,
come find me, OK?
Looks like a church.
The holding cell
is through that door.
Connects to a hallway,
then goes out to a parking garage.
On your right,
there's gonna be an emergency exit.
And that deadbolt
is gonna be taped...
Open.
Why risk it all?
Your career, reputation, freedom.
You could just walk away.
You didn't walk away
from Ethan Turner.
Because you understand, Dexter,
that we're living in...
We're living in crucial times
that demand extraordinary measures.
Miguel's convinced himself
he wants this kill tonight
for lofty and noble reasons.
I'm not quite as high-minded.
You didn't answer my question.
Asshole drunk dad...
Maybe I'm trying to clean up the mess
that I couldn't as a kid, I don't know.
Come on, I'll show you where
you're gonna be hooking up with Galt.
What's the hurry?
You meeting someone?
More like avoiding someone.
This is me not telling you
I'm tailing Ramon Prado again tonight.
Well, this is me not hearing
a word you're saying.
I'm also unofficially
and off the record
telling you to be smart
and watch your ass.
'Scuse me, officer.
Sergeant. How can I help you?
I was just...
released for this legal thing.
- You were arrested.
- And released.
Totally victimless.
Only I live like
a million miles away from here,
and I really need a ride.
How 'bout the bus?
How 'bout you take me home
and I think of some victimless
way of saying thank you?
I'll have dispatch call you a cab.
Just like that?
Just like that.
Sergeant, Barbara Gianna here.
So happens...
I'm hungry.
Hungry enough to--
to see if you are too.
Are you asking me out
on a date, detective?
I don't date, sergeant.
Ever.
Marino's Trattoria, 7:30?
Aren't you gonna ask me
if I really turned over a new leaf?
It could be I'm just not
partial to redheads.
I have no idea what
you're talking about, detective.
I'll see you at 7:30.
Delivered fresh daily
from a little bakery
down in Key Largo.
- Supposed to be the best in the Keys.
- Well, it's not.
Pardon my bluntness, but...
this pie is green.
Means they used food coloring.
Something purists frown on?
Which I'd be doing right now,
except even my face hurts.
The other thing they fucked up--
this wasn't made
with condensed milk.
No, it's fresh and organic.
Only they didn't have
fresh milk in the Keys
back in the day.
Here comes Miss Morphy.
Bringer of bad dreams
and less pain.
If you're as serious
about key lime pie as I am...
you can do better.
Tonight's the night.
But it feels different.
I won't be alone.
Uncharted territory for me...
Not without risk.
And strangely exhilarating.
So what do you think?
Best pizza night ever.
No, I meant about Syl's job offer.
If real estate's something
you're interested in, go for it.
And Syl's great at what she does.
In a market this bad,
she's still always closing.
And I could learn a lot. I just...
But...
What if I...
see a side to her
that I don't like?
That's the risk you run when you go
into business with somebody,
especially a friend.
Makes things more complicated,
no doubt about it.
Still...
without my friend Syl,
I wouldn't have this opportunity.
So I think I'm gonna
take the risk
and jump in with both feet
and see if this new thing
calls to me.
It's getting late.
You don't wanna stay?
Miguel and I have a...
early morning run.
I can sleep in longer
if I stay at my place.
Don't be surprised
if he's a no-show.
What makes you say that?
He's been a complete wreck lately.
Not sleeping,
terrible mood. Syl thinks
something's really bothering him.
Seemed fine today.
You may be his buddy,
but you're not his wife.
And besides, it's not like you can
hide anything from your partner.
So true.
Why would you want to?
Looks like Miguel's got a bad
case of nerves about tonight.
He isn't sleeping
like a baby anymore.
If you're gonna bail off of this,
now would be a good time.
What are you
dressed like that for?
The more the merrier.
Why don't we swing by
and pick up Rita and the kids?
Bring them along too.
What makes you think
you can count on Miguel?
He's just a little jumpy.
He's new at this.
Mark my words, he'll give you up
in a heartbeat to save his own ass.
This is not a guy
who wants to spend the rest
of his life in a cage.
Just one more thing Miguel
and I have in common.
You don't know
what you're getting into.
You've never had to rely
on anyone else before, Dexter.
Because you taught me
loneliness as an art form.
But guess what?
I finally have a life
with a family and now a friend...
who I trust.
We only see two things in people...
What we wanna see
and what they wanna show us.
You don't know Miguel
any more than he knows you.
You aren't seriously gonna
lecture me on relationships
after the debris field
you left behind.
No matter how close two people are,
an infinite distance separates them.
Look at you and me.
Mind if I get
a picture with you, jefe?
You got a cam--
Any truth you're gonna
run for D.A.?
- If I do, I'm gonna need your support.
- You got it, jefe.
Thanks, officer.
You listen to me, pulled pork.
I got no clue why the fuck
you dragged me down here
but you can suck my white dick,
you think I'm helping
your spic ass with shit.
This all ends right here,
right now, Clemson.
This makes us even.
When you walk out the door,
one of your Nazi pals is waiting
for you in the parking garage.
From now on,
all of the threats to my family,
they stop, understand?
I knew my Aryan brothers
would come through, ése.
Have any arrangements been made
in case this guy's testimony runs long
and he has to stay another day?
We're holding a spot in protective
at Miami-Dade.
My good man. Appreciate it.
I got a witness in there, man,
that's taking a nap.
I'm gonna really need him fresh
for court in a couple of hours.
I gotta put a county wristband on him.
Just take a second.
Clem Galt.
I'm your wheel man.
Welcome home.
Heil Hitler.
- Let's get outta here.
- This way.
Have ya outta the country
by lunchtime.
- What's going on here?
- I don't know. Come on.
I'll get ya outta here.
Galt had to have an accomplice.
Just set up a perimeter
around this building.
No one gets in or out.
- Fucking spic set us up.
- This guy cannot get away!
- And I'm gonna return the favor.
- That's mighty white of you.
Galt's right. He's selling you out.
Never underestimate
the capacity of other people
- to let you down.
- It's not the time, dad.
There he goes.
Looking out for number one.
Which is what you should have done.
Like the man said,
nobody gets in or out.
Might as well give up.
No sense risking death by cop.
You keep Miguel's involvement secret,
he might let you off with a few years.
Stop.
Unless they find those blood slides
when they toss your apartment.
Stop!
I'm gonna drop you off at your car.
Then I'll meet you
at the stash house
as soon as I can get outta here.
- Wait for me, huh?
- Thanks for this.
That's what friends are for.
I'm gonna do a loop around the building
until you get more backup here.
You got it, jefe.
Gimme a fucking break, Ramon.
Don't lie!
You can make this stop right now...
If you tell me where he is.
I don't know.
You're making this
very hard on yourself, Felipe.
- You scared the fuckmother out of me.
- You called me. What do we got?
Kidnapping, for starters.
Who's the special guest?
That's Felipe Cepeda.
One of Freebo's hemp suppliers.
I questioned him 2 weeks ago.
Now Ramon's got a few
questions of his own.
Well, so far, I've only heard one--
Where's Freebo?
I'm just waiting
for the skinning to start.
- Tell me where he is.
- I don't know!
Nothing like a nice cold
soda pop before a good skinning.
- Fuck, that's gotta hurt.
- Wait, wait.
We need to be sure
he's the skinner.
You have some answers
for me now?
I don't get it.
That's not the skinner's M.O.
Maybe he's just warming up.
Here he goes...
He's not the skinner.
I gotta take this.
Don't go anywhere.
So Ramon Prado's a sick fuck,
but he's not the one we're looking for.
I'll talk to you about it
over breakfast. I gotta go.
What's up?
So, why are you calling us
in at midnight?
We've picked up
Ramon Prado.
He's... outside.
We got a unit watching him
to keep his mouth shut.
For what?
Kidnapping.
False imprisonment.
And torture.
- Are you sure?
- We witnessed it ourselves.
My god, I--
We can't give him a pass on this.
No, we can't.
Thank you for being
politic at least.
I woulda perp-walked him
right through here.
Morgan insisted we be discreet
out of respect for his family.
Were you aware
of this investigation?
- Yes, I was.
- And you didn't inform me?
I wanted something solid
before involving you.
Thank you for that.
You handled a tough
situation the smart way.
- How do you wanna do this?
- Book him.
I'll notify the family.
That went well.
Internal affairs
is investigating you.
What?
They've been giving me a sandpaper
enema to wear a wire.
This has been going
on for a while.
- And you're finally telling me.
- Yes.
Do you wanna tell me why this I.A. chick
is so gung ho to bring you down?
Wait.
Does this I.A. chick
go by the name of Yuki Amado?
As a matter of fact, yes.
You wanna tell me what's going on?
Yuki and I have a... history.
It's a totally personal vendetta
on her part.
I'll handle it.
I appreciate the heads up, though.
Even in prison, I'm sure you heard about
the big slump in the real estate market.
What the fuck...
There is an upside
to the downturn, though.
Plenty of empty houses.
Do you recognize this one?
It's where you killed
Jenna Kendrick.
No idea what the hell
you're talking about.
I'm talking about
hammer time, Clemson.
You got me mixed up
with somebody else.
You can't imagine how much
I've been looking forward to this.
And none of it
would be happening
if it weren't for my...
friend
Miguel Prado.
You remember him?
He really came through tonight.
In a big way.
I never had a partner before.
I had my doubts initially,
but everything worked out.
But this part, the ritual...
The connection and certainty...
followed by that
pristine silence...
is for me.
And me alone.
Miguel will be disappointed.
I'll explain to him I took Galt
straight to the cemetery
and dumped him in a grave
after the screw-up at the courthouse.
Truth is, I'm not ready to share this
part of me with anyone else just yet.
Present company excepted.
I'm not sure I ever will be ready.
Even if Miguel senses my deception,
he'll forgive me
this one small untruth.
How can I be so sure?
Because after tonight,
I can honestly say
I know who Miguel Prado
really is...
My first good friend.
And those are in short
supply these days.