Previously on Dexter...
I'm on edge.
Thirty eight days have passed
since I killed my brother.
In that entire time,
I haven't had a single night to myself.
Sergeant Doakes makes sure of that.
With Doakes tailing me,
my life's been all Jekyll and no Hyde.
My brother would be so disappointed.
Don't forget:
tell the universe what you need.
I really need... to kill somebody.
I've been waiting a long time for this.
What the fuck...
I'll be okay.
I follow the code. The stalk was good.
I'm just a little rusty
since killing my brother.
Debra can't sleep
in an empty house anymore.
I guess that's what happens
when your fiancé
tries to slice you up
into small bloodless pieces.
Welcome back, Morgan.
Thanks.
You just gotta look her in the eyes
to know she's not right.
- Are you that...
- What the fuck are you doing?
Rita, I'm not doing
real good in here, okay?
Will you help me?
I found the fucking shoe, okay?
That's great!
I'll call the lawyer in the morning!
I'm not gonna let you drag
Dexter into this!
The prison called.
Paul's dead.
And I could have helped him.
That was his own fault.
Was it?
What's the matter with you today?
Just a little off my game.
I'll get it back.
Felt like she was asking me something.
That's her son.
She says she knows who killed him.
Some guy named Little Chino.
She wants you to find Little Chino
and kill him like a dog.
Are you willing to testify
that Little Chino picked up your son
on the night of his death?
Come on, don't back down now.
I want him to pay.
A challenge.
A mountain to climb.
I need this one.
The scene of the failed crime.
No better place to try again.
I don't normally
experience failure.
Thirty nine days, twenty two hours,
and eighteen minutes
since I killed my brother.
I am cursed.
Two treasure hunters
made a ghastly discovery today,
when they stumbled on what appears
to be an underwater graveyard,
in a crevasse, off the coast of Miami.
Do you know what that means?
There might be
a new mass murderer out there,
way worse than the Ice Truck Killer.
Waiting to exhale(del vo)
I'm drifting.
I finally get a chance to kill
and I can't do it.
And a second chance and he gets away.
And now all my secrets are floating
to the surface.
Where is the orderly, controled,
effective, Dexter?
How did I loose him?
How do I find him again?
I'm drifting.
But not to sleep.
A shocking and grusome discovery
of the cost of florida yesterday.
Police are still searching through
mountain of evidence
found lying at the bottom of the ocean.
Sources say
there could be multiple victims...
Here I am.
Back in the belly of the beast.
But how can I solve a crime
when I can't even solve
what's wrong with me?
Yet, duty calls.
Eight confirmed.
Eight confirmed, here?
- Here is just one.
- We're talking 8 confirmed victims
in the Bay Harbor Butcher.
"The Bay Harbor Butcher"?
That's what the press is calling
where were dumped those bodies of shore.
Has a nice ring to it, no?
Well, it's a little...
lured.
- Lured and possibly wrong.
Part of me is hopping they found
the ice truck killer dumping ground.
Tell me about it.
Last thing Miami needs
is another serial killer.
Eva Raines.
All she wanted was justice against the 29th St. Kings for whacking her son.
- First she is the messenger.
- No, she's the god damn message.
Death by machete.
Again.
We got a *bollo* on Little Chino.
Gang crash unit, all local patrols after than grabon.
Last thing I want is for the cops
to bring Little Chino in.
He's mine.
Why don't you take a picture?
Morgan, it will last longer.
What would I do without you sergeant?
Please signora, *mas dispacio*
Please slower...
She saying any fucking cops
aren't do nothing.
- Grand Ma really talk like that?
- Not exactly.
But you got the point.
Right, bitch?
Fuck the people don't want our help.
Shit, she got a little girl.
I know.
This stuff never gets to you?
I'm more of a crying
on the inside kind of guy.
Mister Ice Truck Killer
look like a god damn artist.
Sorry, Morgan.
What?
I'm so over that.
You're just fucking with me.
I'm gonna have to put you on hold.
Fiancé...
*Incarnate*. Couldn't pick a worst time, right?
Hey Yasmeth:
How about you take off,
let me handle this?
I couldn't let you do that.
I'll write up the report and e-mail it to you for signature.
Okay?
I want Morgan to report to me
first thing in the morning
about that bar fight of hers.
I owe you.
Get in there.
There's somebody else, get in there now.
Pobrecita.
Seeing her mother that way...
can you imagine that?
I can even go there, Angel.
This one's on us, man.
If I had kid Chino last night
that little girl's mother
would still be alive.
I gotta find Chino before he finds me.
...bringing to an even dozen the number of bodies
found off-shore.
I have to focus.
Tune everything out.
So far, authorities have no clue
as to who that criminal...
If I don't, being linked
to my beautiful bodies at work
will be the least of my worries.
Shit! Little Chino.
He was out there.
Timing could be better.
That, plus I don't have my tools, but...
It does give me the chance
to tie up one mess of loose end.
That's you, sergeant.
Who else you got following you?
Apparently no one.
Go ahead. Try it.
I've been waiting.
In this neighborhood?
It's full of crazies.
I'd lock my doors.
Bathroom's all yours.
It kind of always was.
We ran out of glasses?
- Clean ones.
- Come here a sec'.
I found a couple of places on Craigslist
that you should check out.
Two bedrooms, two baths,
limited water views...
- It has its own gym.
- I hate it.
Alright.
One bedroom, one bath,
art deco building?
Shitty neighborhood.
It gets morning sun!
- Come on, Deb, give it a chance.
- Look, Dex,
I appreciate the brotherly love,
but I've got the lieutenant
in like an hour.
See you at the job.
I will not kill my sister.
RITA CALLING (del vo)
- Hey you!
- Dexter?
Astor? Sweetie, what's the matter?
Mum's acting all weird and stuff.
What kind of weird?
She keeps talking to people
on the phone about my dad,
then she starts yelling at them.
Then, she yells at me and Cody.
I'm on my way.
No. Calm is what I was 35 minutes ago.
Pissed is what I am now.
Hey! Who wants Eggos?
I got blueberry or chocolate. Or both.
- Both.
- I don't care.
Assholes!
They did everything but help.
Which assholes were you talking to?
Funeral home assholes.
You're having a funeral for Paul?
Not for Paul.
For the kids.
For me.
We had this old insurance policy.
It's about five thousands,
but it should cover everything.
You know, the county
will bury Paul for free.
I mean...
He wasn't even your husband.
Any more.
Technically.
Then, you could use the insurance money
for a starter scholarship for the kids.
Dexter, I didn't ask for your help
or your advice.
I'll never understand how people
deal with death.
What they can't just... put it in its place.
Now, I have to find someone
who knows I'm looking for him.
Not exactly ideal
in the element of surprise department,
and I have to find a new way to dispose
of Little Chino's body.
If I can close the deal, this time...
You totally douched me in there.
You clocked a guy in a bar,
who touched your arm.
Yeah, I told the lieutenant
you weren't ready for active duty.
Well, thank you for the fucking vote
of confidence.
Nice.
13! Confirmed.
You know, buzz in the halls
is that the Feds are coming in
on the Bay Harbor bodies.
Well, that figures.
FBI does all the heavy lifting,
Captain Matthews takes all the credit.
Nice political move
- when you're buckin' for deputy chief.
- Any idea who the FBI's sendin'?
- Some guy named Landy.
- Frank Landy?
He's a rock star.
The Green River killer
and the DC sniper?
The case was impossible, he broke it.
We're damage goods
around here, but you...
You should do whatever you can to get on Landy's task force.
It's a career maker.
Just visualize that door of opportunity
just opening up wide for you.
And just walk right through it.
Angel, you keep up with this whoo-hoo
shit, I'll walk right through you.
Little Chino... Shit!
This guy is officialy
the highest point in all Florida.
But what's he doin' here?
People tell me
you're lookin' for my client.
People tell you right.
Fuck, he's big!
The harder they fall...
That come with the story?
Cut myself shaving.
Well, you should be more careful.
Amigo
My client's been repeatedly
harassed by this department.
- Frankly we considering...
- Cut the shit, Raul.
There was another murder
in East Kendle yesterday and my client...
Word on the pavement is
you're lookin' for me regarding this...
- Tragedy.
- You bet your ass, we are.
The victim was the mother of one of your
compadres who we know you killed.
- But can't prove. Right, Officer?
- It's "Detective".
- And can't prove yet.
- Show 'em the disc.
Time-stamp has this at
yesterday afternoon.
- Same time as...
- Eva Raine's TOD.
That's bullshit. Anyone can reset a time-stamp.
Check it out.
Yesterday's paper.
That arrogant prick.
He knew we'd peg him
for Elena's murder so...
he covered his ass,
had someone else do the deed.
- That makes him an accomplice, right?
- Not without evidence.
Cut him loose.
Red Rover, Red Rover
send Chino back over.
Dex, check this out.
Thirteen and counting.
They're so swamped up there,
they had to bring in outside talent.
Which would be moi.
Bet this guy never expected
his work to see the lighta day.
I bet you're right.
Still it can't be easy
to hide a body now-a-days.
265s
You shittin' me?
Hypothetical:
you're the Bay Harbor Butcher.
How do you make sure
disposed body stays disposed?
Tons of options:
Everglades, alligators...
pig farms, sulfuric acid,
wood chipper, incinerator.
Hell! Even meat pies.
The mind boggles.
Don't all those run the risk
of contact with the outside world?
You got a better idea?
And that's the problem. Where do I put
Chino when I'm done with him?
Captain's comin' up with that FBI guy.
He's got a fuckin' entourage.
So this is the man who stands
between me and death row.
Listen up, everyone.
Briefing room in 2 minutes
for show and tell.
All right.
The Bay Harbor Butcher case
is now a Miami Metro case.
And it is shaping up to be
the biggest one in our history.
Now it's fourteen confirmed.
The FBI has sent over
their top man, Special Agent Frank Landy
to help solve this crime.
Now...
This will not be
a jurisdictional circle jerk.
This will be a shining exemple
of two agencies
working together for the public good.
Agent Landy...
Hello, everyone.
There is no such thing
as the perfect crime.
Not in my experience anyway.
With your help,
and with the mistakes
this person has made...
and will eventually make,
we'll find whoever did
this aweful thing.
I need everyone in every department
up to speed on what we're doing.
While I review your files
and put our task force together.
So, let's get a jump start
on the Bay Harbor Butcher.
A moniker which by the way repulses me.
Well, we have something in common.
Someone get the lights?
First report from the field
had these parts as comin'
- from one body.
- Actually it's two.
Actually it's two.
There has been speculation that this
human harvest might be connected
to a case you've recently solved.
But there are
several inconsistencies between
the two sets of body parts.
Gender, exsanguination...
specific methods of dissection.
Not to mention my guys deserved it.
The evidence just isn't there
to piggy-back this
onto the Ice Truck Killer.
We're looking for a different suspect.
All information regarding this case...
Miss me, brother?
I can't afford to lose it like this.
Not with Special Agent Rock Star
on my case.
I need to clear the decks.
And my head.
I'm coming for you tonight,
Little Chino.
And this time
there won't be any screw ups.
You just slam in your CO2 cartridge here.
Put in your tranq dart and let it rip.
Wham bam
lights fucking out.
So gators givin' you trouble, Dex?
They... ate my puppy.
This sucker...
You load her up right should take down
the goddamn grizzly.
You may have to get closer
than you like.
She'll do the job, I promise you that.
So which'll be?
Both.
Excellent.
First time?
Sort of.
Yeah, I been boxing since I was 10.
- Tough neighborhood?
- Tough family.
And those were just my sisters.
Want some help?
I'm doin' enough damage on my own.
Is that a yes or a no?
That was a yes.
It sounded like a no, but...
Good answer.
First...
we need to wrap your wrists.
So you don't hurt yourself again.
I'm sorry.
You scared the shit outta me.
How you doin'?
How am I doin'?
I saw the man I thought I loved.
No, did love.
Up on some goddamn screen.
With a gallery full of women
he murdered and cut into pieces.
Don't.
You fuckin' asked.
So how am I doin'?
I'm just fine.
I might be playing fast and loose
with my father's code, but I don't think
Harry would disapprove.
Considering...
Attaboy, Chino. A little closer.
Come on, don't get the shakes now.
This is no time for performance anxiety.
I've been waitin' for you.
Take him.
He's there.
I don't know.
I don't know where the fuck he is.
Come out, come out whereever you are, cabr
n.
We'll be out here
all night long if we have to.
You find him, okay?
What the hell is wrong with me?
Someone's coming.
It's okay, I got you.
- Please don't hurt us!
- Oh, my God!
What the fuck is this?
Dexter, don't leave me!
Biney!
- Don't leave me!
- Get in there!
Please, don't leave me!
- Somebody else get in there now!
- Biney!
Wait! Don't leave me!
Bryan... My brother.
Come on,
somebody must've seen somethin'.
Seing and talking
are 2 different things.
Want me to knock out some doors?
Or maybe some heads.
Sorry, I'm late.
What fucking asshole left this here?
It's Special Agent Fucking Asshole.
- Morgan, right?
- We got witnesses to interview.
You seen my brother?
Excuse me, sir.
You have a minute?
Or three.
Good tea takes time.
What's up, Sergeant?
It's about your task force. I think
I can bring something to it, sir.
I've looked into your jacket,
sergeant.
You've done some fine work here,
in Homicide.
- Miami Metro's lucky to have you.
- Thank you, sir...
But I don't think you'd be
a good fit for my team.
I thought you just said I was qualified.
I said you've done some fine work in Homicide.
Frankly, sergeant, you're more
of a leader than a team member.
I'm not convinced
you play well with others.
Can someone clean this shit up?
I feel like a jigsaw puzzle
missing a piece.
And I'm not even sure
what the picture should be.
I've been calling you for hours.
I kinda pulled an all nighter.
I called the station.
I was off the clock.
It's this huge case I'm workin'.
It's...
It's taking me to places
I never thougt I'd go.
What?
I've been thinking a lot...
about Paul's death
and how I'm gonna deal with it.
- And?
-  First of all, I'm not gonna let the county burry him.
I'm using the insurance money to give
Paul a proper funeral. It's in an hour.
Paul was such a...
destructive force.
Why can't you just put him behind you?
It's about saying goodbye.
Goodbye to him
and the grip he had on my life.
It's called moving on.
Go clean yourself up.
The kids are expecting you.
- I'm just gonna make you late.
- Dammit, Dexter.
I need you there, too.
You have no idea what this feels like.
Just gimme 10 minutes.
Come in.
I can't wait to get another door
slammed in my face.
If I lived in this neighborhood,
I wouldn't talk to the cops either.
Brave guy like you?
It's about survival.
These people have families, kids...
It's not easy to be talkative
when you got the 29th St. Kings
playing whack the witness.
It just takes one, right?
That's it!
Put that out into the universe.
Alright?
Miami Metro! Can we talk to you?
Go to hell!
Okay, but before we do that, ma'am,
can I ask you a few questions?
How many is "a few"?
Three.
But one's a two parter.
Go away before I call the police!
We are the fucking police!
I am talking to no one
with language like that!
Look at the bright side.
- What bright side?
- Comically?
We're batting a thousand.
There's something balancing
about that kind of consistency.
Goddamn it!
Shit!
What were you thinking?
Were you thinking that you can spray your damn crap on a police car
and get away with it?
Get off of me, lady! Unless you wanna
fuck me like you fucked that Ice Truck guy too!
You little deadbeat -- we better get every piece of shit!
Please! I'll tell you where the shit is!
The drugs and shit!
- Please, don't shoot me, miss!
- Morgan!
If I believed in God,
if I believed in sin,
this is the place where I'd be
sucked straight to hell.
If I believed in hell.
Come on, Dexter. It's alright.
... hard story of who this man was.
Born into innocence,
as are all of God's children,
are truly the living personification
of God through the magic of family.
Giving love... it was with his children,
that he truly flourished.
It was with his children,
that he, for all his blemishes,
reembraced the perfect innocence.
And that was through his children,
that once again,
God's smiled on Paul Bennett.
And now, the family will come forward
for a few moments of silent prayer.
I hope you find your peace, Paul.
Bye, dad.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Father.
I'm not sorry.
You're still here.
I never left.
Yeah, you did. I killed you.
You just took my life.
So, how do I make you go away?
Well, you can try doing
what these people are doing.
I'm not like them.
Now, if it helps,
then I can tell you it's not your fault,
what you did to me.
I never said it was.
But you feel it.
How do you know that?
It's human nature.
I'm not human.
You're just fucked up.
I need to let you go.
You think it's as simple as that?
Nothing's simple.
Does this mean you will be my dad, now?
29th St. Kings?
Yeah, we got them.
SWAT did a sweep on some auto shop those
animals were using as a front.
Maybe we didn't get them on murder,
but we busted their asses on drugs,
weapons and money laundering.
Half of them are three strikers,
so they're gonna go away forever.
Thanks to officer Morgan.
Hey, something you should know.
Deb pulled her gun on an unarmed boy
to get him to give up the gang.
Some kid named Joey Nunez.
Thanks, Angel. I'll talk to her.
I'll give her one thing, though.
She's in a motherfucking good shape.
Here comes another one.
We got Little Chino too?
That cocksucker wasn't there.
It's too bad.
What you got?
It's none of your business.
Damn
Excuse me, Esme.
I opened this by mistake.
It said lieutenant.
No worries.
Today, Maria, it is all about the win.
I think we really should enjoy this.
Stop me if you think
I'm speaking out of turn,
or above my station, but...
We really don't use to department resources
around here for personal matters.
What are you talking about?
Well, let's, for argument's sake,
say those phone records
belong to your fiancé.
It could open a shit ugly can of worms
you might not be able to close.
Only if someone mentions it.
This is me not mentioning it.
I'm new at this... This.
Not trusting the man
that I thought that I loved, and...
I really appreciate your support.
Hey, Deb. It's me.
Again. You're probably at the gym.
Again.
Look, I got some unfinished business
outside the office
I'll probably be a little late tonight.
I'll catch up with you later.
It was simple, really.
All I had to do was put myself
into the mind of a killer.
Hardly a stretch.
It was only a matter of time
before Little Chino
went after Joey Nunez
for snitching them out.
Here's, hoping I'm back on my game.
Trust me, you're not going anywhere
this time.
Who the fuck are you?
That kind of talk is just gonna
bring you closer to your victims.
Who the hell are you? A cop?
'Cause I was cleared of that bitch!
No, maybe you didn't do the deed,
but her blood is on your hands.
A lot of blood is on your hands.
Why do you care about these people?
Actually...
Fuck!
I don't.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm not so much doing this to you
as I'm doing it for me.
What's that?
I haven't killed no kid.
But you killed most of her.
Her mother.
Her brother.
Her innocence.
You leave pain wherever you go.
If you kill me,
what do you leave behind?
A world without you.
Look at that, steady as a surgeon.
This kill was the first
of the loose ends I needed to tie off.
I found a newer, safer place to dump
my trash.
Moving at over 4 miles an hour,
the Gulf Stream is one of the world's
most powerful deep water currents.
This time tomorrow, Little Chino
will be north of Palm Beach.
After that, it's on to Georgia,
South Carolina,
North Carolina, until, eventually...
Well, let's just say that the North
Atlantic is a pretty big place.
- Hey, you.
- I need to see you.
I was just dropping somebody off,
can't it wait?
No, it can't.
Alright, then.
A shoe?
You want to see me about a shoe?
It's Paul shoe.
What do we do with it?
Paul kept insisting to me
that you knocked him over the head.
Dragged him to his hotel
and shot him with drugs.
Sounds like one of his stories, huh?
He asked me
to look in the yard for his shoe.
Finally, I did.
- Baby...
- Let me finish, Dexter.
I didn't have a lot to hope for...
until I met you.
You gave me something,
to believe in, when...
I didn't even believe in myself.
Maybe I was...
Maybe I was so desperate
that I looked to the other way.
Paul begged me...
to help him.
And what did I do?
I hung up on him.
And he was so upset,
he got into a prison fight,
and he was beaten to death with a pipe.
It's not your fault.
A part of, it is.
A part of me believes that...
with all of Paul flaws,
he paid the price for my dreams.
Did you attack him, Dexter?
I'd understand if you did,
he attacked me.
I hit Paul to protect you and the kids.
It's totally an act of impulse.
Where did you get the drugs?
Stolen from the evidence locker.
Wait.
Wait, I mean...
First you tell me that you...
acted on impulse,
and then you tell me that you stole
the drugs from your police station?
What are you trying to say, that you...
planned on acting on impulse?
It's all kinda jumbled now...
How did you know how to cook the heroin?
How did you know
what dose to give a big guy like Paul.
Oh my God,
Oh my God, why didn't I see this?
They were your drugs?
Now, it makes sense.
That's where you disappeared to
at all hours of the night like...
Clark fucking Kent
Look, if there is anything,
left between us,
you'll answer me this one question
and you will tell me the truth.
Are you an addict?
Yes, I have an addiction.
That's good.
It's the first step.
Admitting you have a problem.
We get you into a program.
We get you the help you need.
And I will be there for you.
If the eyes were a window to the soul,
then grief is the door...
as long as it's closed, it's the barrier
between knowing and not knowing.
Walk away from it
and it stays closed forever.
But open it, and walk through it,
and pain becomes truth.
And now I'm faced with the struggle
for my own survival
that I always knew was coming.
I've been preparing for this
my entire life.
When all is settle down, Chino,
you're the same size as everyone else.
Hey Dex, what the fuck?
Hang on, I'm coming.
It's annoying, isn't it?
I'm not taking the bait.
- You're up late.
- Yeah, just surfing.
You go to the gym?
Then I was sort of driving around.
Around what?
Around town.
- Because?
- Saw some buildings
with some "for rent" signs.
I'm gonna check them out.
Then, "Chez Dexter",
can return to its original
semi-lived-in-museum-quality-state.
- Deb, you don't need to do this.
- Yes, I do.
You don't need to do this now.
And what about the video tours
of eligible apartments?
Temporary insanity.
You sure?
No. Get out.
Asshole.
This way I can take care of my sister
the way Harry would have wanted.
You really wreak.
You right.
I smell like a fucking sewer.
- For every door that closes...
- Fuck.
Sorry.
... it was always right there.
I had to say goodbye,
in order to reconnect
with what's really important.
With who I was.
With who I have to be.
Rest in peace.
I am.