Previously on Dexter...
I found a fucking lead on the skinner case.
The skinner is using tree-trimming
as a cover for surveillance.
He watches from the trees and when
the time is right, he grabs them.
Mr. King.
We met at the scene of our
second victim, is that correct?
Yes, that is correct.
Mario Astorga?
I don't know anything about anything.
Then why would George
King suggest otherwise?
What are you so afraid of, Mario?
This is the shirt I was
wearing when Freebo met his end.
That's his blood right there.
This shirt implicates me in his death.
I trust you, and I want you to trust me.
But he's being secretive.
He's never home.
He says he's with Dexter.
But I think it's a cover.
Freebo's final resting place.
Hiding a body in a cemetery.
You're fucking brilliant.
We need to go after the root cause
this bloodsucking, soulless
defense attorney Ellen Wolf!
We can't kill her.
I see.
- This is personal.
- Fuck yes, this is personal.
I'm asking you to do
this for me as my friend.
- I'm sorry. No.
- Well, then, fuck you.
Someone loaned Freebo some money
and is willing to skin people to get it back.
We're gonna spread the word
that Anton knows where Freebo is.
Which means that the skinner
will be looking for me.
What are you hiding?
Anton is not officially a C.I.
We used him as bait.
I mean, what, are you
in love with the guy?
Anton, you in there?
Shit. Trimmed trees.
The skinner's been here.
I'm ready to get my hands dirty.
I've always done the deed alone.
Never stood outside.
Been a witness to this moment.
You've set something in motion here.
Everything Miguel does from
now on is connected to you.
DEXTER Season 03 Episode 09
Today I wake up, kiss the wife-to-be...
feed the stepkids-to-be,
dress myself in the usual pants, shirt...
and pretense.
But last night, it was no pretense.
Miguel and I took a life. Together.
And today, someone knows my truth.
Shares my reality.
I'm not alone.
Sylvia, good morning.
Sorry for coming over so early.
It's okay.
But I need to see your face when I ask you.
Ask me?
Syl, what is it?
Miguel was out till all hours last night.
He says he was with you. Is that true?
Absolutely. We were just
hanging. Being guys. You know.
Miguel was telling the truth.
You see, there's nothing to worry about.
Dexter didn't get here till late. It was...
it had to be almost midnight.
Miguel got home an hour ago.
He's having an affair.
Um, no. No, no. You don't know that.
When you've been married as long as we
have, you know when your husband's lying.
Something to look forward to.
Maybe Dexter knows where he went.
I really don't.
But he did talk about a
case he needed to look over.
At the office.
This really isn'tyour problem. I should go.
No. No, no, no.
You stay here for as
long as you need to, okay?
I'll just leave.
Work.
With a detour on the way.
Dex. Dex, man.
How you doing? You okay?
- I'm good.
- Me too.
It's like there was an imbalance
in the world, and we righted it.
With our own hands.
It was deserving.
I don't know. I feel real.
Like maybe for the first timein my life.
I know what you mean.
But. If we're thinking about continuing
these extracurricular activities...
- Absolutely.
- You need to work on your alibis.
Syl stopped by this morning,
wondering where you'd been.
Ah, shit. I'm a moron.
I tried to cover for you,
but I thought you went home.
I'm sorry, man.
I went over to Jack's hideaway
over on 57th. I was, like, so wired.
The next thing I know,
the sun was coming up.
Jack's hideaway.
Don't worry about Syl. I can handle that.
I got a motion hearing this
morning, though, I don't wanna miss.
I'll get better at this.
With your help.
I stalked a wife-killer at Jack's hideaway
last year, grabbed him right at closing.
At 2:00 A.M.
Sylvia said Miguel got home an hour ago.
Did he just lie? To me?
Another detour.
There's nothing here either.
Well, what about the blinds?
What about the glass?
Checked 'em. Deb, there's no blood.
Anton didn't just follow
the skinner out of here.
I'll keep looking.
I think we needto recanvass.
We've already talked to
everyone in the building.
What about the kids? They're awake now.
We'll talk to the kids.
What do we got?
The skinner has Anton.
Did you see the trees?
I saw them. It doesn't mean he got nabbed.
The coffee pot was left burning.
I mean, he definitely left in a hurry.
What the hell was Anton doing back in town?
He never left.
He contacted me, but he
wouldn't agree to surveillance.
Who cares if he agrees? He's a C.I.
That's why we used him as
bait in the first place.
Guys. No liner.
The building trash dumpster.
Subscription renewal form from
Rolling Stone addressed to Anton Briggs.
This is his garbage.
So the bag split on impact
with the dumpster here.
He threw it. Defensive move.
Why the hell didn't he use his fists?
He was hurt. There's blood and some hair.
Looks like he hit his
head against the wall.
How bad?
Hard enough to daze him.
A blow from behind could
have propelled him forward.
So Anton comes down to empty the
garbage, the skinner clocks him,
he does a header into the wall,
throws the bag as a last ditch.
Skinner tosses him in the car and peels out.
Got tire marks here.
Fuck.
All right, we got a confirmed
missing person. Anton Briggs.
Find a photo. Get his face
out to all patrols and the media.
Set up a tip line.
Pull in some off-duties
to man the phone bank.
Skinner's had him for 24 hours.
How long do you think he can hold out?
Well, the M.E.'s report on the other
victims suggests the skinner starts slow.
Probably to build fear.
Anton's a big guy. A lot of skin.
That's meant to be comforting.
George King, we need to bring him in.
We gotta find him first.
We got bolos out on him all night long.
Haven't found him yet. We
could search his house, though.
We still holding King's
foreman on resisting arrest, right?
He give us anything that'll buy us a warrant?
Mario Astorga clammed up. Too scared of King.
He would rather be deported away from
his family than to talk about King.
- Is that all we got?
- Yeah.
I'll try and finda flexible judge.
Let me know when it comes in.
I'm gonna go sit on King's house.
We'll go siton King's house.
Hey, I want this above board.
Use restraint. Wait on the warrant.
And I hope they find something
because even if we nab King,
we got nothing to hold him on past today.
A day can save a lot of skin.
I keep telling you. You have to listen.
If I knew where Freebo was, I'd tell you.
Don't you fucking understand,
man? It was the cops.
I was... I was fucking bait.
All right, all right, you're right.
I know where he is. I can
show you. I can show you.
All right, listen to me.
He owes you money, right?
He owes you money? I can get you money.
I can find you money.
I don't want your money.
I loaned Freebo that money.
This is about respect.
With your first cut, you had all
night to consider my questions.
This cut, you only have one hour.
And when I return, there'll be no rest.
Use the time to think about
the skin you have left to lose.
Hi, how are you?
Are you screening your calls? Ellen?
I'm surprised you missed the
motion hearing this morning.
So was Chicky Hines.
Of course, Miguel was perfectly
happy to get a continuance.
Uh, listen, if you're sick, I
can bring you over sopa de pollo.
Either way, let me know
you're all right. Okay? Bye.
Miguel went missing last night.
Ellen's missing this morning.
Could be a coincidence.
Patrol's been set up here all night.
King's not inside.
Well, something in there's
gonna tell us where he is.
Warrant should be here soon.
Motherfuck
Anton? Anton, you in there?
Anton, are you in there?
Hey, I don't hear anything.
Yeah, well, I do.
I hear somebody calling for help.
That's probable cause, right?
We're doing this above board.
The warrant's on its way.
Right. Restraint.
- What the fuckare you doing?
- Anton?
Shit.
Hey, you're not the only
oneworking this case, Morgan.
Prado here.
Hey, just checking in.
How'd the motion hearing go?
Continued.
That's too bad.
Oh, no, serendipitous actually.
It worked in my favor.
Listen, you don't have to
keep on checking on me.
Yeah, no, I'm justa concerned friend.
Well, don't be.
In fact, why don't you
meet meat cojimar for lunch?
'Cause I been coming up with
some more, uh, projects.
Another kill so soon?
I can't. I gotta keep an
eye on the situation here.
I heard. The skinner grabbed
upanother victim, huh?
Let me know if I can help. Adios.
Adios.
Miami metro hotline.
What location?
Who am I speaking with?
can you spell that, please?
Anton Briggs' photo hit the media an hour ago.
I'm gonna bring King's employee up
from holding, take another run at him.
Mario Astorga, already in interview two.
- Thought I'd take a stab.
- I can handle it.
I know. But I wanna help.
Tired of standing behind my glass wall.
Well, we can use the help today.
No, I knew, I knew half those hookers
were pre-op trannies, but is it true...
is it true their junk still
works, but nothing comes out?
It's called slug-fucking.
Hello.
Babe. Hey, vice got word you needed extra bodies.
Thought I'd help out.
That's 'cause you're the best.
Hey, hey, get a room.
Actually, no, don't.
Miami metro tip-line.
Vince, you got a second?
What the fuck are you doing?
What? Helping out on my day off.
You're welcome.
Good place to meet chicks
from other departments.
Yeah, well, that's my chick. I don't
want you talking your filth at her.
Whoa, whoa, hold up, gaucho.
I didn't bring that up.
- She did.
- Bullshit.
Seriously. She's like the Wikipedia of perv.
I gotta find me a girlfriend from vice.
She's awesome.
Fuck. Fucking nothing.
King could be anywhere.
Or right here.
Holy shit.
Remember. We need his cooperation.
Restraint, right.
What are you doingat my house?
Yeah, Mr. King, we have a
warrant to search the premises.
What are you looking for?
More like who. You wanna tell
us where you've been all night?
Oh, I work, ma'am. Nights.
Mornings. Trees keep growing.
It's a good business. I'm
only home to have breakfast.
You wanna grab a bagel down at the station?
Answers some questions for us?
I'm happy to answer right here, sir.
What, you got somewhere you need to be?
- Trees.
- They'll wait.
Am I under arrest, sir?
No, but we can hold you for questioning.
For the day.
what are you, a lawyer?
Oh, no, wait, I forgot.
You're a fucking tree trimmer.
I moved to this country
for its amazing liberties.
- I know my rights.
- Great.
George King is hanging
you out to dry, Mario.
I thought you might want a chance
I've seen the fear.
An inch away from death fear.
It'd be a shame to leave your
wife and your little baby behind.
His is real.
What makes you so scary, George King?
You miss your country, George?
I like this country, sir.
I like Miami, sir.
Nicaragua can be a rough place, huh?
You in the military down there?
Death squads, contras.
You woulda been about the right
age to get caught up in that.
You learn a few things there, George?
I learn respect, sir.
No interrogation techniques?
Maybe a little snatch and grab.
What do they call that? Renditioning?
Oh, I don't know that, ma'am.
Ma'am, sir.
You did learn respect.
Did you show any fucking respect to
Wendell when you tore his skin off?
How about Anton when you
bashed him over the goddamn head?
Morgan, you want a coffee?
Why don't you get a coffee?
Yeah. Sure.
He looks harmless, doesn't he?
They usually do.
I don't know. Maybe he's not our guy.
Well, you should trust
your instincts on this one.
This one of your creepy insights?
Why does it always haveto be creepy?
Fucking tell me.
He's heldl ife and death in his hands.
He likes it.
I knew it.
So how do I crack this sick fuck's brain?
From what I've read about these sick fucks,
they usually have some sort of code.
I'd say disrespect is high
on his list of violations.
Maybe if you came at him with deference.
Deference, huh?
Yeah, think about it. Hey, lieutenant.
I heard you say your friend Ellen
is ill. Was it a stomach thing?
Because I just read this article...
I don't knowwhat it is. I
haven't heard back from her.
I left her three messages.
I'm a little worried.
Yeah, me too.
I hope she didn't get in
an accident or something.
Excuse me. I have an errand to run.
A home office.
If she were sick, this is where she'd be.
Her car's here.
She could have gone for a really long walk.
Or borrowed a friend's car.
Or maybe La Guerta's right and Ellen is
comatose in some hospital, post-accident.
One can hope.
Not that there are any
signs of foul play here.
But Harry did raise me to be paranoid.
Blood. Damn it.
No. Miguel wouldn't do this.
We agreed Ellen Wolf is innocent.
Hello.
It's just blood. There's no body.
He would even know what to do with one.
I never taught him how to dispose...
as far as Miguel knows, the best place to
dispose of a body is beneath an open grave.
Good thinking.
Hello.
Uh, set-ups are in the kitchen.
Miguel?
Hi. Any bites?
No, just nosy neighbors so far.
Syl's office said that she would
be here. Is she out back or...
No, she wasn't feeling up to an
open house, so I'm sitting it for her.
Well, you're a good friend.
Here. You should have these.
How about I make sure Syl gets them?
Miguel.
Flowers are a good start,
but can I be honest?
I like honest.
- You're an idiot.
- That's honest.
You were smart enough to ask her to marry you,
and she's still that same fantastic woman.
You don't think I know that?
Well, you're not acting that way.
I am not having a goddamn affair, okay.
- All right, let's say that's the truth.
- It is.
Either way, you violated her trust.
I just needed space.
I've got everything falling apart around me
now, you know, Oscar, Ramon, now my cases...
and the same things are falling apart
for her, because she's your partner.
You're a wise person, aren't you?
Well, if I am, it's only because I've
learned from my many, many mistakes.
You have insight.
And I tell you what.
I'm gonna follow your lead.
So point the way.
Mr. King, I understand that
respect is very important to you.
Yes, ma'am.
And I'm sure you feel that
people have to earn your respect.
Yes, ma'am.
I feel like you've earned this.
What's the matter, little gardener? Huh?
You feel disrespected?
You'll get used to it in prison
because your foreman Mario's next door,
and he is spilling his guts.
You are so sure he's afraid of you. Why?
What did you do to him?
What did you doto Anton? What did you do?
Morgan!
Fuck.
Help!
Help me!
You know, we're supposed
to be working together.
You keep going off half-cocked.
How am I supposed to trust you?
You trust me? That's unbelievable.
You're lucky Batista wasn't watching the
monitors. What the fuck were you thinking?
I was thinking about Anton.
You oughta try it some time.
I want to find him just as bad as you do.
If you gave a shitabout anton, you
wouldn't have made himyour fake C.I.
And he wouldn't be messed up in this.
You're the one too busy boning him to
provide him with protective surveillance.
You are so crossing the line right now.
Am I?
You knew Anton was in town.
And I fucking told him to call it in.
You should have called
it in your fucking self.
I know. It's my fault.
No, you're right.
I used him. I...
just fucking used him.
We can only hold George
King for a few more hours.
We better get back to work.
Schedule says there are four funerals today.
Graves back-hoed last night.
That's four miguel could have chosen from.
She's not here. That's one down.
That blood might not even belong to Ellen.
Could be a client's blood.
Or the previous owner's.
He did it. Miguel really did it.
And I taught him how.
I guided him to this.
I created... this.
I'm sorry.
Miguel's making his own choices now.
Look who he chose.
She didn't deserve this.
You can say it.
Won't change anything, Dex,
Whether I told you so or not.
Easier to accept it.
'Cause there'll be plenty
more where Ellen came from.
No, there won't.
Hey, Miguel, is it too
late to grab that lunch?
So what do you think of
this George King sicko?
Skinner suspect?
I gotta go from here to your precinct
to discuss whether we're gonna
file charges against this guy.
- You think he's the guy?
- He's the guy.
Skinner.
Well, if the law can't
get him, you and I can.
In fact, I could have this guy
out on the streets in a few hours.
You need some help on this one,
or is this another solo project?
We agreed to leave Ellen Wolf alone.
Technically, we agreed not to
kill her together. And we didn't.
- Technically? - I know.
That's... that's bullshit.
I didn't tell you because
I know you wouldn't approve.
'Cause she wasn't guilty.
Apparently, we have a different
definition of that word.
You got rid of her
because she got in your way.
Whatever happened to serving justice?
Is that really why you do
this, Dex? To serve justice?
We don't have to pretend with each other.
- That's what I thought.
- Okay.
I should have told you.
It was a chicken shit thing to
do, and I abused your trust...
a trust, by the way,
that wasn't easy to earn.
That's not lost on me.
I gave you my shirt
linking me to Freebo's death.
I wish I had another one to prove to you
how important this partnership is to me.
I'd take a little remorse.
You would know that I don't feel it.
Yeah, you'll feel it if you get caught.
I didn't leave any evidence.
They're just gonna think it
was one of her scumbag clients.
Right. Right, just another lowlife
who beat and stabbed an innocent woman.
Again, different definitions.
Dex.
This is the nature of a real friendship.
We're gonna disagree.
And when we do, we just go our own way.
No, no more individual projects.
Individuality is what makes America great.
I don't think that's what
our forefathers had in mind.
Look. I'm a big boy.
I know what I'm doing.
Eventually, you're gonna trust that too.
I'll see you over at the precinct.
He thinks he's untouchable.
He's not. It's time he learned that.
Probably not a lot of leads on that screen.
King's a ghost.
He grabbed Anton without a single security
camera in the area picking up him or his truck.
There's not one shot to implicate him.
So we'll have to get it out of King.
You gonna let Quinn do it on his own.
My time is better spent here.
Away from people.
You know, someone, a good friend, actually
told me I had a big wall around me.
I thought it made me a better cop.
I don't think it did.
They look at him and see a defender
of truth, justice, and the American way.
I see a man about to learn a hard lesson.
tire tracks in the alley are
consistent with King's truck.
And several other thousand
trucks in the Miami metro area.
King's company trims trees.
Now trimmed trees were found in
every one of the victims' homes.
That's the lead that nailed him.
I don't know about nailed.
The trees at my place just got trimmed too.
- Yeah, but Mario Astorga...
- We're talking about a foreman, right?
A foreman who's terrified of his boss.
You can arrest my boss
on that same evidence.
He's the fucking guy.
- Sir.
- miguel. May I?
We really need your help on this one.
And you do owe us for getting Ramon off.
I do. But I can't very well charge
Mr. King with assault on a palm tree.
You have your ways, Miguel.
You've bent rules before.
Getting people lost in the system.
We need to buy time for Anton Briggs.
For you. I'll do everything in my power.
We'll be right there.
Showtime.
Dex, get your kit. You too, Masuka.
- Hey, it's called off-duty.
- Not anymore.
You two, you stay on King. Don't
let up. We got another body.
Anton?
A female at the cemetery.
- Cause of death?
- Take your pick.
Sever beating, strangulation...
plus three stab wounds.
Whoever did this was not a fan.
You have no idea.
Think our killer's a pro.
I haven't seen many
body dumps this clean.
I made sure of that.
Miguel getting caught isn't
part of the lesson plan.
Angel, don't let her see this.
No, they said it was her.
But it's not, is it?
Maria, I'm sorry.
No, I don't believe...
- Oh, my God.
- Walk with me.
Too many people are affected
when the innocent die.
That is partof the lesson plan.
No one is untouchable. I
learned that the hard way.
So will Miguel.
His own vulnerability is about
to become very real to him...
after the stage show ends.
- They won't find anything.
- I know.
So you're just making a point.
Am I?
We follow the code. Or else.
There are a lot of other subtleties, but if that's
what you've gleaned, then yeah, that's my point.
You're a wise person, aren't you?
- You're being facetious.
- No, no, you have insight.
I'd be a fool not to follow your lead.
I thinkyou're gonna save my life.
Is this real?
I should go make a statement to the press.
I wouldn't want anyone getting
ideas about killing lawyers.
Lesson learned. It seems.
Oh, good. Good. You're here.
Come here. Taste this.
This one.
And now this one.
Which one?
I'm more in the mood for steak.
No, this is for the wedding cake.
We have to choose one.
Chocolate or hazelnut?
Is Sylvia still here?
No, because of me.
I intervened.
Apparently, I'm a very wise person.
Apparently?
According to Miguel.
He came to the open house
I was sitting for Syl.
- Really?
- We talked for a while.
Actually, I talked. I just
...I gave himsome insight.
Insight.
He said he thinks I could...
Save his life.
Every word, bullshit.
When did he start lying?
With Ellen? Before her?
So, chocolate?
What about that shirt?
The shirt.
Dexter, what's wrong?
I have to look at some blood.
Evidence. For a crime.
Hazelnut.
Maria, why don't you
head home, get some rest?
I can't. I have to...
- Do something.
- Sure.
I'm here if you need me. Okay?
Tell me that we're close on the skinner.
'Cause this Ellen Wolf
thing is about to take over.
Still running down tips,but
they're bullshit so far.
They're gonna keep being bullshit
because no one saw King take Anton.
What about Mario Astorga?
As tight-lipped as King.
Maybe I can help.
She could use a win right now.
we all could.
You gonna charge King?
Not with what you have.
We release him, he's in the wind.
Anton's dead.
So has King asked for legal counsel yet?
King knows we have nothing on
him. Why would he wastethe money?
Well, technically, if he's not represented,
I can't walk in there and offer him any deals.
Not on the record, anyway.
Come on. No one'll know the difference.
still a year from now, the recorded
document shows upon CNN, uh-uh.
Actually, that camera's been on the fritz.
It wouldn't surprise me if
it didn't record anything.
Freebo's blood.
The link between his murder and Miguel.
If I go down, I can take Miguel with me.
Mutual assurance. A symbol of trust.
Fuck. That's it?
No way we're gonna let that monster walk.
Are we?
I hope we meet again.
I'd like to get to know you better.
But how well can you really know someone?
How much do you want to know?
There's gotta be something.
All we got is Mario, who won't say shit.
I mean, we can start skinning him
ourselves before he'd talk.
Morgan, we're not skinning Mario.
I got a better idea.
Wanna share with the whole class?
No, just you. I need a partner on this.
Here we are. Home sweet home.
It's too bad Anton won't ever
get to do that. Thanks to you.
What?
Los arboles.
Holy shit.
You told him I revealed things?
We didn't tell him shit. He knew you were
in holding. He must have thought you caved.
I didn't tell anyone anything.
Look, I'm sorry. We didn't mean to get
your family caught up in this, all right?
We'll do everything we can to help you.
What can you do? Nothing.
You're right. We don't
even know where this guy is.
You gotta help me, or I
can't do anything to help you.
Then that's it. I'm sorry.
Wait! He has a building.
We went through all of his holdings.
There's no record of him owning any building.
He rents it with cash.
He had me go there and pay once.
- He's trying to grow trees to sell.
- Where?
On 164th under the highway.
It's all I know.
Mi familia.
Go inside. Lock the door.
I'll send a patrol car. Go.
- It worked. Get in.
- Thank you.
Anton! Anton, are you in there?
Anton?
Fuck restraint. Here.
Morgan! Get out of the way.
It's me. It's okay. You're safe.
I need an ambulance at the 164 and the 94 asap.
Get an APB out on George King.
You found me. You found me.
You can't get away from me that easily.
And the results are...
I, uh...
Come on. I'll take you home.
I can't go home.
There's too much silence.
I know.
You don't want to have to
think about what she went through.
- Only to realize that she's really gone.
- Don't.
- Pero, corazon, she's gone.
Okay?
And that's gonna hurt like hell.
I know that too.
But you have friends.
You got me. I'm right here.
Okay? I'm right here for
you. To get you through.
It's not Freebo's blood.
It's not even human.
It's bovine. Cow's blood.
He's been using me the whole time.
I didn't create a monster,
I was used by one.
He used me.
Miguel!
Nine holes tomorrow?
You bet.
Today I keep up the pretense.
But soon, maybe tomorrow, Miguel
will know exactly how I feel.
Because finally there's an
emotion I don't have to fake.
Today, I feel something real