What is this?!
Excuse me.
Can somebody please tell me
what's going on here?
We're collecting material.
For?
For anything that might be
pertinent to the manhunt.
What manhunt?
Manhunt for who?
You're kidding, right?
Look, there's nothing. If you're looking
for Mulder, you're wasting your time.
- Are you listening to me?
- I'm not the man to talk to.
Well, then whose stupid idea is this?
Yeah, well, somebody might have
had the courtesy to tell me.
There are agents tearing apart
Mulder's office...
...who say they're part of
an FBI manhunt.
I know. I heard.
Believe me, this is not my idea.
I just found out about it myself.
They're not going to find Mulder this way.
You know that and I know that.
I told you last night, I will find him.
I'm going to do that.
Okay?
Now, I want you just to cool out.
I don't want you doing...
- ...anything to upset your pregnancy.
- Look, I don't understand.
You are the Assistant Director.
Who is going over your head on this?
Our brand-new deputy director.
A.D. Skinner, Agent Scully.
Thanks for getting right over.
I don't want to lose any time.
We have one of our own missing...
...and the only acceptable outcome is
that we find him safe and alive.
- I'm sure the two of you agree.
- That goes without saying, sir.
Good.
This comes at a stressful time,
with my new appointment.
But I'm thankful for your
cooperation in the hunt for Mulder.
Our cooperation?
With due respect,
there aren't two people better qualified...
...to be directing this action, sir.
Right now, you and A.D. Skinner
are the two primary witnesses...
...to Mulder's disappearance.
I want your statement taken asap.
You make us out to be suspects, sir.
Taken by who?
My task force leader on this,
Special Agent John Doggett.
He's waiting to hear from you now.
One more thing.
Anything leaves this building...
...about aliens or alien abductions...
...or any other nonsense that might cast
the Bureau in a ridiculous light, ...
...hey, you can forget about
looking for Agent Mulder.
You'll both be looking
for new jobs.
That's all.
I don't believe this.
This isn't about finding Mulder--
this is about Kersh covering the FBI's ass.
Why do I get the feeling they'd be
happy if we never found him at all?
Look... I saw what I saw.
I have to make a statement in there.
I'm not going to tell them it didn't happen.
Well, you heard Kersh.
They don't want the truth.
You give them the truth,
and they'll hang you with it.
They can hang me with a lie, too.
I'm not going to sell Mulder out.
What good are you to Mulder...
...if you give them the power
to ruin your career?
We will find him.
Assistant Director,
you can come on back with me.
Agent Scully, I'll ask you to please
wait on the wall until we call you.
Water?
It could be a wait.
Thank you.
- Weren't you his partner? Mulder?
- Yes.
I guess nobody's beyond
suspicion on this thing.
Why are they talking to you?
Me? I knew Mulder back a bit.
They're developing a working
profile-- character background.
I'd say they have all the character
profile they need on him.
Certainly his reputation.
I doubt we agents ever really truly
know each other even our partners.
Not at the end of the day.
Their real lives, their friends, girlfriends,
deeply personal things, issues.
I think I know Mulder as
much as anybody.
Yeah, probably so.
I always took the rumors
with a grain of salt.
- What rumors are those?
- Well, you know.
Well, that, from the beginning he never
felt a real trust with you, ...
...that you were ambitious.
Where'd that come from?
There are women here at the Bureau
that he would confide in.
I don't know if you knew that or not.
No.
- When was this?
- I don't know, it's just talk.
So, what do you think happened?
To Mulder?
What's your theory?
What's my theory?
My theory is you don't
know Mulder at all.
You never did.
"John Doggett."
Kersh's task force leader.
You might have just
introduced yourself.
Well, I was getting around to it.
Nice to meet you, Agent Doggett.
Hi, this is Margaret Scully.
Please leave a message.
Mom, it's Dana. I, uh...
I'm sorry I haven't called you
in a while. I've been...
...busy with work and, um,
with something ...
...else that I should probably
tell you about in person.
I mean, I don't even know if
you're in town or...
...if you're checking your messages.
But, um...
But I really need to see you
and talk to you.
There's a lot of stuff that's going on
with me right now and, um...
...and I just really need to talk.
Mom?
- John Doggett.
- You stay out of my business!
- What? Who is this?
- You better have a court order!
- For what? Who is this?
- How many phones are you tapping?
How many agents are you
doing surveillance on?
Is this Agent Scully?
Thank you. You just answered
all my questions.
Stop there! Right there!
Now come on through the
window nice and easy.
Okay, I'm coming.
It's me, your landlord.
I started fixing the
antennae on the roof, and...
I'm sorry, Mr. Coeben.
I'm sorry. There was a man.
There was someone in the building.
Did you see anyone?
Yeah, yeah, you know him,
he works with you.
Tall guy-- brown hair.
Who?
- You don't mean Mulder?
- Yeah, Mulder.
Mulder?
Are you in here?
- It took some serious voodoo.
- Major satellite hacking.
- But we got your data.
- What am I looking at?
You're seeing real-time images right
off the JPL Topex Poseidon.
We're wired right into the dish.
We're not able to find raw data
with UFO activity on it.
But Langly was able to hack into
the data storage here...
...and pull up something
just as tasty.
You're looking at UFO activity in the
Pacific Northwest just prior to Mulder's abduction.
All these markers correspond with
reported alien abductions.
- It's a regular shopping spree.
- So Mulder's abduction...
Was a UFO whistle stop on the
way to the next pickup.
Where? Where's the UFO activity
after Mulder's abduction?
Like we said, we can't tell.
Not from the data we're pulling down.
Look, if we can figure out where
that ship was going, ...
...where it was gonna be,
we've got a chance to find Mulder.
- Got a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
- You fly, Agent Doggett?
- Flying is for birds and baseballs. USMC, sir.
In Vietnam we used to fly night
sorties ten feet above the treetops.
Before night vision,
before fly-by-wire.
600 miles an hour and all we had
was an idiot gauge and our wits.
Guys used to say they only knew their
altitude by the smell of the V.C. rice pots.
You've come a long way, sir.
Using all the same instincts.
What can I do for you, Agent?
This task force-- the search for Mulder,
I'm running it, right?
- You're the man in charge.
- No one else is involved?
Someone out there acting under
orders from another office?
I think I'd know, Agent.
What prompts the question?
My idiot gauge. My wits.
You got a chance to shine here, John.
Stand in the spotlight.
Show them all you're an ace.
- What are you doing here?
- I could ask you the same.
- I came by to feed Mulder's fish.
- And then you got tired and decided...
...to take a nap.
You've got a way about you,
Agent Doggett.
That might have worked with the NYPD...
...but you're talking to a fellow FBI agent
now and I'd appreciate some respect.
Respect like you showed me
over the phone?
Give a little, get a little, Agent Scully.
Who ambushed me with the phony chitchat
about Mulder and then...
- ...put a wiretap on my phone?
- That's B.S.
And now you're following me.
I just came by to feed the fish.
What do you want to get on me,
Agent Doggett?
What is it you hope to find?
I'm just trying to find Mulder.
You wouldn't know where to look.
It's in the desk, middle drawer.
I know the answer, Agent Scully.
- I don't even know the question.
- What happened to Mulder?
I know what you're gonna say or not
because you think I'm the big bad wolf.
Do you really believe it?
You think by talking in circles,
I'm just going to get dizzy and...
...and blurt it out--
this so-called answer?
- That he was abducted by aliens?
- You said it. I didn't.
I guess I just find it hard
to swallow that a scientist, ...
...a serious person, could buy that.
Ever see an alien, Agent Scully?
You want me to go on record?
I will go on record to say this:
that I have seen things
that I cannot explain.
I have observed phenomena
that I cannot deny.
And that as a scientist and
a serious person...
...it is a badge of honor not
to dismiss these things...
...because someone thinks
they're B.S.
So you think he was abducted?
- I'm just trying to find him.
- Then what are you doing here?
Trying to figure these out.
I found them in his desk there.
Car rental receipts on
Agent Mulder's Visa.
Four consecutive weekends in May.
Same mileage each trip--
370 miles, 375 miles...
Where was he going?
I don't know.
Like I said, maybe you really
didn't know your partner.
John Doggett.
Agent Mulder at the FBI?
Assistant Director, follow me.
- What's going on?  What is this?
- Mr. Skinner, right this way, please.
You can talk with Agent
Scully after we're done.
Have a seat.
Assistant Director, someone came into this office
after hours and removed some material.
Files. We don't know exactly
what just yet.
Who?
The office here is secured by a pass-card lock...
...and whoever came in last night used
the pass-card belonging to Agent Mulder.
You think Agent Mulder took the files?
We're wondering about
Agent Mulder's state of mind.
In your statement,
you said prior to his disappearance...
...Agent Mulder had felt
threatened by the FBI.
No, that's not what I said.
I said he felt the X-Files were
threatened by budget cutting.
Is there anything you're not telling us
about Agent Mulder or his attitude?
Do you think he'd ever
retaliate against the FBI?
- Agent Mulder was only after the truth.
- As are we, Assistant Director.
Agent Scully tells us
she was home last night.
We see from your phone log,
you were here until at least after 10:00.
You think I came in here last night
using Agent Mulder's pass-card?
You were the last person to
see Mulder.
You and Agent Scully.
Skinner is telling the truth.
I believe him.
That still doesn't tell us who
used Mulder's card to get in there.
You think it was Mulder?
I showed you those car
rental receipts.
Well, now I find Agent Mulder's Visa was used
two days ago in Raleigh, North Carolina.
Two days ago?
By who? For what?
Flowers. Automatic debit to
a mortuary there.
Mulder's mother is buried
in Raleigh.
That's the reason he was
going every weekend.
It's one reason.
I don't know what to think.
I don't believe it, Dana.
It just doesn't make any sense to me.
All right.
I got some light on this.
Maybe you can help me out here,
Agent Scully.
What is it?
Agent Mulder's medical records--
recent stuff, over the last year.
Did you know about a medical
condition? Either of you?
No.
A year ago, Agent Mulder was
hospitalized. Ring a bell?
Something to do with his brain?
- His temporal lobe.
- An undiagnosable condition, it says.
Irregular brain activity.
All right, but he recovered.
There was a full recovery.
Was there?
You know Mulder; he would've
told us if there was anything.
Would he?
Would he tell you about this?
About his headstone?
Mulder was dying.
- What?
- It's all right here.
For a year, he was going to doctors.
There's a clear record of his decline.
How well did you really know him?
- How far would Mulder go?
- How far would he go for what?
The truth-- his truth.
Whatever it was he was trying to prove,
how bad did he need to prove it?
- It was his whole life.
- What are you trying to say?
That Agent Mulder found himself
in a place none of us want to go.
Life-threatened, work-threatened,
and all for naught.
Nothing proven.
The effort in vain.
No mark left.
Unless he rolled the dice,
took one big last chance to make it.
You think that Mulder was here?
That he broke in to
steal those files?
Broke into your apartment;
stole your computer.
Took his own computer.
Gathering it up.
To what?
To prove it?
Or cover it up.
Create doubt.
I get Mulder, I get him.
I understand obsession,
believe me.
But the question is:
how far would he go?
I mean, so far as to stage his
own disappearance?
I know what I saw.
I not going to sit here
and listen to this.
I watched it happen.
Agent Mulder?!
Please don't report that.
Don't know what good it
would do me.
Doesn't help me find Mulder.
No, it's not good enough.
These are records of
microburst activity.
What we read is UFO activity
since Mulder's abduction.
- I think this is a waste of time.
- No, it's not. Just look at them.
I'm looking, and what I'm seeing is
activity all over the southwestern states.
That's right.
Mulder disappeared in the
Pacific Northwest.
And if Mulder is on that ship,
this is where he is now.
Here?
In the Arizona desert?
This is what we have.
Okay. Say this is true...
Then how do we even
begin to start finding him?
Maybe with whoever it is they're
looking to abduct next.
- Hey, we're only trying to help.
- We're only trying to find Mulder.
That's it.
- It just came to me.
- What?
What you saw,
why they took Mulder, ...
...why they're in Arizona now--
it all makes sense.
Why do people refuse to believe
in aliens and UFOs...
...after all these years of sightings
and eyewitness accounts?
- Why?
- Because there's no real proof.
Because, maybe, if there are aliens
they're simply going around...
...and they're... and they're removing
all of the evidence before it becomes proof.
This isn't Mulder who's going around
and collecting this stuff. It's them.
Then why Arizona?
Because they are looking to find that
which is not in my computer...
...or Mulder's computer or in the files
that were removed from the FBI.
They are looking to find the whereabouts
of good, hard proof.
That in this case exists in a person, ...
...in a boy named Gibson Praise.
This photograph's a few years old
but take a good look because...
...the objective in this case
has been reframed.
Subject's name is Gibson Andrew Praise.
A child prodigy, pint-sized chess
champion who Mulder and Scully...
...first investigated in 1997 after
a failed attempt on the boy's life.
His files were the ones we now believe
were stolen from this office.
In his investigation Agent Mulder
came to believe the boy...
...was experiencing abnormal
brain activity.
Unexplained activity.
In his field notes here he says
Gibson Praise could, and I quote:
"read people's thoughts."
Agent Mulder went so far in one
report to claim...
...that the boy may have
alien physiology.
Agent Mulder may be looking for the boy
who was last seen in Arizona.
So maybe to find Mulder we first have
to look for Gibson Praise.
Let's go, people!
Let's move!
How do you want this handled?
I want you to put that
on every TV station, ...
...post office, and fax machine
in Arizona and the southwest.
I want to make that face famous.
You better?
I need some navigation.
How to start looking for a 12-year-old kid
in the middle of the Arizona desert.
Well, there aren't a whole
lot of choices.
We got a turn off coming up in five miles.
I take it or keep going straight?
Gibson Praise was last seen here...
...at a power plant about
60 miles outside of Phoenix.
But all the satellite data shows activity
here about 100 miles to the north.
What's out there?
Well, according to this map...
...a whole lot of nothing.
This is Special Agent Crane
calling for task force leader.
Yeah, this is John Doggett.
Just confirmed a location
on this kid.
He's at a school for the deaf
in a place called Flemingtown.
Little dot on the map about
90 miles from where I am now.
I just talked to the school
principal there.
- Is the kid in school now?
- Yeah, he lives at the school.
All right, have the principal
take him out of class and...
...put him someplace where he can
keep an eye on him until we arrive.
Got it. Gonna take me an hour,
an hour and 15 to get there.
All right, well, I'm going to see
if I can cut some time off that.
It's a school 20 minutes from here.
Yes, sir, in his science class.
Is it important enough to take
him away from his studies?
I'll go and get him
right now.
FLEMINGTOWN
School for the Deaf
Where's the boy?
You're just going to have to slow down and
explain a few things to us before we let you...
- Is he down there?
- He's in my office.
Hi. Um ... we're looking for a
boy named Gibson Praise.
- Now who are you?
- Kid went out the window.
- What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?!
Trying to find Mulder.
Kid's on the move.
Spread out!
The kid's on the loose!
You have the photo! Move!
Let me go!
Let the boy go!
Let him go, Mulder!
TO BE CONTINUED