[ Clears Throat ]
I'm on the Clay Street platform.
Got a fare jumper.
White male, shaved head, 20s.
Possible 10-13.
[ Brakes Squealing ]
[ Bell Dings ]
Offiicer Philbrick,
all clear.
[ Man Screams ]
[ Electrical Crackling ]
Deputy Chief Karras, Transit Police.
This is Lieutenant Bianco.
- You're Scully and Doggett, right?
- Yes.
Is the assessment team here?
Downstairs,
waiting 45 minutes.
Where the hell have
you two been?
Agent Scully needed
to examine the body...
of the victim fiirst.
Who's missing
the picture here?
I got lots of people
can examine the body.
What I need from
the FBI now...
is a time frame.
A time frame?
One of the main arteries...
of the Boston public transport system
has been closed...
for exactly 11 hours
and 4 minutes.
My phone is ringing
off the hook right now...
with calls
from the press.
I got 100,000
pissed-off commuters...
who were late to work
this morning who are going to be...
even more pissed off
if they can't get home.
And I got one extremely
pissed-off mayor...
paying me to do one thing--
keep the damn trains running.
We appreciate the pressure
that you're under, but--
No. It's you guys
better kick it in the ass.
The afternoon rush
starts in fiive hours.
Do what you've got to do...
but this line is going back
in operation at 4:00 p.m.
I'm afraid
you can't do that.
Oh, yes, I can.
You've got a dead man...
who's got over 1l3 of his body tissue
completely eaten away...
and until we fiigure
out how and why...
that tunnel cannot
be reopened.
We understand
the FBI's need to do...
a thorough investigation,
but as I see it...
the facts of this case
are actually pretty simple.
Simple?
The train briefly lost power...
during which time an assailant
killed a Boston transit cop.
That man is still at large.
An assailant using what?
Acid, lye.
Your examination of the victim
must've told us something.
No, it didn't,
that's the thing.
Until we culture the tissue
and run the proper tests...
we're not going to know
what killed him...
or if it can infect others.
[ Bianco ]
The Centers for Disease Control...
had robotic sniffers
in the tunnel all night.
They found no trace of
biological or chemical agents.
So let's clear this up.
What we're looking
for is a man--
a cop-killer.
Single suspect.
At least that's
your cover story.
That's what you're
telling the press.
[ Karras ]
The question is...
can you get me the killer
or an explanation...
in less than fiive hours?
Because hell or high water...
this subway reopens
at 4:00 p.m. sharp.
Now, let's go.
Steven Melnick...
Transportation Authority's...
chief structural engineer.
He built this tunnel.
[ Melnick ]
I only oversaw construction of it...
four years ago.
But I know every
square inch down there.
Dr. Hellura Lyle,
special pathogens branch, CDC.
We were told you folks said...
that the tunnel was
clear of pathogens.
Well, I guess I'm just here
for the moral support.
We're just covering our bases.
What base are they covering?
[ Karras ]
Agent Scully is a medical doctor...
who they tell me
has a lot of experience...
with equivocal death.
[ Melnick ]
Equivocal?
I mean, you're dead
or you're not, right?
Deaths for which there may be...
many explanations
or for which...
an explanation may be
hard to fiind.
And what about you?
I'm just a good shot.
Well, good.
Now that we're bosom buddies...
let's get this show
on the road.
You need some help
with that?
No.
- You're going in without me.
- What?
I don't know what kind
of games are being played...
but I'm going to be
much more effective...
analyzing the situation
from up here.
Yeah, but I'm just
a tagalong here.
This is your thing.
You've got all
the experience.
You've got capable people
with you, Agent Doggett.
What I need down there
are eyes and ears.
Okay.
I'll be your...
eyes and ears.
Only I wish someone
would tell me...
what the hell it is...
I'm supposed to
be looking for.
Third rail's powering down.
You're clear to enter
the subway floor...
and as long as you stay
on this line...
there should be no risk
of accidental shock...
or electrocution.
You copy that,
Agent Doggett?
Yep, we're on the tunnel floor.
Hope you got yourself a nice
clear picture, Agent Scully.
We got you every step
of the way.
[ Lyle ]
Ooh, it feels like Atlanta in August.
Yeah, it's the middle
of winter.
How come
it's so hot down here?
They shut down ventilation
last night.
Normally you have almost
a million cubic feet...
of fresh air per minute
pushing through here...
but now we're in a sweat box.
[ Lyle ]
Aren't we lucky?
Hot, sticky and
crawling in the dark.
All so every commuter
in Boston...
can get home
to watch Survivor II.
I wonder why they shut down
the ventilation...
if it's a man we're
supposed to be looking for.
You doubt that so much,
Agent Doggett, why bring a gun?
Agent Doggett, you still
reading me down there?
Like a songbird,
Agent Scully.
[ Man Yells ]
My shirt, my neck... get it off!.
What's going on?
[ Melnick ]
Something's burning!
[ Bianco ]
Just hold still.
What just happened?
I don't know.
He's got a burn
on his neck...
silver-dollar sized.
You get seepage
down here?
Yeah, constantly.
This line was tunneled through
landfiill adjacent to the harbor.
It's a part of
the big dig.
There was a puddle
20 yards back.
You hear that, Agent Scully?
Yeah. Ask Dr. Lyle if
she can get a sample.
[ Doggett ]
We need you to get a sample.
[ Lyle ]
I'm on it.
Maybe it's not a man...
we're looking for...
but some sort of toxic leak.
We were told there are...
no contaminants down here.
Tell her I'm sending this.
[ High-pitched Beeping ]
We're transmitting.
[ Doggett ]
You on line, Agent Scully?
Yeah, I got it.
I'm getting a reading.
Sample analysis is showing...
carbon, bromide, boron
and calcium.
It's just seawater.
Let me get on the phone.
Maybe I can get
a molecular analysis.
Four hours, Agent Scully.
Take it easy.
Agent Doggett!
What?
What is it?
There's somebody in the tunnel.
All right, let's go fiind him.
Open this line in four hours...
passengers will get more
than just a ride--
they'll get
a steam bath to boot.
What are you doing?
If this guy was
going to shoot me...
he already had his chance.
Besides,
I'm sweating like a pig.
Mr. Melnick,
what's this?
It's a tunnel from
the old system.
Been shut down
for years.
You see this, Agent Scully?
You have this
on your graphic?
Yeah.
It's a fork
in the line.
That line is obsolete.
It's been gutted
and decommissioned.
How far from here to where
the train lost power, Agent Scully?
[ Scully ]
It's about a mile up the main tunnel.
He's going to waste valuable time
going in there.
[ Scully ]
Agent Doggett.
I'm just taking a look.
All right,
let's get out of here.
Mr. Melnick...
what's your call?
You think there's
any good reason...
to pursue this section?
Lots of places to hide in here.
[ Doggett ]
Dr. Lyle?
Agent Doggett, look out!
Agent Doggett, what happened?
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Nah, give me a minute.
What hit me?
Well, he came at you
like some kind of phantom.
[ Scully ]
What did?
Agent Doggett.
- Would you call that equivocal?
- Agent Scully...
Uh, okay, I see it.
Um, I'm going to need some data.
Agent Scully needs some data.
[ Lyle ]
I'm already on it.
I think this is the guy that
killed Offiicer Philbrick.
[ Lyle ]
I'm transmitting some photos.
[ Doggett ]
Here comes your data...
Agent Scully.
Oh, my God.
Where you going?
I think I just saw something.
- What's the problem?
- There's no problem.
This man fiits the description
called in by my transit cop.
We found what
we were looking for.
Let's get him wrapped up
and go home.
See it?
There's something
on the floor.
[ Doggett ]
Agent Scully...
we got bodies.
Looks like three males.
Agent Scully?
Yeah, I see them.
Can you get any closer?
Smell's a little overpowering.
They've been here for a while.
Looks like someone wrapped them up
and stashed them down here.
Can you get them uncovered?
They look like squatters,
from the way they're dressed.
I'm not sure
I want to touch these.
I see signs
of the same tissue degradation...
we saw in the other victims.
We may have a contagion here
after all.
[ Bianco ]
What did she say?
Dr. Lyle, down here.
Oh.
The CDC may be wrong.
Somebody's over here!
Agent Doggett?
Whatever she saw--
What did you see?
Somebody out here
just took off.
I don't see where.
Look, we're done
down here.
Let's get this show on the road.
Agent Doggett...
Hold it, Lieutenant.
Agent Doggett, if there's
somebody else down there...
you're going to need
to fiind them.
What are you
doing, Agent Scully?
Get those people out.
""Those people''
just found three dead bodies...
and I want to know
what happened to them.
Look, they are in...
an obsolete,
decommissioned tunnel.
I'll get a crew
down in there tonight...
after rush hour.
You don't understand.
They could be infected
and contagious.
With what? Seawater?
You are being
irrational here.
The CDC says there are...
no contaminants.
I'm going to take
their word on it.
Then who are those dead men
and how did they die?
Probably tunnel rats.
Squatters attacked by the same man
who killed my transit cop.
Then take a look at the man...
who fiits the description
of your killer, okay?
Just look at his injuries.
He died the same way.
There is something down there...
and I am not going
to risk bringing it up here...
before I fiigure out what it is!
Agent Scully...
Yeah?
What do you want us to do?
I want you to leave those bodies
where you found them...
and go after whoever it is
who's in that tunnel.
We need to know whether he is
causing this...
or if he's infected himself.
Either way,
he may kill more people.
I'm sure Dr. Lyle will agree.
All right,
we just got our order.
We're going to continue on.
Says who?
Says the boss.
Agent Doggett.
This agent you work with deals
with weird stuff, right?
She works on something
called the X-Files--
FBI cases dealing
with unexplained phenomena.
You know her at all?
Yeah, I know her.
We've worked together
for a short time.
I wonder why
she sent you down here...
instead of coming herself.
It's the right call.
You got a problem,
Lieutenant?
Yeah.
A problem when somebody
I don't know keeps me down here...
in the dark looking
for jack squat...
when we've already
found our man.
It's a question of contagion.
It's a question
of who's in charge.
Agent Doggett?
Yeah.
You all right down there?
Fine.
What do you got for us?
You're about 50 yards
from the spot...
where the train stopped.
What am I looking for?
I don't know.
Anything.
Get it off me.
Get it off me!
What is it?
I don't know, but it burns!
Just hold still.
Let us see it.
It burns!
What is it?
What's happening?
Agent Doggett?!
I can't tell what it is.
[ Screaming ]
[ Doggett ]
Agent Scully, talk to me.
Yeah, um,
get some fresh water on it!
Give me water here!
[ Screaming Continues ]
What the hell was that?
I don't know, and I don't like it
that you don't know.
Agent Scully, talk to me!
I don't know what to say.
I, mean, i-it's something
attacking the dermis.
Attacking? It ate his arm off!.
I hate to say this,
Agent Doggett...
but it looks like it could be some kind
of biochemical weapon.
Great.
What?
What did she say?
She said a lot of people might...
be taking cabs home tonight.
What the hell is this thing?!
It might be a terrorist using some kind
of biochemical agent.
Might? What, is she guessing?
Agent Doggett, I pulled up a map
of the subway grid...
where you are now.
I want you to listen to me.
Agent Scully's telling me
the tunnel we're in...
connects to another tunnel
100 yards up.
It's the only place
for another mile...
that this guy could be hiding.
Well, this man ain't
going nowhere.
Then you take care of him.
I'll have a Haz-Mat team come down here
and prep you for quarantine.
- Lieutenant, let's go.
- [ Lyle ] All right, buddy.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Come on. Come on.
I've got you, buddy.
Hang in there.
Dr. Lyle...
Dr. Lyle,
how are you feeling?
Me?
Yeah.
Well, I seem to be okay,
but Melnick...
Melnick is
getting worse.
Well, we got vehicles
on the way.
The CDC doctors have been
informed of your conditions.
So, what are they going
to be treating us for?
How are they going
to treat Melnick?
I'm working on that.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Hey, where are you
taking them?
Those bodies go to the CDC.
Look, as a federal agent...
I order you to stop
and explain yourself.
Agent Scully,
we are on a deadline here...
which is fast approaching.
These bodies need
immediate examination and diagnosis.
And that is being arranged.
By whom? I already arranged it.
You knew those bodies
were down there, didn't you?
I'd watch yourself,
Agent Scully.
Look at the way they're wrapped.
Somebody sealed them in plastic,
hoping they wouldn't be found.
Look, if I fiind out you sent my partner
and those others down there...
knowing about this--
You are way out of line here.
I want
to see inspection reports.
I want to know who
was down there in that tunnel...
and what they saw.
I'll get you anything you want.
Good.
Now, let's
get these bodies to the CDC...
where they're supposed to go.
What's this here,
Lieutenant?
Abandoned station-- old stop.
Agent Scully...
Here we are,
we're pissing away our time...
and she's asleep at the wheel.
Agent Scully...
Come on,
Agent Doggett.
Make a decision.
Let's get out of here.
We got to fiind
whoever it is...
that's still down here,
Lieutenant.
And what if we don't fiind him?
Maybe it'll be us they fiind...
lying facedown
on the floor, dead.
Agent Scully knows
what she's doing.
This is
about saving people's lives.
Well, it looks like...
it's about saving her life.
If she knows what she's doing...
why hasn't she
fiigured it out yet?
Lieutenant...
walk towards me.
What?
What, damn it?
That stuff s on me.
You see that?
It's spreading.
I told you, Agent Doggett--
we should've gotten out.
That's exactly why
we got to stay.
You saw!
You saw what it does.
Yeah, I saw what it did.
But I don't see it
having any other effect on you...
so just calm down.
I'm getting out of here.
I'm leaving.
[ Cocks Pistol ]
You'd do it, wouldn't you?
Not because I want to.
But you're pushing pretty hard.
So put your weapon down,
Lieutenant, right now.
Now, we're going
to get out of here...
but we're going
to wait for the okay.
Agent Doggett?
Agent Doggett, can you--
Come in, Agent Doggett.
Agent Doggett!
Come in, damn it!
[ Crash ]
Is this a bad time?
Excuse me?
I don't know, I'm looking for
an FBI agent Dana Scully.
Do you know where
I can fiind him?
No...yes...
I mean, I'm-I'm she.
Can I help you?
Yes. I'm Dr. Kai Bowe.
I was sent a scribbled note...
and a saltwater sample
for analysis.
I'm a marine biologist
from BU.
I'm sorry.
Yes, Dr. Bowe, please.
Um... did you get an analysis?
Well, yes, I have something
to show you, that's for sure.
I'm going to assume
you're in a hurry.
[ Unzips Briefcase ]
This is an image taken
from a stereo microscope...
of what's called a medusa.
Your saltwater sample
was rather deceiving.
Its components are exactly
as you'd expect...
except for higher
levels of calcium.
This creature is
primarily that.
Calcium?
Yes, it's what powers...
its movement and gives it
bioluminescence.
So you're saying that
this is a sea creature?
Which is why
the CDC missed it.
Well, it's hard to fiind.
I daresay I'm not even
sure if it's of the sea...
but... wherever it's from,
it... it's quite incredible.
It's killing people.
How?
I don't know.
There is seawater
in that subway tunnel...
and it's eating
people's flesh off.
It's producing
some kind of a reaction...
that looks almost electrical.
On contact?
No. Something triggers it.
Have you been in the tunnel?
No, I have not.
But my partner is down there,
and I fear the worst.
[ Bianco ]
Hey, hey... anybody out there?
[ Pounding ]
Somebody!
Anybody hear me?!
Anybody?!
[ Scully ]
Agent Doggett?
Agent Doggett,
can you hear me?
Agent Doggett?
Yeah.
I'm here.
I hear you.
Oh, you had me.
I, uh...
I started fearing the worst.
No, I... I got blindsided by...
I don't see Lieutenant Bianco.
He's infected with something.
I saw it glowing on his skin.
And what's your condition,
Agent Doggett?
I'm going to assume
it's not good.
I'm going to send
a quarantine unit down...
to get you, Agent Doggett, okay?
I want you
to stay right where you are.
I appreciate it, Agent Scully...
but I can't do that.
If we're going
to stop the spread of this thing...
I got to stop Lieutenant Bianco.
Dr. Bowe, I need you
to get on the phone with the CDC.
Tell them everything
we know.
We have to learn
as quickly as possible...
what sets this thing off.
Look...
I need you to blockade...
any and every exit
from the system.
You've got a possible
outbreak situation here.
No, no. That's
not going to happen.
No, you listen to me.
Your lieutenant is infected
and at large in the system...
and he is looking
for a way out.
I hear you.
It's just that
there are already...
passengers waiting
on the platform.
Agent Doggett...
we've got a new wrinkle.
Don't tell me.
We're running out of time.
It's 20 to 4:00.
I'm moving as fast as I can.
Agent Doggett,
you shouldn't be moving at all.
In 20 minutes...
I'll be taking a long bath
at the hotel.
Right now,
I got to fiind this guy.
This organism
that's on your skin--
something triggers it,
and I don't know what.
It could be body temperature.
It could be heart rate.
It could be from standing still,
too, right?
Maybe the only thing keeping me
from sparking up right now...
is that I'm moving.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I'm getting out of this thing,
Agent Scully.
Just make sure Karras
holds those trains till I fiind Bianco.
He's got passengers waiting
at the next station.
You tell that son of a bitch
he's got to clear the system.
He's--
Wait. I see something.
Lieutenant...
He's hurt.
You see this, Dr. Bowe?
You see this, Mr. Karras?
You're on with the CDC?
I need anything
they can give me...
about what sets
this organism off--
an idea, a notion,
a wild guess.
Agent Scully...
what do you want me to do?
Get out of there...
Agent Doggett.
What about this man?
I'm going to send a Haz-Mat team
down for him...
but from what I've seen...
the reaction's progressive.
Please, Agent Doggett...
don't leave me.
I hope
you're enjoying the ride.
You see this,
Agent Scully?
Yeah.
Who else is down there?
We don't know.
You, there!
Stop!
Federal agent! I'm armed!
Agent Scully, believe this?
[ Doggett ]
Who are you?
What's your name?
What are you
doing down here?
What's he pointing at?
I don't know.
Is he infected?
Agent Doggett,
turn the light away.
Nothing.
He's unaffected.
How's that?
I think I just fiigured it out.
I might know what triggers this.
What is it?
Sweat.
Perspiration is a conductor
for calcium ions...
promoting
a chemical-electrical reaction.
Electricity?
That's right.
And since the boy's sweat glands...
aren't fully developed...
then he wouldn't
be as conductive.
Just my luck.
Agent Doggett, where's he going?
I don't know...
but he wants me to follow him.
Agent Scully, I don't know
if you can see this.
I think I found the source
of the contagion.
It looks like a big leak
in the ceiling...
is crumbling the walls...
flooding into the system.
It must have seeped in
from the bay.
Hey, where you going?
You see this?
The kid's walking
right through this stuff.
Yeah. I'm...
I'm checking my graphic here.
It... it looks like he's trying
to lead you through...
to a tunnel on the main system.
And, if what I'm looking at
is accurate...
it would put you about 400 yards...
from an access point.
I mean, if I could
put a Haz-Mat team together...
we might be able to have you out
in about 15 minutes.
Come on, Lieutenant.
We're in through
to the main system, Agent Scully...
and we got big,
big problems here.
Yes, we do.
You see this flooding?
No. It's worse than that.
I think this moron Karras...
has started
the trains rolling.
[Train Whistle Blowing ]
[Whistle Blowing ]
Agent Doggett...
what are you doing?
Get off the tracks,
Agent Doggett.
Get out of there!
We got people on the train.
They could get infected.
Get out of there, Agent Doggett!
Let me have this.
Give it to me!
I got an idea, Agent Scully.
[ Scully ]
Agent Doggett?
Talk to me, Agent Doggett.
[ Electrical Crackling ]
Agent Doggett?
Are you there?
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm here.
Thank God.
Uh... I lost you on the visual.
Okay...
Okay, I've got you.
You're back.
Are you okay?
I can only hope,
Agent Scully.
[ Clicking ]
Nurse!
Where do you think you're going?
Find the nurse.
She said she was going
to talk to the doctor...
about me going home.
I could be dying in here
for all she knows.
Well, you're not...
Agent Doggett.
Your skin and body...
have been rid
of the organism.
Simple alcohol bath
cleaned you right up.
I was just down
talking to the nurse...
and I told her I'd
come and give you the news.
Well, can I get out of here?
Yes.
What about the others?
Well, the kid
is with social services...
and plastic surgeons are working
on Melnick and Bianco...
and Dr. Lyle
has been discharged.
You know,
I'd like to think...
that this was over...
but there's going
to be hell to pay...
for these guys.
No. It's over,
Agent Doggett.
Excuse me?
This guy Karras put a train
back on the tracks.
He recklessly
endangered people's lives.
But there is no proof
of that.
What do you mean,
there's no proof?
What I'm saying...
is that the organism
is no longer extant.
It's destroyed.
By what?
I'm guessing by
the electrical charge...
that you set off.
We have victims.
Dead bodies.
Infected by a pathogen
of unknown etiology.
Look, Agent Doggett...
not a criminal charge
is going to stick.
These guys were
just doing their job--
keeping the trains running.
But they've got you to thank.
And not just
for saving their butts.
No. You fiigured it out.
I was just your eyes and ears.
Agent Scully...
Let's go home.