It's freezing out there.
MAN:
You weren't gone long.
Did you do
what I asked?
Yes.
It's important, Gary.
Promise me you did it.
You're sick, Dad.
You should be in a hospital
not stuck out here
in the middle of nowhere.
You don't owe this guy Stites
anything.
It's not about owing.
I freeze my butt off
checking and rechecking
the locks every night.
For what?
You don't need to know.
Yeah, that's for sure.
I'm going to fiix some dinner.
( door closes )
( monitor beeping
soft, slowtones )
( windows flapping )
( beeping speeds up )
( fast, rhythmic beeps )
( groans softly )
( groaning weakly )
( monitor beeping faster )
( rapid beeping )
Oh, Lord.
Gary, you didn't--
( microwave beeps )
Oh, whew.
( steady tone )
Oh, God.
Dad?
( steady tone )
( tone stops )
( soft rattling )
DOGGETT :
Agent Scully.
Mmm.
Can I take your coat?
I'm not staying, Agent Doggett.
My doctor told me
to take my maternity leave.
In fact, she insisted on it.
That's not bad, Agent Scully.
You could use some time
for yourself.
What is it?
It's a medallion commemorating
the Apollo 11 space flight.
I'd like to give this
to you, Agent Doggett.
Thanks.
Because?
Agent Mulder gave it to me
a few years back.
It symbolizes teamwork...
partnership.
It means
no one gets there alone.
And after this past year
and...
everything that we've
been through, I just--
I wouldn't be here without you.
Agent Scully.
This pregnancy leave...
it's just a ""leave,'' right?
I mean...you are coming back
eventually?
( footsteps approaching )
You're not gone fiive minutes,
Agent Scully
and already I'm starting to feel
like a stranger in my own off--
I'm sorry?
Can I help you?
I'm here to help
you, actually.
I'm Leyla Harrison.
I've been looking
forward to meeting you.
Uh-huh.
I've got a case here,
an X-File, I think.
At least the local PD
can't explain it.
A murder last night
in upstate New York.
I booked us on a flight
to Buffalo Niagara.
Here's the crime report.
I'm sorry, Ms. Harrison...
who are you?
Oh, gosh.
They didn't tell you?
This is... so embarrassing.
Uh, I'm... I'm
your new partner.
I asked that the body
be sent to D.C.
It was found
in the woods
about 50 yards
beyond the house.
Maybe we should
begin there.
Let's begin
inside the house.
Okay, then.
The deceased is
Arlen Sacks, aged 72
caretaker for the estate
on which this house
is situated.
There were no signs
of physical trauma
but local PD
suspect homicide
due to the dumping
of the body.
Mr. Sacks was confiined
to a wheelchair
the last few months
cared for since then
by his son, Gary
who's their
chief suspect.
Why?
Um... oh, because
he's missing, too.
If he killed this man
without leaving a mark
that would suggest premeditation
an attempt
to disguise the murder.
But that doesn't fiit with
dumping the body in the woods
or fleeing the scene
both of which
indicate panic, haste.
That is great.
What was that last part again,
about the premeditation?
What is that?
Slime?
There's a small streak of it
on the floor over there, too.
So, it's not someone;
it's something.
God, this really is an X-File,
isn't it?
Congratulations.
I gave the slime
to the Buffalo PD.
I told them we wanted to see
the results right away.
How much fiield experience
you have, Agent Harrison?
Um, actually, this is
my fiirst time in the fiield.
Let me guess--
Deputy Director Kersh
handed you this job
fiilling in for Agent Scully.
Yes. Yes, he did.
I don't know how to tell
you this, Agent Harrison
but you're being used.
Deputy Director Kersh is
no friend to the X-Files.
I don't think you understand
something, Agent Doggett.
I begged for this assignment.
You begged for it.
I was in Accounting.
I processed Agents Mulder
and Scully's travel expenses.
Then you are qualifiied.
Maybe I'm not
but I know the X-Files,
Agent Doggett, inside and out.
Other people don't even want
to admit these questions exist
but you face them every day.
I am just so excited
to be a part of this.
Aren't you?
Mr. Sack's body was found here
but they found no
footprints leading to it.
Oh, my God.
There's more of it.
Looks like it.
You know what
that could be?
It could be bile.
Bile?
From a liver-eating mutant.
Mulder and Scully
chased one
into an escalator once.
It died, but,
but there was--
This is not a liver-eating
mutant, Agent Harrison.
It could be an alien
who shed its skin.
According to Agent
Mulder's case reports
they leave behind
a mucous-like residue
when they, uh--
You don't think
it's that either.
I'll take a
sample of this.
Have it sent to the
lab for comparison.
That's good thinking,
Agent Harrison.
( rumbling )
( knocking )
Hey.
Ready to roll?
Yeah. I'lljust get my keys.
Hey. Don't forget this.
Relax the back.
Breathe in, breathe out.
( forceful panting )
How do you know all
these things, Mulder?
I'm unemployed.
I got a lot of time on my hands.
Oprah.
I watch a lot of Oprah.
Thank you for doing
this with me.
What's the matter?
I don't know. I, uh--
Maybe it's hormones or--
This is just--
I'm just feeling so
strange about all this.
This having a baby, this?
No... no.
Leaving work, I guess.
I mean, I... I walked
out of that offiice today
feeling like a deserter.
You've paid your
dues there, Scully.
More than paid them.
You're concerned about
Agent Doggett.
You know the entire time
that I was down there
I had someone
to watch my back.
I'm betting thatAgent Doggett
can take care of himself.
He's a big boy.
You've got to worry
about the little boy
or little girl.
Boy?
Or girl?
Whoa.
Agent Harrison,
what are you doing here?
I followed the tr--
It's here.
It?
What ""it''?
You're armed, right?
What do you want
me to do?
I want you to go outside
and I want you to stand
by the front door.
Whatever it is, I'm going
to try and flush it out.
Agent Harrison.
Take the safety off.
( soft rattling )
( gunshots )
Harrison.
Agent Harrison!
( creaking )
( telephone ringing )
Skinner.
Is it true?
Agent Scully.
I can't reach Agent Doggett
and someone told me
he's gone missing.
He was investigating a murder.
He hasn't reported back.
Why wasn't I told?
Agent Scully, don't worry.
I'm heading
into the Bureau right now.
No, you're not.
Sir, are you ordering me
not to go looking
for Agent Doggett?
I've got every available
law-enforcement offiicer out here.
You're on maternity leave now.
Just trust that we're doing
everything that we know to do.
I know that you are...
but what if it's not enough?
- I'lljust take this to the lab.
- Thank you.
Seems like old times.
You in scrubs,
slicing and dicing.
What are you doing here, Mulder?
Actually I-I wandered
away from my tour.
A better question is,
what are you doing here?
I found something
that may prove helpful
in locating Agent Doggett.
This is Arlen Sacks
the murder victim
Doggett was investigating.
This old man was not
murdered, Mulder.
He died of heart failure,
evidently after he was blinded
by a chemical substance
of some kind.
The orbits have...
residual traces
of a slimy substance...
known as hydrolytic enzymes.
Venom. Produced by reptiles.
How'd you know that?
Before Agent Doggett
and his partner
went missing, they sent
in samples to be analyzed.
Hydrolytic enzymes.
Skinner told me.
I, uh, also found some bacteria
in the venom
which I'm going to do
a culture on.
Let somebody else do it.
There are other
concerns right now.
I know, but this is
an X-File, Mulder
and you are out of the Bureau,
and now if I go home
where is Skinner going to fiind
someone qualifiied to look into this?
I know where he
could fiind somebody.
( clattering )
( raspy crunching )
( chittering sound)
( gate opens )
Agent Doggett?
I'm right here.
Are you all right?
It sprayed my eyes
with something.
My vision's all blurry.
Makes two of us.
Three, actually.
HARRISON: I think it's Gary Sacks,
the son of the murder victim.
How'd you get down here?
I think it dragged me down here.
I'm not sure.
So what do
we do now?
I don't know.
Mulder and Scully investigated
a case once in Florida.
It involved subterranean men
who took people underground.
This is not a man.
I fell through
some kind of trap.
I'm guessing
somebody put that there
to provide live meals
for this thing.
You're not saying
that includes us?
I don't intend to wait around
and fiind out.
These tunnels were built
by bootleggers
back in Prohibition.
There's got to be one
that leads back to the house.
Something up there,
I think.
Some kind of light.
I can't tell how high
up that is.
Mulder, you're not supposed
to be out here.
I'm not out here.
What happened
to the search?
Police in West Seneca
found Doggett's car
parked at a convenience store
about a half hour from here.
How'd it get there?
I don't know, but we're
redirecting our search.
Where are you going?
I think I'll take
a walk in the woods.
We've already had
40 people looking
around out
there, Mulder.
What the hell?
I'm out of a job
already, right?
( grunting )
( metallic clinking )
MAN:
Thought all you people left.
You are?
Herman Stites.
I own this property.
You're just the man I wanted
to speak to, Mr. Stites.
Have you seen anything
unusual around here?
Unusual? How?
Dangerous animals...
reptiles.
I'm confused.
I thought the police
were looking for a man.
Arlen's son, Gary.
That is what
they're looking for.
Agent Doggett?
I'm all right.
MULDER:
I don't think Gary Sacks committed
this murder, Mr. Stites.
I think he may be
a victim himself.
I didn't catch
your name, Agent.
Kersh, Alvin Kersh.
I'm a scientist,
Mr. Kersh.
What kind of a scientist
are you?
A biologist
so I know something
about animals.
They don't generally
carry men off into the woods
like poor Mr. Sacks.
I don't think this was
an animal.
I think it was a man
using some kind of reptile venom
to blind them fiirst.
That would be
quite a trick.
You'd really have
to know what you were doing.
You'd have to be,
say, a scientist.
Are you accusing me
of something, Mr. Kersh?
No. I'm just thinking
out loud, Mr. Stites.
( grunting )
I need a hand.
Agent Doggett, what happened?
I lost my grip
with a little help
from the man upstairs.
( distant clang )
Hey!
I'm a federal agent!
I don't understand.
Why would he want
to keep us down here?
You wanted to face the unknown,
Agent Harrison.
Well, you're facing it now.
But who is he?
Some kind of scientist,
I think.
I saw some books
and papers on biology
in his library.
It could be some kind
of symbiotic relationship
between this man
and this creature.
Mulder and Scully--
Mulder and Scully
aren't here, Agent Harrison,
we are.
And wild speculation isn't going
to help us fiind a way out.
You think I'm pretty foolish,
don't you?
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but you want to take leaps
that aren't supported
by the facts.
What I want
you to do is
stay with that guy right there
while I look
for another way out.
If this thing
comes near you...
I want you to shoot.
Agent Doggett.
He's gone.
What do you mean he's gone?
I don't know.
It must have taken him.
( phone ringing )
Mulder.
Mulder, what are you doing?
I'm spitting sunflower shells
on Herman Stites's driveway.
What are you doing, Scully?
I just got off
the phone with Skinner
who is furious.
This man Stites just called him
saying that
you've been impersonating
Deputy Director Kersh
and making baseless accusations.
What's he mad about
me impersonating Kersh
or me harassing Stites?
Mulder, the victim had
reptile venom in his eyes.
Are you now saying
that it was a man who did this?
What are you saying it is,
Scully?
I know this may be hard
to believe
coming from me
but some kind
of reptile attack is
the only explanation consistent
with the scientifiic evidence.
I don't think it's a monster
that we're dealing with here.
I think it is a man.
And why do you say that?
You regifted.
I'm sorry?
My Apollo medallion.
You found it?
Yeah. I found it on the grass
on Stites's estate.
Doggett must be
around here somewhere.
( door opens )
Agent Scully?
I got to go.
What am I looking at?
As you asked
we cultured the bacteria
from the hydrolytic enzymes
that were sprayed
into the old man's eyes.
Looks like they're
breaking down the tissue.
That's exactly
what they're doing.
The venom blinds its victim,
then the bacteria excretes
protease and collagenase
throughout the victim's body.
Digestive enzymes.
Muscle, bone,
all of it is slowly liquefiied
for easy digestion
while the victim's skin
is made hard and brittle
forming a sack or shell
from which the
reptile can drink.
So the reptile sprays
its victim
and then all it has
to do is wait.
There are precedents
for this sort of thing in nature.
Yeah, but there are no species
that can do all of this.
At least not yet.
What do you mean?
Talk about the blind
leading the blind.
I owe you an apology,
Agent Doggett.
You're doing fiine,
Agent Harrison.
Hang tough.
You were right.
I'm not qualifiied.
We're going to fiind a way
out of here, Agent Harrison.
I don't think I am.
Why, what is it?
Whatever happened to Sacks--
I think it's happening to me.
I'm completely blind now.
( moist, squishy noises )
( gunshots )
Oh, God,
Agent Doggett!
I think it's Gary Sacks.
( ringing )
Mulder.
You were right
about Herman Stites, Mulder.
What'd you fiind?
Stites is a crypto-biologist
specializing
in reptile genetics.
Listen to this:
It says here that he published
a monograph last year
claiming to be on the verge
of creating
a new species of reptile.
You don't think
he succeeded, do you?
I don't know.
He dropped out of sight
and never published a follow-up.
But, Mulder,
the bacteria inside this venom--
if Stites is genetically
altering reptile breeds
it may explain
the peculiar properties.
Mulder, are you listening to me?
Mulder?
I think Mr. Stites might have
a lot more than that to explain.
Mulder? Mulder?
Mr. Stites!
Mr. Stites, open up!
Mr. Stites,
open the door!
( pounding )
Mr. Stites!
( pounding continues )
( dialing )
What do you want?
Where is it,
Mr. Stites?
This thing
you're protecting--
this creature of yours?
I don't think
you meant for it to
but it got out last night
and attacked
the caretaker and his son
and then
it attacked my colleagues.
Now, I can have
50 men in here
to comb this place
within the hour.
Where are they, Mr. Stites?
( gasps )
It's all right.
It's just me.
Doesn't make any damn sense.
There's no exit
except that door.
Maybe it does.
( pounding )
MULDER:
Agent Doggett?
Right here!
It's all right,
Agent Doggett.
We're going to
get you out of here.
Who's that with you?
It's the man
that lives here.
He's been protecting this thing.
He's kept us down here.
- Agent Doggett, I know--
- It's him.
He's not protecting it.
He is it.
Agent Mulder?
Agent Doggett,
I don't have a weapon.
I'm coming to get yours.
No, I'm not.
Mulder, I can't see.
Mulder, where is it?
It's right above you.
It's coming this way.
Where, Mulder? I can't see!
Aim down.
Aim at the sound of my voice.
No, I'll shoot you!
You're not going to shoot me.
I can't see!
Aim at the sound of my voice.
Where is it?
Aim at me!
Fire when I tell you to fiire.
No!
Fire!
( gunfiire )
Agent Mulder?
I'm right here.
I'm right here,
Agent Doggett.
SCULLY:
Agent Doggett?
Is this it?
- No.
We just came by
to visit
Agent Harrison.
How is she?
She's on the same
antivenin treatment I got.
Her eyesight's
pretty much back.
Doctors say she's going
to be fiine, physically.
Skinner said she won't
be returning to the X-Files.
That was her choice.
Just going to be
me for a while.
I want to return something
to you
that I think you deserve
to keep.
I appreciate the gesture
but if it's all
the same to you
there's someone else
who should have it.
No way.
This means--
I can't tell you
what this means to me.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
When you went to Antarctica
to save Agent Scully from
being taken by that spaceship
and you ran out of gas
in your Snow-Cat--
how did you get back?
Um, well, fiirst of all
it was never actually proven
that it was a spaceship.
It wasn't?
No, what happened was that
we fell off of something
that rose out of the ice.
And what do you
think that was?
Well, I don't know
what it was
but we didn't actually
see a spaceship.
I can't believe you're saying
it's not a spaceship.
It could have
been a spaceship.
Of course it
was a spaceship.
We don't know that it--
But you don't have
a picture of it or anything.
You know it was a spaceship.
You saw it.
No, no, remember,
I was unconscious.
And when I woke up
there was no spaceship.
Mulder, no, no, no.
And you were frozen.
And remember,
I hugged you
until you were not
frozen anymore--