Subs by Zhalom and Raceman
www.forom.com
My name
is melinda gordon.
I'm married,
i live in a small town,
and i own
an antique shop.
I might be just like you.
Except that from the time
i was a little girl,
i knew that i could
talk to the dead.
Grandmother:
It's all right, honey.
Earthbound spirits,
my grandmother called them.
They're stuck here
because they have unfinished
business with the living
and they come to me
for help.
In order to tell you
my story,
i have to tell you
theirs.
Hey, do you want to see
what i'm getting jim?
Sure.
Walk with me.
It's in shiffman's window.
What's the occasion?
It's our anniversary
on friday.
5 years.
Really?
I didn't know
you guys were together
for 5 years.
No, we haven't been.
It's the night we met.
Wait. You're celebrating
the night you met?
That's disgusting.
Was it romantic?
Yeah.
A little scary, too.
Anyway, there it is.
What? Where?
Right there.
And it actually works.
That's sweet.
You know, jim's been
so busy lately,
he hasn't even mentioned
our anniversary.
I think he forgot.
Really? Um... did he say
he wanted one of those?
It means something to us.
Ok.
I will never get used
to that sound.
Is jim working tonight?
Man: Are you guys safe?
As long as you
all are safe.
Ok. Come on.
I'll get you home.
Do you see jim
anywhere?
No.
You're all right.
Wait. There he is.
He's right there.
He's right there
with that guy!
Jim! Jim! Jim!
I'm lit! I'm lit!
Hey, no!
No, please, please,
see if everybody's out.
It's empty, it's empty.
It's all right.
Did everyone
get out?
Please, please,
make sure.
Let us take a look at you.
Get him some oxygen,
get some water.
Are you ok?
Ahh. You see, they saved
the basic structure,
but the interior's
totaled.
What a shame.
And it was
the opening night.
Mm-mmm. Re-opening.
That thing burned down once
before, like a year ago.
And i think i have it
bad when i can't find
a parking space.
Ooh. Ouch.
No, that's my line.
You're too tough
and stoic.
Oh, it's good
you reminded me,
'cause i wanted
to scream when you were
taking off my shirt.
You want a hot pack?
No. Enough heat
for one night.
Ice?
No thanks.
Look, tell me more
about this ghost.
He was on fire?
Yeah. He felt
pretty powerful.
But nobody died
in the fire.
Where'd he come from?
I  don't know.
It like he was getting
his power from the fire.
I mean, he looked at me,
and i got the chills.
Chills. Get it?
Oh, all right.
You're delirious.
Get some sleep.
You're going to be so sore
in the morning.
Oh, i'm already
sore as hell.
Ah. Hell? Fire?
Ok, sleep
before i slap you.
All right.
I think
everything'll be fine
as long as i'm
better by friday.
Really?
Well, what's friday?
Poker night
at richie's.
I didn't know that.
Is it sore right there?
Ow!
Oh, i'm so sorry.
There's
no reason to panic.
Interior collapsed
in the building
next door.
There's no fire
jumping.
Oh, my slipper.
I can walk on my own
just fine, thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh!
So, what is it?
The gift.
I just had to get it
out of the window
before jim saw it.
Anyway, i'm only
going to leave it
here until friday.
So, do you know what
he's going to get you?
Uh, i think he forgot.
He has plans to play
poker on friday night.
Ohh. Trouble
in padise?
No, he's just been exhausted,
working doubles.
And he got his dates
mixed up.
He'll realize it,
figure it out.
So, do you want me
to drop a hint the
next time i see him?
I'm pretty good at it.
No, it's ok. Thanks.
I really want him
to remember on his own.
I mean, it was a big night
for him... for us.
I just can't believe
that he would forget.
Do you smell smoke?
Mm-mmm. You know,
it's probably just
some leftover stink
from the fire
the other night.
I still smell it
on my clothes.
Reminds me
of my clubbing days.
Professor payne!
I can't tell you
how many times
i've walked past
this store and was almost
tempted to come in.
I'm honored. I think.
Delia banks,
this is professor payne
from rockland university.
He teaches a course on...
i teach the use of symbols
in the world of the occult.
Man's need to believe
in the unbelievable.
O-kay.
Uh, i'm going to go
across the street and
get some air freshener.
Air  freshener? Did i...
nothing to do with you.
Your husband got knocked
down in that fire.
Is he ok?
Yes, thanks.
I met him, you know.
I know.
He's a nice man,
your husband.
I know.
Does he always
drool like that?
He's a mouth breather.
Is that a problem?
I don't think
you came here to just
make fun of my husband.
No, i did not,
although i do enjoy it.
I  miss you.
I miss you, and i...
you're avoiding me.
Not intentionally.
Did i scare you off?
I don't scare easily.
Crazy. It's...
new neck exercise?
yes, actually.
You know,
that reminds me, i have
a question for you.
You always have
a question for me.
This time before you ask,
let's talk a little
quid pro quo.
If you get to ask a question,
i get to ask you a question.
Ok. What's
your question?
How many college
professors does it take
to screw
in a light bulb?
No, don't answer that.
That's not the real question.
My question to you is...
do you claim to have
supernatural powers?
Define "supernatural."
Ahh! Now we're
getting somewhere.
Supernatural meaning,
not of this world.
Do you claim to be connected
to the supernatural?
Sometimes
it feels that way.
How do you...
ok, that was
your one question.
Now it's my turn.
If somebody said to you
that there would
be 5 signs and then
death would come,
what would you think?
I would think about
selling my house
and moving to the nearest
police station.
I'm being serious.
That's what scares me.
I mean, aside from...
5...
5 represents
the unification of 2,
in the feminine element,
and 3, the masculine element.
Unification?
5.
5 represents the 5 senses,
the 5 wounds of the christ,
the 5... the 5 pillars
of piety.
In islam 5 is a big one.
A powerful, strong number.
Let's not kid
ourselves, sister.
It wasn't the jackson 4.
So what's going on?
Not yet.
Hi. Can i help you?
Thanks for coming.
Who are you?
It burns.
Everything burns.
What does that mean?
He knows.
He knows why.
Who knows?
so, what are
we saying here?
The ghost set the fire
at the restaurant?
Let's just say
he caused it.
He said "he knows,
he knows why."
Who? The owner?
Yeah. You said that
it had burned down
once before, right?
Yeah, about a year ago.
Ahh. See? That's the one
i need to know more about.
Hey, you know
my buddy freddy diaz?
I've heard you talk about him,
but i've never met him.
He's the county
arson investigator.
He's been on
the scene all week.
Arson?
Does that mean
i'm not the only one
who thinks it was set?
No, it's routine.
You see, every fire gets
investigated the same way
until they've figured out
how it happened.
So, look, i don't think
you're going to find
any wanted posters
for ghosts.
So, why don't
you go, talk to him,
see what
he can tell you?
I'll give him a head's
up. You want a glass?
Mm-mmm.
Ok.
Mmm. Thank you.
Melinda, my husband's
still in there.
Are you sure?
Maybe he came out
around the corner.
No! No.
He's in there.
He's at the bottom
of the stairs.
Ok.
I'm really sorry
to bother you.
Excuse me, ma'am.
You're supposed to be
behind the barricade.
There's a man
trapped inside.
No, there isn't. We got
everybody outside.
Please believe me.
Noah.
Yo?
Come on.
Where we going?
Back  inside.
You're welcome.
Man: Everything ok?
Is everything ok?
Oh, i'm sorry.
You looked like you were
a million miles away there.
You caught me.
Actually, i'm looking
for freddy diaz.
Oh, that's me.
You are...
hi. I'm melinda gordon.
I think that you know
my husband, jim clancy.
Oh, are you kidding?
You have any idea how
much beer i have consumed
with  that man
over the course of...
anyway. Uh...
what can i do for you?
The first fire happened
in the middle of the night.
They were closed,
no customers.
Did you investigate
that one, too?
Oh, yeah.
Figured that one out
in about a half-hour.
Arson?
In a big way.
How can you tell?
Tons of ways.
You look
for accelerants,
pour patterns,
ignition sources.
But the surest way
to know is when you find
the arsonist's
body right where
the fire started.
Pretty much a slam dunk.
Someone died in that fire?
Co-owner.
Tried to screw
his ex-partner over.
Insurance scam
is what we figured.
See it all the time.
It's amazing
what people try
to get away with.
Not too smart, though.
Guy burned to death.
People have
no idea how fast
a fire can spread.
What about this fire?
Any idea what caused it?
This matters to you, why?
Sorry. I'm just doing some
research on arson, fire,
things like that.
Mmm. You mean,
for a book or something?
You never can tell.
I haven't found
any evidence
to suggest arson.
We're gonna keep
looking though.
Say hi to jim
for me.
Watch your step
on the way out.
Thanks.
Lilly chen.
Lilly.
What is that?
Stained glass?
Everything will burn.
Everyone will burn.
Yeah.
I'm fine.
I just got so hot
i couldn't breathe.
I can't decide whether
to move into the firehouse
or have the firehouse
move in here.
Well, at least i know
who the ghost is.
It's the guy who set
fire to his own restaurant?
Yes.
And then a year later
set fire to it again,
after he died?
I think so.
Why?
Maybe... i don't know.
Maybe he's been
in some kind of sleep
state all this time.
You know, it does
usually take some
big event or...
i don't know,
some kind of ripple.
And you think the re-opening
of the restaurant set him off?
Well, yeah!
I need you to lie down.
That's not lying down.
Well, why don't you
turn your head sideways,
and then it'll look
like i'm lying down?
You are a terrible patient.
He said that everything
was going to burn.
Every one
What for?
I don't know.
But, you know,
he's obviously coming
to me for some reason.
Maybe he wants my help.
And maybe he's
just completely evil,
and he enjoys the attention.
Either way i have
to cross him over
before he burns
something else down.
All right.
You said
he recognized his wife?
Yeah, he said her name.
I tried to find her
before you got home,
and there's no listing
for her anywhere.
Why don't you talk
to that guy jesse
at the restaurant?
He knows...
warren chen.
Right. His partner.
Talk to him,
see what he can tell you.
Can you get me
his address?
Well... that depends
what's in it for me.
How's your
blood pressure?
Elevated.
Now lie down.
Ok, i'll lie down.
I hope you don't mind
if i keep working.
I got to get
this place in shape.
It's gotta go on
the market next week.
I know that
this is a bad time
for you right now.
Yeah. Well, that's
what happens when you lose
a business twice
in one year.
Wasn't there
any insurance?
Yeah, but with the first one,
they didn't want to pay.
Insurance companies
tend to frown on arson.
Then i had to borrow money
from my father to rebuild,
and no one wanted to insure
the new place.
Look, i really appreciate
what your husband did for me,
but i really don't
want to think about any
of this right now.
I'd like to talk
about the first fire,
last year.
And warren chen.
Why  are you doing this?
What do you want from me?
I'd just like
to know more about him.
Warren was my partner,
and he was my friend.
He burned down
your restaurant.
And it broke my heart!
He was like a brother to me.
Look, i don't know why he did
what he did that night.
But you didn't know him,
and you can't come here
and talk about him
like he's some kind
of criminal.
Ok, i'm sorry.
Ok. Well, now
i have things to do.
What about lilly?
Do you know
where she is?
She had a total
breakdown after warren.
Look, what do you want
from her and what do you
want from me?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
just leave us alone.
Leave me alone.
Leave her alone.
We've l been through enough.
I really hate being
the only one who knows
how that fire got started.
So, did jesse
say anything helpful?
No. He's pretty raw.
I'm guess i'm going
to have to find lilly
and see if she knows
anything that can help.
Well, how are you going
to do that?
You said there
was no listing.
You can help me.
I knew that was coming.
Ok. All you have
to do is find out
where she lived
with warren.
I'm sure
there's a record
from the last fire.
She might
still be there.
I'll take a look.
Ok.
One kiss.
Go to work.
They're gonna take a look.
Don't worry.
Let's go, let's go.
There's somebody
still here.
You ok?
I'm all right.
Let's do this.
Anybody here?!
Can you hear us?
If you can hear us,
make a sound!
Did you hear that?
What's that?
Man: Get out!
I hear something.
I think someone's here.
Turn off the radio.
Radios off.
Right there.
That's it.
We got 2!
Radio: We got them!
We found them!
Move it!
Let's go!
Make sure you
check on him, ok?
Make sure he's ok?
I will.
Thank you.
Hey, i'm going
across to lentos
on the square.
You want anything?
No, thanks.
Whatcha looking up?
Trying to find someone.
Aren't we all?
Old friend?
Not really.
Old enemy?
It's a long story.
I'm starting
to get the idea
that there's
a lot of long stories
attached to you.
More than you know.
Hey, it's cool,
i was just gonna...
you know, it's a friend
of mine whose husband died,
and i'm trying
to check up on her,
but i don't
know how to find her.
Phone book?
No, i tried
the old number and it just
said disconnected.
Hmm. You know,
i love those kind
of good puzzles.
Yeah. I'll figure
this one out.
So, has jim remembered
your anniversary yet?
No. He's still playing
poker on friday night.
Time for a hint?
I don't want to trick him
into remembering.
You know, men have so
much crap on their minds
this time of year.
There's football,
basketball,
ice hockey...
america's
next top model.
Yeah. I guess
it's no big deal.
I mean, maybe
this stuff isn't that
important after all.
Yeah, my husband
was really excellent
at forgetting
our anniversary, too.
And it didn't really
matter that much,
or at least that's
what i told myself.
And i would drop hints
all the time,
but it never worked.
And finally one day
i just looked at him
and i said,
charlie,
what the hell is it
about our anniversary?
Why won't you
just remember it and
get it over with?
And he looked
at me and he smiled,
and he said...
'cause
it's just one day.
What's one day
when you compared it...
to being married to you
every single day?
That's a really good answer.
Yeah. That was charlie.
The funeral home.
Sorry?
Your friend.
Why don't you check
with the funeral home
where her husband
had his wake?
What if she moved,
you know, after the wake?
I bet they have
a cell number
or maybe
her work number.
You are a genius.
Right.
Please tell my son that.
Bye.
The chens.
I remember the chen family.
Do you remember
the wife?
Lilly?
Just that she seemed so sad.
It was only her and a man,
about her age...
he was just inconsolable.
Cried more than she did,
if i remember.
Must have been jesse,
his partner.
I didn't get the name.
I tried to comfort them,
tried to tell them that
warren was at peace now...
but, of course...
i know.
So sorry
to keep you waiting.
We do still have the records
from that funeral,
but i'm afraid
i couldn't give you any
personal information.
Oh, i understand.
But if i could
impose on you just
a little bit more...
um, would you mind
calling ms. Chen
and just giving her
my phone number,
just let her know
that i have a message
about warren,
and that it's
really important
that i speak to her.
If it's that important...
thanks, i really
appreciate that.
Tell him he did
a fantastic job on the hair
for the woman in room 5.
The family loved it.
So did she.
People really
love your work.
Let's walk.
I have to admit,
i didn't think
you'd call me back.
I'm not sure why i did.
But for some reason
i felt like i had to.
You said you had a message
about warren.
Did you know him?
No, not really. Um...
i've been doing
some research on
the restaurant fire,
the red noir.
You know,
i don't mean to pry,
but do you know
why warren would
do what he did?
It doesn't make sense.
What was he like?
He always said his life
had perfect balance,
except then he got
into business with jesse.
To be his partner.
Yes, and that
was the problem.
He wasn't just
a chef anymore.
He had to deal
with the business...
the hiring, the firing.
He hated it.
Worst of all,
it had nothing
to do with his talent,
what made him happy.
His mood changed.
He was always
so stressed.
Do you think that's
why he set the fire?
So he could
get out of it?
I just don't know.
What if i told you
there was a way you
could ask him?
I don't know what you...
what if i said
that warren's spirit
is still here?
I can help you talk
to him, through me.
No. Lilly, please...
he showed me
a piece of glass.
Stained glass, does that
mean anything to you?
I don't want him to see me.
??????????
Warren?
Warren chen?
I need to talk to you.
I can help you.
I spoke to your wife
and jesse.
They don't really
understand why you
did what you did.
Warren:
What did i do?
Set the restaurant
on fire. Twice.
Don't you remember that?
I remember being mad
at jesse.
Why?
I wanted him to buy me out.
I needed him to buy me out.
He kept telling me
he'd pay me off,
and then he'd always
have an excuse.
He was never going
to give me what was mine.
Did you think you
were going to get money
from the fire?
From the insurance?
Or were you just trying
to get back at jesse?
I don't remember.
You really hate
this place.
I was a chef...
before.
I used to love
to come to work.
I couldn't wait.
People loved what i did.
When i got this place
with jesse,
it all changed.
I used to dream
about fire...
about this place
burning down.
And then i'd be free.
Warren, i know how
much pain you're in,
but you have to cross over.
There's a better place for you.
I can't.
Ok. Look, the revenge
that you wanted to get
on jesse, you got it.
All right? He's ruined.
He's probably
never going to be able
to open a business again.
It's lilly.
There's something
she has to know.
What?
I don't know.
Does it have something to do
with that stained glass?
I love her so much.
I'm afraid i hurt her.
I have to talk to her.
Don't let lilly think
i forgot her.
You know what, noah?
I think i'll see you
back at the station.
Ah!
Sorry...
aah!
It's ok.
You remember me?
Yeah. You threw
my slipper at me.
Tossed.
I tossed it at you.
There's a difference.
Let me see
if i can fix this.
There's a trick to it.
Yeah.
That's not it.
I hope you're better
at putting out fires.
I'll buy you a new one.
Don't worry about it.
I'm jim...
jim clancy,
by the way.
Melinda gordon.
Nice to meet you.
I have to...
where you headed?
Uh... now
to get an umbrella.
Right.
Produce. My apartment
is full of soot, so...
i don't know about you,
but i'm starved.
Well, good luck
with that.
Hey, let me buy you
a late dinner.
I know a place.
What place?
Ever heard
of the umbrella room?
No.
Come on.
?????????
Well, you got class,
i'll give you that.
Anybody can take
you to sardi's.
Thanks, boss.
You won't find
this kind of food there.
One can hope.
Do you live close by?
Well, near.
West 90th.
That's the upper west side.
This is the east village.
That's not close at all.
I was never any good
with a compass.
You got a little, uh...
on your lip.
What?
Nothing.
I know.
You were pretty
sure that guy was
in that apartment.
Lucky guess.
No. You knew.
You were sure.
I've been thinking
about it all night.
How did you know?
You know what?
I have to go home.
I have work in the morning.
You know,
i hate secrets.
So, how did you know?
Maybe someday
i'll tell you.
Earth to melinda.
Sorry.
I was lost in thought.
What about?
Um... about...
about how to get lilly chen
to talk to her husband.
I never got her number
when she met me.
But she called you, right?
So it's probably
in my phone memory.
Hello.
Uh. Here. Look.
This number...
i don't recognize it.
That's got to be it.
So?
I just don't like
doing this kind of thing
over the phone.
You mean you really
don't like the hanging-up-
in-your-face part.
Exactly.
You online?
Yeah...
let me try something.
All right.
This is a reverse
phone directory site.
You put
the phone number in,
you get
an address, unless
it's been blocked.
You never cease to amaze me.
Ditto.
What?
You already
gave me this address.
There was a time
he was like my brother.
I'm so sorry, warren.
And lilly...
she was my wife.
We went through
so much together.
Look, we don't really
know what happened...
or when it happened.
I just died.
How could they...
you died a year ago, warren.
Things change.
People change. Sometimes
they have to move on.
I'm going to burn them.
No.
I will burn everything.
Jesse!
Ow! Jesse!
Hey, what the hell is...
god, it's hot.
Are you all right?
It's just my furnace.
What's wrong with you?
There is nothing wrong
with your furnace.
Ok? Just please
come outside?
Why?
Just please.
Warren's here.
Warren? What are you
talking about?
Warren's spirit
is still here.
Ok? He's been haunting
the restaurant.
He caused the fire.
And he knows about
you and lilly,
and he's really mad...
are you on drugs?
Warren, don't do this!
What the hell?
She says warren's
spirit is still here.
Look, he knows
about you and jesse.
You have to talk to him
before he burns
the house down.
Are you ok?
Aah! Please!
If that's you,
if you're doing this,
please stop!
I'm so sorry!
Tell him how much
you love him.
Use his name.
Warren!
I love you so much!
He's right here...
next to me.
Ask her how long.
How long was she with him?
Before i died?
He wants to know
if you were with jesse
before he died.
No, never...
it wasn't like that.
Warren...
i knew you loved me.
All i wanted was for us
to get our lives back...
i wanted you to quit,
to be happy...
i didn't mean for it
to happen, warren.
I never thought
of jesse that way...
but when you...
when you died...
we were
both so... so lost.
Jesse was destroyed.
He cried for you...
he called your name.
He was so torn up.
Warren: No!
He cried.
Jesse.
Now i remember.
He remembers.
Lilly was making
a stained glass window
for our bedroom.
I saw this beautiful piece
of glass on my lunch hour.
I hadn't bought her a gift
in such a long time.
And i'd had another fight
with jesse about the money.
I left work mad
and was halfway home
when i realized
i forgot the gift.
I went in the back way...
jesse!
What are you doing?
He watched you.
He watched you
set the fire.
Is this true?
Lilly, please.
You have to believe me.
I didn't mean to.
I did it for all of us!
We were going broke!
It wasn't working!
And i thought
if warren found out,
that he'd quit
for sure.
The insurance paid off,
we'd just start over.
Clean slate.
I made one mistake.
He wasn't supposed
to be there.
I don't know why
warren came back.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Get out!
Go on! Go on!
Go back!
I can't!
Why'd you come back here?!
Why did you do this?
Warren, get out of here!
Go on! Come on!
Make a run for it!
No! No, no, not there!
Aah!
Not there!
No!
I swear i didn't
mean to hurt him.
Just let him
take the blame.
Yeah, but what
difference did it make?
Nothing could have
brought warren back.
I never said he did it.
The arson
investigators did.
Lilly please...
uhh!
Get away from me!
It wasn't the reopening
that woke you up.
It was lilly and jesse
being together.
You had to tell her that
the man she was living
with killed you.
Please tell her...
i always loved her.
No matter
how hard i worked...
no matter how much it seemed
like i wasn't there.
I did it for her.
I wanted to give us a life.
He wants you to know
that he always loved you.
And he worked so hard
because he wanted
the two of you to have
a good life...
we did have a good life.
You and me
together, warren.
I didn't need
anything else.
How can i be dead...
if this hurts so much?
If i love her so much?
You'll always
love her.
Tell her no matter
what happens...
i'll be waiting for her.
Tell her i'll never
forget her eyes.
I'll see them again,
with mine someday.
He's ready
to cross over now.
Well, are you going
to open it,
or you just going to
wait for your x-ray
vision to kick in?
Come on.
What's the occasion?
There doesn't have
to be an occasion.
I just saw it
and thought of you.
Ok.
Hot dogs!
Whoa!
It works
and everything.
Ha ha! Perfect!
You are a genius.
I love you.
What a surprise.
Um, you know,
i don't want you
to be late for the guys.
So, you should
get going.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Hey, you know what?
Could you do me a favor?
Grab my jacket
out of the closet. I'm
just gonna plug this in.
I just want to see if
it works once, you know?
I'll get an extension cord.
Sure.
Sometimes these things
are a little temperamental.
Right.
The fuse might not
hook in just right.
I'll get your jacket.
There's a trick to it.
Dinner at the umbrella room?
I'd thought
you'd forgotten.
Never.
I'd thought
you'd forgotten.
www.tvsubtitles.net