my name is melinda gordon.
i'm married...
i live in a small town...
and i own an antique shop.
i might be just like you...
except that from the time
i was a little girl,
i knew that i could
talk to the dead.
woman: it's
all right, honey.
"earth-bound spirits,"
my grandmother called them.
they're stuck here
because they have unfinished
business with the living
and they come to me for help.
in order to tell
you my story
i have to tell y
melinda: well, it was
definitely worth the trip.
i mean, they want to do
the estate sale so fast,
there was very
minimal haggle.
jim: the haggle factor's
very important.
[giggling]
yeah, i'm going to
have to hire a truck
to go up there next week.
damn. this road is
really dark.
hey, be careful.
how far out are you?
i have no idea.
you've got to get a gps.
hey! grandview--
19 miles. whoo-hoo.
hmm. oh, and other signs
of civilization.
hey, an old fruit stand.
you know what?
yeah.
[chuckling]
and, um...
well, a car, sort of.
well, that's weird.
mel?
i think i just went
in a circle.
mel?
jim?
mel.
[static]
jim! oh!
redial, redial,
redial.
ooh.
great.
ok.
i'm talking to the police
right now, and they're going
to be here any minute.
are you ok in there?
oh. yeah.
yeah, i'm ok.
sorry if i scared you.
you stuck?
yeah, it died.
pop the hood.
ok.
are you looking
for it, too?
i am looking for what?
someone's going
to die.
oh.
try it now.
huh? oh. ok.
oh! you're
a miracle worker.
how did you do that?
you need anything else?
how do i make it
back to route 47?
you're all turned around.
just hang a u-ie,
look for signs for 86 south,
and then 47 should be
about a mile after that.
ok, thank you.
bye.
www.1000fr.com present
capture:frm@maoren
sync:frm@¹ûº£îà
i just don't remember
you ever being haunted by an actual skeleton
before.
oh, it was a ghost,
believe me.
don't they usually look
the way they did
when they died
the first time
they come to you?
yeah, so let's not
even think about what
happened to this guy.
how about let's
stay off that road
so we don't ever run
into halloween man
again, huh?
i love the jim clancy
simple approach.
avoidance--it's worked
for guys for centuries.
he said that someone
was going to die.
that doesn't exactly
lend itself to avoidance.
all right.
what does it mean?
i don't know. i'll try
and figure it out.
how?
don't know.
see you for lunch.
same time?
same bench?
yeah.
all right.
wow. what a haul!
melinda: straight sale,
no consignment.
yeah, well, the problem is
i want to buy most
of it for myself.
and you are
my best customer.
yeah, i need to find a
way out of that cycle.
what are you doing?
oh, just trying to avoid
the physical labor
i know must come.
hey, is ned coming by?
no, he is doing
a study group with
3 kids from school.
they take turns
at each other's houses.
oh, that sounds
like a good way
to make friends.
well, i keep
volunteering my house
for all his sessions,
so i can basically sit
in the middle of the
floor and stare at them.
just as a precaution.
yeah. is that
too much to ask?
but, you know, of course
they didn't bite.
mmm, i sense an issue.
it's all starting
to be about his friends.
that's what
he calls them.
"they're my friends,
mom." no names.
[giggling]
sounds like he's turning out
to be a very normal kid.
i guess so.
hey. you know, you never
told me what happened
on your date with tim.
well, there would have
actually had to have
been a date
in order for me
to tell you about it.
what happened?
he didn't show.
what?
it's no big deal.
melinda--
melinda?
sorry.
i'd really
appreciate it if you
wouldn't tell jim.
right.
are you ok?
i'm fine.
you're the one
who looks like she
just saw a ghost.
melinda: why is it
harder when you're
trying to get lost?
jim: you're doing great.
i have no idea where we are.
didn't we used to have
a map in here?
hey, thanks
for doing this.
do you think i'd let you
come back out on this road
again by yourself?
aha! map.
hey, do these mean
anything to you?
19026?
what's left
on our mortgage?
no.
last plumber's bill?
no again.
i have no idea.
oh!
what was...
gas?
no, i have half
a tank.
hmm.
do you see that?
what does that mean?
i was hoping
you'd tell me.
it was in--i wasn't
here the last time.
uh, got the brake.
it won't move!
your feet off
the gas?
both feet are on
the brakes!
oh, damn it!
it's going to be all right.
it's going to be ok.
ok, ok, ok.
i'll pop it into neutral.
ok.
keep your feet down.
i'm trying!
turn it,
turn it.
oh!
all right.
what?
looking for
the midnight circle?
what?
someone's going to die--
see, now i know we're
going the wrong way.
we're all the way on
the other side of town.
well, if i can just get
the adrenaline that's
still coursing
through my veins
to slow down, i might
figure it out.
sorry.
why can't we just go
home at night
and watch dvds
like normal couples?
hey, look, we can stop
and ask for directions.
i don't need directions.
i got it figured out.
i just need to find
this one road.
wait a minute.
that's the girl who helped me
on the road last night.
engine seems fine.
just running
a little hot, i think.
anyway, if you want
to leave it here,
i can run some diagnostics.
oh, no. i don't think
there's anything wrong
with the car.
wow. that's cool.
do you mind?
it's got the roll bar
and the magnesium wheels,
4-inch exhaust, right?
your husband knows
cars. cool.
while he's distracted,
will you please tell me
how to get back
to route 47?
oh, yeah, let me
write it down here.
thank you.
so, how long
have you worked here?
i own it.
seriously?
mm-hmm.
i--i mean,
not that that's--
no, it's ok.
my father, he loved cars
and he didn't have a son;
fast forward, here i am,
or something like that.
wow. i'm in awe.
ha ha!
i don't know
the first thing
about cars.
well, we don't deal too much
with everyday car staff.
most of our clients
are serious racers,
real car people.
the road that you found
me on last night--
do you know if
there have been
any accidents there?
you know, like serious
people dying accidents?
not that i know of.
any other weird things?
weird like how?
i don't know, weird like
cars going haywire,
seeing strange things
on the road.
sorry. other than
the odd roadkill,
not much goes on out there.
anyway, here's
the directions,
and my number's on
there if you have
any more car trouble.
thank you so much.
have you ever heard of
the midnight circle?
what's that?
i don't know.
me neither.
ok, joe. it's ready.
time to unpeel
your husband away
from my cars.
honey, honey.
can we just move in
here for, like, a week?
what do you think?
oh. business, huh?
directions.
the midnight what?
the midnight circle.
is that a name,
a place, a thing?
none of the above.
all of the above.
oh. well, did you
check the phone book?
yeah, there was
no listing.
huh. thank you.
i'll see you next time.
hey, mom.
hey, hey! how was school?
i need $10.
oh. for school?
no.
well, then, for what?
i don't know.
with my friends.
in case we stop for
pizza or something.
are there children at
this midnight circle,
because if not, please,
take me there now.
hey, do you know
what it is, ned?
the midnight circle?
um, no.
never heard of it.
so, jim is working tonight,
and i am starving.
you want to go to lento's
and grab a bite?
oh, i would love to,
but i really have to
make sure that ned's
doing his homework.
can i get a raincheck?
yeah, no problem.
good night.
ok. good night.
aah!
you don't belong.
they were just
giving me a ride home.
i don't want you in a car
with people i don't know.
those kids are
too old for you, ned.
they like me.
they're my friends.
wait. that's
your study group?
what's the big deal?
the big deal is
i'm your mother.
i want to know who you're
with and where you are.
you want to control
everything i do.
most of it, yes.
that's my job.
you are not an adult yet, ned,
as much as you think you are.
and don't blame melinda.
she told me because
she cares about you,
not because she wanted
to get you in trouble.
i could tell things,
too.
hey, where are you going?
home to prison.
melinda: ned!
i keep your secrets.
hey, that's not
what this is about.
who were those guys?
they go to my school.
they help me study.
now i look totally lame.
look, there was
a bumper sticker
with numbers on it.
what does it mean?
hey.
i know when i talked about
the midnight circle yesterday
that you knew what it was.
i don't.
i'm not playing around, ned.
there is a ghost
attached to your friends,
or the midnight circle,
whatever it is--
a dangerous ghost.
you have to tell me.
i don't know anything.
hi. i'm...
melinda gordon. yes.
i know all about you.
i'm kate payne.
i'm so glad to meet
you finally.
are you?
well, yes. ha ha.
man: get on there.
get on there.
i'm telling you
to get on there.
maybe i chose
a bad time.
no. he's in a bit
of a bad mood,
but don't let it
bother you.
it was lovely to meet you.
get on there.
just do me
the favor and
just get on there.
get on there.
you do realize that
that's an inanimate object
that can't understand you?
oh, it understands me.
they all do.
they understand
every word i'm saying.
who?
who? who? the nail,
the picture frame,
the hammer.
the hammer
understands me.
the bastards have the
whole thing planned out.
i was warned you were
in a bad mood.
yeah, i'm in a bad mood
because some people
really know how to get
under my skin, ok?
now, where's my hammer?
i don't even have
my hammer now.
i had my hammer
right here.
i'm losing my mind.
looking for this?
yes, i am.
and you know what?
i've had just about
as much aggravation
as i can stand for
one day, thank you.
ok, sorry. bad timing.
and i don't want to
talk about it, ok?
so, please don't try
to drag it out of me?
ok, no problem.
i'll see ya.
it's about my wife,
if you must know.
well, i don't must know,
so if you'd rather
not talk about it...
thank you.
i feel so much better.
now, what can i do for
you, melinda gordon?
do you have any idea
what these numbers mean?
1 9 0 2 0 6.
map coordinates?
checked it already.
doesn't add up.
well, it adds up
in numerology to...
9.
meaning?
meaning 9.
9 is the divine number,
the number
of completion,
the eternal number.
the chinese considered
it the celestial number.
and there's the famous
9 course meal
at my favorite
vietnamese restaurant,
beef or fish.
is any of this
helping you?
not really.
of course not.
because none of this
has anything to do
with numerology.
it doesn't?
no, it doesn't.
but that doesn't stop me
from going on and on
with all the minutiae
i know, does it?
it's a date!
it's a date.
challenge me next time
you come in here, won't you?
19th of february, 2006.
that's a year ago
next monday.
it's a significant date.
february 19, 1945 was
the battle of iwo jima.
the phonograph was
invented in 1878.
paul simon writes
"sounds of silence"
1964, february 19.
big makeout song for me.
how do you know all that?
well, while the other
kids were out
playing baseball--
you were studying.
no. i was chasing girls.
i never had to study.
studying i never did
because knowledge
came so easy to me.
girls, not so much.
ok. have you ever heard
of the midnight circle?
knitting club
for insomniacs?
you're hilarious.
yes or no?
no.
no? that's it?
wait, there's no medieval
significance or minutiae?
uh, oh! no.
i don't know
anything about it.
ok, then.
i have a picture
to hang.
great.
you know, if you do
ever want to talk,
i'm a really good listener.
ah...
i don't know
if i have any
training for that.
yeah, i didn't think so.
keep it in mind.
i can't believe
you lied to me.
it was a secret.
i had to promise
i wouldn't tell.
and that was the
midnight circle?
there's nothing else?
'cause no more
games, ned.
it's a race, a couple
of times a month.
they race for money,
pink slips, stuff like that.
and there aren't any rules.
where does your mom
think you are?
in bed.
i climbed out the window.
ohh...
you have
no idea how much
trouble you're in.
delia was furious.
i mean, she was
so embarrassed.
here she is thinking
that her son is asleep
in his bedroom.
i thought you said
you weren't going
to go out on that road
again without me.
i had to go when
i had the chance.
is that where
you saw the ghost?
yeah. he was in the car
that crashed.
you think he caused it?
i don't know what
to think.
i mean, i know that
the ghost is attached
to this world,
but it's all so secret.
you should have seen
the way they all scattered
when they heard the sirens.
you think he's trying
to hurt the racers?
yeah. and i'm really
worried about cindy,
because he said that
somebody's going to die.
maybe that's the way
he died--in a crash.
i keep checking online,
but i don't have
a lot to go on.
i don't know his name.
i don't know what
he looked like.
i don't know when he died.
hmm.
i'll check
the records at work,
ask around.
look, no offense.
it's just not something
we talk about.
yeah, i understand,
but people may get hurt.
that's half the thrill
of the whole thing.
for some people.
ok, you almost got
killed last night.
last night?
i don't think so.
i was at home in bed
last night.
i don't know what
you're talking about.
sorry. um, melissa,
is it?
melinda.
yeah, well,
i got to run.
there's coffee
and pastry in
the break room.
help yourself.
thanks for coming by.
yeah.
he died in an illegal
street race 19th of
february last year
in the same spot where
my car first broke down.
yeah. it says he owned
pike custom owners.
he was racing a guy
named ray peters.
there were no charges filed.
there's nothing else.
look at the bottom.
survived by his fiancee
cindy brown.
cindy cindy.
exactly.
now i know who
the ghost is and who
he's attached to.
what's he trying to do?
protect her?
i don't know.
maybe he's going to wipe
out all the people who
race against her?
sounds like
a true romantic.
all right, what are
you going to do?
i've got to find
this ghost tonight.
you doing anything?
cool.
just, uh, stay in the beam
of the headlight.
yeah. i'll wave
if i need you.
i know your name.
gordon pike.
i know that you died
in a car race.
i can help.
i think i know
what's going on.
this has to do with
cindy, doesn't it?
yeah, it's about cindy.
well, i can help you
talk to her if you want,
if it'll help you cross over,
but you can't stay here.
you just can't.
i trained her,
taught her to race.
everything she knows
is because of me.
yeah, but that doesn't mean
you can protect her forever.
i don't want
to protect her.
i'm going to kill her.
she thought she was
as good as me.
she wanted to prove
she was better.
i don't understand.
i thought you two
were a couple.
weren't you engaged?
i was her first love.
she thought i was
a rock star.
most people were
afraid of me because
i wanted to race.
not her.
i've never
had anybody look at
me that way before.
ok, so what went wrong?
i let her drive my car.
what?
i taught her to race.
i showed her
everything i know.
she was good, too.
a natural.
then she didn't
need me anymore.
she wanted to prove she
was faster and smarter.
was she?
smarter, maybe.
she really knew how
to mess with my head
before a race.
it started with
just kid stuff.
????
then she had to keep
pushing it.
like, sometimes she'd
mess with my nitrous.
nitrous?
you inject it into the
manifold when you need
a last-second boost.
come
or she'd mess with
my fuel mixture.
little things.
but then i started
losing,
and it wasn't
funny anymore.
the night i died was
a big race between me
and ray peters,
a 15k payday.
and she warned me she
wasn't going to let me
get paid that night.
so, what happened?
i came out of the turn,
hit the nitrous button.
next thing i know...
boom!
i'm floating above my
car watching it burn.
and i see my body
just laying there,
all the skin burned off.
do you really think
that cindy could do
something like that?
maybe, maybe not.
same result.
she took things too far.
did you cause the crash
the other night?
i was just having some
fun, making jimmy bash
her around a little.
i'm saving the real
thing for monday.
the 19th of february.
the day you died, a year ago.
well, i'm sorry.
i don't mean to make fun.
no, it's ok.
i'm used to people
being in tears
right about now.
ha ha!
i can just picture
gordon running around
like a ghost,
still trying to win races.
what a funny idea.
you know
i'm not kidding.
oh, no. you seem like
you really believe it.
he told me that he made
jimmy run into your car.
what do you want?
i think gordon's
trying to hurt you.
well, he couldn't do that
anymore than he already has.
he told me that he
taught you everything
about racing.
he did. but once i got
the hang of it,
i could make a car do
any damn thing i wanted.
my very first race
i won.
then i won the next one
and the one after that.
it was crazy.
right away, people
started to know my name.
gordon got so jealous.
he still thought he
was better than me,
and he never let
me forget it.
he even got a car
straight from japan
with raght-hand drive--
anything to get attention.
so, naturally,
i'd challenge him,
and i'd beat him.
over and over again.
i wasn't just gordon pike's
girlfriend anymore.
he was cindy brown's
boyfriend.
he said he was
your first love.
oh, he was. ha ha.
he was everything
i thought a man
was supposed to be.
and then he showed
he showed me what
was possible.
i mean, i never
thought i had any
kind of talent,
let alone this kind.
just one problem.
what?
once he saw
how good i was,
he wanted to put
the genie back
in the bottle.
like how?
he'd do anything to keep
guys from racing me.
what happened
the night he died?
gordon was pissed.
ray peters had never
been beaten before.
he had to wait in line
to race him.
me and you, finally.
man, i'm shaki
yeah, you will be.
you're the one i should be
racing, not your old man.
you're the one to beat,
from what i hear.
yeah, well, you have
to get past him first.
done deal.
he was out of control
after that, and i guess ????
what do you mean?
i liked it.
i liked that ray
said what he said.
hell, it was more
of a compliment than
i ever got from gordon.
he thinks that you did
something to his car to
cause the crash that night.
i had nothing to do with
what happened to gordon.
ray peters ran him
off the track.
everyone knows that.
so, ray peters
caused the accident?
the king of
dirty tricks?
he probably did it just
coming out of the turn
where no one could see.
yeah, but gordon's
car blew up.
look!
i did love gordon,
even when i hated him.
you understand?
not really, no.
i would never have done
anything to hurt gordon.
not like that.
and if he is really
here like you say he is,
he knows it.
i feel like i've gone
from "west side story"
to "who's afraid
of virginia woolf."
it's just so weird.
two people who start out
loving each other
end up hating
each other.
how does that happen?
the question you gotta
ask is why do they keep
making it happen.
what do you mean?
well, i mean, everybody's
got a storeroom, right?
resentment, grudges, anger?
most people, they open
up that storeroom
and they let
a few of them out.
you know,
they deal with them.
they get rid of them.
something tells me that
your storeroom would be
standing room only.
yeah, sometimes i
gotta knock down the wall
into the next storeroom,
but the point is,
you
know, a couple, two people,
they start using those bad
things from that storeroom
against each other,
why stay?
why not move on?
maybe they're
getting something
out of it.
yeah. they need
to be miserable.
for some people, that's as
strong as the need to breathe.
it's like they're
feeding off each other,
like they're trying
to convince each other
that they don't
deserve to be happy.
mmm.
makes me glad i'm
basically a simpleton.
ha! far from it.
you gotta keep these
two people away from
each other for good.
how are you going
to do that?
i'm going to a guy
named ray peters.
now you want me
to hang out with racers?
what i want is for you
to introduce me
to ray peters.
it's important.
ghost related?
yeah, if you must know.
i like to be kept a
little more in the loop.
you're unbelievable.
you could just think of me
as a sounding board.
look, are you going
to introduce me to
ray peters or not?
are you going to save me
from my mother hanging
me by my ankles?
you're lucky to have
a mother who cares
so much about you,
and we are not going
anywhere near cars.
do you know where
ray peters works?
so, the much feared
ray peters delivers pizza?
yeah.
very, very fast.
ok.
why is she asking me
so many questions, ned?
look, she's cool.
she's with me.
ok, i got it, ned.
thanks.
i want to talk about
that night.
do you remember
anything?
like i could forget it.
am i happy gordon
kissed the blue wave?
no. am i happy
it wasn't me? yes.
ok, about
the accident.
people say that
you ran gordon
off the track.
people can say whatever
they want to say.
ok, but did you,
'cause cindy
thinks you did.
what if i did?
i want to know.
not because
i want to cause
you any trouble,
but because
it's important.
whatever happened that night
is between me and gordon,
and gordon's dead.
so, i guess you will
really never know.
will i see you tonight?
um...
wait you're racing tonight?
you bet your ass.
i'm racing cindy brown,
finally.
in memory of gordon.
now you know why i like
to hang out with these guys.
you, in the store,
right now.
gordon: if it was ray peters,
how come i don't remember?
you said yourself you
didn't remember exactly
what happened.
cindy was always
messing with my car.
that's the only thing that
coul
not ray forcing me
off the track.
i don't think she'd do
anything on purpose.
i think she still
has feelings for you.
you think?
yeah, i do.
i don't
think she would ever
try to kill you.
look, make your peace,
gordon.
cross over.
be done with it.
there's only one thing
i need to cross over.
what?
and that's for her
to cross over with me.
and i'm going to make sure
that that happens.
come with me to
the garage and let me
help you talk to her.
you go.
tell her i said hello.
man: if you do this,
then you can forget
about turning pro.
cindy: this is more
important than turning pro.
what, revenge?
how about justice?
nobody ever did anything
about how gordon died.
they all just let it go.
and they think i don't care.
well, now they're going
to learn different.
i waited a year to do this.
poetic justice.
that's what gordon
would have liked.
people are going
to see you do it.
i've just got to force him
up into the wall,
and there's a good chance
he'll roll and he'll get
exactly what he deserves.
[sigh] ray peters
killed gordon.
tonight i'm going
to return the favor.
cindy couldn't hurt
me if she tried.
i wouldn't
underestimate her.
why? because she thinks
i made gordon crash?
no, because she thinks
you made gordon die.
she can give me
her best shot.
look, you want to know
who killed gordon pike?
you really want to know?
yes.
gordon pike killed
gordon pike. that's it.
what are you
talking about?
he was trying to run me
off the track.
but i knew his move,
saw him do it
a hundred times.
i braked on him.
he shot off my fender
and went into a bad
spin, rolled over.
i think he ruptured his
fuel tank, i don't know.
but when he hit the
ditch, his car blew.
he died because he
was trying to screw me
and it backfired.
is he right?
gordon:
he was ready for me.
he knew what
i was going to do.
he used my own momentum
to put me into a spin.
what
i hit the nitrous to try
to power out of it.
everything went white.
who the hell
are you talking to?
come lets do it
????
i loosened the bolt on
her steering column.
what?
you're nuts.
stop the car!
????
??
???
????
no
watch out! watch out!
get out of the way!
let me in. watch out!
give her some room.
give her some room!
i'm ok! i'm ok.
what happened?
i don't know.
the steering went out.
i swear, i checked it,
cindy. it was tight.
it was him, wasn't it?
tell me. it was him!
ok, cindy, please.
he knows what happened,
how it wasn't you
and it wasn't ray.
it was his own mistake.
well, he just
tried to kill me!
no, he saved you.
he knew that
something was wrong,
and he saved you.
tell her i'm sorry.
he's here.
you felt him.
you could feel him
in that car with you.
i did.
i did feel him.
ok. he can hear you.
gordon?
do you really hate me
enough to want to kill me?
you want to be
better than me.
he knows that you wanted
to be better than him.
so, you turned on me?
you made me feel like i
was doing something wrong,
just because i got so good?
i thought it would take
you away from me. i...
he was afraid that
he would lose you.
the more he wanted
to stop me,
the more i wanted to
hurt him.
i'm sorry.
i'm sorry that you thought
i could do something
that horrible to you
that night, but...
i guess i would've
thought the same thing.
what does that say
about us, huh?
wait. is this it?
is that light for me?
it means you're ready
to cross over.
what?
can you tell her
that i needed her more
than i ever wanted to.
and that's why i pushed
her away and that's why
i held her so close.
and tell her
if she's smart,
she's going to
forget all about me.
she's never going
to forget you.
gordon!
no, i don't want
to forget about you.
you changed my life.
i--you made a difference.
just couldn't handle it.
i was screwed up.
if i had one more chance...
tell her to take
my chance for me.
hey.
what just happened?
he's gone.
gone for good?
it's up to you.
you can make a place
for him and he will
always be there.
hey...
there are some other
things he wanted me
to mention.
ok.
>
www.tvsubtitles.net