Subs by Zhalom and Raceman
www.forom.com
My name is Melinda Gordon.
I'm married,
I live in a small town,
and I own an antique shop.
I might be just like you.
Except that from
the time I was a little girl,
I knew that I could
talk to the dead.
It's all right, honey.
Earthbound spirits,
my grandmother called them.
They're stuck here because they have
unfinished business with the living
and they come to me for help.
In order to tell you my story,
I have to tell you theirs.
So...
this is really,really great.
Out in nature,
no one but us for miles.
Who knew that camping
could be so much fun.
What'd I tell you?
The clean air. The smell.
- There's nothing like it.
- Yeah. I'm getting that feeling.
I'm just glad you
came this time, ok?
Besides, I thought when you said we were
going to the woods,you meant the woods.
That place where Delia
always wants to take you to?
Yeah. Salt scrubs,
seaweed wraps, massages.
That would be the one.
Pushaw! Uhh!
Besides, we got all
the luxury right here.
Ahh. And these hands,
they got more magic in them
than any seafood wrap.
Seaweed.
Oh, right. That's it.
Ahh. Yep.
Ahh. This place hasn'
changed a bit.
You used to come out
here with your father?
Yeah.
Me, my brother...
and my old man.
No mom?
No. She loved camping
about as much as you do.
Hey! Ha ha.
Oh, no.
Sorry. The wood
probably was just green.
All right.
Oh!
Why don't you-
I'll go-
This the crisp air you
were talking about?
Did I forget to mention-ahh-
we might get a little weather.
Zip it.
Hey, do you hear that?
Hmm? Crickets.
Not that.
- Lanie.
- That.
Lanie.
Hello?
Somebody out there?
Lanie.
Come out,come out,
wherever you are. Come out,
come out
Hello?
Crap.
Oh, where is it?
Where is it?
Hey. No, no, no. It's ok.
It's ok, it's ok.
You all right?
Oh, I'm so glad it's you.
I'm glad I saw your light because when
I woke up and you weren't in bed,
- ... I almost freaked out.
- Sorry. I heard something.
A woman's voice.
I found this.
That's been there for a while.
Yeah. Look at this.
The, uh...
the  moldy sippy cup?
No. No, there was a-
there was a creepy baby doll.
A baby doll.
The woman's voice,
it sounded desperate, and...
I don't know. I just feel like maybe
I should stay in case she comes back.
No.
I think she knows where you're staying.
We're the only ones up here for miles.
Ok. You're right. If she
needs me, she'll find me.
Yeah. Come on. Let's
go and get some sleep.
I got some plans for tomorrow.
Lanie.
Come out,come out, wherever you are.
Hello?
Don't be afraid.
I wanna help you.
Lanie!
Morning, sunshine.
It's disgusting how cheerfu
you are in the morning.
Well, you sleep much
deeper out here in the...
fine air.
Speak for yourself.
Ah. Breakfast smells
so good. I'm starving.
Yeah. Breakfast was about 4 hours ago.
This would be lunch.
Just tell me there's coffee.
All right.
Do I sense a less than
perfect night's sleep?
Well, between the ghosts,
stinking air-
Air mattress,
I didn't sleep all night.
She came back? Why didn't you wake me up?
'Cause I didn't have any dynamite?
You know, it's weird.
She made the doll appear in the fire.
That's creepy.
What's the message?
I don't know. Stay away?
She's done everything she can to get
rid of us,even that weird windstorm.
You know, I'm sorry.
I hope I haven't tainted
this place for you.
No. I feel sorry for your ghost.
Yeah. That hide and seek
song she keeps singing
makes me think
she's looking for a child.
Well, that would explain
why she's so territorial.
She's trying to say something else.
I just don't know what.
Yummy. I'm starving.
You're going to need it.
- Oh? - I was thinking that
we'd go on a little hike.
A hike sounds nice.
Might have to make a small detour.
Oh, come on. You got to admit,
this is kind of exciting.
Ah, I don't know. To me,
a swimming hole's exciting.
Haunted, rusty cars,not so exciting.
It doesn't look like
there was an accident.
Maybe they just ran off the road.
but  there is no road here.
Aha. There used to be.
The main road used to
run through the pass
till the forest service took over
and made this all a reserve.
Look at you with that thing.
Maybe this was a side road.
Well, how long ago was that?
I don't know. My dad and I first started
coming out here about 20 years ago.
car's been here at least that long.
I think I found a registration.
- Only thing I can make out is Anna.
- Well, it's a first name anyway.
Hey,  do you think you can trace this
license when you get back to work?
I can do better than that.
I can request a history of all
911 calls made out of the region.
I can do that if we get out of here now
because I'd really like to
make it to the falls by dark.
Last one there gets pushed down!
Oh, um, there's some really great
vintage baby rattles over there.
Thanks. I'm just waiting on a friend.
Ok.
These alabaster lamps
are really hard to find.
You've got a good eye.
No. Absolutely not.
That skateboard park is an
accident waiting to happen.
You sure grant's mom
is going to be there?
Is my receipt in the bag?
Can you just put
her on the phone?
- What? What do you mean she's not there?
- Here's your receipt.
No solvents. Just some
soap and water and, um...
something for your next purchase.
- Thank you.
Ok, fine,but if I find out that you
didn't wear a helmet, you are dead.
Yes. I love you, too.
I am so sorry.
That woman is never
coming back again, is she?
Oh, I think she will. I gave
her a 20% off coupon.
You definitely don't miss a trick.
Thanks for covering for me.
Anytime. Was that ned?
Yeah.
I always thought I'd worry
about him less as he grew up,
but I worry about him more.
You know, at this rate, I won't stop
worrying about him until I'm dead.
If you're lucky.
- Chances are, I'll still be worrying
from my grave. - Lanie!
It sounds like I chose a
bad time to leave you...
- Come out,come out, wherever you are!
- With the store.
Oh, no. Just the opposite.
It was great to take my
mind off the little daredevil.
So, was camping as dreadful
as you thought it would be?
Actually, it was kind of exciting.
It was good for jimmy and
i to have some time alone.
Aha. Fess up. Do I detect a little
biological alarm clock going off?
Uh, ooh. No, nothing like that. Mm-mmm.
Come on. You can tell me.
I know I gripe,but motherhood rocks.
You are going to love it.
I'm sure I will. Can you just
excuse me for a second?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to
see your adorable baby,
and, oh, my god. She's so cute.
Thanks.
It's like she's testing me,
trying to see if she can trust me.
You think this ghost
is a worried mom...
looking for her kid.
Yeah, but I didn't realize until
today how intense that feeling is.
Wait a minute.
What happened today?
I just had a couple of anxious
moms at the store. Delia being one.
Please tell me that this is not the same
stove that you used with your dad.
Yes, miss change the subject.
That is the same stove
I used with my father.
And it works like new.
I got a little something for you.
That's the trace, with an
address for one anna fowler.
You traced the license already?
Yep. That's how I roll.
It expired in '86.
That's probably around when she died.
Well, we'll know that for sure
when the 911 trace comes back,
which will probably take
a couple of weeks,
because anything more than 10
years old is in the main archives.
You're my hero.
This is brookside. It's close.
Don't get too excited.
Anybody who lives in that house
probably never heard of... anna fowler.
Well, I have a secret weapon.
Delia can trace real
estate transactions for me.
You know, one of these days
she is going to get suspicious.
Yeah, and one of these days, I'm going
to have to do something about it.
Come out,
come out, wherever you are.
Uh, you know,I'll be right back.
Can you throw this thing
in the trash for me?
Yeah, sure.
Anna?
Anna, I can't help you if
you won't talk to me.
Are you looking for someone?
I have to find her.
Who do you have to find?
My baby girl.
She's lost.
Can you tell me
what happened?
I... I was cold.
Mel, where'd you put the, um...
I scared her away,didn't I?
Yeah.
But  she left us something.
Lanie was a baby
she must dead too
I really shouldn't be doing this.
You said you wanted to keep
a foot in real estate.
Yes, to make money,but not
to snoop on other people's records.
Well, it's for a good cause.
A little girl's missing her doll.
Well, she wouldn't be a little girl anymore
if we're looking at records this far back.
Ok. Here it is.
The house was sold in 1991 and
the owner's name was brad fowler.
Does it say anything else about him?
Like what, he's a gemini and
likes long walks on the beach?
I mean, like his occupation.
Uh...  he was a therapist.
Hey, maybe you can kill
two birds with one stone.
You're hilarious. Thank you.
Sure.
I just thought you'd like to
know that the car was found.
This is, uh...
this is strange.
All those years...
I'm guessing it
belonged to your wife?
My wife is dead.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
it's just I found something in the car that
I thought may have belonged to a child.
Lanie.
This was my little girl'S.
It was really very,very thoughtful
of you to go to all this trouble.
It was no trouble.
My wife, anna, we were...
separated at the time.
She died up in those woods...
in a snowstorm.
Just a bit of a shock seeing all of this.
I understand.
I'd rather not have this.
Maybe you can give it to
a hospital or something.
Brings up some pretty
tough memories.
I don't mean to pry,
but did something happen
to your daughter also?
Worse thing that can
happen to a little girl.
I'm so sorry.
She was abandoned
by her mother.
You mean she didn't
die in the storm?
No.
She wasn't even in the car.
She was at home with me.
Where's my baby?!
I don't know yet.
Are you hiding her?
No.
I'm trying to help you, but I need
to know what you remember.
Nothing. I don't remember anything.
Ok. I know that this is hard,
but you have to try.
It will come if you're not
afraid of remembering.
But I am afraid.
Look at the doll.
That's what you were protecting.
I was scared.
It was bad out.
I knew it was stupid
to be on the road,
but I felt like I couldn't stop.
Like I shouldn't stop.
I don't know why.
I panicked.
Where was my baby?
I couldn't remember.
Anna, I...
I found your husband.
Lane was with him that night.
She wasn't in the car with you.
What?
She's alive.
I can't believe it.
Can I see her?
No, I haven't found her yet.
But there's something else.
Your husband said
that you left him...
and lane, that
he raised her alone.
No.
No. No, I would never do that.
She's my life,she's all I have.
Yeah. I'm sure that
that's true,but brad said-
no! I didn't abandon my baby!
Ok.
Maybe I should talk
to her alone first.
See how she feels.
Brad said that she
lives nearby, so...
I have to see her.
You will.
I swear. Just...
let me do this first.
My baby's alive.
Hi. I'm melinda gordon.
I own the antique
shop in town.
I found something that
I think you might want.
I talked to your dad-
oh, my god. My muffins.
Come in. Come in.
please don't burn
Hot, hot, hot!
Oh, oh!god
You'd never guess
I do this for a living.
Ah. Chocolate peanut butter cup.
My new greatest invention.
Those aren't the ones they
sell at village java, are they?
The very same.
I love those. I'm totally addicted.
It's part of my evil plan.
I do birthdays, too.
So, you were saying that,
uh, my father sent you?
But if what you found is a wedding dress,
- ... you can forget about it.
- A dress?
I know he means well, and I'm sure
your vintage pieces are very sweet,
but I told him a gazillion times,
it's a hawaiian luau.
I mean, I love the guy to bits, but
it's my wedding, right?
I'm-you know-actually-
ah! Oh!
Lanie!
I'm  such a klutz.
Don't scare me like that.
I thought you were
at the library studying.
Well, I couldn't stay
away from you so long.
Ok. Enough with the flowers.
I get it. You're sorry,
but we are running
out of vases.
Oh, god. I'm so rude.
Todd, this is melinda.
She owns that cute
antique store downtown.
Oh, yeah. It was nice to meet you.
Hey, babe, I'm gonna squeeze in a
couple more hours before dinner.
Great.
As if getting married
wasn't enough,
he's studying for the bar.
Mmm. Why all the flowers?
he feels bad.
It was a nothing argument really.
It was my fault.
But who's complaining, right?
Right. Um, actually,
I didn't come here about a dress.
I wanted to return
something to you.
Uh, no. That's-that's not mine.
Why would you think it is?
Because I found it
in your mom's car.
Lanie
It;s yours,isn't?
What?
we should go
outside and talk.
Ok.
My mom left
when I was 3,but
it still gets to me.
So you remember her?
Some.
How she used to sing along to the radio,
the way she smelled when
she kissed me good night.
The rest I just
learned from my dad.
Did your dad
tell you why she left?
Look, um...
you're real
easy to talk to, but...
why are you asking me this?
Your mother...
her spirit is still here.
I've seen her.
I've spoken to her.
You're telling me you've
seen my mother's ghost?
I know.
Believe me, I know
that it sounds crazy,
but... it's my gift.
She's the one who
gave me this doll,
and she wanted to find you very badly.
She loves you very much.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
What?
Nothing. I'm just
telling you the truth.
My mother was mentally ill.
My father said she had
delusional paranoia.
She left us.
She left me,
and then she died,
so I couldn't even know her.
Uh! What the hell!
- What happened?
- I don't know.
it just explosion
Anna.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I-I think
anna is doing this.
I'm just not really sure why.
Look,I don't know what you're trying to
pull, but I want you out of here,ok? Now.
You ok?
Uh... yeah.
- What happened in there?
- I had to see her.
She needs me.
She's a big girl now.
She grew up really well.
You don't have to worry
about her anymore.
Yes,I do!
Look,if your marriage ended badly,
I'm really sorry about that,
but you can't take
it out on lane and todd.
Believe me,the best thing that you can do
for your daughter is just to move on.
No.
As long as my baby needs me,
I'm never leaving.
Please!
- Todd?!
- No!
What's going
on in there?!
Todd?!
Hello?
You have to get
over here quick.
I think I need you.
The door's jammed.
Don't worry.
Jim will get us in.
Todd?!
Todd,
where are you,man?
Oh,my god!
Baby!
It's all right. He's all right.
Come over here. Come over here.
Oh,my god.
He's bleeding.
Go away!
He's gonna
need stitches.
- I'm gonna go grab
- my kit. Pressure.
It wasn't enough
that she abandoned me?
She's got to come back from
the grave to haunt me?!
I don't know why
she's not moving on,
but I'll try to fix it,ok?
I promise.
I have no idea
how to fix this.
Oh,yeah?
Maybe this'll help.
911 report. We just
got it faxed to us.
"Anna fowler.
Female. Caucasian.
Cause of death, hyperthermia.
"Page one of 3". Where's the rest of it?
Hey,hey,hey. That was before
we got computerized.
We're lucky to have
gotten anything at all.
I'm sorry
I'm so grumpy.
Grumpy? You got a crazy ghost
making you crazy.
Oh,I married
a comedian.
Hey,the guy who wrote this report,
do you know him?
Yeah. I know andy.
Sure,I remember
that night.
Changed me forever.
Got a call that morning
from the woman's sister...
she was worried because she
hadn't shown up the night before.
Andy,you led
the rescue team up,right?
Not right away. That storm
was something fierce.
Worst I'd seen up
till then.
Had to wait until it was
practically dark for it to subside.
It couldn't have been easy finding her
with all that snow falling.
You're not kidding.
There was no sign of her
along the main road, so we split up.
The footprints were pretty well
covered already.
But I knew
they had to be hers.
So I followed them
for quite a ways.
I knew right away that
she didn't make it.
I went to check
her pulse...
and that's
when I realized...
what?
What did you realize?
The little girl...
was alive.
It was a miracle.
A true miracle.
Her mother used the warmth
of her own body to keep her kid alive.
Lane was with her mother
that night.
Anna died trying
to save her baby.
Why would her husband
lie about that?
y would bradlie about that?
I don't know. But I think
that you do and...
I hope bringing you back here
will help you remember.
She was with me.
Yes. She was. Anna...
no. You don't
understand. It...
it all makes sense now.
Mommy!
Mommy,my dolly!
I knew I should stay
in the car,but...
it was like
a refrigerator.
Mommy,I'm scared.
I thought if
I just kept moving.
Come on,sweetie.
I was scared.
I was trying to get away.
I just couldn't
let him find me.
Who?
Who were you running from?
- My husband.
- Brad?
- Yeah.
- Why?
He hit me.
- Again.
- Anna...
I always thought
it was my fault.
If I could just be
a better wife.
Until that night...
Come back here!
I'm not done!
Open the door!
And we had another one
of our fights.
Anna!
Open the door!
I thought
she was asleep,
but our fighting woke her up.
Oh, baby.
- Oh, baby.
- Anna! let me in!
Mommy,don't
let him in.
Please don't
I saw how scared she was.
And I knew
we had to get out.
But if you
were being abused...
why didn't your friends
or anyone help you?
I was too ashamed
to tell them.
I wore long sleeves
to cover the bruises.
And if anyone did notice,
I'd just laugh it off.
Clumsy me.
Everyone thought we were
the perfect couple.
And we were when
we weren't fighting.
Brad would feel so bad
after one of our fights,
he'd spoil me
like crazy,presents,
big bouquets of flowers,
the works.
Is that why
you attacked todd?
Because you saw him give
lane the bouquet of flowers?
When I saw him
with that bouquet,
something just snapped
inside of me.
She has to know
what you went through.
What you did for her.
Please tell me
she's not here.
It's just me.
She gone for good?
No,but she said she'd stay away
until you're ready to see her.
That would be never.
Anna didn't abandon you.
What?
I talked to the paramedic
who rescued you.
You were with her
when she died.
I was with her
when she left my dad?
She took you
with her.
But...
why would my dad
lie about that?
Maybe he feels ashamed.
Ashamed of what?
My dad? He's the greatest dad
anyone could ask for.
Did some pretty bad
things to your mom.
Look,my dad would
never hurt anyone,ok?
If she said he did,
it's because she's crazy.
I don't know. Maybe she hates me.
You saw what she did to todd.
That was because
of the flowers.
Your dad always gave
her flowers after they had a fight.
It was a gut reaction when she saw todd
give you the bouquet.
Ok. Stop.
You've gone too far.
I don't need you
meddling in my life.
It's complicated
enough right now.
Your mom died trying to keep you safe.
She wanted to protect you.
And now she needs to
know that you're ok so she can move on.
Would it kill you
to just at least talk to her?
That ship's already sailed.
At least I know I can trust my instincts.
Anna isn't crazy.
But lane didn't
believe you?
When I told her her mom was abused,
she just shut down.
Well,that's a pretty big
bomb you dropped on her.
Kind of blows away
everything she grew up believing.
Yeah. Her father is a therapist.
I mean,you'd think he'd
have it all figured out.
I guess she
never really know.
Yeah. Well,I wouldn't
mind meeting that guy in a dark room.
You are a bigger
softie than me.
It was a nothing argument.
My fault really.
I always thought
it was my fault.
- It's happening.
Oh,my god!
I gotta go!
Lane! Lane,
it's melinda!
Are you ok?
I'm fine.
Now isn't a good time.
Do you want me
to get you out of here?
Are you crazy?
You've done
enough damage.
Lane, get in here
Lane!
I left so this would stop.
But it didn'T.
It never will.
Then we have
to do something.
She won't listen to me...
or to you.
Not now.
What?
Is this some
twisted joke?
I'm sorry.
I would normally
do this slowly,
explain gently
that I have a gift,
I can see spirits,I can
cross them over,yada,yada.
Frankly,I don't have
the patience or the time.
- Lane needs you.
- What do you mean?
I think she's being abused,
just like you abused her mother.
What,um...
what makes you say that?
Look,brad,you don't have
to believe I can see ghosts,
but please believe
what I'm telling you about your daughter.
Ok. Ok. I'll admit
I had doubts about todd.
I always thought it was
just my own paranoia,
projecting my own
demons onto him.
But I know he loves her.
You loved me,too.
Said you couldn't live without me.
You always said
your heart beat only for me.
You said your heart beat
only for her.
Is she really here?
Can-can-can you tell her-
tell her that I'm not
the same person anymore?
That I've gotten help,and
now I'm helping others.
I know that look of his,
so full of guilt
and remorse.
She can hear you.
Anna...
I'm so sorry for...
for what I did.
I just...
hope you can forgive me.
All those times
you begged me to forgive you,
and I did...
because I loved you,
because I believed
you could change.
And it looks
like you have,
but I can't
forgive you.
I forgave you too many
times when I was alive.
She wishes she could,
but it's too late.
Right.
Of course...
brad,the reason that anna is earthbound
is not because of what you did to her.
It's lane.
You have one chance
to redeem yourself,
to help your daughter, please
tell her the truth about you,
so she that can she
can know the truth about todd.
I didn't want you to know.
That's why I lied.
I know it was wrong.
I hated myself
for what I did to her.
I couldn't live
if you hated me,too.
My mom didn't abandon me?
No.
She didn'T.
So you let me believe
that my mother left me?
That she didn't love me?
Lanie, the only reason I'm
bringing this up now
is because I don't want you to make
the same mistake your mother did.
What do you mean?
Anna thinks todd
is hurting you.
Lanie...
they say that little girls
marry their fathers-
just stop it,ok?
Todd and I are happy.
We're getting married,
he's gonna pass the bar,
and everything
is gonna be great.
Just stop this.
Lanie,please.
No.
My head is spinning.
I can't even think
about this right now.
So you think she's waiting
to see if lane's okay?
Sure. And believe me, she'll know.
She's got the mommy-radar.
You know,I always wondered how my mom
knew I spiked the punch at junior prom.
Go ahead, make fun of me,
but,you know what, it's powerful stuff.
See, I think anna was in limbo.
Earthbound but unaware.
Her daughter got engaged,
and it sent a ripple effect through
the universe that woke her up.
Oh, to be continued.
Is my mother here?
I always told myself
it would get better.
When he passed the bar...
when we got married.
When we moved
into a bigger house.
He wasn't going
to change.
You did the right thing.
My mother did
the right thing.
Is that why
she stayed here?
To stop me from
staying with him?
Can I...
can I thank her?
You just did.
She's here?
She's so beautiful.
I can't believe this is the
tiny little girl I held in my arms.
Mom?
She wants you to know
how proud she is of you.
No,mom. It was you.
I can't believe how strong you were
to do what you did.
How tough you were.
You protected me.
You saved me.
We saved ourselves.
I'm so scared,mom.
I don't know
what I'm going to do now.
Yes,you do.
It's inside you.
Remember
how strong you are.
And just think of me,
and I'll be with you.
I'll be watching you
from wherever I am.
She wants you to remember
how strong you are.
She will always
be watching over you.
I love you,mom.
I feel like I never
got to say it to her.
You don't have
to say it.
We both know it.
Thank you
for everything.
She's gone?
Yeah.
But she's happy.
At peace.
I can't
thank you enough.
I don't know
what else to say.
www.tvsubtitles.net