Subs by Raceman and Zhalom
www.forom.com
My name
is Melinda Gordon.
I'm married,
I live in a small town,
and I own
an antique shop.
I might be just like you.
Except that from the time I was a little
girl, I knew that I could talk to the dead.
Earthbound spirits,
my grandmother called them.
They're stuck here because they
have unfinished business with the living
and they come to me
for help.
In order to tell you my story,
I have to tell you theirs.
Are you serious?
Tonight?
Yes, I've been dying
to see it.
Are you kidding me,
I would love to.
Oh, thank you so much.
I'll call you if the chest comes in.
Yeah. We haven't
been to a movie in like 6 years.
Oh, all right, maybe it's been
more like a month.
No, it's a great idea.
It is.
I'll close up early.
You know, I'm sorry to cut you short,
but I have a little bit of a situation here.
Yeah, I'll see you
at the house. Bye.
Hey, do you really think
that I can't see what you're doing?
First, no skates
in the store.
They're heelys
not skates.
All right, no wheels on your
feet allowed and, no shoplifting.
I was gonna pay for it.
You just didn't give me
the chance.
They're $275 a piece.
And the register is that way,
not out on the street.
Whatever.
- What's your phone number?
- Why?
I'm calling your parents.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Nope.
Look, my mother's sick.
Real sick. And this
would really upset her.
Do you really think
that I'm that out of it?
Do you think that i am so un
hip that i would fall for that?
Yeah.
- What's your name?
- Ned.
Ned, give me
your phone number,
or I will take you and your
heelys down to the police station.
I am so sorry.
He has never done
anything like this before.
No, it's fine.
I just thought that you
would want to know.
I was gonna
pay for them.
Ned. It's not like he doesn't have
a ton of this stuff anyway.
He's got
signed guitar picks,
keith moon's drumsticks,
old ticket stubs.
None of it stolen,
by the way.
He will never come back in here
again, I can promise you that.
I'm gonna go
wait outside.
You don't have to
do that. He's welcome.
Just with shoes
minus wheels.
- You have kids?
- No.
- No, not yet.
- Well, they're great.
Until they become
teenagers.
And then you realize
you're just being
paid back double for all the rotten
things you did as a teenager.
He seems like a good kid.
He is. He is.
It's just been a little
tough lately, you know?
He's been so moody. He doesn't talk,
he hardly sleeps.
'S just like his whole life
is this big secret all of a sudden.
Anyway, you have
to get back to work, so do I.
I'm Delia Banks
by the way.
Oh, Melinda Gordon.
Nice to meet you.
You look familiar.
I run the real estate office
on the other side of the square.
Oh, well, I'll see you
at village java.
Every chance I get.
Thank you.
And, uh...
I guess I'll see you
around campus.
you know, this was fun.
We should do this like once a week.
Yeah, just not
the same movie.
- I liked it.
- Hey, so did I.
I saw you sleeping.
I was burning
certain scenes into my memory.
Yeah, well, you're tired.
You worked your ass off
this weekend.
Hey, I had
a shoplifter today.
Shoplifting  is something I just don't
associate with antiques, you know?
I think I'm just
gonna take this
chippendale dresser
and stuff it into my jacket.
Yeah, right. It was grateful dead
backstage passes.
At least he had
good taste.
Yeah, he was a kid.
I called his mother.
Ooh, something no thief
worth his salt wants to have happen.
Delia Banks. She's great.
She sells real estate
in town.
Um... yes?
I just thought
maybe I...
hit something
on my way here.
- An animal?
- No. More like someone
who used to be alive
and now isn'T.
Is that what we're
calling ghosts now?
Yeah, I got bored
of calling them ghosts.
Wait a minute,
you tell me about the shoplifter,
but you don't tell me
about the ex living person?
Well, there won't be
a lawsuit.
Sometimes I think a lawsuit would
be easier. What happened?
Do you really want me to tell you
about every single ghost I run across?
Or run over.
Absolutely not.
I prefer to be on
a need to know basis.
Good. Then you drive.
- Hey.
- I'm not a thief.
Glad to hear it.
Shouldn't you be in school?
What, are you gonna
call my mom again?
Can I ask you a question?
If you're not a thief,
then why did you steal
- ... those backstage passes?
- I don't know.
I just felt like
I should have them.
Not you.
Your mom says you have
a lot of that stuff. You collect it?
- What about your dad?
- What about him?
- Where is he?
- In the ground.
Oh, well, that,
that must be hard for you.
For your mom.
He liked old things.
- Look, if you want-
- I gotta go.
Want to check
my pockets?
Jim?
What is it? What?
Come on.
Ok. It's need to know time.
29th doesn't mean anything?
No.  Other than the fact
that it's next friday.
A birthday.
A day somebody died.
Well,  it could be
any of those things.
But until this guy
talks to me, we can only guess.
What?
I don't know, it's just...
another...
another formally
alive person. In our house.
Why can't our home
be off limits?
I don't like it any more
than you do, trust me,
but maybe this guy
doesn't know where he is.
Or what's going on.
It's like he doesn't
actually want me to see him.
Like some kind of
hide and seek game he's playing.
Sometimes spirits
have a kind of amnesia,
and they need time
to figure things out.
Maybe he's hoping that this date
will spark something.
Well, it certainly
sparked something.
Is this because
I was in the shower?
- You're afraid that-
- No. It's just about boundaries.
They don't belong
in our home.
I'm sorry that I have to
burden you with this.
Hey, it's no burden.
I'm just used to
having andrea
to puzzle these things
out with.
Oh, babe...
I know. I know.
- Who are you?
- I'm not sure.
- What do you want?
- I don't know.
Do you know why
you came to me?
- You can help me.
- How?
How did you die?
Were you hit by a car?
I think so.
I don't remember
everything exactly.
What does
september 29th mean?
- Don't you know?
- No.
Then I don't either.
Do you have a family?
Does someone know
what happened to you?
I had a wife.
In eastwick.
- Maine?
- She may not know. Will you tell her?
Well, I'm sure you had
I.D. On you.
The police have probably
called her by now.
I was no good to her. I hurt her.
I have to say I'm sorry.
- Do you remember her name?
- Donna. Donna ellis.
And what's your name?
I think people
callede mac.
Well, mac, eastwick is not
exactly around the corner,
- so I don't know that I-
- You have to find her.
- See her.
- Why?
It's important.
- Are you open?
- I'll be right with you.
I took a guess.
Mocha latte.
Oh, works for me.
That's so nice.
Consider it
a peace offering.
I think my son paid you
another visit the other day.
Oh... man, he's good.
We were talking
the whole time.
Yes. It makes a mother proud.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to make light of it.
No, no. I am so grateful
that you're not upset.
Honestly, I don't know
what his problem is.
He mentioned that his father
had passed away.
3 years ago. It has been really
hard on him.
For you, too.
The shoplifting
helps a lot.
- Good to know.
- I don't mean to pry but...
you lost your partner
recently, didn't you?
Yeah. She was like
a sister to me.
Well, I am right
across the square,
so if you ever need anything...
or you just want to grab
a cup of coffee.
Thanks for
bringing this back.
I tried to make ned do it,
but, you know.
I know.
Does he ever say that he can feel
his father's presence?
Presence?
Like he's around,
you know.
- Watching over him.
- He doesn't say it, but
I think he does.
Sometimes I do, too.
Or at least I wish for it so badly,
that I think I do.
I just wanted to thank you.
I know it sounds crazy,
but he asked me to go to maine.
Maine? As in new england?
Yeah, and you know
what's crazier?
I think I should do it.
You know, this is
one of the reasons why
mr. Alexander graham bell
was so excited
about his new invention
because you can just
pick one of these things up
and call people instead of-
you know what, it is hard enough
to do this in person.
Never mind on the phone.
How are you gonna find her?
Well, he gave me a name,
the town,
and there's that other
little invention, the internet.
I just think it's a long
way to go for a ghost,
a being who no longer
occupies the visual world.
Well, that's true,
but to be honest with you,
I kind of want to get
this guy crossed over.
There's something
off about him.
- Besides being dead?
- You are hilarious.
It's like he's holding
something back,
and you know what,
either I do this thing,
or I don't do this thing,
but I can't just say local calls only.
Well, I think there should be some
metaphysical frequent flyer miles involved.
****
It's pretty nice there this time of year.
Maybe yoshould
come with me. Change of scenery.
I'm back on sundays
starting tomorrow.
You should go.
You're right.
It'll do you good.
I'll call you
a million times.
Yes?
Oh,  um, sorry.
- Are you donna ellis?
- Yes.
I was hoping I could
talk to you for a minute.
Uh, sure. About what?
About your husband,
and please, accept my condolences.
Condolences?
I- I'm sorry.
What is this about?
Well, I assumed you knew.
- Knew what?
- Your husband.
That your husband
passed away.
What? What are
you talking about?
- You didn't know?
- How? When?
Um, he was hit by a car.
I'm so sorry.
I thought that-
where is he?
Where is he!?
Michael? Michael.
You're ok.
I'm fine.
Wait. That's your husband?
Yes. This woman came here
and just said that you,
she said that you
were dead.
That you had been hit
by a car.
No, I'm sorry.
Why would you do that?
What's wrong with you?
It was a mistake.
I guess. I...
I don't know what to say.
I Just don't get it, I had the right name,
and I had the right address.
Well, maybe he's confused.
You said sometimes they don't know
what's happened.
No, I think this guy
knows exactly what's happening.
I think I'm just
being played.
Oh, conned by a ghost, huh?
That's not gonna look
very good on a resume.
Sure. Laugh at my misery,
but you should've been here.
It was the most
embarrassing moment of my life.
Why is this guy
manipulating me like this?
Look, just come home.
Come  home. I'll be off
by breakfast time.
No. It's getting late.
I'm too stressed
to drive.
I'm just, I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to get
a room and start fresh in the morning.
Ok. Just call me before
you go to sleep.
Ok.
Excuse me.
Please leave me alone.
I can't tell you how sorry I am
about that.
It was
an honest mistake.
Ok, look, I don't know
who you are,
or what your problem is, but if you don't
leave me alone, I'm calling the police.
Understood?
Do you know a man
named mac?
- Do you mean my ex husband?
- Ex?
I thought
it was your husband.
Has something
happened to him?
Yes, I'm sorry.
He died.
He was hit by a car.
I came a long way to tell you that.
Why?
Because he wants you
to know.
He feels really bad about the way that
he treated you, and he wants to apologize.
You're speaking
in the present tense.
- Yes.
- But he's dead.
- Who the hell are you?
He wants to say
he's sorry.
It's what he needs to have closure
so that he can move on.
I can help you
talk to him if you'll just let me.
I need you
to stay away from me.
Even if I believed
any of this,
mac put me through hell
in our marriage,
and I have nothing
to say to him.
And I don't care what he
has to say to me.
Nobody's seen her
for 3 or 4 days.
She don't answer door,
she don't answer phone.
Nobody else is asking
around for her,
so I use key
just to check up.
She's gone.
1, 2 days probably.
Heart attack?
I think so.
You want to go downstairs and call this
in. I'll get going on the paperwork.
Yeah, ok.
Ve a nice trip.
She's mine.
Leave her.
Oh, come on.
Talk to me.
You think this is funny?
Making me tell that poor woman
that her husband is dead?
Let me in on the joke, pal.
This doesn't mean that i
believe any of this.
But just, by chance, if it's true, I
thought I should hear what you had to say.
I'm glad you came.
Come in.
Where the hell
have you been?
- I'm sorry?
- Nothing.
So how does this work?
Tell her
she looks good.
He says
you look good.
So he's here, like now?
All right, if he's here,
then...
why don't you ask him to tell you
what happened to our marriage.
Um, he said that you
were married 3 years ago.
That you moved
to this town together,
in the same house
that you live in now,
and then you
divorced him a year later.
Ask him why.
I don't remember.
He says he doesn't
remember.
Well, I remember. He was obsessed
with another woman.
- He cheated on you?
- No, not like that.
That would've almost
been easier.
Instead I had to compete
with the memory of his ex girlfriend.
He didn't realize
how hung up on her he was.
It was like he just
couldn't get her out of his mind.
He was constantly comparing me to her
and talking about her.
I tried to
make it work.
He said that he tried
to make it work.
Oh, bull, you just went
through the motions, mac.
And sometimes not even that.
I don't even understand why
you wasted your time with me.
Do you know how he ended it?
I told him that, you know, maybe we
should take some time apart,
so that he could figure out
what, or who he really wanted.
And he just said, ok.
Let's get a divorce.
Just like that,
like it was nothing.
He should've just gone out
and found that girl
and just figured it out,
but instead, you used me,
and you made me feel like
I didn't count for anything.
I did find the girl.
What?
I did find the girl
I was in love with.
Who  I'm still in love with.
I should've never
let you go.
Kyle?
Kyle mccall?
Just call him kyle?
No one's called him that since college.
We all called him mac.
Tell her you know me. Tell her you're
the one I never got over after we broke up.
Why? What's he saying?
that he's sorry
for the way that he treated you,
and he hopes
that you can forgive him.
Right?
You can do that?
She's not really
the forgiving type.
I can't believe you.
Ok, this is just
too weird.
I gotta get out of here.
And if this is real,
which I highly doubt,
tell him that
I don't forgive him.
He was an idiot then,
and he's probably still an idiot now.
- You played me.
- You're mad.
I could never stand
to make you mad.
Why didn't you tell me
who you were?
Why did you send me
to your ex wife?
Don't you know?
Can't you see it?
- See what?
- You just don't understand.
No...
damn it.
Kyle mccall.
You told me about this guy.
You went out with him
in college.
- You said he hurt you.
- Yeah. That was an understatement.
Kyle was the first guy that I
thought I was really in love with.
Believe me, I did not
trust easily.
We were together
for a whole year in college.
He was complicated.
One of those tortured souls
you think you can save.
I thought if I opened myself up to him,
that if I took a risk and told him my secret,
it would show him how much
I believed in him.
In us.
- You're kidding, right?
- No.
You really believe
you can do this?
Kyle, I do it
all the time.
- See dead people.
- Yes.
- Talk to dead people.
- Don't say it like I'm crazy.
You're thinking it,
aren't you?
- What?
- That I'm crazy.
I didn't say that.
Well, I can see that
you're thinking it.
Well, what am I
supposed to think?
That I wouldn't
lie to you.
And that I'm not crazy.
Stuff like that.
Do you...
talk to ghosts a lot?
- More than I want to.
- Like every day, once a week?
Third tuesday of the month?
I try not to speak to them
unless they speak to me.
- And what do they talk about?
- All kinds of things.
Mostly they need help.
I have to help them
cross over into the light.
Yeah.
I knew it was too good
to be true.
- What?
- You.
Us... I thought I
met the perfect girl.
Kyle, wait, I know that you
don't believe me,
but please don't walk away.
Just talk to me.
Yeah. Maybe when I'm dead.
That was it.
Never called me, never came to
see me again after a year.
- Still hurts?
- I guess.
A little.
First cut and all that.
And now he wants
a second chance.
I guess that explains the talking corpse
I had to deal with last night.
I'm sorry, jim. I wish that you never
had to deal with any of this.
Keeps things fresh.
You were my second chance.
I mean, you know that,
right?
I never thought that i was going to be
able to trust anyone again after kyle.
And then there was jim.
You're not gonna break into
song right now, are you?
I might.
Now what are we gonna do
about this guy though?
I don't know how much longer
I can keep my sense of humor.
I'll get him to cross over
and out of our lives, I promise.
All right, can you tell me
what the hell it is with these passes?
Dude, these are mine
from my collection.
Dude, I bought those
at a trade show in philadelphia.
I know. My mom,
she sold my whole collection
after I died,
and it got spread out all over the
place and this is the last of it.
You've been tracking
the whole collection?
Each and every single
piece meant so much to me.
My mother,
she never got that.
So she sold them
to some guy,
and he sold it to another guy,
and... my collection.
- What's your name?
- Jamey barton.
- You heard of me?
- No.
why are you still here?
I gotta make sure this stuff gets
to the right people.
People who care,
people who know
what it means, you know?
Hmm. So that's why you
attached yourself to ned.
And here I thought the whole time that
it was his father who was haunting him.
Maybe I'm losing
my touch lately.
You see, I hang out
at concerts,
and I try to get, you know,
a feel for the kids.
And then I try to get
the right kid a piece of the collection.
Well, you'll be happy to know ned has been
a real trouper about getting these passes.
That's my boy.
You're making him
a thief.
It's not like I can just
slip him the cash, can I?
How did you get him
to do it?
Well, I wait till he falls asleep, and then I
whisper in his ear all freaking night long.
"Steal the passes,
dude.
Steal the passes, dude. "
It's how I used to rember lyrics.
Well, he's not gonna
steal the passes from me,
and you have to
leave him alone.
You're messing with his energy.
He doesn't even know why.
It's time for you to go
to the big arena in the sky.
No can do.
I mean, he's the one
for these passes.
He understands.
I can't go anywhere until the last
of my collection is in the right hands,
so whoa, 3 o'clock already.
Note to self.
I gotta keep better
track of time.
He's getting out of school
right now, and so, I gotta skate.
Come on, kyle.
We have to talk about this. I can't help
you if I don't know what you want.
You could've told me
how great it is to be dead.
Go anywhere I want.
No travel time.
No one can see me.
Well, almost no one.
I've had more fun being dead so far
than the entire time I was alive.
What do you want?
I was on my way
to see you, you know.
- The day I died.
- Why?
I saw you on the news.
All I can say is that
people in this town are strong.
They're survivors,
and we'll be ok.
What's with you
and this chick?
Melinda? It's like
you're obsessed with her.
I wanted to see how
things turned out for you.
Things turned out
pretty good for me.
I see that.
Not so much
for me though.
And how is that
my problem, kyle?
Look, I made a big mistake
the day I let you go.
I didn't realize that
right away.
- Yeah, you moved on.
- But I didn'T.
- You married donna.
- Yeah, another mistake.
Donna looked like you,
I thought maybe somehow
I could turn her
into you.
It was a disaster.
That's why I wanted you
to meet her.
So you could see that I was
just trying to recreate you.
You affected
every part of my life.
You made me feel like a freak,
and that I didn't deserve to be loved.
I gave you everything.
Even the one secret
that I never wanted
anyone to know,
and you threw me away.
It was so easy for you.
You want to talk about
a ripple effect?
I'm sorry.
I really am. I was stupid.
I had no idea
what I was throwing away.
But don't tell me you didn't
think about me once in awhile.
Remember how we used to
make fun of the space needle?
Remember that movie theatre
in queen anne?
- The uptown.
- The uptown, right.
How many rainy afternoons
did we spend there?
Watching the worst
movies ever.
You used to hate that.
*****
You convinced me to stop
wearing socks.
You though my feet looked
sexy in sneakers without socks.
You remember
that book store?
In pioneer square.
None of that matters now.
But it does.
It should.
I remember the first day
I talked to you in class.
The way you looked at me.
Those eyes.
I remember thinking
to myself,
now I know what it's like
to really be looked at.
No one's ever looked at me
like that since.
It's over.
You made your choice.
There's no going back,
and I'm happy now.
I found a man that I love
more than I ever thought was possible.
But it's not over.
We can be together now.
Like it was
supposed to be.
Are you listening
to me, kyle?
I'm happily married.
And you're dead.
September 29th is the day
we broke up.
And september 29th is gonna be
the day we get back together.
Are you gonna belate tonight?
Uh, I don't know. Friday nights
can be a little heavy.
Well, tonight would be
a good night to be late.
Why?
Because it's september 29th,
and he's got something planned,
I just don't know what.
Well...
I should be here.
- This guy feels like trouble.
- It's my deal, ok?
I have to solve it, and besides,
he's really not that bad of a guy.
He would never hurt me.
Mel, you and this guy,
is there...
I can't believe
I'm asking this about a ghost.
Is there still
something between you?
- What?
- I heard you last night.
Jim, he's dead.
There was a time
in my life when that
meant case closed,
but then I met you.
One or two laughs
with kyle mccall
dead or alive will never compare
to what we have.
There was more depth
on our first date
than I ever had with kyle,
the problem is he doesn't get that.
All right. Be careful.
- Call me if you need me.
- Yeah.
Ned, it's no big deal.
You've just got to go in there
and take those passes.
Technically, it's not
even really stealing
because those passes
are mine,
in the big picture,
we're like one, you know, so...
- that was harsh.
- They're yours.
- Righteous.
- Why?
Sometimes my job
is about making sure
that the right people
end up with the right things.
Something tells me
that whoever owned them
would want you
to have them.
Seriously?
They're not for free.
I need some help
at the store on saturdays,
- For let's say, a month.
- I don't know.
Is that like
minimum wage, or...
- all right. Don't push it.
- Ok. So... thanks.
Slickly done, I must say.
Slickly done.
Oh, thank you.
Whoa.
That is one bright light.
Yeah. The ultimate,
all access pass.
- Do you hear that?
- Hear what?
Check, check,
check one, check two.
Stop it!
Leave my husband's
stuff alone!
******
Kyle, you have to stop
doing this.
You cannot just erase jim by getting
rid of everything that he owns.
Obviously, one of us
has to go,
and it's not gonna be me.
Not this time.
- Jim is not going anywhere.
- I love you, Melinda.
You have no idea
what love is.
I'm here, and he isn't,
so that's a good start.
He's not here
because he loves me.
I asked him to give me some space,
and he gave it to me.
- How is that love?
- That's just part of it.
And it's not the greeting cards
and sunset and flowers part.
That's easy.
That's not real.
It's about doing the things that you
don't want to do.
The stuff that
makes you mad.
The stuff that you do
without even being asked.
It's about having a friend
and knowing when to shut up.
You know, I can't tell you
what love is.
I can only tell you
what it isn't, and this is not it.
No, but you're wrong, Melinda.
I will never forget
the look in your eyes
when you walked away
from me.
- What look?
- Relief.
You were relieved.
To not have to risk
being in an honest relationship.
To not have to give
anything up.
To be able to blame
somebody else so you could be safe.
That's a lie.
Your ex wife told me that you did
exactly the same thing to her.
The first time that she called you on
the way you treated her, you left.
Just like me.
You call that love?
Yeah, but I missed you
every day.
I knew I had made a mistake.
That's because you had
already thrown me away.
I could be imaginary.
Was I that forgettable?
I hated myself for it.
I wanted to call you
a hundred times.
It would've been too late.
You did what you did, I saw what I saw.
There was never any going back.
Now I'm starting to hate
being dead.
Why?
Because the answer
to everything is too late.
Too late to fix
the mistakes.
Too late to catch up
with the things you missed.
Too late to make things
right with the people you hurt.
Too late...
to love you the way
he does.
The beauty part
of my job is, kyle, it's never too late.
You wasted a trip.
I have nothing to gain
by talking to him.
Look, maybe you don't
have anything to gain.
Maybe you just have
something to lose.
A little piece of anger
or bitterness, or disappointment.
He hurt me so much.
You know what,
he hurt me, too.
But you know
what happened, I got stronger.
I met the perfect
man for me.
Found a beautiful place to live,
and you, you're married again.
I saw how much
you loved your husband
when you thought
that he was dead,
and would you really
be this happy
if you were still
with kyle?
Would I?
Transformation.
Sometimes turns out to be
better than you could've imagined.
He just wants the chance
to say that he's sorry.
He's right behind you,
and he's ready to do that.
I screwed up, donna.
I was scared. I took
the easy way out.
I'm so sorry.
He knows
that he screwed up.
You son of a bitch, kyle.
Didn't you know...
how much I loved you?
What I would've
done for you?
How could you...
how could you just throw that away?
I'm glad you're happy now.
You're better off
without me.
He's glad that
you're happy now.
You're better off.
Yeah, well...
I guess I'll never
really know.
- I know.
- He knows.
Can I go now?
Time to cross over.
You ever think I'll get
a second chance?
Come back here again
and do this right?
It's really nice
to think so.
You were never forgettable.
www.tvsubtitles.net