Previously on "Alias."
Get in the van!
I could help you become
more powerful than ever.
You've told Bomani
you'd work for The Covenant?
Yes.
And now I'm telling you I'm in
a position to be a double agent,
working for The Covenant
but loyal to the CIA.
What is it, Sydney?
This is classic.
There.
You see that?
He's saying "Jewel" or "Julie."
Maybe "Julia."
What videotape?
The videotape that clearly
identifies Sydney
as the murderer of a Russian
diplomat, Andrian Lazarey.
I'm withholding this
information from the NSC.
That means, Agent Vaughn,
that you are prohibited
from discussing this
with your wife.
Is that understood?
Yeah.
Vaughn, I have to know
where I was and who Julia is.
What I did.
Hello, Sydney.
What do you want?
The Covenant
is about to make a move.
If you have intel, protocol is
you pass it through Lauren Reed.
She's your handler.
Well, Ms. Reed is very able,
but I'm afraid she cannot
possibly comprehend
the intricacies of serving
two masters simultaneously.
You were brilliant at it.
The way you would walk into
my office, look me in the eyes
and lie to me.
For me to succeed in my work as
a double agent for The Covenant,
I'll need your help.
Your needs don't concern me.
You'll find the details
on toureurope.eu.
It's encoded in the photo
of the Vatican.
Password is "Credit Dauphine,"
for old times' sake.
Clever.
I miss L.A.
I miss Emily.
I miss the friendship
with your father.
I miss your confidence
and trust.
Perhaps I can get it back
someday?
You will never have
my confidence and trust.
Or my father's friendship
and respect.
Ever.
You don't want any Weiss on ice!
Come on, buddy!
Alright, I wasn't ready.
Wait until I say
the words "I'm ready."
Hey! Hey!
- What's the matter with you?
- Nothing.
My brother used to do this.
Do what?
Shut down like you're doing.
Get all quiet.
- That's not what I'm doing.
- He'd deny it, too.
And then he'd brood and
get mopey like you're doing.
Finally it got too much for him.
He had to tell me
what the problem was.
It's been 3 weeks since I found
out Sydney murdered Lazarey.
I've been lying to my wife
for 3 weeks.
Come on, man.
I know guys that lie to their
wives for longer than that.
You understand your brother
didn't like talking to you
because you say
stupid things, right?
Listen, you were ordered
not to say anything, right?
This isn't your choice.
And she was ordered to find out
who murdered Lazarey.
That's my point.
I'm engaged in preventing her
from doing her job.
She's gonna find out.
I mean, you know she is.
And that you're protecting
Sydney.
Yeah.
See where I'm going with this?
Well, this is why
people from the CIA
should not get married
to people from the NSC.
Don't poop where you sleep.
Thanks a lot.
Okay.
Alright, you know what?
That hurts.
This is where Lange will be.
I'll take care of it.
It must be done a certain way.
There is an extraction required.
I assume you've stamped out
the details.
Your partner's been briefed.
My partner?
I don't think so.
This is not a request.
Look, if you
don't trust me by now,
perhaps you should be
in business with someone else.
And you can tell that to San'ko.
We logged on to Tour Europe
and downloaded Sloane's intel.
The Covenant is after a device
that will give them access
to Russia's strategic arsenal.
It was designed by this man,
Robert Lange,
hardware engineer
for a German security firm.
Lange was approached by someone
posing as a Russian official.
They contracted him to design
a test for security flaws
in their nuclear command
and control system.
This guy, Lange, created
this really cool device.
Basically, take it to any
missile silo in all of Russia,
and it interfaces with
the launch-control console
and bypasses
all security protocols.
Initiation codes,
the commander's launch key,
irrelevant.
It's a skeleton key
for Russia's nuclear weapons?
Yeah, and to be honest,
I'm just a little bit jealous.
Did he deliver it
to The Covenant?
No, he discovered the man
who hired him
wasn't actually Russian defence.
Lange went on the run
to prevent The Covenant
from getting what he'd invented.
This is a picture
of what he used to look like.
According to Sloane's intel,
Lange has surgically
altered his appearance
to hide from The Covenant.
We know that tomorrow Lange
is scheduled to meet this man,
Heinrich Strauss,
at the Club Delphi in Milan.
He's picking up
new identity papers.
Remember, Sloane's intel
came from The Covenant,
so obviously they're looking to
grab Lange and the skeleton key.
Sydney and Vaughn, you need to
get Lange before The Covenant.
You'll leave tonight.
Marshall will go over op-tech.
Lauren, Sydney, I need a moment.
Given the current situation,
I need to make a change.
I want you to take over
as Sloane's handler.
No. I'm sorry.
That is not a good idea.
While it's not my favourite job,
can I ask why
I'm being replaced?
It's not an indictment.
It's that Sydney is more
familiar with the players.
What players?
There's Sloane and Sark.
- That's it.
- No, there's another.
Sydney, Allison Doren is alive.
She's alive?
You can thank me later.
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
I truly thought you were dead
the last two years.
You have to start
at the beginning.
Or the end,
after the last time I saw you.
Will Tippin discovered
what had happened.
That his girlfriend
had been killed
and I had been doubled
to take her place.
He had to be eliminated.
What happened with Bristow?
When The Covenant found you,
you were both unconscious.
I can only remember that
in bits and pieces.
She came home.
I realised that she knew.
She aimed the gun at me.
The next thing I remember,
it was three weeks later,
and I woke up in a Covenant-run
hospital outside Marseilles.
It took me six months
to fully recover.
I've been working with them
ever since.
Were you behind them
extracting me from the CIA?
I wish I could claim credit
for that.
I only learned you were
working with us recently.
My tenure began shortly
after my father's murder.
They freed me in exchange
for my inheritance.
Who killed your father?
I don't know.
But I intend to find out.
Bristow should have to pay
for these scars.
She will.
I'm no longer Sloane's handler.
Dixon gave that job
to Sydney Bristow.
Good.
That frees you up to focus
on the Lazarey murder.
We have a source working
inside the Russian government
who's agreed to help us out.
They have the assassin's
identity?
Not yet, but apparently
they hold information
that could lead us to it.
Then why aren't they using it?
Lazarey is a Russian diplomat.
You'd think they'd want
that answer more than us.
The Covenant
doesn't want anyone to know
they're behind
the assassination.
And your source believes
their reach extends
so deep inside
the Russian government
that they can make that happen.
You leave tonight.
Any leak, and our source
could be compromised and killed.
No one from the CIA can know
about this,
including your husband.
Vienna.
Yeah, I know.
Surprised me, too.
For how long?
Well, you know how they go.
It's a NATO security briefing.
Two days at the most.
I'm surprised Lindsey reassigned
you to cover a briefing.
I know, but he said
he needs me there.
Couldn't exactly say no,
could I?
What about Milan?
Should be a quick turnaround.
I'll be back in a day.
When we get back,
when we're done with this,
we need to go away.
Desert?
Anywhere.
My superior indicated,
Mr. Tupikov,
that you have
some information for us.
How does a British woman
become an American spy?
I'm not a spy.
And though I grew up in London,
I was born in the United States.
Now that you know my life story,
I have some questions.
Your government's running
a probe into this.
I would think you want to bring
closure to your investigation.
Why come to us?
I explained this
to your superiors.
I want to hear it for myself.
Andrian and I were colleagues
since our time together
at St. Petersburg University.
I'm sorry.
I have, for some time now,
suspected the existence
of a mole,
whom I believe is still loyal
to The Covenant.
This is a file
of digital recordings,
all of which chronicle
hundreds of phone calls
made or received by our deceased
diplomat, Andrian Lazarey.
Perhaps the murderer can be
traced through these calls.
I trust you will see justice
done for my murdered comrade.
Where can I contact you?
You can't.
We never had this conversation.
So, that camera Marshall gave us
is a miniaturised X-ray camera.
How much you want to bet
this thing's leaking radiation?
So we're looking for Lange.
Yeah, the camera's supposed
to I.D. his plastic surgery.
It will transmit images
back to my PDA
that Marshall programmed
to identify fractures,
scar tissue, or implants.
Anyone who's been
under the knife.
You okay?
Is it Allison?
Since I learned that she's
alive, I just keep wondering...
does she still look like her?
Does she look like Francie?
Because if she does, as much as
I know I should keep her alive
to maybe try to figure out
the last two years of my life,
all I'll want to do is kill her.
Heinrich Strauss.
He's the man providing Lange
with identity papers.
As we speak, he's getting drunk
in the club.
I'll keep an eye on him.
The camera's in the stone.
Do you mind?
No.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Okay, we're looking for someone
with massive
facial reconstruction.
Lange's about 5'10", 170 pounds.
How's the camera working?
The video's linking up now.
Signal strength's at 100%.
I'll start looking for Lange.
Hey, check out
that guy to your left.
Buy me a drink?
Nothing.
I love this song.
Okay, nothing there.
Keep moving.
Oh, check out the guy
with no rhythm.
No, only a nose job.
Not enough to be Lange.
Chin implant at 3.00.
Collagen lips straight ahead.
Okay, those breasts are real.
- Should I get my nose done?
- Maybe a little tapering.
Get the bump removed?
Whoa, wait.
Go back.
Go back to your left.
2.00.
- There?
- Yeah, yeah.
Hold it.
Just like that.
Okay, nose, chin, cheek lift,
eye config.
That's Lange.
And there's Strauss.
He just got his identity papers.
Someone has a laser sight
on him!
Vaughn, Allison's the shooter!
She's up in the balcony!
I'm on my way!
Wait, Lange!
Don't move!
Lange ran out!
I'm pinned down!
Vaughn, where are you?
I'm on the balcony.
- Do you see her?
- No, she took off.
- I'm going after her.
- I'm going after Lange.
Hello.
Sydney, she went down
the elevator shaft.
She has Lange.
- What floor is she on?
- The basement.
- Why didn't she kill me?
- Maybe she likes you.
- Weiss, I'm serious.
- So am I.
Come on, she lived with you
for months.
She doubled herself
as your best friend.
Maybe in that time, she actually
started to like you.
I can see that happening.
It was like she needed
to keep me alive.
I know this sounds weird,
but it felt like
she had been ordered
not to kill me.
Well, that's lucky.
I want to know how she survived
your fight two years ago.
You shot her three times.
- So, she took this guy's tooth?
- She took the guy's tooth.
Just when you think the world
can't get weirder.
- Hey.
Have we checked the records
to see what's strange
about his teeth?
Langley cross-checked all files.
They had nothing.
- But then Lauren was a genius.
- Genius isn't quite what I was.
What did you do?
I miss all the good briefings.
Lauren realised we had
Lange's X-rays,
and we could use them to figure
out what was in his tooth.
The X-cam, Marshall's necklace.
We used it to see
who had plastic surgery.
- I took the pictures myself.
- Nice.
I have a meeting with the NSC.
I'll walk you out.
Vaughn's right.
The question isn't
why she didn't kill you.
It's "how come she's still
alive at all?"
Maybe Allison's a werewolf.
Maybe the only way to kill her
is with a silver bullet.
Yeah.
Okay, if you look here,
this is Lange's jaw
before his tooth was removed.
If we look here,
that looks like a normal filling
that one would have
after having a cavity.
Get it filled, too much sugar
and not flossing...
which I do every day,
twice a day.
But upon further examination,
I actually magnified it
over a thousand times,
and it's actually an RFID chip.
Now, RFID stands for
radio frequency identification.
Flinkman, you know
what would be great?
English.
Oh, right. I forgot.
You're not that astute.
Okay, what can I...
Oh, you guys are familiar
with the "quick pass" things
you'd use at gas stations.
Come on the key chains.
Actually, I think I have one.
Need a visual demonstration.
You know,
this little thing right here
that lets you pay
for your gas at the pump.
Then you don't have to use
your credit card...
- Marshall.
- Yeah?
We're familiar with those.
Lange has something like that
in his tooth?
Sort of, although it doesn't
work at the gas station.
Though, if it did,
it would be wicked cool.
We believe Lange used this
to open a high-security lock.
Yes, and I believe Lange kept
this missile-launching device
locked up
and used this tooth
to open the vault.
Or briefcase.
This device could be anywhere.
We have to assume The Covenant
has the location.
As far as we know, they could
have the device already.
Sloane's our man
in The Covenant,
so I assume
there's a plane waiting.
How do I know
what I'm looking for?
I've supplied you with the time
and date of Lazarey's murder.
Screen all calls made
in the weeks leading up to it.
We think the killer
is someone he expected.
Was Lazarey killed
by a man or a woman?
A woman.
It'll take awhile to filter
all these calls.
Calls with a red flag, run them
through voiceprint analysis.
Maybe we can make a positive
I.D. on one of these callers.
Sydney Bristow
to see Arvin Sloane.
Ja, he's been expecting you.
Right this way.
Yes, of course, Mr. Secretary.
I will. I'd be happy to speak
with the delegation from UNESCO
at their convenience.
Just let me know.
Thank you.
Give my regards to Nani.
Yes. Bye.
Sydney, I was very pleased
when Dixon said that
you agreed to be my handler.
It was an assignment,
not an agreement.
The way a janitor doesn't
agree to clean a toilet.
But as your handler, you'll do
what I say when I say.
I select your assignments.
I design your missions.
I control you,
not the other way around.
Is that what you
used to let Vaughn do?
Control you?
The intel you provided
was accurate.
The Covenant is in pursuit
of a device
that will give them access
to Russia's strategic weapons.
You failed to get Lange,
didn't you?
Lange is dead.
The Covenant has an access code
we assume will open a vault
that contains this device.
I see. And you know
the location of this vault?
No, but Sark and Allison do,
and you're going to get them
to give it to you.
Allison.
I was wondering
when Allison would resurface.
I'm sorry, Sydney.
I can only imagine
that seeing Allison
must be very painful for you.
You will set up a meeting
with Sark and Allison.
You'll explain that their travel
plans have been compromised.
You'll offer assistance
in revising their arrangements.
And pass the information
on to you?
That won't be necessary.
You'll be wearing a wire.
And if they discover
that it's a setup?
Then I get to hear them
kill you.
I went through the disk.
There were 300 calls, and about
12% of them were encrypted,
including this one
from the day before the murder.
Yes, this is Andrian.
Hello, it's me.
- Hello.
- About the stock transfer...
So I trust that you've located
a safe place to park the asset.
I have.
When would you come by
to discuss the particulars?
Can you make time
tomorrow at 3.00?
Of course. I look forward
to seeing you then.
That has to be the killer.
He was murdered at 3.15.
I ran it through analysis.
The woman's voice
has been altered.
Can you restore the original?
No, it was altered
at the source.
I was able to access
the Russian telephone exchange.
- So you can do a trace.
- I already did.
See, whoever placed the call
did an amazing job.
They routed to Lazarey's PBX
via a defunct satellite network,
through the Internet,
VOIP gateway,
and over a landline at a secure
telephone at this address.
London.
34 Trenton Place.
Knightsbridge.
A company called
K.N.G. Microtech.
Good job.
I found the office
where the phone call originated.
It's been empty for some time.
I spoke to the leasing agent.
According to their records,
this office was leased
a year ago, November 24th.
A 4-year lease paid in advance.
- Was there a name on the lease?
- Yes, there was.
I believe she's the person
who killed Lazarey.
Her name is Julia Thorne.
I feel like a field agent again.
Do you have a 20 on the targets?
I've never told you about
my time with the agency, have I?
Yes or no?
I was very patriotic once.
No one's asking.
Here they are.
Mr. Sark.
Allison.
You're looking well.
I look like someone else.
When you hired me
to undergo gene therapy,
you promised you could
reverse-engineer the process.
Ah, but Sydney Bristow
destroyed the technology
that would have allowed us
to return you.
I'm sorry for your loss.
You indicated it was
important we meet.
The CIA is onto you.
My sources tell me
the agency knows
that you extracted
an RFID chip from Mr. Lange.
The plane that you chartered
is under surveillance.
As counsel to The Covenant,
I suggest that you move up
your timetable.
If you let me know
where you need to go,
I'll have a plane waiting
within the hour.
- He's lying.
- Allison.
No, she's a wonderful
judge of character.
Sydney Bristow found you
in Milan.
If I were a betting man,
I'd say she'd find you again.
I'm simply here to help.
There's no way
Sark's gonna go for this.
We're going to Bulgaria.
The device is in a vault
in Sofia.
What did I tell you?
This is the best plan ever.
I can get you there first thing.
Tomorrow morning.
Done.
Then our business here
is complete.
Ask them where I've been
the last two years.
I'll call you as soon as
the arrangements are complete.
Ask them, or I'll send
feedback through your comm
so loud they'll hear it
and know you're wired.
At which point they'll kill you.
Sucks being a double agent,
doesn't it?
You know, Allison,
I'm thinking...
Seeing you again,
I'm reminded of the things
that happened
over the past two years.
I'm curious.
Have you and Sydney Bristow
crossed paths?
Why?
I heard you had an opportunity
to kill her in Milan
and that you didn't take it.
The Covenant asked me not to.
Really?
Why is that?
They want to retrieve something,
something in her memory.
Something she saw?
Something she experienced?
I don't know.
I'm as curious as you are.
Something you saw.
What the hell is that?
I have no idea.
- We've been over this.
- I know.
The NSC techniques to recapture
my memory are invasive.
Invasive is too benign a word.
We're talking
about surgical procedures
that could leave you
with permanent brain damage.
Allison said The Covenant
wants to access something I saw.
And we'll discover
what that is in time.
Dad, I am walking around with
a secret in my head so fantastic
that Covenant operatives have
been ordered not to kill me.
- I need to know what that is.
- I understand.
But we're not doing it
like that.
How do you propose we do it?
I'm losing my mind!
I just got off the phone with
our N.I.S. Iiaison in Sofia.
Once Allison's plane lands,
you and Vaughn will coordinate
with local authorities
and track her to the vault.
We'll wait until she retrieves
the device, then apprehend her.
- I understand.
- You leave at once.
- Is there a problem with that?
- No, there isn't.
I'll go over op-tech
with Marshall.
I want you clear
on the rules of engagement.
Yes, I know.
Allison is another link
to The Covenant.
She is part
of our larger agenda,
and as such,
is not to be killed.
I want her dead.
What?
The order from Langley is
to bring her in dead or alive.
She killed my wife.
She killed your best friend.
So I look at this
as an opportunity.
The only reason I hesitated
before was I hoped
that she might
have information for you.
But now that we know
there's no hope for that,
I want that bitch dead.
You want to track Allison,
right?
Well, I came up with
a solution to that problem.
The chip inside Lange's tooth,
it uses a frequency signature,
and that's how it
unlocks the vault
that contains his
missile-launching device.
You explained this.
Now, this thing will
hone in on the frequency
and lead us to Allison, and
she will lead us to the device.
Oh, however, I wasn't really
sure exactly the frequency
that the chip transmits on,
so I covered a broader spectrum.
- Is that gonna be a problem?
- No. No, not really.
Alright, kind of.
It might be set off by microwave
ovens, so I would steer clear
of pancake houses of
the international variety.
Got it.
See, the Eprom chip
isn't finished burning,
so it's gonna be a while.
Well, let me know
when it's ready.
Actually,
can I ask you a favour?
- Sure.
- I don't know if you've noticed.
But I'm not that smooth
around the ladies.
In fact, I'm a little awkward.
Let's face it.
I mean, you got the looks,
I got the brains.
I wanted to propose to Carrie,
so I came up with an idea,
and I was hoping you
could give me some feedback.
I've got the looks,
you got the brains?
Tell me what you think,
and be brutal.
Just be honest.
Don't hold back or anything.
Okay.
You're the micro in my chip
The giga in my byte
I think about you, Carrie
Every morning, noon, and night
Morning, noon, and night
- That's...
- Carrie!
We had sushi
I'll protect you,
can't you see?
Carrie, marry me
I love you.
No good?
- I think she's gonna say yes.
- Really?
'Cause of the rock-jam song?
Maybe in spite
of the rock-jam song.
Alright.
Oh, hey, your thing's ready.
Thanks, Marshall.
Rock 'n' roll!
Sloane put Allison on the ground
20 minutes ago.
We have a visual.
There she is.
What is that place?
It looks abandoned,
like an old hotel.
- Do you have an address?
- Yeah.
14205 Beckerman.
I'll tell the pilot.
Put us down
near 14205 Beckerman.
Roger that.
What kind of range
does this have?
Marshall said
it should track the signal
Allison's using for 50 yards,
but he also said it could be
set off by microwave ovens.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
Do you have a signal?
Allison's in there, or someone's
making microwave popcorn.
Let's go.
Where is she?
Hold on.
Upstairs.
She's 30 feet down on the left.
We can't track her
without the chip.
I'll go this way.
Okay.
- She's in the west stairwell.
- Copy.
Well, this is familiar,
isn't it?
I was thinking
about this last night.
I couldn't sleep.
If I follow my orders,
if I don't kill you,
you're gonna kill me.
Sorry about Francie.
I was just following orders.
Once I'd been doubled,
I had to take her place.
We did, like, 80 dinners.
We're a huge success.
Hello?
Mom, I'm gonna have to put you
on hold for a second, okay?
Oh, my...
Move into the kitchen.
- You're me.
- I am now.
Mom, I'm gonna have
to call you back.
I had nothing against her.
She just was a casualty
of circumstance.
Don't blame yourself. There's
no way you could have known.
Just like when you recovered
Rambaldi's journal.
You had no idea
it contained a formula.
What are you talking about?
A formula for a medication
that would ultimately be used
to help heal my wounds.
So, yeah, you almost killed me,
but then you also saved my life.
I shot her,
and we got the device.
I know what you wanted,
but she had a pulse.
Where is she now?
They've taken her to a hospital.
Civilian ambulance?
Yeah, with an armed guard.
Why?
I'll call about
getting her extradited.
I want an update on her
condition as soon as you get it.
Okay.
Good work, Syd.
Thank you.
The Rambaldi book.
Do you remember a formula
for a medication?
No.
We've got to find
that ambulance.
You sure this is the route
they would take?
This is the only way
to the hospital.
There is no other.
Wait, this makes no sense.
If Allison had backup,
they would've been at the hotel.
I don't think she needed backup.
What do you mean?
I think she did this herself.
The paramedics said
she barely had a pulse.
I know.
She did this, Vaughn.
She did this.