Previously on "Alias."
I woke up like it was one night!
I have a scar on my stomach
I have never seen.
You're telling me two years have
passed and I need to be patient?
You have to relax.
I deserve to know what happened
to people in my life!
Sydney can no longer be
your primary concern.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Be cruel if you have to.
Make her despise you because
your kindness tortures her.
So what does the prophecy say?
"This woman here depicted
will possess unseen marks.
Signs that she will be the one
to bring forth my works.
At vulgar cost, this woman
will render the greatest power
unto utter desolation."
You wouldn't do
something like this.
Not to your own father.
Now, I'm not exactly sure
what this means.
- What is that?
- What was inside the box.
It's human tissue.
There was a name
etched inside the box.
Milo Rambaldi.
Marshall, have you
analysed the cube?
I wish.
The jerks are here.
Pretentious Classified
Division of Intelligence.
You know,
conspiracy theorists' wet dream.
- I don't understand.
- That's the point.
Who they are exactly
is on a need-to-know basis.
Suffice it to say, their
jurisdiction supercedes ours.
Well, they have a convoy here.
They're taking the cube away.
Wait.
Taking it where?
If I knew, I'd go there.
I should probably
put a tracer on the cube
and track it to their lab.
Imagine how cool
that place would be.
I'm kidding.
Excuse me.
I'm Sydney Bristow.
I recovered that cube.
May I ask what you're doing?
We've been sent to retrieve
the artefact for analysis.
- Sent by whom?
- Department of Special Research.
You're DSR?
We're a division, yes.
Can I ask where
you'll be taking it?
No, you cannot.
If you'll excuse me.
This is unacceptable.
Every time I get close to some
answers, the door gets slammed.
I know.
Lazarey knew
what happened to me.
He led me to that cube.
And before
we just handed it off,
I at least wanted Marshall
to finish his review.
Sydney, listen to me.
We've broken at least
a dozen federal Laws
in pursuit
of what happened to you.
If necessary,
we'll break a dozen more.
But for now,
there's nothing we can do.
We can bring Dixon
into the loop.
This wasn't his call.
The order to remove
the cube came from Langley.
There has to be
something we can do.
We need to re-evaluate
every piece of information
we've collected.
Start from the beginning.
Assume nothing.
Do that, and we may find a lead.
Good to see you.
Kendall.
I'm sorry we had
to do it this way.
You're part of this?
Well, that all depends on
which part you're referring to.
You're Covenant.
No.
No, no.
No, that wouldn't go over
too well at home.
No, I'm with Special Research.
I had a team transporting the
Rambaldi cube to our facility,
and they were ambushed
in transit.
The Covenant got the cube.
What does that
have to do with me?
It has everything
to do with you.
We need to talk
about the past two years.
As you may be aware,
Mr. Kendall,
I have no recollection
of that time.
I know you don't.
But I do.
I know what happened
to you, Sydney.
I know the whole story.
Or most of it.
You've known?
All this time?
Yeah.
Then...
...why haven't you
said anything?
Because you asked me not to.
Place your hand on the scanner.
I need clearance to hear
about my own life.
You understand the information
is classified?
Any unauthorized
disclosure is a violation
of section 23, paragraph 5
of the Patriot Act?
Yes.
Before we get started,
I'm curious about
how you found the cube.
What led you to it?
You got to be kidding me.
Start at the beginning.
I'm all out of patience.
You died.
Or at least we believed you did.
We found a body
in your apartment.
The existing DNA
matched your own.
And I went to your
memorial service myself.
Watched Vaughn spread your ashes
in the sea.
Nine months went by.
One day I got a phone call.
It was your voice.
You were calling from Rome.
You said you had escaped
from The Covenant.
You wanted to come in.
We met at a safe house
in Tuscany.
Does my father know I'm alive?
Does Vaughn?
They will be informed at the
earliest possible opportunity.
What about Will?
Did he make it?
What you've been through
may have National Security
implications.
I need you to get them
on the phone right now!
All your questions
will be answered in time.
First, we need to know
what happened.
You looked different.
It was an alias of yours
I hadn't seen.
I had a lot of questions, too.
We knew almost nothing about
The Covenant at that time.
So you took me back
to the beginning.
You told me the first thing
you remembered
after your fight with Allison.
So this is what happened to you,
in your own words.
I shot her.
Three times.
Then I passed out.
Dead to the world.
When I woke up,
it was days later.
I was in the back of a van,
strapped down.
You and I are going
to work together.
We will spend
lots of time together.
But we will get the results that
my employers have requested.
I always do.
He injected me
with a neurotoxin.
Temporary paralysis.
I couldn't move or speak.
All I could do was watch.
Your roommate was easy.
We unearthed her.
We left her in your apartment
before we burned it.
But you.
That was more difficult.
When a body
is burned badly enough,
the DNA they test for
is in the teeth.
We extracted pulp
from your teeth
and injected it into the teeth
of the corpse that was
to be your replacement.
Of course, they tested
the body they found.
To them, it was you.
He will mourn and move on.
Find someone else, perhaps.
The sooner you accept that
you are no longer who you were,
the easier this will be.
Sydney Bristow is gone.
Why don't I remember
any of this?
I'll get to that.
From your funeral,
you were taken
to a Covenant facility
near St. Petersburg.
This was the man
who took you there.
The man from the van.
Oleg Madrczyk.
I killed this man.
It was only a week after
I woke up in Hong Kong.
He had all the answers.
He died right in front of me.
You kept your promise.
You said you would kill me.
You were my favourite.
Who the hell are you?
What are you talking about?
Why did The Covenant
take two years of my life?
What did he do to me?
The Covenant believed you were
crucial to their operation.
They needed your cooperation,
which you wouldn't offer.
So Oleg began
a brainwash protocol.
He spent months
breaking you down.
He used sensory deprivation.
Electroshock.
He would put you to sleep
by running an I.V.
with a barbiturate into one arm,
and shock you awake with an
amphetamine into the other arm.
I will kill you,
you son of a bitch!
I promise you!
Once Oleg believed
you'd been broken,
he began a conditioning process.
He started with hypnosis.
Your name is Julia Thorne.
You were born in London
on August 2, 1973.
My name is Sydney Bristow,
you ugly bastard.
He disoriented you
with narcotics.
Your name is Julia Thorne.
Really? Then why is my name
Sydney Bristow?
He withheld food
for weeks at a time.
He bombarded you with images,
information.
Classic techniques,
tried and true.
Julia, your father's name
was Kenneth Thorne.
Julia is who you are.
Your two brothers,
Daniel and Tom.
The Latin school.
Confirmation
at the All Souls Church.
After that...
Julia is who you are.
You lost your family in a fire.
After that, you became
a contract killer.
Your first targets were the men
who destroyed your family.
You became a contract killer.
You showed no pity.
Your first targets
were the men...
Julia will eat well.
Live well.
Julia is who you are.
This went on over six months.
It was about that time that Oleg
felt he'd had a breakthrough.
That his therapy
was starting to work.
Yes?
Lunch.
Once Oleg believed
that you were ready,
they gave you a test
to prove to them
that you were a believer.
That you were, in fact,
another woman.
May I present Julia Thorne?
Welcome, Miss Thorne.
The work you'll be doing for us
requires a certain commitment.
Of course.
Who this man is
is not important.
What is important
is the knife on the table.
Use it.
Kill this unimportant man.
No! No!
Please don't!
Who was he?
We don't know.
So I was programmed.
No.
Not by The Covenant.
Wait.
Kendall, I don't understand.
I murdered that man.
What do you mean I wasn't
programmed by The Covenant?
When you were young,
your father subjected you
to the CIA's
experimental programme
to train and prepare children
for intelligence work.
Project: Christmas.
Among other things,
that programme contained
a fail-safe to protect
its subjects from being turned.
Jack hardwired you to stand up
to some pretty intense
efforts at brainwashing.
I traded his life for mine.
That man, whoever he was,
was taken, brought
into a Covenant facility.
He was dead
no matter what you did,
and you must have known that.
It doesn't lessen what I did.
But if you hadn't convinced them
you'd been programmed,
you would have both been killed.
You could never
have contacted me.
I want to go home.
I want to see my dad.
Your father can't be contacted.
He's under deep cover.
And as it is, you have
no home to return to.
Let me be clear.
You return home,
you're putting in jeopardy
the lives of the people
you claim to love.
You're just trying to scare me.
Look at your friend Will.
The Covenant left
the son of a bitch for dead.
Listen to me.
If what intel
we have on The Covenant
is anywhere near accurate,
they have the potential
to be far more deadly
than The Alliance ever was,
which is why it is imperative
you continue as Julia Thorne.
The Covenant believes
they have you programmed.
If you think I'm going back,
you're insane.
If you don't,
they're gonna come after you.
After your friends, your family.
After Vaughn.
I have to see him.
Sydney, you've been gone
nine months.
He loves me.
Nine months is nothing.
So I let you go.
And you went home.
As hard as it was
to see them together,
you couldn't confront Vaughn.
You realised your presence
was a danger to him,
so you did the only thing
you could.
This is Kendall.
I'll do whatever you want.
And that's how we started
working together.
So I became Julia.
Yes, you did.
They sent you to Algeria,
where you met with this man.
Simon Walker.
He was a thief.
You were introduced
as a contract killer.
You started working together
for The Covenant.
The mission was simple. They
wanted you to find the cube.
During your time with Simon,
you pursued a variety of leads,
all the while
keeping me informed
by passing on the intel
to one of our operatives.
You informed me that Simon
had found Andrian Lazarey.
A Russian diplomat,
member of the Romanov family,
who, like Sloane, was devoted
to studying Rambaldi.
You believed Lazarey would know
where to find the cube.
It was a crucial acquisition,
because it contained
the DNA of Rambaldi himself.
You told me
The Covenant wanted you
to get the information
from him and then kill him.
It turns out you saved his life.
You went to Lazarey
the night before you were
supposed to kill him.
He's a reasonable man.
The two of you struck a deal.
I'll make this as simple
as possible, Mr. Lazarey.
Unless you do exactly as I say,
by this time tomorrow night,
you will be dead.
So that's why
I faked Lazarey's death.
So the videotape.
We presumed there'd be
surveillance cameras.
The murder had to look real.
The paramedics
were CIA operatives
working under my orders.
The Kremlin carried out
a thorough investigation,
and they believed,
as did The Covenant,
that Andrian Lazarey
was assassinated.
Assuming everything
you're telling me is true,
Mr. Kendall,
what am I doing here?
Why are you telling me this now?
And where are we going?
We're going to my facility
in Nevada.
Project: Black Hole.
Four years ago when I was
called in to question you,
I was never FBI.
I was Special Research
overseeing the project.
I've never heard
of Project: Black Hole.
Thank you.
This is everything
the government has collected
on or about Milo Rambaldi
since the 1940s.
A quarter of the artefacts
we have were collected by you.
You're actually something
of a celebrity in-house.
Which is also
why The Covenant needed you.
They believe
Rambaldi's prophecies.
They believe a lot of things,
including the idea
that you are...
The Chosen One.
My mother said that
the night I disappeared.
Get off the ledge!
I'll tell you
what you need to know.
Get off the ledge now.
It's you in the prophecy,
Sydney, not me.
Four months ago, you asked me
not to tell you this.
I honoured that request
as long as possible.
Trust me. When I finish
the story, you will understand.
The Covenant had you.
If they could get the cube,
they'd have everything
to fulfil Rambaldi's prophecy.
You continued to feed
The Covenant false leads.
In truth, you and Lazarey
were working for the CIA
trying to find that cube.
And it took you nine months,
but you found it.
Where was it?
Nothing's ever easy, is it?
It was in the Fish River Gorge
in Namibia.
For 500 years,
the key to Rambaldi's prophecy
Iay buried in the depths
of this cave.
To Rambaldi's followers,
this was the Holy Grail.
A mile-long trek brought you
to an elaborate vault
that housed the cube.
Lazarey had devoted
30 years of his life
to acquiring
the 12 keys to the vault,
the last of which he found only
two weeks before your journey.
Each one had a name on it
that corresponded
to a keyhole in the wall.
This lock won't stay open.
I need to hold the key in place.
Lazarey was trapped,
and the cave began
to collapse around you.
Here, bite down on this.
There was only one way
you could both get out alive.
So you got the cube,
and you got Lazarey out.
Come on, you've got to run.
Let's go.
Come on, keep going.
Our agreement with Lazarey
was that after he helped
track down the cube,
we would let him
disappear untraced.
After you let him go, you were
supposed to deliver me the cube.
But I didn't show up.
No, you didn't.
Instead I got this.
Do you want to know
what happened to your memory?
You might want
to sit down for this.
I'm sorry.
I know you were expecting
the cube with the DNA.
Instead you get this.
You've been great to me.
A real friend,
and I am grateful for that.
But I can't go along with it.
The plan we had.
You know what this is about.
And I'm hoping
you can understand.
What am I talking about?
So I'm taking care of it myself.
The DNA.
Even if it's with the CIA,
it'll never be safe, not really.
I've seen too much.
Everything gets stolen.
Everything.
So I've got a plan.
I found someone,
someone who can help me.
A man who has done
advanced research
on how the brain stores
short- and long-term memory.
I'm not gonna tell you specifics
of what I'm doing with the DNA.
In fact, I don't want
to know them myself.
Which is why I'm gonna try
and have my memories...
...erased.
To keep The Covenant
from ever doing
what they want with
Rambaldi's DNA, I'm gonna have
everything that's happened
in the past two years removed.
If this doesn't work.
I mean, if this kills me...
...better I did it
than The Covenant.
But if it works, if I come back
and I don't remember,
do me a favour.
Don't ever tell me
about what I've been through.
Why are you doing this?
Telling me all this?
In his prophecy, Rambaldi
spoke of a second coming.
Those freaks want to clone him.
No. What The Covenant believes
is that Rambaldi's work
was destined to continue
beyond his time.
That he was due a second coming
by way of a child.
"This woman here depicted
will possess unseen marks.
Signs that she will be the one
to bring forth my works."
"She will render the greatest
power unto utter desolation."
The fanatical point of view
believes Rambaldi's DNA
can be transformed.
Used to fertilise the egg
of a surrogate mother.
Someone referred to in his
prophecy as "The Chosen One."
That's why they cut me open.
Yes.
So they could extract my eggs.
And that's why you went
to such extraordinary lengths.
Because his child
would also be yours.
Sydney, that's why
I came to you.
Not protocol.
There was no official order.
Sydney, a couple years ago,
I got to know you a little bit.
What I believed was,
despite your protests,
you would want to know
about this.
The Covenant has it all now.
I got this video two days before
you turned up in Hong Kong.
And despite my being pissed off,
I respected your choice.
I opted to let it go.
But here we are 4 months later,
and you went for the cube.
Why, when you nearly killed
yourself trying to hide it?
Three weeks ago,
Sloane gave me a package
that I had sent to him
in the mail.
It was addressed
in my handwriting.
Inside was a key and an address
to an apartment in Rome
that I had rented
as Julia Thorne.
I found a code there.
Coordinates that led me
to a box buried in the sand.
It was a hand.
It was Lazarey's hand,
which led me to Lazarey.
To the cube.
When The Covenant learned
I'd hidden the cube,
they kept looking.
Eventually, they found it.
They found the cave.
Lazarey's hand.
So they forged my handwriting.
They planted the code.
They wanted me to find
the hand in the desert.
They planted it there.
They wanted me to ask these
questions to smoke out Lazarey.
They tricked me into leading
them back to the cube.
Why didn't you destroy it?
I don't know. And why did I
just leave it at the hotel?
Maybe there was another step.
Maybe there was
someone else involved.
When we get back, I want you
to look at all the artefacts.
I need a phone.
I need a phone right now.
This is Marshall.
Marshall, I need you to
listen to me very carefully.
You said that the jerks
were taking it away.
That you should put
a tracer on it and track it
because you can imagine
how cool it must be.
I need you to tell me the truth.
Did you put a tracer
on that cube?
If you did, and if you're afraid
you're gonna get disciplined,
I swear to God
you're gonna be okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't put a tracer on it.
I know you.
No one is more curious
about technology than you.
I need to find that cube!
I didn't put a tracer on it.
I swear to you I didn't, okay?
Okay.
I put a tracer on it,
but you cannot tell.
If they find out,
they will fire me.
I cannot be fired.
I'm about to have a baby.
Marshall, I love you.
I love you, too, Syd.
But seriously,
you can't tell anyone.
Can you locate the cube?
Well, not exactly,
but I can narrow it down
to a 10-yard radius.
Marshall,
that's called locating it.
Where is it?
Here's the big picture.
At 2100 hours,
you'll be dropped from
10,000 feet over Patagonia.
You'll hit the ground a
quarter-mile from the building.
We have minimal intelligence
on this,
but we believe the fertilisation
will happen tonight.
Chopper will be here
in two minutes.
We'll review the operation
en route.
This is Kendall.
Where is he?
Tell him I'm waiting.
What's going on with you two?
Nothing.
Come on, we got to prep.
What are you doing?
The day you showed up in Rome,
when you called in,
they put you through to Kendall.
I was there that day
in the office.
When he hung up,
he told me that it was you.
I've known the truth
about what happened,
and I was ordered
to say nothing.
Dixon, we've been
working together for months.
It's not easy, is it?
Keeping the truth
from someone you love?
Now I have an idea what
it was like for you at SD-6.
You're coming with us.
Of course I am.
It's personal for me, too.
Let's do it!
Let's move.
Okay.
Kendall wants all of this
brought back for analysis.
Do your thing.
They have my father.
Take care of it.
Mr. Lazarey.
You know about the passenger?
Excuse me?
The passenger.
We'll have time to talk
at the hospital.
Get him inside!
Move!
Shooter! Shooter!
Dixon,
I'm at the naval hospital.
There's a sniper.
Lazarey's been shot!
He's dead.
Get me a team out here now!
The matter's taken care of.
Yes, sir.
I will.