Last season on "Alias."
I'm approaching the finish line
of a 30-year odyssey.
I won't let anyone else
take the final steps for me.
Listen to me,
you son of a bitch.
You have been a plague
on my life.
You repulse me.
Every time I sat
listening to your lies,
all I could do was fantasise
about slashing your throat.
Drop it!
Why are you wearing that ring?
Since that night...
You've been missing
for almost two years.
There was a fire
at your apartment.
Will survived, but you...
They found remains.
The DNA was a match.
You were dead.
And you got married.
I did.
They asked me
to come to Hong Kong.
The agency thought it would be
best if you were reintroduced
by someone
from your life before.
They could have sent my father.
He's CIA.
He's from my life before.
I can't answer that.
I chose not to stay
with the CIA after your death.
You're not with the agency?
No.
I'm a teacher.
This is gonna take me awhile.
They want me to bring you back.
You can imagine what kind of
investigation's being called.
Hell of a way to wake up.
How much time do I have
before I have to go?
They said
they want you back as...
I don't know who the hell
you are, but you are not Vaughn!
Tell me who you're working for!
Is it Sloane?
Tell me you're working
for Sloane!
Don't...
You're safe.
You're at
the Stafford Naval Hospital.
You're home again.
Sydney, there are no words
to make this easy.
It was Vaughn who came for you
in Hong Kong.
And what he told you
was the truth.
Dixon, what happened to me?
We don't know.
Where's my father?
Or my mom? Have you heard
from her since Mexico City?
Vaughn said Will's alive.
If there was a fire
in my apartment,
if he thought I was dead,
how did Will survive?
And where is he?
And Francie, is she dead?
- Did they find her body?
- You have a million questions.
I have more
than a million questions.
I wish I only had
a million questions!
- Be patient.
- I can't be patient.
I woke up like it was one night.
I have a scar on my stomach
I have never seen.
Two years have passed,
and I need to be patient?
I deserve to know what happened
to the people in my life!
Where the hell is Kendall?
Kendall is not the director
of our division anymore.
I am.
Almost six months now.
Congratulations.
How you feeling?
I'm okay.
You look great.
You lost weight.
Oh, thanks. Yeah.
I gave up all the foods I enjoy.
I'm miserable,
but I look really good.
We got something.
I need just a minute.
Excuse me.
- I'm sorry to be all cryptic.
- It's okay. I get it.
We received a transmission
from Mr. Kingsley.
He got the package
and the decoy.
He's on schedule,
aboard a train to Avignon.
We received intel The Covenant
may be moving to intercept
Kingsley and get the chip.
- And we can't reach Kingsley?
- No, he's radio silent.
But we have a lead,
an address outside of Paris,
a possible outpost
for The Covenant.
Contact the SNCF.
Have them stop the train
at the next station
and recheck Kingsley's ticket.
He'll know to make contact.
And get a team in prep.
I want to raid this outpost.
I have to get back.
Dixon, I want to see my dad.
What is the big deal?
Your father's in prison.
National Security Council
has had him in solitary
for almost a year.
Their policy, without exception,
is that he is to have
no visitors.
Mr. Kingsley,
you know what I want.
Give it to me, and I make
your death painless.
One more time.
My shoe.
My left shoe.
Not what I wanted.
What?
You okay?
I think I know.
Oh, my God.
I think I know where I was.
There are so many new people.
I don't know anyone here.
Just give it time.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, hello?
Hi. Sydney,
I'm Marshall Flinkman.
I work here.
Tech Design and Operation here.
Marshall, of course
I know who you are.
Oh, thank God.
Sydney, it is so amazing
to see you.
I can't even really...
Actually, I wrote a poem.
"I've lost my keys.
Where are they?"
- Sydney.
- Carrie.
Welcome back.
- You're pregnant.
- Oh, yeah. Yeah. I am.
I wonder who the father is.
- Are you guys married, too?
- No.
We're not married.
We're not even engaged.
But we're talking
about getting married.
Not really.
She just has
an issue with wedlock.
Syd, Dixon's expecting us.
If you need anything, just ask.
"I've lost my keys.
Where are they?"
That's a metaphor.
We'd like to hear about
what happened last night.
I had a memory, a vivid memory
of the interior
of the building
where I was being held.
I know that it was in Paris,
and I remember the faces
of at least three of my captors.
Mr. Weiss' report says you
recall overhearing voices,
names,
including Mr. Kingsley?
This is Robert Lindsey.
He's our NSC liaison.
Yes.
So far that's all I remember.
It sounds like the group
we're looking for
is the one
that was holding our girl.
Last night there was a mass
murder on a passenger train.
Among the dead was a CIA asset,
Scott Kingsley.
Kingsley did work for us.
He designed an aircraft,
a spy drone,
that could fly undetected
by radar.
Kingsley was en route to Avignon
to deliver the schematics.
They were stolen.
This drone can be converted
into a delivery system.
Biological weapons, chemical.
I get it.
This group. We know
almost nothing about them.
They refer to themselves
as "The Covenant."
We have some intelligence
identifying
one of their outposts.
We believe this is where
they've taken the chip.
We're sending a team to Paris
to raid the building.
Look familiar?
Yes.
See, we're going in
with or without you.
Without you, we're blind.
You might recognise details
we wouldn't see otherwise.
I'm personally of the mind
that sending you into the field
so soon after your recovery
is asinine.
Well, you might ask yourself
how much you want to apprehend
these killers.
Do not question my resolve.
What you are suggesting
is premature.
Listen to what I'm suggesting.
I've experienced trauma myself.
Return to the field prematurely.
It's as dangerous as not
being trained at all.
Excuse me.
I'm standing right here.
I think I might be helpful
in Paris.
But I will not even consider
going unless you help me first.
I want to see my father
right now.
Miss Bristow,
just so we're clear,
I have no intention of doing
your father one single favour.
Ever.
That said, it's not your fault
he's your father.
And I'm not without a heart,
as you will come to see.
I'll get you in this one time.
Thanks.
Sweetheart,
you look so beautiful.
They told me you were charged
with resisting authority.
Yes.
Dad, I don't understand.
I became obsessed
with your death,
with finding those responsible.
And at a certain point
in my pursuit, I needed help.
So I contacted the one person
I believed I could trust,
given the circumstances.
Your mother.
You were working with mom?
At the time, she was number six
on the CIA's Most Wanted list.
The National Security Council,
primarily Robert Lindsey...
- Have you met him?
- Yes.
He discovered I was
collaborating with your mother,
so he threatened me.
Questioned my allegiance
to this country.
He chose to make
an example of me.
An NSC power play.
Here we are.
I was told you have a memory.
That you believe you were
being held in Paris.
It's an anti-eavesdrop device.
I got it from Marshall.
We have 90 seconds.
Dad, I don't remember a thing.
I read Dixon's lips when he was
outside my hospital room.
I made it up to get leverage,
and they want me on a mission.
- Leverage for what?
- To see you.
They told me I couldn't see you,
and I needed to.
I don't know if I can explain
what it's like waking up
and having everything
be different.
My friends are gone.
I have no job, no home,
and Vaughn's married.
- You're in prison, and...
- Vaughn's what?
He got married.
Michael Vaughn is just a boy
who was never good enough
for you anyway.
Sydney, listen to me.
My investigation into your death
became more disturbing
than I expected.
You must continue my work
and find what happened to you.
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
The only way is by getting
your CIA clearance restored,
having access to my files,
getting out in the field.
I don't think I can do this
without you.
We both know that's not true,
and you have no choice anyway.
The CIA, I am certain,
is dubious about your return.
You must get them
to trust you again.
If they learn you are bluffing
about your memory, it's over.
Dad, what did you mean, the
investigation was disturbing?
Sydney, I knew you were alive.
I made a discovery
that you need...
You probably know this,
but I love you.
I love you, too.
The object
of tonight's mission is to find
and retrieve the microchip.
Also, to acquire any intel
about The Covenant,
who we believe is in possession
of this chip.
We've had the building
under surveillance.
It appears to be abandoned,
but no guarantees.
You've all met Agent Bristow.
She was held prisoner
in this building.
So while I will be leading
the operation,
we will take into consideration
any warnings and insights
that Agent Bristow has to offer.
Any questions?
Let's go.
Hey, you alright?
Yeah.
Move, move, move!
Base, we're in position.
Any last-minute fun?
We've got no activity
outside the building,
and thermal imaging shows
the interior to be clean.
- Good to hear.
- Anything from Mountaineer?
Hey, any of this look familiar?
Not yet.
- Negative.
- Roger that.
Retriever, move on your call.
Okay, let's keep an eye out
for tripwires.
Watch your back.
Let's move.
Alpha team, no sign
of hostiles in quadrant two.
Heading east down
quadrant six corridor.
Hallway clear.
Heading towards quadrant three.
Alpha team, hallway clear.
Building
appears to be abandoned.
Hey, you remember this?
- Base to retriever.
- Go, base.
We're picking up some company.
Quadrant 16, heading 2.00.
Retriever to team, be alert
for a possible hostile.
Quadrant 16 headed
toward quadrant 9.
Retriever,
we're seeing activity.
I'm counting three,
now five additionals.
We have five potential hostiles.
Let's get ready to engage.
Base, we're under attack.
We're under attack!
Fall back now!
- Fall back now!
- Go, go, go!
There are two more of them.
Quadrant six.
All agents abort.
Fall back now.
Let's split up
and take them from behind.
Okay.
Go!
Come on, Morris.
Stay with me.
Come on.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, go get him.
They're dead.
All of them.
Oh, my God, Weiss.
If I told the truth,
this might not have happened.
What are you talking about?
I've never been here before.
The dream I had...
I just...
I needed to regain
the CIA's trust.
And now the team's dead.
Syd, this operation was on
whether you came or not.
And if you hadn't,
I'd be dead, too.
I don't know what to do.
I...
Everything's wrong.
Everything is upside down.
- We got to get home.
- I can't go back!
Robert Lindsey hates my father.
He doesn't trust me.
He wanted results from this.
He wanted the chip.
If I go back,
he'll pull my clearance.
I'll never be able
to help my father.
What are you thinking?
This was obviously an ambush.
Those gunmen work
for The Covenant.
The one who was gonna kill you,
I saw his face.
If I can make a positive I.D.,
that could lead to the chip.
- Leverage.
- To do what?
To get my father out of custody.
To recover what was stolen
from the CIA.
To make sure these men
didn't die for nothing.
I'm gonna need a contact.
A freelancer, not with the CIA.
Someone with resources.
All my names are two years old.
You're not gonna like
my suggestion.
You should go see Arvin Sloane.
What?
Sloane negotiated a pardon
after your death.
He's now a consultant
for the CIA.
Yeah, he now runs a world health
organisation in Zurich.
Omnifam.
Listen to me.
We never had this conversation.
After the gunfight,
I disappeared.
- You never saw me again.
- So what are you gonna do?
Excuse me.
Miss?
Miss, you can't go in there!
It's okay.
We're fine.
Hello, Sydney.
There's a group
the CIA has targeted.
They call themselves
The Covenant.
They've stolen something
I need to get back.
I've made a visual I.D.
of one of their members.
I need to put a name
to his face.
You're gonna help me find him.
You must be in real trouble
to come to me for assistance.
His name is Gordei Volkov.
He's a former Russian MVD,
a high-class hit man.
You just happen to have
his file sitting on your desk?
I had it ready because
I was expecting you.
Sydney, I know you've gone rogue
and that your father
is being held in solitary.
And based
on my experience with you,
I would say you're looking
for a way to win his freedom.
Am I right?
Sydney, just try and remember
the bond that we had
between us, you and I.
I loved you like a daughter.
I loved you.
And even you would admit
there were times...
I would see it in your eyes.
You looked at me
like I was your...
Where have I been
the last two years?
I know it was you!
What did you do to me?
- Do you believe in redemption?
- Not for you, no.
We've helped to feed over 3 1/2
million children worldwide.
We do research.
Our work on cancer
has the potential
to save millions of lives,
Sydney.
So much has changed
since you've been gone.
Remember the Rambaldi device?
A machine designed
500 years ago by a prophet.
All I did was bring the pieces
together and have it assembled.
And when I turned it on,
it delivered a message,
as I suspected it would.
I wasn't prepared
for what it said.
The message was just one word,
one simple word.
"Peace."
The epiphany I had
at that moment...
Suddenly I saw
all the mistakes I made,
the pain that I had inflicted on
the world, the people I loved.
So I chose right then and there
to give information to the CIA,
with which they were able
to dismantle
over two dozen terrorist cells.
I don't know how you convinced
the CIA that you're trustworthy.
Why don't you check my files?
I know you too well.
I don't buy any of it.
I tried to reach
over two dozen contacts.
You're the only one
still active.
Thank you for coming.
Of course.
Forgive me if I look
shocking to you,
but I was believing
you were dead.
I was, but now I'm not.
This is why I love our business.
I need some information.
I hope I can help you.
Gordei Volkov.
I just got a call
from the D.O.J.
You had Sydney Bristow listed
as an enemy of the state?
Mr. Dixon, your operative ran.
Sydney Bristow is a fugitive.
This is why I did not
want to send her out.
Given her condition,
we should be helping her.
I hate to pull rank,
but the Department of Justice
is my jurisdiction,
blindly trusting Sydney...
I never suggested
we blindly trust anyone,
but classifying her in this way
makes her a target.
Then make a suggestion.
I suggest that we use
our resources to locate her.
Oh, she'll be located.
I want her back
in this office alive.
Volkov has a meeting scheduled
for tomorrow night in Prague.
I have the address.
He's supposed to be
delivering something.
What it is, I do not know.
Perhaps it is your thing.
Do you know what he drives?
A sedan, armoured, of course,
with a protective detail.
Sydney, if you want to stop
that car, you will need backup.
No, I don't.
But I will need clothes.
I have the plans for the drone.
If you want them back,
get the NSC to release
my father immediately.
Excuse me. I won't be
blackmailed by a fugitive.
Did you really think you could
come in here and threaten me?
- Yeah.
- What the hell are you doing?
I want it in writing that today
Jack Bristow is to be released.
Mr. Dixon, talk to her.
I'm addressing you, Mr. Lindsey.
I want that "get out of gaol
free" card for my father,
or these are gone.
This is ridiculous.
Mr. Dixon, please provide
Mr. Lindsey with a pen.
I got my own pen, and there's
not a chance I'm using it.
It's your call.
5...
- This is insane.
- 4...
Mr. Lindsey, she will
destroy those plans.
3...2...
1.
Fine.
Thank you.
B-R-l-S-T-O-W.
I know how to spell your name.
I came by to see how you were.
Are you kidding me?
No, I just wanted to
make sure you're...
You didn't come here
to see how I am.
You came to see how you are,
because you know what you did.
You want to make sure
you're okay.
I buried you.
Consider that for one second...
Don't use rational thought
as a defence with me,
not after all you and I
have seen.
Vaughn, you and I live
and breathe madness
every day on the job.
There is no rational thought.
I can't pretend to have
a conversation
about anything else with you.
What it comes down to is faith.
What I was hoping
you would say is,
"I gave up on us.
I lost faith."
But what you came here for
was closure,
and there is not a chance
you are getting that from me.
I'm not gonna say I understand.
I'm not gonna sympathise
with you
and tell you how hard
it must be for you.
But you want to know how I am?
I am horrible.
Vaughn, I am ripped apart.
And not because I lost you,
but because if it had been me,
I would have waited.
I would have found the truth.
I wouldn't have given up on you.
And now I realise
what an absolute waste
that would have been.
Thank you.
There's something
I need to show you.
Not here.
Almost a year
after your apparent death,
I was on an operation.
One of the men I was tracking
was this man, Andrian Lazarey.
Russian diplomat.
I've never seen him before.
This was from a hidden camera
that I placed.
This is how I knew
you were alive.
You don't recall that man
at all?
No.
No!