Erica, are you okay?
-  Yeah, you know, maybe I ate too much.
I keep getting these stomach-aches.
They come and go like every few minutes.
-  Oh my God!
-  Relax! We'll just get her some antacids.
-  She doesn't have a stomach-ache. She's in labor!
-  Oh my God!
-  So if you think I didn't say goodbye to you...
....because you don't mean as much
to me as everybody else...
... you're wrong. It's because
you mean more to me.
-  Rach!
-  What?!
Hey.
-  Shh.. Go back to sleep.
I have to go home.
-  Oh. This was amazing.
-  It really was.
You've learned some new moves!
-  Yeah, well, this guy at
work gave me "Sex for Dummies" as a joke.
-  Ah.
-  Who's laughing now?
-  I know!
-  Breathe, breathe, breathe...
.. Good...
-  Next time, can I say breathe?
-  No, last time
you said it like Dracula,
and it scared her!
Can I get you anything? You want some more ice chips?
-  No, I'm okay.
-  Alright, I'll be right back.
-  Where are you going?
-  To use the bathroom.
- You can't leave me alone with her.
What?
-  This is exactly the kind of social situation that I am not comfortable with!
-  What kind of social situation are you comfortable with?
-  It's just that we've never spent any time,
you know, alone together.
-  You'll be fine.
Nah, you won't, but I'll be back in two minutes.
-  Okay.
-  So, ah... Any plans for the summer?
-  I don't know. Maybe church-camp?
-  Hah. May not wanna mention this.
So, you ever wonder which is worse, you know;...
...going through labor or getting kicked in the nuts?...
-  What?
-  Well, it's just interesting.
You know, because no one will ever know,
because no one can experience both.
-  One of life's great, unanswerable questions.
I mean, who knows? Maybe there's something
even more painful than those things?
Like this..
Morning.
Hey!
What's that?
-  It's my house-warming present for Monica and Chandler.
-  It's a baby chick and duck!
-  Uh-huh. And I named them Chick Jr. and Duck Jr.
-  I did not see that coming.
-  Yeah, I figure they'll love it at the new house...
... you know? It has that big backyard...
...And then, when they get old,
they can go to that special farm...
...that Chandler took the other chick and duck to...
Yes.
-  Yeah. It's a shame people can't visit there.
-  That is the rule, though.
-  Guess what? You're almost an uncle!
What?
-  Yeah, Erica went into labor last night...
... Monica and Chandler are at the hospital right now!
-  Oh my God!
-  Yeah, and I have a definite feeling it's gonna be a girl.
-  Phoebe, you were sure Ben was gonna be a girl.
-  Have you seen him throw a ball?
-  Is Rachel here?
-  Uh, I think she's still asleep.
Hey, hey, how did it go with you guys last night?
She seemed pretty pissed at you.
-  Uh, we, y'know, we worked things out.
-  What's that smile? Did something happen with you two?
-  Hey, I'm not one to kiss and tell...
but I'm also not one to have sex
and shut up. We totally did it!
-  Oh my God. You and Rachel?
-  I know, it's pretty great.
-  So what does that mean? Are you guys getting back together?
-  Oh, I.. I don't know. We didn't really get to talk.
-  But do you wanna get back together?
-  I don't know.
It was incredible...
I mean, it just felt so right.
When I was holding her, I mean...
I never wanted to let her go.
You know what? Yeah, I do. I wanna be together.
YAY!
Yay!
-  So, so is she still going to Paris?
-  Wow, I hadn't thought of that. I hope not.
-  Oh, this is like the best day ever. Ever!
You guys might get back together,
Monica and Chandler are getting their baby,
there are chicks and ducks in the world again!
Oh, I feel like I'm in a musical!
"Daa - raa... When the sun comes up,
bright and beaming! And the moon comes..."
-  Morning!
-  Guess we'll never know how it ends.
-  Okay.
-  Hey.
-  Hey. How did you sleep?
-  Good. You?
-  Good.
-  I bet you did!
-  Uh. Would you guys mind giving us a minute?
-  Sure, yeah. Will you just keep an eye on the chick and the duck?
-  Chick and the duck? Didn't they die...
-  Dive.
Yeah, they dove head-first into fun on the farm.
So...
Morning.
-  You too. ..
...Last night was just wonderful.
-  It really was.
-  I woke up today with the biggest smile on my face.
-  I know, me too. It was...
You know, it was like one of those things
you think is never gonna happen, and then it does...
...and it's everything you want it to be.
-  Uh-huh. I know. It was just,
it was just the perfect way to say goodbye.
-  It's just a little bit more, honey.
-  Help me! This hurts!
-  Is it really that bad?
-  Uh-huh! I think it's time to kick you in the nuts and see which is worse!
Doctor: The baby's head is crowning.
-  Oh! Oh my God!
That is the most beautiful top of a head I have ever seen!...
... Chandler, you have to see this!
-  I'm okay.
-  Chandler, you don't wanna miss this...
.... This is the birth of your child! It's the miracle of life!
-  Alright.
Wow, that is one disgusting miracle.
Doctor: Start pushing. Here we go. Here come the shoulders...
-  It's a... It's a boy!
-  Wow!
-  Is he okay?
Doctor: He's just fine.
-  Oh, you did it!
-  It's a baby! A beautiful little baby! ...
...And some other stuff I'm gonna pretend I don't see.
Doctor: Would you like to cut the umbilical cord?
-  Well, that's spongy.
-  Oh, hey handsome!
Oh, I'm gonna love you so much that...
...no woman is ever gonna be good enough for you!...
... Oh, we are so lucky!
-  I know.
He has your eyes.
-  I mean, I know that's not possible, but he does.
Nurse: We'll just get him cleaned up a bit.
- Oh my God, he's beautiful...
...Thank you so much.
-  I'm really happy for you guys.
-  How do you feel?
-  I'm tired!
Doctor: Well, you don't have that much time to relax...
... The other one will be along in a minute.
-  I... I'm sorry, who should be along in a what now?
Doctor: The next baby should be along in a minute.
-  We only ordered one!
Doctor: You know it's twins, right?
-  Oh, yeah! These are the faces of two people in the know!
Doctor: I can't believe you didn't know it's twins!
This has never happened before.
-  Well, gosh. That makes me feel so special and good.
-  (to the doctor) Wait, did you know it was twins?
Doctor: Yeah, it's here in the paperwork we got from the clinic in Ohio.
-  (to Erica) Anybody tell you?
-  I don't think so.
Although, they did mention something about two heartbeats.
But I thought that was just mine and the baby's.
They kept saying both heartbeats are really strong...
...and I thought well, that's good 'cause I'm having a baby.
-  This is unbelievable.
-  Twins actually run in my family.
-  Interesting!
Can I see you for a second?
-  What do we do?
-  What do you mean "what do we do"?
Twins! Twins!!
-  Chandler, you're panicking!
-  Uh-huh! Join me, won't you?!
Okay, what do you say we keep one, and then just like have an option on the other one?
-  We can't split them up!
-  Why not?
We could give each of them half a
medallion,
and then years later, they'll find each other
and be reunited.
I mean, that's a great day for everybody.
-  Okay, what if the person who adopts the other one is horrible?
-  What if they're not? What if it's adopted by a king?
-  Yeah, because I hear the king is looking to adopt.
-  Monica, we are not ready to have two babies!
-  That doesn't matter!
We have waited so long for this. I don't care if it's two babies.
I don't care if it's three babies!
I don't care if the entire cast of
"Eight is Enough" comes out of there!
We are taking them home, because they are our children!
Okay. Shhh...
Okay.
Doctor: It looks like we're about ready over here.
Doctor: Come on, Erica, start pushing again now.
Ow!
Here she comes!
She? It's a girl?
Yeah.
-  Well, now we have one of each!
And that's enough!
-  And then she said it was the perfect way to say goodbye.
-  Oh my God!
What did you say?
-  Nothing! What do you say to that?
-  Ross, you've got to tell her how you feel!
-  No way!
-  You can't just give up!
Is that what a dinosaur would do?
-  What?
-  Dude, I'm just trying to speak your language.
-  Ross, Rachel doesn't know that you wanna get back together...
...If she did, she might feel differently. She might not even go.
-  You really think so?
-  I'm telling you!
Oh, okay! This is the part of the musical where there'd be a really good convincing song.
"Bam-bam, don't take no for an answer. Bam-bam,...
....don't let love fly away. Bam-bam-bam-bam..."
Hi!
-  Can't a girl finish a song around here?
-  Hey!
-  Hi! So I just dropped Emma off at my mom's.
-  Okay.
-  Oh, you're not taking her with you tonight?
-  No, we decided that I would go ahead and set up first,
and then my mom would bring Emma to Paris on Sunday.
-  Wow, eight hour flight with a one-year old? Good luck, mom.
-  Are you kidding?
Eight hours with my mother talking about Atkins? Good luck, Emma!
-  Alright, you know what? You're right. I should at least tell her how I feel.
-  Ross, wait!
-  What? What?
-  Could you get me a muffin?
Gunther: Rachel?
-  Yeah?
Gunther: I... I know you're leaving tonight,
...but I just have to tell you...
...I love you.
Gunther: I... I don't know if that changes your plans at all, but..
...I thought you should know.
Gunther... Oh...
I love you too.
Probably not in the same way,...
...but I do. And,
and when I'm in a café, having coffee,
or I see a man with hair brighter than the
sun,
I'll think of you. Aw.
-  Oh... Bye guys.
-  Oh my God!
-  Unbelievable!
-  Hey, you know what might help?
-  I'm not getting you a muffin!
-  Do you think they recognize each other from in there?
-  Maybe. Unless they're like two
people who have lived in apartments...
...next to each other for years,
and then one day ...
they're pushed through a vagina and they meet.
Nurse: We're going to take Erica to recovery now.
-  There's something that we wanna tell you.
We decided to name the girl-baby Erica.
-  Oh my God, that's just like my name!
-  Son of a gun, it is!
-  Anyway, I'm gonna go and get some rest.
I'm really glad I picked you guys.
You're gonna make great parents.
Even Chandler.
-  Okay, well, bye!
-  Bye!
-  We'll call you!
-  Okay.
-  Have fun at church-camp!
-  Oh, look at these little bunnies!
-  I know!
You ready to trade?
-  Okay.
-  Alright, let's see..
-  We could trade later.
-  Yeah, I'm good.
-  Hey, what are you working on?
-  It's a... It's a "welcome home" sign for the baby.
-  How sweet! Oh, is that the baby?
-  No, I sat in the paint.
-  Hey.
-  Hey. So, did you talk to Rachel?
-  No, and I'm not going to.
-  What?
-  Why not?
-  Because she's just going to shoot me down.
You guys saw what happened with Gunther.
That did not look like fun.
-  How can you compare yourself to Gunther?
I mean, sure, he's sexy in a more obvious way.
You have a relationship with her,
you slept together last night.
-  Yeah, and she still wants to go!
It's pretty clear where she is.
-  Yeah, I know what you mean. I mean, sometimes...
-  Uh, Joe?
-  Damn it!
-  Look, even if I were gonna tell her,
I don't have to do it now.
Okay? I'll be seeing her again. We've got time.
-  No, you don't! She's going to Paris!
She is going to meet somebody.
Do you know how many hot guys there are in Paris?
It's... It's a city of Gunthers!
Mike: Hey!
-  Hey! What do you have there?
Mike: Oh, I made a little something.
If I had more time to work on it,
it'd be better, but..
-  Oh my God! You did that yourself?
-  Honey, that's gorgeous!
-  You know, the baby can't read, Mike!
-  Hi! You guys, the car-service just got here.
I can't believe they're not home yet!
I have to catch my stupid plane. I wanna see the baby!
-  Monica just called from the cab.
She said they should be here any minute.
And apparently, there's some big surprise.
-  Yeah, did she sound happy about it?
'Cause my friend Ethel's baby
was born with a teeny, tiny beard.
-  Oh my God!
-  Hi! Oh my gosh!
-  Hey.
Phoebe, Ross, -  Hey.
Hey, so what is the big surprise?
Oh.
-  Oh my God!
-  What... What...
-  Okay, okay, awkward question. The hospital knows you took two, right?
-  Yes, it's twins!
-  Oh my God.
-  Oh, they're so cute! Now, what, what kinds are they?
This is a boy, and that's a girl.
-  Her name is Erica.
-  Aw..
-  Hey, that pregnant girl's name was Erica.
-  Yeah. It's a shame you
two didn't get to spend more time together.
-  Yeah, we named the boy Jack after dad.
-  Aw, he's gonna be so happy.
-  Oh, Jack Bing. I love that.
Ooh, it sounds like a '40s newspaper guy, you know?
"Jack Bing, Morning Gazette.
I'm gonna blow this story wide open!"
-  Oh my gosh. Wow, so beautiful.
Mike: (To Phoebe) I want one.
-  Oh yeah?
Well, tell me which one, and I'll try slip it in my coat.
Mike: Seriously. Wanna make one of those?
-  One? How about a whole bunch?
Mike: Really?
-  Yeah! Ooh, we could teach them to sing,
....and we can be like the Von Trapp family!
Only without the Nazis. Although that sounds kinda dull.
-  Oh, you guys, I can't believe this...
... But I'll leave now, or I'm gonna miss my plane.
-  I'm just so glad you got to see the babies.
-  Me too.
Oh, I'm just sorry I'm not gonna be
around to watch you two attempt to handle this!
Alright, I can't say goodbye to you guys again...
... I love you all so much.
-  I love you.
-  Call us when you get there.
-  I will.
Ross, come here.
-  I just want you to know..
... Last night..
...I'll never forget it.
-  Neither will I.
-  Alright, now I really have to go.
Okay. Au revoir! Oh,
they're gonna really hate me over there.
-  So, you just let her go?
-  Yeah.
-  Hey, maybe that's for the best.
-  Yeah?
-  Yeah. You know? You just... Look, you gotta...
You gotta think about last
night the way she does, okay?
Maybe,
maybe sleeping together
was the perfect way to say goodbye?
-  But now she'll never know how he feels!
-  Maybe that's okay. You know?
...Maybe, maybe it is better this way?...
I mean, now, now you can move on. ..
...I mean, you've been trying to for so long,
maybe now that you're on different continents..
Right?
-  Maybe now you
can actually do it. You know?
You can finally get over her.
-  Yeah, that's true.
.. Except
...I don't wanna get over her.
-  What?
-  I don't! I wanna be with her.
-  Really?
-  Yeah, I'm gonna go after her.
-  Yeah, you are!
-  Woo!
-  Wait, wait! Get your coat! Get your coat!
-  My coat...
-  This is so cool!
-  I have no idea what's going on, but I am excited!
-  But Ross, Ross. What do you, what do you think she's going to say?
-  I don't know, but I.. Look,
even if she shoots me down,
at least I won't spend the rest of my life wondering...
...what would have happened.
Where - where is my coat?!
-  You didn't bring one!
My cab's downstairs, I'll drive you to the airport.
-  Okay, guys, wish me luck.
-  Hurry!
-  Good luck, good luck!
-  There's no seatbelt!
-  That's okay. If - if we hit anything,...
... the engine will explode, so you know,
it's better if you're thrown from the car.
-  Alright, alright, let's do this!
-  Okay!
-  Hey!
Man: 18th and East End.
-  I - I don't take passengers.
Man: Hey! The law says you have to accept any fare.
-  No, you don't understand. This isn't a real cab.
Man: Alright, I gotta report you. What's your medallion number?
-  My medallion number is, "Get out of the cab!"
Man: What?
Get out of the cab!
-  Get out of the cab!
-  Oh, hey, hey, can I give you guys your house-warming present now?
-  Now, that you can do.
-  Alright!
-  Ah... Chick Jr.? Duck Jr.?
Don't hide from mama!
-  You can open your eyes now.
-  Are we off the bridge?
-  Yes.
-  Is the old woman on the bicycle still alive?
-  Yes, she jumped right back up.
-  Oh my God, Phoebe, slow down!
-  Do you wanna get to Rachel in time?
-  Yes, but I don't wanna die in your cab!
-  You should have thought of that before you got in!
-  Toll-booth.
-  What?
Toll-booth!
Four bucks. There are quarters
in the glove compartment.
-  Hurry!
-  Okay!
-  Okay.
-  Damn, that window is clean.
-  We were wondering
what was taking so long with the gift,
but now we understand you were doing this.
-  Okay, I wanted to surprise you, but
for your house-warming gift,
I got you a baby-chick and a baby-duck!
-  Really? You got us a chick and a duck?
-  Oh, great! Just what you
want for a new house with infants.
Bird feces.
-  Yeah, yeah, they must have jumped off the table, 'cause now they're gone!
-  Oh, don't worry, we'll find them.
- Actually, I'm gonna go check on the twins.
- Alright.
-  Oh God! What did I just step on?
-  It's okay, it's just an egg roll.
-  Oh..
-  You stepped on my egg roll?
-  I'm sorry, I didn't know to look for Chinese food on the floor.
-  Just put it on a plate and leave.
-  Okay, let's find these birds.
-  Wait, wait. Do you hear that?
-  Oh! They're in the table!
-  Well, that can't be good!
-  We gotta get them out of there!
-  How?
-  Oh, oh! Maybe we can lure
them out. You know any birdcalls?
-  Oh, tons, I'm quite the woodsman.
-  Well, maybe we can just tip the table a little.
-  Joey, wait!
The ball!
-  Oh!
-  Oh God!
So what do we do?
-  I don't know. Maybe we can open this up somehow.
-  No... It's all glued together.
-  Does that mean we have to bust it open?
-  I don't know. Maybe.
-  Oh my God!
-  I know! It's.. It's the foosball table.
-  All right, you know what?
We don't have a choice.
It's like I would have said in
that sci-fi movie if I'd gotten the part.
"Those are our men in there, we have to get them out!
Even if I have to sacrifice the most
important thing in my life...
... my time-machine."
-  Did that movie ever get made?
-  It did not.
-  Ross, where are you going?
-  To talk to Rachel, isn't that why we took a ride in the death-cab?
-  What? What are you just gonna walk up to her at the gate?
Have you never chased anyone through the airport before?
-  Not since my cop-show got cancelled.
-  You have to get a ticket to get past security.
-  What? We're never gonna make it!
-  Not with that attitude! Now, haul ass!
-  Okay, if you could all walk slower, that'd be great.
Madame, your passport please?
-  Oh my God!
I was so afraid I wasn't gonna
remember any of my high-school French,
but I understood every word you just said!
Your boarding pass, please.
-  Oh.
-  Oh, shoot. I had it. Oh,
I can't believe this.
Madame, if you don't have your boarding pass...
-  I have it, I have it, I have it.
Oh, okay, I can't find it, but I remember that I was in seat 32C,
because that's my bra-size.
Madame, you must have your boarding pass..
-  Okay, fine! But you know what?
If I was in 36D, we would not be having this problem.
-  Hey, I need a ticket.
-  Just one?
I drive you all the way down here,
and I don't get to see how it works out?
-  Fine, two tickets, I need two tickets.
-  We're on our honeymoon.
And the destination?
-  I don't care. Whatever is the cheapest.
-  I'm so lucky I married you.
-  Oh! Shoot! Damn it! Where is it?
Oh! Oh! I found it! I found it!
-  Hah! I found it!
I told you I would find it! In your face!
You're a different person.
-  Okay, flight 421 to Paris.
I don't see it, do you see it?
-  No, did we miss it?
-  No, no, no. That's impossible. It doesn't leave for another 20 minutes.
-  Maybe we have the flight-number wrong. God.
-  Hello.
-  Hey, it's me. Here's Ross.
-  What? Hey, hey, listen..
-  Oh my God! Ross, you wouldn't believe the cute little noises the twins are making. Listen.
-  Monica?
Monica, Monica, Monica, Monica..?
-  Oh, I'm sorry. Shoot, they were doing it before.
-  That's alright. Listen, listen.
-  Oh, wait, wait, wait! Here they go again.
-  Monica? Monica, Monica, Monica, Monica..?
-  Isn't that cute?
-  That is precious!
Listen! I need Rachel's flight information.
-  Oh, okay. Alright, it's flight 421. Leaves at 8:40.
-  Yes, that's what I have. It's not on the board.
-  That's what it says here. Flight 421, leaves at 8:40,
Newark airport.
-  What?
-  Newark airport. Why, where are you?
-  JFK.
Don't worry, you guys, we're gonna get you out of there.
-  And we're also gonna buy you tiny, bird hearing-aids.
-  Okay. Here goes.
-  What's the matter?
-  I need to say goodbye to the table first.
-  I understand.
-  Okay.
Table,
you have given us so many great times.
And you guys, Jordan, Victor, Joel... All of you guys.
What can I say? You guys...
...make us look good.
You wanna say anything?
-  I don't know.
Except that, for one last time...
Good game, good game, good game, good game, good game, good game, good game.
-  Okay, here we go.
I can't do it.
-  Well, I can't do it either.
-  Hey! Did you find them?
-  Yeah, they're stuck inside the table!
-  We have to bust it open, but neither of us can do it!
-  Oh, well sure. This gotta be so hard.
I'll do it. Gimme!
-  Phoebe! Wow! No, no, no!
-  Well, I've never gone this fast before.
-  Phoebe, forget it, okay? Newark is - is like an hour away.
...There's no way we're gonna make it in time.
-  She's got her cell, you could call her.
-  I am not doing this over the phone.
-  You don't have any other choice!
-  Hello?
-  Rachel? Oh, good. Hey, by the way, did you just get on the plane?
-  Yeah.
-  (To Ross) For what it's worth, we would have caught her if we were at the right airport.
-  Yay.
-  Uh, Rach, hang on.
-  Phoebe? Is everything okay?
-  Uhm, actually no. No, you've...
You have to get off the plane.
-  What? Why?
-  I have this feeling that something's wrong with it.
... Something is wrong with the left Philange.
-  Oh, honey, I'm sure there's nothing wrong with the plane.
-  Alright, look, I have to go. I love you, and I will call you the minute I get to Paris.
Uhm, what was that?
-  Oh, that was just my crazy friend.
She told me I should get off the plane,
because she had a feeling that ...
...there was something wrong with the left Philange.
Okay, that doesn't sound good.
-  I wouldn't worry about it.
She's always coming up with stuff like this,
and you know what? She's almost never right.
But she is sometimes.
-  Well...
-  Wait, what are you doing?
Well, I can't take this plane now.
Excuse me, sir, where are you going?
I have to get off this plane, okay? Her friend has a feeling..
...something's wrong with the left Philange.
-  Could I get some peanuts?
What's wrong with the plane?
There's nothing wrong with the plane.
Yeah! The left Philange!
There is no Philange!
- Oh my God. This plane doesn't even have a Philange!
- I'm not flying on it!
- Ma'am, please sit down!
- What's going on?
- We're all getting off. There is no Philange!
- This is ridiculous! I...
-  Yeah, okay.
-  Alright. My job here is done.
-  That was... Impressive.
-  Yeah, you didn't even use the tools for most of it!
-  Yeah, they were just slowing me down.
Alright, I have to get back to the babies. I'll see you girls later.
-  Sorry about the table, man.
-  Yeah.
-  You gonna buy a new one?
-  Probably not.
...Nah. I don't know how much I'm gonna wanna play after you go.
-  Well, at least we got these little guys out.
-  Yeah.
-  Aww, we were worried about you!
...Hm. I guess I better get used to things crapping in my hand, huh?
-  I'm gonna miss these little guys.
It was nice having birds around again.
-  Hey, you know what?
Maybe we should keep them here with you.
-  What?
-  Yeah, I mean we've got a lot going on right now.
And, plus, here they'd have their own room.
-  I could get a goose!
-  You know, I - I think you're set with the poultry.
-  Thanks man.
Did you hear that, you guys?
You're gonna get to stay here!
And, and it's good,
you know, 'cause,
'cause now you have a reason to come visit.
-  I think there may be another reason.
So...
awkward hug or..
...lame cool guy handshake?
-  Uh, lame cool guy handshake, yeah.
- Ma'am, I assure you, the plane is fine.
- And you fixed the Philange?
- Yes, the Philange is fixed.
As a matter of fact...
...we put a whole lot of extra Philanges onboard, just in case.
-  Where is she?
-  I don't see her.
-  Rachel! Rachel Green!
-  There she is!
-  Rachel! Rachel!
- Wow, excuse me, sir, do you have a boarding pass?
-  No, no, I just have to talk to someone.
- I'm sorry, you cannot go any further without a boarding pass.
-  No, no, no, but...
- RACHEL!!
-  Oh my God... What.. What are you guys doing here?
-  Okay, you're on.
-  What? What? Ross, you're scaring me. What's going on?
-  Okay, the thing is..
-  Yeah?
-  Don't go.
-  What?
-  Please, please stay with me. I am so in love with you. Please, don't go.
-  Oh my God.
-  I know, I know. I shouldn't have waited 'till now to say it, but I'm..
...That was stupid, okay? I'm sorry, but I'm telling you now.
... I love you. Do not get on this plane.
- Miss? Are you boarding the plane?
-  Hey, hey. I know you love me.
... I know you do.
- Miss?
-  I - I have to get on the plane.
-  No, you don't.
-  Yes, I do.
-  They're waiting for me, Ross.
I can't do this right now, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-  Rachel?
-  I'm so sorry.
-  I really thought she'd stay.
-  I'm sorry.
-  Well, that's it.
Everything's packed.
-  Wow, this is weird.
-  I know.
-  Yeah. Uh, does this mean there's nothing to eat?
-  I put three lasagnas in your freezer.
-  I love you!
-  Hey!
-  So did you guys make it in time?
-  Yeah, yeah, he talked to her, but she got on the plane anyway.
-  Where's Ross?
-  He went home. He didn't want to see anybody.
- Ross, hi. It's me. ..
..I just got back on the plane.
And I just feel awful...
...That is so not how I wanted things to end with us...
...It's just that I wasn't expecting to see you,
and all of a sudden you're there and saying these things... And...
And now I'm just sitting here and thinking ...
...of all the stuff I should have said, and I didn't.
I mean, I didn't even get to tell you that I love you too...
...Because of course I do.
... I love you...
...I love you...
What am I doing?
I love you!
Oh, I've gotta see you.
I've gotta get off this plane.
-  Oh my God!
- Excuse me?
- Miss? Please, sit down!
- I'm sorry. I'm really sorry, but I need to get off the plane,
.....okay? I need to tell someone that I love love them.
- Miss, I can't let you off the plane.
-  Let her off the plane!
- I am afraid you are gonna have to take a seat.
- Oh, please, miss, you don't understand!
-  Try to understand!
- Oh, come on, miss, isn't there any way that you can just let me off...
-  No! No!
Oh my God. Did she get off the plane?
Did she get off the plane?
-  I got off the plane.
-  You got off the plane.
-  I do love you.
-  I love you too, and I'm never letting you go again.
-  Okay. 'Cause this is where I wanna be,
okay? No more messing around.
I don't wanna mess this up again.
-  Me neither, okay? We are -
we're done being stupid.
-  Okay. You and me, alright? This is it.
-  This is it.
... Unless we're on a break.
-  Don't make jokes now.
-  Okay, please be careful with that. It was my grandmother's. Be careful.
-  If that falls off the truck, it wouldn't be the worst thing.
Wow
-  I know...
...It seems smaller somehow.
-  Has it always been purple?
- Look around, you guys...
...This was your first home...
...And it was a happy place...
....filled with love and laughter...
.. But more important..
.. because of rent control, it was a friggin' steal!
-  Hey, do you realise that at one time or another we all lived in this apartment?
-  Oh, yeah, that's true.
-  Uh, I haven't.
-  Wait a minute. What about that
summer during college that you lived with grandma,
And you tried to make it as a dancer?
-  Do you realise we almost made
it ten years without that coming up?
-  Oh, honey, I forgot. I promised Treeger that we'd leave our keys.
-  Oh, okay.
-  So, I guess this is it.
-  Yeah. I guess so.
- This is harder than I thought it would be.
-  Oh, it's gonna be okay.
- Do you guys have to go to the new
house right away, or do you have some time?
-  We got some time.
-  Okay, should we get some coffee?
-  Sure.
Where?
THE END