The design is clearly ancient,
launched hundreds of thousands
of years ago.
Where the hell are we?
Several billion
light years from home.
We are on a ship,
but we have no idea where we are
in relation to Earth.
This ship could be
the most important discovery
mankind has made
since the Stargate itself.
These are the wrong people
in the wrong place.
We've got a lot of wounded.
We need to get home.
We barely have enough power
to operate the main systems.
This ship simply doesn't have
the capability to dial Earth.
Colonel, this chair pre-dates
those found in the milky way.
You want this chair to be
awonderful discovery,
that's fine, prove it.
I didn't steal anything!
- What's this?
- Those are mine!
I brought them when we evacuated!
- Where you going?
- What's your problem?
My problem is fat-asses like you
clogging up the hallway!
I've had it with you!
Looks like a sweet potato.
That is so not going to be sweet.
How do you know?
Analysis we did
when we dug the first ones up.
- Just to make sure it was safe.
- It's safe.
It's safe.
Now, that is one sweet potato.
Really?
Everybody try it!
Dig in.
Oh, my god.
I think I'm going to be sick.
It is food, people!
It will keep us alive.
Becker, boil 'em up, mash 'em up,
- and serve 'em up.
- Yes, sir.
Who's on KP duty?
Sergeant Spencer, but he should have
been here an hour ago.
Sergeant Spencer, you have KP duty,
and you are late.
Spencer, get your sorry ass out of bed!
You have KP duty!
I do not have time for this, Sergeant.
Let's go.
What was wrong
with the old schedule?
I'm worried that we may be
pushing them too hard.
- It's not boot camp.
- No.
No, in boot camp you have opportunity
to learn from your mistakes.
Colonel Young,
this is Sergeant Greer.
Go ahead.
I'm in Sergeant Spencer's quarters.
He did not show up for duty.
I came by to check up on him.
Greer, what is it?
He's been shot, sir.
He's dead.
Projet-SG (1.00)
When did it happen?
Rigor's set in pretty good,
but not completely,
so I'd guess...
An hour either side of...
0200.
And no one heard the shot?
He chose to have his quarters
away from everybody else.
Based on the blood on the wall
and the position of the body,
I'd say he was...
Sitting on the edge of the bed.
Suicide.
Why was he even allowed
access to a gun?
- He was a highly trained NCO.
- He was unstable, you know it.
- With duties that required to be armed.
- It was required of him?
- I have said it from day one that...
- It wasn't suicide.
- What are you talking about?
- Do you see a gun?
It was gone when I got here.
I checked the whole compartment.
Whoever did this took the weapon.
So, any suspects?
Excuse me for being blunt,
but there is a killer on board the ship.
Do we have any idea who did this?
I don't know. I'm still trying to
wrap my head around it.
- It's unbelievable.
- Is it?
You put ordinary people
under enough stress,
you'll find they're capable
of anything.
Add to that the fact
he was hoarding water and food,
involved in several confrontations,
I doubt you'll find many tears
shed over this man.
He was one of our own, Rush.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant,
was he your friend?
Did he, in fact, have one single friend
on board this ship?
James hung out with him.
She... Tolerated him.
All right, so no one
could stand the guy.
Does not make it okay.
I didn't mean to suggest
that it did.
What I do suggest
is that Colonel Young,
you should find out
who this killer is quickly.
As I am sure many of you
have already heard,
Sergeant Spencer
was killed last night.
He signed the weapon out
of the equipment lock-up yesterday,
and the nine millimeter handgun
was not returned,
and is still missing.
I'm aware of how extremely disturbing
this is for all of us.
So,
this is what we're going to do.
Lieutenant Scott,
Eli,
Mr. Brody,
Lieutenant James
and Dr. Park were together
playing cards in the mess
at the time of the murder.
They can all corroborate
each others' stories,
which gives them an alibi...
I was in the control room all night.
- I was in the hydroponics lab.
- Check the kino footage!
I'm sure others will have alibis,
but some of us won't.
I was in my bunk sleeping at the time,
but I can't prove that,
and that makes me as much
of a suspect as anyone.
That is why I am turning over
full control of the investigation.
All right.
We are going to do
a room-by-room search,
starting with quarters,
until the weapon is found.
Now, everyone needs to stay here
until that search is complete,
but...
You are not searching my room
without me there.
Anybody who wants to be there
when their room is being searched
can come when their name is called.
That fair?
Dr. Franklin, you can be first.
Who else would like to
be present when their...
It'll take all day that way,
but we can do two at a time.
If that's what you want.
You two, follow me.
All right, Dr. Franklin,
stay near the hatch, please.
Guess I should be thankful
there's no cavity search.
That can be arranged, Franklin.
We don't like this any more
than you do.
Right.
There's nothing here.
You can just stay here now
until the all-clear.
You know, I understand the need
for a thorough investigation,
check all possibilities.
But you shouldn't lose sight
of the obvious.
What?
Sergeant Greer has to be
your number one suspect.
He killed Spencer,
ran away to hide the gun,
then went back and called it in?
Besides, if he did do it,
- you'd have no evidence at all.
- Not helping your argument...
I'm just saying,
he's one of the few people
we can eliminate as a suspect.
Colonel Young, come in.
What is it?
I've found some new information
regarding the Ancient chair interface.
Have they checked your quarters?
I don't know. I've got work to do.
- Where are you?
- The control interface room.
I've come across
some interesting data...
You're supposed to be here,
waiting with the rest of us.
Obviously neither one of us
has anything to do with this business.
That's not the point.
While this was going on,
we could keep working.
Obviously I was wrong.
Rush out.
Rush, get your ass
back to the gateroom.
Colonel Young,
this is Scott, come in.
Go ahead.
You're up, sir.
Do you want to be here, or...
No, you go ahead, I'll wait here.
There's obviously nothing here.
Let's move on.
Come on.
What is it?
Colonel, this is Scott.
I need you to get down
here right away.
Where was it?
In the air vent.
The vent.
That's imaginative.
I didn't mean to look that hard.
That's okay.
I was the one
who authorized the search.
Right.
- You don't believe I put it there?
- No, sir. Of course not.
Somebody's trying to frighten me.
Right.
This what I've been thinking.
We say that we found it
in a storage room.
Only the person who hid it
will know any better.
Maybe we can smoke 'em out that way.
Are we sure that that's a good idea?
He did not kill Spencer.
- I'm not saying that he did...
- This is someone
trying to undermine
the Colonel's authority.
- That can't happen.
- Eli's right.
I want you to take this gun to Wray,
tell her where and how you found it.
Leave nothing out.
She'll know what to do.
I can't investigate myself.
You can't be asked to investigate
your immediate superior officer.
That leaves Wray.
We got to play this by the book.
But with all due respect, sir,
if the book covers this, I missed it.
I need you to listen to me.
Something's going on here.
If we get caught, this is going to turn
into a bigger mess than it already is.
So I need everything
above board, out in the open.
That is an order.
This looks bad.
- It doesn't prove anything.
- That's not the point.
This is a question of morale.
A lot of people onboard
are going to have doubts.
Eli, you were flying a kino
in everyone's face last night.
Just until the poker game,
Then...
I put it in search mode.
Maybe it caught something.
Something that might indicate
that Young had nothing do with this.
Or that he did.
I find that hard to believe.
Have you contacted Earth yet?
I was just about to use
the communication stones.
Well, whatever
your superiors advise...
We are on our own out here.
Best we handle this ourselves.
Thanks for coming.
I need a favor.
You've heard about what's been going on.
That's pretty hard to miss.
I didn't do it.
Unfortunately, it looks like
I'm going to have to clear my name
before I can find out who did.
- I don't understand...
- Wray used the stones
Please.
To talk to her IOA superiors.
She came back authorized to hold
an evidentiary hearing on the matter.
- Doesn't sound so bad.
- Don't kid yourself.
She's going to come after me.
- Why?
- The IOA's been chomping at the bit
to have one of their own in charge.
This is the best shot they've got.
- You could talk to General O'Neill.
- Miss Armstrong, I could stay in charge
without having to run to General O'Neill
if that's what I wanted to do.
This is about more than that.
The point is,
if she's going to be
the de facto prosecutor,
I'm gonna need a defense.
So...
- Me?
- You went to harvard.
Political science.
This is more politics than law.
I would think Lieutenant Scott...
I don't want it to seem like
the military against the civilians.
Please.
Doctor...
Have you ever seen Colonel Young
attack one of his own men before?
I wouldn't call it an attack.
He was defending me.
Have you ever seen Colonel Young
have any kind
of physical confrontation
with one of his men?
But I'm not military.
You did serve at Icarus base
for a period of six months,
which was under his command.
Spencer was out of control.
He had to do something.
Did he?
I was in the control room
running a test.
Colonel Young and Dr. Rush were...
Were talking.
I don't think they realized
that I could hear them.
And what were they saying?
Colonel Young was complaing
about Sergeant Spencer.
Said that he had gotten out of hand,
and if the situation didn't improve,
he might have to take,
drastic measures.
But you have no way of knowing
what he meant by that, do you?
Assuming you heard correctly.
No, not at the time.
I don't remember
the exact details of the conversation.
But you do remember
speaking with Colonel Young
about Sergeant Spencer.
The Colonel
was doing most of the talking.
I think he just wanted
to let off steam.
Do you remember him saying
that if things didn't improve,
he was going to have to take
drastic action?
I'm not sure he used
those exact words.
Do you agree
that Sergeant Spencer
was a disruptive force,
that his attitude
was damaging to morale
and was only getting worse?
Then would you say that his...
Removal from the situation
has been a net benefit,
or a detriment?
I know what you're trying to do.
You want me to suggest that...
We're better off without him,
and therefore imply that Young
may have drawn the same conclusion.
That as Commander,
he may have believed
he had no choice.
That would be pure speculation,
and I'm having none of it.
Didn't stop him
from saying it out loud, did it?
Are you sure there's nothing
in the kino footage?
I've confirmed alibis
for half a dozen or so people,
but I haven't found anything
that helps him.
You found a empty bottle
of sleeping pills
in Sergeant Spencer's quarters,
didn't you?
Did you know he was taking them?
I wish I had.
I might have been able to help him.
You're suggesting
that he had a dependence,
and as a result,
that he was suffering from withdrawal.
It would explain a lot of things.
But you don't know that for a fact.
Hypothetically,
if he was suffering from withdrawal,
it could have caused him
anxiety, depression,
even suicidal tendencies.
In fact, all the physical evidence,
the blood spatter,
the angle of the wound,
the position of the body,
it was all consistent with suicide.
But you're not a forensic scientist.
No, but I've seen
gunshot suicides before.
And in those cases,
was the gun ever absent
when the body was found?
No, but it's obvious
that someone planted...
- It's not up to you to speculate...
- Isn't it true, Lieutenant,
that if we were on Earth,
there is a simple test you could do
to determine if Sergeant Spencer
had fired that gun?
I suppose we could test his hand
for powder residue,
and properly test the weapon
for fingerprints,
but we don't have the necessary...
Is it possible
that a forensic scientist from Earth,
say, using the communication stones,
might have been helpful
even without the equipment
you're talking about?
If we hadn't handled the weapon
or contaminated the crime scene...
Yeah, but whose decision was it
to have us investigate this ourselves?
Ms. Wray, I think it was my turn
to ask questions.
What are you doing?
I'm taking my turn, as we agreed.
Would a proper autopsy
be able to determine
if he was in fact
suffering from withdrawal?
Expert or no expert,
without any actual forensic
equipment or facilities,
is it possible to know for certain
what really happened?
I don't think so.
I think it's time
that we take a short recess.
We'll resume in an hour.
Thank you.
I need to talk to you,
now.
What was that?
- We're trying to get to the truth here.
- I don't think that's possible.
We can't afford to have an unsolved
murder hanging over our heads.
So forget about the possibility
that the Colonel is being framed
- and just get this over with?
- I don't think Young
is so far above reproach
as you seem to think he is.
You're the human resources person.
You would know all about that.
In fact, you know more
about every person
on this ship than anyone.
If we're throwing due process
out the window, who do you think did it?
We'll just go with that.
You don't think he really did it.
I'm not so sure
what to think anymore.
Spencer was a menace,
we all know it.
Maybe it's just like Rush said,
- he thought he had no other choice.
- No, that's crazy.
Well, let's face it,
how well do any of us really know him?
She wants to gather
all the evidence she can
and then put it to a vote.
- What, like a jury?
- No, everyone.
I say we end this right now.
I say we go in there,
tell 'em that the party's over,
and get back to work!
Who's with me?
All right, take it easy, Greer.
This is mob rule.
This is what used to do
to guys like me
for looking at white women
the wrong way.
Now, you think I'm gonna hang back
and let this go...
Am I interrupting something?
No, sir.
At ease.
This has gone on long enough,
Colonel.
We're ready to back your play.
That won't be necessary.
Ms. Wray and I have already
come to an agreement.
She's going to close the investigation
for lack of evidence against me.
I, in return, will be stepping down.
From this moment on,
she's in command.
I hear congratulations are in order.
Really?
I was just wondering
what I'd gotten myself into.
An opportunity to do
things differently, perhaps?
What do you want, Nicholas?
Control over my science team,
including Eli.
But you report to me.
Of course.
That's it?
You sound surprised.
- This is it?
- This is it.
Not very impressive.
I mean, as far as chairs go.
Well, time will tell, I suppose.
So you sit in the chair,
it downloads the secrets of the universe
into your head?
Then you die.
Not necessarily, Eli.
Every time it's ever been tried.
- This close to death.
- Who's tried it?
- General O'Neill, for one.
- And he survived.
We don't have little gray aliens
to set things right this time.
No, we don't, but...
this is an earlier model
of that same device,
possibly a prototype.
Built very early in their evolution.
In my experience, the 1.0 version
is usually the most buggy.
It's also the simplest.
Maybe it's really simple.
It just tells you how to fly the ship.
I'm sure it's a bit more than that,
but your point is well made.
It's knowledge of this ship we need.
If we're to survive,
or for that matter,
get back to Earth one day,
then I'm convinced that this chair
is the only way to do that.
Maybe there's a way
of choosing what information
gets downloaded.
Or it's just a matter of slowing down
the download so it can be cut off.
There's only one way to find out.
This is our priority now.
I don't get it.
If Wray admits that there's
not enough evidence against you...
There may not be enough to convict,
but there's plenty to cast doubt.
If I force the issue,
we risk dividing the crew.
We can't afford that.
These people need a real leader.
- Whether they like it or not?
- Maybe.
Nobody signed up for this,
and I can't just assume
they're going to follow my orders,
and I can't rule the ship by force.
I mean I won't.
All right.
You tell us that Wray is in charge,
that is fine,
but as far as me, and Tamara,
and the enlisted personnel
are concerned,
you are still
our commanding officer,
and nothing is gonna change that.
Still here?
Yeah, I got stuck
with the late shift.
How's it coming?
It's not.
We ran all Ancient systems diagnostic.
Nothing.
Rush is trying to write a new program,
but it seems like this thing
is designed to prevent any access
except through the chair itself.
Which would prevent an Alien species
who doesn't happen
to share Ancient physiology
from trying to hack in, I guess.
Maybe Rush is right.
Maybe we're close enough
for it to work.
Believe me,
if Rush thought it was safe,
he'd be sitting there right now.
Maybe...
You should get some rest.
Rush is due to relieve me at 2300.
If I wasn't here,
I'd never hear the end of it.
Maybe you could go to the mess
get me some alien mashed potatoes?
Really?
I'm starving.
You got it.
This is Eli!
Anybody on this channel?
I need help!
This is Young. What is it?
I have a medical emergency.
I need help now!
- What's...
- I don't know.
What happened?
How long's he been in here?
I went to the mess for five minutes,
when I got back, he was on the chair.
Well, the convulsions have stopped,
but he's completely unresponsive.
He's basically
in a deep catatonic state.
Is there anything
you can do for him?
We could try a high dose of lorazepam,
see if it'll bring him out of it,
but I'm flying blind here.
Do it.
How is he?
You just couldn't wait, could you?
Anyone who had access to that room
was ordered not to sit in that chair...
You knew.
The temptation was there.
In fact, you made sure of it
by telling them it was our only chance!
You wanted somebody there
because you didn't have
the guts to do it yourself!
Both of you, stop!
It was under my authority,
so ultimately, it's my responsibility.
I know.
All right, we need to talk.
You've got those things running day
and night, all over the dang ship,
and you are telling me
not one of them saw something...
Anything out of the ordinary.
I've been over it twice,
there's nothing there.
Look again.
He was framed, Eli.
We are going to find out by who,
and we're going to put a stop to it.
This is Brody in the gateroom.
Go ahead.
We have an active gate,
and we sent through a kino.
Atmosphere is nominal.
Temperature is in the green.
- We're good to go.
- I'll be there in a minute.
- May I have a moment of your time?
- I have to get down to the gateroom.
We're ready to send a team
to the next planet.
That's actually
what I wanted to talk to you about.
I notice that myself
and a few other marines
were taken off
the away team duty list.
May I ask why?
Call it a...
temporary adjustment.
You thought it was me
who killed Spencer at first, didn't you?
You were a valid suspect.
If you can't deal with that,
it's your problem, not mine.
Now, get out of my way.
Yes, ma'am.
But I'm not going anywhere.
It doesn't look like there's
much vegetation around the gate,
so you may have to widen
your search.
Lieutenant James and airman Rennie
will be providing security,
but you're in charge.
Congratulations.
What?
I'm sorry.
I should have caught it.
You have to look close.
- There's nothing there.
- Look at the time codes.
They don't match.
- Wait, what's that?
- That is a deletion.
I wouldn't have even noticed it,
except it caused a glitch in the code.
It's from the exact time
that Spencer was shot.
- So the kino did pick up something.
- It must have.
But if it's deleted,
how does it help us?
Because whoever did this was good,
but not good enough.
But I always back up the last two days
of footage on my hard drive.
Why?
My documentary.
I have to download it to my computer
before I can edit it.
If there's an ancient version
of iMovie in the database,
I haven't found it.
There.
Colonel Young, go to channel 2.
- What is it, Lieutenant?
- I've got something you need to see.
I tell ya, if I could change one thing
about the day we escaped from Icarus,
- I would've worn better shoes.
- Really?
Those are nice shoes.
Seriously, how much longer
do we have to keep this up?
There's obviously nothing here.
Spoke too soon.
An alien ship?
- Are you sure?
- That's what he said.
How long till we jump?
Just over 2 hours.
I'm on my way.
- I was just coming to get you.
- I have to get to the planet.
It can wait.
Look, they found the remains
of a crashed alien ship.
There's very little time
before we jump back to FTL.
It can wait.
It's been about a week
since I ran out of pills.
Haven't slept much since.
I can't think.
Everything's...
I don't know.
These people don't even realize
they're inside
a big floating coffin.
I wish I could come up
with something better to say.
I'm sorry.
The kino kept recording,
but the file must have gotten corrupted.
This was all I could get.
The point is, it wasn't there
when Greer found the body,
so we know someone took it,
along with the gun.
Who would have the skills
to delete the file
- from the mainframe?
- It's not that hard, really.
Anyone with a basic knowledge
of the ship's computer.
At least a dozen people,
if not more.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
Obviously, we need
to re-think our situation.
Obviously.
We should recall the team
from the planet...
No, we can't do that.
In over a dozen planets,
we haven't had a single indication
of advanced technology up until now.
This mess isn't going anywhere.
He's right.
This ship could be important.
I'm going too.
- If you think it's really...
- I'm not asking permission.
I'm telling you.
Let's go.
It's not Ancient.
That much we've figured out of them.
The material, the design,
it's different.
It's not emitting any radiation,
or EM fields.
It's basically dead.
Have you been inside?
We've located a hatch,
but we haven't figure out how to get in.
We'd probably have to cut it open.
How much time would that take?
More than we have.
We're pushing it as it is.
Lieutenant, let's pack it up.
Just give me
a couple of more minutes.
- It's going to make a difference?
- Well, it might.
All right.
I'm willing to push it if you are.
Take your team to the gate.
- Are you sure?
- We'll be right behind you.
Whatever you say.
Volker was right.
This is unlike
any other kind of alien technology
we've encountered before.
If they're indigenous to this universe,
they might be willing to trade.
Knowledge, information...
There has to be a way in.
I know it was you.
I'm sorry?
The files...
were not corrupted.
The kino kept recording
until you came into the room.
Let's hear it.
Let's hear how you lie
your way out of this one.
I heard the shot.
I went to investigate.
Then I found him.
And then,
you decided to frame me for murder.
That's a bit melodramatic.
I knew there wouldn't be
any real evidence against you.
The idea was to create
just enough doubt
to get you to step aside.
I see.
That was the idea.
You're the wrong man for the job.
I'm sorry to have to say,
but I think you know it's true.
Do I?
You don't believe in the mission.
You resigned your position
as SG leader
because you didn't want to make
the hard decisions.
The life and death decisions.
That makes you a liability.
I'm not proud of what I did,
but I did it
for the benefit of everyone on board.
The end justifies the means.
Something like that.
Are we done?
We'll never be done.
We shouldn't have left them.
- So we could get stuck there, too?
- No one is stuck.
Not yet. How much time?
20 seconds.
Where's Rush?
He didn't make it.
So, we just stayed too long.
On the way, Rush tripped himself up,
started a rock slide.
I was ahead,
but I barely made it through.
I just wanted you to know,
that I've informed the crew
of the evidence that's come to light.
Since you've been
completely exonerated,
obviously you should resume
your duties as commander.
Tomorrow.
You need to rest.
She can be in charge one more day.
Thanks.
Shut the door.
The rest of the kino footage?
Even Scott didn't see it.
I want you to make a copy for me,
put it on this,
and then delete it
from your hard drive.
Anything else?