This is what Destiny intended
from the moment it entered the system.
We are going to survive,
we are going to make it home.
Ths ship came here for a reason!
Destiny is powered
by the stars themselves.
He and Young are bumping heads.
Not sure which camp
is the better choice.
We pretend nothing happened.
We need to be ready for
the next encounter...
For the sake of the crew.
You dreamt you were the spy
who leaked everything
to the Lucian alliance?
It wasn't me.
I was Colonel Telford.
The Goa'uld
had brainwashing technology.
It is possible that the
alliance now has that capability.
On Earth, you are on your own.
You must be using
the ancient communication stones.
- What?
- Telford wouldn't make that mistake.
We know that you are a traitor
and a murderer.
Now we know you're a coward too.
You've found another Icarus planet.
We're all very excited
to have Dr. Rush's full cooperation.
Kill me and you kill Rush!
Begin venting the atmosphere
in Colonel Telford's quarters.
Open this damn door!
We both know
you're not going to kill me.
Mr. Brody, this is Wray.
You need
to restore the atmosphere...
Please disregard that request.
By letting this happen,
you are participating in not only
the murder of Colonel Telford,
but Dr. Rush as well.
Sir, you've made your point.
I'm not trying to make a point.
Open the door.
- I know what I'm doing.
- You're killing him!
I know that, Lieutenant.
What should we do?
The Colonel's bluffing.
He's not going to kill him.
What's happening to him?
You've killed him.
- You're all in danger.
- What?
They're coming.
Who's coming?
The Lucian alliance.
They're coming to take Destiny.
Projet-SG (1.00)
www.projet-sg.com
We've been informed
that this ship faces an incursion
by armed forces
of the Lucian alliance.
The group responsible
for the attack on Icarus base.
All military personnel on board
have been placed on high alert.
If the enemy has acquired
the means to dial Destiny,
their point of ingress
will be the Stargate.
We're clear.
So the gateroom is off-limits.
All surrounding corridors
have been placed in lockdown.
No one may enter
without proper authorization.
I've provided homeworld security
with intel on the planet
from which the Lucian alliance
intends to launch their assault.
They're dispatching forces
as I speak.
The best-case scenario,
Earth forces
take the launch point intact
and we gain a supply line from home.
The worst-case scenario,
our forces don't make it
before the attack is launched,
in which case
we'll have to deal with them on our end.
In that event,
all non-military personnel
will be ordered
back to your quarters,
where you will remain
until the situation has been resolved.
Make no mistake...
this will be dealt with swiftly
and decisively.
Thank you. That is all.
A couple of hours ago,
Colonel Telford admitted to being a mole
for the Lucian alliance.
And now, suddenly, he's on our side?
- You trust him?
- I didn't say that.
- What in the hell was that?
- "What in the hell was that, sir?"
- All you had to do was tell me.
- I was keeping you out of it.
You didn't have to.
If I'd known killing him
and bringing him back
was the only way to beat
that brainwash,
I'd have been behind you 100%.
So you'll follow orders as long as
I explain everything beforehand?
No, sir, that is not...
That's great, because if it was,
we'd have a problem, Lieutenant.
Do we have a problem?
Good.
It's not the time for that.
No headaches or blurred vision?
I told you, I'm fine.
Rush is fine. I'll find out about me
when I switch back.
Look, I really need to go, and...
Can you give us a minute?
How are you feeling, David?
- Confused.
- I bet.
You went the whole nine yards.
To the brink and back.
I had to.
In my defense,
it wasn't the first thing I tried.
Yeah. Thanks for that.
At least the brainwashing explains
why you've been such an ass.
I've read the SG mission reports
of that method being done in the past.
I just never...
You have no idea what it's like
to remember things that you've done...
Terrible things.
You weren't yourself, David.
You've got to send me back.
- Not yet.
- I've done all that I can here...
I already killed you once...
I'm more useful to you
in my own body with them.
You know that.
How else will you get Rush back?
- Listen...
- Get him out of there.
You've just come back from the dead.
I want you to get your strength back.
Excuse us.
Listen, when they come,
I want you here, safe.
Safe?
There could be wounded.
We're going to need you.
- What we'll need is a real doctor.
- You're up for this.
Not even close.
What are you planning to do?
Evacuate the atmosphere in the gateroom
the minute they step through.
Kill them all, you mean.
You think I have a choice?
If you're asking for forgiveness,
I can't help you there either.
I'll do my best.
You're back.
That was me.
I had to see
whether you were faking.
Well, I wasn't.
I apologize.
Back to work. I know.
Planetary scans.
It looks like the intel is good.
The planet's laced
with naquadria deposits.
We detect an energy signature emanating
from what looks like a pyramid.
Pyramid?
That takes me back.
The complex inside is shielded
against beaming technology.
So Rush can't be beamed out.
We'll have to go in
with ground forces.
All right, Colonel.
You have a go.
What was that?
We're under attack.
- Can we dial the ninth chevron?
- Not without blowing everything up.
Dial it.
Get ready!
We're going now!
The Lucian alliance
is an organization of humans
from sovereign planets
who have taken control
of the resources and technology...
The air force video?
I'm just seeing if there's anything
that might help.
What's he going to do?
The Colonel?
They're sending an army.
What do you think he's going to do?
This is it.
It's happening now?
Go.
Radio back
when you reach the other side.
And take him with you.
I see them, Eli.
All personnel,
report to your designated areas.
This is not a drill.
Defense teams stand by.
- Which button?
- This one.
How long will it take
till we reach vacuum?
A minute or so?
That's about right.
Defense teams stand by
to secure prisoners on my order.
Copy that.
Monitor from here,
stay on the radio.
Got it.
What happened?
No, no, it's me.
The ship...
- The Lucian Alliance...
- We know everything. Telford told us.
So what are we doing about it?
Let's just say it'll all be over
in a few minutes.
Come on.
I'm reading a huge energy spike.
At this rate, they've got less
than a minute before their core goes up.
Get our people out of the shielded areas
And beam them back to the ship, now!
The core is going to go critical.
I can't stop it.
Still no signal from the other side?
Get as many of our people through
as you can.
Colonel, we still have two 302s
on their way back from the planet.
We can't wait.
Get us out of here.
Aren't we supposed
to go to our quarters?
These are my quarters.
And I'm not going anywhere.
They brought Rush along with them.
We're going to have to use the hard way.
- What did you do to the Gate?
- It wasn't me.
You killed over a hundred of my men!
Massin, your father's name
was my password.
Gate travel must have
severed the link.
Lucian Alliance forces,
you are surrounded and sealed in.
You will also find the intel
provided by Colonel Telford
is now useless.
Lay down your weapons
in front of the doors.
Step back into the center of the room
with your hands on your heads,
Or we will vent
the entire compartment to space.
Can they do it?
Then they should have.
Colonel, they're up to something.
Talk to me.
They've got something
to open the doors!
Vent the atmosphere in the Gateroom.
- Do it now.
- It's too late.
Take cover!
Get back!
Go!
Fall back!
- Rush, you should stay here.
- No, no. The ship's under attack!
It's time to go.
- Just wait.
- Let's go.
Now!
There's an elevator this way.
Oh, God...
Go!
Wait!
You're welcome.
Want to get the hell out of there?
You've been shot.
Sorry, sorry.
See, it's okay.
You'll be okay.
You'll be fine.
I'll be right back.
Okay?
Over here.
Colonel Young?
Who is this?
Commander Kiva
of the Lucian Alliance forces.
We will not be complying
with your request to surrender.
We barely made hyperspace.
This time it was even closer.
What about casualties?
Two of my 302s couldn't make it back,
and if Rush was still on the planet...
I'm sorry, Sam.
Did any of them make it to Destiny?
I haven't heard.
So much for that.
Why didn't you evacuate
the compartment to space?
- That was the plan.
- He didn't do it to save you.
Not me.
The connection was severed
the minute I stepped through the gate.
Give me the lay of the land.
This is the Gateroom.
They've also occupied
the surrounding corridors.
They had advanced further,
but they pulled back.
Just took what they could hold
with limited manpower. That's smart.
Once they retreated,
I locked down the area behind them.
Given the technology at their disposal,
it won't stop them,
but it should give us some space.
The prisoners are being held here.
Between them and us,
30 feet of corridor either way.
Tthe second we hit the outside sections,
those hostages are as good as dead.
I've done a head count.
We have 12 missing
and presumed captured,
including Riley, TJ,
Eli, and Chloe.
Come on!
What happened?
You were shot.
I stopped the bleeding.
You're fine. Look up here.
Look at me. Look at me.
Where are we?
I don't know.
I've never been
to this part of the ship before.
No-one has.
I just pressed some random buttons.
We can't get back.
I'm guessing
someone locked out elevator access.
Us or them?
That's the problem.
I just need to get to a window.
Get an idea where we are.
And then we can walk back.
I've got you.
Come on. Come here.
Ready?
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Lean on me.
I've got you.
Ready?
Here you go.
Colonel Young?
Go ahead.
Here's how I see the situation.
We have the Gateroom
and some of your people.
You hold the control interface room,
which I'm told,
is the ship's nerve center.
What do you want?
We came here
for the same reasons you did.
We don't want to hurt anyone.
You're welcome
to stay aboard Destiny
and help us realize
the potential of her discovery.
Lay down your weapons and join us.
Or, if you prefer, we can drop you off
at the next inhabitable world.
Or I vent the atmosphere
in the sections you're occupying
and keep the ship.
If you had that in you,
you would have done it already.
The point is I have the ability
to end this conversation right now.
She wanted to see you.
- Wouldn't shut up, in fact.
- As you were, Sergeant.
We are way past the point of fighting
our way out of this situation.
We need to negotiate
with these people.
- And I think I should be the one to...
- No, I think you're right.
Him.
And her.
That's a mistake.
It's a demonstration.
All it will do is force their hand.
Do you want control of the ship
or not?
They have some of our people.
But we have some of theirs.
So the first thing we need to do
is suggest an exchange.
Do you think they'll do it?
No. But I think it's worth a shot.
This is the control interface room.
This is the Gateroom.
If we cut our way through the wall here,
we can flank them.
- I can lead a team...
- That will reduce our numbers here.
We take the control interface room,
there's no need. The ship will be ours.
- These sections are in red.
- That section is exposed to space.
The ship's shield will hold
long enough for us to pass.
We will slowly
vent atmosphere to space, yes,
but we could seal the corridor again
after we've taken the ship.
Take six men.
- I'll need twice that...
- Six.
And if anything goes wrong...
These three die.
Not her.
She's a medic.
We can use her in the event...
Who is this?
My name is Camile Wray.
I am the civilian authority
aboard this ship.
I'd like to act as an intermediary
to resolve this issue
without further bloodshed.
Colonel Young
will not transfer control
of this ship to you.
And you will?
But I will expedite
a prisoner exchange.
Your people for ours.
If I release my prisoners,
Colonel Young will not hesitate
to vent this compartment.
You have 12 of our people.
We have only four of yours.
I propose an even trade,
Four for four.
You maintain your advantage
and gain some much-needed manpower.
Colonel Young agrees with this?
In our society,
the military takes orders
from civilian leadership.
I'll consider it.
Nice job.
That should buy us some time.
Look, you're trying to save lives here.
Obviously that's a good thing.
But even if she agrees to the four,
which is doubtful,
she won't go any farther.
Once the equation tips
to the point of acceptable losses...
No acceptable losses...
Colonel Young has already determined
what that number is.
He knows the chances of us winning
without loss of life
are practically nil.
So limit our losses,
yes, all that we can.
But you'll have to do something.
- You don't know that.
- I'm one of your acceptable losses...
- You knew what you were getting into...
- You should have got me out!
You have no clue!
Stop this now, please!
I am going to save
every one of those hostages,
and I'm going to retake this ship.
Do you understand me?
Telford has convinced her
that he is still with them,
otherwise he would be dead.
Sooner or later he
will make his move.
We are to gamble...
this ship
and all of our lives
in the hope that some traitor
has had a change of heart.
Look at that.
I guess those elevators
go more than just up and down.
Right there.
You good?
I must have hit a few buttons
I wasn't supposed to press.
Is the air getting thin?
Life support isn't working out here.
How do you know?
I was the one who shut it off.
Rush's orders.
There's air.
There isn't any new air
being pumped in.
We need to keep moving.
I don't know if I can.
No problem.
I got you.
This is my Lieutenant, Varro.
Save him.
He's badly wounded.
At even the slightest hint
of trouble.
I'll bring you back, sir.
I need to speak to General O'Neill.
Second-guessing a decision
is a waste of time.
I'm not there.
But I'm starting to wonder
if maybe I should be.
I can't speak to that, sir.
This should be done, Colonel.
Over.
At the time, I believed
that venting the gateroom
would kill
both Dr. Rush and Colonel Telford.
They deserved a chance...
We lost two 302 pilots
sent to stop the attack.
Sorry.
Colonel Carter knew she'd lose her ship
if she tried to save them.
But it was the right decision.
Are you up for this, Everett?
Because somebody will take your place
if you're not.
I'm not going to let anybody
take that ship.
Then get your ass back there.
We're good.
What are you doing?
Just checking to make sure
we're headed in the right direction.
This way.
There's no countdown.
What?
We dropped out of FTL
because someone was gating in.
Why haven't we jumped back?
Someone just activated a console
in one of the access corridors.
A console just came on
using Telford's code.
There's a cordoned-off
section coming our way.
That's his move.
- It's cold.
- Really?
What do you find?*
We have to be careful
moving through sections.
There's a reason
we've never beenthis far.
A ton of compartments
are de-pressurized.
Hang on.
Ready?
More dark and gloomy.
We're good.
Gotcha.
- How are you doing?
- Good.
You sure?
Stand by.
We're good to go.
Ready.
Just give the word, sir.
- It's locked down.
- I'll handle it.
Okay, get ready.
What was that?
Ready.
What happened?
You didn't do that?
What is that?
Just a minute ago it was a man.
You need to stand down
till we figure this out.
This is Young.
Everybody stand down.
Throw me a radio.
Radio?
Three clicks, go to channel six.
We're going
to have to try this again.
- Let's stop.
- I'm fine.
- Eli, you don't...
- Seriously.
This is nothing.
Once, I climbed
the Redridge Mountains
on my way to Stonard
with a full pack.
Where?
The World of Warcraft.
That must've given you
quite the sense of accomplishment.
A little break.
What do you think is happening?
We've probably won by now.
You think so?
If we won,
then why haven't we been rescued?
First,
they'll figure out
what to do with the prisoners.
And then
there's that whole
post-victory celebration,
Streamers everywhere.
I'm so tired.
You're still losing blood.
I wasn't able to stop it completely.
I'm going to take care of you.
It wasn't them.
I don't know what happened to our man.
But it's not them.
They aren't able
to do that to a person.
Are you telling me
they had nothing to do with this?
What happened?
Overload in the relays
proceeded by temporary disruption
of all shipboard systems,
lights to life support.
How they did that?
They didn't.
- What caused it?
- That's what I'm trying to figure out.
- They're making their move.
- It wouldn't be that obvious.
Would you care to tell me
what's going on?
We don't know.
One of my men is dead.
You need to know
that we had nothing to do with that.
Yes, so I'm told.
I'm going to ask
for a show of good faith.
What do you want?
How are you?
I'm fine.
We're all fine.
What is it that they want?
Some of their people
are injured badly.
I'm going to need medical supplies
to help them.
What's the point?
A goodwill gesture
doesn't have to accomplish anything.
Of course it does!
So they lack medical supplies.
Who knows what else they might lack?
Water?
They'll get desperate,
make their move,
then they'll be dealing
with the hostages.
There's only one way
this is going to end if we wait.
How do you know?
We don't even know
what's going on with the ship!
All the more reason to act now.
Rush is right.
We have to take them down,
and we have to do it right now.