This is what Destiny intended
from the moment it entered the system.
We are going to survive.
We are going to make it home.
The ship came here for a reason.
Destiny is powered
by the stars themselves.
He and Young are bumping heads.
Not sure which camp
is the better choice.
We pretend nothing happened.
We need to be ready
for the next encounter.
For the sake of the crew.
Dad, wait!
The Icarus project is something
your father truly believed in.
A son?
What's his name?
Matthew.
The few times I was conscious,
they were probing my mind.
It's something
I'd rather not think about, really.
There a reason your radio's off?
You couldn't find a broom closet?
What are you doing?
I should go.
What?
Why?
I can't be doing this.
Right.
You say that now that you're done.
You knew what you were getting into.
You know what?
No. Screw that.
I am not going to let you
kick me aside like you did before.
Whatever.
Move.
Me or her.
You can't have both.
I never said I wanted both.
Now, move.
Me or her, Matt...
Get out of my way.
Projet-SG (1.00)
www.projet-sg.com
Start to Dr. Volker.
Anybody in the control interface room?
How about anybody at all?
Anybody?
You okay?
Yeah, the door control doesn't work.
No, you don't have to...
Stupid ship.
Where is everybody?
I don't know.
The room was empty when I got here.
- Can I help you with something?
- What are you doing?
Nothing you need to worry about.
I like to worry.
I was just updating
some personnel files.
In the gateroom.
Colonel Young and Dr. Rush
know all about it,
in case you'd like to talk to them.
I'll do that.
Have you seen Matt?
I have not.
Lieutenant James, come in!
Lieutenant James, this is Colonel Young.
Please respond.
You're late
with the current ammunition count.
Lieutenant, what are you doing?
Nothing, sir.
I'm fine.
I am...
I just lost track of time,
but I'm on my way now.
James out.
So I heard that Colonel Young's
calling off the search for Franklin.
No one was really looking for him.
The man just vanished.
Weird.
Dunning...
Come on.
What the hell?
You okay?
Something weird's going on here.
What is it?
You look tired.
Maybe you should go lie down.
Maybe I will.
Matthew?
Something wrong?
I need to talk to you,
- about something...
- Just the two I need to see.
Am I interrupting something?
- No.
- Good.
I wasn't even in the gateroom today.
He said it was empty?
Only person in the room was Wray,
working at one of the consoles,
updating the files.
Said you told him that Rush
and I knew all about it.
I don't know anything about this.
And I don't know what to tell you,
Colonel, other than he's lying.
He has no reason to lie.
Please.
Sergeant Greer has had it in for us
since the first day
we came aboard this ship.
Correction. Since the day the two of you
led a mutiny to take it over.
I can understand his suspicion.
I was not in the gateroom.
Are you all right?
You didn't pass anyone
in the corridor just now?
Matt, what happened?
We need help in the work-out room!
Anyone from the military,
as many as possible! Now!
Get it out!
Get it out! Get it out!
He thinks a snake is
crawling under his skin.
Get it out!
A snake?
He said it was crawling around
under his skin, but no one saw anything.
He just flipped out.
I can't find anything
physically wrong with him
other than the wounds
that he inflicted on himself.
Have you noticed
any unusual behavior from him lately?
He's been his normal self.
As far as I can tell.
All right, well, let's...
Let's keep him here,
close eye on him
and let me know when he awake.
I want to talk to him.
No warning or anything?
He just went nuts?
Yeah.
Some kind of nervous breakdown.
It was pretty scary.
Tearing gashes in your own arms?
That's intense.
The stress of life on this ship?
Day after day of not knowing
what's ahead?
It's a wonder
more people aren't cracking up.
I'm just glad
he took it out on himself.
And didn't start shooting people.
You all right?
Hello? Earth to Greer?
I'm fine.
I always figured
he'd be the first to snap.
If you want to accuse me
of something, come forward.
No need for spying.
Who you talking to?
Apparently no one.
Help!
Someone help me, please!
Get me out of here!
Wait!
- Where the hell is she?
- I don't know, sir.
I tried to radio her.
She's not responding.
Lieutenant James, come in!
This is Colonel Young.
Please respond.
I'm so sorry.
You can't be real.
Why did you leave me?
Yeah, Colonel, go ahead.
I need you in the infirmary.
- You're alive?
- She thinks she killed you.
How did you...
You were in my room.
You're hallucinating.
Just like Airman Dunning.
- What the hell is going on here?
- We don't know yet.
- I can't find anything wrong.
- I'm seeing things too.
Hallucinations.
My son.
I keep seeing him on the ship.
I just...
I just talked to him.
Your away team.
James and Dunning went off-world
with you to the last planet.
Maybe they picked something up.
We didn't ingest anything that...
It could've been airborne,
any number of possibilities.
Corporal Barnes was
on the away team as well.
So was Dr. Volker.
Help!
Oh, please, somebody help me!
Colonel, we got him.
Nothing?
No weird things
out of the corner of your eye?
Disorientation?
Feeling pretty much
the way I always do.
Hungry, tired,
but I'm not seeing things.
Maybe she's immune to whatever it is
the others picked up.
Maybe her symptoms are just
taking longer to show up.
Thanks.
- But physically, they're okay?
- So far as I can tell, yeah.
No, he's doing fine, but I'm going
to quarantine the entire away team.
Hopefully isolate the hallucinations
until they pass.
What if they don't pass?
What if it gets worse?
I'm sure whatever it is,
TJ'll figure it out.
I mean, she's done
pretty damn good so far.
Is there anything I can do?
No. No, I'll pass the word.
I'll let everyone know what's going on,
but the situation's been contained,
so there's no need
for anybody to get alarmed.
- As soon as I know anything...
- Colonel Young, come in.
Can you come to the infirmary?
I just discovered something.
You see?
So, it's difficult to see,
which is why I missed it
on my initial examination.
You see right there?
Yeah, it looks like a tick.
I checked the others.
They all have one, same spot,
top of the neck there.
All except Corporal Barnes.
She's clear.
Welcome to our new galaxy.
So, the ticks are causing
the hallucinations?
I don't know for sure,
but I think so.
Maybe they inject a venom,
some sort of toxin
that affects the brain's chemistry.
Okay, I want out.
Get me out of here.
- I want out of here, TJ.
- Okay, just relax, okay?
Can you remove it?
They seem similar to Earth ticks.
I could try and remove it
the same way.
You up for going first?
- What happened?
- I don't know. He's crashing.
Let's start CPR.
He's breathing.
He's back.
All right.
Did we get it? We remove it?
It's dug in even deeper.
His pulse is normal.
BP's back in range.
Listen...
Is removing them impossible?
It's just when I tried to pull it off,
it must have released more toxin.
I just have
to figure out another way.
Get to it.
Hello?
Hello, sweetheart.
It's all right.
It's really me.
No, you're...
You're not real.
Oh, God.
No, this isn't happening.
Look at me.
Whether I'm real or not,
aren't you...
at least happy to see your old man?
I have missed you, sweetheart.
I've missed you so much.
- So, where do you want to put 'em?
- If we do this, then we could...
What's going on here?
What do you mean?
- We're just talking.
- About what?
Is something
bothering you, sergeant?
I don't know.
Should there be?
If you've got something to say,
why don't you just
go ahead and say it?
You're not taking over
this ship again.
- We've no intentions of doing so.
- You're being paranoid.
I know you're up to something.
And you have proof of this, do you?
Of course you don't.
Are we done here?
We haven't had any luck yet
figuring out a way home.
God knows if we ever will.
We do have the communication stones.
I was able to use them
to go see mom.
How is she?
Strong.
Fragile.
Doing her best, considering.
She's a fighter.
Like you.
Sometimes I see you in my dreams.
But they always end the same.
I'm trying to get through this,
but it just gets so...
One step at a time.
Look at that view.
God, I've never seen
anything like it.
I always dreamed
that you would live a life of adventure.
- Travel the world.
- I know.
- You told me frequently.
- Well, look at you now.
Sailing through the universe,
exploring galaxies and planets.
You're living my dream, kiddo.
What do you got?
The venom we extracted
from the jungle planet creature.
It worked as an anesthetic
on Rush during his surgery.
I think that if I apply it
topically to the tick...
Knock it out,
give you time to remove it.
That's great.
Oh, he's coming to.
What happened?
You got a jolt
when we tried to remove the tick.
Relax, just relax.
We're going to try
to anaesthetize it,
and then I'll try and see
if I can remove it safely, okay?
Let's just take a look here.
It's gone.
The tick.
It just died off?
I don't know.
- Theirs are both still attached.
- Volker as well.
Could it have jumped?
Yeah, no, I remember.
Gosh, that's so funny,
I feel like that was forever ago.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
- I'm fine.
- Really?
'Cause you don't seem fine.
My father's here.
I mean, I know he's not...
here.
I'm just...
Just...
Hallucinating?
It's really strange.
He's so...
real.
You're seeing him right now?
Where?
Right beside me.
He can't hear you.
We've got to get you to the infirmary,
just have TJ take a look...
No, I already know what's wrong.
There's a tick on me.
Matt and his team picked them up.
- One must have jumped to me somehow...
- Wait a minute, what?
An alien tick?
Are you kidding me?
TJ thinks it might inject
some kind of toxin that causes...
We have to go...
No! No, wait!
It doesn't hurt.
- That's not the point...
- And he's not hurting me either.
He?
You mean your imaginary father?
I'm not crazy.
I know what's going on.
I know that he's not real,
but I can't...
I'm not ready
to lose him again, okay?
You can't let that thing
stay on you.
I know, okay?
I know.
Just...
Humor me, all right?
Give me some time?
I'll go see TJ soon,
I promise,
but for now, just...
don't tell anyone, okay?
Please, Eli.
Okay, Sergeant, I've...
I don't see anything.
You're clear, too.
What happened?
I want you to go back to your quarters,
and stay there until...
- Just a precaution.
- I need to...
Cole can take over for you.
No, Colonel, please, I'm fine.
We'll check ourselves periodically,
and if I start hallucinating...
She was in here earlier.
I'll go find her.
Ready?
Colonel Young, come in.
Colonel Young, do you read?
- Are you okay? I heard you...
- I'm fine.
Have you seen Chloe?
Come with me to the infirmary.
There's a chance
that the tick that was on me
jumped to you.
Have you seen any weird things?
I'm fine...
She's seeing her dad.
We need to get you to the infirmary.
No, I need a little more time...
We can't risk
letting that thing stay on you.
Don't leave me!
I'm not...
Chloe? Come on.
It'll be okay.
Can I help you with
something, Sergeant?
You can start
by wiping that smile off your face.
What smile?
I'd appreciate
you not telling lies about me
to Colonel Young.
Lies.
Telling him I was in the Gateroom,
messing with the consoles.
I don't know what kind of game
you're playing, but...
What are you doing?
There it is.
I don't know
why you have to remove it.
It's not hurting me.
You don't know that.
It's making you hallucinate.
Who knows what else it's doing.
It's too dangerous
to leave in place.
End of the discussion.
Let's remove it.
Tell your mother I love her.
I miss her.
I love you, Daddy.
I love you, too, sweetheart.
You're living our dream.
Remember that.
Colonel Young, come in.
Go ahead, Sergeant.
Colonel Young, we have a problem.
The civilians are trying to take over
the ship again.
What?
I'm pursuing Rush.
He and Wray are trying
to seize control of the ship.
I don't know who is working with them,
but we need to mobilize.
Now.
I need you to listen to me.
Do not do anything. I will talk to them.
Permission to use deadly force.
No, did you hear what I said?
I need you to stand down.
Do not do anything.
Permission granted.
Use whatever force necessary
to stop them.
Copy that.
We don't know if these channels
have been compromised.
Go to radio silence.
Greer, acknowledge.
I said stand down.
You think
he might be hallucinating too?
How?
All the ticks have been accounted for.
Unless there was more than one tick
when you guys got back.
Go find Greer.
We need to examine everyone
on this ship.
Quarantine anyone who's clear.
I know you're in here, Rush.
Show yourself!
What are you doing?
Open that door!
You're not taking over
the ship again.
- Colonel Young, come in.
- Go ahead, Scott.
No sign of Greer.
Still not responding
to any radio calls.
I'll keep at it.
Rush and Wray
are also unaccounted for.
No one knows where they are. Rush isn't
responding to his radio, either.
All right. I'll put
a few more details together.
Excuse me.
I got to go help look for Greer.
You going to be okay?
But if you feel any different,
see anything out of the usual...
No, believe me,
I'm as concerned about this
as you are.
Keep me posted.
More than one tick attached to you
would explain why
some of the hallucinations were more...
intense than others.
The toxins, maybe they target
the limbic system.
It's the area of the brain
that's responsible for
emotion.
Fear, anger, remorse...
Matt's guilt over his son.
Claustrophobia.
My dad.
Let me guess, issue with snakes?
And you?
Listen to me...
I can't stop the bleeding.
You have to open that door.
If I don't get medical attention...
No, sir, I do not know
who else is involved in the mutiny.
She's refusing to cooperate.
You're not talking to anyone.
Your radio is off!
What is the matter with you?
Yes, I will continue
the interrogation,
but at some point, sir,
we are just better off ending this
once and for all.
Sergeant, listen to me.
We are not taking over the ship!
What do you got?
Can't get the door open.
Must have been disabled
from the inside.
I heard Wray's voice.
- It's lieutenant Scott!
- Scott, help!
I'm wounded!
Sergeant Greer has got us hostage.
Shut...
Quiet, now.
Sergeant Greer,
it's lieutenant Scott!
Stand down!
This is Scott, come in.
We found him.
He has locked
with Wray in one of the storage rooms.
I think he's holding her hostage.
That's it.
I'm done with you.
Please.
Sergeant...
Don't.
Do it.
I said
do it.
Colonel Young...
Colonel, we got 'em.
Send TJ.
We have wounded in here.
How you doing?
I was able to stop the bleeding
and stitch the wound,
so we'll keep an eye out
for infection, but...
She should be okay.
- The rest of the crew?
- I checked everyone.
It looks like we got 'em all, so...
Hopefully things will get back
to normal around here.
Whatever that is.
What do we got?
The atmosphere is good.
10 hours on the countdown.
Shall we send a team?
Our luck's got to change
at some point.
Just remember the bug spray.
Scott, this is Young.
Get a team ready.
You're going off-world.