Destiny.
The design is clearly Ancient,
launched hundreds
of thousands of years ago.
Where the hell are we?
Several billion light years
from home.
We are on a ship,
but we have no idea where we are
in relation to Earth.
This ship could be
the most important discovery
mankind has made
since the Stargate itself.
These are the wrong people,
in the wrong place.
We've got a lot of wounded.
We need to get home.
We barely have enough power
to operate the main systems.
This ship simply doesn't have
the capability to dial Earth.
I read about these Chinese miners
that survived a cave-in for six days
by drinking their urine.
I'm gonna go ahead
and pretend I didn't hear.
You know what they ate?
Coal.
- Coal?
- It's a true story.
Don't get me wrong,
it was pretty stupid.
Almost killed them.
Water level's down.
Nobody went near that compartment
on your watch?
Spencer asked
if he could have a look in the tank.
- Why?
- He's a crazy person.
Sir.
I said no.
Nobody goes in there
without my authorization.
Maybe it evaporated
when we went through the star.
- It's a closed system.
- All that water went somewhere.
We're down to half of what we had
when we got here.
I don't understand this.
You're the one trying to get
the recycling system up.
- Maybe there's a leak somewhere.
- Ship says it's fine.
- If what you're saying is accurate...
- It is.
- We've got a serious problem.
- We wouldn't.
- If you did what I asked you to do.
- Can we stick to one problem at a time?
Running out of water wouldn't matter
if we just dial Earth and go home.
- I explained that to you.
- The ship's recharged.
- The power reserves are full.
- That's the point, they're not!
Where are we at?
Probably about less than 40%
of original design capacity.
I can't tell when someone
pulls a number out of his ass?
What?
I actually pulled that number
out of my ass.
He's not making it up.
If Destiny was ever capable
of dialing back to Earth,
it was thousands of years ago,
when the Ancients intended to come here.
But not now.
You're right.
We have a problem.
- Yes.
- Again.
Get Brody in on this.
He's an engineer.
I need to borrow, Eli.
- 40,000 liters?
- That's what I heard.
We didn't drink it.
It wouldn't surprise me
if there was more water
than they're telling us.
They're hoarding it?
It's a big ship.
You know the military.
Long as they control the water supply,
they control us.
Yeah,
I'm talking about you.
Those two are harmless.
Keep it up.
I need to know who I can trust.
I feel like a spy.
Clean this room up.
Right.
Projet-SG (1.00)
- What is it?
- Nothing, sir.
Just had a strange feeling.
- We just dropped out of FTL.
- Wasn't that.
I'm on my way to the gate room.
There's a planet in range.
Come on.
- What have we got?
- There's only one planet in range.
The ship's already dialed it up.
We're getting readings now.
Looks like
we entered the Hoth system.
Empire strikes back.
The second Star Wars movie.
I refuse to call it Episode V.
Minus 47 degrees Celsius.
Bundle up.
Is that water ice?
But the atmosphere
is dangerously thin.
And poisonous.
13% molecular oxygen,
95% carbon dioxide,
with a hint of argon.
Nasty planet.
The only candidate within range.
We're gonna have to use
the spacesuits we found.
But if that brings back
a half a ton of ice, I'll take it.
Shut it down for now.
Lieutenant Scott, come in, please.
There a reason your radio's off?
Come in.
Colonel Young is looking for you.
- I think I'd better...
- Go, go.
What, you couldn't find
a broom closet?
We're still working on the other suits.
We're close to having a third one ready.
- How close?
- A day, maybe?
We'll be back in FTL by then.
Well, they're not in great shape.
All these years,
there's bound to be degradation.
Keep at it,
we're going to need them.
Looks like
it's just you and me, then.
I could take Kennair, sir.
- She's done EVAs before, you're...
- I'm fine.
How are we gonna cut the ice?
Plasma cutter.
Should cut through the ice like butter.
Just don't get the business end
anywhere near you.
Suit radios are voice-activated
between you.
Press here
if you want to tie
into the ship's communication systems.
You're in command while we're gone.
- Is everybody clear on that?
- I'm sure we'll manage.
Start dialing.
Assuming a fair amount
of physical activity,
you have just over eight hours
of air.
It's what, 11 hours
until the next jump to FTL, right?
Don't worry. You'll run out of air
long before we leave you behind.
Thanks.
Beautiful?
One deep breath, and you're dead.
Destiny, this is Young. Come in.
Yes, sir, we hear you five by five.
I've just tested the ice
by the Stargate.
I read concentrations of ammonia
and several other toxic chemicals.
How high are the readings?
Off the charts.
You could try looking
farther afield.
Maybe on the other side
of that lake.
Is that really a good idea?
The further from the gate we go,
the less ice we can bring back.
I've got just the thing.
Give me two minutes.
Colonel, give us five.
Eli has an idea.
Maybe there's fresh water
in the lake under the ice.
At minus 47,
the ice will be 10 feet deep.
We're better off finding
a pressure ridge.
Sounds like
you've done something like this before.
A million times.
Did you feel that?
It's just a tremor.
You know,
the last planet I was on exploded.
Destiny, this is Young.
We're burning through suit air.
What's going on
with this bright idea?
Here we come, people!
Here we come!
Sorry, it's impossible
to steer by remote.
That's fantastic, Eli.
What made you come up with that?
Actually, it represents
my most recent attempt to fly,
but it should carry a ton of ice.
Colonel, we're sending through
Eli's latest invention.
I love it!
The man gets a gold star.
How much will it hold?
More than you can carry by yourself.
All right, we're heading out.
Keep the gate active.
We'll radio back
when we find something.
Sir?
- Listen, if we don't make it back...
- You will.
We're two guys
in million-year-old space suits
walking around alone
on an ice planet.
If we don't make it back...
you're going to do fine.
Yes, sir.
Good luck.
- The level's dropped.
- Again?
Nobody's been in or out.
Brody said there's no leak,
so that leaves one alternative.
- Who could steal that much?
- That's a lot of water.
I know, I don't know what else to do.
It wouldn't hurt to know where we stand.
Start a search.
Let's go, Gorman.
Dial it up again, Mr. Riley.
We must maintain communication.
It just went off a second ago.
Your timing is perfect!
Because it's been 38 minutes,
the maximum time a Stargate
can remain open.
See, I didn't know that.
It's Dr. Rush.
What's your status?
We've found an exposed area
of ice that looks promising.
Testing now.
We're pretty far out.
Can't see the gate anymore.
It's still worthless.
Keep looking.
Go ahead.
I found something.
So did I.
Can it wait?
It's Spencer.
I can deal with him myself
if you'd like, but...
No, it's fine.
I'll be on my way.
I didn't steal anything!
- What's this?
- Those are mine!
I brought them through with me
when we evacuated!
You brought them through with you?
Give me a reason.
Back off!
I don't have time!
Lock him up.
The Colonel can deal with him
when he gets back.
You said you found something.
To be honest,
I don't know what I saw.
I have to talk to Rush.
You keep searching.
Nothing we find is going to add up
to what's missing.
I know,
but we have to know what we've got.
No one's gone near the tank,
and it keeps going down.
Come on, come on...
Destiny.
This is Young.
We got pure ice.
That's excellent news.
It's a frozen waterfall.
We should be able
to break it up into manageable pieces
and haul it back.
We'll be ready for you.
Busy day on Destiny.
I haven't taken anything.
I don't think you have.
What are you doing?
Checking for stolen rations.
It's okay, Dr. Franklin.
Confess, Miss Armstrong.
You drank 40,000 liters of water.
- He's kidding.
- I know.
I'm just saying, we have rights.
I'm done here, Miss Armstrong.
I hope I haven't inconvenienced you.
I understand.
I knew that you would.
You.
Next.
This is never gonna be enough.
Stand back.
- You've done this before, have you?
- At least five times.
You mind if I give it a shot?
Remember,
all we have are the bullets
we brought with us.
So, are we talking about, like,
one little cloud of bugs,
or are they all over the ship?
I'm not even sure that "bugs"
is the right word for them.
- What about "cloud?"
- Except the cloud was alive.
It was almost like
thousands of tiny...
alien creatures.
I have a problem
with everything you just said.
What you've just described is...
it's the same
as Lieutenant Scott claimed he saw
on the desert planet.
That's what I was thinking,
and maybe some of them followed him.
- Wouldn't we have noticed them?
- Not if only a few came
through the gate.
They're like tiny grains of sand.
And then what, started reproducing?
If it's a living organism,
then, they would.
So now we've got aliens.
What if they start bursting out
of our stomachs?
I don't think they're dangerous.
It almost felt like
they were trying to communicate.
Lieutenant Scott used the same word.
- You said he was delirious.
- I was wrong.
What's your plan?
I guess we should stop everyone
from wandering around the ship.
After you.
Here?
This is Lieutenant Johansen.
We have a situation.
It's under control,
but as a precaution,
I ask everyone
to return to their quarters
and remain there until further notice.
Thank you.
You're...
- you're not going to tell them?
- That we've got aliens?
We'll keep it
on a need-to-know basis.
What else?
You're in charge.
And I'm asking your advice.
What else?
Always consider the greater good.
That's it.
That's enough ice for now.
Let's get out of here.
Gorman, meet me in the gate room.
We have ice on the way.
Copy.
They're on it.
Dial it back, please.
Destiny, this is Young.
How's it going up there?
Offloading the sled now.
Hurry it up.
We want to do one more run.
Just so you know,
another matter has come up.
- We have it under control.
- We have aliens on the ship.
What?
They just shredded Gorman.
What the hell does that mean?
Millions of tiny flying razor blades
floating around the ship
like piranha.
Corporal Gorman is alive.
Lieutenant Johansen is tending to him.
He's probably not gonna make it.
- That's it. We're coming back.
- That's not necessary, Colonel.
Eli is overreacting.
We believe the creatures are the same
as those Lieutenant Scott
encountered on the planet.
They must have followed us back
through the gate.
I doubt those things I saw
were dangerous, sir.
They helped me.
Gorman may have provoked them.
- We'll know more once he comes to.
- If he comes to.
In the meantime, Lieutenant Johansen
has ordered everyone
to remain in their quarters.
They're nothing more
than a nuisance at this point,
but we desperately need more ice.
All right.
We'll figure out what to do with them
when we get back.
Sending the sled back through now.
Rush out.
You're gonna have to learn
when to shut up.
You can't just lie to the guy
and expect...
Once back into FTL,
it could be days
before we find another planet
capable of replenishing
our water supplies.
This ice represents a fraction
of what we need to stay alive.
- We need more!
- I know!
- But that doesn't mean you can...
- It does!
- You're making it sound like we're...
- Just stop acting like a child, please!
We have to figure this out.
I said "we."
I say we torch 'em.
You know, put some teams together,
hunt them down.
- Where'd you get that?
- I can invent things too.
- We've really got to work together...
- Maybe the bugs were responding
- out of self-defense.
- Self-defense?
Did you see what they did
to Gorman's face?
I'm the one treating him, Sergeant.
I saw exactly what they did to his face.
Look, we don't know
what it is we're dealing with,
and "torching" them
may only serve
to antagonize them further.
- We hit them with something else.
- Revenge, that's great.
We got to do something.
If we just sit around
till they drink all of our water,
then we're gonna...
Alien bugs show up
and half our water disappears.
Don't tell me
I'm the only one who...
Obviously not. The question is,
what are we gonna do about it?
Sergeant, you and your team
go search for this alien...
entity, cloud, bugs, whatever
it is we're calling them,
- and report back, okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
And Sergeant.
- No torching.
- Yes, ma'am!
I have an idea!
It's gonna be dark soon.
Stand back.
Nothing's happening.
Yes, there is.
It's like vapor.
We just can't see them.
That's what they did when I saw them.
They disappear.
So they're growing
in numbers exponentially,
and consuming our resources
without us even knowing it.
You have to get them off the ship.
Sergeant Greer, come in.
I'm a little busy right now.
The bugs are getting into the water tank
every time we open the hatch.
Once we locate the main swarm,
we're gonna have...
They're in front of me right now.
Don't antagonize them.
I won't,
unless they antagonize me first.
Do they move when you do?
They do now.
What we need is an airlock.
Unfortunately, there are none
in the habitable compartments
of the ship.
I know what to do.
This isn't gonna keep us going
very long.
Maybe Destiny will figure out
we're getting short on water
and find us a planet
with nice fresh water
right next to the Stargate.
Come on, we deserve a break.
Can you hear me?
I'm sorry, sir,
the ice just gave way.
Are you hurt?
Negative. I'm okay, but...
I'm wedged in pretty good.
Good thing, too.
Looks like a long way down.
All right, just hold on.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna throw a line down.
Here it comes.
I need you to tell me
when you've got it.
Got it.
Now, if you can manage it,
run it under both your arms
and fasten it across your chest.
Done this before, too, have you?
At least a dozen times.
Now, I want you to pull yourself up.
I'm gonna pull from this end.
You ready?
One,
two,
three!
Pull!
Pull, Scott!
Come on!
Pull!
How stuck are you?
Pretty dang stuck.
Is there any way
you can dig yourself out?
I'm not sure.
That's okay.
That's passed.
Still here, sir.
All right, let's just...
let's think about this for a second.
Destiny, this is Young.
Go ahead.
We've got a situation here.
There was a tremor and Scott
fell through the snow
into a crevasse.
He's fine,
but he's just out of reach.
I tried to pull him up,
but that's not gonna happen soon.
How's that other space suit coming?
We stopped work on that.
I confined everyone to quarters.
All right, it was just a thought.
We'll figure it out.
How's your bug situation?
Same as before.
Don't worry about it.
Don't you worry either, T.J.
I'll be out of here in no time.
Good luck.
Johansen out.
Everyone is lying.
Grown-ups do that.
This is Greer. It's working.
They're moving away from us
as we move forward.
Good job.
Keep it up.
How about you lower the gun down,
and I shoot myself free?
That's good thinking.
There's no way
the bullets will ricochet into your ass.
Maybe I can cut my way out
with the plasma cutter.
You get one hole in that suit,
you're dead.
Maybe there's a way for me
to get down there.
That's just as stupid.
"That's just as stupid, sir."
The last thing we need is for both of us
to be stuck down here.
You okay?
Closed in a little tighter,
but I think...
What?
I think I'm losing suit pressure.
I thought we were supposed
to be confined to quarters.
I heard over the radio...
there was a tremor.
Lieutenant Scott
fell into a crevasse.
Oh, my god.
He's okay.
Just...
stuck.
- Do they have enough air?
- Young says he's got it under control.
I just...
thought you would want to know.
Thanks.
I think the ice
tore a hole in his suit.
How big a tear is it?
I can't see it,
but I can hear it.
It's hissing out pretty good.
An hour at most.
Plenty of time to make it back.
If I wasn't stuck!
You have to consider the amount of time
you have left now.
I'm aware of the damn time, Rush.
All I'm saying is
if you delay much longer...
Listen to me!
I know what you're saying,
and I'm not going anywhere without him
and that's the way it's going to be!
What's the matter with you?
Miss Armstrong,
- you should return to your quarters.
- You know where you can go?
Look, Colonel,
I understand your desire
to rescue Lieutenant Scott,
of course,
and only you can decide
how much time you have left,
but Lieutenant,
if Colonel Young
remains there,
trying to free you,
to pull you up by himself,
there's a chance
he might not make it back.
He's right.
Just keep the gate active.
We're gonna make it back in time
with your ice,
which is all you really care about.
Young out!
Damn, he's a lot of work.
This is Greer.
I locked them up.
Closing off
the ventilation in that room.
Vents are closed.
Should be airtight.
What are they doing?
Looking for a way out.
Let's hope they don't find one.
Come on!
Come on...
Sir...
I'm thinking.
Go.
It's okay.
No, it's not.
Come on, sir.
We both know
you've done this before, too.
Done what?
Lost people.
Too many times. I'm not...
I'm not doing it again.
I can't let you do it.
You don't have a choice.
Not that I'm counting,
but this is the third time
in almost as many weeks
that you've been willing
to kill yourself,
there's a pretty good chance
at this point
I won't be around
to talk you out of it again.
You're a fine, young Officer.
You've got a heart
as big as a house,
and I'm not here
because I want to die.
I'm here because I haven't given up
on saving your ass,
so just shut up and think.
They're gettin' pissed off.
Really pissed off.
A few of them got out.
What? How?
We need a plan, Lieutenant!
I'm coming down there!
This is beautiful out here.
Wake up, Scott!
Wake up!
I need you to wake up, Scott!
Scott, come on!
Wake up!
Come on!
Come on, I got you.
That's it, pull!
Pull.
Come on, Lieutenant.
That's it.
That's it, I got you.
You're okay.
Scott, come on.
Hang on, kid.
What's the plan?
We open the door,
they go for the water,
we close the lid.
All right, who's gonna do that?
I am.
- I will.
- I'm not the one with the torch.
Look, I am not
going to let you do that...
I haven't killed any of them.
You are.
I'll stand back, torch them.
- I want you out of sight.
- What, you don't trust me?
I don't.
All right.
Eli, I'm ready.
Make us a clear path
to the gate room.
Seal off everything else.
You're good.
If this doesn't work,
lock this compartment off
from the rest of the ship.
Destiny, this is Young.
I'm on my way back with Scott.
Come in.
Let 'em out.
I got 'em!
All right, dial the gate.
We're on our way.
I'm almost at the Stargate
with Scott.
Shut it down so I can...
dial in.
Colonel, we're about to send
these alien bugs through to the planet.
- We've no other choice.
- What?
We need you
to step away from the gate
and remain as still as possible.
They're coming through now.
Get his helmet off.
Give her a hand.
His pulse's thready, but he's breathing.
Let's get him out of here.
Sergeant Spencer,
you step out of line again,
I will deal with you personally.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
I don't think he does.
I need to talk to you
about the behavior of one of yours.
That can wait. We need to go
over the new rationing amounts
I was scheduled to use
the communication stones this morning...
At approximately 03:00 hours
ship time,
Corporal Gorman
succumbed to injuries
sustained in an encounter
with an alien entity.
Lieutenant Johansen
did everything that she could.
I intend to hold appropriate services
tomorrow at 16:00 hours.
How do I turn it off?