Signora, your school offers
a chance for betterment, escape.
My daughter...
Isabella is 17 now,
but what prospects are there
for the daughter of a boat-builder?
There's no future for us.
No future but you.
I am moved by your
concern for your daughter.
I believe protecting the future
of one's own is a sacred duty.
... she is my world.
Then we will take your world.
I knew it!
Say goodbye to your daughter.
Now, signora?
Why wait?
Time ticks.
Be brave, my girl. Make me proud.
Step into the light, my dear.
That's it.
What say you, Francesco?
Do you like her?
Oh, I do, Mother.
I do.
It's me! Hello!
How are you?
The reason for this call is because
I haven't told you for seven hours
that I love you, which is a scandal,
and even if we weren't
getting married tomorrow,
I'd ask you to marry me anyway.
Yes, I would,
because you are smashing.
MUSIC:
"The Stripper" by David Rose
Blimey.
I've...
I'll see you tomorrow.
Out!
Rory!
That's a relief. I thought I'd
burst out of the wrong cake.
Again.
That reminds me, there's a girl
outside in a bikini.
Could someone let her in, give her
a jumper? Lucy. Lovely girl.
Diabetic.
Now, then.
We need to talk about your fiancee.
She tried to kiss me.
Tell you what, though. You're
a lucky man - she's a great kisser.
Funny how you can say something
in your head and it SOUNDS fine...
U-Sub.net et la Allons-y Team
présentent
Docteur Who - Saison 5
Transcript : Red Bee Media Ltd
Synchro : Citrøn, dauphinus, delphiki,
Imaginos, JOJO13, Sargeros
Traduction : Caya, delphiki,
Imaginos, mmime
Relecture : Arno, citrøn, darkevil
Imaginos, Killarney
Oh! The life out there,
it dazzles.
I mean, it blinds you to the things
that are important.
I've seen it devour
relationships and plans.
It's meant to do that.
... because for one person
to have seen all that,
to taste the glory and then go back,
it WILL tear you apart.
So
I'm sending you
somewhere, together.
What, like a date?
Anywhere you want,
any time you want.
One condition- it has to be amazing.
The Moulin Rouge in 1890!
The first Olympic Games!
Think of it as a wedding present,
because it's either this or tokens.
It's a lot to take in?
Tiny box, huge room inside.
What's that about? Let me explain.
It's another dimension.
It's basically another dimen...
What?
After Prisoner Zero,
I've been reading up on all
the latest scientific theories.
FTL travel, parallel universes.
I like the bit when someone says,
"It's bigger on the inside!"
I always look forward to that.
So, this date.
I'm kind of done
with running down corridors.
What do you think?
How about somewhere... romantic?
Venice!
Venezia!
La Serenissima!
Impossible city. Preposterous city!
Founded by refugees running from
Attila the Hun.
It was just a collection
of little wooden huts in the marsh,
but became one of the
most powerful cities in the world.
Constantly being invaded,
constantly flooding...
constantly... Just beautiful!
Oh, you gotta love Venice.
And so many people did.
Byron, Napoleon, Casanova.
That reminds me.
1580, that's all right, Casanova
doesn't get born for 145 years.
Don't want to run into him.
I owe him a chicken.
You owe Casanova a chicken?
Long story. We had a bet.
Papers, if you please.
Proof of residency, current bill
of medical inspection.
There you go, fella.
All to your satisfaction,
I think you'll find.
I am so sorry, Your Holiness.
I didn't realise.
No worries.
You were just doing your job.
Sorry, what exactly is your job?
Checking for aliens.
Visitors from foreign lands what
might bring the plague with them.
Oh, that's nice!
See where you bring me? The plague!
Don't worry, Viscountess.
No, we're under quarantine
here, no-one comes in,
no-one goes out,
and all because of the grace
and wisdom of our patron,
Signora Rosanna Calvierri.
How interesting. I heard
the plague died out years ago.
Not out there.
No, Signora Calvierri has seen it
with her own eyes.
Streets are piled high with bodies,
she said.
Did she, now?
According to this, I am your eunuch!
Oh, yeah, I'll explain later.
Veils down, girls.
It's the Calvierri girls.
- What do you want?
- Where's my Isabella?
What are you doing?
Get away from there.
It's me!
Girls! Come along!
She's gone.
It's me!
What was that about?
I hate it when he does that!
Who were those girls?
I thought everyone knew about
the Calvierri school.
My first day here.
Parents do all sorts of things
to get their children into
good schools.
They move house,
they change religion.
So, why are you
trying to get her out?
Something happens in there.
Something magical,
something evil.
My own daughter didn't recognise me.
And the girl who pushed me away,
her face,
like an animal.
I think it's time I met this
Signora Calvierri.
Mother?
Mummy's hydrating, Francesco.
And we never interrupt Mummy
when she's hydrating.
We were accosted again.
A man made a grab
for one of the girls.
The longer we wait,
the greater the risk of discovery.
We've already converted more than enough.
Surely
It is time to introduce them
to my brothers?
I shall decide when we have enough.
If it's more you want,
let me take the girls into
the city tonight. We could.
We follow the plan.
Let them hammer on our door...
beg to be taken.
And what have you been doing?
Running.
And fighting. I've been scared.
More scared than I thought was...
Did you miss me?
I knew I'd be coming back.
He was right.
It blots out everything else.
Rory... this is our date.
Let's not do this, not now.
We are in Venice
and it's 1580.
I know!
Flowers, signor?
What was that?
She'll be OK.
Where are you... Amy! Come back!
You have my daughter.
Isabella!
You're not coming in, stop there!
- We've told you...
- You have my daughter. Isabella!
I demand you let me see my daughter.
Isabella! It's me! It's your father.
- I'll arrest you...
- Isabella!
Hello, handsome.
Who are you?
How are you doing that?
I... am... loving it.
You're like Houdini, only five
scary girls, only he was shorter.
Will be shorter. I'm rambling.
I'll ask you again, signor.
- Who are you?
- Why don't you check this out?
Library card.
Of course, it's with...
He's... I need the spare.
Pale, creepy girls
who don't like sunlight
and can't be seen in...
Am I thinking what
I think I'm thinking?
But the city.
*Bout à améliorer jusqu'à « Unless », j'ai du mal au moment où elles parlent en même temps que le Doc'*
- Why shut down the city? Unless...
- Leave now, signor.
Or we shall call for the steward...
if you are lucky.
Tell me the whole plan.
One day that'll work.
Listen, I would love to stay here.
This whole thing... I'm thrilled.
This is Christmas!
- I just met some vampires!
- Doctor! We just saw a vampire!
- And creepy girls and everything.
- Vampires!
- We think we just saw a vampire.
- Yeah, yeah, I know.
Amy was just telling me.
The Doctor actually
went to their house.
First we need to
get back in there somehow.
- What?
- How do we do that?
- Back in where?
- Come and meet my new friend.
As you saw, there's no clear way in.
The House of Calvierri
is like a fortress.
But there's a tunnel
underneath it, with a ladder and shaft
that leads up into the house.
I tried to get in once myself,
but I hit a trapdoor.
- You need someone on the inside.
- No.
You don't even know
what I was going to say!
We pretend you're an applicant
for the school to get you inside
and tonight you come down and
open the trapdoor to let us in.
- You know what I was going to say!
- Are you insane?
- We don't have another option.
- He said no, Amy.
- Listen to him.
- There is another option.
I work at the Arsenale.
We build the warships for the navy.
Gunpowder.
Most people just nick stationery
from where they work.
I have a thing about guns and
huge quantities of explosive.
What do you suggest, then? We wait
until they turn her into an animal?
I'll be there three,
four hours tops.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It can't keep happening like this.
This is how they go.
But I have to know. We go together.
Say you're my daughter.
- What? Don't listen to him!
- Your daughter? You look about nine.
- Brother, then.
- Too weird. Fiance.
I'm not having him run around
telling people he's your fiance!
No. No, you're right.
- Thank you.
-  They've already seen the Doctor.
You should do it.
- Me?
- Yeah! You can be my brother.
Why is him being your brother weird,
but with me, it's OK?
-  I thought you were her fiance.
- Yeah, that's not helping.
This whole thing is mental!
- They're vampires, for God's sake.
- We hope.
So if they're not vampires?
Makes you wonder what could be
so bad it doesn't actually
mind us thinking it's a vampire?
*J'arrive pas vraiment à découper a peu près proprement*
So, basically,
both of our parents
are dead from getting the plague.
I'm a gondola... driver...
so...
money's a bit tight...
... so having my sister
go to your school for special people
would be brilliant.
Cheers.
Have we met?
- I've just got one of those faces.
- I wasn't talking to you.
She's got the same face...
which is because she's my sister!
Carlo, explain yourself.
Why have you brought me
this imbecile?
Signora, they have references
from the King of Sweden.
What?
Let me see.
Well, now I can see
what got my steward so excited.
What say you, Francesco?
Do you like her?
I do, Mother.
I do.
Then we would be delighted
to accept her.
Say goodbye to your sister.
Tell Uncle... Doctor...
I'll see you both pretty soon, OK?
I'll be fine.
Amy!
There are clothes on the bed.
Get changed and wait here.
Blimey.
This is private education, then?
Hey. Hello.
I'm Amy.
What's your name?
Isabella.
Listen,
we're going to get you out of here, but
I need you to tell me what's going on.
What is this place?
What are they doing?
They come at night.
They gather around my bed and they
take me to a room...
with this green light
and a chair with...
with straps,
- as if for a surgeon.
- What happens in there?
I wake up here.
And the sunlight
burns my skin like candle wax.
She'll be fine.
You can promise me that, can you?
We're here.
Right. OK, I'll go first. If
anything happens to me, go back...
What happened?
Between you and Amy?
- You said she kissed you.
- Now!
You want to do this Now!
I have a right to know.
I'm getting married in 430 years.
She was frightened,
I was frightened,
but we survived,
and the relief of it...
and so she kissed me.
- And you kissed her back?
- No. I kissed her mouth.
Funny.
Rory... Rory, she kissed me
because I was there.
It would have been you,
it should have been you.
Yeah. Exactly.
That's why I brought you here.
Can we go and see
the vampires now, please?
Control yourself, child.
Get your hands off me.
Psychic paper.
Did you really think
that would work on me?
Push...
Come on. There we are.
Amy!
Where's Amy?
Amy.
I can't see a thing.
Just as well I brought this, then.
Ultraviolet. Portable sunlight.
- Yours is bigger than mine.
- Let's not go there.
Where are you from?
Did you fall through the chasm?
Mother this is pointless.
Let's just start the process.
Hold your tongue, Francesco!
I need to know what this girl is doing
in a world of savages with psychic paper.
Who are you with?
I scarcely believe
your idiot brother sent you.
What are you doing in my school?
OK, I'll tell you.
I'm from Ofsted.
- Put her in the chair.
- No!
Get your hands off me!
Make sport of me, will you?
Tease me as if I were your dog?
This dog has a bite, girl.
Doctor...
If we cancel now, we lose the deposit
on the village hall, the salsa band...
What happened to them?
They've had
all the moisture taken out of them.
Mother...
where you drink from her,
may we share?
I'm so thirsty.
Of course, darling.
That's what vampires do, right?
They drink your blood
and replace it with their own.
Except they haven't just
had their blood taken,
- but all the water in their bodies.
- Why did they die?
Why aren't they like the girls
in the school?
Maybe not everyone
survives the process.
You know what's dangerous about you?
It's not that you make
people take risks.
It's that you make them
want to impress you.
You make it so they don't want to
let you down.
You have no idea how dangerous you make
people to themselves when you're around.
Who are you?
We should run. Run!
This is how it works.
First,
we drink you until you're dry.
Then...we fill you with our blood.
It rages through you like a fire,
changing you,
until one morning you awake
and your humanity is a dream...
now faded.
Or you die.
- That can happen.
- And if I survive?
Then there are 10,000 husbands
waiting for you in the water.
Yeah, sorry.
I'm kind of engaged.
Rory, come on!
Cab for Amy Pond?
She bit me!
This rescue plan, not
exactly watertight, is it?
Rory!
- Amy!
- Quickly, through here!
Seal the house.
They're not vampires!
I saw them, I saw her.
They're not vampires.
They're aliens!
Classic! That's good news?!
What is wrong with you people?!
Come on, move!
Keep moving! Come on, guys.
Quickly. Get out. Quick!
Come on.
Run.
I can't!
- Is he dead?
- No, he's breathing.
And so in memory of the children
lost to the silence,
the traitor is delivered to the arms
of those she betrayed.
Do you expect me to drown?
I'm Venetian!
I can swim!
We can all swim!
Something touched my leg.
They're all around me!
They bite!
Now leave us.
Mother!
Change your form...
or my brothers will think
they are being fed twice today.
Not long now.
It's not long.
Long way from Saturnyne,
aren't you...
Sister of the Water?
No, let me guess.
The owner of the psychic paper.
Then I take it you're a refugee,
like me?
I'll make you a deal.
An answer for an answer.
You're using a perception filter.
It doesn't change your features,
but manipulates the brainwaves
of the person looking at you.
But seeing one of you
for the first time in, say,
a mirror, the brain doesn't know
what to fill the gap with,
leaves it blank...
hence no reflection.
Your question?
Why can we see your big teeth?
Self-preservation over-rides
the mirage.
The subconscious perceives the threat
and tries to alert the conscious brain.
- Where's Isabella?
- My turn.
Where are you from?
Gallifrey.
You should be in a museum.
Or in a mausoleum.
Why are you here?
We ran from the silence.
- Why are you here?
- Wedding present. The silence?
There were cracks.
Some were tiny...
some were as big as the sky.
Through some we saw worlds
and people
and through others we saw silence...
and the end of all things.
We fled to an ocean like ours
and the crack snapped shut
behind us...
and Saturnyne was lost.
So Earth is to become
Saturnyne Mark II?
And you can help me.
We can build a new society here,
as others have.
What do you say?
Where's Isabella?
- Isabella?
- The girl who saved my friend.
Deserters must be executed.
Any general will tell you that.
I need an answer, Doctor.
A partnership.
Any which way you choose.
I don't think that's such a good idea,
do you?
I'm a Time Lord.
You're a big fish.
Think of the children.
Carlo!
You're right.
We're nothing alike.
I will bend the heavens
to save my race,
- while you philosophise.
- This ends today.
I'll tear down
the House of Calvierri,
stone by stone.
Take your hands off me, Carlo.
And you know why?
You didn't know Isabella's name.
Open the gates.
Attend!
The storm is coming!
Mummy...
What's wrong
with your perception filter?
That idiot child must have damaged it
when she kicked me...
Now...
assemble the girls.
I have a job for them.
You're fine.
Open wide.
Come on brain, think, think. Think!
Think!
If they're fish people,
it explains why they hate the sun.
- Stop talking, brain thinking.
- The school thing I don't understand.
- I say we take the fight to them.
What?
Her planet dies,
so they flee through a crack
in space and time, and end up here,
then she closes off the city and,
one by one,
changes people into creatures like her
to start a new gene pool.
Got it. Then what?
They come from the sea,
they can't survive for ever on land,
what's she going to do?
Unless she's going to do something
to the environment
to make the city habitable...
She said, "I shall bend the heavens
to save my race."
Bend the heavens...
Bend...
the heavens...
She's going to sink Venice.
- She's going to sink Venice?
- And repopulate
it with the girls she's transformed.
You can't repopulate somewhere
with just women.
You need... blokes.
- She's got blokes.
- Where?
In the canal. She said, "there are
10,000 husbands waiting in the water."
Only the male offspring survived
the journey here.
She's got 10,000 children swimming
in the canals,
waiting for mum to make
them some compatible girlfriends.
I've been around a bit,
but, really, that's...
The people upstairs are very noisy.
- There aren't any people upstairs.
- I knew you were going to say that.
Did anyone else know
he was going to say that?
Like I said, they're not vampires.
Fish from space.
Aren't we on the second floor?
What's happened to them?
There's nothing left of them.
They've been fully converted.
Blimey, fish from space
have never been so...
buxom.
Move.
Come on.
Give me the lamp.
Go, go, go, guys!
Keep moving, go, go go!
- Stay away from the door, Doctor.
- No! Guido! What are you doing?
I'm not leaving you.
What are you doing?
Come on. That's it...
Come on.
Guido!
We are Venetians!
Right, to begin,
let's fill the sky with fire.
Yes!
In sight of the Lord,
protect and keep us!
Rosanna's initiating
the final phase.
- We need to stop her. Come on!
- No, no. Get back to the TARDIS.
- You can't stop her on your own.
- We don't discuss this!
I tell you to do something, Amy,
and you do it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, my God! What is going on?
The sky, it's like it's boiling.
You're too late.
Such determination...
just to save one city.
Hard to believe it's the same man that let
an entire race
turn to cinders and ash.
Now you can watch
as my people take their new kingdom.
The girls have gone, Rosanna.
You're lying.
Shouldn't I be dead?
Rosanna, please, help me. There
are 200,000 people in this city.
So save them.
Amy, run!
This way, you freak! Don't!
This way, you big,
stupid, great...SpongeBob!
The only thing I've seen
uglier than you is...your mum!
No.
Did you just say
something about Mummy?
Careful!
Hit him!
This way, bring him this way!
Rory!
You stink of fish.
I'm hardly going to smell of
cheese and biscuits!
Hey! Mummy's boy.
That was lucky.
Why did you make the
sign of the cross, you numpty?
Right!
I'm being reviewed now, am I?
Now we go help the Doctor.
Rightio.
Open the gates!
It's the Almighty! Look at the sky!
Get out!
I need to stabilise the storm.
- We're not leaving you.
- Right,
so one minute it's, "You make people
a danger to themselves,"
the next it's, "We're not leaving you!"
But if one of you gets squashed
or blown up or eaten, who gets...
- What was that?
- Nothing.
- Bit of an earthquake.
- Earthquake?
Manipulate the elements, it can trigger
earthquakes. But don't worry about them.
No? No.
Worry about the tidal waves
caused by the earthquake.
Right, Rosanna's throne is the control
hub but she's locked the program,
so tear out every single wire
and circuit in the throne. Go crazy.
Hit it with a stick, anything. We need
it to shut down and re-route control
to the secondary hub, which I'm guessing
will also be the generator.
Shut up! Shut up.
That's better!
There he is!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
You did it!
Rosanna!
One city to save an entire species.
Was that so much to ask?
I told you,
you can't go back and change time.
You mourn but you live.
I know, Rosanna, I did it.
Tell me, Doctor...
can your conscience carry
the weight of another dead race?
Remember us.
Dream of us.
No...
No!
Now, then? What about you two?
Next stop Leadworth Register Office?
Maybe I can give you away.
It's fine.
Drop me back where you found me.
I'll just say you've...
Stay.
With us. Please.
Just for a bit.
I want you to stay.
Fine with me.
Yeah?
- Yes, I would like that.
- Nice one.
I will pop the kettle on.
Hey, look at this.
Got my spaceship, got my boys.
My work here is done.
We are not her boys. Yeah, we are.
Yeah, we are.
Rory, listen to that.
What? All I can hear is...
silence.
There were cracks.
Through some we saw silence
and the end of all things.
Oh, look at you both,
five years later.
Time to sleep.
Or are you waking up?
If you're the Time Lord,
let's call me the Dream Lord.
Two worlds,
here in the time machine...
and there in the village
that time forgot.
One is real...
the other's fake.
Trouble is, Rory, Amy,
which is which?
So here's your challenge.
If you die in the dream,
you wake up in reality. Ask me what
happens if you die in reality?
- What happens?
- You die, stupid.
That's why it's called reality.
Pick a world,
and this nightmare will all be over.
This is going to be a tricky one.