U-Sub.net et la Allons-y Team
présentent :
Doctor Who Saison 5
Transcript : Red Bee Media Ltd
Synchro : Dauphinus, delphiki,
JOJO13 et Sargeros
Traduction : Caya, citrøn,
Mika et G-Lo
Relecture : Arno, G-Lo et Killarney
The Eleventh Hour
Dear Santa, thank you for the dolls
and pencils and the fish.
It's Easter now,
so I hope I didn't wake you.
But honest, it is an emergency.
There's a crack in my wall.
Aunt Sharon says it's
just an ordinary crack, but...
I know it's not, because,
at night, there's voices.
So please, please,
could you send someone to fix it?
Or a policeman. Or...
Back in a moment.
Thank you, Santa.
Can I have an apple?
All I can think about apples.
I love apples.
Maybe I'm having a craving.
That's new,
never had cravings before.
Look at that!
Are you OK?
Just had a fall. All the way down
there, right to the library.
- Hell of a climb back up.
- You're soaking wet.
- I was in the swimming pool.
- You said you were in the library.
So was the swimming pool.
- Are you a policeman?
- Why?
Did you call a policeman?
Did you come
about the crack in my wall?
What cra...?
Are you all right, mister?
No, I'm fine, it's OK.
This is all perfectly norm...
Who are you?
I don't know yet. I'm still cooking.
Does it scare you?
No, it just looks a bit weird.
No, no, no. The crack in your wall.
Does it scare you?
Yes.
Well, then, no time to lose.
I'm the Doctor.
Do everything I tell you,
don't ask stupid questions
and don't wander off.
You all right?
Early days.
Steering's a bit off.
If you're a doctor,
why does your box say Police?
- That's disgusting. What is that?
- An apple.
- Apples are rubbish. I hate apples.
- You said you loved them.
No, no, I love yoghurt. Yoghurt's
my favourite. Give me yoghurt.
I hate yoghurt,
it's just stuff with bits in.
- You said it was your favourite.
- New mouth, new rules.
It's like eating after cleaning your
teeth, everything tastes wro-agh!
What is it? What's wrong with you?
Wrong with me? It's not my fault.
Why can't you give me decent food?
You're Scottish, fry something.
Ah! Bacon!
Bacon. That's bacon.
Are you trying to poison me?
You see, beans.
Beans are evil. Bad, bad beans.
Bread and butter.
Now you're talking.
And stay out!
We've got some carrots.
Carrots? Are you insane?
No, wait, hang on.
I know what I need.
I need... I need... I need...
Fish fingers and custard.
- Funny.
- Am I?
Good. Funny's good.
- What's your name?
- Amelia Pond.
Ah, that's a brilliant name.
Amelia Pond,
like a name in a fairy tale.
Are we in Scotland, Amelia?
No. We had to move to England.
It's rubbish.
So what about your mum and dad,
then?
Are they upstairs?
Thought we'd have woken them by now.
I don't have a mum and dad.
Just an aunt.
- I don't even have an aunt.
- You're lucky.
I know.
So, your aunt.
Where is she?
She's out.
And she left you all alone?
- I'm not scared.
- You're not scared of anything!
Box falls out of the sky, man falls
out of box, man eats fish custard,
and look at you, just sitting there.
- So you know what I think?
- What?
Must be a hell of
a scary crack in your wall.
You've had some cowboys in here.
Not actual cowboys,
though that can happen.
I used to hate apples,
so my mum put faces on them.
She sounds good, your mum.
I'll keep it for later.
This wall is solid and the crack
doesn't go all the way through it.
So here's a thing,
where's the draught coming from?
Wibbly-wobbly, timey-wimey.
You know what the crack is?
What?
It's a crack.
I'll tell you something funny.
If you knocked this wall down,
the crack would stay put,
cos the crack isn't in the wall.
- Where is it, then?
- Everywhere.
In everything. It's a split
in the skin of the world.
Two parts of space and time
that should never have touched,
pressed together...
... right here in the wall
of your bedroom.
- Sometimes, can you hear...
- A voice?
Yes.
Prisoner Zero has escaped.
Prisoner Zero?
That's what I heard.
What does it mean?
Prisoner zero has escaped.
It means that, on the other side
of this wall, there's a prison
and they've lost a prisoner.
Do you know what that means?
- What?
- You need a better wall.
The only way to close the breach
is to open it all the way.
The forces will invert
and it'll snap itself shut.
- Or...
- What?
You know when grown-ups tell you
everything's going to be fine
and you think they're probably lying
to make you feel better?
Yes.
Everything's going to be fine.
Prisoner Zero has escaped.
Hello?
What's that?
There. You see, told you
it would close. Good as new.
What was that thing?
Was that Prisoner Zero?
No. I think
that was Prisoner Zero's guard.
Whatever it was, it sent me
a message. Psychic paper,
takes a lovely little message.
"Prisoner Zero has escaped."
But why tell us?
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless Prisoner Zero
escaped through here.
But he couldn't have.
We'd know.
It's difficult.
Brand-new me, nothing works yet.
But there's something I'm missing...
... in the corner...
... of my eye.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
I've got to get back in there.
The engines are phasing,
it's going to burn!
But...
... it's just a box! How can a box
have engines?
It's not a box. It's a time machine.
What, a real one?
You've got a real time machine?
Not for much longer
if I can't get her stabilised.
Five-minute hop into the future
should do it.
- Can I come?
- Not safe in here, not yet. 5 minutes.
Give me 5 minutes,
I'll be right back.
People always say that.
Am I people?
Do I even look like people?
Trust me. I'm the Doctor.
Geronimo!
Amelia!
Amelia, I worked out what
it was. I know what I was missing!
You've got to get out of there!
Amelia?
Amelia, are you all right?
Are you there?
Prisoner Zero is here.
Prisoner Zero is here! Prisoner Zero
is here! Do you understand me?
Prisoner Zero is...
They all called out at once,
that's what you're saying?
All of them, all the coma patients.
You do understand that these people are
all comatose, don't you?
- They can't speak.
- Yes, Dr Ramsden.
Then why are you wasting my time?
Because they called for you.
Me?
Doctor.
Doctor...
Doctor... Doctor...
White male, mid-20s,
breaking and entering.
Send me some back-up,
I've got him restrained.
You! Sit still.
Cricket bat.
I'm getting cricket bat.
You were breaking and entering.
Well, that's much better. Brand-new me,
whack on the head. Just what it needed.
Do you want to shut up now?
- I've got back-up on the way!
- Hang on, wait you're a policewoman.
And you're breaking.
You see how this works?
But what are you doing here?
Where's Amelia?
Amelia Pond?
Yeah. Little Scottish girl.
Where is she?
I promised her 5 minutes
but the engines were phasing.
I suppose I must have gone
a bit far.
Has something happened to her?
Amelia Pond hasn't
lived here in a long time.
How long?
- Six months.
- No, no, no!
I can't be six months late!
I said five minutes.
I promised.
What happened to her?
What happened to Amelia Pond?
Sarge, it's me again. Hurry it up,
this guy knows something
about Amelia Pond.
I don't think they were conscious.
Dr Ramsden,
there is another sort of funny thing.
Yes, I know.
Dr Carver told me about
your conversation.
We've been very patient with you.
You're a good nurse, but my God!
I've seen them.
These patients are under
24-hour supervision!
There's no possibility
you'd have seen them
wandering in the village!
Why you giving me your phone?!
It's a camera too.
You need to take some time off.
A lot of time off.
Start now.
Now!
I need to speak to whoever lives
in this house now.
- I live here.
- But you're the police.
Yes, and this is where I live.
You got a problem with that?
How many rooms?
- I'm sorry, what?
- How many rooms on this floor?
- Count them for me now.
- Why?
Because it will change your life.
Five.
- One, two, three, four, five.
- Six.
Six?
- Look.
- Where?
Where you don't want to look.
Where you never want to look,
the corner of your eye. Look behind.
That is not possible.
How's that possible?
There's a perception filter round the
door. Sensed it the last time was here.
Should've seen it.
That's a whole room. That's a whole room
I've never even noticed.
The filter stops you.
Something came a while ago to hide.
It's still hiding.
You need to uncuff me now!
I don't have the key. I lost it.
How can you have lost it?
Stay away from that door!
Do not touch that door!
Listen to me! Do not open that...
Why does no-one ever listen to me?
Do I have a face that nobody listens to?
Again...?
My screwdriver, where is it?
Silver thing, blue at the end.
Where did it go?
There's nothing here.
There stopped you seeing the room.
What makes you think you could see it?
Now. Please, just get out!
- Silver, blue at the end?
- My screwdriver, yeah.
It's here.
Must have rolled under the door.
Yeah.
Must have.
And then it must have jumped up
on the table...
Get out of there.
Get out of there!
Get out!
What is it? What are you doing?
There's nothing here, but...
Corner of your eye.
What is it?
If it knows you've seen it,
it will kill you.
Don't look at it.
Do not...
look.
Get out!
Give me that!
What's the bad alien done to you?
- Will that door hold it?
- Oh, yeah, course!
It's an inter-dimensional multi-form
from outer-space, they're all terrified
of wood.
What's that? What's it doing?
I don't know, getting dressed?
Run.
Your back-up's coming, I'll be fine.
There is no back-up.
I heard you on the radio,
ou called for back-up.
- It's a pretend radio.
- You're a policewoman.
I'm a kissogram!
- But it's just...
- No, it isn't.
Look at the faces.
What?
I'm sorry, but what?
It's all on one.
One creature disguised as two.
Clever old multi-form.
A rush job, though.
Got the voice a bit muddled, did you?
Mind you, where did you get
the pattern from? You'd need a
psychic link, a live feed.
How did you fix that?
Stay, boy!
Her and me, we're safe.
Want to know why?
- She sent for back-up.
- I didn't send for back-up!
I know, that was a clever lie
to save our lives. OK, yeah, No back-up!
And that's why we're safe. Alone,
we're not a threat to you. If we had
back-up, you'd have to kill us!
'Attention, Prisoner Zero.
The human residence is surrounded.
Attention Prisoner Zero.
What's that?
That would be back-up.
One more time. We do have back-up
and that's definitely why we're safe.
Prisoner Zero will vacate
the human residence
or the human residence
will be incinerated.'
Safe apart from, you know,
incineration.
Prisoner Zero will vacate
the human residence
or the human residence
will be incinerated.
Prisoner Zero will vacate
the human residence
or the human residence
will be incinerated.
Run.
- Kissogram?
- Yes a kissograme!
- Why'd you pretend to be a policewoman?
- You broke into my house!
It was this or a French maid!
What's going on? Tell me!
Tell me!
An alien convict is hiding in your spare
room disguised as a man and a dog,
and some other aliens are about
to incinerate your house. Any questions?
- Yes.
- Me too.
Don't do that, not now! It's still
rebuilding, not letting us in!
Come on.
No, wait, hang on, wait.
The shed.
I destroyed that shed
last time I was here,
smashed it to pieces.
- There's a new one.
- But the new one's got old.
It's ten years old at least.
12 years. I'm not six months late,
I'm 12 years late.
- He's coming.
- You said six months.
- Why did you say 6 months?
- We've got to go.
This matters. This is important.
Why did you say six months?
Why did you say five minutes?
What?
Come on.
- What?
- Come on!
What?
- You're Amelia.
- You're late.
- Amelia Pond, you're the little girl.
- I'm Amelia
- you're late. 12 years.
- What happened?
- You hit me with a cricket bat.
- 12 years.
- A cricket bat.
- 12 years and four psychiatrists.
Four?
- I kept biting them.
- Why?
They said you weren't real.
No, come on.
What?
We're being staked out by
an ice-cream van?
What's that?
Why are you playing that?
It's supposed to be Claire De Lune.
Doctor, what's happening?
Hello!
Sorry to burst in, we're doing a special
on television faults in this area.
Also, crimes.
Let's have a look.
- I was just about to phone.
- It's on every channel.
Hello, Amy, dear.
Are you a policewoman now?
Well, sometimes.
I thought you were a nurse.
I can be a nurse.
Or, actually, a nun.
I dabble.
Amy,
who is your friend?
Who's Amy? You were Amelia.
- Yeah, now I'm Amy.
- Amelia Pond,
that was a great name.
Bit fairy tale.
I know you,
don't I?
I've seen you somewhere before.
Not me. Brand-new face...
First time on.
And what sort of job's a kissogram?
I go to parties and I kiss people.
With outfits. It's a laugh.
You were a little
girl five minutes ago.
- You're worse than my aunt.
- I'm the Doctor,
I'm worse than everybody's aunt.
And that is not how
I'm introducing myself.
So it's everywhere,
in every language.
They're broadcasting
to the whole world.
What's up there,
what are you looking for?
Planet this size, two poles,
your basic molten core...
they're going to need
a 40% fission blast.
But they'll have to power up first,
won't they?
So assuming a medium-sized starship,
that's 20 minutes.
What do you think, 20 minutes?
20 minutes.
We've got 20 minutes.
20 minutes to what?
Are you the Doctor?
He is, isn't he?
He's the Doctor!
The Raggedy Doctor. All those cartoons
you did, when you were little.
The Raggedy Doctor, it's him.
Cartoons?
Gran, it's him, isn't it?
- It's really him!
- Jeff, shut up! 20 minutes to what?
The human residence. They're not talking
about your house, they're talking about
the planet.
Somewhere up there, there's a spaceship.
And it's going to incinerate
the planet.
20 minutes to the end of the world.
- What is this place? Where am I?
- Leadworth.
- Where's the rest of it?
- This is it.
- Is there an airport?
- No.
A nuclear power station?
Even a little one?
- Nearest city?
- Gloucester, half an hour by car.
Do we have a car?
Well, that's good! Fantastic,
that is 20 minutes to save the world
and I've got a post office.
And it's shut!
What is that?
It's a duck pond.
- Why aren't there any ducks?
- I don't know. There's never any ducks.
- Then how do you know it's a duck pond?
- It just is. Is it important,
- the duck pond?
- I don't know. Why would I know?
This is too soon.
I'm not ready, I'm not done yet.
What's happening?
Why's it going dark?
- What's wrong with the sun?
- Nothing.
You're looking at it
through a force-field.
They've sealed off
your upper atmosphere,
now they're getting
ready to boil the planet.
And here they come.
The human race.
The end comes,
as it was always going to, down
a video phone!
This isn't real, is it?
This is some kind of big wind-up.
- Why would I wind you up?
- You told me you had a time machine.
- And you believed me.
- Then I grew up.
You never want to do that.
Hang on,
shut up, wait!
I missed it.
I saw it and I missed it.
What did I see?
I saw, what did I see?
20 minutes.
I can do it.
20 minutes, the planet burns.
Run to your loved ones and say goodbye,
or stay and help me.
I'm sorry?
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
- Who are you?
- You know.
No, really, who are you?
- End of the world, 20 minutes.
- Better talk quickly, then!
- I am going to need my car back.
- Yes, in a bit. Now go and have coffee.
Right, yes.
Catch.
I'm the Doctor.
I'm a time traveller.
Everything I told you
12 years ago is true.
I'm real.
What's happening in the sky is real,
and if you don't let me go now,
everything you've ever known is over.
I don't believe you.
Just...
20 minutes.
Just believe me for 20 minutes.
Look at it.
Fresh as the day you gave it to me.
And you know it's the same one.
Amy.
Believe for 20 minutes.
- What do we do?
- Stop that nurse!
The sun's going out, and you're
photographing a man and a dog. Why?
- Amy?
- Hi!
- This is Rory, he's a... friend.
- Boyfriend.
- Kind of boyfriend.
- Man and dog, why?
- Oh, my God, it's him.
- Just answer his question, please.
It's him, though.
The Raggedy Doctor.
He came back.
- But he was a story. He was a game.
- Man and dog. Why?
- Tell me now.
- Sorry. Because he can't be there.
- He's in a hospital, in a coma.
Knew it. Multi-form, you see?
Disguise itself as anything,
but it needs a life feed, a psychic link
with a living but dormant mind.
Prisoner Zero.
- What, there's a Prisoner Zero too?
- Yes.
That ship up there is scanning this area
for non-terrestrial technology.
And nothing
says non-terrestrial
like a sonic screwdriver.
Oi, come back here! Come back!
I think someone's going to notice!
Don't you?
No, no, no, don't do that!
- Look, it's going.
- No, come back, he's here!
Come back! He's here,
Prisoner Zero is here.
Come back,
he's here! Prisoner Zero is...
Doctor!
The drain. It just sort of melted
and went down the drain.
- Well, of course it did.
- What do we do now?
It's hiding in human form.
We need to drive it into the open.
No TARDIS, no screwdriver, 17 minutes.
Come on.
Think. Think.
Barney?
Barney? Can you hear me, Barney?
That thing, that hid
in my house for 12 years?
Multi-forms can live for millennia.
12 years is a pit-stop.
How come you show up
on the same day that lot do?
They're looking for him, but followed
me. They saw me through the crack,
got a fix. They're only late cos I am.
Give me your phone.
- How can he be real? He was never real.
- Phone, now, give me!
He was just a game, we were kids.
You made me dress up as him.
These photos,
they're all the coma patients?
No, they're all the multi-form.
8 comas, 8 disguises for Prisoner Zero.
He had a dog.
There's a dog in a coma?
The coma patient dreams he's walking a
dog, Prisoner Zero gets a dog. Laptop!
Your friend, what was his name?
Not him, the good-looking one.
- Jeff.
- Thanks.
He had a laptop in his bag, a laptop.
Big bag, big laptop.
I need Jeff's laptop. You two,
get to the hospital, get everyone out,
clear the whole floor.
Phone me when you're done.
Your car, come on.
But how can he be here?
How can the Doctor be here?
Hello, laptop, give me!
- No, no, no, no, wait, hang on!
- It's fine, give it here.
Blimey! Get a girlfriend, Jeff.
- Gran.
- What are you doing?
The sun's gone wibbly, out there,
there's going to be a big
video conference call.
All the experts in the world panicking
at once, and do you know what they need?
Me. And here they all are.
All the big boys. NASA,
Jodrell Bank, Tokyo Space Centre,
Patrick Moore
- I like Patrick Moore.
- I'll get you his number,
- but watch him, he's a devil.
- You can't just hack in on a call.
- Can't I?
- Who are you?
This is a secure call,
what are you doing?
I know, you should switch me off.
But before you do, watch this.
- It's here too, I'm getting it.
- Fermat's Theorem, the proof,
and I mean the real one,
never seen before.
Poor old Fermat, got killed in a duel
before he could write it down.
My fault, I slept in.
And here's an oldie but a goodie
why electrons have mass.
And a personal favourite of mine,
faster-than-light travel
with two diagrams and a joke.
Look at your screens. Whoever I am,
I'm a genius. Look at the sun.
You need all the help you can get.
Fellas, pay attention.
- Sir, what are you doing?
- I'm writing a computer virus.
Very clever, super-fast,
and a tiny bit alive, but don't let on.
Why am I writing it on a phone?
Never mind, you'll find out.
OK, I'm sending this
to all your computers.
Get everyone who works for you
sending this everywhere.
Email, text, Facebook, Bebo,
Twitter, radar dish,
Whatever you've got. Any questions?
- Who was your lady friend?
- Patrick, behave!
- What does this virus do?
- It's a reset command, that's all.
It resets counters, it gets in the WiFi
and resets every counter.
Clocks, calendars, anything with a chip
will default at 0 at the same time.
But, yeah, I could be lying,
why should you trust me?
I'll let my best man explain.
Jeff, you're my best man.
You what?
Listen to me. In ten minutes,
you're going to be a legend.
Everyone on that screen is going
to be offering you any job you want.
But first, you have
to be magnificent.
You have to make them trust you
and get them working.
This is it, Jeff.
Right here, right now.
This is when you fly.
Today's the day you save the world.
- Why me?
- It's your bedroom.
Now go, go, go.
OK, guys,
let's do this.
And delete your internet history.
Something's happened up there,
we can't get through.
Yes, but what's happened?
I don't know. No-one knows.
- Phone him.
- I'm phoning him.
Doctor? We're at the hospital,
but we can't get through.
- What did he say?
- Look in the mirror.
Uniform!
Are you on your way?
You're gonna need a car.
Don't worry.
I've commandeered a vehicle.
Officer.
- What happened?
- There was a man. A man with a dog.
I think Dr Ramsden's dead
and the nurses.
- Are you in?
- Yep.
- But so's Prisoner Zero.
- You need to get out of there.
He was so angry. He kept shouting.
And that dog,
the size of that dog,
I swear it was rabid.
And he just went mad,
attacking everyone.
Where did he go, did you see?
Has he gone? We hid in the ladies.
Oh, I'm getting it wrong again,
aren't I? I'm always doing that.
So many mouths.
Oh, my God!
Amy? Amy, what's happening?
Amy, talk to me!
We're in the coma ward.
But it's here, it's getting in.
- Which window are you?
- What, sorry?
- Which window?
- First floor on the left,
fourth from the end.
Oh, dear. Little Amelia Pond.
I've watched you grow up.
12 years, and you never even
knew I was there.
Little Amelia Pond,
waiting for her magic Doctor
to return
but not this time, Amelia.
Right! Hello! Am I late? No,
three minutes to go.
There's still time.
Time for what, Time Lord?
Take the disguise off.
They'll find you in a heartbeat.
- Nobody dies.
- The Atraxi will kill me this time.
If I am to die,
let there be fire.
OK. You came to this world by
opening a crack in space and time.
Do it again.
Just leave.
- I did not open the crack.
- Somebody did.
The cracks in the skin
of the universe
don't you know where they came from?
You don't, do you?
The Doctor
in the TARDIS doesn't know.
Doesn't know, doesn't know!
The universe is cracked.
The Pandorica will open.
Silence will fall.
And we're off!
Look at that.
Look
at that!
I know, just a clock, whatever. But
do you know what's happening right now?
In one little bedroom,
my team are working.
Jeff and the world. And do you
know what they're doing?
They're spreading the word
all over the world, quantum fast.
The word is out.
And do you know what the word is?
The word is zero.
Now, me, if I was up
in the sky in a battleship,
monitoring all Earth communications,
I'd take that as a hint.
And if I had a whole battle fleet
surrounding the planet,
I'd be able track a simple old
computer virus to its source in,
what, under a minute?
The source, by the way,
is right here.
And I think they just found us!
The Atraxi are limited.
While I'm in this form, they'll
still be unable to detect me.
They've tracked a phone, not me.
But this is the good bit.
I mean, this is my favourite bit.
Do you know
what this phone is full of?
Pictures of you.
Every form you've learned to take,
right here.
And being uploaded about now.
And the final score is no TARDIS,
no screwdriver two minutes to spare.
Who da man?
I'm never saying that again! Fine.
Then I shall take a new form.
Stop it, you know you can't.
Takes months to form that
kind of psychic link.
And I've had years.
No!
Amy?
You've got to hold on. Amy!
Don't sleep!
- You've got to stay awake, please.
- Doctor?
That's rubbish.
Who's that supposed to be?
- It's you.
- Me?
Is that what I look like?
- You don't know?
- Busy day.
Why me, though?
You're linked with her.
Why are you copying me?
I'm not.
Poor Amy Pond.
Still such a child inside.
Dreaming of the magic Doctor
she knows will return to save her.
What a disappointment you've been.
No, she's dreaming about me
cos she can hear me.
Amy, don't just hear me, listen.
Remember the room in your house
you couldn't see?
Remember you went inside.
I tried to stop, but you did.
You went in the room.
You went inside.
Dream about what you saw.
Well done, Prisoner Zero.
A perfect impersonation of yourself.
Prisoner Zero is located.
Prisoner Zero is restrained.
Silence, Doctor.
Silence will fall.
The sun, it's back to normal, right?
That's good, yeah?
That means it's over.
- You OK? Are you with us?
- What happened?
- He did it. The Doctor did it.
- No, I didn't.
- What you doing?
- Tracking the signal back.
Sorry, in advance.
For what?
The bill.
I didn't say you could go!
Article 57 of the Shadow Proclamation.
This is a
fully established, level 5 planet,
and you were going to burn it?
What?
Did you think no-one was watching?
You lot, back here. Now!
Now I've done it.
Did he just bring them back?
Did he just save the world
from aliens
and then bring all the aliens
back again?
- Where are you going?
- The roof.
No, hang on.
- What's in here?
- I'm saving the world.
I need a decent shirt.
To hell with the raggedy.
Time to put on a show!
You just summoned aliens back
to earth.
Actual aliens, deadly aliens,
aliens of death,
and now you're taking
your clothes off...
- Amy, he's taking his clothes off.
- Turn your back if it embarrasses you.
Are you stealing clothes now?
Those clothes belong to people,
you know.
Are you not you going
to turn your back?
Nope.
So this was a good idea,
was it? They were leaving.
Leaving is good.
Never coming back is better.
Come on, then!
The Doctor will see you now.
You
are not of this world.
No,
but I've put a lot of work into it.
I don't know.
What do you think?
Is this world important?
Important?
What's that mean, important?
6 billion people live here,
is that important?
Here's a better question.
Is this world a threat to the Atraxi?
You're monitoring the whole planet.
Is this world a threat?
Are the peoples
of this world guilty of any crime
by the laws of the Atraxi?
One more. Just one.
Is this world protected?
'cause you're not the first lot to
come here. Oh, there have been so many!
And what you've got to ask is...
... what happened to them?
Hello.
I'm the Doctor.
Basically...
... run!
Is that it?
Is that them gone for good?
Who were they?
What have you got for me this time?
Look at you!
Oh, you sexy thing!
Sorry about running off earlier.
Brand-new TARDIS, bit exciting.
Just had a quick hop to the moon
and back to run her in.
She's ready for the big stuff now.
It's you.
You came back.
Course I came back.
I always come back.
Something wrong with that?
And you kept the clothes.
Well, I just saved the world,
the whole planet, for about the million
time, no charge. Yes, shoot me!
I kept the clothes.
Including the bow tie.
It's cool. Bow ties are cool.
Are you from another planet?
- What do you think?
- Of what?
Other planets.
Want to check some out?
- What does that mean?
- It means...
it means...
come with me.
Where?
Wherever you like.
All that stuff, the hospital,
the spaceships, Prisoner Zero...
That's just the beginning.
There's loads more.
But those things those,
amazing things, all that stuff...
That was two years ago!
- So that's...
- 14 years!
14 years since fish custard.
Amy Pond, the girl who waited,
you've waited long enough.
When I was a kid,
you said there was a swimming pool
and a library, and the swimming
pool was in the library.
Not sure where it's got to now.
It'll turn up. Coming?
- You wanted to come 14 years ago.
- I grew up.
Don't worry.
I'll soon fix that.
Anything you want to say?
Any passing remarks?
I've heard them all.
I'm in my nightie.
Don't worry.
Plenty of clothes in the wardrobe.
And
possibly a swimming pool.
All of time and space,
everything that ever happened
or ever will...
Where do you want to start?
You are so sure that I'm coming.
- Yeah, I am.
- Why?
'cause you're the Scottish girl
in the English village,
- and I know how that feels.
- Do you?
All these years living here,
most of your life...
you've still got that accent.
Yes, you're coming.
- Can you get me back for tomorrow?
- It's a time machine.
I can get you back five minutes ago.
Why, what's tomorrow?
Nothing.
Nothing. Just you know, stuff.
All right, then.
Back in time for stuff.
A new one!
Lovely.
Thanks dear.
- Why me?
- Why not?
No, seriously?
You are asking me to run away
with you in the middle of the night.
It's a fair question. Why me?
I don't know. Fun.
Do I have to have a reason?
- People always have a reason.
- Do I look like people?
Been knocking around on
my own for a while, my choice,
but I've started talking to myself.
It's giving me earache.
You're lonely. That's it?
Just that?
Just that.
Promise.
So, are you OK, then?
'cause this place, sometimes it
can make people feel a bit...
- you know?
- I'm fine. It's just...
There's a whole world in here,
just like you said. It's all true.
I thought, I started to think
that maybe you were just like
a madman with a box.
There's something you'd better
understand aboute me. It's important,
your life may depend on it.
I am definitely a madman with a box.
Goodbye, Leadworth.
Hello, everything!
My name's Amy Pond.
When I was seven,
I had an imaginary friend.
Last night was
the night before my wedding
and my imaginary friend came back.
All of time and space,
everything that ever happened,
or ever will...
Where do you want to start?
Anywhere you want,
any time you want.
One condition...
it has to be amazing.
Now it starts.
You might want to find something
to hang on to.
It begins.
Tell me the whole plan.
One day, that'll work.
One simple instruction,
don't follow me
under any circumstances.
Will you follow him?
Of course.
'cause this is what I do
every time, every day, every second.
This...
Hold tight.
Because it will change your life.
There's one thing you never
put in a trap if you're smart,
if you value your continued existence,
if you have any plans about
seeing tomorrow, there's one thing
you never, ever put in trouble...
... me!