I'm going to die.
And I was told,
'"He will knock four times."'
What is it? What's inside your head?
It's real!
The darkness heralds only one thing.
The end of time itself.
My head!
Oh, my head!
If she ever remembers me,
her mind will burn and she will die.
What have you done, you monster?
And so it came to pass,
on Christmas Day,
that the human race
did cease to exist.
This day
was the day upon
which the whole creation
would change forever.
This was the day
the Time Lords returned.
Doctor Who - Special New Year 2010
The End Of Time (Part 2)
Transcript: bean
Subtitles: -Ori-, Grîshnak, LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
What news of the Doctor?
Disappeared,
my Lord President.
But we know his intention.
He still possesses the Moment.
And he'll use it, to destroy Daleks
and Time Lords alike.
The Visionary confirms it.
Ending, burning,
falling, all of it falling,
the black and pitch
and screaming fire
so burning.
All of her prophecies say the same.
That this is the last day
of the Time War.
That Gallifrey falls.
That we die,
today.
Ending, ending, ending.
Ending!
Perhaps it's time.
This is only the furthest edge
of the Time War.
But at its heart,
millions die every second.
Lost in bloodlust and insanity.
With time itself resurrecting them,
to find new ways of dying,
over and over again,
a travesty of life.
Isn't it better to end it,
- At last?
- Thank you for your opinion.
I will not die!
Do you hear me?
A billion years of Time Lord history
riding on our backs.
I will not let this perish.
I will not!
There is...
There is one part
of the prophecy, my Lord.
Forgive me...
I'm sorry.
It's rather difficult
to decipher, but...
it talks of two survivors,
beyond the Final Day.
Two children of Gallifrey.
Does it name them?
It foresees them locked in
their final confrontation,
The Enmity of Ages,
which would suggest...
The Doctor!
And the Master.
One word keeps being repeated,
my Lord.
One constant word.
- Earth.
- Earth, Earth.
Earth, earth, earth, ...
Planet Earth.
Indigenous species, the human race.
Maybe that's where the answer lies.
Our salvation.
On Earth.
Now, then. I've got a planet to run.
Is everybody ready?
6 billion, 7 hundred and 27 million,
9 hundred and 49 thousand
300 and 38 versions of us
awaiting orders.
This is Washington.
As President of the United States,
I can transfer
all the United Nations protocols
to you immediately,
putting you in charge
of all the Earth's defences.
UNIT HQ, Geneva reporting.
All under your command, sir.
This is the Central Military Commission
here in Beijing, sir.
With over 2.5 million soldiers.
Sir!
Present arms!
Enough soldiers and weapons
to turn this planet into a warship.
Nothing to say?
What's that? Pardon?
- Sorry?
- You let him go, you swine.
Your dad's still kicking up a fuss.
- I'd be proud if I was.
- Hush, now.
Listen to your Master.
That's a mobile.
- It's mine, let me turn it off.
- I don't think you understand.
Everybody on this planet... is me.
And I'm not phoning you,
so who the hell is that?
It's nobody.
Probably some ring-back call.
And look at this. Good man!
- Who's Donna?
- She's no-one, just leave it.
Gramps. Don't hang up,
you've got to help me.
I ran out...
but everyone was changing.
Who is she? Why didn't she change?
It was this thing the Doctor did...
He did it to her. The Metacrisis.
He loves playing with Earth girls.
- Oh.
- Are you there?
Find her. Trace the call.
Trace the call.
Are you still there?
- Can you hear me?
- Say goodbye to the freak, Grandad.
Donna, get out of there!
Just get out. Run!
She's on Wessex Lane, Chiswick.
Open the phone lines.
Everyone on Wessex Lane.
Red alert.
-  What do I do?
- Run, that's all.
Run for your life!
- There's more of them.
- What's happening?
- Are you still there?
- They're everywhere...
I'm starving.
I'm telling you. Run, Donna!
- I'm still hungry!
- Just run, sweetheart.
Just run!
It's not just them...
I can see those things again.
Those creatures.
Why can I see a giant wasp?
Don't think about that,
Donna, my love...
And it hurts.
My head.
It keeps getting hotter.
And hotter!
And hotter. And hotter. And hotter!
What did I...?
What was that?
Donna, are you there?
That's better. Hello.
But really,
did you think I'd leave my best friend
without a defence mechanism?
- What happened?
- She's all right. I promise.
She'll just sleep.
Tell me...
Where's your TARDIS?
You could be so wonderful.
- Where is it?
- You're a genius.
You're stone-cold brilliant.
You are, I swear, you really are.
But you could be so much more.
You could be beautiful.
With a mind like that,
we could travel the stars.
It would be my honour.
Because you don't need
to own the universe. Just see it.
To have the privilege of seeing
the whole of time and space...
that's ownership enough.
Would it stop, then?
The noise in my head?
I can help.
I don't know
what I'd be without that noise.
Wonder what I'd be, without you.
What does he mean? What noise?
It began on Gallifrey.
As children.
Not that you'd call it childhood.
More a life of... duty.
Eight years old.
I was taken for initiation.
To stare into the Untempered Schism.
- What does that mean?
- It's a gap in the fabric of reality.
You can see into
the Time Vortex itself.
And it hurts.
They took me there.
In the dark.
I looked into time, old man.
And I heard it.
Calling to me.
Drums...
The never-ending drums.
The Untempered Schism.
That's when it began.
History says
the Master heard a rhythm.
A torment that stayed with him
for the rest of his life.
A drumbeat. A warrior's march.
A symptom of insanity, my Lord.
A rhythm of four!
The heartbeat of a Time Lord.
Listen to it.
Listen.
Then let's find it.
You and me.
Except...
Wait a minute.
That's good.
- What is?
- The noise exists within my head.
And now within six billion heads.
Everyone on Earth can hear it.
Imagine!
Oh yes!
The Gate wasn't enough.
You're still dying.
This body was born out of death.
All it can do is die.
But what did you say to me,
back in the wasteland?
You said, "The end of time."
I said something is returning.
I was shown a prophecy.
- That's why I need your help.
- What if I'm part of it?
Don't you see?
The drumbeat is calling
from so far away.
From the end of time itself.
And now it's been amplified
six billion times.
Triangulate all those signals.
I could find its source!
That's what your prophecy was.
Me!
- Where's the TARDIS?
- Just stop.
- Just think.
- Kill him.
I need that technology, Doctor.
Tell me where it is, or he's dead.
- Don't tell him.
- I'll kill him, right now!
Actually,
the most impressive thing about you
is that after all this time,
you're still bone-dead stupid.
- Take aim.
- You've got six billion pairs of eyes,
but you still can't see the obvious,
can you?
Like what?
That guard is one inch too tall.
Oh my God, I hit him.
I've never hit anyone in my life.
Come on!
We need to get out of here, fast.
- God bless the cactuses!
- That's CACTI.
That's racist!
This prophecy of yours, Doctor...
where did it come from?
Come on!
- We've got to get out.
- There's too many buckles and straps.
Wheel him.
Get me out.
Don't... Don't!
What's going on?
- Which way?
- This way.
- The other way! I've got my TARDIS.
- I know what I'm doing.
Listen to me!
Find him. Find him!
Not the stairs...
Not the stairs!
Worst... rescue... ever!
- Underneath the Gate Room, sir.
- Basement. Get him.
Yes, sir.
Stop, and listen to me!
- Gotcha.
- You think so?
Don't, don't!
Now get me out of this thing!
Don't say thanks, will you?
He's not going to let us go.
Just hurry up and get me out!
My goodness me...
We're in space!
- Come on!
- All right!
Get a move on!
Open the teleport and follow him!
- Come on!
- All right!
He's still up there.
Target practice.
- Where's your flight deck?
- We're safe!
We're a hundred thousand miles
above the Earth.
And he's got every single missile
on the planet ready to fire!
Good point.
But we're in space!
Turn everything you've got to the skies.
Find me that ship.
- And prime the missiles.
- Open up the radar, maximum scan.
- We've got to close it down!
- No chance, mate, we're going home.
We're a salvage team.
Local politics has nothing to do with us
Not unless there's a carnival.
Sooner we get back
to Vinvocci space the better.
You're not leaving.
Anything?
I'm sorry, sir. Nothing.
Lost him.
What about teleport coordinates?
I need that information.
He's cut the link, sir.
No trace, all dead.
Still...
Open fire!
No way back now.
He's stranded.
No sign of any missiles...
No sign of... anything.
You've wrecked the place!
The engines are burnt out.
Just auxiliary lights.
Everything else is kaput.
We can't move.
We're stuck, in orbit.
Thanks to you. You idiot!
I know you, though. I bet
you've got a plan, haven't you?
Come on.
You've always got
a trick up your sleeve.
Nice little bit of the old Doctor.
Sort of thing?
Oh, blimey.
Night has fallen.
Are we ready?
Every single one of us is prepared.
Then we listen.
All of us.
Across the world.
Listen.
Concentrate.
Find the signal.
There.
The sound is tangible.
Someone could only
have designed this.
But who?
The signal has been sent.
A simple task of four beats
Transmitted back through time,
and implanted
in the Master's mind as a child.
Then we have a link
to where the Master is right now.
But we're still trapped
inside the Timelock, sir.
The link is nothing more
than a thought, an idea.
Then we need something
to make the contact
physical.
Something...
- so simple.
- So small and shining.
Shining bright and cold.
The tiny
tiny star, falling, falling, burning,
burning, burning.
Small enough to follow the link.
And if
this were on Earth.
The sound...
it's coming from above.
It's coming from the sky!
There!
Find it.
Get out there and find it!
It's a diamond, sir.
The most impossible diamond.
You won't believe this.
It's a Whitepoint star!
Is that you?
Doctor?
Anyone?
I think I'm lost.
And yet you are found.
Events are closing.
The day is almost upon us.
But tell me, old soldier.
Did you take arms?
I brought this.
But, what am I supposed to do?
This is the Doctor's final battle.
At the end of his life,
he must stand at arms,
or lose himself and all this world,
to the end of time.
But he never carries guns.
He doesn't do...
Who are you?
I was lost...
so very long ago.
- Got this old tub mended?
- Just trying to fix the heating.
I've always dreamt of a view like that.
I'm an astronaut.
It's dawn over England, look.
Brand new day.
My wife's buried down there.
I might never visit her again, now.
Do you think he changed them?
In their graves?
I'm sorry.
No, not your fault.
Isn't it?
1948, I was over there.
End of the Mandate in Palestine.
Private Mott.
Skinny little idiot, I was.
Stood on this rooftop,
the middle of a skirmish...
It was like a blizzard,
all them bullets in the air.
The world gone mad.
You don't want to listen
to an old man's tales, do you?
I'm older than you.
Get away.
I'm 906.
- What, really, though?
- Yeah.
900 years...
We must look like insects to you.
I think you look like giants.
Listen, I...
I want you to
have this.
I've kept it all this time,
and I thought...
But if you take it, you could...
You had that gun in the mansion.
You could have
shot the Master there and then.
Too scared, I suppose.
I'd be proud.
Of what?
If you were my dad.
Come on, don't start.
But you said,
you were told...
he will knock four times,
and then you die.
That's him, isn't it?
The Master.
That noise
in his head?
The Master is going to kill you.
Then kill him first.
And that's how the Master started.
It's not like I'm an innocent.
I've taken lives.
I got worse, I got clever.
Manipulated people
into taking their own.
Sometimes I think
a Time Lord lives too long.
I can't.
I just can't.
If the Master dies...
what happens to all the people?
- I don't know.
- Doctor,
what happens?
The template snaps.
What, they go back to being human?
They're alive?
And human?
Then don't you dare, sir.
Don't you dare,
put him before them.
Now you take this,
that's an order, Doctor. Take the gun.
You take the gun and save your life.
And, please don't die.
You're the most wonderful man
and I don't, want you to die!
Never.
A star, fell from the sky.
Don't you want to know where from?
Because now it makes sense, Doctor.
It's an open broadcast.
Don't reply or he'll know where we are.
The whole of my life.
My destiny.
The star was a diamond.
And the diamond...
is a Whitepoint star.
And I have worked all night,
to sanctify that gift.
Now the star is mine
I can increase the signal...
and use it
as a lifeline.
Do you get it now?
Do you see?
Keep watching, Doctor.
This should be...
spectacular.
Over and out.
What's he on about? What's he doing?
Doctor, what does that mean?
A Whitepoint star
is only found on one planet.
Gallifrey.
Which means...
it's the Time Lords.
- They are returning.
- Well,
that's good, isn't it?
That's your people.
Open up the nuclear bolt.
Infuse the power lines to maximum.
Nuclear bolt accelerating, sir.
Send the signal back
and the link becomes a pathway.
Come home.
What's that?
Coming from Earth.
It's on every single wavelength.
Contact!
At last.
We have contact.
Now the High Council
of Time Lords must vote.
Whether we die here, today,
or return to the waking world
and complete the Ultimate Sanction.
For this is the hour
when either Gallifrey falls,
or Gallifrey
rises!
Gallifrey rises!
But you said your people were dead.
Past tense.
Inside the Time War!
And the whole War was Timelocked,
like, sealed inside a bubble.
Not a bubble but think of it.
Nothing can get in or get out
of the Timelock.
Nothing can get in or get out,
except something that was already there.
The signal. Since he was a kid.
If they can follow him,
they can escape, before they die.
- Big reunion. We'll have a party.
- There will be no party.
I've heard you talk about your people
like they're wonderful.
That's how I choose
to remember the Time Lords of old.
But then they went to war,
an endless war,
and it changed them.
Right to the core.
You see my enemie, Wilf.
- They're the most dangerous enemies.
- Time Lords... What lords?
- Anyone want to explain?
- You! This is a salvage ship,
yes?
You go trawling the asteroid fields
- for junk?
- So?
So, you've got asteroid lasers!
Yeah, but they're all frazzled.
Consider them unfrazzled.
You there...
I'm going to need you on navigation.
You, get in the laser-pod.
Laser number two.
The old soldier's got one more battle.
This ship,
can't move.
It's dead!
Fix the heating.
- But now they can see us.
- Oh, yes!
Sir. We've got a fix.
105,000 miles in orbit.
This is my ship.
And you're not moving it.
Step away from the wheel.
There's an old Earth saying, Captain.
A phrase of great power, and wisdom,
and consolation to the soul
in times of need.
- What's that, then?
- Allons-y!
He's moving, sir.
Get a fix on him.
He's moving very fast.
Come on!
You are blinkin',
flippin' mad.
You two, what did I say? Lasers.
What for?
Because of the missiles.
We've got to fight off
the entire planet!
All NATO defences coordinated sir,
awaiting your command.
No need him.
Any second now,
I'll have Time Lords to spare.
Take him out. Launch missiles!
Launch missiles.
Missiles launching
in three,
two,
one,
zero.
How does this thing work?
The tracking's automatic.
Just deploy the trigger on the joystick.
We've got incoming.
- Look at this one! Oh, my God!
- You two! Open fire!
Open fire!
Come on, Wilf!
I wish Donna could see me now.
Second wave. Launch missiles.
Yes, sir.
And there's more. 16 of them.
- And another 16.
- Go to the rear-gun lasers!
You two, open fire!
Now!
No, you don't!
Come on!
Fire!
Lock the navigation.
- Onto what?
- England. The Naismith mansion.
- He's heading straight for you.
- But too late.
They are coming.
The vote is taken.
Only two stand against.
And will stand
as monument to their shame,
like the Weeping Angels of old.
Now the vanguard stands prepared,
as the children of Gallifrey
return to the universe.
To Earth.
Destination?
50 kliks and closing.
We've locked on to the house.
We are going to stop, though?
We are going to stop?
Closer!
And closer!
You said you were going to die.
He said what?
But is that all of us?
I won't stop you, sir.
But is this it?
- I think I should warn you...
- Not now!
My Lord Doctor.
My Lord Master.
We are gathered...
for the end.
Just turn it round, land it!
- We are not going in there.
- I am not
leaving that man on his own.
Not today.
Land it!
Listen to me.
- You can't!
- It is a fitting paradox
that our salvation comes at the hands
of our most infamous child.
He's not saving you.
Don't you realise what he's doing?
That's mine.
Look around you.
I've transplanted myself
into every single human being.
But who wants a mongrel
little species like them?
Because now I can transplant myself
into every single Time Lord.
Oh, yes,
Mr President, sir,
standing there all noble
and resplendent and decrepit
think how much better
you're going to look...
as me!
No, don't!
No, stop it!
Don't!
On your knees, mankind.
No, that's fine, that's good,
because you said salvation.
I still saved you, don't forget that.
The approach begins.
- Approach of what?
- Something is returning.
Don't you ever listen?
That was the prophecy.
Not someone, something.
What is it?
They're not just
bringing back the species.
It's Gallifrey.
Right here,
right now.
Donna. Where's Donna?
Oh, Doctor... please!
We're getting out of here.
This whole planet's
going to be knocked out of orbit.
What about the Doctor?
He said he was dying.
But I... I did this.
I get the credit!
I'm on your side.
Come on, get out of the way,
get out of the way!
Somebody, please!
I've got you.
Wilf, don't... Don't!
I've got you. Come on. Go on.
But... this is fantastic, isn't it?
- The Time Lords restored.
- You weren't there...
in the final days of the War.
You never saw what was born.
If the Timelock's broken, everything's
coming through, not just the Daleks,
but the Skaro Degradations,
the Horde of Travesties,
the Nightmare Child,
the Could-have-been King with his army
of Meanwhiles and Never-weres.
The War turned into hell.
And that's what you opened,
right above the Earth.
Hell is descending.
- My kind of world.
- Just listen!
Cos even the Time Lords
can't survive that.
We will initiate the Final Sanction.
The end of time will come...
at my hand.
The rupture will continue,
until it rips the Time Vortex apart.
That's suicide.
We
will ascend...
to become creatures
of consciousness alone.
Free of these bodies, free of time,
and cause and effect,
while creation itself ceases to be.
You see now?
That's what they were planning
in the final days of the War.
I had to stop them.
Then...
take me with you, Lord President.
Let me ascend into glory.
You are diseased.
Albeit a disease of our own making.
No more.
Choose your enemy well.
We are many.
The Master is but one.
But he's the President.
Kill him,
and Gallifrey could be yours.
He's to blame, not me!
The link is inside my head.
Kill me,
the link gets broken, they go back.
You never would, you coward.
Go on then.
Do it.
Exactly.
It's not just me, it's him.
He's the link, kill him!
The final act of your life
is murder.
But which one of us?
Get out of the way.
The link is broken.
Back into the Time War, Rassilon.
Back into hell.
Gallifrey falling!
Gallifrey falls!
You'll die with me, Doctor.
I know.
Get out of the way.
You did this to me!
All of my life!
You made me!
One!
Two!
Three!
FOUR!
I'm alive.
I've...
There was...
I'm still alive.
They've gone, then?
Good-oh.
If you could let me out...?
Only, this thing seems to be
making a bit of a noise.
The Master...
left the nuclear bolt running.
It's gone into overload.
And that's bad, is it?
cos all the excess radiation
gets vented inside there.
Vinvocci glass.
Contains it.
All 500,000 rads,
about to flood that thing.
Well, you'd better let me out, then.
Except it's gone critical.
Touch one control and it floods.
Even this would set it off.
I'm sorry.
(Sure.)
Look, just leave me.
OK. Right, then... I will.
Cos you had to go in there,
didn't you?
You had to go and get stuck,
oh, yes!
Cos that's who you are, Wilfred.
You were always this.
Waiting for me all this time.
Oh, really, just leave me.
I'm an old man, Doctor.
I've had my time.
Well, exactly. Look at you.
Not remotely important.
But me...
... I could do so much more.
So much more!
But this is what I get.
My reward.
And it's not fair!
Lived too long.
No...
no, no, please, please don't.
No, don't.
Don't... Please don't! Please!
Wilfred...
it's my honour.
Better be quick. Three, two, one.
What...?
Still with us?
The system's dead.
I absorbed it all.
Whole thing's kaput.
Now it opens, yeah.
There we are then. Safe and sound.
Mind you, you're in hell of a state.
You've got some battle scars there.
But they've...
Your face!
How did you do that?
It's started.
It's no good. How long was
she lying there? It's like hypothermia!
Try them again.
I did, it's engaged. Everyone's
dialling 999, I can't get through.
We've got to do something.
Wake her up. Donna?
Can you hear me?
It's me, I'm here.
You're safe, you're home.
But... I was...
What happened?
Did I miss something... again?
She's smiling.
As if today wasn't bad enough.
Anyway...
Don't go thinking
this is goodbye, Wilf.
I'll see you again,
- one more time.
- What do you mean, when's that?
Just keep looking. I'll be there.
Where are you going?
To get my reward.
- I told you to stay behind.
- You looked like you needed help.
Besides, you're the one
who persuaded me to go freelance.
Yeah, but we're being fired
at by a Sontaran.
A dumpling with a gun. And this is
no place for a married woman.
Well, then.
You shouldn't have married me.
If we go in here
and down to the factory floor
and down past that corridor,
then he won't know that we're here.
Mickey...
That was the maddest Christmas ever.
Mum doesn't know what happened.
She got Mr Smith to put out
a story saying wi-fi went mad,
all over the world,
giving everyone hallucinations.
How else do you explain it?
Everyone with a different face...
But it's you!
You're...
Mum?
Mum!
- What? What is it?
- It's him.
It's the Doctor.
From the man over there.
So, Alonso...
... going my way?
How do you know my name?
I'm kinda psychic.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Do you know what I'm thinking
right now?
No, it's not just a story, no.
Every word of it is true.
I found my great grandmother's diary
in the loft.
She was a nurse in 1913, and she fell
in love with this man called John Smith.
Except he was a visitor...
from another world.
She fell in love
with a man from the stars.
And she wrote it all down.
Thank you.
And who's it for?
- The Doctor.
- To the Doctor.
Funny, that's the name he used.
Was she happy... in the end?
Yes. Yes, she was.
Were you?
Three cheers. Hip, hip...
Hooray!
- Hip, hip...
- Hooray!
Right, come on then, you lot.
This photo is just with friends.
Come on. And I want all of you
in it, come on. That's it.
Well, friends, and Nerys.
I'm only joking. Oh, look at her!
- You made me wear peach.
- That's cos you are a peach.
- Furry skin, stone inside, going off.
- OK, smile.
Cheese!
How about it, Wilfred?
Well, it's never too late.
Will you behave, Minnie!
Honestly!
I'm going to catch that bouquet.
Oh, dear.
Dad...
And here you are, same old face.
Didn't I tell you
you'd be all right?
Oh! They've arrested Mr Naismith.
It was on the news. Crimes
undisclosed. And his daughter.
Both of 'em, locked up.
But I keep thinking,
Doctor,
there's one thing you never told me.
That woman. Who was she?
I just wanted to give you this.
Wedding present.
Thing is, I never carry money.
So I just popped back in time,
borrowed a quid
off a really lovely man.
Geoffrey Noble, his name was.
"Have it," he said.
"Have that on me."
Smile!
Oh, don't tell me, it's a bill.
Just what I need, right now.
A lottery ticket?!
What a cheap present.
Who was that?
Still, you never know, it's a triple
rollover this week, I might get lucky.
Come on, we're on a tight schedule,
oxtail soup at 2.30.
I'm late, I've missed it. It's midnight.
Mickey'll be calling me everything.
- This is your fault.
- No, it's Jimbo!
He said he was going to give us a lift,
then he said his axle broke.
I can't help it.
- Get rid of him, Mum, he's useless.
- Listen to you! With a mechanic.
Be fair though, my time of life,
I'm not gonna do much better.
Don't be like that.
You never know.
There could be someone out there.
Maybe. One day.
- Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year!
- Don't stay out all night.
- Try and stop me.
- You all right, mate?
- Yeah.
Too much to drink?
Something like that.
Maybe it's time you went home.
- Yeah.
- Anyway...
- Happy New Year.
- And you.
What year is this?
Blimey, how much have you had?!
2005. January 1st.
2005.
_Tell you what...
... I bet you're going to have
a really great year.
See ya.
We will sing to you, Doctor.
The universe will sing you
to your sleep.
This song is ending.
But the story never ends.
I don't want to go.
Legs. I've still got legs, good.
Arms. Hands.
Ooh, fingers, lots of fingers.
Ears, yes. Eyes, two.
Nose, I've had worse. Chin, blimey.
Hair...
I'm a girl!
No! No... I'm not a girl.
And still not ginger!
And something else,
something important, I'm, I'm...
Crashing!
Geronimo!
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~