So then the guy says to the housekeeper,
"make sure she's dead."
- Stop me if you heard this one before.
- He'd could say it27 minutes ago.
The housekeeper says to the guy,
"we don't have a pool."
- And the guy says...
- Good morning, Greendale!
Just a reminder,
our debate team will bring home
the championship tomorrow
versus City College.
Go, Human Beings!
Great. Now I got to start
the whole joke over again.
So this guy...
I've got one for you.
A doddering old fool
walks into a bar,
tells a stupid joke,
and I crush his windpipe
with my three-ring binder.
- I don't get it.
- She's trying to stop smoking.
Don't tell them my business.
I will slap that smug look
right off your pointy face.
I'm saying this
because I care about you
and you're my friend.
You need to start smoking again.
You should.
It makes you lose weight, and your skin
looks great when you do it.
Guys, I really appreciate your support,
but I've got to quit this time.
Have you thought about hypnotherapy?
I know a dynamite hypnotherapist.
- Ten-to-one says it's him.
- His name is Pierce Hawthorne.
And I'm very effective.
Can you block out people's voices
I find extremely annoying?
Jeff, she's right there.
I would be grateful for your help.
You would?
Super. I'll set it up.
What?
I feel bad for him.
- Plus, I just yelled at him.
- You yelled at me too.
Did I hurt your feelings,
pointy face?
Have you seen the film
department's web site?
What do you think?
All of Abed's films are about us.
- What?
- Check it out.
What else is new?
Stop being so relaxed.
We need to talk to you about...
You're living out of your car.
Why, on lord's good earth, boy?
Those people look just like us.
That's eerie.
Fine, it's true.
I'm living out of my car.
And I don't want anyone's help.
We had almost
that exact conversation last week.
Yeah, but Abed posted this video
two weeks ago.
That boy's a soothsayer.
- This is wrinkling my brain.
That's wrinkling my brain.
Get a load of these wrinkles.
- Who's that old guy?
- Hi, I'm Pierce Hawthorne.
Come on!
There he is.
- Did you hear my announcement?
- I hang on every word.
I'm gonna assume that's sarcasm.
So you didn't hear my announcement?
I'm barely listening now.
My debate partner dropped out,
we need you to fill in for him tonight.
Jeffrey, as debate coach,
I am offering you an opportunity
to spend the night
drinking from the cup of life
rather than romancing your nether
regions in front of the e! Channel.
Come on, Jeff.
Who better than a former lawyer
to really stick it
to those city college snobs
and their star debater Simmons?
Pass.
Wait. Wait.
Okay, no, no. Look.
Listen, jerkwad... I'm sorry.
That got heated.
Greendale needs a win.
The best compliment
our sports program gets
is that our basketball team
is really gay,
so what's it gonna take?
A plum parking space,
free meals,
a night of companionship
if you know what I mean.
I'll do it for the parking space.
And if you promise
not to tell me what you mean.
Thank you.
I really appreciate
you helping me out.
And I appreciate the opportunity.
You know, sometimes,
- people don't take me seriously.
- So what are you gonna do?
Wave a pocket watch
in front of my face
and tell me I'm getting very sleepy?
Just checking the time.
Now close your eyes.
Keep them closed at all times.
And listen to the soothing sound
of my voice.
The only word
that will bring you out is...
gorilla.
Okay, now focus on the rhythm
of your own breathing.
And when you feel the desire
to light up a cigarette,
you will associate these urges
with things in your life
that disgust you.
Bad-tasting food.
Sex with men.
Wearing attractive clothing.
And soon...
Oh, God,
I think I really hurt myself!
Somebody help me.
Britta, wake up!
Why'd I put you under so well?
Damn my talent.
Topic for debate is
"are people inherently good or evil?"
So when do you want
to get together to strategize?
Annie, I was a lawyer.
I was a debater for money.
I think I can handle this.
- How was hypnotherapy?
- He fell down and screamed in pain
while I laid there with my eyes closed
to make him feel like he's good.
- This will never end.
- It's already done.
He just wants one more session.
Where's Abed?
I need to talk to him about his films.
That boy's flat-out prescient.
He can read our minds.
I know what you're gonna say.
You watched my movies.
- He's a witch!
- Get him!
I'm not a witch.
I'm a student of human character.
I know you guys all so well
I can predict your behavior.
Like Shirley.
I know you're a sweet, christian,
generous person.
Oh, that's nice.
You have thinly veiled rage issues.
Careful, boy.
Here. Check this out.
May I?
Jeff's character acts
like nothing affects him.
But things bother him.
Hey, I'm top of the class.
He's also very vain.
Ridiculous.
Why am I crying?
What, I accidentally listen
to Come sail away by Styx again?
You don't have to worry. It's a movie.
I can't predict the future.
My leg. I hurt my leg.
What up, happy people?
You tell me my future right now,
you evil wizard!
By the way, I think your shirt's trying
to get out of your pants.
As golding's Lord of the flies
demonstrates, man,
when left to his own devices,
will descend
into chaos
and evil.
And now, from City College,
Jeremy Simmons.
There were 23,000...
kidney donations
in America last year.
Man is good.
The average life expectancy
for a man in a community
is 23 years longer than a man...
alone.
Man is good.
And just ten minutes ago,
a bald, bespectacled man
held the door
for a man in a wheelchair.
Man is good.
I hate this guy.
By the end of this debate,
I will prove with... facts
and data
that man is inherently...
good.
Old trick for achieving
the proper competitive mindset,
I always envision my opponent
having aggressive sex
with my mother.
This feels so formal.
Let's just talk.
People are evil.
They can't help it.
I didn't catch your name.
It's Jean.
Take Jean here.
She spent a lot of time this morning
making herself look so lovely.
Tell me.
How many people bothered to tell you
how great you look today?
- None.
- Man is evil.
But you just said
how great I looked.
For my own selfish purposes.
The fact is, as hot as you look,
and it is quite hot,
I wouldn't have said anything.
When I talk about people being evil,
I could cite quotes
or dig up statistics,
but those are just words
and numbers.
I think...
we could...
have a little more fun
if I express myself
in song.
Evil woman
That's my time, everybody.
Thank you very much.
At the end of round one,
City College: 50,
Greendale: 8.
- I only got 8?
- She got 8. You got 0.
It's a debate.
Not American Idol.
Nice work, L.A. Law.
All sizzle, no steak.
I don't care, dude.
I'm doing this for a parking space.
Let's go, boys. Come on.
I want to see some hustlers out here.
Let's go.
By Zeus,
what sort of jackassery is this?
We're in the middle
of a championship debate.
We reserved the gym for practice.
They reserved it.
They've got us by the short ones.
The debate is suspended
until tomorrow.
Hopefully, by then,
we can get our act together.
Oh, great try, Bruce!
Great try.
When are we getting together
to prepare for tomorrow?
Never, it's stupid, I don't care.
Bite me.
Maybe Simmons is right.
You really are all sizzle and no steak.
- You couldn't beat him if you tried.
- What do you mean I can't beat him?
You and I will study harder
than we've ever studied before
- and beat City College tomorrow.
- Really?
No, who am I, Carly?
Abed is right.
You act like things don't bother you,
but they do.
Look, six months ago,
I was a lawyer.
I wore suits.
I used to say stuff like,
"objection" and "sidebar".
Now I'm losing
a community college debate
to Jeremy "soul patch" Simmons.
You like to sing?
I like to sing too.
Zero for Winger...
Kick that.
Was a big shot lawyer...
Now he's a...
looser.
Lay off.
Jeff didn't understand the rules.
- What's your excuse, eight points?
- Dude, leave her out of this.
Little Annie Adderall
was an outcast
in high school
That's it.
Dude, we are gonna debate
the living crap out of you.
We've got some preparing to do.
I liked you better
when you were smoking.
I'm so sorry.
No, you're right.
My feet are long and stupid.
You can't unring that bell.
- That's my newspaper.
- What do you need a paper for?
You knew what's happened yesterday,
you middle-eastern magic eight ball.
Pierce hurt his leg,
Britta made Troy cry.
What's my destiny?
Am I gonna die in a car?
Is it gonna happen soon?
I have no psychic abilities.
I'm just an entertainer.
But if it'll make you feel
any better,
here, let me show you
what I'm working on.
I'm sorry. Is that me
being chased down by a werewolf?
That's how you'd behave
in that situation?
The situation being me
being chased down by a werewolf.
And that's Jeff
locking lips with Annie.
You're a fool.
So, in the experiment, Stanford students
were divided into prisoners and guards.
The guards immediately started...
- What's wrong?
- I've this weird pain
right above my eyebrow.
It's called a stress headache.
I got my first one when I was four.
I hate it.
Get used to it.
You're knee-deep in it now.
This is debate.
If you want to win,
you need to prepare.
Agreed, but if you want to win,
you need to loosen up.
Go off book, robot debater.
You're right.
Simmons is so good at using his...
inherent magnetism
to sell his points,
and here I am,
like a spinster librarian
with my hair pulled back.
What do you think?
Thanks.
Be careful.
Abed thinks you two are gonna kiss.
Ridiculous.
Us.
Kissing.
That is ridiculous.
Totally.
We should get back to work.
The people are inherently evil.
We can use this Hobbes quote.
"Man is a collection
"of base animal urges."
"To act on them and experience
"sinful pleasure would be morally
no different than taking a breath."
That's poignant, right?
You know, maybe we should study alone.
Separately.
That way we can be more reproductive...
Productive!
Bye.
- You forgot your phone.
- Well, I can get another one.
The next time you even see
a cigarette,
you will think of things
that disgust you.
And while you're under so deep,
you'll find yourself attracted
to slightly older men.
Perhaps, some barrel-chested stud
with just enough tummy to love.
You'll want to buy him dinner,
then go back to his hot tub.
Perhaps, you'll invite one friend
to join us for a three-way.
Maybe someone
with low self-esteem, and...
slightly larger breasts.
Go to hell, you disgusting pig.
Pierce, I was awake the whole time.
I was faking it.
I know.
I saw you.
What do you think I am, a joke?
I was trying to make you feel better
about yourself.
How dare you pity me?
I may be a little older,
my ideas may seem weird,
and my fashion sense may cause envy.
But I have a lot to offer.
And I will not be pitied.
Do not help me up.
And as German poet Franz Wickmeyer
once wrote...
"Snow falls from the heavens pure.
"We cannot blame
the snow for being...
"soiled by the earth."
Man is good.
What?
That dude gets it.
Jeff Winger will now offer
a two-minute rebuttal.
What are you gonna sing tonight?
I'm in the mood for some Sade.
In the Stanford prison experiment,
21 out of 21 students,
when given absolute power,
abused and tortured
their fellow students.
My competitor likens people to pure,
falling snow.
I would respond,
"There is none righteous."
"Not one."
Now I realize Mr. Simmons' quote
was from the great Franz Wickmeyer.
Mine was just
from a simple desert handyman...
named Jesus.
That's nice!
Survival of the fittest
wires an impulse
to eliminate people into our hearts.
- Counterpoint.
- Mother Teresa. Joan of Arc.
- Rebuttal.
- Nuclear bombs.
- Nuclear families.
- Abu Ghraib.
- Apu from the Simpsons.
- Double rejoinder.
- Telemarketers.
- Organ donors.
- Hate crimes.
- Executions.
Ketchup is a vegetable.
This is a real barn-burner.
God, did I just say cross-burner?
- No, you did not.
- Good.
- We make an amazing team.
- I know. We're so in sync.
It's like a perfect duet or great...
Professor Whitman.
Your preparation was impeccable.
You remind me of a young me,
with slightly worse hair.
I checked with the judges.
They'll need a miracle
to win in rebuttal.
Simmons is finished.
This is too much for me.
He's going off book.
Why is he ripping up the cards?
Doesn't he need them?
It's a gambit.
He hates me.
Yet he caught me.
Man is good.
He was horny.
So he dropped him.
Man is evil.
Greendale wins.
Eat that, Simmons.
That off-book enough for ya?
Simmons got robbed.
They kissed.
You do have powers.
I'm gonna die by werewolf.
Shirley, I don't have powers.
Trust me.
In my next film,
we discover that Pierce is an genius.
- That's not gonna happen.
- No, it's not.
I can't smoke a cigarette
without thinking of a three-way
in your hot tub.
You did it.
- I did?
- You're a genius.
Who's the third?
You did great in there!
Let's take this bacchanalia outside.
Full moon tonight.
I'm going this way, so...
Congratulations...
buddy.
Thanks...
pal.
Just pat me.
Cut.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you hate this?
Do you hate doing this?
Do you?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Just hold on.
Just have fun with it.
Take 36.