Missed you at lunch today.
You had a quickie
with professor hot stuff?
It's Michelle, how did you know?
There's a gold star on your fly.
You weren't kidding.
Nice to have a girlfriend with humor
and one who recognizes good work.
Let me teach you the chords.
See, that's "g".
The most important chord.
In my mind, it stands for "god".
Why is Annie talking
to micro-nipples?
Vaughn?
Whatever.
But not like a bible god,
cause I think god is in everything.
You're complicated.
Annie
Annie, where are you going today?
Spanish class?
Spanish
You know what I don't get?
He never wears a shirt.
He never wears shoes.
Why hasn't he died
from lack of service?
Watching another movie tonight?
Kickpuncher, starring
Don "the demon" Donaldson
Cyborg cop whose punches
have the power of kicks.
That sounds awful.
I'll bring the popcorn.
You watch bad movies on purpose?
Yeah, we make fun of 'em.
Don't embarrass yourself.
They don't want to invite a housewife.
Actually, if she doesn't mind
reinforcing the stereotype,
She would have fun
talking smack at a movie.
- You join us?
- When a movie's bad,
I stop watching,
but this sounds college-y.
What time you want us there?
Pierce, you don't wanna watch
a cyborg movie in Abed's dorm.
You wanna lay on your twin bed
and think about what you used to be.
What?
You think I'm too old
to make monkeyshines at a picture show?
I'm younger
than the three of you put together.
Everyone talks about his nipples,
but his feet freak me out.
Can I ask you something...
about Vaughn?
Still don't know
if that's his first or last name.
He's sweet, actually.
I mean, you must have thought so.
He has a sincerity
I found attractive in a simpler time.
Would you...
I haven't...
We haven't...
anything.
I mean...
Wow, you and Vaughn.
- Would it bug you?
- What about you and Troy?
The other day after Spanish,
I thought he tried to hold my hand,
but he'd just mistaken me for Abed.
He'll never think of me that way.
Well...
I would have to be a villain
to tell you who to date, which I am not.
Thank you!
You're the coolest girl
I've ever met.
Damn right!
Give me some fivesies.
Turning it into a snake.
- Feygnasse Team -
.:: La Fabrique ::.
1x15: Beginner Pottery
How's it going? Did you hear?
It's cute, Annie and Vaughn.
- Get to the cute part.
- She's into him.
- She asked for my blessing!
- And you gave it?
- Yeah, I'm done with him.
- It's not about you, groovy hipster.
It's about Annie.
We're like her Greendale parents!
You gotta say no to that stuff.
He's not that bad.
Not if you're 28
and fooling around with him.
She's 18.
Her taste in men
is still being established.
Creepier and creepier dudes
will start thinking of her
as an option,
and it all starts with Vaughn.
A gateway douche bag.
People collide, things happen.
It can't be controlled, right?
And that can be your toast
at her shotgun wedding to Star-burns.
Yeah, turn to your left.
Now turn to your right.
Yes, we can see both of them.
Like a constellation on your face.
What's up, dude?
That guy over there,
he's a douche bag.
- Hey, guys.
- Hola.
You don't mind I invited Senor Chang.
We're Netflix friends.
Cool that you're hanging out,
drinking beers with your students.
Clearly,
none of my other plans fell through.
Let's get to the movie.
Wait, sorry Shirley.
I'll wait
if you wanna serve beverages.
You gonna be waiting
a long-ass time.
FBI warning... I'm so scared!
That's not fair.
I didn't know we started.
It is the year 2006 a.d.,
and nuclear war
has ravaged the planet.
I must have missed that.
Nice.
... is a free-fire zone
ruled by scavengers,
drug dealers, and terrorists.
Sounds like a thanksgiving
at my house.
That's pretty crazy.
They just come to me.
You guys wanna buy some mega dope?
It gets you mega high.
Will it get me through this movie?
Shirley is in the house.
Freeze, police!
Freeze police?
Don't do that, they'll get cold.
You have done so much for our city.
Kickpuncher,
is there anything
that we can give you?
Two hours of my life back.
Don't call me Kickpuncher.
Call me David.
"Directed by Kim Yang."
Asian...
Can't direct, can't drive.
Dude, I'm right here.
Right there.
So...
Clearly we're all a bunch
of funny people.
- When are we doing this again?
- Well actually...
Tomorrow we'll get together to watch
Kickpuncher 2: Codename Punchkicker.
I was just warming up tonight.
Tomorrow you better foam the runways,
'cause I'm bringing my "a" game.
Awesome.
He's got her
in some kind of hippie collar.
I can hear her armpit hair
growing from here.
We got to do something.
Even if I agreed with you,
what are we gonna do?
If we disapprove, we'll drive her
into his hemp-braceleted arms.
We need to be smart, hatch a scheme.
Hatching schemes
is not my wheelhouse.
Let's not confine
to your wheelhouse.
It won't respond to tap dancing
or casual revelations
that you spent time in New York.
If you get upper east side
about this, we're done.
Hey, Winger, check out Annie.
Somebody just went to the top
of my "to do" list.
OK, we need to hatch a scheme.
Thank you.
It's all very simple.
In Annie's world,
long before Vaughn,
she only had eyes for Troy.
So if Troy becomes a real option,
Annie will drop Vaughn
in a hippie's heartbeat.
Crash course in manipulation...
You don't actually tell the person
what you want them to do.
You help them realize
they want to do it
so it can't be traced back to you.
Chemistry... sexy.
You know what else is sexy?
I know chemistry is sexy.
But Annie? I don't see it.
Every other guy on campus does.
You really don't see
how pretty Annie is?
Maybe cause I knew her in high school,
before she dropped out.
She had braces, acne,
a pill addiction, a nervous breakdown
ending with her running through a door,
screaming, "everyone's a robot!"
I see what's happening here.
I want you to clear your head.
- Done.
- I'm gonna describe to you
a complete stranger
who happens to be in our study group.
Would you excuse us for a moment?
No kidding.
Come on, you gotta be exaggerating.
Oh, man.
And she's jewish?
I can't believe I didn't see that.
I guess she deserves another shot.
Wait, never mind. It's too late.
She's hooking up with Vaughn.
- Only to make you jealous.
- What?
She's in love with you.
She's with Vaughn to get your attention.
You have to give it to her now, right?
Sure.
But the point is,
we're not telling you what to do.
Yeah, you didn't hear it from us.
I have the weirdest boner.
I saw you die.
How can you be alive?
I guess it's just a bad day
for drug-dealing terrorists
and a good day for...
Kickpuncher!
All right, guys,
you hear that pause
after "and a good day"?
- What do you got?
- A good day for a nutritious breakfast.
I don't get it.
It's a good day
for a terrible movie.
A good day for hair products.
Buzz, how many times
can you keep going to that well?
Come on, guys.
I'm starting to wonder if you deserve
to call yourselves a community
college sketch comedy troupe.
Told you, on movie night, I need
to blow these punks out of the water.
I need Phyllis Diller-grade stuff.
Wouldn't you rather just watch a movie
with your friends and have a good time?
What are you,
my third wife's therapist?
What if he said,
"it's a good day for... "
and you said, "for being gay"?
You're a genius.
He likes gay jokes.
- What?
- I said we write great jokes.
Don't flatter yourselves.
It's me, Troy.
I don't know where Abed is.
I could try calling him.
Not looking for my other half.
I'm looking for you, girl.
Let that sink in for a second.
You know, I never noticed how...
beautiful you are.
Troy, you're being weird.
Sorry it took me so long.
They made me find a shirt.
Vaughn, you remember Troy.
We went to high school together,
he's in my study group.
What's up, man? Hi, bro.
I'm not your bro... bro.
Actually,
everyone
is my bro in the entire universe,
everything's connected...
Rocks,
eagles,
hats.
Some things
are more connected than others,
like tarantulas
and me peeing my pants...
- Or me and Annie.
- What? Wait.
- Troy, what?
- Tell him.
That you love me since high school.
What?
Is that true, mountain flower?
I never wanna lie to you,
I will tell you I did have feelings
for him, but it's over, I swear.
You're swearing?
Like Britta swore she didn't like Jeff
and then gave him my poem
so he could laugh at me
with that Sherri Shepherd lady?
It's happening again.
Your study group is evil.
And you don't deserve ice cream.
He's a baby.
Where were we?
I like him.
Why would you do that?
Come on. Everybody knows
you want a cut of the T-Bone steak.
Jeff and Britta
told me how you feel.
Jeff and Britta did what, now?
You're even hotter
when you're angry.
Let's do this.
Red Shoe Diaries...
I think you know I have
a thing for butt stuff.
To Annie's inevitable breakup
with Grodie J. McConaughey.
And to her and Troy.
We did the right thing.
They belong together.
Plus, their babies will be so cute.
- Why you say that?
- Come on.
Babies are extra cute
when their parents are...
Both cute?
You want kids?
We'll see. Put on something nice,
and find me after lunch.
Thanks for involving in my love life.
That was cool and mature of you.
Since you're both clearly idiots,
I should probably let you know that
I'm being sarcastic.
Thanks for taking ugly Annie
out of the palm of my hand
and turning her into yet another
hottie that will never get with me!
Thanks for eating all the macaroni!
Shut up, Leonard.
Nobody knows what you're talking about.
I did eat all the macaroni.
It's messed up that he knows.
Let's light this candle.
Who's ready for some kickpunching?
We decided to watch Runaway instead.
Tom Selleck fights mechanical spiders.
What?
You can't. We just watched Kickpuncher.
We have to see Kickpuncher 2.
I have many unanswered questions.
I want to watch Tom Selleck
fight mechanical spiders.
My brother died
on the set this movie.
One of the mechanical spiders...
just went haywire
and tore him to pieces.
Tom Selleck just stood there.
He just stood there
and watched him die.
Okay, then let...
Let's watch Kickpuncher 2, then.
- Sorry for your loss.
- That's messed up, dude.
Kickpuncher 2.
My punches were only
as strong as my punches,
and then things changed.
Change?
Time to change the channel.
He's gonna be begging for change,
if he keeps making movies this bad.
Change this to something good.
This movie stinks.
We better change his diaper.
A change we can believe in.
Something strange is happening.
What do you mean?
I'm making jokes during the movie.
But you're doing it
with the speed and the determination
of the incomparable Robin Williams.
I'm that brilliant.
I think you came prepared.
Dude,
even I know you're lame,
and I'm a tenured professor
sitting in a beanbag chair.
- You're not a professor.
- Shut up.
Fine!
You got me.
I did a little advance work.
Pathetic?
I'll tell you what's pathetic,
you sitting there
making fun of other people's work.
You don't feel good about yourselves,
so you tear down everything.
Mama Chang didn't breast-feed?
She read
it wouldn't make a difference.
You all sicken me!
And I will no longer participate
in your destructive, negative behavior.
Pierce, that was deep
and total b.s.
This isn't about us, it's a deflection,
cause you can't get a genuine laugh.
That in itself is a laugh.
I know I'm funny.
I don't need any of you
people to validate me.
I'm sorry.
Biggest laugh of the night.
Then I was gonna say,
"it's a good day to be gay".
We're sorry.
We were worried about your well-being.
I guess we feel like
we're sort of all a family,
and Jeff and I are like...
your Greendale parents.
You're not my mom.
She'd never wear boots going that high.
And what about respecting me
as an adult and as a friend?
You want to be treated
as an adult and a friend?
Try not dating your friend's ex.
Find your own man.
But you don't like Vaughn.
No, I don't, but I also don't like
seeing him with anyone else.
I asked you if you cared,
and you said no.
Fine, I cared.
I'm a girlie-girl. I like boys.
I don't like when they're mean to me,
and when they stop
kissing me and start kissing my friends.
I'm not that cool.
I'm not "Juno", homeslice.
This is what it was about?
You were jealous?
Please, you can't tell me
that you weren't jealous that Vaughn
had his hippie hands all over
your debate/makeout partner.
What are you insinuating?
I took that kiss for the team.
What?
That kiss wasn't for pleasure.
It was strategic and joyless.
What?
You did get weirdly specific
when you were describing Annie's body.
More specific than the stuff
you told me about Britta?
What?
- Does anyone get specific about me?
- Check your email.
- I'll mark you as spam.
- Who the hell is Pam?
First, we were wholesome and healthy
as the family in The Brady Bunch.
Now we're dysfunctional and incestuous
as the cast of The Brady Bunch.
I agree with Abed.
This is getting creepy.
No more creepy than when Jeff
wears tight jeans and you say,
"i'd like to slap those
buns on the grill."
What?
I don't talk like that,
and where I'm from,
it's normal for women to talk
about their male friends' backsides.
You don't see me saying anything crazy
about Abed and Troy's.
They're jealous.
All right,
maybe we're not a family.
Maybe it's more complicated.
Because unlike a real family,
there's nothing to stop any one of us
from looking at any of the others
as a sexual prospect.
Why are we even talking about this?
Because you started having sex
with Britta's ex-boyfriend.
What?
We haven't even kissed.
That doesn't mean
you're not having sex.
Vaughn told me he would take
things as slowly as I wanted.
He likes me for who I am,
and I like him.
Do you guys hear that?
- Old man river.
- Eat me.
Did you get my messages?
I threw my phone into the river.
I thought that, if I can't be with her,
who am I gonna call?
And then I thought, well,
my landlord, my sister, and...
you.
Anyway, I've been doing
a lot of soul-searching, and...
this is something
I really need to say.
I see you when you smile
And I want to sing a song
But then I write the words
And they always come out wrong
They come out wrong
I feel it in my fingers
I feel it in my toes
But then the words get frozen
In my mouth like eskimos
I like your nose
Annie's song
His songs are dumber than he is.
Yeah, but they're honest.
I'll be right here.
Vaughn wants to show me a cloud
that looks like a pumpkin...
If that's okay.
Annie, it's more than okay.
Please date Vaughn.
Or anyone else outside
this creepy circle.
I wouldn't hang out with you guys
if you were creepy.
Trust me.
I have good taste.
So just to be clear,
I don't have a shot with any of you?
I am kickpuncher.
My cyber punches have
the power of kicks.
I am punchkicker.
Meet your match.
I love you, kickpuncher.
The only thing beyond
the reach of my fists is humanity.
You're sure Britta
couldn't do your part?
I asked her.
She wasn't available.
Let's go film the sex scene.