I'm Jeff.
I try to lock down my schedule
before the deadline.
I heard this class was a cakewalk.
Are you passing it?
- Do you like Dane Cook?
- Yeah, he's awesome.
So far so good.
Death...
so-called...
is a thing
that makes men weep.
And yet
a third of life is spent
in sleep.
Open your textbooks to page 37.
Now...
Close them and throw them away.
Throw it away!
For those of you who are new,
the motto of this class:
Carpe diem.
"Seize the day!"
No tests! No papers.
You want an A?
Live in...
the moment.
Jackpot.
Take off your shoes. Quick.
Everyone, take your shoes off.
Throw them across the room
over there.
Today, we learn to walk!
Get up and walk out the door!
This day could be your last!
You could die in your sleep.
You could get hit by a bus.
You, that mole is raised and dark.
It's not a good combo.
- You are new.
- Yes, I'm new.
But I'll be old too soon.
Carpe diem, sir.
I like it!
Voice command.
Would you please use the buttons?
Okay, grandpa.
God bless you, dear.
- What's so funny?
- You guys, I found it.
The ultimate blow-off class.
Professor Whitman.
He thinks he's in Dead Poets Society.
There's no tests.
There's no work.
It's just "day seizing".
The deadline to enroll is tomorrow.
I suggest you all do it.
Well, some of us are here
to actually learn things.
- I'm in.
- Me too. It sounds educational.
I'll do it.
I love Robin Williams.
Not a fan. An authority figure
always gets mad for making us laugh.
- Are you going to take the class?
- Can't.
My dad pay for classes that will help me
run the family restaurant.
It's been struggling since 2001.
9/11 was the same for falafel business.
So your dad has your whole life
planned out for you?
- Are you even interested in falafel?
- I'm interested in making movies.
Dad says all media's western propaganda
that negatively stereotypes arabs.
Then he should see Aladdin.
Jafar was a bad-ass.
- How much does a film class cost?
- $70.
Isn't Abed's dad a hardcore muslim?
Ain't as understanding as christians.
You can get your head cut off.
That's the most racist thing
I've ever heard.
Pierce beat it in one minute.
This is really nice of you.
The memo says "for dreams".
Are we going to study Spanish
or keep getting involved
in each other's lives?
- Troy sneezes like a girl.
- And how about I pound you like a boy?
That didn't come out right.
Why don't you all just leave him alone
with his cute baby sneezes.
- You're not my mother.
- She's not?
29 seconds.
- Feygnasse Team -
- La Fabrique -
Episode 1x03
Introduction to Film
- What's your name?
- Shirley Bennett.
Shirley, you get an A.
If you can tell me
why you are here at Greendale.
What'd I tell you?
Okay, but never again.
To get a degree in business
to sell my baked goods on the net.
Why... are you here?
To get a degree in business
to sell my baked goods on the net.
Why are you here?
Cause I wasted 15 years
on a man who left me
with nothing but stretch marks
and a memory of two orgasms.
And it's time to get what's mine.
Day seized.
Only when we stop stopping our lives
can we begin to start starting them.
Ms. Edison here,
would rather write
about what happens to other people
than live what is happening to her.
- I thought there might be a quiz.
- Well, here's a quiz for you.
Why did the pretty young girl
die alone
surrounded by sweater-wearing cats
who are trained to use human toilets?
Get up on your desk.
Come on.
Stand on your desk.
Up on your desk.
She made it!
Everyone stand on your desks!
Up, up!
Come on.
Rise, rise above the programming.
All your lives you were told
don't stand on your desks.
Well, why not?
She's okay. Go to the nurse.
Seize the day.
You know, I was really moved
by your honesty earlier.
Particularly the part about your husband
not being able, you know...
Your homework.
I want you to swim in a lake
and tell ten people that you love them.
Can I have a word?
- Are you okay.
- Maybe I'm not.
I like to think every life that passes
through this class is changed.
But every year,
there's always one cocky opportunist
who's just here to coast
and grab an easy A.
His name's Pierce.
I can talk to him for you.
It's actually you.
You have no intention
of seizing the day.
What? Listen,
I have never lived until I met you.
I love you.
There's one down.
Nine to go.
- Not that I want the grade!
- Well, I'm glad to hear it.
Cause if you don't genuinely
seize the day before the end of the week
then you will be seizing an F
for the semester.
This is no way to teach accounting!
I have to plan in advance
how to prove
that I live in the moment.
I'd rather take an actual class,
but now it's too late to drop or add.
It is not fair how hard it is for you
to cheat here.
- How's your film class, buddy?
- It's cool.
Our first assignment is a documentary.
Like real movies, but with ugly people.
- I'm learning a lot.
- That is wonderful.
Some don't like getting involved
in other's lives. I think it's great.
If you're making a documentary
about Britta patting herself on the back
- you're gonna need a backup battery.
- I'm doing a movie about my dad.
That is brilliant. How did he react
to you signing up for the film class?
That part hasn't happened yet.
Here he comes.
You want to get involved
in my family's business?
Holy... War.
Where do I find Mr. Britta?
I'm Mr. Britta.
That's right.
I'm a woman with rights.
And you can see my whole face.
I get it!
Because I'm Arab, I must hate women.
Let me tell you something,
I love women.
But I'm getting a major B-word vibe
from you.
Can't believe I missed out
on getting involved in this.
You go host American Idol
and you stop messing with my son.
He's a special boy.
I raise him, okay? Not you.
- Means letting him follow his dreams.
- Dreams are for sleeping.
- False!
- It's clinically proven.
- So's polio.
- You lost me!
Abed wants to study film.
- What is he saying?
- "We're leaving".
- Tell him you wanna stay to study film.
- I'm not really in the scene.
It was hard enough to talk to him.
Now we have this between us!
Let's go!
Don't touch me!
Guys, guys, stop it.
You have a right to your faith
and your family's privacy.
But Abed is an adult
and a US citizen.
Right?
And he has the right to stay.
Fine.
You want to raise him,
you raise him.
I'm out!
- Wait, what?
- You know, I had a father like you.
And the day
I finally cut myself loose
is the day
I finally started being happy.
That went well.
I'll have to make some adjustments.
You should play the role of my father.
- I don't wanna be your father.
- You already know your lines.
What?
Why are you dressed
like an '80s rapist?
Professor whitman comes by here
every morning and I need him to see me
celebrating life.
- What's all that?
- I am calculating Abed's expenses.
There's books, meals.
He's renting that camera.
He needs a little spending money.
All money is spending money.
It's amazing
what you're doing for Abed.
A lot of people talk a good game.
But you, you follow through.
- Love you.
- Shirley, thank you.
- Bet that doesn't happen to you a lot.
- Happened yesterday.
- Shirley's just doing her homework.
- Thank you for getting people coffee.
I love you.
Abed, how's it going, buddy?
Good. My film is coming together.
Cool tie, Jeff.
You wearing it cause you play my dad,
or is it really Christmas?
- Definitely Christmas.
- Is that a new camera?
It's more expensive, but it lets me
adjust really specific settings
that most people don't notice
or think about.
Hi, I would like a latte.
And, Jeff, let me get you something.
- I'm okay.
- Come on. I got you.
- I don't need anything.
- You insult me. Look at this cash.
I will get a small, black coffee.
An ordinary coffee
for an ordinary life.
Good morning, professor Whitman.
Sorry, Mr. Winger,
these won't cut it.
- Shazbot!
- I shall have...
A birthday cake!
I've seen men in your situation.
No, those are both for me.
You were on top of the world before
and now no one gives a rat's ass.
I can help you with your image.
First, lose the jacket.
You look like a high school bitch.
But more importantly,
it's your sneeze.
When I was a CEO,
I had an array of masculine sneezes
that asserted dominance.
You know, like, the explosive,
shock-the-room-into-silence sneeze.
Or the draw-them-in sneeze.
And maybe I wouldn't sneeze
because I'm in control.
You could even use a sneeze
to drive home a point even.
I think the cubs are going to win it
all this year.
What do you think?
Tell me more.
It's showtime.
Good morning.
Hi! Good morning!
Watch the kite.
Mind if I get a chance?
Bring it in here.
Nice. Thank you so much.
That was really fun.
Sloppy.
And considering the age of these girls,
unwittingly creepy.
Damn it.
- Beat it.
- Professor,
look at the amount of work
I'm putting into this.
Throw me a bone!
Had I not already cried
at the sunrise this morning,
I would be weeping right now.
- What does that mean?
- What do you mean, Jeff?
What does your life mean?
How long does it take you in the morning
to make it look like you have bed head?
How many sweat pants,
sport jacket combos did you try
before you found the one
that said "I don't care"?
Seize the day, Jeff, for real.
Go running naked in a hailstorm,
kiss a girl in the middle of the day,
fly a kite, but do it for yourself.
Or you won't just fail my class,
you'll fail life.
- That guy's really got your number.
- Drop the flower.
I really need to talk to you about Abed.
I went by his film class.
He wasn't there.
He's cutting.
I want to know
why he would do something like that.
- Ask him.
- Every time I try to ask him about it,
he just keeps filming me and telling me
that I'm playing the role of his mother.
Abed is not normal.
That's what you bought
when you tangled yourself in his life.
Look, will you please talk to him?
I've got problems of my own!
I'm trying to seize a day!
What in the hell?
Is he gonna kill us?
Thanks for the pizza, Abed.
I was starving.
- Yeah, it's nice. Like a picnic.
- Or a family dinner.
It's just a study group
and a pizza.
- How's film class?
- Good.
- Did you go to class today?
- Not really.
Not really.
Well, Britta's paying for those classes.
- Don't think you should go?
- I was shooting my movie.
- But your movie's for class.
- My movie's more important.
- Someone order seven lattes?
- I got that.
No, you don't got it.
I got it, Abed.
I got everything.
What is wrong with you?
All I want to do is take care of you.
I know you're not stupid.
Are you doing this on purpose?
- Why won't you answer me?
- Cause it's the scene where you leave.
You better believe it.
- What do you think, Dad?
- I think you are really weird, Abed.
The wrong person just left.
That's a wrap.
That guy was your dad?
You don't really have tickets
for Ravi Sshankar.
I lied to get you here
because it's time to communicate.
Communicate.
Have you met Abed?
It ain't the two of you who need it.
- Wait a minute, where's Weezer?
- They're coming.
The only reason why
this whole mess got started
is because both of you wanted the best
for Abed.
And I think the lesson
we can all take away from this
is that everyone should always do
whatever they want
and leave each other out of it.
- Is that your take?
- Let me give you mine.
You and your pillow-lipped girlfriend
got all up in my stuff
because you wanted to be cowboys
and then you turned chicken
when you found out it will take
more than speeches and guided missiles.
Interesting.
Hadn't seen the Iraq metaphor, but...
What Iraq metaphor? I am talking
about your speeches and her guided...
Got it!
- Point is that Britta is sorry, right?
- Wrong.
Abed may not be a great filmmaker,
that doesn't mean he wanna make falafel.
You need to let him
make his own decisions.
Make his own decisions?
Have you met Abed?
You know who he is?
I'm finished.
How's it going, buddy?
I don't want to be your father.
I think you are weird, Abed.
Look, I need to talk to you
about Abed.
He's not normal.
What is wrong with you?
All I want to do is take care of you.
Why will you not answer me?
What do you think, Dad?
I think you are weird, Abed.
I think the wrong person just left.
It's not exactly Citizen Kane.
I feel a little out of the loop.
That's called the joy of freedom.
My son is hard to understand.
If making movies
help him be understood,
I pay for the class.
- I made this all happen.
- With falafel as a fallback.
Did you do all of that to me
on purpose?
That's not a very nice way
to treat your friends.
It isn't called friend business,
it's called show business.
- He's smoking.
- Honey, let him leave the nest.
Get your hand off my knee.
God bless you.
Thank you.
For someone
who doesn't like getting involved,
I owe you.
You owe me.
That cannot be comfortable for you.
You should kiss me right now.
Day seized!
We're even.
A plus, Winger.
I know a life-changing kiss
when I see one.
Fooled you.
- Am I crumping?
- No.
This is crumping.
We're crumping.
No, you're not.