Synchro:
zelda-zelda
Season 2 Episode 11
"The Jet Set"
**
You make me old with wisdom.
You make wine taste sweeter.
Who wrote that?
I write a lot of poetry
when I'm inspired.
I guess I shouldn't be
surprised by anything you do.
You shouldn't.
It's insulting.
I have to keep you in line,
or I'll lose you.
Yes, you will.
I don't like the idea
of making you older.
I just meant...
I don't know.
It doesn't matter how old I am.
Our souls are the same age.
Oh, God.
You're getting to me.
How do I know I'm not just going to eat
another mushroom and
this room will disappear
and I'll be back on a train to Trenton?
Because I love you, Jane.
This is hard for you. I know it.
You don't want me to talk about it, but
Margaret and Mona have been
your life for the last 40 years.
30.
Listen,
I'm not being impulsive, because I've
been thinking about this all the time.
I want you to be my wife.
What?
Marry me.
- Roger, are you serious?
- Will you do that for me?
90% of Right Guard users
say they play sports.
60% wear it
for their girls as well.
Most impressive, 80% of the fellas
saying yes to the question
"Does Right Guard make you
feel more confident at work?"
Did anyone watch
Loretta Younglast night?
I was supposed to. What happened?
I can't even describe it,
it was so awful.
Creative,
you think old Donny Draper will mind
if we think better on a full stomach?
Well, if you'll all swear
Gillette dropped in.
Are you kidding?
Absolutely.
I'll pretend they're here
if you give me some actual ideas.
Right Guard already has
a great campaign, men being men.
You know, women smell bad, too.
Not you, of course.
- Women have perfume.
- "Perfume does not fight wetness."
Loretta Young.
She's my dad's favorite.
The aprons.
The nauseating upholstery on the couch.
Strangers who drop by.
- Hear from Kinsey?
- What do you mean?
Did you read what's
going on down there?
In this day and age.
The papers said it's going to
be Little Rock all over again.
I don't know why people
keep stirring up trouble.
It's bad for business. Just another
reason not to watch TV.
- Kurt doesn't even have one.
- You have to have one. It's your job.
You're going to miss the playoff.
It's a different life
for single men.
- What do you do with your spare time?
- I like
- concerts. I like park.
- He saw Bob Dylan at Carnegie Hall.
I heard him on the radio.
So we're not going to work at all.
Tell Right Gua, short of a
new product just for women,
we need more research and time.
And lunch.
Ooh. Can we split a lobster?
Does he sound like the album?
When you hear him,
he plays it himself.
It must be something to see.
I'd love to go sometime.
- So go.
- Yes, I should.
You will go with me.
What?
You would go with me?
Oh, no. I...
I don't want to impose
if you have plans.
When you hear him,
you will smile like this.
- Pick you up at 8.
- I live in Brooklyn. It's a hike.
Neighbors.
Joey says that Duck's in the blind.
It's now or never.
This is why I booked a day early.
What did Ricardo in there say?
He's an hourly contact with TWA, and
they've offered to buy you new luggage.
And fill it with my things?
Ricardo recommended a tailor.
Chinese.
And they said they've got
a whole shop full of swim trunks.
I brought mine.
There's not going
to be any swimming.
The convention doesn't
start for another day.
You want to be the hundredth person to
shake someone's hand at some convention?
For what, a free pen?
We'll follow-up face to face.
Forget Santa Monica.
Take your list, target some of
these guys, and make them feel special.
Didn't Roger give you leads?
He did.
I'm going to need sunglasses.
Come on.
You wanna be on vacation, Pete?
'Cause I can make that happen.
Old-fashioned.
Excuse me.
My friends and I have
been speculating about you,
trying to decide who you are
and what you do.
Why?
Are you an actor?
- No.
- Are you an astronaut?
No.
Someone over there would like
to meet you, a young woman,
only if you were
none of these things.
I'm Vicompte Monteforte d'Alsace.
- Willy.
- Don.
This is Don.
She's been staring at you all day.
Can't stop talking about you.
I'm Joy.
Oh, and this is Rocci.
You look so
comfortable alone by the pool all day.
I wonder if you're waiting for someone.
I am.
Hmm.
Do you smell that jasmine?
Mmm. Dine with us.
- Maybe another time.
- Well. That never happens.
Hello.
Pete, this is Joy and Rocci
and Vicompte Monteforte.
Very good.
D'Alsace. Willy.
That's quite a name.
Peter Dykeman Campbell.
Have we met somewhere? Newport?
I have a terrible memory for faces.
Nice meeting you.
Yes.
A pleasure to meet you.
Look for us.
Everybody here
is late for everything.
Oh. I just saw Tony Curtis
in the men's room.
Handing out towels?
Tony Curtis, Don.
A thing like that.
- Who's for dinner?
- Rodney Barnes.
Classic salesman turned executive.
And this interesting scientist,
Caleb Sawyer.
He has this "optiman" thesis.
In addition to rockets,
they're going to start engineering man,
you know, for travel in space.
Uh, new organs, super strength.
You know the Soviets
are working on it.
Are all of our meetings like this?
It's American Aviation
and Rocketdyne.
It's not a joke.
Can I get a drink here or what?
Raphael was a little tired.
But the Fifth Arrondissement
has most of your good restaurants.
Of course, we kept getting lost, and
every time Sherry asked for directions,
it turned out to be
another American.
Well, there you go. I'll take Jane
to Paris, and I'll send Mona to Reno.
You don't have to
marry her, do you?
No.
Maybe you and Mona could work out
one of those modern arrangements.
George, stop.
It is possible that you'll get tired
of her, and then where will you be?
Mona doesn't have a right
to anything not my company money,
not my family money.
She's lucky I'm giving her anything.
You know what?
We've been miserable for years. I don't
want to die with that woman.
Calm down.
I didn't know that.
This is the life I was
always meant to have.
Congratulations.
Mona has the marriage license,
and she was to hurt you.
If you want to be with
this 20-year-old girl,
you're going to have to buy it
from her. And I have to warn you.
Women in this situation
become extra irrational.
Well, how badly
does she want to hurt me?
I have a list of conditions
and an alimony that could
support Rita Hayworth.
Think of all the good things
in life and cut them in half.
I want you to push as hard as you can,
but I want it done.
Mr. Phillips is here.
In a minute.
I'll proceed.
But I want you to think about it.
Duck Phillips,
this is George Rothman.
Actually, we know each other.
Roger.
It's good to see you, Duck.
Was he for you or against you?
He's supposed to be the best.
Him or Marvin Hughes.
That's who Mona has.
He's her cousin.
How bad was it? Do I want to know?
I don't think my circumstances
were the same as yours.
What can I do for you?
Actually, this might not be
the best time to talk about this.
Can't you tell I'd welcome
a change in subject?
Well, good, then.
What the hell, right?
Listen, we're coming up
on two years together here.
Did you get me something?
I think we're at a point in time
where I need to know
what your plans are.
A partnership.
I think I've earned it.
Right.
I'll bring it up at the
next meeting of the partners.
Thank you.
Of course you might have to come in
and be an advocate for yourself.
I'd be proud to present
my accomplishments.
Good. Because I'm at a loss.
What is that supposed to mean?
You haven't exactly delivered
on that 30% you promised.
I think we've really performed
in a very dismal year.
These things are cyclical.
You know that.
Is there some question
about my value to Sterling Cooper?
Just think about the board.
Bert Cooper hates everyone,
and his sister, well,
she does whatever he says.
Don...
Don... he's only 121/2%, but I can't say
he's your biggest cheerleader.
- What are you saying?
- Everyone thinks you're a fine fellow.
But if I were you,
I'd go out there and make rain.
Thank you for being so candid.
This year
we have seen an historic collaboration
in American aerospace.
Building on Lockheed's
newPolaris A3,
Bell Aerosystems,
Areojet General, and NASA
have developed
a restartable rocket engine.
Can we get the lights, please?
We at Space Technology Laboratories
have set our minds to the
challenges of the future.
In July,
Khrushchev said the Soviet Union
now has an anti-missile
that can hit a fly in outer space.
Space Technology Laboratories
is leading a coordinated effort
to create an invulnerable warhead...
multiple, independently targetable
re-entry vehicles, M. I. R. V. s.
And North American Aviation's vernier
thruster allows the primary missile
to correct its trajectory before
shooting off several warheads
hidden inside its nose cone.
The M.I.R.V. can be launched from a
submarine or land into the stratosphere.
Then it splits off
into 14 individual warheads.
That's 14 different targets.
14 different cities.
14 individual warheads,
each with ten times
the payload of Nagasaki.
Even if Khrushchev hits 35%,
that's 5 out of 14.
Secondary strike capabilities
will be extremely limited...
... due to the decrease
in infrastructure and population.
Total annihilation.
Do you realize that one of these
companies spends more annually on media
than three Lucky Strikes?
It's a gold rush.
Where are the valets?
So much for cheap labor.
Go see if General Dynamics
beat us here.
Drop these by the front desk.
You don't want them under your arm.
Hello.
I think you're happy to see me.
Well, take a good look.
I have to be on my way.
Are you working?
Yes.
Oh. That's too bad.
I'm going to Palm Springs.
You should come with me.
I don't know about that.
Why would you deny yourself
something you want?
You want to get your things?
No.
Well.
Why don't we give it a few
more minutes? Enjoy the scenery.
Order some drinks.
I think Don need
to make a phone call.
Hello?
Just leave the bags there.
- Who lives here?
- Friends. They're in Sardinia.
I'm supposed to be
in Edward's room.
That's Stephanie
in the swimming pool.
And Willy and Rocci you've met.
And there's Greta
and her friend Carlos.
I'm surprised to see them
in the same place.
Come with me.
Hello, Greta.
Hello, Joy, darling.
Who's this?
This is my friend Don.
I'm Carlos Villa Declan.
It's medicinal.
Alguien importante?
Good-bye, Carlos.
Come for a swim with me?
You can go inside and ask for some
trunks, or you can goau naturel.
I think I should... go inside.
You're white as a sheet.
Don, are you okay?
Where am I?
You're with me, remember?
You have heat exhaustion.
- What are you doing?
- It's fine. It's medicine.
Klaus is a doctor.
No. It's okay. I just need
some water and some aspirin.
Everybody out.
I thought you were
going to break your neck.
Next time you feel faint,
lean towards the pool.
See you at dinner.
Little girl, don't get any ideas.
This man needs rest.
I found you some clothes upstairs.
Who are these people?
They're friends.
We're nomads together.
What are you all doing here?
There's an open door policy.
You should rest up for dinner.
Have you ever had Mexican food?
- No.
- You're going to like it.
Come out when you're ready.
You're spoiled. This is
great food. This is Mexican.
It's not. I don't like Mexican.
I wanted the French again.
Sweetheard.
Mexican does pig. I don't eat
pig. I've already told you.
Okay, well.
- Oh, he's here.
- Oh. Ah! Don!
Klaus, will you let Don sit here?
Would you like some wine, Don?
- Klaus, is that okay?
- Hmm, he looks healthy enough.
- You must be hungry.
- Everyone,
to our guest.
To not being carried out in a box.
So, Don, what's your story?
I don't know how to answer that.
Where are you from?
New York.
Try this. It's a pepper
filled with cheese.
- Darling.
- And there's the sauce.
Joy and Willy think
that you're a spy.
But your wallet fell out
when they carried you inside.
- You're in advertising.
- Or I'm a really good spy.
You'll never meet a group people
more interested in professions, and yet
there is not one of us here who has one.
I'm a physician.
But you don't work.
So I assume you're all well off.
I should take something up. I'm smarter
than I've ever been in my life.
Not only do I know so much,
- but my brain is more agile.
- And I didn't know that was possible.
And my muscles are remembering
their skills. Are you an athlete, Don?
I've played some football
in high school.
Willy was a champion fencer.
I made the Olympic team twice.
1948 London, 1952 Helsinki.
Foils.
It's hardly a sport.
Let's play places.
I start.
You have to name a place
that starts with the last letter
of the place that's named.
Guarnavaca.
Alaska.
It's not a city.
- Oh. Amalfi.
- Iran.
Naples.
- Stockholm.
- Malaga.
Athens.
Sarajevo.
Oslo.
Whoo!
Wow.
- O is impossible.
- Odessa.
Orezzo.
- Osaka.
- Oakland.
- Dunkirk.
- Kabul.
- London.
- Nice.
Essen.
Nairobi.
Itanbul.
Lisbon.
Negril.
Lausanne.
- How old are you?
- I'm 21.
How old are you?
I'm 36.
You're still warm.
Who are you?
I'm Joy.
There's glazed.
Coconut, crullers.
Oh, Bismarcks.
- Who brought these in, Cosgrove?
- I haven't seen contracts,
but this is certainly a good sign.
Gosh, Joan, thank him for me.
We're going to be getting a delivery
like this every week,
- with all the varieties.
- Hmm, Lemonaires.
Are these for us?
The spoils of victory.
8:00 in this ening.
- Excuse me?
- Our destination.
Oh. Okay.
- Where are you two going?
- To the Bob Dylan.
Isn't that interesting?
Peggy and Kurt
in the Village, oh, my.
Oh, don't be shy.
I think you two are adorable.
What is with this?
You think Peggy and I?
We do.
I'm homosexual.
I don't think that means
what you think it means.
Kurt.
No.
I make love with the man, not the woman.
What?
Eight?
Of course. Absolutely.
Enjoy the dancing beans.
Did you know about this?
He's from Europe.
It's different there.
More for me.
So Kurt is a pervert.
How about that?
He certainly had me fooled.
Mr. Cosgrove, do you want me
to invite the girls in?
I knew queers existed. I just
don't want to work with them.
What, he's the first homo
you ever met in advertising?
You think Smitty's in love?
Which bathroom does he use?
Joan, get the girls in here.
What are you reading?
William Faulkner.
I took a survey
of American literature.
So you're in school?
I was at Pembroke.
Willy has a house in Rhode Island,
so it seemed convenient.
Didn't fit.
Is it good?
Sex is good.
This book is just okay.
I like sex.
You do, too, I can tell.
Greta and Carlos are arguing.
I knew they had problems.
Greta has.
Carlos never had any.
Good morning.
Do you hear them in there?
Oh, the humiliations
have been spectacular.
Christien is coming with
the children. I hope you don't mind.
No matter how late I show up,
I'm never later than Christien.
Look at him.
You are so beautiful.
Papa, ne touche pas.
You are a brat.
She has her mother's temperament.
That's why you love me.
I make beautiful babies, don't I?
I'll see you outside.
That's your father?
He doesn't want people
to think he's old.
Yes, it's Peter Campbell from
Sterling Cooper for Clarence Hastings.
Is there any way we can meet here?
I can't drive,
and there doesn't seem to be a taxi
that will take me to Pasadena.
We can meet by the pool.
Thank you. How are you two today?
Duck Phillips.
- St. John Powell, how are you?
- Capital, capital.
This is Alec Barton.
Duck Phillips.
By Jove, man, catch up.
I have a bit of a cold.
Well, it's warm already.
It'll open up the passages.
Oh, it's warm or
he would have drunk it.
So, how are you finding New York?
Brief.
We're going to visit
a candy plant, the Cadbury.
- Then it's fate that I caught you here.
- You say fate.
I say another round, garçon.
Have mine.
If y're not drinking,
what's this about?
I keep thinking how I miss
doing things your way.
Two years ago, you said you wanted
to come here and be with your children.
They're grown.
It's not a good time.
I'm not going to take "no"
for an answer.
I wouldn't expect you to.
You know,
if we were hiring, you
would be at the top of our list.
That's too bad.
I love you New York ad men.
To our noble profession.
Cin-cin.
How old are your children?
Alec's wife is about
to have their first.
Do you think that I have
nothing to offer you?
No, of course not.
You represent
over 20 American companies,
doing business in Europe.
I know you want a U.S. presence.
You're wasting your time doing things
like digging around here for Cadbury.
And you could make a difference?
What if I were to bring you
every account at Sterling Cooper?
Fully serviced
and completely satisfied?
What are you talking about?
I'm suggesting that you
buy Sterling Cooper.
There are very few
client conflicts.
All you have to do is
change the welcome mat.
I didn't know it was for sale.
Roger Sterling has
a 20-year-old fiancée,
and his wife's lawyer's not going
to leave him a pot to piss in.
Alec, would you excuse us?
Did he send you here with a price?
Send me here?
51% will cost you a lot less than
you think, plus a finder's fee.
2%.
I want to be in charge of
all international business,
and I have to be president.
Creative reports to me,
or the whole thing falls apart.
Thank you for thinking of us.
To old friends.
Hello.
Did you have
any trouble finding me?
- Neighbors.
- Right.
- Would you like some wine?
- Very much.
Listen,
in the office, I hope
you weren't embarrassed.
No. It's okay. It's good.
Well, if you have a man
that you'd like to go to the concert
with tonight, I completely understand.
Are you not on the trip tonight?
I don't know why I pick
the wrong boys.
You're drinking sad.
I don't know.
What's wrong with me?
You are old style.
No, I'm not.
This is not modern office.
A working woman.
What are you talking about?
I fix you.
We should leave.
Each time, Bob Dylan is late.
He will not miss us a half hour.
Sit.
Look at me. I'm very good.
Just a trim.
Yes. Yes.
For you.
- Oh, my God.
- It's okay. It's good.
We're headed to Lyford Cay, Nassau.
Why?
It's what we do.
Something about taxes.
It's very different than here.
I think you'd like it.
You'll need a tuxedo.
Will I?
You don't need a passport, unless
you want to follow us to Capri after.
Stephanie's uncle's an ambassador.
Joy.
My father will take care of you.
He likes having you around.
You're beautiful,
and you don't talk too much.
I'm not possessive.
You can be with anyone you want.
Hello, Joy. Who is this?
Christien, this is Don.
Bernard and Amelia.
Hello.
Hello there.
Did Isabel ring?
Why would she?
Because I'm sick of her attorneys.
These are my children.
They should be with me.
Are you in Edward's room?
You can have it.
Thank you.
As you can see, we're very tired.
Come, Bernard.
You gave away our room?
Looks like someone
doesn't want to sleep.
Come in.
Joyce seems to have stepped away.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Crane
accidentally opened this.
Thank you, Joan.
My, oh, my. A case.
They're all there. I checked.
All the card says
is that it's for you.
Well, thank you, Miss Holway.
Why don't you just take this?
As a finder's fee.
- A whole bottle?
- It's the good stuff.
I know. Thank you.
- Anything else?
- No, thank you.
The town of Oxford
is an armed camp,
following riots that accompanied
the registration of the first Negro
in the university's
118-year history.
James H. Meredith was formally
enrolled in the University...
Hello, all.
How the hell was California?
Looks like Draper
let you off the leash.
Did you see this?
Yes, I did. Strange, isn't it?
Americans are free in short
to disagree with the law,
but not to disobey it.
So how was it?
Spectacular, business-wise, but I
don't know that I'd want to live there.
Here. These are for everybody.
I'd like to see it for myself.
What's wrong with it?
The people.
I don't know.
I'm glad to be home.
Has Don checked in? Is he here?
No. I don't think so.
... by force, or threat of force,
could long deny that man...
You look different.
It's my hair.
Right.
Kurt's a homo.
No judge would be sure of his...
So...
are you leaving us?
No.
So? What, then?
What if I told you that
the international divisions
of General Foods, Bird's Eye,
Campbell's Soup
Chevron Oil, Lever Brothers, Hoover,
Warner Brothers, Eastern Airlines
and Chrysler can all
be part of Sterling Cooper?
How is that possible?
St. John Powell,
of Putnam, Powell, and Lowe,
called me the other day.
They want to open up a New York office
to deal with their American clients.
They love the idea of just sticking
a key in the door at Sterling Cooper.
Really?
Is this as solid
as American Airlines?
I guess you're happy having to scramble
on the third tier of this industry
waiting for minor divisions
of major companies to drop in your lap.
On the table will be
mountains of money,
international prestige,
a chance at going public, and we
don't have to change our name.
- I guess we could think about it.
- No.
I need to know
that you're open to this.
If so, I'm giving them
five business days to try to impress us
with a price for controlling
interest in the agency.
There he is.
There's the man
I heard so much about.
Five days to make an offer.
Or you can give me a price
and I'll pass it on.
No.
Let them open the kimono.
Daddy! Daddy! Over here!
This water is cold.
Stop splashing!
Don't do it, darling.
Hello. It's Dick Whitman.
Yeah.
I'd love to see you.
Soon.
No. I didn't bring it
with me. Hold on.
I'll see you soon.