Previously on Nip / Tuck:
This is a business.
A very good business that is
on the verge of setting us up for life.
Maybe I don't want to be
in this business anymore.
We didn't give you a circumcision
because you were six weeks premature.
Just give me something that I need.
I'm not one of your patients, Sean!
I'm your wife!
And on your watch, a death has occurred,
the death of you and me.
-How's the sensitivity?
-Fine.
Your partner didn't go back to your office.
Where did he go?
We have to go to the police.
No. I am not going down for this.
What do we do?
I think we should hire
a full-time psychologist to screen better.
And I want 20% of our client base
to be pro bono from now on.
Dr. McNamara, you wanted to see me?
Dr. Pendleton, please put on your mask.
Sorry. I haven't been
in too many surgeries.
That's exactly the reason
I thought you'd like to observe today.
It's vital you know the risks and rewards
of our procedures...
if you're going to counsel our patients.
Are we doing
a breast augmentation today?
Actually, we're correcting one.
Jesus, she looks like Murray Feltman.
This patient received C implants
a month ago.
Before the gels could set properly...
her abusive boyfriend
pushed her against a wall so hard...
that the implant
ruptured through the capsular wall.
We're repairing the damage
and the capsular wall pro bono.
Liz, how deep's the patient?
It's Marie, and she's ready when you are.
Sorry.
Liz was our previous anesthesiologist.
We begin by cutting into the nipple.
Oh, shit!
-Good hire, Sean.
-What's wrong?
Other than the new mandate
that all patients...
have to be psychologically screened
and approved by both of us?
I have a consult in my office.
Step in when you're finished.
Miss Dante, tell me
what you don't like about yourself.
It's not that I don't like myself.
I just don't want to look like her anymore.
Yeah, and I don't want
to look like her, either.
See, we've made this agreement.
-I want to change my face.
-And I want to change my body.
We were thinking it would be so great
if one of us could wear a miniskirt...
and not feel self-conscious
about our chicken legs.
So l'd like bigger calves,
and l'd also like to go up to a C cup.
And I was thinking
that maybe I could have her ears...
'cause they don't stick out
like ours do, see?
See?
And I like her nose.
That is Jennifer Garner.
-She kicks ass!
-She so kicks ass!
I tore that picture out of teen Vogue
magazine so you guys could copy it.
Miss Dante, Miss Dante, l'd like you
to come back later in the week...
and meet Dr. Pendleton,
our on-site psychologist.
lnterestingly enough, Mandi and Randi
have already given me...
the contact information
of their own psychologist.
Yeah, and she's completely cool
with the fact...
that we're sick and tired of going through
our lives being mistaken for each other.
Even our own father
can't even tell us apart.
They are going
to the University of Miami in the fall...
and they believe
that now is the perfect time...
for them to establish
their own singular identities.
Not to play devil's advocate,
but have you tried less drastic measures?
For instance,
maybe styling your hair differently.
Didn't work. I mean,
people still confuse me with Randi.
We even went as far as to get tattoos.
And they were pretty much worthless.
Why were they worthless?
We realized that people could only use
them to tell us apart if we're naked.
God, it's good to be back!
Heads up.
-What's this?
-It's a prophylactic, Matt.
Yeah, I know what it is, Dad.
Why did you give it to me?
You're worried about your girl's reaction
to your foreskin in the first time, right?
You responsibly slip this on
when that time comes...
she won't even know.
Once you get your sea legs,
you can be confident enough...
to initiate a conversation
about what foreskin is...
and how it really won't affect her pleasure.
-How does it look now?
-Hey, that looks great.
Just want to write something on the top.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
What are you guys drawing over there?
It's so we can find Frisky.
Don't worry, honey, he'll show up.
Jules, that smell is terrible. We gotta get
a plumber out here to fix the toilet.
It's the entire septic system.
It's completely backed up.
Can you get someone out here this week?
Sure, Sean. Can you pick up
the dry cleaning today?
Sure.
Are you getting the jump
on Easter, Jules?
I'm starting a new business with Suzanne.
-Crazy Suzanne?
-Creative Suzanne.
What kind of business?
They're gift baskets for women,
and they're very popular right now.
There's a real market for them.
Well, Jules, I think that's great.
You can work out of the home...
and be with the kids. That's great.
I can go back to school
and be with the kids, too, Sean.
My priorities aren't changing that greatly.
Christ!
God, this is ridiculous. Why don't
you guys just go to marriage counseling?
Because marital counseling never works.
It's just a way for people
to figure out how to break up.
You're helping no one
by doing what you're doing.
Stop dealing in stupid half-measures
and either shit or get off the pot.
He said the "brown" word.
Yeah, I did. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I haven't seen you here in a while,
Christian. You look like an albino.
I had a work-related injury.
But now I'm back on my game
and resuming my regular activities.
Can I interest you
in our mystique tan today?
Just a regular bed for me, sweetheart.
I'm a traditionalist.
How about some...
tanning accelerator lotion, then?
Well, Janelle...
that all depends.
Does it come with an application?
Don't worry. I'll turn you over
when the timer goes off.
-Too early in the morning for you, baby?
-Help me out a little.
Christian, can you help me out here?
I'm getting lockjaw.
Dr. Santiago, how long
have you been treating the Dante sisters?
Three years, at the Miami free clinic.
I'm the director there.
I think physical change is a last resort,
but in their case, it's a necessary one.
How so?
Last year, they both lost their virginity
to the same person...
a 40-year-old fetishist
they met in a twins chat room...
who promised to love them both equally,
and he did.
They felt like shit about it,
and they decided...
that they wanted to be different
and not interchangeable.
Half-measures have ceased to work.
So you don't believe in half-measures?
I believe in committing fully to change.
It's the commitment
that brings constructive results.
lf Mandi and Randi can look
in the mirror and see singular reflection...
only then are they going to be able to
view themselves as whole and not halves.
I'm still debating. Go ahead.
-I'll have the sea bass and a Pellegrino.
-All right.
And I'll have a hamburger, fries,
and a margarita.
You got it.
You know what?
I'll have what she's having.
-Sure.
-I don't have any surgeries this afternoon.
-One margarita will be fine. You?
-I need to drink.
I have an ADD patient right after this
who spends half the session...
lining up the Kleenex box just so,
and the remaining 20 minutes...
recounting how he obsessively thinks
about me while he's masturbating.
You must get that a lot.
Attention Deficit Disorder patients.
I want to try it.
Okay.
Where are you going?
I was gonna get a condom.
I want to see it first.
Okay. Yeah, sure.
lt looks like a Shar-Pei.
Are you part Arab or something?
No.
Does it turn you off that I'm not...
circumcised?
No, not at all.
Maybe we should just make out today.
This isn't your father's coffeepot. lt
actually grinds the beans in the machine.
It's amazing what you can afford
when you nix a steam room...
and put that money
towards something more practical.
That cost more than my car.
What a perk it would've been...
to hang out in here and have
a double macchiato in between tit jobs.
A macchiato, you say?
Sean, why did you ask me here today?
To make you an offer. lf you come back,
I'll double your salary.
That sounds like hush money, Sean.
You're an invaluable part of the team.
You're the best anesthesiologist
l've ever worked with.
And as an additional bonus...
I'll throw in something
you've always wanted:
Complete health benefits
for your partner, Jean.
Jan.
I can't work this goddamn thing.
I'll do it.
Jan and I broke up.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm not.
For 15 years, I put up with
her pot smoking and her cynicism...
and finally, two weeks ago...
I just said, "Honey, I love you,
but I am not in love with you."
What got into you?
Someone pushed a gun into my temple.
You might remember
that moment, Sean. You were there.
l've never really...
apologized for putting you
in that situation, Liz.
No, you didn't.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, Sean.
Actually, it was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
A shift has happened in me. I can feel it.
I broke up with Jan
because I want to be in love deeply.
I sold my condo. I'm moving to the beach
'cause that's always what l've wanted...
and I figured, "What are you waiting for?"
What happened that night
got me thinking.
What if I can't put off stuff
until tomorrow...
because I don't get another tomorrow?
I felt similarly.
What happened
really changed my outlook.
Yeah.
Well, there's a big difference
between changing your outlook...
and changing your life, Sean.
Where are you gonna stay?
A hotel for tonight,
and then I don't know.
This is so typical of you, Sean.
You don't even show me
the respect you show a patient.
At least with a patient, you tell them
what the diagnosis is before you operate.
Let's just cut the shit, Julia,
starting right now.
You want out of this marriage.
lf you didn't, you'd fight for us.
But instead, all you do is fight with me.
Fighting denotes communication,
which you don't do!
We've talked in circles. I'm dizzy from it.
I have no perspective anymore.
You're a goddamn hypocrite.
And I am miserable with you!
And you are miserable with me,
and the big difference is, let's just say it...
you're content in your misery, Julia.
l'd rather separate and try and figure out
a way to make us connect again.
We have to change this,
or we die on the vine.
And if you're too paralyzed
to take any action, I will.
What about the kids?
I'm not abdicating my role as a father.
-Of course I'll see them.
-For one hour a week, like you do now?
Don't I get a say in any of this?
You do get a say.
Say you're still in love with me,
and I'll stay.
Have you ever done twins?
Mother and daughter once,
but never twins.
I left last night.
I left my family.
I swore I wouldn't turn into my asshole
of a father, and God help me.
How did Julia take it?
She's hurt, angry, afraid.
You gonna get a divorce,
or is this just another separation?
I just want to feel something again.
Hey, celebrate, you dumb mick.
You're a single doctor now.
Translation: ass galore.
I can't just turn into you, Christian.
I'm not that guy.
Now's your chance.
Welcome back.
At double the salary,
how could a lady refuse?
I'll do facial, you do bodywork?
10 Blade.
Scalpel.
ls it fixed?
No, it's a wicked, big clog.
I had to run out and get a bigger snake.
Don't be embarrassed, Julia.
Joe used to clog up the toilet, too,
and leave it for me to fix.
It's not until they leave
that you realize how much you've settled.
I'm sorry, Suzanne.
Why are we putting these eye masks
in our baskets?
You get a hot flash.
You pop it out of the fridge...
and onto your eyes.
Menopausal women will love them.
-Mrs. McNamara.
-Yeah?
I fixed your clog...
and I found this.
What's she gonna do with a turd,
bronze it? Jesus!
It's a gerbil. My daughter has one.
Annie lost her gerbil, right?
I saw the sign outside.
Poor Frisky!
lt must've climbed up and fallen in.
No, that's impossible.
Gerbils can't climb porcelain.
There's no traction for their claws.
Somebody threw this in.
I saw a boy's bike outside the house.
You have a teenage son,
isn't that right, Mrs. McNamara?
I don't want to freak you out about this...
but they say Ted Bundy
started out this way.
Torturing small animals.
Oh, my God. Matt.
My son didn't do it.
I did.
You accidentally ran it over when
you were vacuuming or something, right?
And you didn't want Annie to know.
See, that explains it.
lt wasn't an accident.
There'll be no charge.
I don't want your money.
What kind of mother are you?
Why won't you give me the circumcision?
He doesn't even have to know.
Carving up your dick
is a little more telltale...
than buying you a six-pack on the sly.
Hi, I'll have a Dewar's straight up.
He'll have a Coke. I'll have
the Dewar's, sweetheart. Thank you.
Besides, I'm of the opinion that
your father's right about this one.
You don't need a circumcision.
lf you guys won't help me,
I'll go to another surgeon.
Who will operate without a signed
parental consent form. Good luck.
The problem isn't your dick, Matty.
It's your confidence.
You were timid and embarrassed.
She saw that and it turned her off.
Thanks.
Why are we here?
Because we are gonna
work on the confidence part.
-You're kidding me, right?
-Au contraire, my little Virginator.
l've arranged for you
to just get it out of the way.
A bang under your belt, and I believe...
you'll be able
to bicycle over to Vanessa's place...
grab that peachy ass,
and show her how it's done with no fear.
Girls don't care
if you have a two-inch pecker...
a hairy ass, or balls like cranberries.
What they care about
is that you know what you're doing.
-So, which girl?
-Behind me, on the stairs.
Her name's Avanti.
Rumor has it
she can suck the peel off an apple.
I feel entirely creepy about
paying someone to pretend they like me.
No. Hey, besides, man,
I'm not gonna cheat on Vanessa.
I love her.
Haven't you ever had that?
Once.
Hey, papi.
-Hey.
Yeah, thank you...
but, no.
No, thank you.
Fair enough.
lf you'll excuse me, I'm gonna go upstairs
and pay someone to pretend they like me.
What's wrong, baby? You like boys?
I think you like boys.
Come on, baby,
why can't you get caliente?
Because you've got a carved face,
and in my estimation...
that's the worst tit job l've ever seen.
Here's my business card.
You want to look like a woman
instead of a carnival freak, call me.
Mr. Brancato, l've invited
our psychologist, Dr. Pendleton...
to sit in on our consultation.
Mr. Brancato, tell me what
you don't like about yourself.
It's my dick.
I hate my dick.
You feel it's inadequate?
Would you like to show us?
lt looked like one of those
summer blood sausages...
you get in the Hickory Farms
Christmas gift sampler baskets.
How many enlargement surgeries
has this guy been through?
Five. He wants us to harvest fat
from his glutes and inject it into his shaft.
lf he can't go longer, he'll go wider.
Dr. McNamara, I take issue
with your condescending tone.
Mr. Brancato's not to be pitied.
Are you saying you're for
giving him the operation?
-That wouldn't be my recommendation.
-Why, Sean?
Because you find it personally disturbing?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but didn't you hire Dr. Pendleton...
to make recommendations
based on psychological profiling?
That's what he's doing.
Dr. Pendleton, as you were saying....
With every operation,
as his penis becomes larger...
Mr. Brancato takes a personal risk.
lf he needs a self-esteem boost...
to actually make a positive change
in his life, I say we give it to him.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go for a jog...
and let my miso dressing set for an hour.
Dr. Pendleton, l'd like to join you,
if you don't mind.
That would be nice. Thank you.
I'll catch up.
lf you have issue
with something I do or say...
take it up with me privately.
Not in front of our staff.
Absolutely. And likewise,
l'd appreciate it...
if you could send me a memo
notifying me of staff salary increases.
lf calling Mr. Brancato and scheduling
surgery is too distasteful for you...
I'm happy to do it.
You agreed we needed to rethink our
ethical philosophy here. I'm doing that.
I'm fine with hiring a shrink
and doing pro bono...
as long as we take on other cases
to finance your sainthood.
I'm playing your game. Once in a while,
throw me the goddamn ball.
Really? So, you're telling me...
you couldn't even get it up
for some hot geisha gash like that?
My urologist says it's psychological.
I'm sorry. I feel like we're
crossing the professional line here.
You're my employer.
That's right. I pay your salary.
So give me my money's worth.
I think I know why this is happening.
I just don't know how to fix it.
Recently, a married woman
threw herself at my jock.
I passed...
but since then I find myself thinking
about her when I'm with someone else.
She's mentally stalking me.
The problem is further complicated
as she's the wife of one of my friends.
Quod me nutrit me destruit.
Sorry, I was never an altar boy.
It's Latin for
"that which nourishes me, destroys me."
You have two choices.
You can destroy your friendship
and nourish your sexual appetite...
by banging the horny housewife.
Or, you can nourish your friendship...
and destroy the sexual fantasy
by rejecting her.
And once you choose, once you're firm...
that feeling will be reciprocated
in your Dockers.
That'll be $150, and I'm not available
the entire month of August.
Three sugars, right?
I don't drink coffee.
Three sugars in your iced tea.
Now I remember. I'll get some.
Does Sean know you're stopping by?
No.
Should we call him and tell him?
Thanks.
Look, about the other day...
my exam was unprofessional,
and I apologize.
Don't. You saved me
from an excruciating operation.
I'm the one who should be sorry
for not calling you when you were sick.
-The Bell's palsy thing?
-Right.
A few weeks of antivirals later,
I'm back on my game.
And a legion of thong-wearing
cocktail waitresses rejoice.
Sorry.
Hey, it's okay.
-You were married almost 16 years.
-No. I'm not crying about him.
They kicked me out.
Who?
The mothers in my kindergarten carpool.
Suzanne told them what had happened,
and then they said...
they felt nervous about trusting
their kids' safety to a murderer.
-Back up. Who got killed?
-Frisky.
-Frisky, the gerbil?
-Yes!
I don't know. lt just kept shitting,
and I felt overwhelmed, and I flushed him.
I'm a terrible person.
You're not a terrible person.
I just think you make bad,
if understandable, choices sometimes.
You have a history of that.
Come on. Drink my tea and sit with me.
What happened to the girl I knew,
the most confident thing I ever saw?
Who was, and is, by the way,
going back to medical school?
Who used to sing at the top of her lungs
to Fleetwood Mac...
even though she was tone deaf?
Who made me forget
there was ever another girl in the room?
I miss us...
the way we used to be.
Then let's fix that. Tomorrow.
7:00.
My place.
We'll grill steaks
and get shitfaced on merlot.
Okay.
You're still in there.
I see you even if you don't.
Shit.
I gotta go check on a couple of patients.
Are you....
Hard? Yeah.
We'll pick this up tomorrow night.
Hello!
Hey, Matt. I was wondering
if you were free for lunch tomorrow?
I'll pick you up at school.
We can go to Joe Stonecrab's.
You like that place, right?
Tomorrow's no good for me, Dad.
Okay, how about Friday?
I need to talk to you about
what's happening to our family, Matt.
We don't need to play catch-up. I get it.
You and Mom can't stand each other
anymore. You bailed.
We'll talk later, okay?
I gotta study.
He didn't notice me.
Who didn't notice you?
The male nurse.
When he came in,
he didn't even look at me!
She's prettier than me now.
She's prettier!
You misunderstood, sweetheart.
I'm Mandi! Don't call me sweetheart
because you can't remember my name!
We just wanna go back
to the way we were.
And we wanna be treated the same.
Please help us.
Please.
This is Matt. He's 16, going on 40.
And this is Annie. She's seven.
ls your son the mailman's?
Yeah, we laugh about that.
My wife, who I'm separated from...
is Black lrish on her father's side.
My daughter looks like her, too.
Actually, she looks a lot like you.
She's beautiful.
This really wasn't necessary.
This place is expensive.
You helped me a lot with the Dante twins.
It's the least I could do.
Actually...
I hope to do it again.
l'd like that.
What are you doing?
Did I read something wrong here?
I thought there was
an attraction thing going on.
lnteresting, because I thought
we were being professionals.
Did you think that I kept meeting with you
because I wanted to get laid?
I thought you respected me.
I do.
No. Apparently, you don't.
I actually thought these second opinions
could lead to better work.
Most people, they get paid
for their consultations.
Please don't.
lf my share is more than that, bill me.
When are you gonna start dating again?
Dating? I'm not dating. Who's dating?
Corpse isn't even cold.
Believe me, I understand change is hard.
Sometimes you just need
a strong jolt to move forward.
By jolt you mean shock?
Yes. Like finding out
that Julia is dating again.
Maybe that would make it easier
for you to get back on the horse.
-Would you like to know if she is?
-ls she?
How would I know? I haven't talked to her.
I'm just musing, theoretically.
No, I don't want to know if she is dating.
I can honestly say that would kill me.
-Dr. McNamara, congratulations!
-For what?
For operating on Joe Brancato
and admitting your mistake.
Taking ownership of personal error
is the first step...
toward healthy growth and change.
Good job, buddy.
Dr. Pendleton...
you're fired.
You look spiffy.
-Where're you off to tonight?
-I have a business dinner with Suzanne.
I should be back by 10:00.
Dinner is in the fridge.
Heat it up for five minutes at 350°.
And, Matt, don't show Annie
The Exorcist again.
She needs to know that evil exists.
Okay.
I know your dad and I separating
really sucks for you.
I'm sorry we didn't do this better.
Hey, Mom.
Do you have any cuticle scissors?
-Why do you need those?
-Why do you think?
I have a hangnail.
Upstairs bathroom.
Third drawer on the right.
l've been waiting for an hour.
Why didn't the guard let me in?
l've had stalkers before,
but they were patients, not fellow doctors.
That guy, last night, that wasn't me.
I haven't had a date
since Reagan was in office.
-I'm bad at it.
-What do you want?
To tell you how sorry I am.
lt won't happen again.
I don't want your apologies.
Then how about a job?
-Hi.
I thought we said 7:30.
7:00. We said 7:00.
Did you think it was easy
for me to come here?
What did you think
you were coming over here for?
I'm sorry you had to catch me in the
middle of a Doublemint moment there.
But let's not fool ourselves.
That's who I am. Always will be.
You want a regular Friday-night date
and a father for your kids...
stay with Sean.
When did you become so cruel?
-What are you doing?
-I'm moving back in.
Might not be able to change me,
but I can change me in this marriage.
I realized I'm not a single guy
who wants a new life.
I'm a married man who wants to fix
this family. That's what I'm gonna do.
I don't want a fix. I want you out!
I want you to take your pettiness,
and your control issues...
and your sad, lonely midlife crisis,
and get out of my house!
And notice, I said "my house," Sean.
Because I'm not selling it and splitting
the difference when we get a divorce.
This is not California, buddy.
I put you through medical school...
and this is all I have to show for it.
-You want a divorce?
-Yeah! You should be happy, Sean.
You'll be legally free
to screw every hot 20-year-old...
that waltzes through your office.
How it must kill you
that Christian gets the pick of the litter.
-Hey, calm down.
-Let go of me!
-I don't wanna screw around.
-Yeah? Well, maybe I do.
You always were a lousy lay, Sean.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
You're either a liar or a very good actress.
I know your body. I always have.
I know right where you live and breathe.
Then why haven't I had an orgasm
in two years?
Because I didn't wanna work that hard.
Right there.
That's where you like it, isn't it?
Hey. How's it going?
You've logged on
to Joey's Self-Circumcision web page...
a guide for guys like me
who have a foreskin problem...
and are too embarrassed
to have their doctor do the duty.
First things first, guys. Relax.
A shaking hand means you could slip.
I took a mild muscle relaxant.
But other guys I know
have fared well on a glass of red wine.
Be smooth and confident.
Your surgical tools have to be sharpened
to razor sharpness.
When you do this, the cuts are
virtually painless and bleed very little.
I didn't use ice or anything.
There was no need.
For the first cut,
grip the foreskin and pull it out.
Cut in a circular motion,
removing a thin quarter-inch strip.
Rip youyoup