Previously on Nip / Tuck:
-Are you a doctor?
-Plastic surgeon.
Girls don't care
if you have a 2-inch pecker...
a hairy ass, or balls like cranberries.
What they care about
is that you know what you're doing.
You ever done twins?
Mother and daughter once,
but never twins.
-Hi.
How do you seduce women?
It's about charm, Sean, and confidence.
You wine, you dine, you romance.
Julia needs that.
She's clearly starved for it.
-How do you know that?
-Every woman is.
God, it's good to be back.
Tell me what you don't like about yourself.
My eyes.
Mr. Dempsey, what exactly do you think
is wrong with them?
I'd like them to look more like hers.
It's for my parents, actually.
We're very close, and they are....
-Traditional?
-Xenophobic.
Her mother's Nisei. She was born
in a Japanese-American internment camp.
Her family lost everything,
their home, their business, their dignity.
She's always disapproved of any man
I went out with who wasn't Japanese.
I just can't take the chance this time.
Not with him.
Not when you've found the one.
Miss Moriata, if he's the one...
why not elope
and then introduce him to your mother?
It's a lot more reasonable than asking
your fiancé to rearrange his face.
The last man I was serious about
was also white.
She said if I married him,
I will never see her again.
Our children will never know their family.
I can't let Leigh
make that kind of sacrifice...
when I can prevent it
by having this operation.
lt isn't quite so simple, Mr. Dempsey.
There's no guarantee that the surgery,
no matter how good a job we do...
is going to adequately convince
Leigh's mother that you're Japanese.
I'd hate to put you through the pain
and trauma of an operation...
and not have it come out
the way you'd like it to.
And the procedure
is somewhat uncommon...
so there would be some extra expense.
Whatever the cost.
-Maybe you should think about it.
-My mind's made up.
Haven't you ever loved someone so much
that you're willing to do anything...
to keep from losing them?
Mom, I can't find my pyramid.
I don't know what you did with it.
I'll be right there, Annie.
I'm just a little busy at the moment.
Shit.
It's real.
-Yes.
-You weren't even looking, were you?
I have firsthand knowledge.
You know, women in this country,
they've got no modesty.
-God bless America.
-You interested?
I'm looking for something higher
on the food chain.
-What about you, Victor?
-I'm through looking.
You're only engaged.
Monogamy doesn't go into effect
until after the wedding.
-Susannah doesn't see it that way.
-She'll never know.
Yeah, she bloody will.
After you commit,
it don't matter what you wash with...
they smell infidelity on you like cat piss.
I get it. Two of you are just jealous...
because I get all I want
whenever I want it.
Ever notice
how monogamy rhymes with monotony?
I feel sorry for you, man.
-Obviously, you've never been in love.
-Of course I have.
It's that beautiful moment between
meeting the woman of your dreams...
and seeing her stretch marks.
-Does Susannah give you head?
-All the time.
Well, don't get too used to it.
Once you say "I do," they say "I don't."
Untrue. Some of the best blowjobs
I've had were from married women.
Americans don't know
the meaning of oral sex.
Okay, here we go.
So everything European is better,
right, Serge? Cigarettes? Wine?
German women, they're the best.
Speaking, of course,
as the expert on international head.
Has to do with their ability
to follow orders.
Excuse me, gentlemen,
but that poor girl looks parched.
I'd better buy her a drink.
Don't you ever get tired of it, man?
The whole
who-am-l-gonna-lay-tonight scene?
Yes, Victor, I do.
I get absolutely exhausted.
It's not just peas and corn, people.
Mendel and McClintock have provided us
with the key to understanding...
how physical appearance,
metabolic capacity, and intelligence...
are passed on from parents to offspring.
Of course, we're talking about
inherent potential...
which some organisms may reach,
while others will not.
Someone's been studying, I see.
Well, I guess I know who I'll be
sitting next to during the MCATs.
Better pick someone else.
No, listen, I promise I'll only copy
questions on Mendel and McClintock.
Why don't we discuss it over lunch?
-Have you ever been to Tantra?
-Oh, Jude, I'm--
No, it's great. They got this movie of the
Kamasutra playing in the dining room.
Perfect place to discuss reproduction.
Look, Jude, I'm flattered in every way.
But you'd just be wasting your time.
I'm probably
not even going to med school.
So what are you gonna do
with all that beauty and brains?
I don't know.
Pass them on to my offspring?
Apparently, she left him for someone else.
If she looked like this,
he probably paid the guy to abduct her.
-What would make someone do this?
-Love.
He was obviously
deeply in love with Toyota.
The butt crack's tough to read.
It's a sign of commitment.
Maybe it was his way of telling the world
he'd met his soul mate.
Whom we'll now scrape off his back...
along with two layers of skin
down to the dermis.
You and Julia love each other.
I don't see you branding
each other's names all over your butts.
Then again, I haven't showered
with either of you since college.
We discussed it before we got married.
She thought I was crazy.
I would've done it.
I have a tattoo on my right breast.
-Two female symbols intertwined.
-Double dykes.
I'm expressing my lesbian identity.
Excuse me. I have a couple
who have been waiting an hour.
They want to talk to one of you.
You go. I can do this.
So can l. You go.
Well, I need one of you.
They've read the brochure so many times,
they've memorized it.
Things won't improve unless
you work on them. You're not even trying.
Believe me, if I wasn't trying,
she'd be dead by now.
The car was totaled.
People who saw what happened
couldn't believe I just walked away.
I just thank God she's alive.
I don't know how I'd make it without her.
Nothing else broken?
-No, just my nose.
-I see.
Since it has to be reset anyway,
if that is the right expression...
I was hoping you could do something
to make it a little cuter.
-Your nose couldn't be any cuter.
-Never mind him.
I had a zit the size of Mt. Saint Helens
that he thought was adorable.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Let's see.
Maybe we could take off a little here.
-And then--
-Any other side effects from the accident?
Dreams? lnability to focus?
Undue fear? Sleeplessness?
No.
Excuse me, Dr. Santiago,
I'd assumed you'd asked these questions...
while they were waiting for me
to get out of surgery.
I tell you what. I'll talk it over
with my partner, Dr. McNamara...
and we'll schedule you for surgery.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Anything you'd like to add, Dr. Santiago?
-Not a thing.
-Excellent.
Thank you, Dr. Troy.
Make sure Nurse Linda
gets all your information.
-This way.
-Thank you.
I see no problem
after a life-threatening accident.
A little change can be therapeutic.
Dr. Santiago, do me a favor.
When a patient is waiting for me...
for whatever reason, please begin
your consultation in your office.
-And when I'm through?
-Stay there.
-What?
-Nothing.
I was just thinking, it's a shame
turtlenecks aren't in style anymore.
Hi, honey. These are for you.
That was a joke.
Thank you. They're lovely.
You shouldn't have gone to the trouble.
-What the hell is that stink?
-Decay.
I kept meaning to throw them out, but....
You need some help?
Why don't I set the table.
Hey, you got an A.
Minus.
Still, I'm impressed.
-It's just one test.
-Is this the teacher you knew in college?
lt was multiple-choice,
in case you think she showed favoritism.
I meant you've always been
a great student. Better than me.
-That was a long time ago.
-You've obviously still got potential.
You know what potential is, Sean?
Nothing.
Just wishful thinking.
A possibility that doesn't exist
unless it's fulfilled.
The truth about the acorn is the tree.
-Remember? Junior year Philosophy?
-Nietzsche?
-Hegel.
-I rest my case.
But just look at us, Sean.
I'm still the acorn
and you became the tree.
You want to go to med school?
We'll make it happen.
You've got my support financially,
emotionally, whatever it takes.
I'm pregnant.
Hey, what's for supper?
What's that smell?
Did something die in here or what?
So you guys ready
to turn Charlie Brown into Pokémon?
Does anyone here besides me
think it's morally reprehensible...
for a white man
to pass himself off as a victim...
of the American racial hierarchy?
Tell her to quit using
those big words around me.
-It's our job to alleviate pain.
-That's your answer?
Why don't we just turn everyone
white and hetero?
We can change
the obstacle that separates this guy...
from the one thing he wants.
I see nothing wrong in doing that.
-Liz, you shave under your arms?
-Of course.
Why, trying to pass yourself off
as being straight?
Keep talking.
You are so close to a harassment suit.
Could you act professional
around her for a change?
Is that too much to ask?
Who pissed in your CREAM OF WHEAT
this morning?
Julia's pregnant.
Congratulations.
Or should I not say congratulations?
I don't know, actually.
Is Julia excited?
It's complicated. I mean,
she started taking these premed courses.
This was supposed to be her time to,
you know, do her thing.
That was sort of the plan.
So she's ambivalent.
Timing has never been my strong suit
as far as Julia getting pregnant.
Like with Matt, remember?
What you said back then really helped.
I can't imagine my life now without him.
I just told you
what you wanted to hear, that's all.
Well, do it again.
You mean talk you out of
pushing Julia into having an abortion?
Yeah.
I don't think I can.
You were in a different place back then.
-You guys were young. You were in love.
-We're still in love.
Listen, if your gut is telling you
something is not right, maybe it isn't.
Or maybe it is. Maybe it'll give us
something good to focus on.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you haven't exactly been Superdad.
So I'll do better this time. People change.
Faces change, and asses and thighs,
but people? Come on, Sean.
You think he'll be Japanese
'cause we make him look Asian?
No one changes. We are who we are.
Oh, my God!
It's considered a courtesy for the person
who finishes the pot to make more.
Is it? I just assumed you had a coffee girl
who provided you with that service.
No, we don't.
Odd. I'd have thought
making coffee would be...
a lot more difficult than watering plants.
Jasmine's special.
She has a gift for making things grow.
Are you repeatedly flaunting
this adolescent behavior...
in front of me because a woman
has invaded your boys' club?
If it makes you feel too uncomfortable,
feel free to leave.
I'm sure that Sean will give you
a glowing recommendation.
I hope you'll take this
in the spirit in which it is intended.
I can tell you going any further
with that sentence is a mistake.
The Presbyterian Church
on 64th and Collins has S.A. meetings...
every night from 8:00 to 9:00.
Sexaholics Anonymous.
I'm speaking to you as a professional,
Christian. I think you've got a problem.
Do you know how many men
would give their right nut for my problem?
Too much sex is as strong an indication
of intimacy problems as too little.
I've given you the information.
What you do with it is up to you.
Dr. Santiago, perhaps you should consider
having your own orgasm...
every now and then so that you don't
have to live through mine.
-Hey.
Listen, I've been giving it
a lot of thought...
and I think we should have the baby.
I have, too, Sean,
been giving it a lot of thought.
Come on, Jules. I think it'll be good for us.
-Us?
-Yeah. Just what we need.
I'm not sure you know what I need, Sean.
I like being back at school.
When am I gonna take the MCATs,
when I'm 50?
Who's stopping you?
You're always working.
You have no idea
what it takes to raise a child.
The energy, the patience.
How much of yourself you have to give up.
I don't think I can do it again.
I'll stay home.
I'll take off as much time as we need.
There's no reason for you to give up
being a doctor if that's what you want.
You'll stay home?
Don't say it if you don't mean it.
I have no intention of missing out
this time around.
Macallan 18?
-You know your scotch.
-I know my scotch drinkers.
You don't remember me, do you?
Shelly Edwards.
I came to your office a couple of years ago
to have something done...
in exchange
for you having a little something done.
An awfully good time.
Till I made the fatal mistake
of asking if you had any feelings for me.
Eyes, chin.
Especially nice job on the jaw line.
Shelly Edwards, of course.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
Underneath the ruins?
So, think you could freshen me up?
Same arrangement?
I don't think so.
-Raised your prices?
-No.
Prices are the same.
-The currency's--
-Changed.
It's late.
I've got surgery tomorrow morning.
Remember my daughter?
Seventeen now.
Looks just like I used to.
Not a mark on her, tight as a drum.
You ever have
a mother-daughter, Christian?
You can have both of us, baby.
Two for one.
I know just how you like it.
I'll show her.
...serenity to accept the things
I cannot change...
courage to change the things I can...
and the wisdom to know the difference.
-Hi, I'm Gina.
-Hi, Gina.
Before we begin, I'd like to ask
if there are any new people here...
could you please raise your hands?
I left halfway through
my first time here, too.
Then I went out and got laid.
I was considering that,
but I have surgery in the morning.
Oh, boy.
They must cream their panties
when they hear that.
They do.
However, it's frequently the truth.
So, how's it usually go?
Girl meets surgeon, surgeon bangs girl...
surgeon has great excuse
to leave before dawn?
Am I close?
We go to my place, and I give her cab fare.
A gentleman. Nice.
So, how many women
have you slept with in the last year?
Like you said, I'm a gentleman.
How about in the last month?
I'll go home
and count the notches on my bedpost.
Last week?
I bet you're searching
for that special someone.
The one who's hotter and smarter
and better than the one you're with.
You're good.
Since I started the program,
things have changed.
I don't go home with anyone
who reinforces my low self-image.
I don't blow anyone off because he has
the bad taste to actually like me.
I've gone eight months
without a one-nighter.
Here's my number.
You want a sponsor, give me a call.
-Hello?
-Want to go for a drink...
Sponsor?
A plastic surgeon. Perfect.
God, I must have wanted you to see
my flaws and find me repulsive. Shit!
You're not repulsive. I said we could
do something about your stretch marks.
Eight months of meetings,
my life was finally under control.
Under who's control?
The anonymous sex-crazed sycophants
who meet once a week...
to group-think
their way out of desperation?
Well, I would not expect you
to believe in a higher power.
You already think you're God.
Here.
What the hell is that?
Cab fare.
You're throwing me out?
I really do have surgery in four hours.
If I don't get some sleep...
I could wind up scarring someone for life.
And you're not scarring me for life?
No, forget it. I am not leaving.
I have too much self-respect for that.
That's it. Come on!
Time to 12-step your way out of here.
You are a narcissistic bastard,
you know that?
You want the wisdom
to know the difference between...
what you can and can't change?
Here's Step 13: Everything disappears.
Love, trees, rocks, steel, plastic...
human beings. None of us get out alive.
You can huddle in a group
and face it one day at a time...
or you can be grateful that when
your body rubs against somebody else's...
it explodes with enough pleasure
to make you forget even for a minute...
that you're only a walking pile of ashes.
Now, that is the truth.
If you're strong, it'll make you free.
If you're weak, it'll make you...
you.
You still got my number, right?
Just wanted to tell you the work
you did yesterday on that cleft palate...
-didn't suck.
-Flatterer.
And Julia and l
have decided to have the baby.
If that's what you guys want, then...
congratulations.
And I want to take some time off
for paternity leave.
At least three months.
We'll hire somebody.
Plastic surgeons
aren't your standard office temps.
You can't put an ad in the paper saying:
"Must type 70 words a minute
and do mammoplasty."
I'm gonna make this work, Christian.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
I'll do everything I can to minimize it.
I'd love to feel you're behind my doing it,
but even if you're not...
I'm doing it anyway.
Shit!
-What's the problem?
-Her jaw won't open far enough.
-I can't see her cords.
-Maybe she broke it.
I have to intubate her fiberoptically.
I got it.
Nose, nose, anything goes.
Thank you, Nurse.
Very gritty.
Scar tissue, lots of it.
She's a gusher.
There shouldn't be that much blood.
Dr. Santiago,
have you ever been sued for malpractice?
As a matter of fact, I haven't.
'Course not. lt'd be like suing
a witch doctor for a spell that didn't work.
-Good night.
-We hired you to weed out the sickos...
because you had professional insight...
but when the big one came along,
it slipped by you just like everybody else.
-What are you talking about?
-Ellie Collins.
She was never in an accident.
There, that's where the trouble is,
right there.
-I can't see anything.
-I don't understand.
I didn't have this problem
with Matt or Annie.
We don't know why it happens, Julia.
Your age may be a factor.
You've had two kids.
I don't even know where to look,
and I'm a doctor, for God's sake.
Here. You can't see the embryo.
It's still too early.
lncompetent cervix. That fits.
It's nothing to be too alarmed about.
What's usually done in this situation
is something called a cerclage.
I place a stitch around the cervix
to reinforce it...
so it won't weaken and dilate
under the weight of your growing baby.
Because we could miscarry.
That, or have a premature rupture
of the fetal membranes...
possibly preterm delivery.
Okay. Good. That's what we'll do then.
A cerclage.
I would, however,
strongly recommend bed rest...
both before the procedure and after,
until you are full-term.
How much bed rest?
Modified. I like to play it safe.
You can sit up for meals,
shower every few days...
bathroom privileges, but try to avoid...
too much walking or lifting
or sexual intercourse.
I don't think I can stay in bed
for seven months.
You'd be amazed what you can do
if you want something badly enough.
I've known my ex-friend here for 10 years.
I've known him from school and sports.
Okay, take-out menus
for when you're hungry...
and more catalogues
for when you're bored and want to shop.
I believe you're encouraging me
to spend money?
I'm not an idiot.
You never buy clothes
when you put on weight.
I almost forgot. Here.
The bed rest chat room says
it's the best thing for boredom.
A Game Boy.
Honey, you shouldn't have.
Batteries included.
Call me if you need anything.
So let's answer that.
Did you sleep with him?
-No, I didn't.
-Okay.
I got you some take-out.
Honey, you don't have to keep doing this.
It's sweet of you, but--
It's chicken and vegetables
with a ton of garlic.
It's supposed to boost
your immune system.
I'm not sick, Matt. I'm pregnant.
When I asked for one of these,
Dad said no.
I got this lecture about how I was using
only one-tenth of my brain.
Like they say,
a brain is a terrible thing to waste.
What about yours?
A son's brain.
Apparently a wife's is just excess baggage.
I can't believe you're doing this again.
What?
Having a baby you don't want.
What do you mean "again"?
Maybe if you hadn't gotten pregnant
with me...
you'd be a doctor today.
I have never regretted having
you or Annie.
Do you understand that?
There is not a degree in the whole world...
that would make me half as proud.
-And once the baby's born--
-You'll go back to school?
lsn't that what you said after I was born?
After Annie?
This baby's not about you, Matt.
Is it about you?
Do you even want to have another kid?
Or are you just glad
to have another reason...
why you can't go after
what you really want?
How does it look?
It'll be fine, Ellie...
considering there's practically
nothing left of the septum...
and evidence that the cartilage
has been operated on previously.
We'd like to talk to you before
your husband gets here, if that's all right.
lt wasn't an accident, was it?
Dave did it.
You just said it was an accident
to protect him.
No.
lt won't stop
unless you want it to stop, Ellie.
You have to know he's lying
when he promises it'll never happen again.
What'll never happen again?
Mr. Collins, visiting hours
aren't for another 15 minutes.
If you could wait outside?
Does your accident insurance
cover wife beating, Mr. Collins?
Is that what you told them?
She didn't have to. The inside of her face
looks like a patch quilt.
Did you break her nose, Mr. Collins?
Yes.
Well, you bought her flowers,
so I guess you're even.
I'm going to need to talk to you both.
We're required to file a report.
I made him do it.
Ellie...
battered wives are often made to feel
as if they've had it coming.
No, I forced him to break my nose.
You never would've fixed it
if you'd known about the other operations.
You would've been like the other doctors...
who had said I'd done enough to my face.
That it looked fine. But it didn't.
My nose was hideous!
Like some sort of freak.
She begged me to break it
and tell you that it was an accident.
That way you'd do the operation
with no questions asked.
I didn't want to, but she swore:
No more surgeries after this.
I love Ellie.
Watching her suffer,
hating herself that way...
I couldn't stand it.
I had to do something to stop the pain.
Are you gonna report us?
What's my crime?
Is it loving her too much?
Time. Pencils down.
Pass your tests to the aisle.
Hey, I haven't seen you in a while.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I've been
a little under the weather...
but I wasn't gonna miss the midterm.
Well, good.
I thought I was gonna die without you.
It's true. I actually had to pay attention
in the lecture.
My God, this shit is boring.
Why is becoming a doctor so tedious...
when playing doctor was so much fun?
You okay?
-Do you have a car?
-Yes. Why?
-Can you take me to the hospital?
-Sure.
Is this seat taken?
lt will be.
You're meeting someone?
And he's keeping you waiting?
He must have balls.
He called.
And, yes, he's got major-league balls.
I can take him.
Can I buy you another drink?
Now, that would be pointless, Dr. Troy...
since you're the reason I'm drinking.
Call me Christian.
Haven't we seen enough of each other
for one day?
How many of those have you had?
Apparently not enough.
I can still see you.
Please go away.
Look...
I blamed you for Ellie...
because I couldn't take responsibility
for my own negligence.
I was an asshole.
-I'm sorry.
-Damn it.
What?
No witnesses. It's like a UFO sighting.
lt happened clear as day,
but no one will believe it.
It's all in the delivery.
You believed that crap Collins said
about loving Ellie so much...
that he had to stop her pain?
I believe he believes it.
So you think that was what, love?
They have a connection.
They show each other
the darkest parts of themselves...
without fearing
the other will run screaming for the hills.
Because they're both psycho.
I guess.
Still, it's a kind of sharing...
most people won't experience
in a lifetime.
lt gets old, doesn't it?
Looking for that person?
Yes, it does.
lt gets...
absolutely exhausting.
I'll notify the bed rest chat room
to take this off their anti-boredom list.
lt was very sweet. Really.
Ronald will be disappointed.
Who?
The guy I was interviewing
to take over during my paternity leave.
I can't believe
you were really considering that.
Yes, Julia, I was really considering that.
I was actually putting you
ahead of my career.
I know you've been doing it
for the past 16 years.
It's not what it's cracked up to be.
You made that pretty clear.
For God's sake, Sean!
Do you think I took the midterm...
hoping I'd miscarry?
You knew the risks.
You're not the only one
who's lost a baby, Sean.
But I was the only one who wanted one.
You didn't even call me
to take you to the hospital.
You asked that kid.
He was there, that was all.
The truth is, Julia, you didn't love me,
us, enough to even try.
lt was too much of a sacrifice.
I don't know where we're going, Sean.
But if you think that by having a child...
we can make
all our real problems go away...
then maybe we are better off.
You're saying you're relieved?
Aren't you, just a little?
Or is it easier
to live in denial and vilify me?
It's the office.
Hello?
Dr. McNamara, I have a call for you.
It's Leigh Moriata.
Yes, put her through.
Miss Moriata, this is Dr. McNamara.
Dr. McNamara...
I'm calling you
from my engagement party.
Congratulations.
I'm glad your mother was convinced.
She didn't buy it for a minute.
I don't understand.
But she could see that any guy
who was willing to change his face...
to please his mother-in-law...
the man must really love me.
If I invite you to the wedding,
would you come?
Of course, if I can.
Thanks for telling me.
I'm very happy for you.
Rip youyoup