I'm offering you the chance
to destroy Sydney Bristow.
The moment this assignment is over,
we'll give you back your daughter.
Sydney Bristow was not to be harmed.
You locked her in a train car
and you sprayed her
with a chemical agent.
It's all there...
Everything you need to bring Nadia back.
We loaded the Bristow D.N.A. template
into the sequence.
Her genetic fluid is primed and ready.
Synchro : Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Spécial thanks : Lemonhead
Honey, that's not good enough.
What am I, a dog whistle? I said no.
"N-O." that's right.
That's better. Thank you.
- Mr. Halbe?
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Hi!
- I hope your trip wasn't too arduous.
My trip was fine.
It's these marketing people.
B.A.S, M.B.A.S
and not a lick
of common sense among 'em!
They almost didn't launch my new perfume
L'Eau De Passion.
They said the name was tacky.
Can you believe that?!
- It's a lovely name.
- I know.
That's why I always trust my instincts,
and now it is flying off the shelves,
flying!
I assure you, we can take care
of all your customer service needs.
I don't want my people suffering through
no ten minutes
of pan flute to place an order.
Of course not.
Let me show you our main call center.
I think I came to the right place.
We just got a lead on Anna.
She's routing her calls
through a call center in Jaipur;
using what?
Encrypted router.
She must have put something
on a line outside.
So they have no idea
she's piggybacking
on their system.
She's totally anonymous.
So we locate the router
and remove the encryption key.
Next time Anna makes a call,
we listen in.
Right, maybe even trace her location.
What's the approach?
All you need to do
is get this perfume bottle
within 5 feet of...
a Wi-Fi access, point.
And then you can just map
the phone system.
We can figure out
which line she's using.
- "L'Eau De Passion"?
- What, you think it's...
too tacky?
I'll work with it.
Soon, we'll be doubling
our call volume capacity.
You're gonna need to triple it
when you start getting calls
about this baby.
...the Mandarin Stripe
is on back order,
but the Heather Sprig is available.
Excuse me, ma'am.
How do you like this smell?
It's called L'Eau De Passion.
Nice.
Well, you keep it.
Sorry, my computer's working
a little slow today.
Signal's good.
I'm mapping the system now.
If you outsource,
you can cut your customer service budget
by at least 30%.
- Interesting.
- Syd...
We've got a problem.
Their router is not out here.
It's in the building.
Could I come back tomorrow?
I need to think about it.
No, don't go. Just follow my lead.
Nobody move!
Drop it!
You get on the ground.
You in the pink, come here.
Get down!
Get on the ground!
Watches, jewelry, wallets in the bag!
Hurry up!
No reason not to be nice!
Come on!
All right now. That's enough for today.
Get up.
If anyone does anything
in the next three minutes, she dies.
Let me see this.
Hey, I saw a watch I liked.
It's probably a Knockoff.
Renée, what you did back there...
- You don't approve.
- No, it was brilliant.
You should think
about joining A.P.O.
In case you forgot, I'm a criminal.
We could try for a pardon.
You should think about it.
I was surprised to hear from you.
You made it very clear
that your dealings with us were over.
I read the instructions.
In order for the serum to work,
Nadia's heart needs to be stopped.
Only briefly,
as I recall, 30 seconds or so.
You're asking me to kill my daughter.
I'm asking you to have faith
in Rambaldi.
You're saying
Rambaldi designed the cure?
Well, given that Nadia's illness
stems from his invention,
doesn't that make sense?
Surely, I don't have to convince you
of the genius behind his designs.
You spent decades pursuing his works.
If things had gone differently,
you'd be working with us right now.
You'd be there.
When we realized
his greatest achievement.
You still could be.
My pursuit of Rambaldi is over.
I won't allow it to consume me again.
I'm only here for Nadia.
That's unfortunate,
but we upheld our end of the bargain.
We gave you the cure.
Whether or not
you choose to administer it,
that's up to you.
Anna's line just went active.
Marshall and Rachel
are standing by to intercept.
Initiating the back-trace.
Bringing the optical sats online.
- Hello?
- Did you bring your umbrella?
The weather report
calls for rain.
That's not Anna but Kelly Peyton.
- Can you locate them?
- Already on it.
- Who are you?
- That's not important.
Anna Espinosa works for me now.
That's all you need to know.
- I don't do business with strangers.
- Check your account.
You've already been compensated.
I got him. He's in Zurich.
47-22 north, 8-32 east.
The kh-12 feed is up.
I'm zooming in now.
I suppose given your generosity,
- I could make an exception.
- I figured.
Check under the bench
at the base of the stairs.
- We need Peyton's location!
- I know,
but she's routing it
through too many hubs.
- Can you get a better view?
- Yeah.
I've got it in front of me.
What exactly
do you want me to do?
There's a message hidden
in the text.
Page 47.
What sort of message?
A code, a transfer, microdot?
If I knew that,
I wouldn't have to pay you, would I?
Got it... Barcelona.
- Where?
- I don't know, just give me a sec.
Keep talking. 1 more minute, please.
Use the protocol
you had with Anna
to contact me
when you unveil the message
hidden on the page.
Barcelona.
That's all we have.
I don't know, Anna.
He sounds a little skittish.
He's the best.
If it exists, he'll find it.
It doesn't make any sense.
If this guy in Zurich
was Anna's contact,
- why is Peyton the one calling?
- It's unclear.
But now I want you and Marshall
to work together.
See if you can I.D. him.
If we can bring him into custody,
we can use him to get to Anna.
Tom, Dixon, reach out
to all our contacts in Barcelona.
If Prophet Five has established
a new outpost there,
perhaps someone's heard about it.
What about the message?
You mean the one buried
in a 500-year-old piece of paper?
Are we taking that seriously?
We've seen too much not to.
Look, we still have a copy of page 47.
- I could take it and analyze it and...
- I'm taking it with me.
You have your assignments.
If anything develops, notify me at once.
Wait, where are you going?
Not that you have to tell me,
unless you want to.
I'm going to see Sloane.
He had page 47 in his possession
long before it was turned over
to the D.S.R.
Given his obsession with it,
maybe he knows something we don't.
I can't just let you lie here like this,
not if there's a way to get you back.
I'm sorry.
God, I'm sorry. It's the only way.
Transcript : www.1000fr.com
www.forom.com
- Move away from her.
- You don't understand.
- We don't have time.
- Stop!
This is not your decision to make,
- no matter how much she's suffering.
- I have to do it now!
Oh, my God. It's too late.
It was a cure, Jack,
A cure.
It's okay.
It's okay. We're here.
So she's working with Prophet Five?
Well, that explains how Anna escaped
from prison, but why?
I mean, why would they want her?
- She's good.
- Yeah, I know.
But Prophet Five
has always been low profile.
Anna is on everybody's radar.
Maybe they had to go to her.
Maybe there's only something she can do.
We've identified the man from Zurich:
Mortiz Koller.
He used to be an art historian,
was kind of a big shot.
Supposedly discovered
Da Vinci's lost drawings.
Supposedly?
He forged them.
He was completely discredited.
It looks like he went freelance.
And plenty of criminal organizations
are more than happy
to put his talent to good use,
including Le Corbeau.
- He worked with Renée?
- More than once.
Well, that means
she'll know how to find him.
Syd, your father's on line two.
Nadia's awake.
Looking at her like this,
I'm almost afraid to believe it's true.
It must be an overwhelming relief.
Yeah.
I know you have questions, Jack.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I wanted to,
but I was afraid for people to know.
Conventional medicine
gave up on my daughter.
I couldn't.
I've been funding dozens
of back-channel research projects,
phase-one studies using class "A" drugs,
methods that no country would condone.
And then one of them paid off...
A study out of Barcelona.
- Barcelona?
- I had no guarantee that it would work.
My options had run out.
- Sydney.
- Is she okay?
She's with the doctor now.
She's doing wonderfully.
You need me for anything,
you call the nurse, OK?
Hi.
Everything seems normal.
I need to run some tests,
see if we can determine how...
- Nadia's condition reversed itself.
- No.
My daughter has been poked
and prodded enough.
If her health is no longer in jeopardy,
I want to make arrangements
to take her home.
She deserves her life back.
I understand.
I'll update her file now and...
see if we can get her out
of here as soon as possible.
Thank you.
You want to go in?
In a minute. I have a call to return.
Hello?
It's me.
I need you to look into something,
off the record.
Sure. What is it?
Sloane's recent activities.
That is travel itineraries,
call logs, meeting reports.
Anything you want me to focus on?
Barcelona.
Did you find Koller?
Tom's en route to meet Renée in Paris.
But you called me away from Nadia.
Sydney, how much do you know
about Nadia's cure?
- Why?
- Sloane's travel records indicate
he's made several trips to Barcelona.
He was there shortly
before we intercepted Peyton's call.
Sloane told me he acquired
the cure in Barcelona
where Prophet Five is based.
We know they've used Nadia's condition
to blackmail him in the past.
Perhaps Sloane's association
with them...
...didn't end there.
You think he's working with them,
that Prophet Five gave him the cure?
Perhaps in exchange for information.
Sloane's been breaking protocol,
incorrectly logging phone calls
made from A.P.O. for months,
dozens of calls, Syd, all of them made
to numbers that no longer exist.
He's already admitted
to using illegal research channels.
Perhaps he's trying to cover it up.
Or the back-channel research
could be a cover for something else.
I know what Sloane is capable of.
You don't have to remind me,
but Nadia has her life back
because of him.
Which is why
I hope I'm wrong about this.
Well, do what you have to do.
But until you have something concrete,
I'll be with my sister.
You cold? Want me to get you a blanket?
- No, the air feels good.
- Okay.
Sydney should be here soon.
I can't wait to spend
some time with Isabelle.
I'm even looking forward
to changing diapers
in the middle of the night.
So you're going to stay at Sydney's?
Yeah, I assumed so.
Oh my God.
Let me see her.
Come here, baby.
She's dying to meet her aunt Nadia.
Yeah, there you...
Hi, beautiful.
Well, I'll leave the three of you
to enjoy each other's company.
- Where are you going?
- A.P.O.
Jack wants to see me. I'll be back.
We'll be fine.
Won't we?
Okay, enjoy the sun.
What's happening?
Hi.
What is it?
You wanted to see me?
I arranged for the leave of absence
you requested.
The forms are all here
for you to sign.
Thank you.
Look Jack, I realize the timing
on this might be less than ideal,
but if you need me...
You should be spending this time
with Nadia.
Well, unfortunately,
I'm not sure if she feels the same.
Give it time, Arvin.
I know.
You're right.
One last thing.
We intercepted a call from Prophet Five.
Turns out Anna gave them page 47.
They're looking for a hidden message
encoded in the text.
Were you...
...aware of this?
Apparently, the message is hidden
in a substitution cipher.
Marshall believes
he's close to decoding it.
I could let you know when we find out.
No.
No, I think it's better
I not be involved.
I understand.
I talked to Marshall.
He'll confirm he's working on page 47
if Sloane goes to him.
And the taps are in place?
If Sloane alerts Prophet Five,
we'll know.
Thank you.
- Any words from Tom?
- He's connected with Renée.
They should be making contact
with Koller soon.
We should get this going.
We're following Koller's protocol.
It's 10:00.
It's 9:59.
I didn't realize
the French were so punctual.
We're not.
It's you Americans
who are always in a hurry.
And we get fat, too.
Is there anything else?
Now it's 10:00.
We're on.
We need to meet...
Tonight.
- How's Isabelle?
- She's asleep, finally.
I'm all yours.
You shouldn't stay up.
You must be exhausted.
Well, what about you?
It's strange.
I've already missed so much time.
I wish I had been here for you,
- with everything that's happened.
- I know.
And I know what it's like to have
a part of your life taken from you.
For what it's worth, it gets easier.
My father wanted me to stay with him,
but I couldn't.
Ever since he came into my life,
it's always the same.
I just don't want to get hurt anymore.
I don't blame you.
You have every right to be guarded.
But...
You should know
that while you were sick,
he was completely devoted to you.
I mean, I've never seen him
so dedicated to anything.
Even Rambaldi?
From what I've seen, even Rambaldi.
You can stay here as long as you want,
as long as you don't mind a crying baby.
Are you crazy?
I love having so much life around me.
It's my dad.
- Hey, dad.
- Sloane set a meet.
- When?
- Tonight.
I'm going to surveil it.
I thought you should know.
I'll wait for your call.
What is it?
There's something you should know.
- Nadia.
- Sydney told me what you're doing.
- I want to go with you.
- You sure that's wise?
Whatever you're about to find out
about my father...
I need to know.
All right, let's go.
Security is armed.
Aren't they always?
Just try to buy me
a couple more minutes.
Renée...
Almost there.
Three, two...
- I hate that word.
- I'll remember that.
You finally got the Ford hybrid.
Electric.
It comes in handy
when you have to be quiet.
Regardless of what we find,
I believe your father's feelings
for you are genuine.
I wish that was enough for him.
Sloane's not the only family
you have, you know.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
We can't see anything from here.
All right.
What were they saying?
I couldn't make it out.
We're in.
Sloane took something from in here.
- Clothes?
- Mine.
These are my things.
He was getting them for you.
I don't know what the rest of this is.
Findings from clinical trials.
Trials for what?
Studies from a facility in Barcelona.
It appears that
I've misjudged your father.
Help!
Dear God, someone!
Anyone!
Help!
Are you done yet?
Please, I don't know
what you want from me.
We want information about Anna Espinosa.
I-I... I can't help you.
Yes, you can.
We know she hired you
to decode a message in this.
I don't have the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
Anna who?
I know you're trying
to do right by your client.
But you and I both know
you are not cut out
to withstand extended interrogation.
You're just some unlucky bookworm
who's in way over his head.
Please, don't hurt me!
Then stop screaming and talk!
I have a meet set
with Anna tomorrow... in Ghana.
She knows what the message was?
No.
I want to get paid.
Why wouldn't she pay you?
Anna doesn't like bad news.
The document... it's a fake.
Very well done, but...
but a fake.
And you believe him?
He has no reason to lie.
He found a small amount
of titanium dioxide in the pigment.
Well, that means the document
can't be older than 80 years.
Give or take a decade.
- How do you want to proceed?
- We keep the meet.
We can still use Moritz
and the counterfeit page
- to bait Anna.
- Guess I'll see you in Ghana.
And the real one-- where is it?
- Nadia...
- I'm sorry. I should have called.
No, of course not. I...
I thought you were staying at Sydney's.
Sydney went to Ghana.
They're going after Anna.
That's not the reason I'm here.
I was hoping I could stay with you.
Maybe we can take some time,
get to know each other again,
if it's okay.
How could you even ask that?
Come in, sweetheart.
This is my favorite sweater.
I remembered.
Thank you.
Chamomile. You remembered that, too.
I need to admit something to you.
I didn't think you'd want
to be with me at all.
Especially not after
what my actions caused for you.
I've been quite angry.
Well, you have every right to be angry.
Nadia, when I first met you,
I didn't know how to be a father.
I assumed it meant being needed.
And then I saw you lying
in the hospital in that bed,
and I realized something.
I realized that I need you
more than you will ever need me.
I'm sorry. I...
I promised myself
I wouldn't put any pressure on you.
It's no pressure.
Dinner's almost ready.
- You need some help?
- No.
Let me explain.
Nadia, you're going to have to trust me.
You said it was over.
- No, it's not what it looks like.
- You've been lying all along.
Look,
I handed everything over to the D.S.R.
except for that page.
I couldn't part with it.
I-I'd spent so much time...
I don't want more excuses.
Just talking about Rambaldi,
your face, your voice-- it all changes.
- This obsession you have--
- No, it's not an obsession.
It's faith.
Do you have any idea
what your faith cost me?
What did you think,
that I was sleeping peacefully?
The last 12 months were an extended nap?
I heard people talking.
I felt tubes
being shoved down my throat.
I couldn't open my eyes.
I couldn't move. I couldn't scream.
But I felt everything,
so forgive me
if I don't have much tolerance
for your faith.
Nadia, please!
You have to understand--
I'm done trying to understand you!
You have to make a choice.
Either me or this.
Please, don't make me choose
between the two most important
things in my life.
I suppose then you'll lose us both.
My god, the message!
- I see it.
- You're not getting it!
- Get out of my way!
- No, you can't have it!
I won't let you! Stop, please!
- Stop it!
- Nadia, move!
Okay, now this place-- crazy crowded.
I'm not talking about mall crowded,
I'm saying like people, cars, goats.
That's why Anna chose it--
hard to surveil.
What's the plan?
How are we apprehending her?
Visual aids here.
Courtesy of Mitchell.
Okay, uh, well, we have Anna,
who will be arriving
on the main road right here.
Now, uh, let's see.
Dixon and Rachel
will be stationed right here.
- Are the exits secured?
- Yeah.
Tom will be cutting off the back,
and... Sydney will... sorry, Syd...
will be at the entrance.
- So here comes Anna--
- Okay, thank you.
Notify me when they have her in custody.
Well, I wasn't done with the--
- It's fine. Thank you.
- The car was...
I get it.
Everybody's getting set up.
When you see Anna,
you'll take her out with this.
Government issue.
I never thought I'd have one of these.
Don't get too excited.
It's only a tranq gun.
That's too bad.
Have you give any more thought
to my offer about A.P.O.?
Yeah, I work better on my own schedule.
When are you going to start trusting me?
I trust you.
It's everyone else that's the problem.
Okay, go.
Beautiful jewelry for a beautiful lady.
No cash, sorry. I'm a starving student.
Is everything all right?
Wonderful,
considering I might get killed today.
Relax. We've got you covered.
This will be fine. Thank you.
Target approaching.
Copy.
Copy that.
What's going on? She's not getting out.
Something's not right.
Hold your positions.
They're retreating.
I've lost visual.
Don't let her escape!
Repeat, Anna's car
is headed toward the entrance!
- Rachel, follow the car.
- Copy that.
Renée, block off the back alleys.
She knows it's an ambush!
Someone tipped her off.
She's not here. Repeat--
- Anna is not in the car.
- Copy.
She must have gotten out.
Let's search the perimeter.
A few days ago,
I was absolutely horrified
that you would suggest
I would turn against A.P.O.,
that I would kill my own daughter.
I realize now that both were inevitable,
that death is a necessary sacrifice,
necessary to complete
the final leg of this journey.
I have been preparing
for this my whole life.
I knew it was coming.
I have betrayed everyone I ever loved,
but I was chosen...
We appreciate what you've done.
And this is my road to follow.
Welcome back.
Suggestions critics insults :
aliassub@gmail.com