- Did you crack Dean's encryption?
- Well, I was working on it, but...
I got a little sidetracked.
I intercepted a strong
of MI-6 transmissions.
They're all about the testing
and sale of a prototype M.P.B.
- That's impossible.
- Yeah, I thought so, too.
What's an M.P.B.?
Sorry, it's a Micro-Pulse Bomb.
These things... super nasty.
Incinerate the people,
leave everything else intact.
There was an incident aboard a train
in Siberia two days ago.
Information's leaking out slowly, but...
You think that's the test?
There's no way the Brits
are pursuing an M.P.B.
That breaks every arms treaty
own to man.
Well, have you notified
the Director General?
Until we know who we can trust,
we can't approach MI-6 officially.
Jack and Sydney are in England
trying to find out more.
In the meantime, we're going to go over
every single transmission
Marshall pulled off the server
to see if we missed something.
- I'm working on these.
- Okay.
I'll take these.
You should see my youngest grandchild
Daisy...
4 years old and already
a master of the computer.
Have you chosen a name?
I myself have always been partia
to "Rupert"...
such a distinguished name.
A shame it's fallen out of favor.
Wouldn't you agree, dear?
- Rupert... it's classic.
- Excuse me.
Can't seem to get enough
of that Devonshire clotted cream.
We don't have it in the States.
If you'll just pardon me?
- Yes, of course.
- Thank you.
I prefer the cinnamon,
but the blackberry is also very good.
Excuse me, ma'am,
you forgot a napkin.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Do you still play?
No, gave it up years ago.
You shouldn't have approached me here.
I take it Joseph still doesn't know
what you do for a living.
How would it look for
the French Ambassador
to have a spook for a wife?
Besides, this is where
I get my best intelligence.
I already talked with
the Minister of Finance. He's a dimwit.
What's this about, Jack?
We believe someone operating within MI-6
is attempting to acquire
a Micro-Pulse Bomb.
Well, that's outrageous.
- MI-6 would never sanction...
- I agree.
More likely, whoever it is
represents some corrupt element.
Are you suggesting
we have a double agent?
Yes, but it goes much deeper than that.
Have you ever heard of Prophet Five?
- Have you seen Elizabeth?
- No. Sorry.
Excuse me!
Are you Joseph Vachon,
the French Ambassador?
Why, yes, I am.
I knew it. Hey, I've been taking
French classes at night,
'cause little ones are supposed
to pick up so quickly, you know?
I was just wondering if I could just
practice a little bit on you.
- I suppose so, yeah.
- Great. Okay. All right.
The network behind Prophet Five
is far-reaching.
They appear to have infiltrated
multiple intelligence agencies,
not just MI-6.
And you think that following this weapon
will give us the key
to finding out more?
You want me to investigate my agency
from the inside?
I wouldn't be coming to you
if it didn't also involve Sydney.
Sydney? Is she all right?
She's fine.
You just met her, in fact.
Oh, my goodness!
It has been a long time.
And unless she's wearing
a very convincing disguise...
I'm going to be a grandfather...
A very young grandfather.
Jack...
She's lovely.
She is. The agent I told you about,
Michael Vaughn...
- He was her fiancé.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
What you're asking me to do,
to investigate my own agency...
that's treason.
What's a little treason
between old friends?
My source got back to me.
She confirmed what we suspected.
The acquisition of the M.P.B. weapon
is strictly off-book.
MI-6 has not sanctioned it.
Could she identify the double agent?
No, but she was able to identify
the engineer who designed the weapon...
this man... Lukas Basarov.
Tenured faculty,
University of St. Petersburg.
Holds advanced degrees in physics
and thermonuclear engineering.
Apparently, he has a side business.
Basarov is currently en route
to a conference
being held in Sao Paolo, Brazil.
He's scheduled to give a talk
on theoretical microdynamics.
Sounds awesome.
Well, Brazil. Isn't that, you know,
the place where they have string...
what are they called?
Not bikinis, but...
- Thongs.
- Yes.
My source found evidence
which indicates that
within approximately 48 hours,
Basarov will receive a transmission
regarding where and when
the sale is taking place.
We can presume
he'll be receiving this one
at the conference via his laptop.
Well, that's easy.
We just access the laptop,
upload the bugging software...
piece of cake.
I could definitely do it.
You need to be here
to decrypt the transmission.
Rachel's perfectly equipped
to do the work in the field.
Wheels up in two hours.
- Hey.
Here's your program.
It's a Flinkman special.
Thanks.
You're sure you're okay with this?
Yeah. I'm actually glad
that I'm going...
Anything to keep
the investigation moving.
When's the last time
you did something just for fun?
Hitting Gordon Dean on the head
with a shovel, that was fun.
Okay.
Okay, it hasn't been high
on my list of priorities.
But you have to have a life.
I know. Okay.
I'll work on it, I promise...
after Brazil.
Hi, I'm checking in. Lydia Sand.
The room you requested is available.
- I see you're here for the conference?
- Yes
Let me get your information packet.
I don't care what sort of
geek convention you have here.
I was told an upgrade
wouldn't be a problem.
Americans.
So, Lydia, you here on business?
Yes.
The geek conference.
You heard that, huh?
I did.
What are the odds, huh?
I'm in place.
Yes, I'm looking at him right now.
I'll have the details
of the trade by tomorrow.
Don't worry, Benjamin.
For what you're paying me,
I won't let anything stand in my way.
Dr. Basarov? Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
I was just reading your article,
and, well, I was wondering...
would you mind signing it?
Look. I have...
what do you call them? Groupie.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I would like the shrimp stew,
the pork and beef skewers
and also the tomato salad.
I'm trying to lay off the carbs.
Get it here in ten minutes,
and I'll triple the gratuity.
Room service.
- Agent Grace.
- Hi, it's me.
- How'd it go?
- It went fine... great.
Good. I'll notify Jack and Marshall.
So what do I do now?
Keep your P.D.A. with you.
It'll alert you as soon as it intercepts
Basarov's transmission.
Then go ahead and send it to Marshall.
Till then, it looks like
you got the night off.
Just relax.
All right.
Lydia?
Right?
I'm sorry about that crack
I made earlier.
12 hours on a plane next to
a screaming toddler.
You know how that can be.
- Of course, that's no excuse.
- Don't worry about it.
Whatever beer you have on tap, please.
My name's Bob Brown.
Lydia. But you already knew that.
Thank you.
Conference that bad?
No. It's just, you know, tough day.
Sometimes at these work events,
I feel like I'm in over my head.
I just started in a new division.
It's a lot more responsibilities,
more risks.
Sounds like you need to rethink
your perspective a little bit.
Anything in life worth doing
has an element of risk.
It's what makes life interesting.
I can definitely say my life has been
interesting lately.
And I did manage to do
what I came here for, so...
Well, then good for you.
As you say, cheers!
Cheers.
So, Bob, are you here
on business as well?
Yep.
I'm in international trade.
What do you trade?
Whatever my clients pay me to trade.
Do you like it?
Hell, yeah.
I work freelance, so I get to travel,
meet all sorts of fascinating people,
present company included.
Last year, I tried something
a little different...
something more conventional, stable.
How'd that work out?
It didn't. I was terrible at it.
I was so bored that I wanted
to blow my brains out.
So I decided to take
less drastic measures and do something
I know best.
I just moved.
Left my entire life behind, actually.
Well, new starts are good, right?
And the new people I work with
are great.
You don't sound too convinced.
No, they are.
That's part of the problem.
They're so good at what they do.
I mean, there's this one woman...
she's amazing,
and she's about to have a baby.
I'm not sure I could manage
work and a goldfish.
Well, aquariums are overrated.
Remember that.
Okay.
- You want another one?
- I would love one.
So, um... thank you
for keeping me company.
It was my pleasure.
- Good night.
Do you have your key?
Oh, no, we can't go in my room.
There are clothes all over the place.
Can't we go into yours?
- Uh...
- Please?
Please.
What the hell. Yeah.
Just so you know,
I don't usually do this.
Well, I appreciate you
making the exception.
You should know that
gorgeous engineers have a way
of throwing themselves at me, so...
I did not throw myself at you.
Okay, okay. If that's
what you need to believe.
Want something to drink?
- Yes, that'd be lovely.
- Okay.
We're in the tropics,
so how about some rum?
Okay, so you hate rum.
Sorry, I forgot how early my flight was.
What are you talking about?
We got a couple hours, right?
Seriously, I've got to meet with my boss
and I'm completely unprepared.
Well, I'd hate to be the one
to make you lose your job.
- Bob, it's been...
- Yeah, it has.
Carrie, honey, ln, I'm into something
really huge right now, okay?
No, no, no, Marshall. It's Rachel.
The transmission's coming in early.
Okay. Uh, give me a sec.
- Transferring now.
- I'll get right on it.
Rachel, you did great.
Marshall's almost done
analyzing the transmission.
- It won't be much longer.
- I'm glad.
You're in a good mood.
Anything you're not telling me?
I... nothing. Just...
The trip was really relaxing.
What did you do? Spill it out.
I met a guy at the hotel.
Some business guy,
which is not at all my type.
We were just talking at the bar,
and, well, one thing led to...
Another, obviously.
Are you going to see him again?
He thinks I'm Lydia, a British engineer.
Oh, rats. Yeah.
So no, I guess.
Guess what happens in Brazil
stays in Brazil.
What happened in Brazil?
Oh, Rachel got food poisoning.
Sorry.
Marshall decrypted the transmission.
The double agent is due to meet Basarov
in Spain in 14 hours.
I'm leaving now to surveil the exchange.
Are you taking anyone with you?
My MI-6 contact is joining me.
You'll coordinate from here?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Well, this is charming.
I knew you'd like it.
I could have spared you the trip,
handled this alone.
Someone from my agency is involved,
you can't expect me
to stand in the sidelines.
I figured as much.
Why don't we start with the cameras?
This is Phoenix. How are you doing?
We're almost set up.
Connection's good.
Okay, should be getting visuals.
Got it. We're standing by.
We can tag the weapon
with this tracker. Once they...
Joseph.
Where does he think you are?
Developing Nations Summit.
You were saying?
Once the weapon's in transport,
we'll notify the C.N.A.
so they can recover it
without tipping the double agent.
Sounds good.
Looks like they're ahead of schedule.
Do you see that?
Yeah. Given the size, I'm assuming
it's got at least
a 20-mile blast radius.
I thought he was showing up alone.
So did I.
That man... can you get a better image?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Oh, my God. That's Masari.
Who?
Dad, those are not MI-6 agents.
Repeat... those are not MI-6 agents.
That is Benjamin Masari.
Wait, who's Masari?
Sudanese head of the R.L.F.
Terrorist squad responsible for bombing
western targets in Africa.
This is an ambush.
The bomb!
Dad, can you hear me?
It's no good, Syd.
They're jamming our signal.
Oh, God, dad. Dad, do you copy?
Dad, can you hear me?
I want intel from anybody
who's ever done business with Masari.
I don't care if they crossed the street
next to him,
find out what they know.
Anything yet?
Well, I'm indexing passenger manifests
to and from Malaga.
- So far, nothing.
- Find something.
The head of Interpol is on the line.
Any trace from the signal?
No. They must have disabled the tracker.
I want everything we have on the R.L.F.
Right away.
I came as soon as I heard.
I'm sorry to pull you away from Nadia.
How did it happen?
They were surveilling a weapons trade.
An M.P.B. was supposed to be delivered
to a double agent within MI-6.
Masari and his men showed up instead.
I've been reviewing the footage.
- What time was the meet set?
- 2:30am, local time.
- Masari and his men?
- Showed up at 2:17.
The double agent never had a chance.
They beat him to it.
You think it's unrelated?
Micro-Pulse Bomb...
it's the kind of weapon that would be
coveted by most criminal organizations.
Masari must have found out.
How?
How did you get your intel, Sydney?
Rachel intercepted a transmission.
Well, maybe she wasn't the only one.
Someone else was in that hotel.
Say hello to an old friend...
Julian Sark.
Footage places him
at the hotel in Sao Paolo
at the same time that Rachel
intercepted the message,
which makes it likely
that he did the same.
I thought he was out of the game.
Apparently not.
He must have been working for Masari.
He was probably paid
for the information.
Who is this guy?
Kidnapper, extortionist, murderer,
the list goes on.
Formerly tied to SD-6 and the Covenant.
He mostly works for himself.
Freelance.
I had no idea. I will do anything.
I have to ask... did he use you
for information?
No. There's no way.
We were never in my room.
He never even had access
to the transmission. I can find him.
He's probably halfway
around the world by now.
No, when I was in his room,
I saw a plane ticket.
He's going to the Bahamas.
Lydia.
How nice. You remembered my name.
Do you remember me?
Sydney.
I suppose a congratulations is in order.
I'm warning you,
if you're planning on arresting me,
I'm not gonna make it easy on you,
people could be hurt.
My father and another agent
have been taken captive
by Benjamin Masari.
We need to find his base of operations.
My clients pay handsomely
for their privacy.
It would be unprofessional of me
to give that information to you.
Which is why we aren't here
to arrest you.
We're here to hire you.
I was beginning to wonder
if you'd forgotten about us.
I imagine for you this cell
seems somewhat inhuman.
You westerners, so accustomed
to your indulgences.
Why are we here?
You were transmitting a video feed
when you were found.
Where was it going?
Holiday photos.
Costa Del Sol in winter.
As you say,
we do like our little indulgences.
Do not touch her!
If you want to spare her, answer me.
Where was the transmission going?
Take me.
I'm not easily frightened.
You should be.
The right one.
If you want to spare her,
answer me.
Perhaps we should try this again.
Who do you work for?
- Wait.
- Don't tell him!
Clearly, you don't work
with your hands, huh?
What is it?
My sources tell me
things got complicated in Spain.
What do you know about it?
Everything. You've kidnapped two agents.
One's C.I.A.
The other's British intelligence.
There's an international search
underway.
I appreciate the information.
You've saved me some time
and a few bullets.
Perhaps I could do more.
I have a proposition.
Always the businessman.
Well, those agents you've kidnapped
are quite valuable.
I know some people that would pay
an exorbitant amount of money
to get their hands on them.
Best kill them and be done with it.
Do whatever it takes.
Benjamin, you have many enemies.
Given what I know,
I imagine I could broker
a pretty lucrative deal for myself.
Are you threatening me?
As you said, I'm simply a businessman.
When opportunity knocks...
I'll expect you
within the next 24 hours.
Where should we make the exchange?
Tunisia. My compound.
Can we trust him?
He is telling the truth.
I'll arrange for transport.
Sydney, getting your father
from Masari...
We need to go in tactically.
How am I supposed to sit here
and do nothing?
It's my dad.
We both know he wouldn't want you to go.
I can't lose him.
You won't.
- A gift?
- A locator.
We need to know exactly
where Masari's holding them.
We can't risk tipping him off.
You haven't done this before, have you?
Look, I imagine you feel
somewhat to blame for all of this,
but you're not.
I'm very good at what I do.
When you're with them,
press the winding stem on the watch.
We'll do the rest.
I must admit,
you're quite fetching in black.
I will gag you.
Does this mean we can't be friends?
- Time to switch.
- Thank God.
Hey. Heard the phone ring.
Wasn't them.
Um, you want some company?
You know, while we wait?
I'd like that.
Masari's expecting me.
I'm sure Colonel Masari
will be very pleased to see you.
If you expect to be paid,
have this wreck fixed
before I'm done with my business.
How was the trip?
Exhausting, as usual.
Have you ever thought about
moving somewhere more accessible?
Remoteness is a virtue.
Yes, and it's also time-consuming.
So I'm afraid we're gonna have
to cut this visit short.
If you could take me to the prisoners,
I can be on my way.
Why the rush?
I need to be in Tunis by nightfall.
I'm afraid that, uh...
won't be possible.
Cover the entrance. Come on!
She needs medical attention.
You don't look so good yourself.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
An extraction team is standing by.
I'll call for them.
- Yeah.
- We've got them.
And Masari?
He and Sark are still missing.
- Yeah?
- Sydney, it's me.
Oh, thank God. How's my father?
He's alive, but we've got
another problem.
Can we evacuate?
No, there's not enough time.
They won't get very far.
Rachel, we're going
to talk you through this.
Okay, Rachel,
there should be a front panel.
Do you see that?
Uh... yeah. It's screwed in.
- Okay, great. Just unscrew it.
- Unscrew it? With what?
Might I suggest something sharp?
Hold on.
So what happened?
I overestimated my friendship
with Masari.
He assumed I was betraying him,
and he took the money and he left.
Oh. So then he knows you pretty well.
Okay, I unscrewed the front panel.
Now what?
Okay. If this bomb works
on microwave energy,
it should have a coaxial capacitor bank.
Do you see that?
Uh, maybe. I don't know.
It should be attached to a power source.
Okay, I found it.
Okay, great. You need to jam the pulse.
How?
Reroute the wires to a neutral bank.
- Okay.
- Wait.
- If that's the wrong wire...
- I thought you liked risks.
I also like my body.
As I recall, you do, too.
It's still armed.
That's okay. You just need to disable
the compression generator.
Look for a wire running
to the microwave antenna. Okay?
Don't you want to get Dixon?
No offense, but you haven't had
the best judgment lately.
Okay, I got it.
Cut that. That should work.
- Should or will?
- Should.
Just so we're clear...
you approached me.
You were the one that was stupid enough
to let me into your room.
And afterwards, you were the one
that wanted to cuddle.
It's disarmed.
That was spectacular, Rachel.
Thank you.
About what you just heard...
Don't need to know,
don't want to know.
I've spoken with the driver.
There's a plane waiting in Tunis.
You'll be in a London hospital
by nightfall.
Wish Sydney well for me.
I'm sorry, Elizabeth.
Don't be.
About your payment...
You'd love to arrest me right now,
wouldn't you?
Next time.
Give us the account number.
We'll wire you your fee.
Don't bother.
This one's a freebie.
You sure you don't need anything?
I could stop by on my way home.
- I'm fine, just exhausted.
- That's understandable.
Why don't we meet for breakfast?
I'll come by and pick you up.
That'd be great.
Dad...
If anything had happened,
and I couldn't have been there...
Sydney, you did exactly
what I would have wanted.
You and the baby are all that matters.
I love you, dad.
Sleep well.
Translation : Anyone Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Guilamu
Suggestions critics insults : aliassub@gmail.com
www.forom.com