Okay.
Whatever it is, I can handle.
Just don't tell me you are a bad guy.
You're not a bad guy, are you?
What?
It's no accident
that I was the one you came to
when you walked into the C.I.A.
with your story about SD-6.
Vaughn, I don't understand.
What are you telling me?
Well, for starters,
my name isn't Michael Vaughn.
Vaughn?
Don't worry.
We're gonna get you outta here.
Is he okay?
You just stay still, all right?
I don't need anything. I'm fine.
I don't need any of that.
The girl's alive.
We'll take care of her.
Copy four minutes out.
There she is!
We're gonna run a few tests
just as a precaution,
but everything appears normal.
When can I go home?
Soon.
But you're gonna have to take it easy.
Of course.
Miss Bristow?
How you feeling?
Oh, Gordon Dean,
Office of Special Investigations.
Any word on Vaughn?
No, I'm afraid not.
I hate to do this now, agent Bristow,
given what you've been through.
I already called in a report.
Yes, I know. I just need for you
to clarify a few things,
if that's all right with you.
In your report, you indicated
you two were going on vacation.
- You didn't say where.
- Santa Barbara.
And you were struck about halfway there?
About that, yeah.
What about before the accident?
Did agent Vaughn seem anxious,
perhaps preoccupied?
He seemed relaxed.
We were taking a few days off.
You're not writing any of this down.
You are not telling me
anything worth writing.
I'm telling you exactly what I remember.
I mean, if that's not enough--
You two are engaged.
- Isn't that correct?
- Yes.
And you understand
that marital privilege
does not trump
matters of national security.
Of course I do.
Then I am asking you
to remember where your loyalty lies.
My loyalty? My fiancé was just abducted.
Perhaps.
That's what we're trying to determine.
Wait a minute. What are you suggesting?
Whatever information you need,
my daughter will be happy to cooperate,
but she's just been through
a traumatic experience.
I'm sure you can afford her some time.
Of course, Director Bristow.
We'll talk again.
Soon.
Thank you.
Dad.
Sydney, when your mother defected,
I spent a year
in prison because the C.I.A.
assumed I collaborated with her.
Before you say anything
that may implicate you,
we need to go over your story.
My story? Dad, what is going on?
Vaughn is currently under investigation.
There have been a number of red flags
raised by his conduct.
What red flags?
Langley believes
Vaughn may be a double agent.
They think the crash
may have been an extraction.
I've been hearing about you
for a long time.
It's nice to finally meet you,
Mr Michaux.
Translation : Anyone Travis Sixe Guilamu
Transcript : RaceMan
Synchro : Guilamu
Suggestions critics insults  : aliassub@gmail.com
www.forom.com
You've had a bad day.
Where's Sydney?
She's in better shape than you.
Your shoulder's dislocated.
We'll take care of that.
I, uh...
I believe this was intended for you.
Oh, come on.
Don't tell me you're not curious.
Open it.
Catchy, but dated.
You mind telling me what this says?
- 5, 7, 3, 8, 4.
- We know what this is about.
We know who sent it.
What we don't know is where's Lehman.
Who?
You must be in a lot of pain.
Maybe that's why
your memory's a bit fuzzy.
Why don't we help Mr Michaux out?
It flew somewhere. Those helicopters
are stealth. They're not invisi...
Then retask the satellites.
All right, call me back with something.
- Syd.
- Any word yet?
No.
But there is a guy here from Langley,
-  and he's been insinuating...
- I know.
Why was Vaughn
assigned to be my handler?
What do you mean?
Six years ago,
when I walked into that C.I.A. office,
why was Vaughn assigned to my case?
I don't know. He asked to be.
You came in. You were all screwed up.
You had that freaky red hair.
He likes a challenge.
Hold it. You're not actually
considering this, are you?
Syd, the idea that he's disloyal,
that's insane.
Y eah.
Just tell us what we want to know.
I'm tired of playing these games.
Quitter.
Are you really gonna hold out
until we kill you?
I can respect that.
It seems Mr Michaux
needs a little incentive.
Go down the hallway to his fiancée.
- Bring her in?
- Just her finger.
- Leave her out of this.
- That's up to you, isn't it?
The one with the ring.
Kind of poetic, don't you think?
Stop!
The message,
it's in code.
I need a pencil.
Can you speed it up, agent Blinkman?
Flinkman. With an "f" sound.
Not that hard, really.
Look, I know you wanted me
to access agent Vaughn's personal files,
but I'll tell you right now,
you're not gonna find anything.
No one is judging agent Vaughn.
If he was up to something,
I'd know about it.
I mean, we're friends.
We do lunch.
How much longer?
- Hey.
How are you holding up?
What if I was wrong about him?
Sydney, you remember
when we were working for SD-6,
that night on the pier?
I caught you breaking
into a secure facility.
You asked me to trust you, but I didn't.
The proof was right in front of me.
You were a traitor.
If I had to do it over again,
I'd give you the benefit of the doubt.
Is there a problem?
I can't write. Would you mind
setting my shoulder?
Where's Sydney?
Where is she? Answer me!
She escaped. She got away!
- Hello?
- Sydney, you okay?
Thank God.
I'm fine.
Hang on.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Where are you?
- Look, I know you have questions.
- About a million of 'em.
I'll tell you everything
as soon as I can, but, Sydney,
no one can know you're talking to me.
I need my father's watch.
You need to get it to me.
Do you remember the dead drop
we used to contact Tessina, the lockers?
Of course I do...
I don't know.
Syd, please,
I need you to do this for me.
I need to think about it.
Where is he?
I don't know what you're talking about.
By withholding information,
you're only implicating yourself.
I'll give you one more chance.
Sydney, I understand your inclination
is to protect Vaughn at any cost,
but assume you're right,
that this wasn't an extraction,
that Vaughn was abducted.
Then even if he's escaped, he's still
in a tremendous amount of danger.
If you really wanna protect him,
let us bring him in safely.
He's in Mexico City.
- Perimeter's set.
- Good. Let's do it.
Go, go, clear!
You're looking for this?
I want the truth.
Start with your name.
André Michaux.
I'll tell you the rest on the way.
7 years ago, a woman came to me,
said that her father
had been involved in a project,
something that people had gone
to great lengths to cover up.
She said my father was part of it,
said it was called Prophet Five.
- You father was an agent.
- Before he joined the C.I.A.
She said his name was Michaux,
that he was a mathematician.
The day you walked into the C.I.A.,
you described a mission-to-secure device
made by a man named Muller,
the same man I was told
originated the Prophet Five project.
Now this was my first proof
that this woman's story was true.
But whatever it was
my father was running away from,
he changed his identity,
he changed mine.
I was 18 months old at the time.
And this man we're meeting,
James Lehman--
Renée and I have been trying
to find him for years.
We believe he worked with our fathers.
Renée  who? Who is this woman?
Renée Rienne.
Vaughn!
The watch-- show it to me.
You were supposed to come alone.
Whatever you say to me, she can hear.
Follow me.
I was prepared to bring
agent Vaughn in for questioning.
You think I know where he is?
Oh, I think it's possible, yes.
Your daughter, too.
I don't.
Then I have no choice.
I am now officially
classifying him a fugitive
and your daughter an accomplice.
Now if you want me to show her
any leniency,
find her and tell me where she is.
Maybe you should try Mexico City.
You'll be notified
when they've been apprehended.
- Hey, Mr Dean.
- What is it, Marshall?
He's not gonna find Sydney
and Vaughn, not from what I gave him.
I encrypted Vaughn's files, 4,096-bit.
It'll take 'em years.
I mean, he's an ass. Deal with it.
Do you still have the originals?
Get them for me.
Before I start, you should know
your father did everything he could
to protect you from this.
Mr. Lehman,
I want to know about Prophet Five.
I was a cryptologist,
a specialist in patterns
working for the Pentagon.
In 1972, a private foundation
recruited me along with others,
scientists, linguists,
the best and the brightest.
That's where I met your father.
What was the objective?
We were given one page of a book,
the "Profeta Cinque,"
"the Fifth Prophet."
A 15th-century text that supposedly
had been written in an unbreakable code.
And they wanted you to break the code.
- Were you successful?
- After years, yes.
It referred to proteins,
amino acids, nucleotides.
It seemed to be some sort of
advanced genetics
500 years ahead of its time.
Just a few days after
we turned in our report,
your father contacted me.
He told me what was happening
to the others--
accidents, car crashes,
fires, heart attacks, strokes,
all people involved with the project.
So I followed your father's advice.
I changed my name.
I disappeared.
What's changed now?
Why did you contact us?
Over the years, I've developed sources,
leads as to where
the book might be stored,
but all my attempts
at recovery have failed.
You have another lead.
These people, whoever they are,
when they know you're on to it,
they'll stop at nothing to silence you.
I'll contact you when I have the book.
Thank you, Sir.
Your invitation, please.
My husband is right. It is my fault.
Go ahead.
I was sitting over there.
I misplaced my sunglasses.
We're waltzing.
Yeah, I've been practicing
for our wedding.
With whom?
Weiss.
- Hey, I found the junction box.
- Ready when you are.
It's been customized.
Hang on. I'll call you right back.
- Hello?
- Do you remember what you said,
if you had to do it over again?
What do you need ?
Service records, pan Global Security,
serial number 16154131.
Just admiring the collection.
It's pretty gruesome if you ask me.
My dad's really into guns.
I think he's overcompensating.
You're Walter, aren't you?
What gave me away?
Dad's always going on
about the new guy at work.
Aren't you a little young?
I'm a little young
to be stuck at this snore-fest.
Looks like the safe's been rerouted
through the central alarm system.
You'll need to repatch.
Do you see a purple wire?
- Yes, I do.
- Cut it.
Got it.
Okay, tie it to the last terminal.
My dad's threatened by you, you know?
I very much doubt that.
Seriously...
he's so lame.
But you're young,
smart,
cute.
You know, this party would be
a lot more fun if we were naked.
That's not going to happen.
-  Done.
- That's it.
You just need to reset the system
and wait.
You know, there are better ways
to get back at your father.
None that involve me...
and you.
Whoa, okay.
You need to leave now,
or your dad's gonna find out
what his little girl's really like.
Jerk.
Oh, Dixon,
- Thank you!
- Be safe.
Oh, Walter?
Guess you're getting fired.
I'm heading to the extraction point.
Sydney?
This is Dr. Park.
Your test results are in.
Now isn't really the best time.
- Let me get--
- You're gonna want to hear this.
We have to go.
The doctor called.
- I'm pregnant.
- What?
You two ! Stop right there!
Arvin.
- Nadia-- how is she?
- There's been no change.
I have to get out of here, Jack.
If you're not prepared
to charge me with a crime,
you have to do something.
I am trying to expedite your release.
It's not enough.
My daughter is being kept in a coma,
a coma Jack.
She's suffering from a condition
that no one understands.
It is a condition that I am
responsible for with no hope for a cure.
I can't help my daughter
sitting in a cell
coming through obscure medical journals.
I know.
I'm sorry, Jack. I...
You didn't come here for that.
What is it?
Are you aware of the off-book trips
Vaughn took to Marseilles,
3 over the last 12 months?
They occurred
while you were head of A.P.O.
If you're looking
to find out if I tasked him. No.
Tell me what this is about.
Serbia, two years ago.
Istanbul, 2001.
Are you familiar with Le Corbeau?
The Raven, Renée Rienne.
That's right.
She's wanted for the assassination
of the Turkish Interior Minister in 2001
and for the murders
of 3 C.I.A. agents stationed in Serbia.
Vaughn's movements track with hers.
Does Sydney know about this?
Tell her, Jack.
Tell me you have something.
4,096-bit. Not bad.
But whoever screwed with these files
he used a modified version
of D.O.D.'S encryption algorithm.
I hacked in Tenesse's network
and pull the decryption key.
What did you find?
Your fugitive used a handful
of documented aliases,
one of which passed through
Italian customs last night.
You're a genius.
Yeah, I know.
He said 9. We're early.
Are we both gonna just sit here
and not talk about the thing
we're thinking about?
Where are you with this, Vaughn?
I just need to know how you feel.
Is it something you want?
The truth?
Of course.
What we do, the things
we see every day, honestly, no,
I didn't think this is what I wanted...
I mean, bringing a baby
into this world that is so messed up,
I just assumed that I'd wait,
that we'd wait.
For?
For things to be safe or at least safer.
Yeah.
I get it.
But looking at you,
all I can think about is
what our kid is gonna be like and I'm
not worried about the world.
I just..
I can't wait
to meet this new little person.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, it's pretty great, right?
Yeah and you're gonna be
an amazing mom
and I'm gonna be a disaster.
I've never changed a diaper.
Neither have I. We're gonna have
to call Marshall for an assist.
He's here.
You should go.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Start thinking of names.
Can you decode it?
It'll take awhile.
When I'm done, I'll contact you.
From now on, do not initiate
contact with me.
Vaughn.
God.
He's still in surgery.
No one's come out.
No one's told me anything.
I hope you understand what you've done.
What?
Your heroic efforts
to help Vaughn were shortsighted.
You acted impetuously
without the benefit of the facts.
You don't know
what you're talking--
Sydney,
Vaughn is not the person you think.
He's been working with a known criminal.
Renée Rienne. I know.
Then what on earth
prompted you to risk your own life,
not to mention
your professional integrity?
Dad, Vaughn and I,
we're having a baby.
There's an explanation for all of this
if you'll let me tell you.
Is he out of surgery?
He's in recovery now, but
the organ damage he sustained
was significant.
Our expectation is
that we will stop the bleeding, but
we'll know more in the next 24 hours.
I need to see him.
Well, you can wait in his room
until he wakes up.
Sydney.
I will do everything I can
to help you both.
Yes?
I just spoke with Director Chase.
Gordon Dean
wasn't Special Investigations.
He went off the grid two years ago.
- Status?
- He's presumed dead.
Hi.
Gordon Dean is a ghost,
well-placed and well-connected.
What are we gonna do?
Hey, I just broke about 30 federal laws.
If I get caught, I'll be sharing a cell
with a guy named Bruno.
It's white collar.
More like Martha Stewart.
I contacted our Italian friend.
He's got the passports.
He'll coordinate the transport
as soon as Vaughn is stable.
What's the outlook?
Sometime in the next 24 to 48 hours,
we hope.
Weiss, are you there?
Yeah, I've got the blueprints
of the Cape Town villa
right in front of me.
We're gonna have no problem getting in,
but we will need two teams.
You have my full authorization.
What about the Pentagon records?
Well, I already cross-referenced
the 1972 archives
for the name "Prophet Five."
So far, no luck.
Keep looking.
Go back at least ten years.
Someone might have slipped.
I've always liked "Owen."
Owen.
That sounds like
something you name a gerbil.
"Clementine" is cute.
For a fruit.
It's also a name.
It's also a campfire song.
Okay, you don't like that one.
What about "Isabelle"?
Isabelle Vaughn.
Isabelle Bristow Vaughn.
That's pretty.
I like that.
Me too.
I'm sorry. I'm just getting so tired.
Close your eyes. I'll be right here.
Syd?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Can I help you?
You're a hard person to find,
but if I can do it, so can they.
Sorry,
no idea what you're talking about.
I know who you are, Renée.
We need to talk.
We have nothing to talk about.
It's about Michael Vaughn.
You're Sydney.
Yeah.
How did you find me?
I know everything.
Then you should have walked away.
You don't know me very well.