Three fucking weeks
it takes you
to put me on
your visitor's list?
Just be careful.
These motherless fucks
listen to everything.
A nephew's
visiting his uncle...
who loves him.
I got nothing
to say to you.
So many tragedies
and near tragedies
to those close to you.
Don't be
so fucking smart.
Things could have
gone the other way,
my little nephew.
Yeah, but
they didn't.
What's all this shit
i'm hearing about your heart?
This problem
you and me had...
i want you to know your mother
had nothing to do with it.
She's dead to me.
She's a sick woman,
she don't have all her marbles.
Who the fuck
are you kidding?
It's killing you
that people are talking...
that an old woman
made an asshole out of you.
Not half so bad
as certain rumors
floating around
this place about you.
How tony soprano likes to
fluff up his mother's pillow
so she can get
a nice long sleep.
Who said that?
You want to make all this
nonsense disappear?
Make peace with her,
it'll look like no bad blood,
it'll be good for all of us.
No fucking way.
You tell
that fat fuck, bacala,
tell him to come out
from his mouse hole,
i want to see him tomorrow.
What for?
The black man
industrialized the north
but we're still
fighting for jobs.
Over 25 joint- fitters
on this work site,
not a black man
to be found.
Tell'em, reverend.
I'll tell you why.
Black joint- fitters,
like all black artisans,
have been shut out
of the union.
Out of work while
their white joint- fitter
is filling his stomach.
My father put his life
on the line for this country.
C'mon up here, papa.
Somebody help
my papa up here.
This is my papa!
Fought in world war ii
, the war against tyranny,
came home to establish
his own tabernacle.
When he came home,
i said when he came home,
he had to fight a differen
t kind of war all over again.
Talk to them, papa,
talk to the people, papa.
Since then we have
spilled our blood in korea,
vietnam and iraq.
Every time i say,
sweet jesus,
let them do right by our boys
when they get back here.
But somebody forgot
to tell the man.
Now, you know
what i'm talking about.
Tell them!
Yes, i'm gonna
tell them.
I'm gonna tell them no more
cutting us out.
No more!
You hear that,
mr. Masserone brothers'
construction?
No more!
Somebody tell me
what we want!
Jobs!
When do we
want'em?
Now!
Want do we want?
Jobs!
Hey, med!
I'm going to visit
"she who's name
may not be uttered".
Wanna come?
Grandma?
You mean like now?
I'd really like to
but i gotta study my french.
Stupid verbs.
No biggie.
Hey.
I want
to talk to you.
What the fuck were you doing
with that real estate sign?
Oh, yeah, i wanted
to talk to you about that.
I'm selling ma's house,
you understand, janice?
Now put that fucking sign
back in the fucking ground
and that's it!
End of discussion,
period!
You're so
left- brain.
Whether the sign's
there or not
the house is still
for sale, the agent
still has the listing.
Then what was the sign doing
in the back seat of your car?
Don't try
to deny it!
Because i'm trying
to save a little money,
is that alright?
Do you remember
cathy fiola?
She was in my class
at sacred heart
with the birthmark.
What about her?
She's in
real estate now.
She said she'd only charge
a three percent commission.
That's half, tony,
thousands of dollars.
It may not mean
anything to you, but
maybe ma could use it.
Yeah?
Fuck her.
And next time
you disappear for a week,
take that piece of shit and
park it in the fucking street!
This isn't
a fucking hotel!
We're out of cran- apple,
mrs. S. , is plain apple okay?
Oh, sure, dear.
Oh, honey?
Do you suppose you could get me
some strawberry ice cream?
They can't expect me
to eat this tapioca.
I'll see
what i can do.
She cracks me up.
Well, i can't
believe it.
It's my daughter
from california.
It's seattle, ma.
Would you like
some of my tapioca?
Good morning.
Oh, you reek
of cigarettes.
Look at you.
All dressed,
out of bed.
You see my hand?
It's all
black and blue
from where they
stuck in the needle.
That's how
you get better.
You don't care.
You weren't here
five minutes.
I had to go to
the city for a few days.
I'm pitching
my self- help video.
"Lady kerouac",
or "packing for the highwa
y to a woman's self- esteem."
You could never
stand it here.
stand yourself
and that's
why you ran away.
Let's not go there
today, ma.
You think it was
easy for me?
You don't know the kind of
man your father was!
What do you mean?
Nobody knows!
Nobody knows
what i went through.
What about daddy?
One thing
i could tell you,
it would kill him
to see me now.
Here's your ice cream, mrs. S,
then we can take our walk.
Leave me alone,
please.
Open the window
and just push me out.
I can't
take this anymore.
Mrs. Soprano, what's wrong,
what happened?
She just
started crying.
You, i know
why you're here.
You don't fool me
for a second.
You're here because
you want to take my house.
Ma!
You don't know what goes
through this mind of mine.
That's for
fucking sure!
Someday i hope you have
children of your own
and they treat you
like this.
I gave my life to my children
on a silver platter.
This is bullshit.
Talk to me.
These fucking activists,
they're killing me.
They're picketing
my place 24- 7.
Three days
i'm down already.
Who?
This hard- on,
rev. Herman james jr.
He's an old song,
not enough minorities
doing the joint fitting.
You were told
the joint- fitters union
is under my uncle's
jurisdiction.
I know.
But if you could pave the way
for me to talk to your uncle,
so he could maybe
send some guys down
and make it uncomfortable
for these people.
Like you did with
your unions before.
It's gonna
cost you.
Besides what you're
already raping me
for those no- show
electrician jobs?
You're not such
a fucking citizen
when you want a construction
bid to go your way.
Take it easy.
I'll see
what i can do.
Meantime,
call animal control.
Watch you don't
get followed meeting me.
You're late.
Bobby baccalieri,
the last man standing.
I don't want to
say nothing, tony.
You don't want to get
yourself in trouble.
A lot of funerals in
your corner of the world,
huh, bobby?
What'd you have to do,
refinance your house?
Don't look at the floor,
bobby, look at me.
I want you to talk
to that bald cocksucker
who calls himself
my father's brother.
Tell him i'm gonna let him
keep on earning.
Subsistence level.
He'll be able to pay
his defense lawyers.
Let me say for him,
thank you.
You're gonna hear
some high- end shit.
And "a", i hope
you could understand it,
and "b", i hope you keep it
between this room and junior.
Because if you don't,
i promise you,
they're gonna find
pieces of you in
eight different dumpsters.
I inherited junior.
I don't think you got reason
to talk to me this way.
I always liked you.
Bullshit.
But we'll assume
you do now.
You tell my uncle that
he gets to keep five percent,
five percent of his shy,
his sports betting,
same with the coke.
The joint- fitters union,
it's all his, okay?
Bobby, listen,
this is very important.
He also gets
to keep his stripes.
As far as the feds
are concerned,
they got the boss
of the family in jail,
awaiting trial,
and if they hear different,
it creates confusion.
Got it.
As far as the rest of
everything that junior owned,
it's now mine.
I'll get this to him, tony.
That's it.
"To the victor,
belongs the spoils."
Why don't you get
the fuck out of here
before i shove
your quotations book
up your fat fucking ass!
Mr. Bompensiero?
Is your wife here
to drive you home?
Skip.
Skip?
How we feeling?
Fucking great.
He's gonna be out of it
for another hour or so.
The injection
went great.
You'll feel the difference in
your back in a couple of days.
Buzz me when he feels
ready to leave.
Yeah, we'll
buzz you, honey.
Bzz, bzz...
my back don't feel
one iota different.
Doctor said it'll take
a couple days for
the steroids to kick in.
I gotta get
my jacuzzi.
Too much stress
in your life, sal.
Tony doesn't know
you're back yet, does he?
Jesus christ, no,
i didn't go see him yet.
You guys
are all alike.
We've seen guys
drag their dicks before,
take advantage of
the government's generosity,
playing both ends
against the middle.
Will you give me
a window over here?
Tony already thinks
maybe i flipped.
I gotta
be careful.
Jimmy altieri
ate the pill for you.
Any suspicion abou
t being an informant
went to the grave
with jimmy altieri.
Yeah, yeah.
I know tony 30 years,
now this?
Spare me, okay?
You've been on our tit
since'98.
Fucking chauffeur service
to and from the doctor,
that we had
to find for you.
If we're gonna let you
back on the streets and earn,
we want results.
The fuck tried to
suffocate his own mother!
She's a disgrace.
His own uncle
wanted him whacked.
You said so for yourself,
he's been shitting
on you for years.
I know
what i said.
Plus he's been crying
to a shrink twice a week.
You don't
owe this man dick.
Don't sit there
and tell me
you're gonna take a bullet
for some yuppie
who thinks
you're his errand boy.
Your honor,
this man should not be
removed from custody
for medical reasons.
Every time we get one
of these elder mafiosos
incarcerated,
we get the same
bag of tricks.
Your honor,
i take offense
to the characterization
of my client as a mafioso.
Mr. Soprano has not been
found guilty of anything.
He's awaiting trial
for alleged offenses.
Noted.
With all due respect to
the state's medical facilities,
in his condition,
mr. Soprano has every right
to pursue the best
possible medical care
that he can afford.
Mr. Soprano is suffering
from a very benign illness,
a few clogged arteries,
your honor.
I'm leaning towards releasing
this man from lock- up
unless you can demonstrate
a serious flight risk.
Mr. Soprano,
if i approve this
you will be under
what is called "house arrest".
Do you understand
this concept?
Not really.
It means that you must remain
in your primary residence
and cannot leave,
except for
doctor's appointments,
food shopping.
Your honor,
the government asks for
an electronic bracelet.
Your honor, while we certainly
agree to house arrest,
we are asking that mr. Soprano
not be further persecuted
for yet to be
proven allegations.
He shows no prior arrest
since 1968.
He pays his taxes,
and he's a veteran
of the second world war.
Mr. Soprano,
do you have any problem
with wearing
an electronic bracelet?
It sounds like
nazi germany to me.
Obviously, you need
a history lesson, sir.
I don't think that we--
you and i,
should let our shared
sorrow or biases
enter into this, judge.
He's wearing
a bracelet...
to avoid any risk
of flight.
Who are you?
Jesus christ, you scared
the shit out of me.
Jesus ain't got
nothing to do with it.
Now what do you
want here?
Looking for your son,
is he around?
You a friend?
Is he around?
He'll be
back here soon.
Well, c'mon in.
You were a good- looking
guy back then.
Still am.
Still got the same teeth
as in that picture.
Oh, yeah?
Go on and laugh.
Picture was taken
57 years ago.
So that makes you...?
Old.
C'mon,
how old are you?
75.
Add eight more
and you got it.
83, get the fuck
out of here.
What do you want
with my son?
Got a little business
i gotta discuss with him.
If you say so.
So, you're 28 years old
when world war ii starts.
That's a little long
in the tooth, isn't it?
'43, they was
taking everyone,
no matter how old
or how ugly.
Even took this
fat boy i knew.
He was already 34.
Wasn't no good to nobody,
except he could cook.
I swear he was more dangerous
with that stove
than he was
with that rifle.
You ever watch
the history channel?
Television?
No, this is
the history channel.
I think
you'd like it.
They even do a lot of
that bible shit.
Only shit in the bible
came out of pharaoh's ass
when moses
parted the red sea.
Parted the red sea,
praise his name.
Never underestimate a man's
determination to be free.
Um...
i'll catch up with your son
another time.
You break that,
you're paying for it.
If i'd have known you
were gonna get out so fast
with this medical shit
i never would've talked
to that calzone with legs.
He gave me
the message.
Don't fucking pout.
Be grateful
i'm letting you earn.
What's on your mind?
How'd you swing this?
This dr. Schreck,
he's monty schreck's kid.
Monty, the bookie's son?
He's a cardiologist.
That's not bad.
Law says feds can't
bug your doctor's office.
Let's me use this place
whenever i need to
to conduct business.
So, you heard about
masserone construction?
Bacala is
taking care of it.
The joint- fitters
know he speaks for me.
It's gotta go
60- 40, my way.
Did you do
what i asked?
What did you
ask me to do?
You know,
make peace.
You listen...
that's enough with that shit,
that woman is dead to me.
You let it go!
Why the fuck should i
? she's my brother's wife.
She doesn't realize
what she says half the time.
Let's put our cards
on the table here.
I heard your radio debut
on those tapes the feds
made at green grove.
So she doesn't know what
she's saying half the time.
Which half
did you listen to?
The half that doesn't
make any sense,
or the half that
we both know played you
like a fucking child?
Nobody played me.
She didn't know that she was
setting you up to get popped.
That's right.
Your uncle isn't
as dumb as you think.
You and that
miserable fuck, altieri.
That rat bastard,
all of my capos,
meeting behind my back.
Let sleeping dogs
lie, okay?
I have my reasons.
I'll tell you one dog
you left still barking,
that fucking
freddie capuano.
That motherless money- grubbing
little son- of- a- bitch--
the guy who owns green grove
retirement community?
He's like
an old fucking lady!
He's been going around
telling soprano business
to anybody
who'll listen!
He's the one that's been
saying that shit
about you trying
to whack your mother.
Even implied
that me and her...
that hairpiece
motherfucker.
Did everybody take a vow
of silence or something?
Nobody's got
anything to report?
I gotta write a report
on dna for biology.
Isn't that
interesting?
I just saw
on "inside edition"
how there will be
no more unknown soldiers
because of
dna now.
They will be able to
identify every single
casualty of combat.
Pass me more of that
macaroni and cheese.
You know, tony,
i know you don't like
to talk about her, but...
that woman
is impossible.
She's a complete narcissist,
i mean,"me, me, me".
Really kudos.
You are a saint.
You were right the first time,
i don't want to talk about it.
You talking
about grandma?
She pushes those buttons,
she's a big baby.
You know?
Excusez- moi.
Tony.
This is my house.
How many times
i gotta say it?
Thank you,
il duce.
You got
something to say?
The little girl who's
about to get her license
might want to use one of
those cars in driveway
in the next
hundred years.
It's my fault, med.
I wasn't sensitive
to his feelings.
Thank you.
You see that?
You see how
easy that was?
So, mr. Delegated
power of attorney,
have you given it
any thought?
Can my girlfriend
have the listing?
You know,
of the house?
As long
as it gets sold,
i don't give a fuck
who lists it.
Hey, what did one prick
say to the other prick?
You see that?
See what happens with you
cursing at the dinner table?
Thanks for this,
aunt par,
it's hard to find people
over 25 to drive with.
Just don't let them know
you drove me to buy some pot,
which should
be legal.
It's the only things
that works for these hands.
Med, wasn't that
a stop sign?
I just hate the way
he thinks he can talk to you.
It's so obnoxious.
He's insecure.
He's afraid
to leave new jersey
and he's threatened
by anybody who's broken free.
He's too pathetic.
How about grandma
in that rehab center?
I know, i'm dying
to go over and see her,
but i've had
so much homework,
plus all this community service
you have to do
to even think about getting
into a decent college.
I bring food
to homeless shelters.
You know grandma
pretty well,
don't you?
I guess.
What is she into?
I don't know,
negativity?
Seriously,
there must be something
that gives her pleasure.
Isn't there anything
she likes doing?
My dad used to try and find her
these old records,
these sisters.
Oh, the de castro sisters,
right.
The andrews sisters
would have been too easy.
He used to bring her
that mario lasagna guy.
Oh, yuck,
i hated that shit.
Your glasses
will be ready on thursday.
Thursday,
that's good.
Did you see me
on tv?
You were on tv?
What show?
The evening news.
Oh, yeah.
What about it?
How'd i look?
Be honest.
You looked, you know,
like you.
You looked good.
I didn't like
the way i looked.
Maybe i should get new frames,
what do you think?
What's wrong
with them?
How much those frames
set you back?
Insurance pays,
i never see the bill.
Nice country.
I got cataracts.
My father told me,
"never get old."
I should have
listened to him.
Yeah.
A chinaman goes
to see the eye doctor,
after the exam
the doctor says,
"i know why
you're having trouble."
Chinaman says,
"why?"
Doctor says,
"you have a cataract."
Chinaman says,"no,
i have a rincoln continental."
You don't
get it?
I get it,
he drives a lincoln.
What?
Excuse me,
where's the men's room?
Through the doors
to the left.
You're awake.
What--
what is that?
That music?
"Non ti scordar di me."
Pavarotti.
Did you bring it?
I never forgot how much
you liked a good tenor.
Remember when we saw
mario lanza on tv?
You and me and daddy
on the sofa,
watching ed sullivan.
I don't think we ever
missed a sunday.
Oh, my god
, my children.
Music hath charms, ma.
Thank god, huh?
I think it's time for you
to start to seriously
consider salads.
What do you mean?
What do i mean.
Get off my car before
you flip it over,
you fat fuck.
Junior wants
to know when.
Tomorrow morning.
We're short a couple of guys,
so make sure you're there.
Consider it exercise.
"Fat fuck."
Why don't you look
in the mirror some time,
you insensitive
cocksucker.
Tony,
we're sitting down!
Ma, dna,
it's invisible, right?
But guess how many nucleotides
are in each strand.
Just tell her.
A hundred million.
Wow,
that's amazing.
She knows
what time we eat.
I don't want you
setting a place for her
if she's not here.
Anthony jr. ,
want to do the honors?
Bless us our lord
on thy gifts
we're about to receive...
hello!
You guys started
without me.
Good, great.
Bless us
our lord, amen.
Janice, you know
what time we eat.
If you're gonna be late, call,
or you're not gonna eat.
Don't send me
to bed hungry, daddy.
Everybody, guess who passed
her driving test today?
She learned
from the best.
Go, girl!
I had to parallel park
behind this van
and i was so nervous.
The guy was a
real dork with a
clipboard and everything.
Oh, wow,
fascist martinet.
Salsice, janice?
Oh, i forgot,
you don't eat pork...
no.
...in that way.
Oh, i get it.
There's nothing to get,
she's a vegetarian.
I missed the fireflies
out west.
That's why
i moved out here.
Little bit
of nature.
When you were
in seattle,
you ever drive
by jimmy hendrix's house?
Mm- mmm.
You know, tony,
i know it's not your
favorite subject, but...
we had some really great news
about ma at the hospital today.
Her rehab therapist says
she's making tremendous strides
and it's not gonna
be long before
they release her.
How can she make
tremendous strides
when there's nothing
wrong with her
in the first place?
It's called
face- saving therapy.
The patient has to believe
that they're getting therapy.
Believe me, medicare's
not gonna pay for it
if it's not
as necessary as real,
would they?
And the taxpayer
foots the bill.
It's not
much longer now.
But she's gonna
need a place to stay.
She's out
on the street.
Tony, it is
her house.
Dead people
don't have houses.
Daddy bought
that house.
Tell you what...
take her back
to green grove.
What,
the nursing home?
It's a
retirement community.
You know i don't have
that kind of money.
Fuck you.
You should've seen the look
on that blimp's face
when i told him
he had to be here today.
Bacala's always
been a lazy bastard.
You can't get nobody
good anymore.
They're either
on fucking drugs
or compromised
with the law,
or they're young and
don't listen to orders.
Please.
It's all
"me, me, me".
I hope you don't feel
that way about me, tony.
It's just this back.
You done plenty.
You paid your dues.
That's
tony soprano.
What the fuck?
Hey, tony!
This is what i'm talking about,
motherfucker.
Am i supposed to be seen here,
you fucking idiots?
Now we look
like jerkoffs.
Get out of
the way!
When do
we want'em?
We want to talk
to your foreman.
You want to talk
to the foreskin?
You a wise- ass
motherfucker.
Keep your mother
off the streets
and i won't fuck her.
Justice...
motherfucker,
c'mon?
Hi, ma.
Oh, nicholas antonelli.
Dead at age 73,
of heart failure.
Mmm...
so, ma...
you're gonna be
getting out of here soon.
Want to go home?
Home?
Back to the house?
My house?
Uh- huh.
No, i don't think so,
i'll go back to
the other place.
To the nursing home?
That's for people
who don't have anybody
to look after them.
Oh, it's
not that bad.
And they give you
fresh towels every day.
Barbara said
you hated it.
It's too much
trouble.
No, ma, you can't
go back there.
Why not?
Because.
Because,
it's dangerous there.
What are you
talking about?
The owner...
is missing.
Mr. Capuano?
They suspect
foul play.
Yeah.
Ma.
Ma, you okay?
Nurse!
It's my mother.
What is it?
What's the matter?
Are you okay,
mrs. Soprano?
Oh.
Take a deep breath.
Breathe.
Why do they make
cookies that way?
You scared me, ma.
Would you just stop it,
stop it!
Just give me a minute,
go, go, stop hovering.
Perhaps this is a good time
to talk about this.
There's no emergency provision
for your mother on file.
I tried to talk
to her about a dnr
and she got
very agitated.
Dnr?
"Do not resuscitate."
It's to save the family
a lot of anguish and decisions
at a difficult time,
when there is
no quality of life.
Janice, where are
my glasses?
I can't find the tissues,
janice!
I'm sorry, tony,
but the hospital is gonna
need a decision on this.
Auxiliary "b",
what the fuck?
It you're gonna have
power of attorney, tony,
you're gonna have to
act like one.
Who gives a fuck,
dnr, no dnr?
Yeah, okay, great,
so then what happens
when she goes into a coma
and they have to keep her alive
with tubes and machines,
because you won't
sign the dnr?
What?!
When she becomes
a vegetable
she's not gonna
give a fuck about anything!
To deprive your mother
of a place of live.
To deprive me my chance
to make peace with my mother.
You know what,
janice?
Take her,
you can have her.
The two of you in that house,
you deserve each other.
It'd be worth it
just to watch.
It'll be like,
"whatever happened to
baby janice over there."
I'll give you
your fucking dnr!
Mom, i can't
find the keys.
Keys to what,
to the car?
You got
a driver's license,
not a license to g
o carousing around
on a school night.
Mother, i was going to take
anthony to visit grandma.
You said
we can visit her.
If you want
to drive us, fine.
Now you want to
visit grandma?
Can we mom?
No funny business.
You go to
the hospital and back.
The level of trust
in this family,
check the mileage
if you want to.
God.
You go ahead,
i'll come down later.
Why, where are
you going?
Hunter's back in
"eating disorders"
upstairs.
No, that's not fair.
I'm just gonna
say hello.
I'm telling.
I was gonna let you
drive in the ibm
parking lot this sunday.
Look who's here!
Anthony,
come over here.
Give your
grandma a kiss.
Oh...
ah...
i thought
you were janice.
She comes over everyday
to play pinochle with me.
Daughters take better care
of their mothers, that's why.
She's home,
i think.
You didn't ride over here
on your bicycle in the dark?
No, meadow
drove me.
Meadow?
Well, where is she?
I don't know.
She's another one.
They don't care
what happens to you, johnny.
They stick you
away somewhere
and they forget
you ever existed.
I guess.
Have a torrone.
No, i don't like
those italian candies.
Go ahead,
take one.
He's not even
washing his hands.
You know the thing about
louisiana food,
is that it's not really spicy,
it's just well- seasoned.
Don't we season
everything down there?
Absolutely.
So what we're
gonna do is i got a
little cayenne pepper...
grandma, what's dnr?
Who?
Dnr, it's initials,
like, i had to do
this report on dna,
but i heard dad and
aunt parvati talking
about your dnr.
So, is that
like similar?
Aunt?
You mean, janice?
Janice? They were
talking about me?
About your dnr.
'Cause that's what's confusing,
like, dna,
everybody's got that.
She thinks
i should have a dnr?
Or that dad should
give it to you or something.
Because what if you went
into a coma or something?
But dna doesn't
prevent coma's,
does it?
I don't know, i gotta
do this report by monday.
Very good, livia,
that's perfect.
I know my alphabet.
Guess what, ma?
I got great news.
Tony's not gonna
sell the house.
When you get released,
we're gonna take you back home.
Really?
Yeah.
And i'm gonna
live with you.
Why?
So you cannot
resuscitate me?
So i can what?
Oh, i seen that movie
with richard widmark.
Movie, ma?
Oh, mrs. Soprano.
No, take this one.
She gets her ballet shoes,
she sells them
and she takes the money
to newark,
and she buys
amphetamines.
She was
a child then.
I think you should go
live with your daughter,
mrs. Soprano.
I think i'm gonna leave
all my money to you, honey.
What are you
talking about, money?
I've gotta catch up
on some charts.
Janice, what'd
i tell you last week?
Where'd
i put my money?
You know,
this is very important.
I must have
put it somewhere.
Oh, c'mon, settimia.
No, you don't
fool me.
I know what
you're thinking about.
My name's janice.
Janice, ma.
You named me.
It's something else
you threw away of mine.
Are you sure?
I didn't tell you
where i put that money?
Let's not
worry about that.
Let's just
get you better
so you can go home
and i can take
good care of you.
And if it's there...
we'll find it.
Your sister's cunt!
That was wonderful, reverend,
thank you.
Now you call us
if you need anything.
Thank you.
Goodnight.
What's all this?
My father'
s passed away.
I was just
talking to him.
He lived well.
God blessed hi
m with longevity.
What are you gonna do?
We all will have our time.
My father didn't know about
our business arrangement.
He wouldn't
have approved.
Yeah, i got
that feeling.
Your moms and pop
still here?
My old man's
been gone for years.
Moms?
She still around,
she's too miserable to die.
Their generation's
almost all gone.
When the
last one goes,
we become the old folk
s at the family functions.
What are you
talking about?
We're still fucking kids,
for crying out loud.
Don't you
believe it, tony.
When the last one dies,
it signals the beginning
of the last stretch for us.
Don't get me wrong,
i'm not looking to go
no time soon,
it's just...
just feels funny now
being...an elder.
This is your end of
the demonstration bust- up.
Your guys went
a little too far.
Rasheen taylor
almost lost an eye.
How'd you do
overall?
Masserone gave me
five no- shows.
We whack it up
two and a half each.
Three- two.
I should be looking for
three- two my way.
I got to kick upstairs
to uncle junior.
Two and a half each.
All your guys
are in on this shit.
These protesters find out
i'm lining my pockets
with their blood,
it's me
they're crying for.
Hell, no,
three- two.
I'll think about it.
What'd you hear about
the public school
asbestos removal project
over in kearney?
Just waiting to see
who gets the bid.
Alright.
Hey, rev...
sorry about
your old man.
Hello.
He did?
Where is
he now?
Hello?
Oh, you're home.
How dare
you call here.
I called now on purpose.
Because i know
johnny's at work.
Anthony, your son,
anthony.
He harbors resentment
against me
and to this day
i don't know what i did.
I'm hanging up.
I just want
you to know
what pennies i have,
i leave to the children.
Your children
and barbara's children.
I raised three children
of my own.
I did a pretty
good job on two.
They are all unhappy.
Sure, you listen
to that janice.
Be very careful,
because she's a real
snake in the grass.
She has no work ethic,
why is that?
If anything
happens to me...
hello?
Hello?
Oh.
Where is he?
Did you
call an ambulance?
I don't need
no fucking ambulance.
See?
Oh, yeah, sure,
look at you.
C'mon, we're going
to the emergency room.
Fuck that,
i'm alright.
Why don't we just
go down there and make sure?
Uncle jun.
Hey...
you still here?
No fucking ambulance.
I'll drive you, okay?
Bacala will come.
Yeah, sure.
We'll all go.
Help me up.
Can you walk?
I think
he broke his hip.
Oh, fuck you.
Take it easy,
hold on a minute.
I'll be okay.
Give me a minute
to catch my breath.
Alright.
What are you doing?
What, do you
want a piggy- back?
Get the door.
Anthony...
don't let me go to my grave
with this guilt.
You listen to me,
you old prick,
you're not
going anywhere.
Make things right
with your mother, please.
Captions copyright 2000
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.