A division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.
Okay, listen up.
This is the nasd series seven
stockbroker's exam.
It will test your
basic knowledge
of stocks, bonds,
and other securities.
If your last name
starts with a through l,
you should be
next door.
The exam
is in two parts,
each part
is three hours long.
There will be
a one hour break.
As i call your name,
please answer,"here".
Martin,
samantha.
Here.
Mcclure, peter.
Moltisanti,
christopher.
Here.
Tony...
ton'!
Jesus christ!
Talk to you?
Where the fuck
you been?
We're gonna
talk here.
Come into
the house.
I got your word
if i walk in there,
i'm walking back out.
I don't see you
for all this time,
no word, nothing.
And this is the way
you come back to me?
Do i got
your word?
Coffee?
No.
You look good.
Tan.
Yeah, right.
The tan ghost.
You're a good guy, tony,
but you abuse that joke shit.
What do you go
t to say to me?
I'm back, tony,
i'm tan.
I'm in a fucking
tan nightmare
what do you think,
i'm stupid?
I don't know it,
when every fuckin'
one of my friends
turns their hearts to
stone against me, fuck!
Easy, okay.
I don't think
you're stupid.
There was a fuckin' rat.
So, you finger me?
You think i didn't realize
what was going on
when you come to my house,
three o'clock in the afternoon,
telling me
you're my friend.
That's when i knew
i was in trouble, anthony.
When outta the blue,
you come,
and for no reason,
you start telling me
you're my friend.
Oh, is that right?
Anthony jr. , get up!
You owe me the
fuckin' explanation,
and you know what
i'm talking about.
Well, remind me, tony,
never to get sick again, huh?
Remind me, please, never
to have a serious illness,
because, with you,
and silvio, and paulie,
and all you pricks,
weakness could spread
as fuckin' treason!
You know what?
Fuck you!
I don't wanna hear about
your fucking back anymore!
Who's your
fucking boss, huh?
fucking boss?
Who gets the
explanation?
What, am i
supposed to trust you?
You- fuckin'- off- the
reservation- cocksucker!
It was a broad, tony,
it was complicated.
My back was for shit,
you knew that.
I don't wanna fuckin' hear
anymore about your back!
That's how we met.
That's why i was
popping percosets
like freaking jujubes!
Anyway, my doctor,
he prescribes this
clinic for me,
in puerto rico.
I didn't exactly
object, tony,
given the fuckin'
vibes around here.
Go ahead, check.
You don't tell your wife
you're in the hospital?
That twat brought on
most of this.
How?
Listen, down there,
i met this girl.
26, an acupuncturist.
It was the only thing
that fuckin' really helped
with my sciatic nerve.
Anyway, one thing
lead to another.
You can't send
one feeler to me?
I'm gonna trust
you, paulie?
Take the word
of a degenerate
cop over me?
Tony, who are you
talking to down there?
Jesus!
So, why'd you
come back, huh?
What changed?
Nothing changed,
that's the problem.
I still got two kids
in college, tony.
One just got married,
needs my help.
I gotta start
earnin' again.
I gotta get
my action back.
Oh, just like that?
I came to you, tony,
i'm in your hands.
Bring up two cases
of bottled water with you!
Come here.
Come here,
you fat fuck.
Hey, my back, hey.
I still gotta get
these freaking shots.
You fuckin'
beached whale.
Hey, you wanna
pat this down, too?
Come here.
Come on.
Don't you ever pull
shit like this again.
So your uncle's
under indictment?
12 rico predicates.
Who stepped up
to run his crew?
His piss boy,
philly parisi.
Oh, yeah, philly.
Philly, don't
forget the pastries!
That's my favorite bag,
don't lose it.
Yo, philly.
Were you
waiting long?
Not bad.
We were late
landing, anyhow.
Hey, thanks for
doing this, philly.
Coming off the lam
, every nickel counts.
These fuckin' cabs.
So how's boston?
Well, it was good
to be back for a while,
then, you know.
Do i?
That place
is scranton,
with clams.
So, what's been
going on?
Same tale of woe.
What the hell do i hear about
tony soprano and his mother?
Some kind of accident?
He had her in a
nursing home,
you know?
Get the fuck
out of here.
And this, upse
t junior, no end.
And when junio
r come after him,
tony went to the home,
and tried to suffocate
his own mother.
Maybe you shouldn't
spread that rumor.
That's some ugly shit.
I'm only telling you.
Listen, you'd be
fuckin' amazed.
There's more?
Ehh...
no, what?
He was seeing
a psychiatrist.
Tony?
Fuckin' broad
from montclair.
Anyway, this,
is who leads us now.
There you go, kid.
There you go,
you big mouth fuck!
It's done.
Maybe she's
seeing someone.
You know,
the way i see you.
If she were,
she'd never tell me.
I'm afraid we'll
have to stop now.
When's your office
going to be finished?
Oh, my new carpet's
not in yet.
I'm sorry, i know
this is awkward.
My old therapist used
to work out of his home.
That's not
convenient for me.
Yes?
It's all over, it'
s safe to go home now.
How did you get
this phone number?
Where are you
calling me from?
Are you watching me?
You know, from
what you told me,
webistics would be perfect
for your portfolio.
I understand you're
on a fixed income,
but, with webistics,
you could triple
your money in a year.
Uh- huh, yeah,
10, 12 months.
What time is it?
So,"e. F.",
i'm listening.
It's fuckin'
tedious, this shit.
Well, you
are the boss.
And if it's your
executive decision
to go down the shore,
fuck it.
Yeah.
Yo, matthew.
I gotta take
a meeting...
keep things
in control here.
Word up,
later chief.
I really shouldn't
be telling you this.
The company's
webistics.
It's the next
yahoo right now.
We're really
only selling it
to prefrred clients.
Yeah, american forestry,
19 and 1/2, up 3/8s,
a very
sound company.
Uh- huh.
Well, it depends o
n whether you wanna go
for growth or value.
We got hundred
s of mutual funds
you can
choose from.
Ahh!
You're supposed
to push webistics!
I was giving
them alternatives.
Webistics is our
pick of the week.
Why, it's got a three
million float,
and their technology's
two years behind.
Your stock's a dog.
Ahh!
Hey, stop that!
Hey, i'm still
the manager here,
this is unacceptable.
Where's moltisanti?
I'm gonna make a call
if you don't think i know
who really
runs this operation.
Get back in your
fuckin' office.
Anybody else got a problem
with webistics?
Tony...
hey, counselor,
how are you?
How are you?
Good.
You look
good, huh?
Have a seat.
You want a drink?
No.
Before we commence,
a thousand thank yous
for webistics.
I sold off some of
my disney to buy it.
My pleasure.
So, where do we
stand this month?
Your uncle's petitioning
to get out of jail
on a medical
pending trial.
Let him.
Neil thinks they're
liable to let him out.
Maybe as a temptation
for you to act, again.
Since you are
at the helm,
it all gets back to
putting up bigger blinds.
Really limiting your exposure
to potential rico boo- boos.
The only way to run
a family these days
is bunker style.
You peer out
through the slit.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
You're not gonna
believe this.
Your sister's here.
Barbara?
Nope, janice.
You're shitting me.
Nope.
I wonder what
the scam is this time.
Whatever it is, i'm gonna
be five grand lighter
before she raindances
back to the commune.
Alright, tell her she can
stay with us if she wants.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
We'll get barbara
and tom and the kids,
and we'll make
a family reunion out of it.
But obviously...
your mother
isn't welcome.
Give janice my love.
See you later.
My sister's here
from seattle.
Nice.
Where is he?
Let me pinch those
bulldog cheeks.
Come over here.
Puerto rico?
Yeah.
That water
down there...
you think you woulda
shit some of this
weight off!
Did you tell him
we were about to
start crabbin'
the hackensack river
looking for him?
What the fuck's
the matter with you?
Tony explained it.
Listen to this.
You heard abou
t jimmy altieri?
Yeah, flipped,
fuckin' asshole.
He had two assholes
when they buried him.
So, all my money that
was on the street,
all those payments,
i guess, just evaporated.
We made your
pick- ups,
they're ready and
waiting for you.
Thanks, paulie.
I mean that,
no shit.
All those pricks
paid up to the letter?
A few things got
lost in the confusion.
I'm sure you could
picture.
We did the best we could
with the information we had.
The boss of the family
deserves the credit
right here.
Salut.
Salut. Salut.
Hey, sil?
What?
"What."
I've been gone a long time,
let me hear it.
"Just when they
thought i was out,
"they pull me
back in.
"Alright, just
this one time.
I'll let you ask m
e about my affairs."
"Is it true, michael?"
"No."
"You fuck!"
"Our true enemy,
has yet to
reveal himself."
He's on a roll!
I gotta get
the fuck out of here.
Oh, tony, i hate
to ruin the party.
I got a call from
loiaco down at
brokerage.
Fuckin' chip and dale
sent one the brokers
to the
emergency room.
Oh, fuck me,
these kids!
My fuckin'
nephew, right?
You call him,
and you tell him
i wanna see him
right away.
It all checks out.
Puerto rico,
the clinic.
All that shit from
what i can tell.
How was the guest bed,
did you sleep alright?
Great.
Except, usually
i bring my own pillow,
ergonomic,
it got ripped off at
the bus stop in rapid city.
Linoleum's not good enough
for you to sleep on no more?
Look who decides to join us,
my little brother.
How you doing, jan?
Parvati.
I'm her brother,
i get a pass.
You look good,
you look...
like a teenager.
My therapist says
i'm regressing.
Oh, your therapist,
who pays for that?
The state of
washington.
Total disability.
Oh, yeah,
the epstein- barr.
Was. Chronic carpel tunnel
from my last job,
the steam milk machine.
No worse pain.
Hey, i stayed up
waiting for you,
when'd you get in?
Late, morning.
What the fuck
is that smell?
Miso soup,
it's seaweed.
She's been telling us
all about seattle.
If i see those
grunge pants on you,
you'll be on the
ground looking up.
Dad, how do you
stay so hip?
I'll be back in a sec.
And don't let your
father near my soup.
He makes fun,
but before noon,
he'll eat anything
that's not locked away.
You don't see your
sister for years,
right away you start
in on her diet?
Hey, believe me, she gives
as good as she gets.
Give me a hit
off that.
Oh, who's in
charge here?
You look sensational,
janice, really.
Not a line.
Two beautiful kids
, you must be proud.
Yeah, yeah,
how'bout that, huh?
Even with
our genes.
So, you still
with that, uh, adolph?
Rolf.
No.
Rolf went back
to andorra.
You seem good,
mood- wise.
Yeah, things are
very good nowadays.
So, how are things
really, with ma?
She's dead to me.
I don't wanna get in
your way here, tony.
You're the one who stayed,
you took the brunt.
Barbara and i, we're
never gonna forget that.
Well, you forgot it okay
for about 20 years.
At least barb
pitched in.
I know i made
my share of mistakes.
But, ma can't stay in
the hospital forever.
Let me tell you something
about this stroke of hers,
and i got this
from a doctor.
It's called a
conversion reaction.
It's a big fuckin' opera
brought on by repressed rage.
It's bullshit.
There was no infarc-
whatever- the- fuck.
But they also said
the symptoms are
the same as a stroke,
so the results is the same,
she cannot take
care of herself.
She's on the lam in
that fuckin' hospital,
from me.
Well, who did what to who,
it's not my business.
All i know is mom is
bewildered by all of this.
I mention you, her eyes
fill up with tears.
Oh, boy.
I'm not asking you
to step in, tony.
It's my turn now,
that's why i came.
She's a streg',
she's the devil.
She was.
Now, she's
just a confused,
frightened, old woman.
So, look, all i need is
a couple hundred bucks.
To fix her car
so i can get back and
forth to the hospital.
Then i'll take her
home to seattle.
Maybe, stay at her
house here temporarily.
Oh, i doubt that.
I just put her house
on the market.
Oh.
Look...
...i'm glad
you're here, okay?
You wanna play
florence nightingale,
that's your choice.
Only this is
the last time
we mention her
in this house.
Okay.
Hey, t!
Seven and seven
over here.
Whoa, whoa, what's
the matter now?
What's the matter?
I got a call from loiaco
down at the brokerage.
Your two friends beat
the shit out of a broker.
Two others quit.
The guy was pushing
some other stock.
It attracts
negative attention.
Then the two fucks
rip off a porsche carrera
from our
own building.
I'll call them.
No, you'll
go down there, now.
What did you get your
license for, christopher,
your resume, huh?
I've been
telling you,
spend more time down
at the brokerage.
You're the fuckin'
sce compliance officer
for christ's sake.
You gotta exercise
impulse control.
Okay, tony.
I'm sorry.
Okay, alright.
I can't show it
in this condition.
What the hell
is this?
There's a
high school
up the street.
A sink was left
on upstairs.
You don't even wanna
see the toilets.
Excuse me.
Wait until i catch
the kids who did this.
Break a few windows,
they think they're
johnny bad- ass
the fuckin' jackals.
Will you stop,
please?
Your sister barbara and
the kids are coming down.
You better not be
in this mood.
And i need you
to pick up sausage.
Yeah, yeah,
how many pounds?
Hot or sweet?
Don't you act
like it's a chore.
This party was
your idea.
You said
you were happy
janice was home.
And my parents
are coming.
Oh, really?
What, now that
the dragon lady's gone,
they'll step foot
in our house?
She said some
horrible things
to them
over the years.
I'm not defending her,
she's dead to me.
I'm telling you,
you mope your
way through this,
i will cut
your throat.
What are you
talking about, mope?
I've been in
a great mood lately.
Right.
I think you need t
o start therapy again.
You're self medicating
, we haven't had sex in--
forget it,
no therapy.
You really should
take a look
at what they did to
your mother's bedroom.
They're rookies,
they're young guys,
they're not used to
this kinda of stress,
so, they get
impulsive...
he better not say
one fuckin' word.
...you got
my word on that.
I appreciate it,
chris, thank you.
Come on in.
Hey, chris, brough
t you a little capp'.
Thanks.
Sit down.
Refresh my memory abou
t this play we're making
on webistics.
We own 400, 000 shares.
Trade on the
bulletin board, otc.
If we cold- call enough
senior citizens,
pump and dump.
Yeah, listen, you guys
ain't spent much time
in the nfl,
let's face it.
What the fuck
you talkin' about?
Two years with
eddie stakes.
Besides waxing
eddie's car.
When he did
the jolt in county--
then you know when
you're bleedin' a guy,
you don't squeeze him
dry right away.
Contrarily, you let him
do his bidding,
suavely.
So, you can bleed him
next week
and the week after,
at a minimum.
You mean, we don't need one
of these guys getting pissed
and running to the sce.
I mean, is that
what you're saying?
Break it down.
Sorry, chris.
Webistics is at 80,
when are we
dumping the stock?
You'll know that
when you need to know that.
Excellent.
This is cold,
by the way.
Guys...
anymore porsches disappear,
make it two towns over,
and i want a taste.
You're the man.
Grandma's gonna be
so happy to see you.
Grandma, it's me.
Look who's here.
Ma, i'm going
downstairs.
You spend the whole day
on that elevator.
Grandma,
you've gotta eat.
Let me die.
Don't say that.
I saw a light,
there were voices
calling out to me.
Grandma, what went on
between you and dad?
Mom won't tell
me anything.
What, why,
what did he say?
Nothing, he won't
mention you at all.
Oh, that one.
He blames me
for everything.
I know,
me too.
At night,
they hit us.
Why can't this family
just get along?
Some peopl
e don't wanna.
But you, you
listen to him.
You do what
he says.
He's your father.
I won't let them leave
you here like this.
They can't stop me
from seeing you.
Meadow, meadow,
take that.
In the drawer.
In the drawer,
take it.
Oh, my god.
This was your
grandmother's,
wasn't it?
It's so you won't
forget me.
Come on, motherfuck!
Motherfuck...!
...fuck...
i told my family
i got broadsided, but,
i passed out
behind the wheel.
See, my mother and me,
we had a fallin' out.
And, since then,
things have been good.
Clean break.
What kind of
falling out?
One of those
unfortunate
situations.
A lot of
screaming.
Profanity.
Anyway,
things were good.
And then my sister
came back.
It's good to see her,
i guess.
Cues from childhood
kick in, older sister.
That should be
obvious enough.
Yeah, but
those feelings
are starting to bleed
into my business.
What sort of
business are you in?
Commercial waste.
Mr. Spears,
i watch the news,
like everyone else.
I know who you are,
and i saw "analyze this".
I don't need
the ramifications
that could arise
from treating someone
like yourself.
"Analyze this"?
Come on, it's
a fuckin' comedy.
I'm not taking
new patients right now.
Oh, my baby
sister!
Oh, you look great.
Who is thi
s little guy?
Traffic was terrible.
Keep it down out there,
you'll scare the neighbors.
Fuck!
Carm, tony says
the fire's almost ready.
Great, par',
i'll be out in a second.
Parvati, she's
a cheese now?
It's a hindu goddess.
Nice for her.
She still answers
to janice, ma,
if it makes you
more comfortable.
Hugo, go t
o the market,
pick up a couple
of cans of pears.
Canned pears,
not fresh.
That's the secret
to my pound cake.
Get some basinigol
' while you're there.
The pears,
you want
the dole?
I'm not even gonna
answer this time.
There is a new market, dad,
down on pompton pike.
A lot of changes
since you've been here.
With that
"mommy dearest" around
never again,
i swore it.
Which is exactly
what she wanted.
You played right into
her hands with that.
Remember what she said
to you at your wedding?
She said it
was a mistake,
tony would get
bored with you.
Hey, take
it easy!
I love seeing them
like that, over a fire.
They're better
over a spit.
Who's anthony look like
to you, right now?
Dad.
We stopped in to see
ma on the way over.
How do you
think she is?
Mom, a little weak,
but, she's all there.
Some family reunion.
The woman who
bore them all
is barred from
the premises.
I don't think you should
get too close, janice,
look what she tried
to do to tony.
I have no fantasies
about my mother.
You know, he's trying
to sell the house?
What house?
Ma's house.
See, that's what
i'm talking about.
Don't get involved
, let tony handle it.
I only called you
'cause you're far away.
I thought you
would wanna know
if your mother was ill.
$180, 000 he's asking
for that place.
Like he needs that.
Well, i'm glad
someone's taking charge.
You'll get your cut.
Ma's not dead yet,
and there's no will.
What?
I mean, ma still
has rights.
Tony pays for the
retirement home,
the upkeep
on her car.
Hey, parvati,
take it easy.
According to you, that
coulda been robert mitchum.
Jesus christ, fuckin'
paulie gaultieri.
Isn't he dead yet?
You're not gonna
stay for dessert?
We got ben
and jerry's,
we got a pear grappa
cake my mother made.
Yeah, i know,
but my friends
are havin' this gallery
opening in chelsea.
I'm tryin' to get them
to finance my video.
I'll leave some
cake out for you.
Hey, i'm sorry.
Hey.
What's up?
What the fuck?
I'm sure there's
an explanation.
There is,
there is.
Take ma back
to seattle.
She came here for the
house, and a $400 car.
That was the con
from the first.
That's the level
she works at.
Maybe the sign
was broken.
Maybe it fell down.
I'm still a little
fat kid to her.
What does she think?
She's gonna stop
the house sale
by picking up one
fuckin' sign?
If she were here
i'd be bouncing her
head against the wall!
Look at yourself, tony.
Look at how
angry you are!
What do you care
about that house?
It's not gonna stop
with the house.
The $300 pillow which
we're gonna pay for.
The video equipment,
which you already
heard her talkin' about.
When are you getting
back into therapy?
Don't star
t with that.
I'm not fuckin' insane,
and i'm not overreactin',
'cause you don't know
this wretched little...!
Alright, alright, this
is getting you no place.
Go outside,
join the party.
Be with your friends,
have some pleasure.
Go ahead.
Fuckin' bitch.
Tony, go ahead,
go have a beer.
What the fuck
are you doing?
Second seatin'
coming up.
Fuckin' moron.
Look at my wife
over there.
No wait, ton',
the neighbor's st. Bernard
is on your property.
You're a
fuckin' moron.
Anyway, we flew
first class...
what service,
forget about it.
Since when do you get
frequent flier upgrades?
The only time
you ever took a trip
was with that rockette that
you claimed you were fuckin',
and then she put
lsd in your drink.
Where'd you get the tickets?
The cuban?
I always thought
there was some way
to divert frequent flier
mileage on a grand scale.
To do that, yo
u gotta break into
the airline's
main computer.
What do they
call it, crackin'?
Hackin'.
Shelley hack,
remember her?
You didn't like it?
Fuck off.
So, when do we get
to roll with tony?
What?
What, are
you trippin'?
We gotta work
our way up,
get introduced.
You must be deep,
hangin' out with him.
Who?
Mr. T. You's cap
motherfuckers together?
Nah, he's
too big for that.
He doesn't get
his nails dirty.
You tell him,
we don't mind that shit.
We'll do
anything.
Wet work,
pick up his shirts.
Does tony ever
talk about us?
No.
You gonna drink or
just sit there?
Sit.
What the fuck is
the matter with you?
What's the matter?
You leave
my gas burner on?
I almost lit a cigarette,
i could have died.
I apologized.
Why you can't
use a lighter
to cook your shit
like normal people
is beyond me.
When everything was finally
going good between us--
shut up
about that!
Why, they're still
gonna kiss your ass.
They don't care
if you're a junkie.
Sit down!
I hate you,
fuckin' pig,
get off me.
You fuckin' whore.
Fuck you!
That's it, go home,
get my dinner ready!
Don't yell,
don't scream.
All cutlery stays
right where it is.
How's the bagels
in this place?
Come on, you don't
answer my calls,
i got no choice.
Walking away
is a choice.
Ruining my practice,
it's a choice.
You got your office back,
no harm done.
One of my patients
committed suicide
because i wasn't
available to her.
You know what
that means to me?
She can't eat bagels,
she can't call in sick
because she's feeling blue,
she's gone.
She's in the ground,
because of you.
I don't deserve
your help.
I hate your
fuckin' system,
i told you.
Fuck you.
But, i got a family,
and believe it or not,
they're better off
with me than without me.
I don't know
what else to do.
I drove off the road
a couple days back.
You look fine.
The air bag.
You always told me
if i was drivin'--
that was a different
time for us.
Alright,
i don't blame you.
Maybe you can recommend
somebody else?
I would never ask
another colleague
to get involved
in this.
How many more
people have to die
for your
personal growth?
Look at me.
I swear,
to jesus christ,
nobody got killed
because of you.
Get out of my life.
Hey.
What are you doing
home at this hour?
Nothing.
I thought it was a. J. ,
home from school.
Yeah.
You alright?
Want a little
cold past'?
I can microwave it.
Looks good.
You want cheese?
Something to drink?
No.
Sit down.
Captions copyright 2000
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.