(Man) ...Has Traffic Backed Up
On The West Side Highway.
The Red-Carpet Event
Was Thought To Be A Fund-Raiser
For Patrick Darling's
Senate Campaign,
But Turns Out
It's Just A Birthday Party
For Their Family Lawyer
Nick George.
And That's Your Weather
And Traffic...
(Man) Mister--Mr. George,
How Did You Do It?
Will Tripp
Be Putting His Powerbehind Patrick's
Senate Campaign?
Yes, But To What Extent
Remains A Question.
Nick, Tell Us,
As The Darling Family Lawyer,
How Were You Able To Broker
This Historic Reconciliation
Between Father And Son?
Well, It Was, Uh,
It Was Quite An Adventure.
Thank You.
(Man) What--What Are Your Plans
For Your Birthday?
(Letitia)
Here's The Birthday Boy.
Letitia Darling,
You Look Beautiful.
How Are You?
Mm. Sorry We Didn't Have Time
To Plan Anything Too Fancy.
Oh, Well, I'm Sure
This Will Be Just Fine.
Happy Birthday, Nick.
Thank You.
Have You Seen My Wife?
Lisa's Not With You?
No. No.
If You'll Excuse Me.
Patrick, Where's That Wife
Of Yours?
Ellen's Not Alcoholically
Indisposed Again, Is She?
No, Mother.
I'm Sure She's Just Running
A Few Moments Late.
(Laughs) No.
Brian Used To Be A Minister.
He Was One For Ten Years
But He's Working For Me Now.
Got A Little
Too Much Sun, Hmm?
Yeah, Paddy And I
Went Sailing Yesterday
Off Our Place
In The Hamptons.
Hey, Nick.
I Want You To Meet
An Old Friend Of Mine.
Hal Matheson, Nick George.
Nice To Meet You.
Your Dad
Was A Hell Of A Guy.
He'd Be So Proud Of You
If He Was Still With Us.
Thank You.
Hey, Brian.
(Lowered Voice) You Haven't
Seen Lisa, Have You?
No. But If You See
A Waiter...
Hello, Princess.
Hi, Daddy.
Have You
Got Something For Me?
A Kiss...
And This.
Thank You.
Hey.
You Made It.
I Did.
So Are We Okay?
We're Okay.
Can The Birthday Boy
Come Up Here, Please?
You Ready?
(Letitia) Over Her Nick.
Nick...
What Can I Say?
Never Before--
Well, Maybe Once Before,
And I'm Thinking
Of Nick's Dad Dutch--
Has One Man Done So Much
To Hold A Family Together.
What's This?
That...
Is The Key To That--
That Boat.
It's Yours.
Happy Birthday.
Thank You.
What's Going On?
(Man) N.Y.P.D.
Prepare To Be Boarded.
What's Happening, Nick?
Nobody Move.
What Did You Do, Nick?
Prepare To Be Boarded.
What The Hell Did You Do?
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
48 HOURS EARLIER
Tripp And Letitia Want To
Throw Me A Birthday Party.
It'll Be Small And Simple,
Just Us And The Darlings.
The Darlin Don't Do
Small And Simple.
Well, Then It'll Be
Large And Complicated,
But We Have To Do It.
Where Are You Going
All Dressed Up?
Gallery Hunting.
Nick, I Was Really Hoping
It Would Be Just Us
For Your Birthday This Year.
All Right. Here's What
We're Gonna Do--
We're Gonna Get A Sitter
For Tonight,
And We're Gonna Have
Our Dinner, Just Us.
Thank You.
But Tomorrow, We're Gonna Go
Yachting Wh The Darlings
Semiformal.
Perfect. I'm Looking
Semi-Forward To It.
All Right.
I Have Got To Go.
Six Months Of Mending Fences
Between Patrick And Tripp
Are About To Finally Pay Off.
Must Be Some Fence.
Well, You Said It
Yourself, Lisa.
The Darlings Don't Do
Small And Simple.
If You Don't Want Me Involved
In Your Senate Campaign, Son,
Just Say So.
Of Course
I Want You Involved, Dad.
But You Don't Know How To Be
Involved Without Creating An Air
Of Constant Judgment
And Pervasive Meddling.
Patrick,
We Just Made Headway.
Let Me Guess Where You Get
Those Ideas From. Simon Elder.
I Get My Ideas
From My Own Mind, Dad.
I Severed Ties With Simon
A Long Time Ago.
Ever Since You Left This
Family's Sphere Of Influence,
Your Life Has Spun
Completely Out Of Control.
Out Of Your Control, Perhaps.
Listen,
You're A Passionate Family.
You're A Family Of
Strong Opinions, So Naturally,
Sometimes You're Gonna
Get Into Conflict.
But At The End Of The Day,
You're Still A Family.
You Love Each Other.
You're There For Each Other.
His Campaign Is In A Shambles!
We're Still Ahead
In The Polls.
Not For Long
Keeps Showing Up
At Every Campaign Speech,
At Every Fund-Raiser
Three Sheets To The Wind.
The Rigors Of Public Life
Have Taken Their Toll, Yes.
Maybe It's Just That She's
Trying To Deaden The Pain
Of Having Lost You
To Your Vanished Carmelita.
That's It, Nick.
We're--We're Done, Here.
Wait A Second.
Everybody Just Calm Down.
Now I Have Worked--
We've All Worked--
The Last Six Months
To Make This Moment Happen.
Well, This Moment Is Over.
(Tripp)
Oh, Don't Be A Fool, Paddy.
Because When You
Come Back To Me,
Asking For My Assistance,
Asking For My Acceptance--
You Don't Get It, Dad, Do You?
I'm Never Going To Ask You
For Anything...
Ever Again.
Lisa. Bella Bambina!
Come Stai?
(Honks Horn)
Jeremy Darling, Stalker.
Is That The Headline You're
Longing To Read On T.M.Z.?
What Do You Mean?
I'm Just Tooling Around.
This Just-Showing-Up Thing Was
Cute, Oh, The First 17 Times.
Now It's Just Starting
To Get Weird.
Cut Me Some Slacks. I Can't think about you.
Ever Since That Night
We Kissed.
That Was Six Months Ago,
And We Didn't Kiss.
You Kissed Me.
You Kissed Me Back...
A Little.
I Mean, It Wasn't
"The Notebook,"
But I Diinctly Recall
A Kiss Back.
Look, Marriages
And When I Let You Kiss Me,
Mine Was In A Bad One.
It's In A Better One Now.
Can We Have Dinner Tonight?
I Am Having Dinner At Etienne
With Nick, My Husband,
And We--You And Me--
Are Not Happening,
For Dinner Or Anything.
Please Leave Me Alone
And Get A Helmet.
That Was Amazing.
I'm All Discombobulated Now.
Yeah. Mm.
Would You Make Me
Some Orange Juice, Please,
With A Little Gin In It?
Sure.
Actually,
Hold The Orange Juice.
All Right,
All Right.
Oh, Hey, There's, Um,
A Fund-Raiser Tonight
At The Brooklyn
Botanical Gardens.
I'm Giving Them A $10-Million Grant
To Do Research In The Rain Forest.
You Want To Go?
Sure. Sounds Planty.
I Just Have To Make
An Appearance At Home First.
Ah, So Tripp Still Has
No Idea His Daughter
Is Sleeping
With The Enemy, Huh?
No, He's Completely Clueless
Still.
Well, Don't Be So Su.
People Figure Things Out.
What--What--
What Are You Doing?
Going Through Your Stuff.
What's The Story
With This One?
Well...
When I First Came
To New York...
I Wasn't Sure If I'd Ever
Amount To Anything...
So I Saw That
In A Shop Window,
And It Reminded Me
Of The Ugly Ckling.
You Know,
It Turned Into A Swan.
It's Not Worth Much,
But It's A... Reminder
Of A Simpler Time.
That's Sweet.
What?
I Love You.
Thank You.
I Think
You're Really Neat, Too.
Good Afternoon.
Oh, I Hope So, Daisy.
'Cause The Morning Monumentally Sucked.
Oh, Karen Darling's
Here To See You.
Hi, Nick.
Karen.
What Can I Do For You?
Well, For Starters,
Close The Door.
Why?
I Have To Give You
Your Present.
Happy Birthday.
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
黑金诱惑 第二季第1集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
时间轴：流窜  校对：个人ID
Karen, Put Your Dress  Back On.
I Brought You Some Grappa.
No, The Nudity Was Enough.
Get Dressed.
All Right. Gee.
Grumpy Gus.
Would You
At Least Pour Me A Drink?
Thank You.
What The Hell Is Going On?
Why Are You Doing This?
Simon Told Me Heoved Me.
Mm.
You're Still Seeing Simon?
Oh, Yeah, I'm Snooping On Him
For Daddy.
Thks For Keeping Me
In The Loop.
You Know What, Nick?
When You Have A Problem,
I'm Always There For You.
Sorry.
Okay.
What's The Problem, Karen?
Simon's Falling For Me,
And... (Sighs)
I Kinda Feel Like,
I Don't Know...
Bad.
Huh?
Yeah.
So Remove Yourself.
Well, That's What
I'm Trying To Do.
Yeah?
By Showing Up Here Naked
And Coming On To Me?
You're My Exit Ramp,
You Know.
No, I Am Not
I'm Just Your Old Boyfriend
That You Run To When You Start
To Have Feelings
For Anyone Else.
Yeah, That's Kinda What I Mean
By "Exit Ramp," Nick.
Listen, If You Want Out
Of This Predicament, Which You
Got Yourself Into, You're Gonna
Have To Do It Yourself.
I'm Not Gonna
Kiss You Out Of It.
Well, I Was Hoping
For A Little More Than Aiss.
Well, You're Not
Gonna Get Anything.
So Pull Back, Step Out,
Absent Yourself.
You Have Choices.
(Normal Voice) Wow.
Okay.
Thanks For Understanding, Nick.
Oh, Hey.
Happy Birthday.
I Hate This.
We're Almost Done.
Well, We Could Wreck It
And Start Over.
Ate Logo To You, Too.
What's Your Problem,
Cruella?
That Was
The Brazilian Consulate.
There's Still This
Strangely Unspecified Holdup
With Our Visas.
Shrimp Doesn't Mind.
Go Rub A Crystal.
This Was Supposed To Be
A One-Week Visit, Brian.
It's Stretched Out
To Nearly Four.
And You're Telling Me You Had
Nothing To Do With This.
Why Is It So Important
That You Get Back To Brazil?
I Mean, Why Are You Even
Living There At All?
Andrea.
Oh, Hi, Tripp.
Your Stay Continues
To Be Pleasant?
More Long Than Pleasant.
Brian, Could I--
May I Steal You Away?
I Need You To Talk To Ellen.
Why, You Need Me To Get
Her Recipe
For Long Island Iced Tea?
No, I Want You
To Counsel Her.
Counsel?
Yes.
Patrick May No Longer
Think Of Himself
As An Extension Of This Family,
But The Rest Of The World Does.
And His Wife...
It's Obvious That Ellen
Is Terribly Unhappy.
But That Unhappiness Is Turning
Her Into A Public Embarrassment.
I Left The Church
And Took This Job
So I Wouldn't Have To Smile
And Nod And Pretend I Care
About
Other People's Problems.
When You Sent Me To Munich
To Fire All Those People
And Close Down That Factory,
That Was Fun.
Are You Telling--
Are--Are You Saying No?
Yeah. I'm Saying No.
Well, Yes.
Thank You For Your Frankness.
I Count On It.
It Is The Biggest Dead End
In The World, Mr. Darling.
This Carmelita,
This So-Called Lady Friend
Of Yours,
She Doesn't Want To Be Found.
But To Have Her Just...
Out There Somewhere...
Not Knowing...
Just... It Kil Me.
You Want My Advice,
Mr. Darling?
Go Home To Your Pretty Wife.
My Pretty Wife, Mr. Cameron,
Is A Belligerent Drunk
Who Calls Me Names
In Front Of My Children
And Takes Swings At Me
In Public,
That Is When She's Not Online
Ordering Single Barrel Bourbon
By The Case.
Keep Looking.
Never Give Up.
Where The Hell Have You Been?
Good Evening, Foster Brooks.
Answer Me.
You Were Looking For Her Again,
Weren't You?
"Her." (Scoffs)
I Should Say "It."
I've Been Out Campaigning...
And Working At My Office,
Ellen.
Oh, God, You Disgust Me.
You Know That?
I Disgust You, Really?
Yeah. You're A Pervert.
I'd Forbid Our Children
To Be Alone With You
If You Weren't Their Father.
I Could Still Do It.
What's The Matter
With Me, Pat?
What Did I Ever Do To You?
Well, You Shot Me
In The Leg, Ellen.
Ring A Bell?
God.
You Smell Like A Still.
I'm Going To Take A Shower...
And Try To Wash Whatever's Left
Of This Marriage Off My Body.
Try Not To Fall Down.
Hit Me.
Jeremy Darling.
What If I Told You
I've Been Coming Around Here
Every Night
For The Past Two Weeks
Waiting For You To Show Up?
(Scoffs)
I Wouldn't Believe You.
Oh, Well.
Do I Know You?
Does Anybody
Really Know Anyone?
Your Drink, Sir.
Should I Ask About The Girl?
How'd You Know
About The Girl?
Come On.
There's Always A Girl.
I, Uh...
I Overextended Myself...
Heart-Wise.
You Know,
I Put Myself Out There,
But She Just Doesn't Want Me.
If You Want My Advice,
Don't Take No For An Answer.
Sometimes A Girl
Just Wants A Guy To...
Push.
It Makes Her Feel Pretty.
Thanks For The Drink.
* Mirror, Mirror On The Wall *
* Who's The Greatest Of Them All? *
* 'Cause I Came *
* And I Saw *
* I Conquered All *
What The Hell Are You Doing?!
You Are Making Me Do This.
Look What You And Your
Perversions Turned Me Into.
Ellen, Stop It!
You Have A Perfectly Good Woman
Who Loves You, But No,
You'd Rather Be
With That Shape-Shifter.
Are You Crazy?
You're Never Gonna Find Her.
You Know That, Don't You?
You Will Never Find Her, Ever.
Oh, My God, Ellen.
What--What Did You Do?!
I Had Her Taken Care Of.
Oh, My God.
Sw-Sweetheart?
Ellen?
Baby?
(Whispers) Ellen?
What Have You Done?
(Voice Breaks)
Oh, What Have You Done?
Why Did You Do This?
Hello.
I Need Help.
(Tripp) I'm Here, Paddy.
What Can I Do?
I Promise, Lisa,
I'll Be There.
But What You Don't Get Is I'm
Fine With You Saying You Can't.
I Can, I Promise.
Look, I Just Got To Patrick's.
I'm Gonna See What They Need.
I'll Be Outta Here
Intes. 1
(Ding)
I Just Want To See You,
You Know?
Lisa, It's My Birthday.
I'll Be There.
Mr. George.
Thank You, Clark.
What The Hell
Happened Here?
Somebody Start Talking.
Now.
Oh, Finally.
I Was Just Ab--
Jeremy.
What Are You Doing Here?
I Heard You Were Flying Solo.
I Thought I'd Pull Alongside
And Refuel.
How Did You Know I Was Alone?
Don't Sit Down.
I Called Francois, The MaTRe'd.
He's An Old Coke Connection.
Get Up.
I Was Gonna Have
A Bottle Sent Over
For The Two Of You
Love Birds,
But He Said
There Was Only One,
And That You Were Looking
Kinda Blue.
Voil?
Nick Is Going To Be Here
Any Moment.
Well, When He Arrives,
I Will Totally Flee The Scene.
No.
Five Minutes.
Seven Tops, I Promise.
Possibly Ten
If We're Vibing.
I Get That It Was
An Accident, Patrick.
I Get That You Didn't Lay
But We Still Have To Call
The Police Now.
I Completely Agree.
If Paddy Had Been Able
To Tell Me On The Phone
What Had Transpired,
I Would've Called Them Myself,
Right Then.
Okay. All Right.
Let's Do It.
Nick.
Tripp, Every Moment We Delay
Increases The Appearance--
I Know.
That's What I'm Thinking About,
About How This Will Look
And The Toll That It Will Take.
On What, The Election?
No, On The Family,  On The Kids.
You Know What The Press
Is Going To Do With This.
What Are You Asking Me
To Do?
I'm Not Asking You
To Do Anything.
Although You Do Make A Very
Strong Case About The Election.
I Mean, If This Gets Out,
That'll Be Done.
Did You Seriously Expect Me
?? Move Her Body,
Put It Somewhere Else,
Set It On Fire And Make It All
Look Like An Accident?
It's What Dutch Woulda Done.
And Look What It Got Him,
Pat--A Permanent Address
At The Bottom
Of Long Island Sound.
Nick.
What?
This Isn't Some Case Of Me
Running Down To City Hall
And Fixing A Parking Ticket.
You Do Realize That?
This Is A Woman's Life.
And A Man's, And A Family's.
It's Many Things, Nick, Many.
All Right, Look...
If I Were You,
I'd Call The Police.
Once This Situation
Becomes A Legal Matter,
I Hope You'll Call Me As Your
Family Lawyer To Do My Part.
But Right Now
This Isn't A Legal Situation.
It's A Moral One,
And As Of Right Now,
It's Not Min It's Yours.
Good Night.
What Are We Gonna Do?
Well, There's Only
One Thing We Can Do.
We Must Follow
Nick's Sage Advice.
Hey.
The Car's Waiting For Us
Downstairs.
You're Going Dressed
Like That To The Benefit?
Oh, Yeah.
No, I'm Not Going.
Okay.
Wild Guess--
I'm Tired. That's It.
That's All.
Karen, Uh, You Know
That It's Okay
If You Don't Want
To Say I Love You.
I Mean, That's What
This Is All About, Right?
No. Maybe A Little, Yeah.
Okay.
You Know I Could Have
Any Woman In New York?
But I've Chosen You
Because I Enjoy Being With You,
So I Said It.
You Don't
Have To Say It Back.
But While We're At It
And We're Being Honest,
Let's Just Get It All
Out On The Table.
(Scoffs)
I Know Why You're Seeing Me,
And I Know It's For One Reason
And One Reason Only,
And That Is To Gather Dirt For Daddy.
Well, I...
Y--'Cause It Started Out
That Way, But It's Not--
Let's Cut To The Chase.
Karen...
I Made My First Fortune
On A Prism,
A Computer Processor
That Could Read Information
On Waves Of Light.
Now...
In Six Months...
I'm Gonna Roll This Out.
What Is That?
A Fuel--
Cleaning Burning...
Nontoxic.
This Is Going To Do
For Transportation
What My Prism Did
For Information.
It's Gonna Change Everything.
It's Yours. I Want You
To Take This To Your Father.
Let Him Hand It Over
To His Chemists.
They--They're Gonna Have Fun
Figuring This Out.
And Your Father Will Make More Money
Than Even He Could Ever Imagine.
I'll Lose Millions In R&D,
But Hey, Daddy's Happy,
Right?
Because That's What This
Is All About, Right?
Keeping Daddy Happy?
Oh, My God.
We Really Did Not Need To Drink
That Whole Second Bottle.
I Respectfully Disagree.
A High-End Buzz Becomes You.
Oh. Jeremy
Jeremy, You Saved Me From
A Night Full Of Self-Pity.
Thank You.
But This Is Where It Ends.
Meaning?
Meaning Don't Try
And Kiss Me.
I Wasn't Going To.
Damn It, Jeremy.
Why Do You Do That?
Ow!
Because I Think
You're Beautiful.
Come On, Lise, You Got Stood Up
For A Birthday Dinner
You Were Trying To Throw
For Someone Else.
You're The Prettiest Girl
In New York,
And You Know You Want Me
To Kiss You.
Or You Want To Kiss Me,
Whichever.
I Don't.
I Know You Are Unable
To Believee When I Say It,
But I Really Don't.
Nick!
Nick! Nick, Nick, Wait!
Let's Go.
Nick, Wait! Wait!
Nick!
Maybe My Family And Your Family
Are Just A Bad Combination,   You Know?
You Ever Think Of That?
It's Crossed My Mind.
Your Mom And My Dad,
My Wife And Your Brother...
I Don't Know,
You And Me...
I Mean, There Are People
All Over The World
Whose Interactions
Are Simple And Clean
And Generally Lead To
Good Things Happening, Right?
Yeah, Well...
(Clinks Glasses)
Here's To Them.
I'm Sorry.
About What?
Just The Way I Talked To You
When You Showed Up Here Naked...
When I Said
You Have Choices.
'Cause Maybe We Don't,
Really.
You Know, Maybe Lisa Doesn't.
Maybe Jeremy Doesn't.
Maybe You Don't,
And Maybe I Don't.
I Don't Know.
Maybe Patrick Doesn't.
Patrick?
I Just Mean That Maybe...
It's All Just Chemistry,
You Know?
You Know, You Just...
You Want What You Want
And You Can't Stop Wanting It.
Maybe It's That Simple.
Yeah, You're Drunk.
And You're Beautiful.
And You're Thinking About Simon.
I Am.
I Can't Talk Right Now, Lisa.
No, I'm Sorry.
It's Nothing.
Everything's Fine. No.
No, It's Nothing.
Yeah, I Can Be There.
I'll See You Then.
Who Was That?
That Was Your Father.
8:00 Tomorrow Morning--
I've Been Summoned.
What?
You And I Are Not
A Bad Combination, Nick.
It's Just It's--
It's--It's Bad Timing.
Hey, Mom.
Where The Hell Is My Son?
He And Andrea Just Left.
I Begged Her To Stay
And Say Good-Bye,
But She Said That They Could
Still Catch The Flight.
Their Visas Came Through?
Yes. She Said She Got
A Phone Call From The Consulate
Out Of The Blue.
Next Thing I Knew, She W--
She Was Grabbing Little Brian
Along With The Luggage
And, Well, To Be Honest,
A Few Of Our Best Towels.
Where's Tripp?
Why? Do You Want Him
To Intervene?
He Already Did.
Excellent, Clark.
Well Done. Thank You.
You Wanted To See Me?
Yeah. Please.
Do You Know How Many Men Died
Building The Brooklyn Bridge?
No Idea.
27.
27 For A Bridge That,
Every Day,
More Than A Million People
Go Back And Forth On.
So This Is Your Way Of Saying
That Ellen Wasxpendable?
No, No, No, No.
Just That For Every Venture...
There Are Costs.
People Aren't Costs, Tripp.
They're People.
Ellen Contrived A Life
That Can Be Best Described
As A Venal Venture
In Which, Regrettably,
She Did Not Have The Strength
To Play Her Role.
In The End, She Resorted
To Drink And...
Finally, Last Night,
Once Again...
To Violence.
She Had None Of The Patience
And Grace
That Make Your Marriage
To Lisa Such A Blessing.
Yeah, I'm A Lucky Man.
All I Asked Her To Do
Was To Help Protect My Son
And His Innocent Children
From Whawould
Surely Have Become
An Immensely Destructive
Misunderstanding.
What Do You Want
From Me, Tripp?
I Want You To Allow Yourself
To Become
A Part Of This Family.
Oh, I Know We're Not Perfect.
We're Messy.
But You Yourself Said
That At The End Of The Day,
We Love Each Other.
Let Yourself
Be A Part Of That.
You Are A Son To Me.
Let Us Love You.
Dad.
I'm Gonna Have To Bail
On Nick's Party.
D--Hey, Nick.
Hi, Jeremy.
Did You...
What--I-I Should Go.
Jeremy, Wait, Wait, Wait.
There's One Thing.
I Will Be At My Office...
If You Need Anything Else
Taken Care Of.
You Ready To Talk?
I'm Ready To Listen.
I Was Drunk, Nick, And...
You Left Me Waiting Ere
When I Told You--
Are You Seriously Defending
The Idea
That You Were Kissing Jeremy?
Are You Seriously
Not Willing To Forgive Me
When You've Done
The Same Thing With Karen?
Oh, So We're Even Now?
Is That The Moral To The Story?
At The End Of The Day,
That's What This Marriage Is?
You Tell Me
What This Marriage Is.
Doesn't It Ever Occur To You
That You Are Headed Down
The Exact Same Path
Your Dad Went Down?
Little By Little,
They're Pulling You In.
I'm Losing You.
You're Losing Me?
You're Kissing Jeremy,
And You're Losing Me?
We're Losing Us.
You Know It's True.
I Know When You Took This Job
You Thought You Could Walk
This Razor's Edge All The Time
Between Their Values And Ours,
Between Their Family And Ours,
But Someday, Nick, You're
Gonna Have To Make A Choice.
And When That Day Comes, I...
I Hope You Choose Us.
You're Coming, Right?
Lise, You're Coming To The Party?
I'm Going For A Walk.
Lisa!
It's Because I Wouldn't Do It.
I Wouldn't Go To Ellen
And Talk To Her
And Tell Her To Sack Up
And Play Darling Ball,
So You Disappeared My Family.
I Had Nothing To Do With It.
You're Full Of Crap.
No, I Am Not, Actually.
If I Had Known Events
Were Unfolding That Way
With Theirisa,
I Would Have Jumped
At The Chance To Help.
If You Had Come  Me...
That's What Family Does.
We Help Each Other.
Well, I'm Sorry
I Didn't Talk To Ellen.
If You Had Taken The Time
To Let Her Air
Her Troubled Mind...
Things Might Have Gone
Differently.
What Are You Talking About?
It Would Be A Great Help
To Your Brother Patrick
And To Me, Too,
If You Could Agree That You
Spent The Past Two Days
Sailing With Him
Out At The Hamptons.
Why?
Will You Do It Or Not?
Sure. Why The Hell Not?
And Spend Ten Minutes
In The Tanning Bed
Before We Go To Nick's Party.
Well, You Look A Trifle Pale.
Well, Look Who's Here.
Aren't You Going
To Nick's Party?
I'm Running Late. He'll Live.
So...What Did Your Daddy Think
Of My Little Concoction?
I Didn't Give It To Him,
And I'm Not Going To.
You Sure About This?
Yeah.
Look, My Whole Life,
There's Only Been One Man
Who--Who Ever Moved Me,
You Know, Who--
Who Made Me Feel Like
I Was Actually Living.
Nick.
YEAH.
But Something's Happening
To Me, Simon, With You.
I Don't Know What It Is.
You Know, Maybe I'm Growing Up.
I--Maybe.
Maybe You're Just Amazing.
I Just--I Know That I--
I Don't Want To Let You Go.
What You Do To Me,
It Scares Me A Little, You Know?
But I Like It.
I'm Gonna Go.
I'm Gonna Go To... The Shindig.
Hey.
You'll Come After?
I Will.
Okay.
Yeah, It's Me.
We've Got Her.
Let Me Guess
It's A Long Story
Make It Short
I'm Amistake
I'm Always The Mistake.
Always?
So Since You're Such
A Master Of Mistakes...
Is It A Mistake
You Came Back Here?
Probably.
Is It A Mistake Letting Me
Stand Next To You?
It's Kinda Hard
To Say, I Guess.
Would It Be A Mistake
To Take Me To That Limo
You've Got Parked Outside
And...
Only One Way To Find Out.
This Is Definitely Not A Mistake.
No.
(Man) I'm Standing In Front
Of Valhalla,
The Legendary Rural Compound
Of America's First Family,
The Darlings.
Mr. Clark! Mr. Clark. Look.
Valued Aover $30 Million,
The Property, Which Was Once
The Home Of Legendary Gangster
Bugsy Siegel...
The Country House.
Is Expected To Be
Completely Destroyed.
Should We Call Mr. Darling?
Investigators Are Already
On The Scene
Trying To Determine
The Source Of The Blaze.
Nah.
(Woman) Gabe, This Is A Truly
Shocking, Shocking Tragedy.
Let's Not Ruin The Party.
(Man) The Red-Carpet Event
Was Thought To Be A Fund-Raiser
For Patrick Darling's
Senate Campaign,
But Turns Out
It's Just A Birthday Party
For Their Family Lawyer
Nick George.
And That's Your Weather
And Traffic.
(Man) Mister--Mr. George,
How Were You Able To Broker
This Historic Reconciliation
Between Father And Son?
Well, It Was, Uh,
It Was Quite An Adventure.
Here's The Birthday Boy.
Letitia Darling, You Look Beautiful.
How Are You?
Mm.
Happy Birthday, Nick.
Thanks.
Have You Seen My Wife?
Lisa's Not With You?
No, No.
If You'll Excuse Me.
Patrick,
Where's That Wife Of Yours?
I'm Sure She's Just Running
A Few Moments Late.
No, Brian
Left The Ministry.
Got A Little Too Much Sun,
Huh?
Yeah, Paddy And I
Went Sailing Yesterday
Off Our Place In The Hamptons.
Hey, Nick.
Want You To Meet
An Old Friend Of Mine.
Hal Matheson, Nick George.
Nice To Meet You.
Your Dad Was A Hell Of A Guy.
He'd Be So Proud Of You
If He Was Still With Us.
THANK YOU.
(Tripp) Have You
Got Something For Me?
Yes, Daddy. A Kiss...
And This.
You Made It.
I Did.
So Are We Okay?
We're Okay.
Can The Birthday Boy
Come Up Here, Please?
Never Before--
Well, Maybe Once Before,
And I'm Thinking
Of Nick's Dad Dutch--
Has One Man Done So Much
To Hold A Family Together.
Happy Birthday.
What's This?
That...
Is The Key To That--
That Boat.
Thank You.
What's Going On?
I Don't Know.
(Man) N.Y.P.D.
Prepare To Be Boarded.
What's Happening, Nick?
I Have No Idea.
What Did You Do, Nick?
What The Hell Did You Do?
Nobody Move.
Prepare To Be Boarded.
(Man) Stand Back, Please.
You Ratted Me Out?
What Did You Do, Nick?
I Didn't Do Anything.
(Man) Excuse Me. Step Back.
Step Back, Plee.
Sorry To Have To Do This,
Mr. Attorney General.
I Got My Orders.
Detective Larrabee,
What Seems To Be The Problem?
Murder, Nick,
In The First Degree.
But--
Here's An Arrest Warrant.
Letitia Darling,
You're Under Arrest
For The Murder Of Dutch George.
What?
God, This Is Outrageous.
You Have Theight
To Remain Silent.
Anything You Say Can
And Will Be Used Against You
In A Court Of Law.
Patrick.
Nick.
You Have The Right To Have
An Attorney Present...
Lp. Nick, Help.
(Tripp) Patrick.
(Larrabee) If You Cannot Afford
An Attorney,
One Will Be Appointed For You.
(Letitia) Tripp, Are You There?
(Tripp) I'm Here, Darling.
I'm Here, Dear.
Mrs. Darling...
Do You Understand These Rights
As I Have Spoken Them To You?
(Leticia) Nick, Help!
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入