Hey, Mom, you down here?
Clark, I thought you went to the hardware
store with your father.
We were on our way, then Dad remembered
he had the part he needed in the barn.
What are you doing down here?
I came down to get some peaches
for dessert. I'll be right up.
Okay.
Well, that ought to do it.
That was fast.
I offered Dad a bit of spot welding,
but he said it'd slow him down.
As hard as it is to believe,
your abilities are no substitute...
...for a 3/4-inch copper washer.
Well, it sounds like the two of you deserve
a nice, cold glass of lemonade.
Mom, you all right?
Martha!
Dad, she's not breathing. Mom? Mom!
Martha?
The good news is we've managed
to stabilize her.
She's breathing on her own.
I don't understand.
She worked outside all morning.
She seemed fine. How could something
come over her so quickly?
My guess is we're dealing
with some sort of toxin.
I'll have a better idea after we finish
her blood work.
All right. I'm gonna stay right here.
I'll have an orderly bring you some coffee.
Thank you.
She's gonna be okay.
I know that, son.
I also know that she wouldn't want us both
out here standing guard.
I'm not leaving.
Your mother had a list of things
she needed to get done for the fundraiser.
You know how important
the food bank is to her.
All right.
As soon as I'm finished, I'm coming back
to camp out with you.
I thought that your mom was bringing over
the prizes for the raffle.
She was, but she came down
with something this morning.
My dad's at the hospital with her.
Hospital? It sounds serious.
Any idea what's wrong?
- They're waiting on some test results.
- They have to know something.
- What were her symptoms?
- What is this, an interview?
She stopped breathing, okay?
This whole event was your mom's idea.
Maybe we should just postpone
until she's back on her feet.
No, I appreciate the thought, Lana,
but she's gonna be okay...
...and she'd be really disappointed
if we cancelled.
- Clark, I didn't mean to just...
- It's okay, Chloe.
I'm gonna get back to the hospital.
Mr. Kent?
I know we've already gone over this,
but I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Has Martha been exposed to any
unusual substances over the last few days?
Nothing she hasn't been around before.
What is this about?
I've been going over Martha's
blood cultures...
...and her symptoms indicate
an acute toxic reaction...
...but I can't identify the source.
- But you can do something for her, right?
I've sent her blood samples
to Metropolis for further testing.
But I have to be honest with you,
I'm concerned...
...for both Martha and the health
of her baby.
Baby?
You didn't know?
There must be some kind of mistake.
The doctors said that she
could never have a baby.
I asked your G.P. To fax over Martha's
medical records.
There's no mistake.
I saw Mr. Kent in the hall.
He looked worried. Is everything all right?
We're doing everything we can.
Johns Hopkins. Good school.
Go ahead. Read it.
They're offering you
a three-year research fellowship.
I'm impressed.
It's an opportunity to do pure research
at one of the best hospitals in the country.
As opposed to the rural pleasures
of Smallville Medical.
Lex, I like my work here,
but research has always been my first love.
So...
...what do you think?
Trust me...
...there's nothing worse
than a missed opportunity.
Dr. Bryce?
I'm Dr. Neil Moore.
We're here about Martha Kent.
I'll let you get back to work.
A baby?
She didn't tell me anything about it.
- Why would she keep it a secret?
- I don't know.
Mr. Kent.
This is Dr. Moore
with the Disease Control Agency.
Mr. Kent.
Disease? I'm sorry, but what does
that have to do with my wife?
The Disease Control Agency gets called in
whenever it's a matter of public safety.
The Metropolis lab sent them
Martha's blood work.
I don't mean to alarm you...
...but your wife's condition is caused
by some unknown toxin.
We're here to find it and identify it.
Can someone else come down with this?
Frankly, son, we can't know that
until we find the source.
We need to backtrack Mrs. Kent's
movements over the last couple of days.
She hasn't left the farm
since the weekend.
She's been on the phone
doing fundraising.
Then that's where we need to start.
Start what?
Searching your property
for the source of the poison:
The house, the out buildings...
...anything Mrs. Kent might have
come in contact with.
Clark, the ship.
Pete, you're sure the ship will be safe
in your shed?
Yeah. I'll put it between the old Betamax
and my dad's Pong game.
Indiana Jones couldn't find it down there.
Clark!
Clark, what are you...?
Pete, you okay?
I'm fine.
What happened to you?
I'm not sure.
Let's get out of here.
Come on, let's get this thing back
on the road.
Come on, stop fooling around.
I've seen you bench-press a trailer.
- Let's go.
- I'm trying.
I can't do this, Pete.
Clark, X-Files alert.
That's the DCA team.
We've gotta get this thing back
on the road.
We got it.
- Find anything yet?
- No, not yet.
- You got the ship out of there?
- Yeah, it's at Pete's. It's safe.
Dad, when I was driving...
...my vision suddenly blurred
and I lost control of the truck.
- You and Pete are all right, aren't you?
- Yeah.
For a moment, I lost all my strength.
- Dr. Moore.
- Go ahead.
I'm getting a hit in the storm cellar.
I'm registering a positive
for organic particulate matter.
Looks like someone was digging around
and kicked up some sort of irradiated spore.
Get a surface sample.
Ten centimeters and 50 centimeters.
Mr. Kent, we found this in a tin
buried inside your storm cellar.
Have you ever seen it before?
No.
Has Mrs. Kent been down
in that cellar recently?
Not that I know of.
We usually keep it locked.
Actually, Dad,
she was down there this morning.
This is Moore.
I want a cleanup team to sterilize
every inch of that storm cellar.
I don't get it. We've been searching
for that key for months.
How did it end up in the storm cellar?
When I fixed the leak under the sink,
I noticed the flour jar.
Your mother must have moved it.
- Why didn't she tell us she had it?
- She must have her reasons, Clark.
Right now, I'm more concerned
about her health.
Me too. What do you think
those spores are?
I don't know, but whatever they are,
you were exposed to them too.
Maybe that's why you lost your strength.
No, Dad, I just had a glitch.
I'm fine.
You don't have to worry about me.
We need to think about Mom.
Sweetheart.
How you feeling?
I should have told you about the baby.
I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you tell me?
I was worried if I said it out loud,
it would go away.
Martha.
How is it even possible?
The day of the tornado...
...when Nixon opened Clark's ship...
...something strange happened.
And there was a blinding light...
...and I felt a surge of energy
go through my body.
You're saying you think the ship
has the power to heal?
I think the ship made it possible
for me to get pregnant.
However it happened, Martha,
it's a miracle.
They found the key.
In the storm cellar?
- Why did you hide it from us?
- I know it was wrong...
...but I was afraid if Clark
opened the ship...
...and found out the truth
about his origins he'd...
He would want to leave us.
Martha, that's not going to happen.
- Clark.
- Hi, Lana.
I just wanted to make sure you were okay.
It's weird how random memories
can just pop into your head, huh?
When I was in second grade,
I was afraid to go to school...
...because I thought Mom would disappear
while I was gone...
...and never come back.
I wouldn't even get on the bus...
...until she promised she'd be there
when I got home.
Sure enough...
...every day, there she was when
I walked through the door.
Don't worry, Clark.
In a few days, you'll walk through the door
and your mom will be there again.
Clark, you okay?
Clark. Clark!
Clark.
What happened?
Lana, would you excuse us, please?
Clark was exposed to the same toxin
his mother was.
You should've called an ambulance. He needs
a hospital. We need to inform the DCA.
- I'm sorry, I can't let you do that.
- Why the hell not?
I need you to promise me
that you won't tell anybody...
...about this, and I mean anybody.
Mr. Kent, I take my doctor-patient
confidentiality very seriously...
...but Clark needs proper care.
Doctor, Clark isn't exactly
what you'd call a normal boy.
I need to get a blood sample.
Listen, Dr. Bryce, you can't do that.
- Is this some sort of religious thing?
- No, I mean literally, you can't do that.
You can't take that sample to a lab.
I'm trying to help your son...
...but I can't unless you tell me
what's going on.
You need to promise me that you will do
the lab work on this blood yourself.
If you do the blood work yourself,
I think you'll understand...
...why you can't tell anyone about Clark.
Oh, my God.
Lex.
Came by to see how Mrs. Kent was doing.
I saw the DCA, must be serious.
You know I'm not allowed
to discuss my patients.
The Kents are like family to me,
more than my own.
I know, and I would tell you everything
if I could.
I understand. I just wish there
was something I could do to help.
Unfortunately, modern medicine doesn't
always have the answers.
I guess that's the attraction
of a research fellowship...
...the chance to help unlock
the mysteries of science.
I'd better get back to work.
Helen.
Johns Hopkins will be lucky to have you.
Hi, Mr. Kent.
Lana told me what happened.
- Is Clark okay?
- Yeah, he's just resting on the couch.
I'll be sure to tell him you stopped by
to say hello.
I'm sorry, I must be more annoying
than a door-to-door salesman.
I was wondering if I could just sit
with him for a while?
Yes.
Chloe, I'm sorry. Sure, go on in.
- I'll wait upstairs.
- Okay, thanks.
Hi, Clark.
Well, this is gonna make quite a story.
"Clark Kent Ends Record-Breaking
Perfect Attendance Streak."
Sorry.
I'm doing it again.
I just...
I've never seen you sick before,
and it just got me thinking.
What if something did happen to you...
...and I never got to...?
So in yet another classic maneuver
to avoid emotional intimacy...
...I wrote my feelings down
so that I could read them to you...
...thereby avoiding embarrassing
eye contact.
I want to let you in on a secret.
I'm not who you think I am.
In fact, my disguise is so thin...
...I'm surprised you haven't seen
right through me.
I'm the girl of your dreams masquerading
as your best friend.
Sometimes I wanna rip off this facade
like I did at the Spring Formal...
...but I can't, because you'll get scared
and you'll run away again.
So I decided that it's better to live
with the lie than expose my true feelings.
This is so much easier
when you're unconscious.
My dad told me
there are two types of girls...
...the ones you grow out of
and the ones you grow into.
I really hope I'm the latter.
I may not be the one you love today...
...but I'll let you go for now,
hoping one day you'll fly back to me.
Because I think you're worth the wait.
Clark?
Lana?
Dad.
Clark, you shouldn't be up.
Where are you going?
- I'm going to Pete's to get the ship.
- Now?
How is Mom?
Dad?
Clark, Helen says that your mother probably
won't make it through the night.
And now you too.
You can't think about me.
We gotta help Mom.
I'm not gonna lose my family,
not without a fight.
Now, if it takes a miracle,
I'll have to go out and find one.
The ship.
You think it can cure me and Mom?
I don't know, Clark.
I'm grasping at straws.
The doctors can't help you...
...and your mother thinks the ship
helped her get pregnant.
I don't know, maybe it's crazy.
The only way to get it to work
is with that key.
I know that, son.
I also know where the DCA
took everything.
- I'm going there now.
- I'll go with you.
No. I want you to stay right here,
you're too sick.
Go to bed, son.
Hold it right there. On the ground, now!
Hands at your sides!
Clark!
I thought you could use a hand.
We gotta run, son. Come on!
He's moving down to the gate!
Unlock the gates! Let's go!
Code blue, room 117. Code blue.
This is the DCA.
Stop your vehicle immediately.
Get out of the truck
and put your hands up!
Something wrong, officer?
This guy doesn't fit the description.
Clear.
Come on.
Time of death, 2:17 a.m.
- So is it a boy or a girl?
- Clark...
- Doctor, please, don't answer that.
- We wanna find out the old-fashioned way.
The important thing is that
the baby's healthy and so are you.
In medical terms,
it's nothing short of a miracle.
Your family seems to have
a stockpile of them.
I saw Clark's blood test...
...and I saw Mrs. Kent
make an impossible recovery.
If you know how that happened,
you should tell me.
Just like you said, doc...
...it's a miracle.
Dr. Trenton, I appreciate you keeping me
apprised of the situation.
I shouldn't be doing this.
If anyone finds out I'm giving you a file
on a patient, I could lose my job.
Mrs. Kent was a very sick woman.
What's your interest in her?
She's a good friend of mine.
That's all you need to know.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I ran into Clark in the hall.
He said Martha's gonna be fine.
Congratulations, doc.
Don't know how much I had to do with it.
Then how do you explain it?
Right, I almost forgot,
you can't discuss your patients.
I got you something.
A going-away present?
On the contrary.
Open it.
It's a key to the mansion.
I want you to move in.
Lex.
I'd never want to stand in the way
of your ambitions...
...but I'd be the one missing an opportunity
if I didn't tell you I want you to stay.
- "Attack of the killer mold spores"?
- Yeah.
I'll never look at blue cheese
the same way again.
I couldn't bring myself to go back
and visit Clark when he was sick.
Does that make me a horrible person?
No.
I guess it just really scared me
to see him like that.
Me too.
Kind of makes you realize
who's important in your life.
Yeah. And who's important to Clark.
- What do you mean?
- Nothing.
I'm gonna head home
and finish changing for the benefit.
Are the programs ready?
They are, right behind the desk.
I'll see you there.
Thanks.
I want to let you in on a secret, Clark.
I'm not who you think I am.
In fact, my disguise is so thin...
...I'm surprised you haven't seen
right through me.
I'm the girl of your dreams masquerading
as your best friend.
Pete, this is awesome.
Clark. It's good to see you
among the living, man.
Check it out.
It's the latest Talon mix.
Thanks, Pete.
- And thanks for helping with the police.
- No problem.
Although, if I had a choice,
I'd rather play DJ than decoy any day.
So...
...is the investigation over?
- Yeah. I hope so.
- I'll catch up with you later.
- Good seeing you, man.
Hey, Chloe.
My dad said you came to visit
when I was sick.
It was really sweet of you. Thanks.
Sure. What are friends for?
I'm just gonna go buy a raffle ticket
before the drawing.
I mean, what could be more poetically just,
me winning a computer?
Clark.
Hey, Lana. This is a great party.
Your mom deserves a lot of the credit.
Is Chloe okay?
What happened to you really affected her.
Me too.
It was really hard seeing you sick.
Guess I somehow always thought of you
as invincible.
Now you think I'm just human.
I guess that's my way of saying
that you mean a lot to me, Clark.
And I know it's not that eloquent...
...but I guess some people are just better
with words than others.
Subtitle by:
(MFMS)d
www.tvsubtitles.net