Fear not, Kal-EI.
- Who are you?
- I am Jor-EI, your father.
- I thought you died.
- I am his memory.
His will.
I am to fulfill his promise
and guide you all the days of your life.
You are the last son of Krypton.
When you traveled through the cosmos,
you carried the hopes and dreams...
...of your people.
They now live through you, Kal-EI.
It is time.
Time for what?
Time to accept your destiny.
I don't know what you have
in mind for me, but l...
By the setting of the sun Sol...
...you will return to me.
Your destiny will be fulfilled.
Your thoughts are not
a mystery to me, Kal-EI.
But these people have served
their purpose.
It is time to leave them.
Please...
...everything and everyone
I love is here in Smallville.
You must let go of your past.
I will guide you to your future.
No, I don't want your guidance.
- I want to create my own future.
- You have no choice, Kal-EI.
Well, you're up early.
Never went to sleep.
Clark, what's wrong?
I kind of met my biological father
last night.
When I heard his voice,
it was coming from the ship.
But it sounded like
it was from my own head.
He said it was time.
- He said it was time for what?
- To leave Smallville and fulfill my destiny.
He said that?
- I have until sundown today.
- Or what?
I'm not sure.
But he said I didn't have a choice.
Why is it happening now
when my life is coming together?
The farm's out of debt,
I'm gonna be a big brother.
Lana and I are finally getting together.
Whatever your biological father
may have had in mind for you...
...they're his hopes and dreams,
not yours.
Clark, you choose your own destiny.
Nobody can decide that for you, son.
This is my home...
...and you're my parents.
It's where I belong,
and I'm not going anywhere.
Haven't seen you two together since...
Well, Dad, since you tried to bribe
Helen into dumping me.
And now Dr. Bryce refuses to accept this,
my wedding gift to her.
If you two star-crossed lovers
will excuse me.
You want to tell me
what that was all about?
Exactly what your father said.
You know what, I'm tired of being
a pawn in this never-ending struggle.
We both said some things last night.
I don't want to go into this marriage
with any secrets between us.
I haven't held anything back, Lex.
I have. Look inside.
I did break into your office.
And that's what I was after.
I told you because
I'm trying to break the cycle.
I don't want to be the person
who did this anymore.
But you did do it, Lex.
You committed a crime.
You violated my privacy
and that of my patient.
- I know.
- What did you think would happen?
That you'd give it back,
tell me what you did...
...and I'd just forgive you
and we'd live happily ever after?
I don't know what I expected.
All I know is that I love you.
I'm sure in some part
of that twisted mind, you do.
I didn't have it analyzed.
What was so important
about this blood, anyway?
I thought it would give me
the answers I've been looking for.
All it did was end this relationship.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
You know...
...I can always tell
when you're being less than truthful.
It's just, I've...
I've waited for this for so long.
For us.
I just don't want it to go away.
I'm not going anywhere.
Neither am I.
So, Lana, does this mean you're
officially my date to Lex's wedding?
Only after we officially tell Chloe
about our change in status.
Clark, I've been avoiding her all day.
All right, just let me tell her.
Chloe and I agreed that we'd
be upfront about things like this.
Well, I'm sure if we're honest,
she'll be fine.
Never realized the small-town press
could be so pithy.
What do you think your father's up to?
He's already got a team
working overtime...
...installing some pretty sophisticated
machinery down there.
What for?
I wish I could tell you, but I'm the last
person he'd ever let back in those caves.
He's tightened security.
I doubt even you'll be able to sneak past.
Where's this tailor?
Kind of pressed for time today.
I canceled him.
Why?
Because Helen's not walking
down the aisle tomorrow.
I saw her last night.
She seemed really happy.
- A lot can change in 24 hours.
- Why'd she break it off?
I've always been fighting my destiny.
Trying to avoid becoming my father.
But we all have certain genes that...
...no matter how much we want
to change, dominate us.
What'd you do?
I betrayed Helen's trust.
Then I fought my own nature
and did something very un-Luthor-like.
I confessed my sin,
hoping she'd forgive me.
My guess is she didn't.
Don't tell anyone, Clark.
I want to hold on to my romantic notions
for one more day.
I'm gonna have to put a stop
to these unauthorized visits.
Mr. Luthor.
What are you doing here?
I was just curious.
I'd suppose so.
According to poor Dr. Walden, you're
talked about quite a bit on these walls.
Apparently, you are going to rule us all.
I'm surprised someone like you would
put stock in anything he had to say.
I know you worked closely
with the man, Clark.
I'm sure there are insights you could
give me. It would be extremely helpful.
He didn't tell me anything.
What's with all the machinery?
I'm going to unlock the secrets
hidden in these walls.
Didn't you see what happened
to Dr. Walden? It's dangerous.
Yes, but I have something he didn't:
The key.
Once I insert that key into the slot...
...I'm convinced the answers
will be revealed to me.
I thought your key
was stolen from your vault.
It was. But before it mysteriously
disappeared, I had it analyzed.
The composition was...
...unique.
There's nothing like it on Earth.
With one exception:
The meteor rocks found here
in Smallville.
So I have fashioned my own key.
It's identical in every detail.
Isn't it beautiful? Look.
Clark, you don't look well.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Just...
...be careful.
Lionel Luthor's never gotten
anywhere in life by playing it safe.
- I'm sure you'll render Clark speechless.
- Chloe, hi.
Be careful you two don't upstage
the bride and groom.
- What do you mean?
- You two are going together, I assume.
Yeah. Yeah, as friends.
Right. Friends.
Have you seen Clark?
He's been looking for you.
No. I've been trying to track
him down all day...
...but his parents said that he was
mired in best-man duties.
When did you see him last?
Oh, I ran into him at the Talon.
He wanted to talk to you,
said it was important.
Well, I guess it couldn't be as important
as you thought.
Have fun tomorrow.
I figured this is where I'd find you.
Just watching the sunset.
Hope it's not the last one
I see from up here.
It won't be, Clark.
Son, it's just another sundown.
Come on, your mother's got dinner ready.
Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
Dad?
Yeah.
Thanks for always believing in me.
You're welcome, son.
It is time, Kal-EI. Come to me.
You will obey me, Kal-EI.
You're not my father.
I won't let you control me.
This is the mark of your ancestors.
You cannot fight it, Kal-EI.
At the zenith of the star Sol,
you will begin your journey.
If you do not, you will hurt
the ones you love most.
Clark, why aren't you ready?
The wedding doesn't start for
a few hours.
- Your mother wants to get a good seat.
- I promised I'd go early...
...and check the flowers.
I gotta pick up Lana,
so I'll meet you there.
We obviously have to get used to the fact
that you have a girlfriend now.
Clark...
How's it going today, son?
Good.
- No voice?
- No voice.
Looks like you'll have to face the future
the old-fashioned way.
I guess so. It's pretty scary.
Heck, yeah.
- Mom.
- Yes?
You look beautiful today.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Helen.
- You're here.
- I am so angry at you.
- What you did was unforgivable.
- You're right.
But the farther I got
from you and this town...
...I realized that, while any sane person
would have kept driving...
...I needed to turn around.
I started to look at myself and mistakes
that I've made in my life.
I hope I'm not one of them.
No, Lex, you're not.
That's the thing.
I still love you.
Oh, man.
- Does it hurt?
- No, not now.
You got any idea what it means?
It's my biological father's way
of telling me I have to do what he wants.
I'm afraid by noon it'll control me.
Your parents must be freaked out.
I didn't tell them.
Why wouldn't you tell them, Clark?
Because, Pete,
I know what I have to do...
...and they'll never agree with me
in a million years.
I have to destroy the ship.
What?
Clark, no.
This traveled millions of miles through
space. I don't think we can even dent it.
What if we had a kryptonite key?
Clark, this is whacked.
Pete, remember Lana's necklace?
What's it have to do
with destroying the ship?
Everything, Pete. When Tina Greer
tied me up down here, it nearly killed me.
But before it could,
the ship neutralized it.
- You said the ship was protecting you.
- What if it's actually protecting itself?
Think about it, Pete.
I'm from Krypton and so is this ship, and
what's the one thing that can kill me?
So you're thinking that kryptonite
can destroy the ship?
Clark, it's too dangerous.
Do you hear me? You've never done this
before. You don't know what'll happen.
It could kill you.
Besides, where are we gonna get
a kryptonite key?
How much longer now?
- Another 10 minutes, sir.
- Another 10 minutes.
Hey, Luthor!
I've got something to say to you.
Security.
- Get him out of here.
- Don't put your hands on me. Get off me.
If they don't let me go, I'll lay a lawsuit
on you so fast your head will spin.
All right, all right, I'll talk to him.
Do I know you?
- The name's Pete Ross.
- Ross, Ross, Ross...
As in Ross Creamed Corn?
You stole my family's business.
- I overpaid for that ramshackle factory.
- Nobody in this town likes you.
- Don't touch me. You hate him.
- I know that.
But I value their hatred.
I find it very useful.
You see, people are always
at their weakest when they're angry.
Ask your father.
I'll do that.
Get him out.
No.
No!
You.
Search him. Search him.
- Search me? What are you doing?
- Where is it?
Where's what?
Careful, Mr. Luthor.
Wouldn't want to look weak.
Lex.
Mr. And Mrs. Kent.
Where's the best man?
Well, Clark and punctuality have never
been on the best terms, but he'll be here.
I got you something.
- A compass.
- Yeah, it's a Kent family tradition.
My father gave me one at our wedding,
in case I got lost going down the aisle.
Thank you, Mr. Kent.
Why aren't you dressed?
- There's something I have to do first.
- What?
I can't tell you.
Just know it's for us and our future.
Last time a guy said that to me...
...he went off to war.
You should go.
I'll meet you there.
You sure you're all right?
Yeah.
Go.
Okay.
- Lana, l...
- Yeah?
I just wanted to remember this moment.
Any word on Clark? Helen's already
circled the church five times.
He was coming with Lana.
Lana, where's Clark?
He said he had something to do.
It seemed important.
- Mr. Kent...
- I'm sorry, Lex.
You'll have to start
without your best man.
- We can wait.
- Hey, don't worry about Clark.
You've got far more important
things to do here. Good luck.
Hey, Clark.
I'm glad I caught you
before the wedding.
- Chloe, what are you doing here?
- I heard you were looking for me.
Yeah, I was.
I can't talk to you right now.
- What are you doing?
- I'll find you later.
- Clark, I couldn't...
- Don't worry. I'll find you, okay?
So how'd you decide?
Rock, Paper, Scissors? Coin toss?
Or did you just draw the short straw?
Decide...?
Who was gonna tell me
that you and Lana are together.
You know?
Yeah. I came over to the barn the other
night to warn you about something.
- About what?
- You know, it doesn't matter now.
The point is,
I saw you and Lana in a major lip-Iock.
- I didn't mean...
- Didn't what, Clark?
News flash! You've always
been in love with Lana.
I tried to deny it, thinking that maybe
we could work something out, but...
It's like fate, Clark.
Inevitable, but always surprising
when it actually happens.
- I was gonna tell you.
- Really?
Obviously it was on
the top of your to-do list.
I can deal with the fact you guys are
together. It hurts, but I was prepared.
But we just made a promise
to be honest with each other...
...and you didn't have the guts
to keep your word.
Or was it too much fun making a fool of
me that you couldn't reveal your secret?
Have a nice life, Clark.
Mr. And Mrs. Luthor, welcome aboard.
It'll be a couple of minutes.
The tower's generator just kicked in.
The county suffered
some sort of power failure.
Good. It'll mask our getaway.
To our new life.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Everything's perfect.
- How is she?
- Doctors don't know yet.
What did you do, Clark?
I stole Lionel's kryptonite key.
I put it in the ship.
Why did you do that?
Dad, I lied about the voice.
It did come back.
It told me I had to leave by noon.
I didn't have a choice, Dad.
- I had to destroy the ship.
- Why didn't you tell us?
I knew you wouldn't agree
with what I did.
Dad, I didn't want it to take me
away from you.
- I'm so sorry for what I did.
- Your actions have consequences, Clark.
- Didn't your mother and I teach you that?
- Yes, but...
There's no time for excuses, Clark.
It's too late.
You didn't think this thing through.
You had no idea what was gonna
happen, and now...
Now your mother...
...is lying in a hospital bed.
Mr. Kent.
Doctor, how is my wife?
She has a mild concussion,
but she'll be fine.
And how is our baby?
I'm sorry.
Dad.
Clark, what happened?
It looks like a bomb went off.
Where are your parents?
Hospital.
They're fine.
My mom lost the baby.
The baby?
This is all my fault, Lana. I did this.
How could you do this?
The same way I always do.
Bring pain and suffering
to everyone's lives.
- Clark, that's not true.
- Yes, Lana, it is.
Lana, I've kept so much from you.
If you knew the truth,
you'd never talk to me again.
I don't believe that.
I tried to cover up my past
and push it away.
I couldn't.
He said if I didn't go,
everyone I love would be hurt.
He was right.
Clark, you're in shock.
- You're not making any...
- No, Lana, stay away from me.
Stay away from me
before I hurt you too.
I'm glad you finally decided
to accept my offer.
You know you have a very exciting
future ahead of you, Ms. Sullivan.
Well, opportunities like this aren't
dropped on your doorstep every day.
Why the sudden change of heart?
You were right about Clark.
He wasn't who I thought he was.
I'm surprised I hadn't noticed earlier.
So much for my journalistic instinct.
No. No, love has a way of blinding
even the sharpest minds.
We don't look because
we don't want to see.
But once love has been stripped away,
then we see the real person clearly.
They're revealed to us
with all their flaws, their foibles...
...and their secrets.
I've got a meeting.
- I'm sorry to rush you out like this.
- That's fine.
Mr. Luthor, why are you
so interested in Clark?
You don't expect me to show you
all my cards now, do you?
No, I guess not.
All will be revealed in good time,
Ms. Sullivan.
Thank you, Mr. Luthor.
I'm here, sweetheart. I'm here.
Clark, I've been looking all over for you,
I heard what happened.
You here to tell me I screwed up
in a major way?
No, I'm here to say I'm sorry
and I want to help.
It's too late for that, Pete.
No one can help me now.
Clark, what are you looking for?
I know Chloe kept one of those
red kryptonite rings here.
Why do you want it?
You know what it does.
Yeah, it makes me feel better.
That's not the answer, Clark.
I saw Lana. I heard what happened
to your mom's baby.
- Clark, you need to talk to your folks.
- I did talk to my parents, Pete.
You should've seen the way my dad
looked at me. It was like I was an alien.
If I'd done what I should've,
none of this would've happened.
Clark, don't do it. When you put
that ring on, you're not yourself.
Exactly who I don't
want to be right now, Pete.
Clark!
Clark, where are you going?
Away from here.
The Clark Kent I know wouldn't
run away from his problems.
The Clark Kent you know is a lie.
- Why won't you let me in?
- Because you won't like what you see.
- I am not giving up on you.
- No one can save me.
- Not even you.
- Your parents need you. I need you.
I love you, Clark.
I love you too.
More than you'll ever know.
That's why I have to leave.
Come with me.
Smallville's my home.
It's your home too.
Not anymore.
Helen.
Helen?
You will obey me, Kal-EI.
www.tvsubtitles.net