All right, Ryan, what am I looking at?
Ryan.
A dog.
What kind of dog?
- A lab.
- What color is it?
- What color?
- Brown.
A tree.
A pine tree.
Ryan.
A father, mother and son.
Another pressure headache?
Let's try and push on.
- I don't want to answer any more questions.
- There's just a few more left.
Full moon.
A butterfly.
Train.
You're afraid you're not gonna get
all your research done.
Get some coagulant.
Yes, doctor.
What is it, Ryan?
What's OxyContin?
It's a very powerful narcotic. Why?
He's stealing it.
I knew it.
I'll be right back.
- What do you got there?
- The coagulant.
It's what you asked for, right?
Son of a... Son of a bitch!
Ryan.
Ryan?
Ryan, open the door.
Open the door now. Open up.
Clark, can you get that?
Yeah.
- Hello?
- Clark, you gotta help me.
Ryan, is that you?
- You gotta get me out.
- Calm down. Where are you?
A hospital called Summerholt.
Clark, you gotta get me out, please!
Get in there.
- Give me the phone.
- They're experimenting on me!
- What?
- Let go, help! Clark! No!
Calm down, Ryan.
- Let go, let go! Let go!
- Lay him down.
Ryan!
I'll stop! Don't put that in me! Stop!
Let go! No! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Ryan's aunt's phone has been disconnected.
The operator said there's no new listing.
- It's like she disappeared.
- Doesn't make any sense.
- What about this Summerholt?
- No, I checked.
There's no hospital by that name
in Edge City.
When did you last hear from Ryan?
He sent an e-mail a few weeks ago.
He was getting ready for school.
I'm calling the Edge City police.
I've never heard him so scared.
Maybe somebody's filed
a missing persons report.
I keep thinking I missed something.
Some clue in his e-mail,
some sign that things weren't okay.
I guess I just wasn't listening.
I know Ryan means a lot to you, Clark,
but you've gotta cut yourself some slack.
Second-guessing isn't gonna help.
Hey, remember that cute guy Henrik,
who works at the phone company?
Yeah, you mean the Hungarian one
with the toy scooter?
He's Austrian, and it's a classic Vespa,
but anyway...
...he traced Ryan's call
back to its point of origin.
You found something.
Summerholt Neurological Institute.
- It's not in Edge City, it's in Metropolis.
- That explains why we couldn't find it.
The weird thing is that Summerholt is
a research facility. They don't take patients.
And if they did, why would
Ryan be in lockdown...
...in a place that specializes
in super-esoteric brain research?
Mr. Mayor. Thank you for seeing me
on such short notice.
Always a pleasure, Lex.
How can I help you?
As you know, LexCorp is in the midst
of major plan expansion.
But we're still awaiting final approval
from the zoning commission.
Well, you know how it is these days, Lex.
With all these environmental
and safety regulations.
There's no such thing
as a rubber stamp anymore.
If this project collapses,
it's gonna cost Smallville a lot of jobs.
I've been friends with your father...
...ever since LuthorCorp bought
the old creamed-corn plant.
He was always a very generous supporter.
I never realized my father had an interest
in local politics.
I don't think he does. But I know he's never
had a permit held up at the commission.
You want a bribe?
I never said that.
But now that you're running
your father's plant...
...you should learn
how business gets done.
Let's be clear.
I don't work for my father anymore,
and it's not his plant. LexCorp owns it.
And I have my own way of doing business.
I'm up for re-election soon.
It's my fourth term.
Think of this as the beginning of
a long-term relationship, which could have...
...beneficial consequences for both of us.
Call this man.
He'll explain how things work.
Oh, and imagine how much you'll lose
if construction shuts down.
Hey.
Hi. How was your ride?
Oh, it was great. We took the long way
around Crater Lake.
Do you remember riding at
the Metropolis Equestrian Center?
And you said you wished you
belonged to a club like that?
Yeah. They've got fantastic facilities.
Well, what would you say if I told you
you could ride there every weekend...
...and any time you wanted after school?
I'd say it'd be a long drive.
I know this is sudden.
But...
Well, Dean's taking a job in Metropolis,
and he wants us to move with him.
And you said yes?
I know it's a lot to ask, Lana.
But it's important to Dean...
...and I think it'll be a great opportunity
for you. It'll be great for all of us.
I can't believe you agreed to do this
without even asking me.
- I know it's difficult to imagine right now...
- What about school? And my friends?
Not to mention the Talon.
Lana, you can visit Smallville
any time you want.
This Summerholt Institute has
more bureaucracy than the IRS.
I was on hold for an hour before
they told me to call tomorrow.
I want to go and check it out.
The police have been there,
and there was no sign of Ryan.
- This might not even be the place.
- Ryan's like a little brother to me.
If something happened to him,
I'd never forgive myself.
We understand how you feel.
But you can't just go and start
ripping the doors off this place.
His name is Ryan James.
I told you, we have no one here
by that name.
- I know he's here.
- Lf you don't leave, I'll call security.
I want to talk to someone in charge.
- Mary, is there a problem?
- Dr. Garner.
This man believes we have
a friend of his here.
It's okay, I'll handle it. Dr. Garner.
Clark Kent.
- Kent. Did your parents call earlier?
- Yeah.
We're looking for our friend Ryan James.
He called and said he was being held here.
There's been a mistake.
We're a research facility.
I know he's here.
Don't take my word for it,
talk to the police.
They came by and checked. Twice.
I wish I could help you,
but your friend isn't here.
I hope you find him.
- Ryan.
- Clark?
Hey. You're not supposed to be in here.
It's okay, we'll get you out of here.
- Here you go.
- I knew you'd come for me.
Here you go, Ryan.
How you doing?
Okay. Thanks to Clark.
Ryan, do you have any idea how we can
get ahold of your aunt?
I think she moved to Arizona.
How could she just leave you?
A few months ago, I started getting
nosebleeds and headaches.
She took me to doctors,
but no one knew what the problem was.
The bills were becoming too much
for her to handle...
Then Dr. Garner showed up
and offered to pay for my care.
Ryan, what were they treating you for?
They were...
- They were treating me...
- They were holding him for observation.
Clark, can I talk to you for a moment?
Clark?
Yeah?
Never mind.
Get some rest, okay?
I appreciate you taking Ryan in.
If I took him home,
my parents would have freaked.
Yeah, kidnapping has that effect on people.
Why did you break him out if they
were only keeping him for observation?
Look, I didn't have a choice.
- They were treating him like a lab rat.
- Clark, you abducted a minor.
They'll trace him to you and me.
We're in serious trouble here.
I shouldn't have involved you.
I'll find someplace else to hide him.
Ryan's staying here.
At least for tonight.
Tomorrow I'll talk to my lawyers,
see what our options are.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it through. I saw him
hooked to wires, I had to do something.
So you staged a one-man prison break?
How did you manage to get him out
without anybody stopping you?
Just lucky, I guess.
You're the luckiest guy I've ever met.
Let's hope it doesn't run out
before tomorrow.
Mom?
Hey, Dad.
What's going on?
Where's Ryan?
- He's safe from you.
- Clark, what did you do?
Sheriff, search every inch of this farm.
Wait, you can't do that.
- They have a search warrant.
- Place him under arrest for kidnapping.
What?
Look. Give me till tomorrow morning.
I don't know how you got him out of
Summerholt, but if he's not here by 9 a. M...
...federal marshals will be crawling all over,
and your life is going under the microscope.
Ryan. Hi.
Hi, Ryan.
Mr. Kent.
Please don't be mad at Clark,
he was trying to help me.
I know that, Ryan.
You should've seen the way
he threw that orderly.
- He must have weighed, like, 300 pounds.
- No, he's exaggerating. A little.
Look, Ryan, we're glad
that you're okay, but...
...Clark did go about this the wrong way.
I'm afraid that we don't have...
...much of a choice but to give you back.
How did you end up in Summerholt?
Dr. Garner told my aunt that there was
something wrong with my brain.
That's why I can read minds.
She found out about my ability,
it just freaked her out.
Ryan, I'm so sorry.
She's not a bad person, she just couldn't
accept that I was different.
They're here.
Hello, Ryan.
Please don't let him take me.
Dr. Garner's agreed to drop the kidnapping
charges if you turn over the boy.
Come on, Ryan, we need to get back
to Metropolis.
I'm Ryan's legal guardian,
and I have the paperwork denoting such...
...please do your job.
Having custody of a child is not the same
thing as having a pink slip to a car.
Can't you see he doesn't want
to go with you?
Ethan, please.
The choice is yours, Mr. And Mrs. Kent.
You can lose one boy here today,
or both of them.
I believe kidnapping comes
with some juvenile time.
I'm sorry, folks, but...
Sheriff.
Before you do anything...
...take a look at this.
It's a restraining order giving the Kents
custody until the situation can be reviewed.
You want to try a judicial roadblock?
You go ahead. I'll have Clark arrested.
You could, but I have a countersuit
ready to be filed.
Metropolis DA is very interested in
Summerholt's research practices...
...especially involving minors
held under duress.
Your move, doctor.
This isn't over.
Your rich friend saved you today, Clark.
Sheriff.
Surprise!
It's your jailbreak party.
We even have the obligatory
pistachio log ice cream cake...
...and we managed to rustle up a band.
This is so cool. Thanks, guys.
Good to see you, man.
I'm so glad you're back.
Yeah, me too.
You knew about this
the whole time, didn't you?
- Half a block away.
- Yeah.
- Thanks for not ruining the surprise.
- I was tempted to. I hate pistachio.
But it was definitely worth the kiss.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Pete. Tell your mom thanks.
- Thanks for what?
- She cosigned the restraining order.
Imagine getting a call from Lex Luthor
at 5 in the morning?
Hey, Pete. Come here a second.
- Pete knows your secret.
- Yeah, I know, I told him. It's all right.
- Did you know he's stressed out about it?
- No.
- Why?
- He's worried one day he'll slip up and tell.
Then they'll lock you up
in a place like Summerholt.
Brought you guys a couple of pieces
before everyone eats it all.
Hey, what's wrong?
- Just a headache.
- I'll go get you a glass of water.
You sure you're okay?
Clark.
Lana's moving to Metropolis.
Hey, Clark, got your message.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I just wanted to thank you for the party.
It was really great.
Sorry we left early,
Ryan wasn't feeling so good.
Yeah, how's he doing?
He didn't look so hot.
To be honest, I'm not really sure.
He's got a doctor's appointment tomorrow
to try to figure out what they did to him.
You should have seen him, Lana.
But he's safe now, thanks to you.
Yeah, he's just such a good kid.
Seems like life's always
kicking him in the teeth.
Makes you realize how lucky we are.
- You okay? You seem a little preoccupied.
- Oh, no. No, I'm fine.
Things aren't as solid between us
as they used to be...
...but I'm still here for you
if you want to talk about anything.
Nell and Dean are moving to Metropolis,
and I'm supposed to go with them.
How do you feel about that?
How would you feel if you were uprooted
and sent somewhere far away...
...where you didn't know anyone?
I think it'd be really tough.
I feel like a piece of luggage
they want to throw in the trunk...
...as they drive off to their new life.
Have you talked to Henry Small
about this?
No, I'm not ready to dump this in his lap.
Just because we might share the same DNA
does not mean we're family.
Well, you can come stay with us.
It's just kind of crowded right now.
Ryan's lucky.
At least he got to choose his family.
I'll see you later.
Don't go.
Don't go to Metropolis.
Or what? You gonna kidnap me too?
Nell shouldn't be able to dictate your life
without your input.
If moving doesn't feel right, don't go.
Mr. Luthor's in Metropolis
so I won't be long...
...and then we'll get you to the doctor.
You pretend around Mr. Kent
you don't like your job. But you do.
Now that you're in our lives, I may
give it up to spend more time with you.
- I don't want to be a problem.
- Ryan.
You are a gift. Like Clark.
I know your secret.
Why don't you tell Mr. Kent and Clark?
They'd want to know.
I will, when the time is right,
but in the meantime...
- I promise, my lips are sealed.
- Thank you.
Ryan.
- Hi, Lex.
- Hey, how you feeling?
- Much better. Thanks again for...
- Harboring you? My pleasure.
- I'd better get to work.
- See you.
So can I check out that
Warrior Angel collection?
That depends. Your hands clean?
Warrior Angel, number one, mint condition.
I had two copies of every issue.
One for the collection...
And one for reading.
Why do you like Warrior Angel so much?
Helped me through some tough times
when I was younger.
After your mom died?
How did you know that?
Clark told me.
The world between these glossy covers
was reassuring.
You knew who the heroes and villains were.
When you grow up...
...you learn that not everything's
black and white.
So now all you see is shades of gray?
Ryan.
Real life is not a comic book.
Sometimes you have to get
your hands dirty, make compromises.
That's what your father told you.
That doesn't mean he's right.
You are either remarkably intuitive or...
Ryan?
Ryan, what's wrong?
It's so loud.
Hey, buddy, how's your head?
Still hurts a little.
- The newest issue.
- Yeah, they had it at the gift shop.
- So, what's up with the floating balloon?
- It's Warrior Angel's aerodrome.
A floating fortress where he can get away
from his troubles.
Sounds like something
everyone should have.
- Not sure about the floating part though.
- Why not?
I have this little fear of flying.
- I didn't think you were scared of anything.
- There's a lot of things I'm scared of.
Guess I just put on a brave face.
Yeah.
Me too.
My parents said the doctors
are gonna run more tests.
They don't need to, I know what's wrong
with me. I read Dr. Garner's mind.
What is it?
There's a tumor in my head, Clark.
- It's getting bigger.
- I'll tell the doctors.
They know.
I'm dying, Clark.
And no one can save me.
Clark.
- We're going to the hospital, wanna come?
- Is there any news?
Son, the tumor is growing
at an accelerated rate.
The doctors think it's probably due
to the experiments that were done on Ryan.
This is Ryan's.
He thinks I'm a hero.
- Hey, you've helped a whole lot of people.
- I can't help Ryan.
- What kind of hero is that?
- Listen...
...this thing is beyond
even your ability, son.
The doctors are doing everything
that they can. We...
...have to pray for the best.
What am I supposed to do,
just sit here and watch Ryan die?
- No. Nobody's asking you to do that, Clark.
- Good.
Because I'm not gonna give up.
"Facts on child emancipation." I have
a feeling this isn't for a research paper.
I decided to tell Nell that I wasn't
moving with her to Metropolis.
Well, that's very Erin Brockovich of you.
How did Nell take it?
One, she's my legal guardian,
two, I'm a teenager, and three:
- I don't have any say in the matter.
- That pretty much covers all your bases.
Are you gonna pursue
the emancipation thing?
It could take up to a year and a half
to complete the process.
- Sounds like you're talking yourself out of it.
- It's my last shot.
You know, you might have
one other option.
This is the man you want to talk to.
He's developed a radical new serum
that shrinks primary brain tumors.
- It's experimental.
- How can I get in touch with him?
That's the problem.
His office in Hub City said he's flying
to Helsinki this afternoon...
...he won't be back for six weeks.
By that time, it'll be too late.
Clark.
When I was looking into Ryan's condition...
...I found that some scientists
think the type of tumor he has...
...can give a person ESP-like abilities.
- What are you saying?
Ryan is unnervingly insightful.
I think he may be able to read
people's minds.
Are you even interested in helping Ryan?
Or just exploiting him too?
I just spent three hours on the phone
tracking this doctor down.
What do you think?
I'm sorry.
I understand what you're going through,
but sometimes...
...no matter how much you want to save
someone, there's nothing you can do.
I'm not gonna let Ryan down.
When my mother got sick, I spent my time
researching doctors and treatments.
But the most important thing I could
have done was spend time with her.
By the time I realized that,
it was too late.
I wasn't at her side when she passed,
Clark. Don't make the same mistake I did.
I'm not gonna let him die, Lex.
Hey.
Brought you some comics.
- Clark beat you to it.
- Yeah?
Well, I bet he didn't bring you number 66.
That's the rarest issue.
It's the one where Devilicus
turned against Warrior Angel.
- Weren't they best friends?
- Once upon a time.
What happened to them?
Well, they ruled the Guardian Realm
together...
...until Devilicus told Warrior Angel...
...that they should join forces
and conquer humanity.
Together, no one would be able
to stop them.
- What did Warrior Angel say?
- He refused.
He believed it was a hero's sacred duty
to protect those weaker than himself.
Devilicus thought he was naive and vowed
to destroy him and everything he stood for.
Why do you think Devilicus went bad?
I'm not sure.
Probably wasn't aware of it.
You see, Ryan...
...in life, the road to darkness
is a journey...
...not a light switch.
You should remember that, Lex.
- Excuse me, have you seen Dr. Burton?
- Who?
This guy, right here.
You just missed him, kid. Right there.
Wait!
- Wait!
- Who is that?
Dr. Burton!
- What are you doing? Who are you?
- I'm Clark Kent.
My friend is really sick. Would you
take a look at these scans?
Doctor, please, by the time you get back,
it'll be too late.
- Get your hands in the air now!
- Doctor, please.
- I said, hands in the air now!
- Wait a second.
Where's your friend now?
Mom, Dad, when's Ryan
gonna be out of surgery?
- In a couple of hours.
- Clark...
...I don't think I've ever been
as proud of you as I am right now.
Your mother's right, son.
It was an amazing thing that you did.
But I hope you understand that even though
you did get Dr. Burton here...
...Ryan isn't necessarily out of the woods.
- I know it's no guarantee...
...but I think it's gonna work.
I have a great feeling about it.
Over the past 12 years...
...thirty-two city contracts have been
awarded to firms with ties to Mayor Tate.
His sweetheart deals have
endangered our environment...
...and harmed businesses trying to compete
on an uneven playing field.
Can Smallville really afford
another four years of Mayor Tate?
Why are you doing this?
Smallville needs an honest mayor.
- Are you planning on running?
- No.
But I'm putting my support and money
behind your opponent.
You'd save yourself a lot of trouble
by announcing your retirement now.
You can kiss that plant expansion goodbye.
I will see that it never gets approval.
I'm prepared to sacrifice it to defeat you.
You know, you're not from here.
People don't like you.
Don't laugh at me.
All it'll take are some fiery campaign
speeches about outside interests...
...controlling this community
and you'll start to feel the heat.
When Winston Churchill heard
about the attack on Pearl Harbor...
...he broke out a bottle of champagne
and said, "We've won the war."
His generals looked at him
like he'd lost his mind.
America's Pacific Fleet was wiped out...
...France was overrun and the Luftwaffe
was bombing London.
Churchill said America is like a giant boiler.
Light a fire under it...
...and there's no limit to the amount
of heat it can generate.
If you start a fire, Mayor Tate...
...you'd better be prepared
to deal with the flames.
Clark.
- Hey, Lana.
- Is there any news?
Ryan's still in recovery,
but Dr. Burton is optimistic.
- Everything's gonna work out.
- Yeah, I think it is.
Oh, by the way, I took your advice.
Chloe and her dad have offered to let me
stay with them until I finish high school.
- And Nell's cool with that?
- Not really, but she's agreed to it.
Well, I knew you were a fighter.
It's scary...
...but then I think of Ryan
and everything that he's gone through.
It kind of puts things in perspective.
You and Chloe as roommates.
- Did you ever see that coming?
- Not in a million years.
What is it?
Nothing.
It's just you won't be
the girl next door anymore.
I'm not going anywhere, Clark.
Maybe now you can give
your telescope to Ryan.
Mom?
Clark.
What you reading, buddy?
The infamous aerodrome, huh?
Every year for my birthday,
I'd wish for my own aerodrome.
So I could fly high above the Earth.
Up there all my problems would seem
so small and far away.
It's a good idea except for the flying part.
This is one of Lex's favorites.
- Would you give it back to him?
- No, you give it to him.
When you get out of here.
I know I said
you should be careful of Lex.
But I never told you how much
he admires you.
Promise me you'll keep an eye
on him after I'm gone.
Ryan. Don't talk like that, all right?
You're not going anywhere.
- Clark.
- Look, you don't just give up hope.
- There's more doctors we can see.
- You're not listening to me.
The doctor said you bought me
a few extra days.
I want to spend that time
with my friend.
Ryan, what's wrong?
Ryan.
- Ryan, what's wrong?
- It's so loud in here.
All right, look. I'll take you
somewhere quiet, all right?
What do you think?
It's peaceful.
I thought you were afraid of flying.
Not when I have you here to protect me.
Thanks, Clark.
For what?
This moment.
It's perfect.
I don't want you to be angry or sad.
You changed my life.
You're gonna change
a lot of people's lives, Clark.
Promise me you'll never give up.
I promise.
Subtitle by:
(MFMS)d
www.tvsubtitles.net