- Clark, you're gonna be late.
- Okay, Mom, I'm going as fast as I can.
How can you be fast as lightning and
as slow as molasses all at the same time?
Sometimes, Mom, I'm even
a mystery to myself.
Wait a minute, didn't I fix
your alarm clock recently?
I crushed it this morning
hitting the snooze alarm.
- Guess I'm not much of a morning person.
- Must have gotten that from your mother.
She could be late to her own wedding.
- In fact, she was late to her own wedding.
- Not all of us were trained by roosters.
I was up late studying
for an exam, Greek tragedy.
Speaking of Greek tragedy,
I've gotta get your mother to work.
- Want a ride?
- No, I'd just slow you guys down.
Thank you, baby.
Hera freaks out because Zeus
has been two-timing her...
...with a mere mortal, no less, so she
sends a bunch of snakes to kill Hercules...
...who is the illegitimate babe
in the cradle.
It's just family dysfunction
of Dionysian proportions.
It sounds like these people
ought to be on Ricki Lake.
While I don't condone her behavior,
Zeus did break his vows.
Doesn't give her the right
to go Fatal Attraction.
Hey, Clark, hell hath no fury
like a woman scorned.
Hello, Clark.
- Do we know each other?
- No.
Well, yes.
Clark, I'm your mother.
It's obviously a mistake,
she's not your mother.
That's what I told her. She said I probably
just need time to get used to the idea.
She gave me her phone number,
told me to call if I wanted to talk again.
I don't want you to have
anything to do with this woman.
She's gonna be hard to avoid.
She said she just bought a house...
...in Smallville.
She also said the agency that handled the
adoption was Metropolis United Charities.
That's the same place
Chloe told me about.
I thought the only adoption
they handled was mine.
So did I.
- Dad, tell me what happened back then.
- That's not important right now.
Your mother's right. We need to get
this woman to back off.
We don't want her making people curious
about where you came from.
Mrs. Kent...
...I know what you're thinking:
"This woman gave her baby up.
What right does she have
to show up after so many years?"
Well, the thought did occur to me.
Look, Mrs. Dunlevy,
I'm sure you mean well.
And I know you've gone through
a lot of trouble finding Clark...
...but he's not your child.
Oh, I've done the research.
My Lucas was the only baby turned
over to Metropolis United Charities...
...and Clark was the only child
that they ever placed.
We are Clark's legal parents,
we raised him.
Believe me, I'm not trying
to take Clark away from you.
I just want a chance
to get to know him.
Giving up Lucas was the worst thing
I've ever done.
I didn't do it because I wanted to,
I did it because I had to.
I sincerely hope that you
find Lucas someday.
But I'm afraid I'm going to have to ask you
not to bother my family or Clark ever again.
No.
Sure, Clark, you can use my computer.
Knock yourself out.
You've been getting e-mails
from Rachel Dunlevy.
You've been reading my e-mails?
You promised me you'd stop
digging into my adoption.
All I did was post a few notices on adoption
websites to see if I could get some hits.
This Dunlevy woman responded.
So you said, "Why don't you check out
my buddy Clark, he may be your son."
You have to believe me,
I didn't tell her anything about you.
So it's just a coincidence she shows up
in Smallville claiming to be my mom?
She's here? Clark, what makes you
so sure that she's not the real thing?
I'm not giving you
an exclusive on my life.
- You're not curious she might be your mom?
- Why are you obsessed about my mother?
- Do I ask you questions about yours?
- I guess not.
If you want to find somebody's mother,
find your own.
I know where she is, Clark. The difference
is she's not interested in me.
Since you may never speak to me again,
there's something you might want to know.
Metropolis United Charities
was founded by Lionel Luthor.
I admit, I'm even more intrigued now
than when I got your note.
But I'm still not sure what
this has to do with me.
Well, I understand that you
and Clark are good friends.
Mr. Kent has forbidden me
to speak to him.
I thought you might be willing to talk
to Clark, ask him to give me a chance.
Ms. Dunlevy, Jonathan Kent
doesn't exactly see me...
...as the ideal role model for his son.
I wouldn't want to encourage Clark
to defy his father.
Even if it meant giving him a chance
to know his real mother?
I'm sorry, but it's just not appropriate
for me to get involved.
I wasn't going to bring this up
unless I had to...
...but I once worked for your mother.
- You knew my mother?
And your father.
He and I became very close.
He got me pregnant and made me
give the child up for adoption.
You're claiming that Clark...?
That Clark and I...?
He's your brother, Lex.
Chloe. Hey, I've been looking
for you everywhere.
What's wrong?
Clark and I just had
a massive blowout.
About what?
Secrets, privacy, my pathological inability
to curb my curiosity.
- How are you?
- Hey, we can talk about it later.
No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to dump on you.
- Lf you can't dump on your friends...
- Exactly.
So, what did you want to talk about?
- His name's Henry Small.
- As in the Smallville Smalls?
Our very own first family.
Well, who's the hottie
hanging all over him?
My mom.
- Oh, I'm sorry, Lana.
- It's okay, you didn't know.
I think he may be
my biological father.
You okay?
I think so.
I want to find out everything
there is to know about him.
I thought...
...maybe you could help.
- But if you don't feel comfortable, it's...
- Actually, I'm flattered.
It's nice that someone trusts me enough
with their big family secret.
Then you'll do it?
I can tell you where he went to college...
...how many outstanding
parking tickets he has...
...I can even pull up his dental records
and tell you if he flosses regularly.
But if you want
to know who he is...
...I would suggest using the high-tech
research device called the doorbell.
- Clark?
- Grab a sack, son.
I just found out that Lionel Luthor
founded Metropolis United Charities.
Why was he involved in my adoption?
- Would somebody tell me what's going on?
- Jonathan, he needs to know.
All right. It was the day of
the meteor shower when I realized...
...that nothing was gonna be normal
around here again.
What's happening, Jonathan?
Martha?
Teddy!
Jonathan, look out!
Help! Stop, please! I need help!
- Are you all right?
- It's my son.
- What about him? Is he hurt?
- He... I can't...
Mister, calm down here.
Where is your son?
He... He's...
Give me a hand.
What happened to him?
His hair is...
Can't we go any faster?
We're doing the best that we can.
What are you carrying back there?
It's slowing us down.
Hey, how's your son?
He's in shock, but he'll survive.
You saved him, acting so quickly.
I'm glad I could help out.
I'm sorry. I don't
even know your name.
Jonathan Kent.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Kent.
If there's ever anything I can do for you...
...please, call me.
I mean that, Mr. Kent.
Dad, you were a hero.
I don't know why you thought
you had to keep that a secret from me.
Ethan. Is there something
we can do for you?
I'm sure you know there's a woman
in town claiming to be Clark's mother.
Well, she's petitioned Judge Ross
to order a DNA test.
- But that's crazy. She's not my mother.
- Lf that's true, this test will prove it, son.
I can have somebody come out and take
the sample to Metropolis Genetics Lab.
They can run the test in the morning,
we can get this thing over with quick.
I'm sure you folks have
nothing to be afraid of.
Not to mention, it's an eyesore.
No. They're dumping there.
Oh, come on.
What do you mean, that's it?
I don't care what
Lowell County Water and Power says...
...they are illegally dumping, and
I'm not gonna sit here... Hello? Hello?!
- Mr. Small?
- What?
I'm sorry.
I'm not taking on
any more law students right now.
No, no, I'm not a law student.
Wait, I know you.
You do?
Yeah, you run the coffee place
in town.
Yeah, yeah, the Talon.
I don't think I've seen you there.
And you never will. I boycott it.
Do you have a thing against coffee?
No, I've got a thing against Luthors.
Lex Luthor's just a silent partner.
That's what the Vichy said about Nazis.
Look what happened to France.
I didn't catch your name.
Lana Lang.
You knew my mother.
Where did you get this?
I found it.
Did you love her?
What do you want me to say?
It's ancient history, it doesn't matter.
Henry, can you stop saving the world for
one minute and give me a hand, please?
Okay, honey, I'll be right there.
- Look, Lana...
- I think you might be my father.
- Honey, are you coming?
- Yeah, I'll be in in one second.
Look, Lana, you've made a mistake.
- But l...
- I have a family now.
Please, don't bother me again.
There. Now that didn't
hurt a bit, did it?
I'll let you know.
Dad...
You had to do it, Clark. If we'd refused,
they'd have dragged us into court.
What happens when they look
at his DNA under a microscope?
If I even have DNA.
That's why we have to make sure nobody
gets a chance to analyze that sample.
This is it.
There.
Man, this Mission: Impossible
stuff is great...
...but other than my scintillating
conversational skills...
...I still don't understand
why you brought me along.
I need your spit.
You can relax. We switched
the sample, no one saw us.
Clark, I'm sorry to have put
you through all this.
It's not your fault, Dad. I guess
it just comes with the territory.
Yeah. I'm gonna go
work on the combine.
Everything's okay. Why does
Dad still seem upset?
This has been tough on him.
He always said making
a deal with the devil...
...was gonna come back to haunt us.
- Then why'd he do it?
Come on, Mom.
Why'd you need Lionel Luthor's
help in the first place?
You have no idea
the kind of pressure we were under.
We suddenly had this new
little person in our home.
We didn't know what to do with you.
We were completely overwhelmed.
Thank goodness
your mother was a pack rat.
Sweetheart, he's not ours to keep.
I just keep feeling there's
a reason he's here.
He's exactly what I wished for
in the flower shop this morning.
Hey. Since when did Martha Kent
believe in magic wands?
Since the moment
I laid eyes on this little boy.
Get him upstairs. Hurry, go on.
Just a...
Just a second.
- Evening, Jonathan.
- Ethan.
I saw what was left
of your truck out on Route 17.
I wanted to stop by
and make sure you're all right.
We're just a little banged up,
but we're fine.
Look, I'm sure there are folks who need
your attention a lot more than we...
- Who's the little fellow?
- He got away from me. He's strong.
- That's...
- Clark.
I thought my family name
would make a good first name.
Deputy, I would like you to be the
first one in Smallville to meet our son.
Adopted, of course. We just brought him
back from Metropolis this morning.
I didn't know you folks
were planning to adopt.
Oh, Ethan, you know us,
we like to keep to ourselves.
But it's been in the works
for quite a while.
Well, congratulations.
It's nice to see something good
happen in the middle of all this tragedy.
He was right.
You were the one good thing
that happened that day.
So you just made it up,
spur of the moment.
I couldn't say we'd found you
in a corn field.
Once the words came out, I knew
we'd have to back them up eventually.
So we called Lionel Luthor, cashed in
that favor. He arranged everything.
If everything worked out,
why'd you keep it secret?
Hey, I hope I'm not interrupting
anything important.
Not at all, Lex.
Ever wish you had a big brother
to help you with your jump shot?
I think I've managed to become
a pretty decent player on my own.
Rachel Dunlevy came to see me.
She says you and I have
a few chromosomes in common.
My father's chromosomes, to be exact.
You mean...?
Personally, I think I got
all the looks in the family.
I don't know what happened
between her and your father...
...but she's not my mother.
- Trust me, I'm as skeptical as you are.
For all I know, this is an elaborate scheme
to win a paternity suit against my father.
Did you ask him about it?
I didn't want to make any accusations until
I had more facts. It's not hard to imagine.
In the annals of extramarital exploits,
my father probably has his own chapter.
It doesn't bother you? I mean,
I know how close you were to your mother.
To the extent that it caused
my mother pain...
...sure, it bothers me.
Unfortunately, not every marriage...
...is quite as Rockwellian
as Jonathan and Martha Kent's.
Anyway, I told Ms. Dunlevy
that in the 21 st century...
...people shouldn't make claims like hers
without the DNA to back them up.
So, what do you think, Clark?
No chance we could be brothers?
As cool as that would be,
Lex, we're not.
Rachel.
When the guard called and told me
you were down at the gate...
...I didn't believe him.
We had an agreement.
I just got the results
from the DNA test.
I don't know how, but you
did something to alter them.
Did what? What are you
talking about?
Clark Kent is our son,
and you know that!
You haven't changed, Rachel.
You are still completely irrational.
No, the only irrational thing that I ever did
was to let you rip my child from my arms.
You were well-compensated
and well taken care of.
You think money made up for
seven years in a psychiatric ward?
You needed help.
No, what I needed was
a home and a family.
After you were through with me
that wasn't going to happen.
Not with Lucas, not with anybody.
Why didn't you
continue your treatment?
I didn't need any treatment.
You just wanted me out of the way.
Classic denial.
Oh, this isn't over, Lionel.
I'm gonna expose you.
Expose me? To whom?
My wife is dead. You know that.
Are you still as beautiful, Rachel?
Oh, you were lovely.
You have to move on.
Forget the past.
If you need help, I'd be happy
to call Dr. Friedberg.
I'm sure he'd be more than willing
to make room for you at the clinic.
Ms. Dunlevy?
Is everything all right?
There.
Wow, that is quite a catch.
Took all my strength to pull that one in.
My dad even had to help me land it.
You're lucky you've got
such a great father.
I heard you and Chloe had a big fight.
Don't worry, she didn't
give me any details.
I assume that this is shrouded
in the usual Kent cloak of secrecy.
Chloe promised not to look
into my adoption, and then she did.
Now I've got a woman in town
claiming to be my mother.
- Is there any chance?
- No, not in a million years.
She just showed up
out of the blue?
She ambushed me at school. "Hi, Clark,
I'm your mother." I mean, who does that?
Do you remember that guy
in the photo with my mom?
I found out who he was. His name's
Henry Small. I went to his house.
- How'd it go?
- Well...
...he hates the Talon, hates the Luthors,
compared me to the Nazis...
...and told me to never
come back again.
That good, huh?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I have done pretty well
without a father this long...
...I don't know why I thought
I needed one now.
I do.
Lana, we're different. We don't get to see
our biological parents every day...
...and see a little piece of who we are
or who we may become.
If I had a chance to get to know
my birth parents...
...I wouldn't give up just because the first
meeting didn't go the way I hoped.
There.
- No, no, no. You're okay.
- Where am I?
You're at my house.
I bought it with the money
your father gave me.
I knew I'd need it one day,
so I never spent it.
I'm fixing it up so that Clark
will feel at home here.
I know how hard it must be.
No, no. No, you don't.
All those lost years.
Martha Kent getting to
bake the birthday cakes.
Martha Kent getting to dry his tears.
So that gives you the right
to kidnap me?
Believe me, I didn't want to do this,
but your father gave me no choice.
Look, if my father's lying,
Clark really is my brother.
I want to know just as much
as you do.
How does holding me prisoner help you?
Because, Lex, either your father
tells the truth...
...or he's going to know
the pain of losing his son.
What's wrong?
Rachel Dunlevy.
She's kidnapped Lex.
Oh, my God.
If I don't call a press conference announcing
that Clark's adoption was a sham...
...and that he's my illegitimate son,
she's...
She's gonna kill Lex.
Chloe, I'm so glad I found you.
Okay, there's a sentence
I never thought I'd hear again.
We both did and said things
that we regret.
I know I did.
Look, you have to believe that
I would burn my press pass...
...if I thought it would
come between us.
No, you wouldn't. It's too much of who
you are, and right now I need it.
If Rachel Dunlevy did buy a house,
she'll be listed with the county clerk.
It's just gonna take a minute
to get a hit.
Chloe, what I said about your mother,
I was way out of line.
It's cool. We all have
family secrets, I guess.
She left when I was 5.
I came downstairs, and there
was my dad trying to make waffles.
He never even really explained
why she left. It was weird.
I'm sorry.
It's hard thinking you weren't
good enough for someone to love.
Don't ever think that.
There is no record of Rachel Dunlevy.
Try the name Lucas Luthor.
Okay, you're gonna have to explain
that one to me later.
Bingo. There's his address.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
for coming on such short notice.
I have an important announcement
to make that concerns my family.
My son, Lex Luthor, has been kidnapped.
I want to say to his abductor:
I will never give in to your demands.
- No.
- Lf you harm him...
- No! No!
...in any way...
...I will not rest...
...until you are hunted down
and locked away, this time forever.
It's always been the policy of my company
and my family never to negotiate...
- Where are you going? No!
- Your father just killed you, Lex.
Who are you?
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
I'm not your son.
No.
Oh, no.
- Lf you need anything else, give me a shout.
- Thanks.
Cute place, very colorful.
Mr. Small.
Call me Henry.
Can I get you a coffee?
- Of course, you wouldn't want a coffee.
- Regular coffee would be great.
I got your letter.
And yes, you did ambush me.
But from the way you describe yourself,
it might just be a habit you got from me.
So you are my father?
I don't know.
But I'm willing to find out.
Rachel's been admitted to
a private psychiatric clinic.
Even if she tries to explain what you did,
nobody will believe her.
- I really feel sorry for her.
- We all do, son.
I can't even imagine what it was like
giving up that baby.
I'm just glad our own family
is still in one piece.
Not even Lionel Luthor
could tear us apart.
But Lionel helped us.
Dad, why do you hate him so much?
The morning he came by
with the adoption papers...
...I thought I'd never lay eyes
on him again.
Mr. Kent.
Mr. Luthor.
You call me Lionel, please.
Lionel.
I think you'll find everything in order.
Thank you.
And thank you for bringing it out yourself.
You really didn't have to do that.
We're taking Lex back
to Metropolis today.
Hey, that's fantastic. I'm glad
your son's gonna be all right.
Thank you. Thank you.
There is one thing I'd like you
to do for me.
- Yeah?
- I'm sure you've heard...
...the Ross brothers are having second
thoughts about selling me their factory.
They don't want to sell to an outsider.
They're friends of yours, aren't they?
- Yeah. Yeah, they are.
- Talk to them.
Convince them that I only
have Smallville's best interests at heart.
I think it would make a difference.
I really don't think that's
really any of my business, Mr. Luthor.
I understand.
I'd be careful with that. I wouldn't
want the Department of Family Welfare...
...to find out young Clark's
adoption's a sham.
Wait, are you threatening me?
Of course not.
I'm just asking for a small favor.
So you did it.
You convinced the Rosses to sell.
I helped the Luthors get
a foothold on this community.
The smokestacks, the toxic dumping...
...all the people who were cheated,
including Pete's family...
- It wouldn't have happened, if not for me.
- You couldn't have known.
I should have known. I knew exactly
what kind of a man Lionel Luthor was.
Why didn't you tell me?
I knew you would do exactly what
you're doing now, which is blame yourself.
- You were protecting me, it is my fault.
- No.
You never believe that.
This was my decision.
This is my fault.
Mine alone.
Lex, is that you?
Still alive and kicking, Dad.
No thanks to you.
You're a survivor, son.
I knew she wasn't gonna kill you.
Not for lack of trying.
I couldn't give in to her.
You must know that.
Like you did all those years ago?
I loved your mother
very deeply, Lex...
...but I was not a perfect husband.
I strayed.
If you've never been tempted,
I'm sure one day you will be.
We're not talking about me, Dad.
We're talking about Rachel Dunlevy.
Did she bear your illegitimate son
or not?
I never knew she was pregnant.
Then she reappeared one day
with a child she claimed was mine...
...demanding that I leave
your mother and marry her.
So you bribed her to give
the child up for adoption.
She was imbalanced.
She threatened me.
Your mother was too sick
to burden her with a scandal.
Your altruism is inspiring, Dad.
I did what I thought
best for everyone.
I had the child placed
with a suitable family.
- Not the Kents?
- The Kents?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Then where is he?
He...
...died...
...before his first birthday.
Forgive me, Lex, I'm very tired.
It's been a long day.
Sure, Dad.
Subtitle by:
(MFMS)d
www.tvsubtitles.net