Previously, on Prison Break...
What are the charges?
Attempted murder.
He's also being arraigned for the murder
of his mother and his stepfather.
Don't look at me like I'm some con.
You're as crooked as Scoliosis.
I don't get caught.
- This is as far as you go.
- Come on, bro.
You and I, we're not bros.
When were you planning on
telling us about the money, man?
What money?
The $5 million that Westmoreland
planted in the desert in Utah.
I found Steadman.
I'm with him now, Linc.
He's alive.
What are you talking about,
you found Steadman?
Oh, my God.
My hand has been in that box
for hours now. It is dying.
I can promise you nothing.
Story of my life.
These?
Keys to a car that's waiting for us
a couple hundred yards from here.
Are there 2 of us or 5 of us?
That's the two of us.
We got company!
How did he know?
It's only a matter of time
before we know everything
that is in Scofield's head.
where he plans to run to,
how he plans to get there,
so when the time comes
that he does get there,
we'll be waiting for him.
Canadian and Mexican border patrols
have all the mug shots.
Bortac's on high alert.
See if we can get
the Mexican border patrol
to set up checkpoints 50 miles in.
The warden over at Fox River called,
asked to be kept in the loop.
What should I tell him?
That he's no longer in it.
That info that you asked for
is on your desk when you get in.
Thank you.
What's the plan, man?
No bars on these doors.
Do what you like.
With what?
We're supposed to be in Mexico
right now.
Sipping on margaritas, waiting for
the heat to dip. That was the plan.
You see, they just used us to dig, man.
We're gophers.
- Where's Michael?
- He'll be here.
- Okay.
- You know what, Sucre?
Maybe you and I should go
and get that $5 million,
Know what I'm saying?
I mean, it's just sitting there
in Tooele, Utah, ready to get some air.
You all stay here, so shut your mouth!
You got one more time to touch me, man!
- All right, guys, chill.
- What?
Relax.
Honey, are you sure
you packed everything?
Yummy.
Our photos are in the paper.
We're probably all over the news.
Yeah, and you didn't see that coming?
What's so funny?
The two of you, cracks me up.
Here's to amateur hour.
What do you say, saludo?
Yeah, yuck it up, funny man.
Last Supper, boys.
This is the part where we say good bye.
It's not much.
It's enough to get you started.
No.
I'm not telling you where Fibonacci is.
Well, I didn't ask.
I only ask for a quarter
for a phone call.
Make forward.
Thank you.
I wonder what happened
to the other guys.
They all had a head-start, except T-Bag.
Yeah, he was,
he was bleeding pretty bad.
Think he's dead?
Are you done?
No. I...
I still have to clean it.
But you're done?
Yes.
It's time to move.
We got everything we need.
Just a quick stop in Utah
and then we're off to Mexico.
L.J. has a hearing today to determine
if he gets tried as an adult.
I can get him.
It's not the right time.
- When will it be?
- After we go to Mexico.
After we're off the news.
They framed him for a double homicide.
As soon as he loses his hearing,
they're gonna ship him out
to an adult facility,
so today in the courthouse
is my only chance to get him.
They took Veronica,
they're not going to take my son.
I know.
I would never leave L.J. behind,
but we can't do this now.
There's no plan in place.
Believe me, I know that courthouse.
I've been there more times
than I can remember.
The only one guarding him's the bailiff.
He carries mace and a big stick.
So you're going to bum-rush
the courthouse, that's your plan.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Hey, yo, we're headed out, man.
Well, good luck
to everyone.
- Stay out of trouble.
- Definitely.
This is it, buddy.
I hope you find the girl, buddy.
She is all I have,
I'll die trying.
Good luck.
You be easy, man.
- Adios.
- Cuidate.
Maybe we'll see each other again.
You never know, Michael.
You never know.
Tell me everything you know
about the courthouse.
Sync: fisherchen www. YDY. com
Amended by www.sub-way.fr
Did you get any sleep?
A couple hours.
Eight of 'em, I still can't believe it.
This exhibit A/, why you don't let women
work in the military the police force
and especially inside a male prison,
'cause look what you get.
Dr. Sweetcheeks leaves the door open
for Scofield and here we are.
Sounds like there's a little bit more
to the...
If Tancredi doesn't leave
her office door unlocked,
those eight dirtbags would be
in the SHU right now, okay?
Bottom line!
Brad.
- Any updates?
- None.
They were last seen
at that cemetery in Oswego.
- They'll get 'em.
It's been handed over to the F.B.I.
- That doesn't mean we can't work it.
- It does, actually.
You and I have been
pulled off the pursuit.
- Why?
- We're going to find out shortly.
We have to report to the DOC
headquarters. I'll meet you there.
Sir, we can get these guys.
Just give me a couple more days
- and I swear I'll...
- Brad!
We've got to go.
No family with Patoshik, nothing?
Yeah, until about 4 years ago
when he killed them all.
Updated rap sheet on Apolskis!
Take a look when you get a chance.
Man, I'm so sorry.
My bad. My bad, bro.
I'm sorry.
Scott Kolbrenner.
It's this one here.
Don't touch the radio.
Hi. I'm with the Des Moines Herald.
I'm covering the L.J. Burrows hearing.
What time does that start today?
Come on.
Thank you.
3:00. The hearing lasts a half hour max.
He'll be taken down to transport bay
at ten till they catch the 4:00 van.
So how do we get close to him?
Well, when I was locked up, I had
nothing to do except study the briefs.
Nick Savrinn's bar number is
on the front page of every one.
We want to talk to L.J., we just...
we pose as one of his attorneys.
Yeah.
Hogwash.
That is absolute hogwash.
Please answer the question.
How was Scofield able
to have exclusive access to you,
pull a shank on you,
and bind you to your chair,
the warden of the penitentiary?
I trusted him.
Obviously, he betrayed that trust.
Officer Bellick,
is it true that almost all the inmates
who either escaped or tried to escape
worked in prison industries?
That's right.
Why did these inmates have
so much time to dig a hole in the floor
of the guard's break room
while working prison industries?
I can answer that. With all due respect,
if any of you have ever worked a day
in a prison, you would know that
since an inmate only gets
19 cents an hour,
some are bound to drag their feet.
Officer Bellick,
is it true you sold the right
to run prison industries
to the highest bidder?
No. Who the hell told you that?
This is unbelievable.
While we're wasting time in here,
there are eight escaped convicts
out there...
Were you employed at Fox River
as a correctional officer, Mr. Geary?
Yep.
Yeah, until he was fired
for shaking down inmates.
That will be your last outburst,
officer.
Were you aware of any arrangement
officer Bellick had with any inmate
regarding prison industries?
Yeah, he sold it to John Abruzzi.
John Abruzzi, who was one
of the escaped convicts?
Yep.
We'll get other C.Os to substantiate this
if we have to, officer Bellick,
so I'm giving you one chance
to get in front of it.
Did you sell prison industries
to John Abruzzi?
Yes or no?
Yes, but at no time was I aware...
- That'll be all.
- ...of any talk of escape.
That will be all!
Warden, you and officer Bellick
can step out into the hallway.
We'll call for you
when we've reached a decision.
I'm going to get some coffee.
Well, I did my best
under the circumstances.
The good news, sir,
is you had the hand iced,
so I was able to restore
blood flow and...
the bones are bent.
However, I recommend you get
medical attention asap.
Meanwhile, some Aspirin will help
thin the blood and avoid clotting.
Some antibiotics and painkillers.
I usually tell the owner of the dog,
cat, whatever,
to coat them with peanut butter
so they're easier to chew
but, obviously, in your case...
You did one hell of a job, doc.
Well, thank you.
Well...
It's okay for you to leave now.
Oh, I'm leaving.
You're not.
- What?
- You heard me.
Look, sir, I haven't seen anything
and I won't tell anyone.
Well, you know...
you know, I fell for that bill of goods
once before.
Never again.
Sir, I swear to God I will tell nobody.
You would, and I would die in prison.
Please, please, please.
Now, you did me a solid,
so I'm going to return the favor.
This can go down humanely
if you don't fight,
but if you pull a stunt like that again,
it's going to get inhumane right quick.
Your call.
But, one way or another...
I am putting you down, doc.
- Lincoln Burrows Junior. - Yeah.
In here, you got a visitor.
You must be L.J.
Agent Mahone, F.B.I.
Thank you.
Please.
I'm assuming you've heard.
Yeah.
I have to tell you.
What your dad and uncle pulled off...
very impressive.
I've been doing this 14 years,
and most escapes can be attributed
to dumb luck or brute force.
The level of planning and sophistication
that went into this one,
and eight guys got out.
I really do, professionally speaking,
have a lot of admiration
for Lincoln and Michael.
Cool. Now we're buddies.
What do you need?
Help me bring them in...
peacefully.
I don't know where they are.
I don't know where they're going.
There's another way you can help.
- How?
- Go on TV.
I can have a camera crew down here
in a half an hour.
You know what, man?
The murder charge they put on my dad,
the two murder charges they put on me,
everything's been a setup
coming from way up top.
So the fact that you work
for the government...
I got nothing to say.
I'll give you the same advice
that you'd get from the guy
working at the deli downstairs.
Start thinking about yourself now.
In fact, the sooner the better,
because no one,
not your father, L.J., not your uncle
is going to do your time.
And, at 16 years old,
you're looking at a long stretch.
How much time you get,
where you serve it,
who your cell mate might be.
You need to start
thinking about yourself. Now.
I want your dad, I want your uncle,
and I'm willing to deal.
Don't wait and let someone else
get the reward.
What's up?
Hey, man, you look familiar.
Did you rush Sig ep last semester?
- Sig what?
- Sig Ep.
- No.
- Next in line.
Where to?
Utah.
How we doing here?
Nothing until tomorrow.
All right, yo, I got 45 bucks.
How far will that get me?
Nick Savrinn.
Bar number is 56437.
I've got a call time with my client,
L.J. Burrows.
Hello.
Know who this is?
Yeah.
Yeah, Nick Savrinn.
How you holding on?
Doing what I can do.
How about you?
I'm worried about you.
I'm sorry about
what you're going through.
Thanks. Word is...
after this hearing, because of my dad
being so high profile,
they're...
They're shipping me to an adult facility
in Kingman, Arizona.
Yeah, well, hopefully,
that ain't gonna happen.
You hear from Veronica today?
She didn't show up.
They gave me some court-appointed clown.
No.
I haven't heard from her.
Hey, this...
this fed came by and talked to me today.
Yeah?
He wanted me to help try
in getting my dad to turn himself in.
Well, knowing your dad,
I doubt that's gonna happen.
Listen up, L.J.. This is real important.
All right.
On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
You got that?
Until then, keep you head up.
What?
Just remember that.
I'm going to do
everything I can to get you out.
Hey, Nick...
if you talk to my dad...
tell him no matter what, I love him.
Did you get him?
Let's do this.
Got one more stop.
There is a belief in my religion
which I know to be true
and it applies to everyone,
Hindu or not.
The acts we commit in this life
determine where we go in the next.
And he who commits evil
can never hope for eternal happiness.
Never been a goal of mine, doc.
I'm more a here and now type.
I'll tell you something I know is true.
The Indians here,
the Tomahawk variety,
some of them believe... well,
used to believe before
most of them were slaughtered,
that when a warrior
kills another in battle,
he absorbs that fallen warrior's spirit.
So this isn't the end for you, doc.
You're with me now.
And how are you doing in this fine day?
I'm great. How are you?
Couldn't be better.
Anything in particular
I can help you find?
Just looking, thanks.
Well, if you need any assistance,
just give a holler.
- How are we in this find day?
- Great.
Can I help you find anything?
I'm good, thanks.
We gotta go.
- I just need to pay up.
- Now.
How are you today, officer?
Yeah, they were right, uh...
well, they were...
they were right back here.
We can make it to the courthouse
on foot from here.
You don't understand...
everything is in that car.
Forget the damn car. We don't have time.
Come on, man, let's go.
Hi.
It is the finding of this panel
that warden Pope,
you'll be docked two weeks,
placed on three months probation.
Officer Brad Bellick,
will be terminated.
Effective immediately.
Mr. Bellick, you can retrieve whatever
belongings you may have from Fox River.
That will be all.
I've...
I've worked at Fox River
since I was 18 years old.
Being a C. O. is my life.
And we appreciate that.
Look, we could have saved a lot of time
if you would have just told us
in the beginning
- that this was gonna be a railroad.
- That'll be all, warden.
There is only one person
responsible for this escape out there.
His name is Michael Scofield.
It's not officer Bellick.
It's not me!
But you need a fall guy, fine.
But you're not gonna be just
taking officer Bellick's job.
Because even though I am not proud
of many of his actions,
it will be a cold day in hell
when I turn my back on 1 of my own men.
I quit.
That will be all.
If this thing doesn't work out
and you end up going back to Fox River,
I ain't coming to get ya.
I mean, you are the brains
and I am the brute.
Seriously, Michael,
you don't have to do this.
Let's go.
We're good.
You got a call from Nick Savrinn
earlier today. What was that all about?
He's my attorney. That's privileged.
That's odd because Nick Savrinn
was found dead in his apartment
an hour before that call came in to you.
- Listen up, LJ, this is real important.
- All right.
On the third, look out
for Otis Wright.
You got that?
You know, for someone who's
so convinced that the government
is capable of so many
underhanded things,
you sure are playing
fast and loose with me.
What are you going to do, throw
another fake murder charge on me?
Who's Otis Wright?
- I have no idea.
- I think you do.
And if you don't tell me,
after you're convicted,
I will be in that courtroom
when you're sentenced
and I will hang you out to dry.
Take it to the bank.
Yeah.
Put me in touch with the prosecutor
in the LJ Burrows case.
I want a meeting.
On the third, look out
for Otis Wright.
Until then, keep your head up.
Otis Wright.
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Move it.
I'll escort the boy.
Otis Wright.
Otis elevator on the right.
What is he planning?
Keep it in the holster
and no one gets hurt.
Keep it in the holster.
All right, LJ, hit stop.
He's coming with us.
So just stay cool, stay cool.
Hey, buddy,
give me his gun.
LJ, give me your hand.
That a boy. Come on.
Hey! Back off!
Back off! Back off!
I'm not shooting anybody,
neither are you.
Give yourself up and your kid can walk.
It's the only way
he's getting out of this place.
It's the only way!
Dad!
- Dad, you gotta let me go.
- No.
You gotta let me go!
Up there. Scofield is in the building.
Take him!
You guys go, cover that way!
Scofield and Burrows
are in the building!
Come on.
Freeze! Do not move!
Truck!
Stop!
Bradley?
Yeah, ma.
What are you doing home so early?
I had to take...
my personal day, you know,
before they went away.
Shouldn't you be looking
for the convicts?
Well, they got somebody else
doing that, mom.
You okay?
I'm good.
Okay.
All right.
I think we should break
a bottle of champagne across its bow.
If you're intending to get this thing
home for your anniversary tonight,
- I wouldn't recommend it.
- No.
Listen, I want you to know I...
well, I feel very fortunate
to have met you.
I'm breaking out.
And you're gonna make sure
my brother goes with me.
Thank you for calling Autostar, dr...
Gudat? Am I pronouncing that correctly?
Dead on.
How can help you today?
I need...
directions.
Where to, sir?
Utah.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Are you Scott Kolbrenner?
Yeah, I am. Yeah.
You must be Debra Jean.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yes, same here.
It's so funny. I was almost ready
to leave when you called.
No one else responded.
I guess there's not a lot
of Utah people out here.
Are you from there?
No, I just, you know...
I'm headed up there to
collect an inheritance.
My grandpa died.
- Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
- It's alright.
He went out with his boots on.
So where's your stuff?
I mailed it yesterday.
Mailed it? I've never heard of that.
You know, you don't wanna lug it around.
Plus, I got a boy who works for UPS,
so he hooked it up.
So you wanna bounce?
I'm parked out front.
Bradley?
Yeah, ma.
They've just announced
the rewards on the tv.
What reward?
The convicts. For the convicts...
the ones who escaped.
- How much? - $100,000 apiece.
$300,000 for the animal who killed
president Reynolds' brother.
Every whacko in the country is gonna be
after those bums now, wouldn't you say?
Step out of the vehicle
with your hands up!
- We gotta move.
- I can't.
Oh, my God.
I failed him.
I sure hope you packed a lunch.
It's gonna be a long ride to Arizona.
Move your ass.
Get men in all the area hospitals.
Wherever they are,
one of them is bleeding good.
Which means,
they either come to us,
or they die.