Previously on "Lost"...
Jason.
These people are smart.
And they're animals,
and if you think that
one gun and one bullet
is gonna stop them,
think again.
I'm going after my son,
and nobody is going to stop me, okay?
I'll come with you.
No. I have to do it alone.
I'm going out to the line that
we're not supposed to cross
and telling them
that we've got you.
They'll never give you Walt.
Michael.
What's wrong with him?
Michael. Michael?
Michael.
Jack? Where are you going?
Maybe they just let him go.
Let him go-- he's alone!
They didn't just push him out into
the jungle, Jack. He's alone!
Okay.
Let's go.
See ya, Ana Lucia.
- You look tired.
- Yeah, thanks.
What?
Where were you last night?
- Home.
- All night?
Yeah. Cooked myself some dinner,
watched some tv.
What'd you watch?
Let's go for a drive.
Remember Jason Alder?
Found him in a parking lot just
after 3:00 in the morning.
He was dead an hour
before anyone saw him.
Crime scene pulled a
gun from the dumpster.
Registration was filed off--
no prints, no witnesses.
He was executed.
Any idea who did it?
Yeah, Ana. You did.
This man confesses to
shooting you in cold blood,
and you refuse to I.D.
him, so we had to cut him loose.
A week later, he shows up with
five bullets in his chest,
because someone shot
him in cold blood.
Guess I should get a lawyer.
Look, we both know that this is
gonna be a dead-end investigation.
But, Ana, if you did this...
if you did this,
you have to let me help you.
Yeah, thanks, mom,
but I don't need your help.
You don't want my help? You're gonna
have to get it from somewhere else.
You're a police officer, Ana.
If you don't respect me,
at least respect that.
Then I quit.
Hey, Henry. What do you say?
How long you gonna keep up
this hunger strike, Henry?
Did I ever tell
you I was a cop?
I've been around a lot
of killers in my life.
You know what surprises
me the most about 'em?
How much they love to talk.
But you're different... Henry.
Hmm?
Quiet.
What was that?
If you're gonna say something,
you're gonna have to speak--
You killed two of us--
Good people who were
leaving you alone.
You're the killer, Ana Lucia.
I guess he decided to
start talking, huh?
2x20:
Two for the Road
Hey, Mike. Tequila and tonic.
Long day, huh?
Good to see you again.
You, uh,
"wanded" me at security.
Another one, please.
So how does one get into "wanding"?
One stops being a cop.
What a coincidence.
I just stopped being a doctor.
Why'd you quit?
I didn't.
My son ratted me out for
drinking on the job. Thank you.
Lost my license.
Hmm. Yeah, I know.
It's hilarious.
No, no. It's just that...
I don't believe that parents and
their kids should work together.
Too many issues.
I'll drink to that.
So where you headed?
Sydney. Sydney, Australia.
Want to come?
I'm serious.
Why would I go to
Sydney with you?
Maybe fate has just thrown
the two of us together.
You know,
like two drinks in an airport bar.
Why would fate do that?
Oh, the same reason
fate does anything--
so that we can help
each other out.
You do need help, right?
Unless you don't.
What I'm doing down there
could be a little dangerous,
and I need someone to protect me--
a bodyguard.
It's perfect for someone
who stopped being a cop.
I  don't even know your name.
Oh, let's not use real names.
I tell you what--
why don't you pick a name for me?
And then I'll pick one for you.
You look like a Tom.
Tom. What an excellent name.
And you should be a...
Sarah.
A ustralia.
What happened?
I cut myself shaving.
The guy in the hatch
tried to kill me.
You okay?
I'm fine...
but he won't be.
- Hey, Ana?
- What?
Don't do anything stupid.
If you've come to apologize,
I forgive you for hitting
me with your crutch.
I'm so glad my head
didn't break it.
Why?
Well, that's a broad question.
Why did you try to hurt
Ana Lucia but not me?
I'm not sure I know what
you're getting at, John.
I was trapped under that
blast door... helpless.
You could have crushed my skull,
but you didn't do a thing.
Why didn't you?
Because you're one of
the good ones, John.
What? What? Good what?
None of this matters.
I'm dead, anyway.
The doctor's gone
to make a trade,
and we both know he'll come
back empty-handed, and then...
I've lost my value.
So either Jack comes
back here and kills me,
or my people find out where
I'm being held, and they do it.
Why would your own
people want to kill you?
Because the man in charge...
He's a great man, John--
a brilliant man.
But he is not a forgiving man.
He'll kill me because
I failed, John.
I failed my mission.
What mission?
When that woman caught
me in her trap,
I was on my way here, John.
I was coming for you.
Locke!
Locke, get out here!
John!
Hey, I've been knocking those
things down for 20 minutes.
Get your hands
off my damn mango.
Didn't figure you for
the fruit-picking type.
What do you want?
I need a gun.
Well, here's an idea.
Why not go to your buddy Jack?
He's got himself a gun.
Oh, that's right. He's still
traipsin' around the jungle with Kate.
If you've got a problem 'cause he's
making time with your girlfriend,
don't take it out on me, man.
How about you just
give me a gun?
Here's another idea-- scram.
You heard me. Now git.
Sarah.
Sarah, open the damn door.
Good, you're up.
It's, uh, it's time.
Protection duty.
Come on, let's go.
After four days of drinking
and doing nothing,
now, in the middle of the night,
you're ready to go?
That's exactly right.
It's time. Come on.
Fate's calling, Sarah.
This is it.
Pull over right here.
This is what you needed protection for--
the suburbs?
Stay in the car.
Should I keep the
meter running?
Can I come in?
Look, she's my daughter,
and I have every right to see her.
No, you don't have a right!
Get out!
I'm coming in here.
You can't stop me! She's my daughter!
I pay the mortgage on this house!
I want to see my daughter!
What the hell is
wrong with you?
Don't you ever come back here!
I was just having a
conversation with the lady.
You need help!
Dude, nice hole.
What is it, Hurley?
Hey, man,
you remember that radio we made?
I was thinking maybe I could
get it to play some music.
You know, for Libby.
Well, it worked only once,and
then just for a minute.
I've tried several times
since and only gotten static.
Here's the thing.
Even that would be good.
Because then,
Libby would be like,
"it's the thought that counts,"
and I'll score major points,
especially when she sees me
holding it over my head.
And  why would you hold a
static-generating radio over your head?
They didn't have "Say
Anything" in Baghdad?
It's awesome.
This dude, like, gets this boom box,
and he holds it over his head
outside this chick's window,
and he plays some Peter Gabriel song
for her, and bam! The girl's, like, his.
I mean, after her dad goes to jail.
But then he gets her!
I  think I get the idea.
You should really
check it out sometime.
I mean, if we ever, you know,
get off this island.
If you want to do
something nice for Libby,
there's a beautiful beach
3 kilometers from here.
You could take her there.
You think she'd like that?
I took Shannon there once.
Michael. Michael.
So it worked?
What are you
talking about, John?
Your deal. The trade.
- If they gave us Michael--
- They didn't give us anything.
So it was just a coincidence
that he came wandering out?
I was shouting.
He heard my voice.
What? They just let Michael go,
hoping that we would keep
up our end of the bargain?
You think they're on
the honor system?
- Hey.
Come out, come out,
whoever you are.
I know you're there.
Don't make me come
in after you.
Ahem!
Well, well, well.
What do we got here?
Is little red riding hood gonna follow the
big bad wolf back to his stash o' guns?
Why don't you give me
that one right there?
I ain't gonna
gimme-you nothin'.
We been through this, Lucy.
What you gonna do
now, muchacha?
We need some damn
music in here.
- Who is she?
- Who is who?
That woman.
She is a very long
story, Sarah.
It's Ana Lucia.
Well, I'm still Tom.
You're pathetic,
that's what you are.
You bet your sweet ass I am.
Why are you here?
I'm here because I can't
apologize to my son.
He tried to help me,
so I thanked him by cutting him off.
I thanked him by hating him.
You came here for the same reason I did,
kiddo. You ran away.
My, my. Look what fate has
delivered up this time.
Come on.
Let's go have a drink or ten
and be pathetic together.
What do you say?
No.
That's your call.
Hey! I'm walking here.
Wait.
Don't.
Let's just get the
hell out of Sydney.
Let's just go. Let's go back.
I can't ever go back.
See you, kiddo.
What?
Don't you want my phone number?
You tell anyone about this...
and I'll kill you.
Guess  that takes
cuddling off the table.
Hey there.
- Oh!
- How's it going?
This isn't what it looks like.
And...what does it look like?
It... looks like something...
that... it's not.
Oh, man.
I'm so busted.
Hurley, I'm not here to tell
you how to act around food.
No, I'm not busted for that.
I'm busted for...
something else.
I was packing a picnic,
'cause I was kinda hoping that
you'd wanna go with me.
You know, as an "us" thing.
But it was a surprise.
Really?
That's very sweet.
- So, do you wanna go?
- Where to?
Can that part still
be a surprise?
- Hey, you're back.
- Hey.
So, the others--
they didn't show up?
No.
Michael's back, though.
What happened here?
My fault.
I left the tap on in
the bathroom sink,
and Ana wiped out and hit
her head on the counter.
And I'm sorry-- again.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Jack. Jack.
I think he's waking up.
Michael. Hey, Michael.
Hey... Jack?
Hey, man.
Man... where...
- How did I get...
- Oh, wait.
Try to take it easy, okay?
You're back in the hatch.
We found you out in
the jungle last night.
Oh, my head.
Welcome back.
Hey, John.
I found them.
After I left,
I hiked north,
back to where we were.
Hiked to the beach,
followed the shoreline.
A day later, I saw one.
What did he look like?
Dirty. Worn clothing,
no shoes. Simple--
just like the rest of them.
- Like the rest of them?
- Yeah.
His people, the others.
I followed him back to his camp.
They live in tents-- canvas
tents and teepees.
They eat dried fish.
They're worse off than we are.
- How many of them were there?
- I counted 22.
- And, uh, the boat...
- I didn't see it.
Did... did you see Walt?
No.
But I know he's there.
What about everyone
else they took?
Cindy? Did you see
any other kids?
No, no, no kids.
No, but I think they were in
the same place as my boy.
They have a hatch.
How do you know that they--
There's set of metal doors leading
underground. What else could it be?
And you think that that's
where they're keeping the kids?
They keep it guarded 24/7.
2 guards, 2 guns, and two guns is
all I saw. They're barely armed.
Most of them are old,
and half of them are women.
I wanted...
I couldn't save him.
So I came back to tell you...
tell you that we can take them.
As  soon as I get my strength back,
I will take us back there.
And we are gonna get
my boy back.
You were right.
Right about what?
About Henry.
What you and Sayid did to
him when you first found him.
You were...you were right.
I don't like how you did it,
but I shouldn't have
gotten in your way.
Well, you did what you thought was
right at the time you thought it, Jack.
I just hope the next time you decide
to do something, you include me.
And something tells me...
that's gonna be soon.
You heard Michael.
We can take them.
Our friend with the beard told
us not to cross the line.
These people are liars, John.
Why the hell should we take
their word on anything?
I couldn't agree more.
So...
now what?
Where are you going?
Get our guns back from Sawyer.
We're gonna need you
to help convince him.
Who's gonna take
care of Michael?
I'll stay. You guys go ahead.
- You sure?
- Give Sawyer my best.
All right. We'll be back soon.
Watch your head. Almost there.
You ever watch
"The Flintstones"?
Sure. I used to watch it all the
time when I was in the hospital...
when I... broke my hip.
Did you ever notice how Fred would run
by the same thing over and over again?
Third time past this tree.
Uh, that's a different tree.
Hurley, it's okay
if you're lost.
Dude, I'm not lost.
Will you trust me?
We're right about to walk onto the most
excellent secret beach on the island.
And... surprise!
Uh... Hurley?
This is our beach.
There's Jin.
Hey, I tell you what.
Why not have the picnic here?
Come on, give me the blankets.
Blankets?
You don't have any blankets?
How about drinks?
Okay, I tell you what.
I will handle the blankets.
You just track down
Rose and Bernard.
I saw them pull wine
from the pallet. Okay?
Oh. Wine.
Groovy.
Hey, maybe if I get drunk enough,
I'll remember where I know you from.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sawyer.
Put the book down.
It's not a book.
It's a manuscript.
I'm about to be the first and
only guy to find out who done it.
I think I got it figured out,
so cool your damn jets and
walk around the coconut trees.
I got, like,
ten pages left-- Hey!
Wanna figure it out?
Aah!
What the hell is
your problem, doc?
It's time to give
us the guns back.
You burn the ending
of my book and now--
- Where are they, James?
- You too, Brutus?
Just take us there, Sawyer, all right?
Quit playing around.
What, did you bring her
along for a sympathy vote?
She ain't in my head, doc.
So why don't you two just
go play in the jungle?
Take us to the guns. Now.
Oh, that bitch.
She stole my damn gun.
Ana Lucia.
- Why would she need a gun?
- Son of a bitch.
Jack...
I need to tell you something.
Pick it up.
Cut yourself loose.
What?
Just do it.
Why?
You know why.
He kept saying you
were misunderstood.
- What are you talking about?
- Goodwin.
Yes, he told us all
about you, Ana--
How he thought you were worthy
and that he could change you.
But he was wrong...
and it cost him his life.
He was gonna kill me.
Was he?
Are you done?
Yes, Ana, I'm done.
So this is it, huh?
Yes, Henry. This is it.
I want you to listen to me, okay?
Because I'm asking you a favor, Chrissy.
I'm standing in front of you in
the same suit that I'm
wearing to my father's funeral,
and I'm asking you a favor.
In 16 hours,
I need to land at L.A.X.,
And I need that coffin
to clear customs,
because there's going to
be a hearse waiting there.
And I need that hearse to take me
and that coffin to a cemetery. Why?
Chrissy, why can't I just
bring him to a funeral home
and make all the arrangements?
Why can't I really take my time with it?
Because... because I
need it to be done.
I need it to be over.
I just...
I need to bury my father.
That was an airplane.
No, I'm not at work.
I'm in Sydney.
That's right, Australia.
I...
I don't know, I...
I made a mistake, mom.
You knew, so I got as far
away from you as I could.
But now...
I want to come home, mom.
So come home.
- What flight are you on?
- I'm on Oceanic flight 815.
I'll be there when
you land, mija.
Where is everybody?
What you said got
'em worked up.
They went to get all the
guns back from Sawyer.
Sawyer.
Sawyer has all the guns.
Long story.
At least he didn't
get that one.
Yeah.
- Too bad I can't use it.
- Use it on what?
We caught one of them--
the others.
He's locked up in there.
- How long has he...
- Over a week.
And you're what,
taking care of him?
He tried to kill me today.
So I wanted him dead.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't even kill him.
I looked at him, and he...
I can't do this anymore.
Then let me do it.
They're animals.
I've seen these people,
and they are animals.
They took my son right out of my hands.
They took my son and...
I'll do it. Give me the gun.
I'll kill him.
'Cause that's what they'd do.
What's the combination?
18 right...
1 left...
31 right.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Michael?
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com