Isn't this nice?
I kind of... prefer breathing.
Come on, you're doing great.
You know, exercise is addictive.
Wow...
I can...
I can see why.
Guess I need to
drop a few pounds.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It's not going to happen overnight.
Some people's metabolisms
are just a little slower.
It's not my metabolism.
I'm sick.
What?
What's wrong?
Never mind.
Hurley!
You can trust me.
Okay.
But... it's bad.
When we first crashed here,
I thought this isn't all bad.
It's like the all-mango diet.
I wasn't turning any
heads or nothing,
but I did drop a
couple belt sizes.
Then we found this hatch,
and it was full of food...
tons of food.
I tried giving it
all away, but...
I guess I kinda kept
some of it for myself.
Wish I could just
get rid of it.
Then get rid of it.
You want to change?
Then change.
How do you feel?
Oh. I feel free.
They found something! Come on!
Hurry, guys.
Risotto. Nice.
No.
Where did this come from?
Locke said some kind of blast
doors trapped him in the hatch.
Maybe it was because of this.
So no one would see who dropped it.
Any of you guys see
a plane last night?
Yeah, I saw it, tattoo.
Just decided not to tell.
Hey, put that back, man.
Come on.
Oh, man, I saw it first.
You saw me put those in my box.
No! Give me my stuff!
Take it easy! You guys are like locusts.
How about a little order here?
Shouldn't we let someone a little bit
more trustworthy take care of this?
- Like you, baby-napper?
- No. Like Hurley.
Why not Hurley? He's done it before.
He can do it again.
No! No way!
Not me! No, not again! No!
Hey, hey, guys, guys.
How about no one's in charge, okay?
I'm sure everyone can manage
to just take what they need.
Great plan, moonbeam.
After that, we can sing
"kumbaya" and do trust falls.
We can do it any way you want.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Uh-oh.
Hey.
Whatcha doin'?
Nothin'.
Who were you looking
for out there?
No one.
When you ran off, it sort of seemed
like you were looking for someone.
- I tried to find you...
- I kinda...
don't want to talk about it.
Sure. Okay.
Pretty weird, huh?
You said the island won't
let you lose weight--
you destroy your stash,
then bang--
more food falls from the sky.
How about that.
I'm proud of you.
- Proud of me for what?
- Not freaking out.
How's the diet coming, Hugo?
Ah, it's okay.
I had a salad and some
chicken breast for lunch.
That's great.
It gets easier, I promise.
So, I heard you had a visit
with your mom. How did that go?
Good.
You're not still
mad at her, then?
Nah. I know she put me
in here for a reason.
What reason is that?
The accident.
You want to talk
about that today?
Do we have to?
Hugo, you've been in here
almost two months now.
Don't you think it's time to start
getting our hands dirty? Hmm?
Okay, why don't we,
uh, talk about the--
the homework assignment
that I gave you?
I was never really
good at homework.
You remember what you
were supposed to do?
Just make a list of things
that you like about yourself?
Nobody else did it.
Nobody else? Meaning?
Well, dave didn't do it.
He said it was a stupid idea.
Well, you know,
I'm not Dave's doctor, but
we have talked about how he can
be a very negative influence.
Dave's the most normal
person in this place, man.
But he doesn't want you to change,
does he?
Come on, give me the ball!
Give me the ball!
Dude, dude!
I'm open! Dude, dude!
It's called "dribbling."
Not "drooling," "dribbling."
Well, shoot it, then! Shoot it!
What-- oh, high percentage shot.
Excellent choice.
You want in the game, man?
Go for it.
Something tells me no one will care.
What's the matter with you?
Nothin'.
Dude, dude, give up the rock!
Fantastic. Give it to the guy
who's not even in the game!
Hey, it's taco night, dude.
Let's blow this pop stand.
What?
Brooks said...
you're, like, negative.
Well, duh!
So, what, you don't want to
hang out with me anymore?
No, I don't know. It's just--
is that quack getting inside your head,
man? Do not let him!
You got much more important
things to think about.
Like what?
Like hard or soft shell, baby?
Chicken or shrimp?
Sour cream or hot sauce?
Yeah, I guess I could eat.
Yeah, I thought so.
Noche de tacos, amigo.
Good. Now,
can you do the other one?
Is it broken?
Without an x-ray, you're gonna
have to do with my best guess.
Sorry.
How you holding up?
Depends on Jack's best guess.
There's a small fracture,
probably a hairline.
This will keep the swelling down
until I can get the splint on it.
How long until I
can walk on it?
You're gonna have to keep
off it a couple of weeks.
There's a wheelchair
back at camp--
No!
I don't need a wheelchair.
We took a pair of crutches from the
fuselage when we moved down the beach.
Okay.
Be back in a while.
He could've escaped.
- Sorry?
- Henry.
During the lockdown.
I was hurt.
He could have escaped...
but he-- he came back to help me.
Why would he do that?
He didn't come back
to help you, John.
He came back because he thought
his story was gonna check out.
He was dead already.
Four months ago,
I was part of the search party.
Henry Gale was hanging out
of the basket, neck broken.
So he was already dead.
Yes.
And then you buried him
and left a grave marker.
Yes.
You really should have checked
his wallet before you did that.
I assume Henry Gale did not have any
paper on which to compose his thoughts.
So he had to improvise.
There wasn't much
space for that.
"Jennifer...
Well, you were right.
Crossing the Pacific isn't easy.
I owe you a beer.
I'm hiking to one of the
beaches to start a signal fire.
But if you're reading this,
I guess I didn't make it.
I'm sorry. I love you, Jenny.
Always have, always will.
Yours, Henry."
So, tell me...
how did Henry Gale write a note
to his wife with a broken neck?
Wasn't me. I didn't kill him.
You don't understand--
How did you know his wife's name?
Did you interrogate him?
Please, just listen.
I'm just a--
How many of you are there?
If I told you about them,
you have no idea what he'll do.
He?
You mean their leader?
The guy with the beard?
Him?! He's no one. Nothing!
Where are your people?
- I can't...
- How many of you are there?
- You don't understand!
- Understand this.
Hey.
You have three seconds
to answer my question.
How many of you are there? One.
- He'll kill me!
- I'll kill you!
- Two.
- Sayid!
You can't do this!
I am not a bad person!
Three.
What the hell's wrong with you?
What's going on?!
I heard a gunshot!
- What happened?
- He's a liar!
It's fine.
Just get him out of here.
Jack!
- Jack!
- I've got it covered, John.
Thank you.
Shut up.
Hey.
I noticed you were
building something.
I thought maybe you could
use this for whatever it is.
That is very thoughtful
of you, Charlie.
Why don't you help me?
What are you making?
Hold that end.
Is it a Starbucks?
Help me carry one of
those loads, please.
You gonna tell me?
Not right now.
You're not here!
Hey! Wait!
Wait!
Wait! Dave!
You okay, Hurley?
Did either of you see
a guy run through here?
In a bathrobe?
With a coconut?
No. Saw a polar bear on
rollerblades with a mango.
I did not see anything, Hurley.
Yeah. Me neither.
- 4. 8. 15 .16. 23. 42.
- Oh, dude.
Pretty sneaky, Leonard.
You're using those magic numbers of
yours as a psych-out, aren't you, man?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You just play dumb.
- I'm on to your juju, man.
- They're just numbers, dude.
- What the hell is that?
- My midafternoon snack.
Dude, that's celery.
Celery's not a snack.
Leonard's got graham crackers, man.
You should snag one.
He won't notice.
What's he gonna do,
call you a "23"?
Four... hike!
15, 16, 23, 42... Hike.
Okay, Hugo, here's your meds.
Hmm. Thank you, nurse Lazenby.
Dude, you wanna get
out of here with me?
Don't take the
horse tranquilizer.
What do you mean,
get out of here?
I mean escape, man.
Me and you, A.S.A.P.
They're getting to you, dude.
We gotta split.
Dr. Brooks says--
Dr. Brooks does not
care about you, man.
He's the one
prescribing that crap.
- What the hell is it, anyway?
- Clonazepam.
Hugo? Something wrong
with your meds there?
No, uh... me and dave were just,
you know, talking about stuff.
Right, well,
sorry to interrupt.
Hello there, Dave.
Hello there, Dr. Brooks.
- And how are you today?
- Never been saner.
I've been taking some pictures
for the bulletin board.
I've got everyone except you two.
Uh, would you guys mind?
Okay.
Why don't you get a
little closer together?
Are you gonna make us
look at the ducky, too?
Say "cheese".
- "Cheese".
- "Queso."
Great.
Okay, you need a little
water with that?
Nope, I'm good.
Okay. Well, fine. See you later, guys.
Thanks for the photo op.
Dude...
Dude.
The revolution has begun, man.
Lay low.
When the time is right, we fly.
You gotta twist it...
To get the frosting.
Pulling it will only break your cookie.
Well, that's what I get for not going
to the expert in the first place.
What can I do you for,
deep dish?
Uh... I'm kinda
looking for something.
Forget it. I'm done trading.
I've got enough food now to
open a chain of mini-marts.
Hey, you think
Sayid needs a job?
Well, actually... I was sort
of hoping you'd do me a favor.
Remember when I helped you
out with that tree frog...
which you killed?
Yeah, I remember.
Well, I sorta...
need some medicine.
What do you need?
- It's called clonazepam.
- Clonaze-what?
What the hell's that?
So you can calm down for...
for when... you're seeing things...
that... aren't
supposed to be there.
What stuff you seeing?
I don't know...
maybe like a bald guy in a bathrobe.
You mean like that guy there?
Gotcha.
You think you're funny?
What the hell are you doing?
Get off me!
Who the hell do
you think you are?!
Get off me!
Let go off me, mutton chops!
Pork rinds!
Babar! Jabba! Stay-puft?!
Lardo! Kong! Deep dish!
Get him off me!
Get off me!
The hell's the matter with you?!
What the hell's the
matter with you?!
You're crazy!
I'm not crazy.
So he just attacked you, huh?
Try to contain
yourself, freckles.
What? I'm worried.
You look like you got your ass kicked.
Don't you got an
adventure to get to?
I think Timmy fell down
a well over that way.
Seriously, though, why'd he--
I got no idea. I didn't do nothin'.
He just hulked out on me.
For no reason at all.
Okay. You walk off and have
yourself a nice, long giggle.
But steer clear.
The man is crazy.
Hurley?
Hey. You okay?
What happened with Sawyer?
I don't want to talk about it.
So... you beat him up?
Guess you know what
happened, then.
I'm on your side.
Whatever you tell me--
Look, I don't want
to talk, okay?
What?
It's a lot of peanut butter.
Well, I'm gonna need a lot
of protein where I'm going.
- Where are you going?
- Back to the caves.
No one lives there anymore,
so I won't bother anybody.
See, I'll live alone and
be one of those guys.
You know, the crazy guys,
with the big beard and no clothes,
who's naked and throws doody at people.
Hurley, you don't
have to do this!
Just leave me alone!
You can't help me.
No one can.
You're not here!
You were in the hospital.
You can't be here.
Sorry, dude. I am here.
"I like that I have a good
relationship with my mom.
I like making my
grandpa Tito laugh.
I like chicken."
No, that last one
wasn't about you, Hugo.
I like that I like chicken?
So, uh, tell me...
how did it feel, writing that?
Was that difficult?
Kinda. I think I messed
up some spelling.
Well, I notice you didn't say
anything about the way you look.
Are you...
comfortable with your appearance?
It's not like...
I mean, I can't really do
anything about it, right?
If I, uh...
if I...
wasn't so fat...
they never would have died.
There were 23 people on that deck.
It was built to hold eight...
and it would have collapsed
whether you went out there or not.
Yeah, but I did walk out there,
and it did collapse.
I killed them.
- It was an accident.
- It was my fault.
But after those people died,
you were in a practically
catatonic state.
You stopped talking, you stopped
going out, you stopped sleeping.
But you never stopped eating.
Because that's how
you punish yourself.
Dave's right about you.
You're nothing but a quack.
Dave doesn't want you to lose weight,
does he?
You know, Dave cares about me.
He's my friend.
Okay. Let me show
you something.
It may upset you.
This is the photo that I
took for the bulletin board.
Dave isn't your friend, Hugo.
Because dave doesn't exist.
Psst! Hey, wake up, dude.
Finally. You could sleep
through a damn Nascar race, man.
Man, you're not... you're...
you're a hallucination.
Ow.
Was that a hallucination?
Maybe I just imagined
you slapped me.
Ow! Damn it!
We can do this all night.
Dr. Brooks showed me a
picture from the rec room.
My arm was around,
like, nothingness.
Uh, Kinko's? Photoshop?
What, do you think they really
blew up the "Death Star"?
No.
Then stop talking crazy, man.
Come on, we're on a clock here.
Hey, you in or you out, dude?
Okay, come on, come on.
Yo, check it out.
Marcus didn't finish his lasagna.
That is a waste, man.
One for the road?
Shh!
Wait for it. Wait...
Tiptoes, big guy. Vamanos.
Okay, man.
You got the keys, hombre.
You took them off
Brooks' desk earlier.
Hee hee hee hee!
Come on, man. Open it, open it.
Oh, oh, oh...
can you taste that?
That is freedom, baby.
You know what tastes even
better than freedom?
Cheeseburgers. Ha ha ha ha!
Come on, man!
Chili fries on me.
I don't think I can do this.
I'm sorry.
Sorry? What,
are you kidding me?
You're not real.
You're trying to get me to run away
and get cheeseburgers because...
I want cheeseburgers.
Did you take those pills, man?
No, man. I'm just not coming.
Look, you don't want me to get better.
You don't want me to change.
you don't need to change, man.
You are fine. You're great.
No, I'm not.
You just want me to stay fat.
You don't want me
to get better.
You wouldn't care if
I ate myself to death.
Do not do this, man.
If you don't come with me right now,
you will never get outta here.
Bye, Dave.
You wouldn't happen to have my slipper,
would you?
Thank you.
Oh, man!
You got peanut butter on it.
Okay, look...
I know you're freaking out right now,
and I'm sorry. But
it's gonna get a little
worse before it gets better.
- Worse?
- Yeah... kinda.
You ready, dude?
You remember that night you
closed that window on me?
You remember what you
did after that night?
Yeah.
I realized you were imaginary.
Mm-hmm.
And... that was a breakthrough.
And a little while later,
Brooks let me out
and I went home to
live with my mom,
and I got my job with Mr.
Cluck's back, and I got better.
Okay, good. Great. Yeah.
Except, see, here's the thing... uh...
None of that ever happened.
What?
You're still at
Santa Rosa, man.
You never left the hospital.
That's... not possible.
It's hard, I know. But, I mean,
all this? You? Me? This island?
That peanut butter--
none of it's real, man.
None of it's happening.
It's all in your head,
my friend.
The second you closed that window,
your brain popped a gasket.
You went back into your
little coma thing,
and that's where you are
right this very second--
in your own private Idaho,
inside Santa Rosa.
No.
I had... my mom...
my friend Johnny... I won the lottery!
Whoa, wow! Awesome, dude!
What numbers did you play?
Leonard's numbers, right?
From the hospital?
What a coincidence.
You, uh...
seen him around anywhere else?
- The hatch.
- Bingo!
The hatch,
with a button that you gotta push
every 108 minutes,
or the world ends.
Oh, oh, oh, and-- and what's the
code for the button? Oh, yeah.
The numbers.
But I got better.
- I changed.
- Changed?
What, are you kidding me?
Take a look at yourself.
You've been on a deserted
island for over two months,
and you haven't dropped 10 pounds.
How is that even possible, man?
I just destroyed my stash,
and I've been exercising.
Libby says it won't happen overnight--
Oh, right, right, Libby.
The mega-cute blonde chick
who magically appeared from
the other side of the island.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah. And who just
happens to have the hots... for you!
Come on, man.
Let's take a walk.
So this is all in my brain?
Every rock, every tree.
Every tree frog. Even me.
The real me,
the one they told you was imaginary--
he went out that window, man.
Right now he's probably bouncing
from hot chick to hot chick.
Unlike me, who's really you,
who's got more
important things to do.
- So I'm making you up.
- Well, sorta.
I'm part of your
subconscious, man.
All the people on
this island are.
What part of me are you?
I'm the part of you that
wants to wake up, man.
Follow me.
This is it, dude.
It?
The big finale!
The answer to all
your problems.
A way for you to wake up,
snap out of it.
I don't want to kill myself.
Who said anything about
killing yourself, man?
This is gonna bring
you back to life.
The only way for
you to bust out
is to tell your mind that you
don't believe any of this.
So... if I...
all this'll be gone?
- I'll just wake up?
- That's right.
Now when you do wake up, come find me.
I'm sure I miss you.
See you in another
life, Hurley.
Dave!
Ha ha ha ha!
Jack not back yet?
Nope. He's telling everyone at the
beach that we've got one of them.
Something tells me people have a lot
of questions about our houseguest.
I want to talk to him.
I don't think that's
on today's program.
Well, all due respect, Ana Lucia,
but I don't care what you think.
Five minutes.
I earned five minutes with him.
What's your name?
Your real name?
Why don't you just...
keep calling me Henry?
You've gotten used to it.
Did you get caught on purpose?
You and your people have been
here for God knows how long,
- and you got caught in a net--
- God doesn't know.
Excuse me?
God doesn't know how long
we've been here, John.
He can't see this island any better
than the rest of the world can.
May I ask you a question?
What possible reason could I have...
for putting myself through all this?
Maybe your people were
looking for this place.
This place?
This place is a joke, John.
What are you talking about?
I crawled through your vents,
and I stood at your computer
as your alarm beeped.
And you know what happened?
The timer went all
the way down to zero.
And then some funny red pictures
flipped up in its place.
They looked like hieroglyphics,
but I'm no expert.
And then things got
real interesting.
There was a loud...
clunking and a hum like a...
magnet-- a big magnet.
It was really very frightening.
And do you know
what happened next?
Nothing happened, John.
Nothing happened at all.
Your timer just
flipped back to 108.
I never entered the numbers.
I never pressed the button.
You're lying.
No, I'm done lying.
Dave!
Who's Dave?
- What are you doing here?
How'd you know where I was?
Jin saw you while
he was fishing.
Ha!
Jin doesn't speak English.
Sun was with him.
She translated.
Hurley, what is going on?
No! You're just the part
of me that's scared.
You don't want me to wake up.
Well, guess what.
I'm not scared.
Okay. Okay, Hurley...
You're having some sort of panic attack.
I get that.
But this isn't like you.
Like me? You don't know me.
I was starting to.
Yeah, well, did you know I'm so
fat that I killed two people?
And that I have an
imaginary friend?
Hurley, please.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
No, I'm not!
Because this isn't happening.
None of it!
I'm just imagining it.
This isn't real life.
Why would you say that?
Because in real life...
no girl like you
would ever like me.
You remember when I said
I knew you from somewhere?
Well, maybe it's
'cause I made you up.
What was the man's name
who broke his leg?
The day of the crash,
on the other side of the island?
Eko brought a man with a
broken leg to me for help.
What was his name?
I... don't know.
You don't know. You know why?
Because it happened to me.
His name was Donald,
and I buried him.
I buried a lot of
people, Hurley.
So don't tell me that
that wasn't real.
And don't tell me...
you made me up.
It's insulting.
When you saw me on the
beach this morning...
was I holding a slipper?
Not that I can remember, no.
Hurley... look at me.
I am real.
You're real.
The way I feel about you...
that's real.
And that...
was real.
Maybe you should do
it one more time...
just to be sure.
Ready to go back?
Do you really think I can...
you know... change?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Why don't you get a
little closer together?
- Say "cheese".
- "Cheese".
Great.
Do you need, uh,
some water to go with that?
- Nope, I'm good.
- Okay. Well, fine.
See you later, guys.
Thanks for the photo op.
Here's your pill, Libby.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com