Previously on "Lost"...
The plane was
loaded with heroin.
- He said he found it in the jungle.
- Where in the jungle?
- It's just a statue.
- Just a statue?
Where is Charlie?
What's this?
Because this was in
your little statue.
I didn't know.
Look, if it's sealed up inside a statue,
how would I know?
- You lied to me, Charlie.
- I'm sorry.
Look, I can't have you
around my baby, okay?
Claire--
Charlie, I don't want you
sleeping anywhere near us, okay?
Voltron! Whoa!
Where are my presents?
Right over here, Charlie.
It's a piano!
This is mine?!
Yes, Charlie.
Father Christmas must have
known how talented you are.
You're special, love.
Someday you're gonna get us outta here,
all of us.
Now...
go on, play us a tune.
Come on, baby brother.
You can't save your
family if you don't play.
Come on, Charlie.
Play. Play me a tune.
Come on, now. Let's hear it.
He ain't savin' no one,
he is. Music...
Music will never get you anywhere,
Charlie boy.
- You need a trade.
- Dad?
Do it, baby bro. Save us.
Save us, Charlie. Save us.
Aaron?
Aaron!
It's okay, Aaron.
It's all right.
Aaron!
Sun. Hey, Sun!
Have you seen Claire and the baby?
They're gone.
They're right over there.
- Is Aaron okay?
- Yes, he's fine. Charlie!
It's okay.
Hey.
I made Aaron some
nappies this morning.
I'll just put those there.
Thanks.
Has he been asking about me?
Charlie, don't.
I'm sorry.
I should have told
you about the statue
and what was in it.
I just wish things could get back
to the way they were before.
There is no "before", Charlie.
We were strangers on a plane,
and we became friends.
Now Locke's your friend, huh?
Please, Charlie, just for now,
give me some space, okay?
Yeah. Space.
See ya, mate.
Take care of your
mum now, okay?
- Charlie?
- Hey.
- Hey. Hi.
What are you doin' up?
You should be laying down.
I just needed to see her again.
Isn't she brilliant?
She's beautiful, Karen.
I named her Megan.
Where's Liam?
He's not here.
Karen, look,
it wasn't his fault.
We were leaving the club in dresden.
I was in a cab.
He was in a van with the gear,
and he blew a tire on
the way to the airport.
He missed his flight,
but he's on the next plane, all right?
He'll be here soon.
But he's okay?
He's great. He's a dad.
Yeah.
Oh, for the...
Liam...
Unbelievable.
Liam?
Liam, wake up! Hey!
What the hell's wrong with you?
What the hell are you doing?
Hi, baby brother.
You're supposed to be cleaning up.
Get up.
I told Karen you
missed your flight.
She's all alone at the hospital,
and you're here fixin'.
- What's the matter with you?
- I'm cool, I'm cool, I'm cool.
I just needed to get right,
that's all.
Don't  worry. I left you some.
"Get right"?
Why don't you get up?
Take a shower, get dressed,
get to the hospital?
All right, all right, I'm on it.
I'm on it.
Oh, by the way,
you have a daughter.
Her name is Megan.
After mum?
Yeah, after mum.
Now clean yourself up.
You're a sodding father now.
Easy. That's good.
That was good.
Okay, one more.
Uh, Sawyer, when you were
over there across the island,
how well did you get
to know those tailies?
Well enough, why?
That Libby chick
seems pretty cool.
I mean, is she?
Whoa, you got a little love
connection brewin' over there, Jabba?
- No, just askin'.
- Yeah, I hear you askin'.
Forget it.
What's with you? You're acting
like you're in junior high.
Well, what do we have here?
Looks like Ana Lucia's
gettin' the $20 tour.
That's  the third time I've seen
'em walkin' out of the jungle.
What do you suppose
they're doin' out there?
Why don't you just do
your exercises, Sawyer?
Oh, bloody hell.
Hey!
Hey! The baby!
Help!
The baby!
Aaron!
I'm coming! I'm coming, Aaron!
It's okay.
You're safe now.
I got you. It's all right.
It's okay. You're okay now.
You're safe. You're safe.
There you go. It's okay.
Mum?
C laire?
He's in danger.
You have to save him.
The baby's in danger. You have to
save the baby. You have to save him.
The baby is in danger.
The baby, Charlie. You have to save him.
Charlie, only you can save him.
You have to save him.
Charlie?
What are you doing?
What?
What are you doing, man?
What's goin' on?
It's the middle of the night.
What are you doing with the baby?
I don't know.
Help! Somebody stole my baby!
- Claire, what's wrong?
- I don't know! Aaron's gone!
It's okay! We're over here!
Is he all right?!
- Is he okay?!
- Claire...
I don't know what happened.
I'm sorry.
He's okay, though.
I had this dream--
Stick?
I don't know, dude. Don't you need 21?
I think you should hit.
But I got a six.
I'm gonna bust.
How do you know that?
Well, I don't, but you gotta
assume that I'm gonna bust.
Why?
Well, well,
look who's off to the laundromat.
Well, go on.
I'm sure you've got a load you need
to drop in, don't you, Jethro?
I'm kind of waitin'
for my moment.
Well...
your moment is now, Hoss.
Hey, Libby!
Hey, yourself.
Hey, John.
Talk to you for a second?
Yeah. What is it, Charlie?
I take it you heard about
what happened last night?
If you mean you taking the baby out of
Claire's tent in the middle of
the night,
yeah, I heard.
This whole thing was a big
misunderstanding, John. I
was sleepwalking.
I don't know how or why--
Is there something you
want from me, Charlie?
I was hoping you could
speak to Claire for me,
you know, put in a good word.
- Are you using?
- What?
Heroin. Are you using again?
Kate sees a horse-- nothing.
Pretty much everybody's seen
Walt wandering round the jungle.
But when it's Charlie,
it must be the bloody drugs, right?
It's funny,
you didn't answer the question.
You remember the plane, John?
We burned it, Eko and me.
We burned the whole thing-- the heroin,
the statues. It's all gone, destroyed.
- All of them?
- All of them.
Trust is a hard
thing to win back.
Claire needs time.
You should leave her and
the baby alone for a while.
Can you do this?
You look green.
Sod off. I'm fine.
All right,
let's give this another go, shall we?
Well, get it together, all right?
Lest you forget, we need this.
Tea? So you lads ready?
Yeah, we're ready. Let's go.
Let's try not to blow
it this time, eh?
Thank you.
- You good?
- Yeah.
We've only 20 minutes till we're
in overtime. Now get it right.
All right...
Camera...
Rotate on the 8-count.
Hold the product up.
"Butties diapers, take 53.."
Playback.
And action!
Cut!
It's all right.
That's it. We're wrapped!
Wait, no!
Oi, mate, hang on! Wait.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Let's not waste any more time,
shall we?
You were only hired as
a favor to your lawyer.
I wanted Dirt Spigot.
Come on, mate.
Give us another chance.
You want another chance?
Take my advice--
ditch that one.
He's a bloody disaster.
I'm not ditchin' anyone.
He's my brother.
Right. Well, then,
I guess you're fired.
Is this washer and dryer newer
than everything else in here?
It washes clothes.
That's all I need to know.
Ah, finally.
Someone who keeps it simple.
Oh, hey, look at this.
I got it in some of
the abandoned luggage.
You think I can pull this off?
Let me give you a hint-- uh,
when a girl asks that kind of question,
she's looking for validation.
Do I...
know you from somewhere?
You mean other than the flight?
Flight...
- Okay, turn around.
- Huh?
Turn around. I wanna try it on.
Turn around.
Oh. Oh, sure, yeah. Go ahead.
No peeking.
I cannot believe you don't
remember stepping on my foot.
I did?
Yes, you did, and it was hard.
I know that because I remember you
were the last one on the flight,
and you were all sweaty,
and you had headphones on and...
crunch! You stepped on my foot.
Okay, turn around.
- What do you think?
- It's awesome.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
I'm marking trees.
Why?
'Cause these...
are the ones I like.
Did you tell Locke you gave me
one of the statues from the plane?
Why would I do that?
He knows, man.
The bald wanker
knows something.
Something wrong, Charlie?
Apart from me losing my mind,
no, everything's just peachy.
And why would you say
you are losing your mind?
How about the fact that
I've been sleepwalking,
stealin' babies
from their cribs...
Oh, yeah,
and then there's the vivid dreams
that make me feel like I'm
completely awake until of course,
I wake up.
What are your dreams about?
Variations  of Aaron
being in mortal peril...
trapped in a piano,
driftin' out to sea...
and there's the flying dove and
Claire and my mom dressed as angels
tellin' me I need
to save the baby.
What?
Have you considered that
these dreams mean something?
Like what?
What if you do need
to save the baby?
I have to talk to her.
You know,
now's not a good time, okay?
No, I have to talk to her.
She'll want to hear this.
Okay, you know what?
Tell me, and I will tell her.
Kate-- no, no! Claire!
Claire, listen to me.
Aaron's in danger.
- What are you talking about?
- The baby's in danger!
Look,  I've been having these dreams.
I know what they mean now.
- Charlie--
- Kate!
Claire, listen,
we have to baptize Aaron.
What?
We can do this.
Eko's a priest. We can do this.
You've said your piece.
It's time for you to go.
No, wait! I'm not leaving.
Claire, we have to baptize Aaron!
Claire, he's in danger.
We've got to do this! We have to!
Here. For when it rains.
Thanks.
So when are you gonna tell me
what happened in the jungle?
I already did.
Pull it tighter or it'll sag.
You told me what that guy said.
You didn't tell me what
made you turn around,
what made you come back.
He had a gun at Kate's head.
You hittin' that?
What?
Plane crash...
you both survived...
nice beach...
she's hot, you're hot.
It's what people do.
I'm not "hittin' that."
Hey.
Karen kicked me out, man.
What?
What happened?
She, uh...
she thinks I'm dangerous.
Why would she think that?
Because I dropped her.
I dropped Megan.
Oh.
Hey, Liam.
It's all right.
I've got no money, got nothin'.
What are we gonna do?
- We'll get through this.
- Yeah? How's that?
I'm writin' again.
I got a new song.
It's about two brothers.
Two  brothers who
should've been butchers.
Don't say that.
It's a good one.
I feel like this
might be the one.
All right,
listen to this, okay?
Nice, man.
This could work.
- It's good, right?
- We could make it work.
Write all night,
just like the old days.
- All right.
- How about that?
So, baby brother...
do you got any?
I'm disappointed
in you, Charlie.
You followed me?
How long you been
comin' out here?
John, you got the
wrong idea, man.
You said you destroyed them all, and
yet, here they are. How is that the
wrong idea?
I came out here to
finish the job.
I'm gonna get rid
of these right now.
Yeah, that's very convenient
now that I've found them.
What are you doing?
There was a time when I let
you choose whether or not
you were gonna do
this to yourself.
Now I'm making that
choice for you.
Oh, you don't believe me?
Give 'em to me.
Give 'em to me right now.
I'll destroy 'em. Look!
I'll throw 'em in
the sodding wind!
Look, John,
I know I lied, all right?
Just wait. Wait, wait, John.
Remember all those
talks we had?
You and me,
we said everything happens for a reason.
This island tests us.
That's what this is, John--
A test. This is my test.
That's why these are here.
These are here because
you put 'em here, Charlie.
No, wait. John, wait.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna tell Claire?
You can't.
Look, if she sees them, I'm done.
She'll never trust me again,
and she has to, John.
It's about the baby, all right?
Aaron's in danger.
You have to believe me.
You've given up the right
to be believed, Charlie.
Hey.
Hi. How's our boy?
Oh, he's good.
Hey, John,
can I ask you something?
Sure.
Do you think, uh,
Aaron and I could stay in the
bedroom in the hatch for a while?
Pretty loud alarm goes
off every hour and a half.
It's not the best place for a
baby to sleep through the night.
Oh, yeah, sure.
How about if I move my stuff
down here for a couple nights?
Set up right next to your tent?
That would be great. Thanks.
Yeah, consider it done.
Hey, John, you don't...
you don't know anything about baptism,
do you?
Not a whole lot. Why?
Charlie came by my
tent before and...
he told me Aaron had
to be baptized...
that he was in danger.
My understanding is that baptism is
about making sure that children get
into heaven,
should anything happen.
Call it "spiritual insurance."
There isn't any danger, Claire.
Charlie just...
Charlie just feels like
he has to save the baby
'cause he can't save himself.
- I'll see you tonight.
- Okay.
Charlie, can you
give us a hand?
Now's not a good time, Sayid.
Let's lift this.
Okay, I got it.
Fire! Fire!
Grab tools, containers for sand,
anything you have.
If we don't stop it now,
it'll burn right through the camp!
Stay here with Aaron.
We need to cut a fire break right here!
Form a bucket line!
Some of you people,
down to the water!
Sawyer!
We'll hand 'em up. Wait here!
Liam?!
My piano.
What's... what's going on?
Liam, where's my piano?
- I sold it.
- You what?
- Hey, wait, come on.
- Get off of me.
Where's the money?
Is it up your soddin' arm?!
I'm clean.
I haven't used in two days.
Two days?
Well, happy anniversary!
Well, how long you been clean?
Where's the money?
She was gonna leave me, Charlie.
She was gonna take Megan.
What did you do, Liam?
Karen's got an
uncle in Australia.
He's gonna get me a job.
There's a rehab clinic in Sydney.
I just needed the
money to get us there.
I have to do this.
I have to take care of myself,
for them, for my family.
I'm your family!
- Wait. Will you just wait?
- I can't, Charlie.
What about the band?
What about the song?
Try to understand,
I have to go.
I have to.
Look, I'll give you a call when
things settle down for me.
For you? What about me?
What about my family?
What about my family?!
Charlie! What are you doing?!
I'm doing what I have to do!
- He's got my baby! Stop it!
- No! Claire, it's all right!
- Charlie, stop!
- It's not... no! I...
Help! Help! Somebody help!
He's got my baby! Help! Help!
Come on, Charlie,
please, stop it.
I just want to save him!
Charlie! It's all right.
Give me the baby.
Eko, tell them! Tell them, Eko!
Tell them what you told me,
that the baby has to be baptized!
This is not the way.
Charlie... come on,
give him to me.
Who the hell are you, John?!
Aaron's not
your responsibility!
Where were you
when he was born?!
Where were you when
he was taken?!
You're not his father.
You're not his family!
Neither are you, Charlie.
I have to do this, I need to.
I'm not gonna hurt him.
You're hurting me, Charlie.
Claire.
I'm sorry--
You need stitches.
- Try to be still.
- Yeah.
I started the fire, Jack.
Yeah, I know.
I was desperate. She didn't--
I need to know you're never gonna
do anything like this again, ever.
I know what this looks like,
what people think.
It doesn't matter now, but...
I didn't use.
I wanted to.
I really wanted to.
But I didn't.
That's not what
I asked, Charlie.
It's not gonna happen again.
Charlie told me
you're a priest.
Yes.
He said that you told
him that I had to have--
I did not tell Charlie
to do what he did.
I'm sorry if he misunderstood.
But do you think the
baby has to be baptized?
Do you know what baptism is?
It's what gets you into heaven.
It is said that when John
the Baptist baptized Jesus,
the skies opened up,
and a dove flew down from the sky.
This told John something--
that he had cleansed this
man of all his sins,
that he had freed him.
Heaven came much later.
I haven't been baptized.
And does that mean that if
you do it to Aaron, and
something happened to us,
that we wouldn't be together?
Not if I baptize you both.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com