Previously on "Lost"...
Right here, there's a line.
You cross that line,
we go from misunderstanding to...
something else.
- What do I do?
- That button has to be pushed.
I never entered the numbers.
I never pressed the button.
- You're lying.
- No, I'm done lying.
It's a parachute.
All right.
Cereal goes on the left, Bernard.
So this isn't
bothering you at all?
What's "this"?
Well, this.
This.
Why is a bag of potato
chips gonna bother me?
Well, aren't you remotely curious
as to where all this came from?
You're acting like we just
got back from the supermarket.
Well, I guess I was raised
never to question my blessings.
I was raised to
question piles of food
with weird labels that just
fall out of the sky, Rose.
Well, honey,
just because you're having a bad day,
doesn't mean you have
to raise your voice.
Bad day? I've had seven weeks of bad
days on the other side of the island,
just trying to stay alive so I
could get back to you. But here...
my god, Rose,
they've built a kitchen on the beach.
They've given up.
Given up? On what?
On getting rescued.
Hey.
You gonna get that?
When's the last time
you went in to see him?
A couple hours ago.
He was sleeping.
Did he eat?
Nope.
That's two days now.
No food, no water...
nothing to say.
I don't know about you,
but I'm tired of waiting.
I hear you've lost
your appetite.
Okay, don't talk.
I was never that good at
bedside manner anyway.
I'm gonna change that dressing on
your shoulder. If you try anything,
we've got a problem.
So, Henry...
"Henry."
I was thinking about
something you were saying
before we found
out who you are.
This is gonna sting.
Yeah. You were saying that
if you were one of them,
that you'd lead
us into a trap...
capture our people...
force a trade.
Us, for you.
Pretty good idea, Henry.
And since you are one of them,
I thought now might be
a good time to use it.
I'm going out to the line that
we're not supposed to cross
and telling them
that we've got you.
And if they want you back,
it'll cost 'em.
And when we get Walt back...
You might just have been
worth all the trouble.
Did you say something?
They'll never give you Walt.
Don't gun it.
You're digging yourself in.
Just tap the gas lightly.
All due respect, I have been
driving in snow my whole life.
- You mind stepping back?
- Well, you have to rock it out.
You're not gonna be able to--
I'm calling triple "A".
Why, so they can send a tow truck?
Trust me, I can do this.
Okay. Ease on the gas.
That's it. You're doing great.
Almost.
Go, go, go-- Oh!
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah. Sure. I'm fine.
You know,
I would have gotten it out eventually.
Oh, sure.
July's right around the corner.
Well, um,
thanks for helping me.
Sure.
By the way, I'm Rose.
- Oh, uh, Bernard.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Oh. Okay. Yeah.
Okay.
- Drive safe, now, okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah. You, too.
- Um... uh, Bernard!
- Yeah?
Can I buy you a cup of coffee?
Uh, coffee would be nice.
Yeah. Okay.
I had to beat back half the group
to get these. I saved 'em for you.
No way. I'm on a new diet.
Nothing but fish and water...
and... fish and water.
Hurley, what are
you doing right now?
Uh... talking to your wife?
Good.  Can you get Libby
and meet me at the edge of
the tree line in five minutes?
Oh, and if you can
get Jin and Sun,
Jenkins and that frogurt guy,
the guy who used to make frozen yogurt.
Neil?
Yeah. And Craig and
anybody else you can get.
Bernard, what are you up to?
I got an idea.
Hey, Richard. Craig, Ralph, come here.
I've got a great idea.
I'm not so sure trading
people's their thing.
Well, talking to him
is getting us nowhere.
So, maybe we can get
something for him.
You want me to come with you?
You need to stay here.
You need it more than I do.
Do yourself a favor, man.
Don't go out there alone.
All right.
Ha ha. That's how it's done.
Oh, well look at you.
What, that's, like,
four in the last half hour?
Let me call the Guinness book.
You wanna help or not? 'Cause I got
better things to do with my time.
Oh,  happy day.
Here comes Dr. Giggles.
- Hey.
- Hey yourself.
I'm going back out into the jungle to
talk to our friend with the beard.
See if we can make a trade.
Ah, the old prisoner exchange.
And you're inviting me along
'cause you want a gun, huh?
I'm not inviting you.
I'm inviting Kate.
And I've already got a gun,
but thanks for offering.
How in the hell
did you get a gun?
Does it matter?
I'll get my things.
Okay. Two months we've been on
this island, right? Two months.
And already we have a water trough,
and we've got a food pantry,
and people are taking
showers in your... hatch.
Have you forgotten that we
all crashed on this island?
It's like none of you
want to go home again.
How can you say that?
Of course we want to go home.
Then why aren't we
doing anything about it?
Dude, we, like, built a raft...
that got blown up.
Okay.
So what are we doing now?
That pallet of food
had a parachute,
which means a plane
dropped it here,
which means that there are other
planes that fly over the island.
So, we are gonna build a sign.
A massive sign along the beach.
So that way,
if a plane flies over,
or a satellite takes
pictures from up there,
we want to make damn sure
that they know we're here,
that they know about us.
Maybe we should speak to
Jack about this first.
Well, do we have to
run everything by Jack?
I mean, he's not the president.
He's a doctor.
You're a dentist.
Ahem. Uh,
could I speak to you for just a second?
Come on.
Honey, it is just a sign.
I don't see what the harm is.
The harm is, you are telling
these people about airplanes
and satellites coming out
of nowhere to save the day.
I'm just trying
to do something.
I want to get back to our life.
Well, the only thing you are doing
is giving these people false hope.
Excuse me.
I have a sign to build.
Ahem. All right. Um, uh,
I wanna get this going right away.
We've waited long enough.
It's just amazing, isn't it?
Oh, sure, it's beautiful.
- You're not impressed, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
So, what does God have to
do to get your attention?
Bernard... what are you doing?
Rose...
I've been a bachelor
for 56 years.
And then I met you, and...
we just fell into this rhythm like
we had known each other forever.
I had always dreamed of
finding somebody like you,
but I'd given up hope
that I ever would.
Bernard...
Oh, I know, I know. It's crazy.
Uh, we just met
five months ago.
But five months is long enough.
Because I knew
after five minutes.
Rose...
I love you.
Will you marry me?
Bernard, I'm dying.
I'm sick, and I'm dying.
Uh, would you excuse us
for a minute, please?
I've been in remission for
the last couple of years.
But now, it's back, and this time,
it's not going away.
My doctor says I
have about a year,
maybe a little longer.
You haven't answered
my question.
Are... you sure?
Oh, I'm sure.
Yes...
Y es.
Well, you bunk with a guy for 48 days,
now he doesn't call or write.
Hello, Bernard.
What do you boys
got going up here?
Just working.
Well, listen.
I've got a whole team of folks
throwing together a big
sign down along the beach.
Hopefully, it'll get us spotted
by a plane or a satellite.
We could sure use all the bodies we
could get to help put it together.
Sorry, I'm busy.
Charlie?
Ah, regrets, Bernard.
I've only got two hands, you know.
Good luck, though.
Well, could I at least
grab some of these logs?
We  could sure use--
we're using them.
- For what, exactly?
- A church.
- A church?
- Yes.
Everybody on this island
is building something.
I'm trying to get us saved.
People are saved in
different ways, Bernard.
I think I liked you better when you
just hit people with your stick.
I like you just
the way you are.
I need to talk to him.
The gun's with Jack.
The door stays closed.
But if you wanna talk to him,
talk to him.
Henry, can you hear me?
It's John, Henry.
Henry, did you
enter the numbers?
Did you push the button or not?
Henry! I need to know.
I want you to answer me.
Answer me, Henry!
What happened to everybody?
Where's, uh, where's Craig?
Where's Frogurt?
Okay. All right. Moving on.
We're gonna put the sign
across this entire beach,
which means the letters have to
be really big-- about 40 feet.
These black rocks will get
maximum contrast with the sand.
Dude, we're likely to
need a lot more rocks.
Yes, Hurley.
We are gonna need a lot more rocks.
There's a lava field about
a half a mile inland.
It's just loaded with them. We're
gonna haul them out in 2-man teams.
So, uh, you guys double up,
and I am gonna start sketching off the
letters in the sand. Let's do this.
Hey, um,
I can sketch the letters.
Everybody's got a job, Hurley.
I do my job, you do yours.
What? What'd he say?
I think he's not so crazy about the
whole "carry the rocks a half
mile" thing.
Okay... well,this
is gonna take time.
But if this is the thing that gets us
off this place, isn't that worth it?
Rome wasn't built in a day,
you know.
Ah, no, you don't... okay.
All right, let's get started. Come on.
We're lost. Oh, you saying we're lost
doesn't make us lost, sweetheart.
- I know exactly where we are.
- Me, too.
Driving around in circles in
the middle of the outback.
That's why I wanted to be on
a beach for our honeymoon.
Thank goodness. Civilization.
Bernard, let's get directions.
Oh, I don't need directions.
I told you, honey. We're not lost.
Bernard, what's going on?
I brought you out here...
because I want you
to see this man.
His name is Isaac of Uluru.
And he's helped hundreds of people.
Now, I know how it looks,
but believe me, he is completely legit.
Bernard...
you brought me to
a faith healer?
He's the real deal, Rose.
Once I started telling
people about your situation,
I got three separate
calls recommending him.
My situation?
This is why you wanted
to come to Australia?
To bring me to some
kind of a kook?
No, he's not.
Rose, I made a $10,000 donation just
to get you in to see him. Normally--
I didn't ask for this!
It's just...
Bernard...
I have made my peace with
what's happeningto me.
Well, I haven't.
I can't just do nothing, Rose.
That's not me.
That's not who I am.
I have to try.
Will you try, Rose?
For me.
Okay, it's just gonna be great.
It's gonna be a really big sign.
That's great.
If you have time to fix your hut,
you'll have time to move some rocks.
Come on.
We could really use your help.
What, you got union trouble down
at the sand factory, Norma Rae?
Come on, Sawyer. I need your help.
Now what do you say?
I say...
pas-adena.
- Well, I hope you're happy.
- About what?
This morning I had 15 people
willing to work on the sign,
- and now I'm down to 4.
- And how is that my fault?
At the very least, I expected your
support. You had to go and attack me.
Have you ever stopped to think,
maybe the reason people are quitting
is because you've got yourself
a management problem?
What is the matter
with you, Rose?
I am just trying
to do something.
That's  exactly right.
You're always trying to do.
Why can't you just
let things be?
If I didn't always have to do something,
you wouldn't be here.
I'm flattered.
Yeah? Why is that?
'Cause you chose me to go
with you instead of Sawyer.
I asked Sayid first,
but he turned me down.
And I only asked you
because they don't want you.
They grabbed you,
had you at gunpoint.
They could have kept you,
but they didn't.
Then again,
they didn't really want me, either.
Damaged goods.
Both of us.
What's that?
K ate.
It's a doll.
Wait, wait, no-- no, don't--
Sorry.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Oh, good. So you can hear me.
This isn't one of theirs.
No. It's not
sophisticated enough.
Must be one of Rousseau's traps.
Hopefully she's not far from here.
Could be a week
before she shows up.
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to get the gun.
- I can't get my arm around.
- All right, here, let me.
All right.
Sorry.
- I don't wanna shoot you.
- Okay.
- You got it?
- Okay, ready?
- Yeah.
Got it, got it, got it.
Oh, all right.
There, got it.
Now, give me the gun.
Why, what for?
Gonna try to shoot the rope.
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey, hey!
I'm a better shot than you are.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I told you.
I grew up hunting with my dad.
Damn it!
Well, at least they
know where we are.
Okay, now give me the gun.
And you're gonna
waste another bullet?
Don't worry. We'll still have 13 more
to shoot each other with. Come on.
Fine. You have a better
angle than I do, anyway.
Oh, that's gonna be your
excuse when I make the shot.
When you make the shot.
Okay.
Nice shot.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
You're doing it all wrong!
I told you three rows.
Three-- so they can
see it from the air.
Three rows! How hard is that?
Do I just have to do
everything myself?
No! No, no, no!
No, Jin. No, wait.
Please...
I just want to
get my wife home.
Rose.
I wanna get Rose home.
Sorry.
You're in my spot.
I can move.
Can you?
Oh, that's funny.
I guess your sense of humor got
trapped under that door with your leg.
I saw your husband walking
through the jungle, hauling rocks.
He's building a big
sign in the sand,
so the satellites will see it.
That man doesn't know the difference
between an errand and a fool's errand.
Well, Rose, most of us don't.
So what are you doing
down here, John?
Can't remember the last time
I saw you out of that hatch.
I'm done with the hatch.
Oh, now,
you're just frustrated.
You'll be out of that splint and running
around the island again in no time.
Hmm. And yet Jack said it'd
beat least four weeks.
But, honey, you and I both know
it's not gonna take that long.
Right this way, Rose.
Please, make
yourself comfortable.
Isaac will be right with you.
You must be Rose.
Why don't you have a seat?
So, um... how does this work?
I sit here and you chant?
Or, um...
pray or what?
There are certain places
with great energy--
spots on the Earth,
like the one we're above now.
Perhaps this energy is
geological, magnetic.
Or perhaps it's something else.
And, when possible,
I harness this energy
and give it to others.
May I?
What?
What-- what is it?
I'm sorry.
Can't do anything
for you, Rose.
I didn't expect you to.
It's not that you
can't be healed.
Like I said,
there's different energies.
This is not the
right place for you.
Where is the right place?
I wish I knew.
I'll return your
husband's donation.
Don't.
I'm gonna tell
him you fixed me.
I'm going to tell
What did you mean back there?
What?
In the net.
You said they were sophisticated,
the others.
Uh... last week,
when the baby got sick,
Claire and I went into the jungle and,
uh, found another hatch.
What?
Like a medical station.
There was nothing you could use.
It was all cleared out, but...
I found some lockers.
They had clothes inside,
all worn and dirty.
They were on hangers, like...
like costumes, you know?
And there was a make up kit...
and a fake beard.
When were you going
to tell me this?
When you decided to let
me back in the club.
What?
You can keep one of them locked up in
the hatch for a week, and say nothing.
But then, when I--
We're here.
Are you sure? I...
That's where they took
the shot at Sawyer.
Right over there is where they
pushed you out of the jungle
with a bag on your head.
And right there is where I...
where I laid my gun down.
Hey!
Hey, I'm back!
You say you're watching us?
Do you hear me?!
We've got your man!
If you want him back,
you're gonna have to come out here!
- Come on out!
- Jack!
I know you're out there!
I know you can hear me!
Jack, they're not here.
I'll be right here
until you talk to me!
I'll be right here!
I brought you some supper.
Thanks. You can just
set it down there.
Where is everybody?
I owe you an apology.
You don't have anything
to be sorry for.
It's my own damn fault
I'm out here by myself.
That's not why I'm apologizing.
I lied to you.
Back in Australia.
Isaac-- he didn't heal me.
He didn't do anything.
- Of course he did. You're-- you're--
- Bernard... he didn't heal me.
But that doesn't
mean I'm not healed.
When you're sick,
and you've got something inside you
that doesn't belong there,
you can feel it. And after the crash,
I couldn't feel it anymore.
At first,
I thought it was just shock.
But it wasn't.
It's this place.
But-- but you said
Isaac fixed you.
I told you that so that
you wouldn't spend what time we
had left trying to do something.
Uh... Rose,
you could just be in remission.
How do you know it wasn't
Isaac who healed you?
How do you know that
he didn't heal you?
I know.
These yours?
Uh, thank you.
You're welcome.
Trust me.
I know.
You don't want to be rescued,
do you?
You think if you leave...
it'll come back.
And if you can't leave...
neither can I.
We won't ever leave, Rose.
I would, uh, I would offer to
take down the sign, but, um...
we didn't get very far.
Hey.
Hi.
I pressed your button.
It's not my button.
Where'd you go?
I just needed to...
How long are you
gonna wait, Jack?
Till I get my voice back.
Then I'm gonna yell some more.
Maybe they can't hear you.
They can hear me.
I'm sorry I kissed you.
I'm not.
Michael.
Synchro Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com