Sorry, man. I know this hurts.
Michael told me you pulled the
bullet out with your bare hands.
You have to show me how
to do that sometime.
Where is she?
- What? I didn't--
- Where is she?
You mean Kate?
She's been watching over you
for the past 24 hours straight.
The only way I could get rid of her was
to send her out to get some food
for you.
I love her.
Well, hey, girl.
What are you doin' here?
Hey, there.
All right,
let's get you to bed.
Watch your step,
watch your step!
What the hell is that smell?
- Probably your breath.
- Yeah, right.
Come on.
You're beautiful.
Hey.
Hey! I just gave
you a compliment.
Yeah, I heard you.
Aren't ya gonna take
my pants off first?
You are beautiful.
Good night.
Coffee, pie? Both?
How about a beer?
I'd like to see some I.D.
I'm 24, ma.
You want to ride around on that
death trap of yours without a helmet,
I'm not going to help your
cause by getting you drunk.
How's that wrist?
What, this?
You know, that shelf in the
kitchen sticks out sometimes.
You'd think I'd remember it was there,
but I banged it--
Don't.
I made my bed, Katherine.
Well, your bed's gone, ma.
What?
What is this?
An insurance policy
for the house.
- What? I never--
- I took it out in your name.
What did you do?
Does Wayne know about this?
Just remember that you were here
and you didn't see me, okay?
Katherine, what did you do?
I took care of you, ma.
I gotta go.
You're not gonna
see me for awhile.
Katherine!
What did you do?
- Hey.
You okay?
Yeah. Uh, yeah,
I think I'm just...
I think I'm tired.
How is he?
Fever's still up there.
Can't tell if the
antibiotics are working.
It'll help to get
some food in him.
You should get down
to the beach for...
for Shannon.
I was actually thinking that I
should stay and watch Sawyer.
I'll stay with him.
You should be there.
Keep him hydrated.
Maybe mash upsome of that fruit,
see if you can get him to eat it.
And everybody will beat the beach,
so don't forget the button.
I got it.
Be back in a couple hours.
Yep.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
Hey.
I'm going to go to the funeral.
I don't think I'm
gonna make it.
I think most of them
realize it was an accident.
Shannon and I were strangers.
We never would have met if...
we wouldn't even
have spoken if...
but we did meet,
and we did speak.
At least...
I loved her.
May she rest in peace.
You hungry?
I'm just gonna mash
you up some fruit here.
When you wake up,
you're going to get a kick out
of me feeding you like a baby.
I saw a horse.
Yeah. That's what happens
when you don't sleep.
Sawyer? You awake?
Good for nothing...
You killed me.
Why did you kill me?!
It's the alarm.
Kate!
Sawyer.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
- But you said--
- I don't know, John!
Well, where's Kate?
Kate. Hey,
you missed the funeral.
Yeah, uh, I was with Sawyer.
Oh, right.
A few of them came,
the new people.
Not her, the one who killed Shannon.
That would have been awkward.
They seem to have had
a rough time of it.
Looks like they went bloody
"lord of the flies" out there.
You haven't listened
to a word I've said.
Do you think there
are horses here?
What?
I think I saw a
horse in the jungle.
I've seen polar bears.
I've seen monsters.
Well, heard monsters.
But horses?
No.
Kate!
Where are you going?
Tallahassee, one way, please.
Tallahassee? I spent a week
in Tallahassee one night.
It's all strip malls
and waffle houses.
What's a pretty girl like you
gonna do down in Tallahassee?
I'm sure I'll find something.
Bet you got family
down there, huh?
Actually, I'm just visiting.
Hey.
Hey!
Don't I know you?
No, I don't think so.
Don't run, Kate.
I got her.
Kate Austen,
you're under arrest for murder.
- I didn't do anything.
- Oh, yeah, you did.
Your mama gave you up, Kate.
Charlie, have you seen Kate?
Uh, a little while
ago in the jungle.
She was acting kind of balmy,
asking me about horses on the island.
You know where she is now?
She's on the path heading
back to the caves.
Everything okay?
Yeah, Charlie,
everything's fine.
Thank you.
Free at last, huh?
Yeah, man. Looks good.
Hey, Locke.
What's up with the blast doors?
Blast doors?
Yeah.
Like in case of an explosion,
they'll come from the ceiling.
That guy down here, uh...
Desmond?
Yeah, Desmond. He didn't tell you
about these, what they're for?
No, no, he didn't,
but he did leave a movie.
A movie?
Yeah.
You want to see it?
I would like to see it, too.
If you don't mind.
Why not?
The more, the merrier.
Kate, what the hell
are you doing out here?
What happened in the hatch, Kate?
Why'd you leave?
I come back. I find Sawyer just lying
on the ground. You just took off.
- Is he okay?
- Yes, Kate, he's fine.
I'm sorry.
Are you?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I am
not as perfect as you!
I'm sorry that I'm not as good!
- What's going on with you?
- Just forget it.
No, don't walk
away from me, no.
- Let me go! Don't!
- Kate! Kate, Kate, Kate.
It's okay. It's okay. Kate.
This place...
this place is crazy.
I can't. It's driving me nuts.
I know. It's okay.
It's all right.
All right?
Kate!
From the moment
the alarm sounds,
you will have four
minutes to enter the code
into the
microcomputer processor.
Induction into the program.
When the alarm sounds,
either you or your partner
must input the code.
It is highly
recommended that you
and your partner take
alternating shifts.
In this manner,
you will stay as fresh and alert.
It is most important that
when the alarm sounds,
the code be entered correctly
and in a timely fashion.
Do not attempt to use
a computer for any--
Congratulations.
Until your replacements arrive,
the future of the
project is in your hands.
On behalf of the Degroots,
Alvar Hanso and all of us
at the Dharma Initiative,
thank you, namaste,
and good luck.
All right.
So you've been pushing that button
every two hours since you got down here.
That's right.
How's that even work?
I've set up 2-person shifts, 6 hours.
Everyone's on the roster.
Don't they want to know why?
I think the film is
pretty self-explanatory.
Really?
All I heard was something about
electromagnets and an incident.
What about all the
missing pieces?
Oh, you mean the splices?
Yeah, just a frame here and there,
I think, nothing important.
What do you think?
About the film,
what do you think?
I'm sorry I missed it,
her funeral.
I... I had to be
with Sawyer, so...
Why aren't you with him now?
'Cause I'm going crazy.
Do you believe in
ghosts, Sayid?
I saw Walt in the jungle just
before Shannon was shot.
Does that make me crazy?
It's a long drive back to
the arraignment. You comfy?
Why now?
What?
Nice corn-fed farm
girl like yourself,
no history of violence,
straight A's, no record,
a couple of speeding tickets.
I just gotta wonder,
why'd you kill him now?
Oh, right, yeah, don't tell me.
You wouldn't want to
incriminate yourself,
not after you were so
smart planning it.
That jury back in Iowa sure ain't
gonna get hung upon premeditation.
And a gas leak?
Come on,
it's amateur hour from top to bottom.
It sounds like you've
got it all figured out.
I do have you all figured out.
You don't know
anything about me.
White-trash mom divorces dad,
starts up with some guy who's a drinker,
maybe he knocks her
around a little bit,
and so she marries him because,
you know,
that's what happens.
And then this drunk, this Wayne,
he moves into your house,
and you get to lay
there every night
and listen to him doing your mom right
there in your daddy's old bedroom.
And even that wouldn't be so bad if
he didn't beat her up all the time.
But she loves him,
she defends him.
If that don't make a person want to
kill somebody, I don't know what does.
But the question is, now?
Why now?
Why after all these years
did you just decide to
blow poor Wayne up?
He come knocking on your
door late at night?
He never touched me.
Look out!
Get... get off!
Well, why can't you just
put the numbers in now?
No, it doesn't work that way.
The alarm goes off
in four minutes.
You can't type
anything till then.
You mind if I check out
some of this hardware?
Sure.
Just don't break it.
- Hello again.
- Hello.
I have something I
think you should see.
If you don't mind,
I will begin at the beginning.
Long before Christ,
the king of Judah was
a man named Josiah.
Boy, when you say "beginning,"
you mean beginning.
At that time,
the temple where the people
worshipped was in ruin,
and so the people worshipped idols,
false gods,
and so the kingdom
was in disarray.
Josiah, since he
was a good king,
sent his secretary
to the treasury
and said,
"we must rebuild the temple.
Give all of the gold to the
workers so that this will be done."
But when the secretary returned,
he had no gold.
And when Josiah
asked why this was,
the secretary replied...
"we found a book."
Do you know this story?
No, afraid I don't.
What the secretary had found
was an ancient book,
the book of law.
You may know it as
the Old Testament.
And it was with that ancient book,
not with the gold,
that Josiah rebuilt the temple.
On the other side
of the island,
we found a place
much like this.
And in this place,
we found a book.
I believe what's inside there
will be of great value to you.
Hey.
So Rose's husband's white.
Didn't see that one coming.
Is there something
you need, Hurley?
No. Just taking a walk,
thought I'd say "hey."
Who's taking care of Sawyer?
Sun is.
So you're, like, mad at him?
Why would I be mad at Sawyer?
Maybe 'cause he's the one
always comes down here and
chops wood and now you are.
It's, like, transference.
What are you, a shrink now?
Well, that's what they call
it in the mental hospital.
I'm not mad at anyone.
Where's Jack?
I don't know.
He didn't come back.
Has he said anything?
Sawyer?
No, he's still sleeping.
Can you watch him?
- I can stay if you--
- No. Yeah, I can.
Thanks.
Uh-huh. Yes, I'm sure that's the
exact form you've got. Uh-huh.
I'll send one over
to you, right.
I'll call you back later.
Hi, dad.
Katie, the police and the U.S.
Marshals are looking for you.
You shouldn't have come here.
I've been waiting outside for 2 hours.
They're not here.
Is it true what they're saying?
Katie, what did
you come here for?
Why didn't you tell me, dad?
Tell you what?
I was making a scrapbook,
a surprise for your birthday,
so I called one of your C.O.s to
get some pictures of you in uniform.
The pictures that he sent
me had dates on the back,
photos of you in Korea up until
four months before I was born.
Why didn't you tell me
that Wayne was my father?
Why?
I didn't tell you because
I knew you'd kill him.
And your mother...
loved him.
You were 5 years old.
I wanted to take you along with me.
She wouldn't let me.
So why didn't you kill him?
Because I don't have
murder in my heart.
I'm gonna have to call 'em.
Can I have an hour?
Bye, daddy.
Can you hear me?
Sawyer?
Wayne?
I'm probably crazy,
and this doesn't matter,
but maybe you're in there.
Somehow you asked me a question.
You asked me why I...
why I did it.
It wasn't 'cause you
drove my father away
or the way you looked at me
or because you beat her.
It was 'cause I hated that
you were a part of me,
that I would never be good,
that I would never
have anything good.
And every time that
I look at Sawyer,
every time I feel
something for him,
I see you, Wayne,
and it makes me sick.
That's about the sweetest
thing I've ever heard.
Sawyer?
Who the hell is Wayne?
Where am I?
A bunk bed?
Yeah, you're in a bunk bed.
Are we saved?
No, Sawyer.
Not yet.
Voilà.
What are the odds?
- The odds?
- Yeah.
Here, hold this down on the table here,
nice and flat.
I mean, think about it.
Somebody made this film.
Someone else cut
this piece out.
We crash.
Two halves of the same plane fall
on different parts of the island.
You're over there.
I'm over here.
And now here's the missing piece,
right back where it belongs.
What are the odds?
Don't mistake
coincidence for fate.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Air lock's over this way.
Oh.
Come on, admit it.
We've been rescued.
You got it? Sorry.
Watch yourself.
Son of a bitch.
Watch yourself, okay?
Okay.
Home sweet home.
Yeah.
I really thought you
were yanking my chain.
What do you keep smiling at?
You need a haircut.
Oh, really?
Maybe you ought to
take me back inside.
You see that?
If you mean the big-ass horse standing
in the middle of the jungle, then,
yeah.
You know that horse, freckles?
Yeah, I do.
Tequila and tonic.
That's your drink, right?
Where's the tonic?
We're running a
little low on mixers.
Sure you want to
waste that on me?
I figured you
could use a drink.
I know I could.
You're gonna try to convince me
that everyone here doesn't hate me?
Only if you're gonna try to convince me
that every woman in the world's
not crazy.
When the alarm sounds,
either you or your partner
must input the code.
It is highly
recommended that you
and your partner take
alternating shifts.
In this manner, you will both
still stay as fresh and alert.
It is most important that
when the alarm sounds,
the code be entered correctly
and in a timely fashion.
Here it comes.
Do not attempt to
use the computer
for anything else other than
the entering of the code.
This is its only function.
The isolation that attends the
duties associated with station 3,
may tempt you to try and
utilize the computer for
communication with the outside world.
This is strictly forbidden.
Attempting to use the
computer in this manner
will compromise the
integrity of the project and
worse, could lead to
another incident.
I repeat,
do not use the computer for anything
other than entering the code.
Congratulations.
Until your replacements arrive,
the future of the
project is in your hands.
Hello?
Who is this?
This Michael. Who is this?
Dad?
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: RaceMan
www.forom.com