이 이야기는 허구이며
특정 인물과 사건을 묘사하지 않습니다
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
January 2, 1982
Steven totally suprised me.
I've seen that street.
Those houses are glamour to the max, okay?
Steven told me I could decorate
however I wanted.
I mean, he's at the hospital
all the time anyway.
No way.
Anyway you wanted?
So far, I've got leopard skin chairs,
a Persian carpet and
faberge eggs for the mantel.
If I was you, I'd get like a big
neon sign, like with my name on it
- and put it in the living room.
- I'm thinking more classical.
Oh, sure.
No way.
Your doctor's here, Mrs. Chase.
Steven?
Lindsay.
Is there something wrong?
Baby, you're sweating.
Alan...
died.
What do you mean?
You are gonna operate on him today.
On the table.
During the surgery.
While..while I was operating.
No...
I think.. it's gonna get ugly, Lindsay.
Don't worry about the bill.
Chase. L. / May `82
Closed
Victim's name is Melanie Castle.
All right.
The place looks ransacked.
Junkie housekeeping.
- What have we got?
- Melanie Castle, 44.
Looks like a heroine overdose.
No foul play.
Well, I'm guessing we're not here because
the apartment just came on the market.
You two remember
the Lindsay Chase murder?
Doctor kills his wife
for the insurance money?
23 years, Steven Chase has been in prison
telling the same story about that night.
So what's the connection here?
Well, the doctor swore he heard
a gunshot, came downstairs,
and saw a shaggy man and
a blond woman running out the door.
Only, no one ever found evidence
they existed.
Right.
Melanie here was wearing this.
There's an inscription.
Doctor Chase,
all my love, Lindsay.
- Steven Chase was right.
- Yep.
Which ended up ....
on a blond woman.
Cold Case
2x17  Schadenfreude
영어대본
진현경(jhk8012@nate.com)
자막편집/싱크
남효주(hyojunet@nate.com)
한글번역
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
번역수정
맞춤법교정
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
캐서린 모리스(릴리 러쉬役)
대니 피노(스카티 발렌스役)
존 핀(존 스틸만役)
제레미 래치포드(닉 베라役)
톰 배리(윌 제프리스役)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2005/03/20
This whole box is
wacko phone calls.
Useful citizens offering info
on a blond gal and a shaggy guy.
Gotta love the specifics there.
Jury didn't buy the doctor's story,
convicted him in two hours.
So, Steven Chase is a big league
surgeon till he loses a patient.
No, not just any patient.
Friend, Alan Moore.
And Moore's widow sues
for malpractice.
Doc's medical license
gets suspended.
And now, he can't pay the bills,
but he has a million on
the life insurance on the wife.
Ain't that sweet. She ends up
shot in her own living room.
Gun was never found?
No. This a receipt for a .38
Chase bought a month earlier.
Guy's a doctor living in Chestnuthill.
How's he hard pressed for cash?
Well, it says here he was pulling
in ten grand a month, but spending 14.
That was the '80's, Lil.
Why save for a rainy day when
the sun's always shining.
So, we thinking this dead junkie
might've been half of this intruder team?
- She's got the doctor's ring.
- New day for the blond-shaggy story.
Lousy alibi, but Chase has been
sticking to it for a long time.
You were quite the news item in
'82, Dr. Chase.
City follows your trial like it was
a World Series.
Yes, it's called, Schadenfreude.
We're dumb cops, so you'll
have to talk down to us.
Taking pleasure in
other people's misfortune.
Works best if the other's got
a long way to fall.
Rich doctor, beautiful wife...
Suddenly it's a wall?
Now he lives in a box
with the scum of society.
Makes you feel good about
your life, right?
There was also a rich
stack of evidence against you.
Like the gun you bought.
Just before Lindsay was shot.
That was for me.
Not her.
I had dark days.
And your flimsy intruder story?
If I were a liar, I would've
thought of something better.
Recognize this ring?
Lindsay gave it to me
when I graduated med shcool.
How did you get it?
Tell us about the patient you lost.
Alan?
He and Diane were our
best friends.
I made this mistake and it
changed course of all our lives.
Especially when Diane sued you.
I couldn't face her.
I..
shrank.
But Lindsay didn't.
We shouldn't be here.
Yes, we should.
Alan was our friend.
What can I say to her?
I don't have any words.
You will.
I know it.
You always do.
Diane, we are so sorry.
How can you come here?
We loved Alan.
You killed him.
He didn't, Diane.
It was a horrible accident.
I've contacted a lawyer.
Diane. No.
I want to see you
lose something too.
I'm sorry for loss.
And you'll be sorry
for your losses.
Sounds like a threat.
She was in shock.
Grieving.
That's when people do things
they couldn't normally stomach.
My wife was killed by a blond
and a shaggy man.
Diane had brown hair.
Still, no one had
motive like she did.
It's not possible.
We weren't those kind of people.
No one ever is.
Diane Moore?
- Do I know you?
- I'm Detective Valens, Homicide.
Nice ride.
Well, it gets me there.
It's about Lindsay Chase.
- What about Lindsay?
- We're looking at her murder again.
Poor Steven's been paying for that
for twenty years.
Poor Steven?
He was a good friend at one time.
Are you singing a different tune
than you did in '82?
The way I heard it,
you gave it to Steven and Lindsay
pretty good at your husband's funeral.
Sent them away.
I was out of my head
when I lost Alan.
I couldn't see pass the pain.
- Yeah?
- I wanted their world to crumble.
- Like mine had.
- And that's why the lawsuit.
And it broke them.
He couldn't practice, pay
the mortgage. They were a cash poor.
Plus, Chase got real depressed.
It was a horror show.
And I couldn't get enough of it.
Lindsay, hi.
- D'you need a color?
- No.
Well, yeah.
But that's not why I'm here.
I'm looking for employment.
I don't have professional experience,
but I'm good with hair and nails.
Kitty, I've got aerobics in 20 minutes.
2 secs, Diane.
No, now.
I'm the one paying you.
Look, all I've got is hair
sweeping stuff.
It's a minimum wage and it's
your friends's hair.
They're not my friends anymore.
So I don't mind.
I just need to make enough
for groceries till Steven gets better.
Sure.
It'll be great, Linds.
Welcome.
I was so distraught...
I actually enjoyed
watching her suffer.
It wasn't until later I thought
maybe it was me.
- You what?
- Who caused her death.
Maybe the lawsuit drove
Steven over the edge,
made him kill her.
Anything on our dead blond junkie?
Looked into her glorious past.
Few jobs, stint in rehab, usual story.
No connect to the Chases?
Scotty have better luck?
Well, Lindsay Chase may have taken
a low rent job a few months before she died.
Will's running that down.
Struck out.
IRS has no record of her working
at the Patrick Brea Salon or anywhere else.
What's it Salon?
Brea.
B.R.E.A.
That was Melanie Castle's
employer, January to August, '82.
That's the same time Lindsay
was killed.
So our blond and Lindsay Chase
were co-workers.
Kitty Shaw?
Katarine.
I figured I'd upgrade the name
and the rest of my life would follow.
Tada.
Detectives Rush and Jeffries.
Homicide.
We're wondering if you remember
Lindsay Chase.
Of course.
She was my friend.
Why don't we...
What about Melanie Castle?
We worked together like,
million years ago.
Yikes, why?
Melanie died two days ago.
- Heroine overdose.
- Oh god, no.
What does that have to do
with Lindsay?
We're taking another look
at her murder.
I thought her husband killed her.
We heard she might have worked
for you back at Patrick Brea Salon.
That's what we hear,
but there's no record of it.
We paid her under the table.
Paid most of the sweepers
under table.
- Like Melanie?
- Yeah.
Now, those two, that,
that was a culture clash.
And Melanie didn't appreciate
the extra help with the broom?
I don't think Melanie thought of Lindsay
as a helpful presence in her life.
No.
Feel better?
I'm sorry.
You probably had plans.
- I didn't mean to cry at work.
- Hey.
I'd cry too if my super-hunk hubby
was depressed in bed all day.
Plus, I thought 8 hours would
add up to more than this.
Steven's gonna pull through.
He's got a million reasons
to get out of bed.
You, is one.
- We're talking, okay?
- Tell Timmy.
I wanted to sit at the bar.
Is this a girl thing?
No, it's fine.
Hi.
Timmy, this is Lindsay.
Yeah, I saw you before.
You're not driving
the beemer anymore.
Got repo'd.
You got money problems.
That hair sweeping job isn't gonna help
you out, but I know about other stuff.
Real stuff that could help you out.
She's not like that.
Take a chill.
Okay, I can see that
she's classy, okay?
You don't have to point it out.
I wanna go.
Now.
Why?
Just got one gulp down.
What's...?
Psycho!
Mel.
So Melanie was a little sensitive about
her boyfriend making eyes at Lindsay?
Sounds like she wasn't too crazy
about her before that.
She kind of felt Lindsay was
lording over us, but...
It wasn't like that.
Know where Timmy ended up?
Jail, half way house, something
sensational like that.
Have you..
Have you ever thought about
doing a rinse?
Sometimes.
You could go copper.
You got the skin for it.
I'll think about it.
- Hey.
- Scotty.
Timothy Horan.
How's he looking?
Shaggy.
Starting in '83, methamphetamine,
methamphetamine, methamphetamine.
Three time loser
with a blond girlfriend.
Yeah, who hated Lindsay Chase.
- We'll go pick him up.
- Think so.
Scotty.
I got something for you.
- Who's this?
- It's doctor, a grief counselor.
- I don't need that, boss.
- Well, it can't hurt, can it?
- Boss.
- You never talk about it, Scotty.
I do better not talking.
All right, throw it away.
Timothy Horan.
I ain't done nothing wrong, officers.
I live straight now.
Sober, except for beer.
So, this how you making it by?
- With your Windex?
- I tried working regulars.
Took too much out of me.
Well, see what you can
muster up for this.
We hear about Lindsay Chase.
You and your girlfriend Melanie
knew her.
Yeah, you two fit the description
of the couple Steven Chase saw
bolting out of his house that night.
Whoa, Lindsay was my friend.
Is that what you call girls
you got a mission to bang?
There were sparks, that was mutual.
Not how we heard it, Timmy.
We heard Melanie hated Lindsay for
acting like she was better than you two.
Yeah. She got real bent out of shape
at you for drooling over Lindsay.
So maybe you made it up to Melanie
by taking the lady down.
Me and Lindsay made a true bond.
She came to me for help.
Yeah?
How'd that go?
She asked me if it was
really true I could make money.
- What'd you say?
- Well, I said yeah, for you, sure.
I just need a place to cook.
Kitty, my house smells like pee.
Steven's coming home tomorrow.
We'll roast coffee grounds.
That'll cover it.
Hey, those are our wedding gift.
They work good.
Look at me.
I'm a doctor's wife.
That's Steven's ring.
He's gained weight.
It doesn't fit him.
- Put it back, Melanie.
- Why? You got her shirt on.
Cuz Lindsay gave it to me.
I didn't lift it. Put it back.
After this, no more. It's not right.
All this in your nice house, okay?
Hey.
He's here.
So I owe you half.
- That's only three thousand dollars.
- Lindsay.
It's 25 hundred now.
Okay, Mike.
No.
What did you say?
Lindsay, don't.
Take it off.
6 thousand, a deal's a deal.
Except when it's not.
I could kill you right now,
get the whole batch for nothing.
If I wanted to.
Take the deal or leave my house.
And you never see anything like it.
You don't talk to Mike like that.
He was in the big things.
- What kind of things?
- Big money things.
Did you tell Lindsay
about the big money?
Well, yeah. She was real curious
about the stuff he did.
Money laundering,
insurance scams.
You know if Lindsay and Mike
ever met again?
She'd be dead if they did.
Which she is, Tim.
Looks like Lindsay was getting in over
her head trying to make some quick cash.
Fell in with the bad crowd,
speed freaks.
It could be why she didn't
tell her husband about the salon job.
Didn't want her meeting the low life
she was hanging with.
We think her slide might have
ended up with Mike Doherty.
Well, despite what Timmy said
about him, the guy ain't got a record.
He worked under the radar.
Made a pile collecting insurance from
staged robberies.
Put some meth deals on the side.
What's Mike up to these days?
He owns Doherty Systems,
a home security store.
Moved up in the world.
Put his crapulous skills to use.
I gotta get Scotty.
Drop in on Mike.
See if he and Lindsay met again.
Wonder why Kitty never mentioned
the meth cookout.
You'd think cooking drugs with
Wiliams Sonoma would ring some bells.
I can't feel my face.
Southern comfort,
it melts it right off.
Speaking of comfort,
how's your barmaid?
You're gonna henpeck me now too?
I waved the red flag once.
You don't heed, it ain't my worry.
Well, she keeps me guessing.
So, this ain't just a move for you?
Chris, a move?
Nah.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
- What?
- Well, you should figure that out.
- Right.
- Soon.
Yeah.
Dead bolts, chain locks.
This what's call
on systems, Mike?
Keep out the bad guys, don't they?
You'd know, I guess.
Don't get your meaning. / Your customers
know they're being protected by criminal?
Never been arrested in my life.
So what can you tell us about
Lindsay Chase?
Her husband killed her.
Blamed druggy intruders.
I read all about it.
Oh, you had closer seat
than that, Mike.
You were at Lindsay's house.
Remember?
To buy meth.
- You threatened her.
- I may have negotiated with her.
I could kill you right now.
- That a negotiation?
- She couldn't have been too scared.
Cuz she invited me back.
Alone this time.
Well, let's talk about that.
The woman had guts.
That's what I remember.
This real?
Yes, we were in Shanghai last year.
What's that?
No, not that. Steven's great-grandfather
was turn of the century's water colorist.
It was a wedding gift.
He famous?
Grandpa.
Experts know him.
But you can't have it.
It has sentimental value.
If you don't want to this,
sell your house.
Don't waste my time.
I told you.
We can't.
He'd fall apart.
Then here it is.
The night of the job, I'll call
you from the minimart on Highland.
I'll ring twice and hang up.
You got it?
Yeah.
That call's your 5 minute warning.
Get upstairs.
Turn off the lights.
Okay.
Next morning, call the cops.
And then you wait 6 months
to collect the insurance.
I can't wait.
I need the moeny.
- You can't look needy.
- I am needy.
6 months, or we don't do this.
Fine.
We split insurance money,
I sell your stuff for cash
which I keep.
- What are you doing?
- You're high maintenance.
I need a bonus, I'll take this.
Just a deal, not this.
No this, no deal.
She buttoned up,
no sale.
And you just let that happen.
I had 30 other deals going,
I didn't need her.
Gal gets you all worked up
and you just walk away?
Nobody gets me all worked up.
And her dying a week later,
that's coincidence.
I wasn't thnking
about her a week later.
She wasted enough of my time.
I still can't get used to 50 bucks
for a haircut.
And now I make a living, I...
Hate to spend money.
Not me.
Minute I wasn't scraping by,
I spent like it was my job.
Look at yourself, Lilly.
So, Kitty. How come you didn't tell us
about Lindsay and the meth?
She was my friend.
I was protecting her.
How's that work?
She was ashamed of how
desperate she was.
She wouldn't want people knowing
that she had a bunch cretins turning
her nice house into a meth lab.
I'm not judging Lindsay.
She was a good person
in a tough spot.
You know, I might as well just
tell you the worst then.
She stooped even lower than that.
This have something to do with Mike?
- Timmy.
- Melanie's guy?
Kid was tripping over himself
to get with Lindsay.
She knew it.
And she needed someone to help
her with what she was planning.
You know what I think?
I think people underestimate you.
- Yeah?
- You're sweet.
You're fun.
Having fun, huh?
And you're smart.
You're so sexy.
I need smart.
What's going on?
Me and her are talking.
Beat it.
- Where's Melanie?
- Cousin's funeral.
Butt out.
How about some
more peanuts, Timmy?
Yeah.
Coming up.
What are you doing, Linds?
Just hanging with Tinmmy.
You mean you're
shaking your ass for him.
What's going on?
You know how that guy, Mike pulled
the plug on the robbery.
Cuz you wouldn't give it up for him.
And that was the right thing.
But I thought if I got
someone else to do it.
Someone I can control.
Linds, look at me.
That's not the kind of people we are.
We don't work it for twerps
like Timmy. We're above that.
You just gotta hang in there.
You know what song Steven loves?
Don't Stop Thinking about Tomorrow.
That is so true, Linds.
That's what I wanna
hear you saying.
Things are gonna get good again.
Fresh nuts, sexy.
Take a hike, Timmy.
You are so out of line.
Lindsay.
I know I'm jumping the gun,
but maybe you should tell your friend.
There are sparks.
I'm not making it up.
Right?
So Timmy got rejected by Lindsay
hours before she died?
Yeah, he was dreaming.
She was so far out of his league.
It doesn't mean he couldn't have
lashed out at her for sending him away.
I guess not.
How did he take Lindsay's death?
Truth is, I don't know.
He and Melanie split.
He never showed his face
at the bar again.
I never
downed so much of this
I forgot where I was.
You don't wanna play
"I never" with me.
I never stole a liquor from
my employer after hours.
I never caused
complications for myself.
Just cuz of some guy.
Worth it.
I never checked my cell phone
ten times in an hour.
Cuz I was hoping someone
had called.
What kind of someone?
Complicated.
Never ...
pictured someone so vivid
from the night before,
I missed my stop.
Went 5 miles out of my way
before I realized.
You ain't sick of me?
Feels like you just got here.
Lindsay Chase treated you
real bad, Timmy.
- Led you on.
- Me, I can't stand a tease.
You go down the rope,
you should deliver.
You tell her that?
You go to Lindsay's house that night
and tell her your terms?
No. / High class lady like that,
I bet you she laughed in your face.
- She wasn't teasing me.
- She lied about the sparks.
Yeah, but in front of her friend.
Something happened when her
friend wasn't around?
Before Kitty had to butt in,
Lindsay and me were confidants.
Is that so?
She told me about how it really
was in that big fancy house.
It's all roses on the outside,
but inside she was crying.
About what, Timmy?
Her husband, inspite of having
a grade A wife, had a dish on the side.
Steven Chase had a girlfriend?
Hurt Lindsay especially bad.
Cuz it was her friend.
Some Diane girl.
Diane?
You sure about that?
So it was the doc and Diane, huh?
Puts a new spin on her husband
dying on his table.
I think I figured it out, doc.
The way you live, solipsism.
Oh, I'm not Ivy Leavue,
but I pick up a thing or two.
It's a belief that you're the only
thing that really exists.
- I know what it means.
- It's your world.
We're just living in it.
Sound right?
- No, it doesn't.
- You had an affair with Diane Moore.
Yes.
Left that part out.
I wonder why.
Her husband dies on your operating
table just months before your wife gets shot,
clearing the way for
you and Diane.
- No.
- No?
Yes, it happened.
No, I didn't plan it.
Two dead people and all,
but who cares it's your world.
You get what you want.
- Diane.
- Alan dying ruined my life.
- That's cuz she turned on you.
- Wrong.
And the jury didn't buy your lame
story and sent you away forever.
Suddenly the world didn't
revolve around you.
The affair was nothing.
Hurt Lindsay enough to
bring it up to a virtual stranger.
- What stranger?
- Young buck named Timmy.
Loser to the core.
But he loved Lindsay.
I loved Lindsay.
Nothing says that sweeter
than banging her friend.
The times were indulgent, selfish...
I caught up in it.
Well, while you were being
selfish and indulgent,
your wife was down on the ground with
the rest of us, trying to scrape out a living.
- What do you mean?
- She was dealing drugs,
planning to rip off your house
to get the insurance money.
What?
Lindsay?
She was desperate.
To save you.
Then we both hit our lowest point.
Funny thing is that's when
we found each other again.
Steven, what are you
doing on the dark?
I ruined our lives.
What are you doing?
Who are you dressed like that for?
- No one.
- You seeing someone?
- No, Steven, give me the gun.
- I wouldn't blame ya.
Please, give it to me.
Without me,
you can get
your life back.
This is my life.
Us.
I miss you.
If you leave,
I don't know
what will happen to me.
I've been so lost.
I just want to get away
from here, okay?
Okay.
Honey, yes.
We'll sell the house
and we'll leave.
Okay?
I just wanna be with you.
Will you go upstairs with me?
You go.
I'll be right there.
I love you, babe.
I love you.
I went upstairs and
heard the shot.
End of Lindsay and me.
You said the phone rang twice.
What does that mean?
Two rings and hang up.
That was your signal, Mike.
Except the deal was off,
remember?
Then how come we have a phone call
coming from a convenient store in Highland.
Minutes before Lindsay's murder.
- You tell me.
- Your plan was in motion.
You telling us you weren't part of it.
I hope you got more
than a phone call.
You afraid we're
wasting your time, Mike?
Like Lindsay wasted yours.
You didn't answer me.
Is this all you have?
No, it ain't.
We were just wasting our time
looking into your finances
and came up with
something interesting.
Seems Doherty Systems has been
receiving payments from Katarine Salon.
Since the early '80s.
Now why would
Kitty be paying Mike?
- That's pretty mysterious.
- Yeah.
You two secretly family, Mike?
I ain't talking.
Okay.
- We'll talk to Kitty.
- That should be easy.
You know how these
hairdressers are. Talk, talk, talk.
I was there.
Were you?
But I didn't kill her.
- I can prove it.
- How?
I have the gun.
With her prints on it.
That's why she pays me.
So Kitty was the blond?
- Keep a look out.
- What?
You're supposed
to be out of here.
The plan is off.
What are you doing here?
- Kitty?
- Linds. Go upstairs.
Me and Mike can do this whole thing
right and you can get your money.
- I don't wanna do this anymore, Kitty.
- You don't have to do anything.
- I took care of it.
- This is a mess. You said it was set.
Lindsay.
I gave him what he wanted.
So don't worry.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Just like I said.
Why did you do that?
Well, duh, for you..
For tomorrow.
You better tomorrows.
Like it?
It's my Stevie Nicks thing.
Are you crazy?
You're the one who talked
about the song.
Steven's upstairs.
Just please go.
Yeah, no problem.
This is way too sloppy.
Why are you pissed at me?
I'm doing this as your friend.
This is crazy.
I was crazy, okay?
- I'm not like this.
- And I am?
I am like this, I guess.
Right?
We're selling the house and leaving here.
Leaving this all behind.
So just go.
Got it.
- No. / - Hey.
- Kitty, please.
I thought I was like
your closest friend.
Put that down.
Kitty, please.
Was I?
Kitty, my god.
I just wanna know.
Was I your friend?
Did you ever even care?
Yes. Fine.
Whatever. Please.
Just get out.
Get out of my life.
Lindsay?
♪ Journey의 'Don't Stop Believing' ♪
♪ Just a small town girl ♪
♪ living in a lonely world ♪
♪ She took the midnight train
going anywhere ♪
♪ Just a city boy born ♪
♪ and raised in south Detroit ♪
♪ He took the midnight train
going anywhere ♪
♪ A singer in a smoky room ♪
♪ A smell of wine
and cheap perfume ♪
♪ For a smile they
can share the night ♪
♪ It goes on and on and on and on ♪
♪ Strangers, waiting, ♪
♪ up and down the boulevard ♪
♪ Their shadows
searching in the night ♪
♪ Streetlight people, ♪
♪ living just to find emotion ♪
♪ Hiding somewhere in the night ♪
♪ Working hard to get my fill ♪
♪ Everybody wants a thrill ♪
♪ Paying anything to roll the dice ♪
♪ Just one more time ♪
♪ Some will win, some will lose ♪
♪ Some were born to sing the blues ♪
♪ Oh the movie never ends ♪
♪ It goes on and on and on and on ♪
♪ Don't stop believing ♪
♪ Hold on to that feeling ♪
♪ Streetlight people ♪
♪ Don't stop believing ♪
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)