Life Season02
Episode09 Badge Bunny
uniforms recognize him as felix bana.
Dealt drugs off this corner.
one gunshot wound to the chest.
Burn marks on his shirt.
Whoever shot felix pushed the gun right
up against him and pulled the trigger.
Pockets have been turned inside-out.
Someone took whatever felix was holding.
Got one gunshot but four casings.
The other three shots went that way.
The killer shoots felix at close range.
She runs.
Killer stays down there with felix
and puts three bullets into her back.
That's when she stops running.
She got tequila coming
off of her. Lots of it.
White powder up the nose.
This girl was rolling.
potter elementary.
That's way out in the valley.
She's a long way from home.
People go a lot further than
this to get what she needed.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
I know she's a cat, but
fluffy is dear to my heart.
If she needs an operation,
get her an operation.
Got a sick cat?
Bad liver.
Maybe she should lay off the booze.
That's what I tell her. But you
know cats, they can be so willful.
Felix bana.
- He sold for you.
- He sold for me?
Don't repeat what I say.
I know felix sold for you.
Now felix is dead.
Maybe you can tell me
who might want felix dead.
Okay.
You know what I do.
Then you also know that how felix
died is an occupational hazard.
Just surprised law enforcement cares.
About a dead drug dealer? We don'T.
About a dead school teacher...
found shot with felix?
We care about her.
Kendall and I started
teaching here the same year.
Kids love her.
Heidi, do you know why kendall
was in that part of town?
No, I don'T. We never go there.
Well, she'd been doing drugs.
The place she was found, it's
where you go to score drugs.
Kendall didn't score drugs.
A few beers after work or
when we played pictionary.
Did kendall ever mention a drug
dealer named felix bana to you?
Okay, look. I understand that you
want to protect your reputation,
but you need to tell us the truth if
you want to help us find who killed her.
Kendall didn't know any drug dealers.
She didn't do drugs.
Maybe not with you. Maybe...
maybe she had a boyfriend
that she did 'em with?
She didn't date much.
These kids take up all our time.
I wish I could help
you, detective. I do.
I want you to find who killed my felix.
But I don't know anything about it.
Think another minute.
This is a nice house.
These are nice chairs. I'm
sure fluffy is a nice cat.
Which means you must
have a nice businesS.
A dead school teacher.
That's the kind of thing that
really hurts a nice business.
Okay.
I'm thinking.
I'm thinking if teachers looked
like that when I was a kid,
maybe I'd have stayed at school
and made something of myself.
Kendall'S.
She left it in her desk.
Felix bana sold for justin tapp.
Narcotics says the dealing in
that area had been pretty stable.
No turf wars.
Uniforms canvassing the
area turned up nothing.
No murder weapons. No witnesses.
And ballistics didn't match the
bullet to any previous crime.
Bana was a drug dealer.
Odds are his untimely death was caused by
an unhappy customer with an unregistered gun.
That still leaves the question of
our school teacher, kendall shay.
Nothing connects her to felix bana.
Except all the devil's dandruff
up our school teacher's beak.
She's a coke head. He's a coke dealer.
Her school did a random drug test
on her last month, she came up clean.
Well, maybe something happened since then
that caused her to get all gacked out.
Hey, I got a list of five-digit
numbers in the back of her address book.
I spoke to her parents in ohio.
They said that kendall could
not have been in a better place.
She loved her job.
She loved her students.
Oh, okay. You tell
your parents everything?
Those were in her address book?
I know what those numbers are.
Those are badge numbers.
They're lapd badge numbers.
And these grades. B
plus, b, b minus, a minus.
Kendall shay dated and rated L.A.Cops.
She's a cop groupie.
Badge bunny.
What? You don't use that term out here?
We use it.
Let's look up the names
attached to the badges.
Or maybe we shouldn'T.
This doesn't change anything.
Kendall shay was found shot
dead next to a drug dealer.
It was a drug killing.
Follow the drugs.
how does she follow the drugs?
How did kendall get down there?
Her car was in her house.
How did she get down to that place?
Someone must've driven her.
Maybe someone she was dating?
Okay, you two have to
talk to the men she dated.
But you do that very carefully.
Understood.
Aw, jeez, we gotta bring cops down herE.
No, we don't have to
bring 'em down here.
We can go see 'em.
There's a death in the cop family.
It's gonna be a cop family wakE.
Called around the cop bars.
Lucky seven is having a
thing for kendall shay.
These are six lapd cops that
match those badge numbers.
Graham there got the a minus.
- Hey, charlie, you got a minute?
- Yeah.
Heard you and reese caught
the kendall shay shooting.
Yeah, bobby. Do you know kendall shay?
No, charlie, never met her.
But you question her friends,
my name just might come up.
So if it does, just let me know, okay?
- Yeah, okay, bobby.
- Thanks, charlie.
Stark, huh?
It was wtten all over his face.
Let me guess.
He got liquored up, he
strayed, he felt bad.
She took him back and it's all good now.
Close?
I really can't say.
Okay.
We'll go to the lucky seven.
We'll see if we can find
the six cops on this list.
We'll ask 'em a few questions.
And then we'll leave.
- Sounds like a plan.
- Okay.
There a bird that mates for life?
Parrot, I think. Or the goose.
I hate birds.
you knew kendall?
No, not really.
- You're just paying your respects?
- Yeah.
That's sweet.
After all, she was one of us.
You're a detective, right?
I can tell.
Do I know you?
No, but I know you.
You're charlie crews, right?
- You a friend of kendall's?
- No, you?
No, I just came to pay my respects.
I haven't seen you around the softball
games or the car washes, have I?
Why would you see me at a car wash?
Because you're A...
a what?
Aren't you A... a cop.
Oh, I haven't seen a girl cop
here when the bunnies are around.
Did you just say girl cop?
Hey, if you're a girl cop, does that
mean there are lesbo badge bunnies?
Did you just say lesbo?
Isn't that the word, "lesbo"?
They're a support group.
Charity events, fundraisers.
Car washes. I heard.
Any luck?
No. It's more crowded than I
thought. She must've been liked.
I'd like to come to my own wake.
Then you'd be dead.
Except for that part.
Just to see who'd show
up. See what they'd say.
Pretty girls in black dresses,
weeping quietly in small groups.
Or all by themselves.
Let me know when you touch down.
Hey, we need to talk to
the six men on this list.
We don't want to embarrass anyone.
So if you know where they
are, just point them out.
We'll get this over
nice and quietly--
you guys investigating kendall's death?
That's right? And you are?
Alex lauer. Officer alex lauer.
Your name isn't on that list, alex.
So maybe you want to hand it on back.
You need to talk to these guys,
I think I can help you with that.
Cody, kill that music, will you?
Okay, listen up!
We got two detectives here
investigating kendall's death.
Now I got a list in my hand with the
names of kendall's friends written on it.
Now, you all know who you are.
You all knew this was coming.
And you all know what you need to do.
So in the back room,
right now. Let's go.
So you all knew kendall shay.
She was one of ours.
Anything you need from us to find out who
did this to her, go right ahead and ask.
And you got a room full of guys out
there who feel the exact same way.
We just need to ask you a few questions.
First, any of you ever
see kendadall do drugs?
We heard she was found
all coked up, but...
that wasn't kendall.
She was wine and beer, that's it.
There are six men on this list,
but only five of you are here.
We've id'd you all.
Any of you know where
we can find sean graham?
I'm guessing sean's your partner?
Yeah.
Look, I understand you wanting
to protect your partner.
But now we have to ask
if you know where he is.
Yeah, he's, uh, upstairs.
Sean, some detectives
here need to talk with you.
You here about kendall?
We are.
She's dead.
Someone shot her.
We'd like to ask you
some questions about her.
Maybe we should be alone.
No, it's okay.
She was kendall's friend too.
Hello, heidi.
Didn't recognize you out of school.
You were seeing kendall shaw?
Yeah, for about four months.
How come you weren't
downstairs at the wake?
I got a small case of the whirlies.
Too much to drink because...
yesterday, before she died,
kendall and I had a fight.
About that ring on your finger?
Yeah, left my wife six months ago.
Can't seem to take this off though.
The fight, sean. You hit kendall.
No. She scratched me.
You do your forensic work, you'll
find my skin all up under her nails.
- What else will we find?
- Me.
All over her.
You had sex?
Where were you after the fight?
I slept it off up here.
heidi, you didn't tell me you knew sean.
I knew sean and kendall had a bad fight.
And I didn't want you thinking that he
killed her, so I didn't say anything.
It was wrong. I'm sorry.
Heidi, are you seeing sean too?
Just a little bit.
Not like kendall.
She wanted the whole
thing. The ring, you know?
And did it bother kendall that you
were seeing sean just a little bit?
Why would it?
Where were you last night, heidi?
Home. Alone.
Are you, uh, you gonna book me?
No, not just yet.
You make yourself available
to us though, okay?
And, uh, we'll have
to talk to your wife.
Then protect yourself at all times.
Vairam went back to india.
And ed's in the hospital.
He got beat up during the earthquake.
Oh, that's terrible.
He was selling water for $50 a bottle.
Why...
is it wrong...
to charge $50 for a bottle of water?
Because business isn't just about
money. It's also about people.
How we treat each other as people.
I called you.
Nine times.
I know.
You didn't call me back.
I know. I'm sorry.
Ted, why is there only
one person in your class?
One person who's enrolled.
If you're not enrolled,
you're gonna have to leave.
You know, sean has girlfriends.
That wasn't a question, was it?
No, ma'am.
'Cause I'm his wife and
of course I would know.
It was my experience my wife knew things about
me even if she didn't know that she knew it.
Sean didn't have girlfriends
when we were still together.
Like you say, I would know.
We had our problems, but
that wasn't one of them.
What kind of problems?
You're a cop. You should know.
How'd your marriage work out?
Oh, there were, uh,
there were complications.
Was sean ever violent?
He hit you?
Once.
He'd been through some
stuff on the job that day.
Once. Never again.
I'm a suspect, aren't I?
You know the answer to that.
Heidi and kendall play for
this team, the badge bunnies?
You're asking that 'cause you
want to see if heidi had motive.
Maybe she killed kendall.
Honey, we only date cops.
We eat, sleep, and
breathe law enforcement.
If you're looking at heidi, you're gonna want
to establish means, motive, and opportunity.
You want a beer?
No.
I'm working right now.
I was at a dinner party at my sister'S.
She's trying to set me up with a friend.
Nice guy. Not a cop.
You know how to use a gun, diane?
I surely do.
Sean took me to the gun range
when we were first dating.
Did you like that?
I liked a lot of things
about him back then.
He wasn't the first cop you dated.
That wasn't a question either.
No, it wasn'T.
You were one of 'em.
Cop groupie. Badge bunny.
Yes, I was. Till I married sean.
And then I wasn't one of them anymore.
Detective, if I had met you back then, I
would've wanted you to take me to the gun range.
It would've been my pleasure.
You only date cops?
That's right.
Because cops risk their lives and
what's wrong with a little extra love?
That's pretty close. You date cops?
No, I am a cop.
I need to ask you
about kendall and heidi.
- They ever fight over sean?
- Fight? No.
Kendall loved sean. So does heidi.
We all love sean.
Heidi know how to use a gun?
Sure. Most of us can shoot.
If you're done, we have practice.
Yeah, sure.
.........
Only one occupant per stall.
I'm a close friend of the range
master. He wrote me a note.
So you found a dead girl
in an alley full of drugs?
Yeah. That's part of the job, right?
And all that time at the bar?
Who are you, my sponsor?
No, I'm your friend.
Mind if I try your shooter?
How come you don't have
anything on your walls?
- Like what?
- Like art or something.
Hey, there's a pool.
We should go swimming.
You want to go swimming, detective?
I want to ask you a question.
Your partner already questioned us.
I thought this was a social visit.
One question.
What?
Now I want to try yours.
Oh, I think this might be too
much gun for a little gal like you.
Did you just call me gal?
Gal? No, no.
I said "cal... ifornia woman."
Be
careful--
it has a kick.
how do you tell a good
cop from a bad cop?
Isn't that kind of your job to
tell good people from bad people?
You see cops differently than I do.
You mean naked?
You live your lives observing cops.
Can you tell the good from the bad?
- Yeah, we can.
- How?
Okay.
It's all about taste.
You're a good cop.
Mm,good cop.
Definitely good cop.
Now we're going swimming.
Luckily I have a
swimsuit under my clothes.
Oh,you don't have your swimsuit on.
Oh,yeah.
I forgot.
I don'T.
There are naked women in the pool.
- Ted.
- Yeah?
I've made a decision.
What's that,charlie?
I'm going swimming.
No man would hold that against you.
BobbY.
Is cathy here?
Hey,this is a nice pad.
You should have a party here sometime.
Cathy!
You out there?
bobby,is that you?
You get outta there right now!
Bobby,I didn't
know you were--
brother and sister.
Get dressed.
What did I tell you about
playing around at my station?
I'll take her home.
And you get back to what you were doing.
You didn't think to mention
you were bobby's sister?
Would you have let me kiss you if I did?
They look nothing alike.
I--I never
would've guessed.
Cathy,get dressed.
outside!
Crews.
Thanks. I'm on my way.
You wanna get kendall's killer?
Maybe I'll,uh...
I'll hold onto this.
I'm not used to doing this sober.
It's kind of the same thing.
Except no one gets sick.
I'll be the judge of that.
Call came in over the tip line.
The gun that shot kendall and that drug
dealer is in that house right there.
Let's serve a warrant,shall we?
You two drive here together?
No.
We just happened to get
here at the same time.
Is that glitter on your face?
I told cathy over and over. No
man likes that glitter stuff.
Who's cathy?
His sister.
Call,tip line,gun that shot kendall.
House,warrant.
That's not your gun.
You must be fluffy.
Fluffy?
What should I name him,kimba?
Kimba was a lion.
That was simba.
Kimba was first.
Why've you got glitter on?
Found this in the garage.
Welcome to the frame job.
Got some burnt skin and fabric here
on the muzzle which makes me think
that this was the gun that was pushed up
against felix's shirt when he was shot.
And why would I shoot my own man?
Maybe he was stealing.
Maybe he was unhappy
with his health plan.
And maybe there's a dead badge bunny and
all you cops just want someone to pay for it.
I hope that piece of
cottontail was worth it.
Officer stark,why don't you go
ahead and cuff up mr. Tapp here.
Think they brought a rope?
Why don't you let us take him in?
Why don't you go sleep it off
in the back of your car,sean?
Stark,what would you do if it was
your sister he shot in the back?
I'd go home and get drunk.
I can't go home.
You can't be here.
You know that.
Kendall was one of ours.
She loved us.
Let us take him in.
It's not gonna happen.
Are you gonna draw down on me?
Does it hurt that much
that you want it all over?
Because you take that gun
out and it's all over,sean.
You're a cop.
So are you.
Come on,sean.
Let's go.
You did this.
How--how did
you do this?
It was easy.
I just told them that
you killed a man in jail.
With your hands.
You did?
Well,that's what I told the guys.
What did you tell the girls?
Ted.
I'm getting married in a month.
I'd like you to be there.
we know she was a school teacher.
We know she loved cops.
We know she had no
history with narcotics.
Fig?
You want me to eat that?
It's the sweetest of all fruits.
55% sugar.
You know it's a fig that
the snake offered to eve?
The snake?
Most people think it was an apple.
It wasn'T.
It might not even have been a snake.
Just some kind of serpent
that led her astray.
We know sean dated her.
We know sean showed up last night
itching to pull his gun and end it all.
We know the murder weapon.
An unregistered gun was found.
And tapp,a drug dealer,was
booked into central.
So...
do we really want to keep looking?
What we don't know is how kendall
ended up down there packed with drugs.
Sean said they were only drinking.
What if they were taking drugs?
How long after you do
coke can they test for it?
You can detect the enzyme the body
makes when you do coke for 30 days.
Let's get a warrant for a test.
You're kind of like an expert witness.
Yeah,I kind of am.
Fig?
We're looking for your partner.
I haven't seen him today.
What do you want with
him? Maybe I can help.
Got a warrant here for a drug test.
You gonna take away his
gold medal in the 400 relay?
We'd rather not.
If he passes his blood
test,we're all done here.
Uh,yeah,him just taking that
test is the problem though.
why's that?
You give sean that test
now,you question him now,
that's just ammunition that the defense
will use to get that scumbag tapp off.
Not interested in finding out how
kendall ended up down there that night?
Not if asking those questions
puts doubt in the jury's mind.
No,I'm not.
Look,kendall's dead,okay?
Now let's put tapp away
and find some peace in here.
That's what a real cop would do.
Someone here not a real cop?
Hey,you tell me.
I mean,is that a settlement or a
badge you're wearing on your belt?
It is not what we carry with us,but
what we let go that defines who we are.
Yeah,what did you let go?
irish coffee?
You work a little whiskey in there?
Yeah,hair of the dog.
You want some?
Something you'd like to share?
That's what i was gonna ask you.
My partner has a super power.
You wanna guess what it is?
Does she fly?
No,tragically. Not anymore.
But you're getting warm.
all right,we're all cops
here. I'll be blunt with you.
My partner used to use. And now she
can tell when other people are using.
You wanna tell us something?
Yeah,I'll let sean know that
you were looking for him.
Do me a favor.
Clean up that mess when you're done.
You sure?
Yeah. I'm sure.
Okay.
Maybe it was an allergy
you were picking up on.
It wasn't an allergy.
Alex lauer's a solid cop.
He's not a suspect.
There's no way I can get
a warrant for a drug test.
Let's ask the experts.
Someone who could tell a
good cop from a bad cop.
how exactly do you do that?
I'm not gonna show you that.
Maybe reese can help you out.
All right,let's get in there.
we got this.
What?
We'll let you know if we need any help.
But...
there are five badge bunnies in there.
Ladies,thanks for coming down.
Is this about kendall's killing?
We just have a few follow-up questions.
Questions about sean?
I'd rather not hear my husband's
name come out of your mouth.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
We're widening the investigation.
We're not just looking
into sean anymore.
We're looking into his partner too.
Any of you seen alex take drugs?
See,that's the weird part.
'Cause we found your friend full of
coke,but no one ever saw anyone using?
I don't know what department you're in.
But the guys we know
don't mess with that stuff.
Okay,did alex and kendall
ever spend any time together?
Like sex?
Not alex.
None of us spent time
with alex like that.
why not?
alex is married.He's got kids.
Not like sean?
Not like sean.
Diane.
Heidi said your husband's name again.
I'm sorry.
Is there something you'd
like to tell us about alex?
You think he had something
to do with that girl's death?
You tell us.
Is he a good cop?
I thought he was.
Why'd you change your mind?
Last year,I was having
a rough time with sean.
Didn't really know who to talk to.
So you talked to his partner?
Alex listened to me.
Had a few drinks,a few more.
At the lucky seven?
No,not there.
He took me somewhere else.
Some other bar.
Not the kind of place
I would usually go to.
Not a cop bar.
Were there drugs?
It was the kind of place
where you could get them.
I didn't do anything.
I don't think I did.
And then I did not want to be there.
Didn't want to be with him.
So you left.
Did alex kill that girl?
If he was partying with kendall,he
might've taken her there.
If we can put them together
on that same night...
diane,what was the name of
that bar alex took you to?
Stubb'S.
I know that place.
What do you know about that place?
I know if you go there,take antiseptic,and I
know it's around the corner from the crime scene.
I hate cops.
No offense.
Run around trying to fix everything
and you're the ones who are broken.
We called the owner.
You tend bar over at stubb's?
Walk to work.Must be nice.
I've gone green.
You know these two?
Yeah,isn't that that couple from that tv dance
contest who won all that money doing the tango?
Tango?
Yeah,okay.What are
you doing this weekend?
I was gonna organize my shoes.
Why?
Not this weekend.
Murder happened here.
You work around here.
You live around here.
You know how it happens.
We take you down for questioning.
Papers get shuffled.
You find yourself in lock-up.
There's an old warrant out.
Now you're
out in county--
He comes into the bar.
How often?
Was,uh,every few months.
Lately it's been a few times a week.
You know his name?
No.
He likes it when I call him boss.
Like,uh,"another beer,boss?"
How about her?
The other day...
with him.
They were drinking hard.
She was crying about breaking up
with her boyfriend or something.
They make any trips to the bathroom?
Yeah.
She didn't want to
go,but boss convinced her.
After he ran out of
cash,I asked him to leave.
And now I'm leaving.
A drunk cop with no money
and a need for drugs.
A drunk cop with no money,a
need for drugs,and a gun.
A few times a week?
Alex was on a downward spiral,but
none of his buddies knew?
Maybe they didn't want to know.
'Cause then they'd have
to do something about it.
Yeah,I guess they would.
We got one jittery smackhead bartender.
That's not a good eyewitness
against a career cop like alex.
We can get some better witnesses.
How's about a beer,boss?
Hey,two waters,please.
To kendall.
Hey,do me a favor.
My partner here just broke
up with her boyfriend.
Now don't say anything.
She's proud.
I told her not to date cops.
She wouldn't listen.
Women.
And why are you telling me this?
Because,well,'cause we heard that you're the guy
to go to when you break up with your boyfriend.
You know,that you have a soft shoulder.
We heard you took diane out when
she needed a shoulder to cry on.
You talking about my diane?
Well,whether she's your diane or
not,I think it'd be a question for her.
We're talking about your wife.
You took diane out?
I didn't take diane out,okay?
You might want to talk
to diane about that,sean.
You might want to talk to
diane about a lot of things.
But you should talk to her about that.
Took kendall out too,when she
needed a shoulder to cry on.
Kendall?
What about kendall?
All she wanted to do
was talk about you,sean.
And alex was there.
Got her all coked up,right,boss?
And then when there were no more
drugs,you went looking for more.
You rolled that dealer,and then what?
Kendall saw it.
She freaked,and then you freaked?
Been there.
You passed your drug test,sean.
You think alex'll pass his?
Hey,how long have we been partners?
Does any of this sound like me?
Come on!
You two need to go.
Yeah,okay.
Tight cluster!
Just like they taught us at the academy.
Remember those drills?
Remember the hours on the range?
Remember what they told us?
That when the time came,when we had to
shoot,we wouldn't even have to think about it.
We'd shoot like a cop.
Kendall had that pattern on her back.
Three shots.
Tight cluster.
We all had it drilled into us.
You didn't even have to think about it.
Just like we were trained,right?
Something you want to
ask your partner,sean?
Where's your off-duty piece,alex?
Here it is.
You know it's illegal to
carry an unregistered firearm.
Tell them that that is not my gun.
Tell them.
Are--are you gonna let these two
come in here to our place and do this?
Seanie.
Good night.Lovely to see you.
Take me home,fin.
I've done enough damage for one night.
You're not fin.
No,I'm not fin.
You're charlie crews,aren't you?
It's a real pleasure to meet you.
I've been meaning to call you.
You have?
Yes.
A man like yourself.
You are the perfect person to help out
with some of these charities I'm into.
Why would that be?
To go through what you
did and not be broken?
did and be made better?
We all like to think we could do that.
But which one of us could?
I got a photo of you.
At the funeral of a
slain police officer.
I was a cop a long time.
There's so many of us
who gave their lives.
This photo was from jim dunn's funeral.
Poor jim dunn.
A suicide.
Many of us do go that way too,detective.
I think that photo
connects you to jack reese.
To the bank of los angeles shootout.
To all that missing money.
To my murdered friends,and to
me going to jail for 12 years.
And I think this is a kidnapping.
Kidnapping?What does that really mean?
We're not kids.
No one's napping.
We're just two guys talking.
That's all.
No,no,you misunderstand me.
This isn't a kidnapping.
This,detective,is a kidnapping.