previously on life...
the police report says
she was out of the house.
Rachel seybolt was there
the night of the murders.
hey,uh,you know mark
rawls,don't ya,arthur?
you told his son you
could get him out of jail,
Then you broke
his son's heart.
What does the bank of los angeles hold up
have to do With the detective who put you away?
They both have
jack reese in common.
He's our suspect now.
What did you say about
the bank of los angeles?
You're stepping
over a line here.
You might wanna step back.
son,you keep going where you're
going,And you're gonna find trouble.
And you would do well to
keep my daughter out of it.
kyle hollis,jack
reese's informant?
There's a mug shot here
From his last arrest.
This is the picture rachel drew.
That's the killer.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about
where i'm going next.
"fill it up"
this is a maximum
security facility
You just can't
stay away,can you?
If i didn't know any better,I'd
say you liked it here.
You ever wanna come back,We got
a room ready for ya,detective.
Well,you better keep it
ready,'Cause i just might need it.
You two play nice,now.
Yeah.
Use your words.
how ya doin'?
Getting by.
How's life in the world?
Gettin' by.
I'll tell you,though...
Out in the yard today,Felt
like earthquake weather.
Yeah?
Felt that way.
You need something,Mr. Crews?
I do.
I'm not sure what
i can do for you.
I need to find somebody.
Been under for
about 12 years.
None of your police friends
can help you with this?
No. No,this guy's
more in your world.
My world.
- Prison.
I need to find this guy.
We both know who has the best
information About how to find¡ª
How to find one of us.
I guess this will be the
thank-You For what you did.
For getting that
guy that killed my son.
I guess so.
Tell me his name.
I'll reach out and
see what i can touch.
Hollis.
Kyle hollis.
And what's Mr. Hollis done That you're
here without your pretty partner?
I have some questions i want to ask him.
Questions.
Okay.
Earthquake weather?
Sure feels that way.
domestic disturbance call.
People heard screaming and yelling.
He was banging on the
door,yelling to be let in.
She was yelling
back to take a hike.
Neighbor said
that was usual.
But when the neighbors heard the missus
screaming,"I'll put a bullet in you,"
They decided maybe a call
to 911 was a good idea.
We roll up just in time To see the
blast come through the door One shot,
got him right
through the heart.
Two hours his dinner sat
on the table,Two hours!
Dinner in the morning?
Apparently,he
worked nights.
if she shot him through the
door,Why is there blood on her hands?
It's not blood,it's meat sauce.
Why is there meat
sauce on her hands?
I really don't know.
And where's the gun?
well... We're thinking...
She threw it in there.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly presents
sync:
Ö¥Ê¿µ°¸â -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Life
Season 01 Episode 11
constance griffiths
ex-attorney for charlie crews
you're aware that most men Who come out of
prison after 12 years Just end up back inside.
Detective crews
isn't most men.
How is he different?
Detective crews is innocent.
When he went in,he was innocent.
Did he come out that way?
he comes home o hours late,And
she shoots him through the door.
I'm guessing they had other
issues in their marriage.
Apparently so.
we cannot find
the gun in there.
Keep looking.
We're looking,detective.
We came through the door about
two minutes After she popped him.
Not a lot of places
she coulda stashed it.
But it is just not there.
You are free to
look for it yourself.
Perhaps detectives Have
better eyesight than us grunts.
Is there something maybe
i can help you with?
Someone wants
to talk to ya.
Crews.
how's the world,Mr. Crews?
You tell me.
Found that man
you're looking for.
Where is he?
He's in indio.
He's been there five years.
He's got a daughter,new name.
Reverend orson parker.
Reverend?
Found the lord or
something like that.
When i put the word out i was
looking for kyle hollis,It came ck...
A lot of other people
are looking for him.
I guess they all just wanna
ask him some questions too,huh?
I gotta go.
Don't wanna miss
my hour in the yard.
They can't find the gun.
i told her we
couldn't find the gun.
And we can't leave
until they find the gun.
We're doing our
best,detective.
Maybe the plants are making
the boys A little absentminded.
I think you have to smoke
it for that to happen.
Well,i wouldn't know
about that myself...
Charlie?
I gotta go deal
with something.
Will you cover for me?
You have to go
deal with something?
We've got a dead guy in the hall,Half
an acre of thc in the living room,
We can't find the gun,And you
have to go deal with something?
Will you cover for me?
sure,charlie,no problem.
We'll partner on up while you're
gone,Ain't that right,detective?
the buddha was asked
if he ever felt anger.
"Of course," said the buddha.
The buddha was asked if he ever
felt the desire To strike another.
"Of course," said the buddha.
"But if i am connected to
all things," Said the buddha,
"Hurting another is hurting myself.
And how does that better me?"
Because it just does.
Cop kid,huh?
Dad was a cop,you're a cop.
You know,my dad?
Meat packer.
Which,as it turns out,is
not as romantic as it sounds.
But you...Daughter
of captain jack reese.
Man!
That must come in pretty handy being jack
reese's daughter When you want a leg up,huh?
Let's just find the gun,okay?
Focus on the job,huh?
I guess that's how
you become a detective.
Where you going?
I'm gonna search somewhere else.
Reese,what's up?
What's up? Are you
planning on coming back?
I just left.
Crews,it's been two hours.
Crews,is everything okay there?
Yeah,i just gotta...
One thing i need
to take care of here,
And then,uh...
I'll be right back.
i was****
i was guilty****
*****
The fire is here.
we burn every
day,we are not right!
i was****
Hallelujah,brothers and sisters.
you can****
you can*******
but he****
just****
can you turn that back on,please?
That's my dad.
I kinda wanted to
see him,you know,so...
Could you turn
that back on,please?
Maybe you wanna
open that door.
I wanna ask you
something first.
What you wanna do is
open that door,officer.
Every time we're together,
You got a look as though There's
something you wanna say to me.
I've been known to misread A
woman's intentions on occasion,
So let me just
ask you,detective.
Is there something
you wanna say to me?
All right,bobby.
What i wanna ask you Is how come
you weren't there for your partner?
They asked you at the trial
About the cuts on his hands.
Charlie said he got
cut during an arrest.
And why didn't
you back that up?
Because i didn't see it.
Well,i didn't ask
if you saw it,officer.
I asked why you didn't
back up your partner.
You wanna know why?
Because i.A.D. Put me in a
room And they told me that
if i lied And backed up
charlie, I'd go to jail too.
Wait-- You
hear that?
I don't hear nothin'.
Man... These folks
got a lot of pet mice.
These aren't pets.
This... This is meat.
Meat for wha...
Now,what do you
think was in there?
Want my guess?
A snake.
A big one.
I need an ambulance
immediately to 12 west athens.
You coming to
get my daddy?
Why would you say that?
The guys who did this,Cut
me,they were looking for him.
I wanna take a
look at this,okay?
You're a policeman?
Am i going to die?
'Cause...That's
my blood,and...
it's... It's supposed to be inside me.
Am i gonna die?
Not for a long time.
How do you know that?
I can see.
What can you see?
I see you older.
Can you see it?
No.
Sure you can.
You can see tomorrow.
You imagine yourself in tomorrow...
And there you are.
You can do that.
Look.
Okay.
Do you know the guys
who did this to you?
They were looking for your father?
Yes.
Did you tell them where he was?
I don't know where he is.
He's been gone
since yesterday.
How come you're here?
I didn't call you.
They cut the lines. Why are you here?
Came here to be with you. Hmm?
Be with you while you were
waiting for the ambulance.
So you didn't
have to be alone.
I don't know you,do i?
No. You don't know me.
Can i see my daddy?
Can you do that for me?
Can you turn that back on,please?
*****
I made this tape.
The fire is now.
I made this so...
I could still watch
him when he went away.
we burn every day
we are not right!
Reese.
no,this isn't reese.
Who is this?
It's kyle hollis,detective crews.
I hear you been
looking for me.
The fire is not
some distant image.
The fire is now.
I'm in your house,kyle.
What the hell
are you doing there?
I was looking for you.
I wasn't the first person
to get here,you understand?
Somebody else got here.
How is she?
She's gonna be okay.
Where are you?
I'm in trouble,that's where i am.
Well,i'm sorry to hear that.
I'll bet you are.
They all want me dead.
Why'd you call me?
You have money,you have a
badge, You can get me out of l.A.
Meet me at the bank of
los angeles in two hours.
You know which branch,right?
You're gonna be okay. Okay?
They're gonna
take care of you.
They'll take care of you.
You're gonna be okay now.
are you hurt anywhere else?
Do you have any other pain?
Are you allergic
to any medications?
Gimme some abdominal dressings Two large
bore ivs,and get some fluids on board.
You called my dad
kyle. On the phone.
That's what the
other men called him.
The men who were looking
for him Called my dad kyle.
You wanna kill my dad too?
he's the one.
He's the one that did this to me.
He's the one.
He's the one! He's the one
who tried to kill me! He--
Stop. Do not move.
We are looking
for a burmese python.
Its name is cato.
It is a constrictor.
It is not venomous.
Try not to let it wrap itself
Around any of your appendages.
What could a python eat?
What can or what does it eat?
Could it eat a gun?
They don't like anything cold.
Could it eat a warm gun?
They're not fond of metal.
What about a warm gun
Covered in meat sauce?
Yeah. It'd go for that.
You find the gun?
The wife fed it
to her pet snake.
That's why she had
meat sauce on her hands.
Did you find the snake?
We're looking
for it right now.
You planning on coming by?
What i'm doing...
it's gonna take
a little longer.
Is this the part where i
ask what it is you're doing?
Probably better if you didn't.
Nice ride.
Thank you. You want it?
What do you mean?
I mean,do you
want the car?
You're just gonna gimme your car?
You said you liked it.
Just like that?
Just like that.
This isn't some trick?
The trick is to not
become attached to the car.
What do you think he's doing?
I wouldn't know.
You think it's about a girl.
Charlie gets lots of girls.
I wouldn't know.
I don't think it
was about a girl.
Because now that i think
about it,Kinda had that look.
Oh,yeah? What
look is that?
A look that he was about to do
something He'd be better off not doing.
Look like he had
that look to you?
*****kyle
ted earley
ex-ceo attercliffe capital
you say charlie saved
your life in prison.
How exactly did he do that?
He convinced some,um...people
to leave me alone.
How did he convince them?
In a way that
i was unable to.
You mean with violence.
If crews was set up And
found the person who did it,
What do you think he would do?
What would you do?
Too bad you can't kill me.
Come alone?
I used to think
none of us were alone.
Now i'm not so sure.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means i came alone,kyle.
You surprised
i called you?
I made you call me,kyle.
- Yeah?
How'd you do that?
I squeezed carl ames.
Ames squeezed jack
reese,and out popped you.
But you wanna know what's
it got to do with you.
You wanna know What's it got
to do with that dead family.
You get me to l.A.X.,
You get me on a plane With a
suitcase full of that settlement cash,
Then i'll call you with
what you wanna know.
Yeah,okay.
I got photos,i
got documents.
Anything happens to me,I
get tortured or i get dead,
Those documents and
photos,they go away.
Yeah,okay.
You killed my
friends,kyle.
When you killed that
family,you killed my friends.
Like fruit,kyle?
This is a pluot.
A dappled dandy,to be exact.
I grew this one myself.
Some people call
'em dinosaur eggs
Because,um,That's what
they kinda look like.
Dinosaur eggs.
Now...i,uh,I know that there is all
sorts of information You wanna tell me.
Questions you
think i wanna ask.
But that's not
important,because...
Today... I have only
one decision to make.
You shouldn't have
killed my friends,kyle.
Let me ask you a
question,detective.
I.E.D. Comes to you.
Said what they said to me.
What would you have done?
step forward.
Slowly.
Behind me,isn't it?
Yep.
Step forward slowly,please.
Let's go,get up. Let's go!
jennifer conover
ex-wife of charlie crews
have you seen your ex-Husband
Since his release from prison?
Once.
Is he a different man than
the one who went to prison?
I couldn't tell
you who he is now.
Thanks for coming,jennifer.
Well,if i didn't, you'd
pull my husband over
Or leave a horse
on my lawn,right?
I wanna ask you something.
what,charlie?
What could you
possibly want to ask me?
I want to ask you
for your forgiveness.
All that time i was
in prison,i was angry.
I was angry at you.
But we were so
young when it happened.
You were so young.
Anyone would've
done what you did.
Charlie-- -
Let me finish.
I was angry at the wrong person,And
now i'm asking for your forgiveness.
Okay.
I gotta go.
How's it going
in there,kyle?
The first six months i was in
solitary,I did pushups everyday,
and i never talked to myself.
The next six months,i stopped
doing pushups And i-- I confess.
I did talk a little to myself.
The six months after
that,Those next six months...
Kyle... You don't wanna
know what happened then.
is that a new car?
Do you like it?
Well,it looks,uh,Roomy.
Tell me what you found
out about jack reese.
Every year,jack reese Would give
$250 to his favorite charity.
Right,like clockwork.
All through the '70s and '80s.
That $250 check Would go
to the blessed sisters.
Is everything
okay with you?
Ted,i'm fine.
Okay.
And then?
And then...
Just four months after
the bank of l.A. Robbery,
The blessed sisters receive an
anonymous check For $4 million.
Anonymous.
An untraceable cashier's check
From a cayman island account.
Now,who does that,charlie?
You give to a charity
to take the deduction.
You don't send in a
check with no name.
Four months after the robbery?
So what do you think?
Either he's laundering or...
Or?
Or it's guilt
money. But...
That's bank of
l.A. Money,ted.
Charlie?
I'm not alfred,am i?
Alfred?
You know,batman and alfred.
No. No,ted. You're not alfred.
I'm not higgins.
Charlie,tell me
i'm not higgins!
Hello?
hey,how's your day,jack?
It's charlie crews.
What the hell do you want?
Do you know what i wish?
I wish that the day
before i was arrested,
Someone had told me that this was
gonna be my last day As a free man.
I'm not sure i
care about that.
Well,you should,jack.
'Cause that's what
i'm telling you now.
This is your last day.
Where's the preacher?
We saw you in
indio,detective.
So we're gonna
ask you once more.
Where's the preacher?
Are you upside-Down
or am i upside-Down?
It's kind of hard to tell.
Should we do him now?
Not yet.
I know you.
You were standing in the park with jack
reese When he was arguing with ames.
You killed ames.
You're not really cops,are you?
No,not really.
Check the trunk.
But we took your gun.
You're a real
popular guy,kyle.
jennifer conover
ex-wife of charlie crews
if you could say one thing to
charlie crews,What would it be?
I'd want him to live his life.
Does that make sense?
what are you doing?
What are you doing?!
I got right,you understand?
After what happened,Who
i was,I got right.
Fire found me,cleaned
me out,I got right.
I got right!
Made myself a new man.
Made myself a family.
I got right!
What are you doing?!
Tell me.
Okay.
I was jack reese's
confidential informant.
Worked for him too.
I would get calls to pick up
envelopes,Drop off envelopes from that bar.
From your bar.
Those envelopes
were filled with cash.
Your friend seybolt was laundering
money For jack and his friends. Okay?
And one night
i got the call.
"Go straighten tom out."
He was skimming.
I went there.
It got out of hand.
Wife was there.
She was screaming.
The kid...
I was jacked up.
I... I killed that family.
But i didn't set you up.
What are you doing?!
Some of the bank money
they-- They took¡ª
It got washed through that
bar,and that's all i know.
I got no papers.
I got no documents.
That's all i know.
I got right.
The fire found me.
I killed that family,but
i didn't set you up.
I didn't. I didn't.
where are you,charlie?
I'll send some of our
people to come and get you.
You need to come in now.
There's something
i gotta do first.
Please.
What are you doing?
Dig a hole,Fill it up.
you know,You'll need a warrant
to cut that out of there.
Basic fourth amendment stuff.
You look like
crap,charlie.
Where you been?
I need you to do
something for me.
Both of us?
It's 1991,jack.
You got real problems, crews.
You're up here
with your swat buddies,
Six guys come out of
the bank down there,
And you take out five of 'em.
Then you start
washing the cash.
Then more people start to die.
Then my friend tom gets
into business with you.
And... He and
his family die too.
Ames dies.
Why,jack?
He starts drinking himself
to death when i went away.
He feel guilty
about what happened?
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
It's 1991,jack.
It's all connected.
Hollis connects
you to the bank.
Hollis connects you to
the seybolt killings.
Hollis is connected to me,and
now,jack,Now i am connected to you.
I thought i told you to
keep my daughter out of this.
Your daughter doesn't know
who i'm up here talking with.
Her partner said he needed
her,and that's all she needed.
Come in now,jack.
It's over.
Hollis is gonna roll on you.
You wanna make
a deal with me.
Come in now,jack.
Get right with your
daughter,cut a deal with the d.A.
It's over. It's done.
It's all connected,isn't it?
I think,detective crews,I'll
stay up here a while longer.
Charlie,it's over.
Hollis killed those
people,connie,that family.
But he's not the
one who set me up.
It's bigger than hollis.
It doesn't stop with him.
I know.
But let somebody else do it.
Let somebody else do it.
I got a lot of
questions for you.
You may not like the answers.
I usually don't.
This is crews.
Hey,charlie. Jack reese.
This a good time for you?
Thought about
my offer,jack?
We can get to
that in a minute.
First i want to
congratulate you.
You caught the killer.
You're next. You know that.
That is not gonna happen.
Because,detective crews,I
have something you want.
What could you
have that i want?
I have the girl.
The one you're looking for.
I have rachel seybolt.
You don't know her.
No,crews,you don't know her.
You didn't even recognize her
When she was bleeding in your arms.
You don't know her,crews.
i need the status
of a patient,a girl.
Last name hollis.
just one moment.
Hmm,that's strange.
What is?
Her record is
not here anymore.
It was here before.
I know,'cause i
checked her in myself.
Let me try again.
I'm not good with technology.
No. That is so odd.
I can't understand.