Previously on life...
Is that Mark Rawls over there?
You know Mark Rawls, don't you, Arthur?
You told his son you
could get him out of jail.
And then you killed him.
Send me somewhere now, and I'll talk.
Start talking now.
I killed the kid.
The thing about Olivia, Charlie, is...
She's marrying your father.
She seems really nice. Really.
Life Season02
Episode06 'Did You Feel That?'
Chasing after the
world brings only chaos.
Allowing it to come to
be brings only peace.
Retreat from the world,
and it shall pursue you.
To exist, to allow the world to exist,
all things at once, all things as one.
This is the path to
serenity, to balance.
See yourself as part of the world...
You having a moment?
I know every moment is now,
but now we're ten minutes late.
Did you feel that?
Does someone always have to say that?
I'm standing right next
to you. Yes. I felt that.
- It was an earthquake.
- it was a tremor.
Did you feel that?
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
All right. Here's the
latest. Four freeways cut.50 fires.
Power grids and water
services out city-wide.
Busted water mains.
Dorm collapse at L.A.U.
Now, according to this
lapd emergency manual,
county emergency operation center will be
calling us with our emergency assignments.
So buckle up. It's an emergency.
He's reading with his foot.
No, he's just using
it to turn the pages.
It must be his first earthquake.
Detective Crews.
Officer Danny Ritenour, state corrections
office. We're having a little emergency.
Yeah? Us too.
Yeah, well, that earthquake just
facilitated the escape of a prisoner
that you put away last
year, one Arthur Tins.
What happened?
He was on a work detail when the
earthquake hit, and tins got away.
He's in Los Angeles?
The mother of the
kids Tins killed--
I do have her address,
and we will notify her.
Good. She testified in the
penalty phase of tins's trial.
Now, is there anyone else
he'd wanna even things up with?
'Cause we have to contact these people.
Uh, no. Tins confessed. No one
gave him up. The victim's dead.
Okay. We're just trying to
cover every angle. Thank you.
Hey, have we spoken before?
I don't think so.
You have any connection to
the corrections department?
No, sir. Not anymore.
Good luck today.
Yeah, okay.
Should we tell him that's not a weight-bearing
wall and it won't do him any good?
Arthur Tins is not
gonna go after anyone.
That weasel's gonna find a rock
to hide under and stay hidden.
It's not a question of who
Arthur Tins is gonna go after.
It's a question of who's
gonna go after Arthur Tins.
Mark Rawls?
Paroled out three months ago.
I don't think I like what you're saying.
I don't think I like
what I'm saying either.
You're saying we have to stop
Arthur Tins from getting killed?
Yeah. I guess we do.
Yeah, I guess you don'T.
Since when do you go by the book?
You don't even have
a regulation haircut.
I go by the book.
I go by this book, the
lapd emergency manual,
since about an hour ago when the earth opened
up and tried to swallow Los Angeles whole.
Besides, we have a lot
of things to do today.
And none of them are stopping
crimes that haven't happened yet.
Oh, god, this is it! Hold on,
everyone! It's the big one!
That's funny. Real funny.
Okay. No mug shots. Sorry,
lapd computers are down.
Arthur Tins. Low rent scam artist.
Last year, he killed the
10-year-old son of Mark Rawls.
Mark Rawls happened to be doing
ten years inside at the time.
Arthur Tins confesses to killing
Mark Rawls's 10-year-old son.
He gets life.
Yeah, I heard about that confession.
I heard Tins wasn't talking, and
then I heard two lapd detectives
that look a lot like you two took tins to go
see rawls in the joint he was doing his time in.
Tins took one look at the hard
case Rawls and sang like a bird.
- Is that what you heard?
- That's what I heard.
Rawls got paroled three months ago.
Tins escaped this morning, so
now they are both out there--
lapd computers are down.
The prison grapevine is not.
And by tonight, Arthur
Tins is gonna be dead.
Ooh, two psychos killing each
other. You know what that is?
That's a civic
improvement project, okay?
Like I said before, we're not the future crimes
unit, and we all have our assignments out there--
Even your very own Tidwell.
Oh, well, how is Tidwell gonna get his assignment
out there if Tidwell can't leave his doorway?
Tidwell is working on it.
And as for you two, today...
you're on foot patrol.
Hold on!
Did you feel that?
Tidwell said foot patrol.
We just happen to be patrolling
the street where Mark Rawls lives.
How do you get over something like that?
Someone like Tins killing your son?
You sit in your cell every day, think about
what you'd do to Tins if you ever got the chance.
And that gets you over it?
Call for backup. We're gonna
take Rawls in when we see him.
Maybe you should, uh...
Button up a little.
Button up?
You know, we're goin' into a
building full of violent ex-offenders.
You ever see the cartoon where
the wolf is staring at the lamb,
but what he really sees is lamb chops?
Lamb chops.
Very kind of you two to stop by...
to see how I came through the quake.
Always a pleasure to see you.
You want some mint jelly with that?
As you can see, I'm doing all right.
Nothing structural.
I'd think there'd be a lot of
people out there needing your help.
Like Arthur Tins?
Oh, Arthur Tins is a guest of
the great state of california.
What kind of help could he
possibly be needing, detective?
Tins escaped. This morning.
He's out.
- No. Not angry enough. Try again.
- What?
We come here to tell you the man who
killed your son has escaped from prison,
and you go with, "he's out."
You're lying to us.
How were you planning on
spending your day today, Mark?
I did you a favor.
Now you do me one and
walk away from all this.
Okay. I'll do you a favor.
My partner's gonna take her
gun out for this next part.
You know the drill.
You should walk away.
He put a bullet in my son.
It's my job on the street
to die. You should walk away.
Yeah. There is a lot of things
I should do.
California penal code 12021 is a
person who has been convicted of--
He killed my son!
What would you do, huh?
You know what you'd do.
No killing today, all right, Mark?
Why not? Nothing else to do.
Get up.
All right, central's not processing
new prisoners 'cause of the quake.
So book him in Valley division
and forward me the paperwork.
We have an assignment to get back to.
- I guess you really are a cop.
- I guess I am.
You had to do it.
Doesn't mean I have to like it.
Oh, come on. Go direct traffic...
it'll make you feel better.
It's Tins!
Is he okay?
What are you thinkin'?
I'm thinking that when I woke up today I
wasn't thinking that I'd have to kill somebody.
Now you think you have to?
No. Now I think I want to.
Okay, see, as your commanding officer, I hear
something like that, I have to take your weapon.
So it's a good thing I didn't hear that.
When did Tins get so smart?
Prison gives you a lot of
time for self-improvement.
Yeah, prison.
You go in afraid of your own shadow,
and you come out a full-blown psycho.
They all come out
worse than they went in.
Well, maybe not everyone.
Yeah, but how did Tins find us?
Location status check. D-247,
400 block. Alvarado street.
Our call for backup.
Tins heard it off the radio.
We told him where Rawls was.
We thought we were trailing
him, he was trailing us.
Wait a minute.
How'd he even know you were gonna
go see Rawls in the first place?
State corrections didn't even know
tins escaped until ten minutes ago.
Well, if they didn't know Tins escaped,
then who called us this morning?
- Tins.
- Must have been.
He called to tell us so
we'd lead him to Rawls.
No Tins, but we found
his state prison jumpsuit.
It was stuffed in the
garbage can downstairs.
So he's still dressed like a cop.
Perfect disguise, especially
with the city going to hell.
This is it? No more clothes?
No. Why?
Because Tins wasn't alone.
Corrections says he escaped from
that work detail with two other men--
A Leonard "Crete" Debs
and a Donnie Wayne Johnson.
When did this get here?
"Thanks for making me the
man I am. Arthur tins."
So now he's out there somewhere
with these two knuckleheads.
Any thoughts as to where out there?
Known associates from his file?
Problem is, all closed case
files are computerized now.
Yeah, and what with the quake, the
police computers are still down.
What about a living
file? Wasn't Tins married?
Ex-wives are a beautiful thing,
but how are we gonna find her?
If only we had a really big book that listed
everybody's names, addresses, and phone numbers.
Dude, you are old-school.
I'll roust one up.
Charlie! Yeah-- yes. Oh,
yes, I-I-I sure did. Yeah.
Yeah, it was quite something.
Listen, I-I need to ask for--
no. Y-you know what? No,
never mind. It's--it's fine.
I-I was really just
calling to see how you were.
Yes. I'm fine. Yeah, yeah.
Just... have a pencil in my hand.
It's Ted. Yeah. Yeah. How are you?
Oh, I sure did feel it over here. Yes!
Problem, uh... yeah. S-sort of.
The greatest mistake is to be
continually fearful of making one.
All the other cars were
out on quake patrol?
Yes, crews. That's right.
A stumble may prevent a fall.
Besides, my car goes faster.
Yes, Crews, that's right.
But why are you driving?
That's one of your zen questions, right?
One you don't really want an answer to?
To say that we are alive.
When we cease to make mistakes, that
is the moment when we cease to be.
The buddha was asked if
he ever made mistakes--
He answered, "I am
making a mistake--"
even now.
Nothing more.
This is actually kinda
awesome. Watch your back!
Thanks for seeing us, Mrs. Tins.
Ms.Ehrlich.
I don't use Tins since the divorce.
Anything I can do to hurt
arthur, I'm happy to help.
So you don't particularly
miss your ex-husband.
I've had cramps I miss
more. Shoot him on sight.
You need me to chip in
for bullets, just ask.
And your son wouldn't miss his father?
As far as my son is concerned,
his father is already dead.
We need a list of your
ex-husband's friends or associates,
anybody he'd go to
if he were in trouble.
Arthur has no friends.
His associates are lowlifes
with names like spider and itchy.
They smell like bad meat.
Any idea where they work?
When they work, it's in porn stores as clerks
so they can steal people's credit card numbers.
Or they're installing satellite tvs in people's
homes so later they can go back and steal them.
Real bunch of winners. All of 'em.
But you want names, addresses? Gimme
some paper. I'll make you a list.
It'll be therapeutic.
There are over 50 names on this
list. We've gotta narrow it down.
No problem. We just need to talk to the one
person who knows the most about Arthur Tins,
Even more than his ex-wife.
Who would that be?
His cellmate.
Olivia. Thank you for coming.
Of course, Ted. What is it?
I was hoping that maybe you
could drive me to the hospital.
It's not bleeding much, so we
don't have to worry about your car.
Or we could take my car, but
you'd probably have to drive,
because I have a, uh, pencil in my hand.
Ted. They just announced
it on the radio.
There's a 24-hour wait
at all the area hospitals.
You have officer Mc Shane on the line.
I have Arthur Tins'
cellmate in front of me.
His name is Carl Rossbarrow.
Tins was always talking
about the getaway,
how everybody in prison spent all their time
figuring out the score but half-assing the getaway.
Tins wanted to figure out something that was
the score and the getaway rolled into one.
Now do me a favor-- when you catch
Tins, don't arrest him, just kill him.
Arthur's all about the getaway.
Anybody on that list good at getaways?
Uh, there's a guy named
Chip. Says he's a driver.
- Have you killed Arthur yet?
- No, not yet.
I saw the caller I.D.,
And I got all excited.
We had a question about your list.
Chip. He's a driver?
Anything with an engine.
You have any idea where we
might find Chip these days?
Last I saw him, he was
working some secure car job.
- Like armored car?
- Yeah.
That would appeal to Arthur.
Yeah, the score and the
getaway rolled into one.
Ma'am, do you know what
company chip worked for?
Yeah, it had a raccoon on
the patch holding a pistol.
A raccoon?
It might have been a badger. I
don't know. Just do me a favor?
Call me back when Arthur's dead.
A badger? With a pistol?
I'll run a trace on Chip, but...
but all the police computers are down.
All the police computer systems
were built by the lowest bidder.
What we need are other computers.
What we need is blended coffee drinks.
Just... work the phone.
What do you do for a living?
Assistant buyer, nordstrom's. Why?
You're my deputy now.
- For real?
- This is an emergency. I need your help.
I need you to google armored
car companies in the L.A. area.
W-what can I do?
- Blended coffee drinks?
- Sweet.
- Deputy.
- That's right.
You think I could get a certificate?
- Did you feel that?
- Yes, I did. Thank you for asking.
What is that?
- It's a gun.
- He's a cop.
He's my deputy.
Okay.
Must be nice, pretty girls
falling into your lap like that.
Any luck with those
armored car companies?
Got a badger with a pistol?
No, but this one...
has a bear with a shotgun.
Did you want a muffin too?
Hello, Arthur.
How ya doing?
I think you just dislocated
my shoulder there, pally.
Yeah? If you're lucky,
I'll pop it back in.
Oh, yeah? If you're lucky,
maybe I won't kill you.
Where's your partner, arthur?
I don't know. He should
be around any minute now.
Please!
Do what they say, or they'll kill me!
That's true. You should listen to her.
He'll kill her.
He wants to.
Chip, drop the gun. Let her go.
That's not gonna happen.
Know why? 'Cause today is my day.
And if I want her to die on my day,
Chip there's gonna kill her for me.
I made a promise to Mark Rawls that
I'd get you back to prison, Arthur.
Yeah? I don't think so.
See, I don't feel that institution
has anything more to teach me.
You gonna uncuff me?
Wanna point those guns
to the left, please?
That's right... left.
That's a great getaway
car. Or follow car.
So I want you to shoot it up for me.
- You want us to shoot the--
- the car!
That pretty I-talian car.
I want you to put some
po-lice lead into it.
Now!
Not bad!
Now, I know you got more to give me
than that. I want you to get some!
Now!
Wanna get some! Get some!Get some,
get some, get some, get some, get some!
Wanna get some, get some! Get some,
Wanna get some. Get
some, get some, get some.
You don't feel it? Can you feel it? Can you feel it,
can you feel it? Can you feel it? Can you feel it?
Gimme the baby. Start the car.
Shoot me, I'll shoot her.
They broke in.
Chip Lanter and this other guy, Tins.
Chip's been here two years.
You all right?
He's a good driver.
Is there an electronic trace on this
truck we can use to track his movement?
Yes, of course.
It's not coming up.
Chip must have disabled
the transponders.
That car could be anywhere.
I'm really more of a
leave it in kind of guy.
I've always heard pull it out.
Always? What about a corkscrew
or-or a stingray barb ?
It's not a corkscrew. It's a pencil.
And it's a day's wait at the
E.R., So it's coming out right now.
You are so... lucky, Olivia.
Why is that?
Well, to be so sure of things.
I used to be sure of things.
I can't imagine ever
being that way again.
That's just the pencil talking, Ted.
You're gonna... take it out, huh?
All we need is some alcohol.
Not rubbing alcohol. Drinking alcohol.
Now, what goes with a
yellow number 2 pencil?
I did it!
Always knew I'd get out. Get
you... get this armored car.
Then the quake hits, and
everyone runs to the atms.
But the atms run dry.
So the bank needs to get all that
extra cash out to the panicked populace.
That's a miracle,
Chip. A seismic miracle.
You know what the best part is?
They gonna load it up for us.
- Like a
drive-through. - Yeah.
Like a drive-through.
detectives.
There's something you should see.
Chip Lanter's personal security beacon.
All the guards carry one.
He's calling us for help.
- Why would he do that?
- where is he?
Looks like somewhere in the valley.
- You're it?
- I'm it.
Swat's camped out in front of the federal building
in anticipation of some sort of civil unrest.
And apparently, the national
guard's off somewhere else.
so it's just us.
Yeah, but I'm pretty pissed off.
who is it?
My guess... that's Arthur Tins.
Chip was the driver.
Never really got to use his getaway car.
Yeah, looks like things didn't
work out like he expected.
Okay. All right. Yeah.
All right, dispatch says since
these two here are pretty well dead,
it's gonna be awhile before
they can send anybody over.
They're stretched pretty thin today.
All right, so they
disagree about the cut.
They start shooting at each
other, and one of the shots...
hits the car's gas tank?
Looks that way.
Yeah, but you think
that's what happened?
No. I just said it looks that way.
Because you really have to be aiming if
you want the gas tank to explode like that.
You really would.
And you really can't tell
if that's Arthur Tins or not.
You really can'T.
You know, he could have burned up half the
cash and still walked away with a fortune.
he really could have.
But Tins is smart.
Why do such a bad job
at faking your own death?
Maybe he doesn't want
us thinking he's dead.
Well, what does he want?
He wants the next people
to think he's dead.
The next people?
Bobby, don't! Don't
move! Bobby, don't move!
Don't move, okay? Bobby, don't move.
Tins needs a bigger mess.
He needs more bodies.
Wait a second.
There.
- I open that door...
- something goes boom.
okay. All right?
Pull your hand away from the door.
Okay. Walk away.
Charlie, I'm... I'm stuck. My
watch is, uh, tangled on the line.
All right. Okay, don't
move. I'm gonna cut it--
no. I'll cut it.
I'm the commanding officer
here. Give me the knife.
Step back. Now, detective, give
me the knife. Now stand back.
You know, I always had a desire to be
standing next to jessica alba when I died.
I get that.
You pull the handle...
the wire pulls the trigger...
and... boom! Gas goes up.
He wanted the next people
to think he was dead.
Yeah, the ones who came to clean us up.
That's why he invited
us along here today.
Okay, so where is Arthur Tins now?
- Tins left her behind.
- Who?
June Brimmer.
The president of the armored car
company. They left her behind.
Maybe they didn't wanna
bring her with 'em.
But what good is a hostage if
you don't take 'em with you?
Why did Tins leave her behind?
Maybe...
tins didn't disable the
armored car's transponder.
Maybe Brimmer told us he disabled it.
Maybe tins left brimmer behind 'cause he didn't
want the lapd to go looking for that armored car.
Maybe you two should go
pay a visit to june brimmer.
Stark and I will
babysit the bacon. What?
Think I'd leave you here
alone with all this cash?
- You have a pencil in your hand.
- I do.
But you know, now that I look
at it, you can hardly notice it.
Really, maybe it's not so bad.
Maybe I'm going to have a glove made.
A special glove to fit the pencil.
You're not having a special glove made.
You're having the pencil
taken out of your hand.
Ah, but maybe now you've had too
much to drink to pull out the pencil.
Are you kidding me?
I pull pencils better this way.
Are you ready?
- Olivia...
- Ted...
you know, when I, uh, woke up
at the bottom of the stairs...
and I saw... this...
it was not Charlie that I
thought of calling first.
Ted.
Don't say it's the pencil talking,
because it's not the pencil talking.
It's me talking.
- I wanted to call you, Olivia.
- Ted...
I'm marrying Charlie's father.
Yeah.
Why haven't you yet?
It's not the pencil talking.
It's not... the pencil talking.
- Ted...
- Yes?
I'm so sorry.
- Don't be. Don't be.
- Not for this.
For this.
Detectives.
Hi, June. How are you feeling?
Okay. Just... spending
time with my family.
You like music, huh?
we're more about
old-school stuff. Beatles.
I really like their second movie.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay, well, we'd just like
to ask you some questions.
You know, if you could come
by the office tomorrow...
that'd be great.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
the Beatle's second
movie was Help, you moron.
Hey, June, why don't
you show our guests in?
Come on in. Sit down.
Hey, you doing okay there?
Of course Simon's okay.
You're okay.
Why don't you let Simon come
and stand over here by me?
Oh, I don't know. Maybe after dinner.
Where's your partner?
She should be here any minunute.
Call for backup?
Gonna get the swat all
set up on the perimeter?
You came here this morning,
took over the house, set up camp.
You should get in on this.
I mean, you can't have
any of the crunchy part,
but she'll scoop you up some of the
gooey stuff in the middle if you want.
Won't you, cupcake?
I know what you wanted to happen
to us in that warehouse, Arthur.
I'm sorry about that.
- I'll live.
- Maybe.
Or maybe I'll kill you.
Why don't you show me
your other hand, arthur?
See, it'd be better for all concerned
if your partner would come on in here.
No. It'd be better for all concerned
if your partner were to come on in here.
Is there someone else in here?
You leave someone here, Arthur?
Leave someone while
you were out and about?
Come on! Don't be shy now.
Now you get to see
something really good.
Dude, you didn't tell me
there was macaroni and cheese.
Dude.
Crete was just keepin'
Mr. Mom company upstairs.
He'd been crying.
A son shouldn't have to
see his dad like that.
Take him to the car, crete. We're goin'.
Actually, why don't you
stay here with us, Crete?
How you doing? Where you been?
What's the matter, honey, no swat?
I forgot. Major seismic disturbance.
And you and your
understaffed police force--
now, if I could
vote, which I can't--
I vote
yes--more cops.
Just so you know.
Now... we're going for
a little family drive.
I'd invite you all-- this
family's got a big old suv--
but there's already a bunch of us going.
Now, I was gonna take off tonight
and leave in the dark, you know,
but I suppose we should go right now
before the gas prices get any higher.
Crete? You know Chip is dead?
Yeah, that was the plan. Kill Chip.
- What about the other guy?
- What other guy?
- Hey, Crete.
- Donnie Wayne Johnson.
The third man you two
escaped with. Where is he?
Hey, crete!
They're trying to trick you, mess
with your head. You ignore them.
He'd be right if there was no third
man, but there was a third man.
You... and Arthur, and Donnie
all busted out this morning.
- What did Arthur do with Donnie?
- Crete, go to the car.
Arthur killed donnie...
and used his body to fake his death.
Crete, go to the car!
Arthur... where's Donnie, man?
On his way back from the warehouse.
Well, he'd be back by now.
But he's not comin' back, is he, Arthur?
he kills his partners, Crete.
Donnie, Chip, you sooner or later.
My guess is sooner.
Arthur, where is donnie?
Crete, as god is my
witness, we are a team.
Why don't you go ahead
and give him a call?
Call him on the phone, Crete.
Go ahead, give Donnie
a call just to say hi.
Arthur! Where is Donnie?
He's at the
warehouse--
What...
you kill me?
I can't kill you, Arthur. Remember?
You're already dead.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
I'll see you later then, crews.
What are you sitting on?
Earthquake kit.
I can live out of this
thing for five days.
Water, radio, blankets, food.
It's got a seat.
So after you empty out the
bucket, you can use it as a toilet.
You stepped up to a car full of
explosives, but earthquakes scare you?
The earth cracking
open-- that I don't get.
Messed up things people do...
that, detective, I
understand. Don't you?
This isn't even a weight-bearing wall.
- What?
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Did you feel that?