Previously on Life.
Now that Charlie Crews is free,
do you need
someone else to save ?
It's not about what I need.
Do I feel bad
about what happened ?
Yeah, I feel bad.
Do I feel guilty ?
No.
I was looking for you,
and I didn't even know it.
Now you're here,
and I can't have you.
You're married.
- Buy me a drink.
- Do I know you ?
Does it matter?
I'm Neil Cudahy.
You're the reason I'm sitting here.
Is that right ?
When I saw on tv,
that Constance Griffiths got you out,
I said "That girl's gonna be my lawyer."
Is that right ?
"The Fallen Woman"
- Hello ?
- Charlie ?
What's wrong ?
I didn't know who else to call.
Constance, what happened ?
I'm so scared.
What happened?
Hey.
It's Cudy.
He didn't...
No, no.
Not like that.
He just... wanted money.
Like you got.
He thought that I can get that for him,
and when I said that
I couldn't do that,
then he hit me,
and I...
I'm so stupid.
And I wanted him to be you.
'Cause you're not mine anymore.
All those years,
you were mine.
I know.
Hold me.
Please just hold.
It's gonna be okay.
www.1000fr.com presents
capture:frm@xxy
sync:frs@‚Ú≤®
It's a dead angel.
It's a dead woman
with a pair of fake wings.
- How do you know ?
- Well, I know the wings are fake,
because I can see
the harness right there.
Maybe she's a real angel
with fake wings.
Why would a real angel...
No. No.
I'm not doing this with you.
A witness says she just fell out
of the sky.
Wham!
Angel wings?
The med's gonna have a filled day.
No i.d. Just the black dress and the wings.
She must have hit
that car pretty hard.
Do you think she came from...
That window.
I think she came
from that window.
- Hey Bobby.
- Yeah.
I was wondering if I could
ask you a favor.
Sure, Charlie. Just tell me.
I don't remember her checking in.
Well, she probably wasn't
wearing wings at the time.
No clothes in the closet,
no suitcase. There's nothing in the
bathroom. No personal effects at all.
The computer says the room is vacant.
A woman, wearing angel wings,
was pushed out of a 9th
storey window and smashed...
Oh, this was already on hand.
unfortunately her wings
could not save her.
If you're here to i.d.
the angel,
please stay in line.
She wasn't an angel.
What were it then ?
They only look like angels,
but they're not.
They're aliens.
- It's the end...
- Of the world.
- When angels die...
- It's the end.
Our singer, Angel,
left us after a gig in the HB*.
I think it's her.
You wanna touch them ?
You'll feel like real is.
No, it's not her. I guess we went back
to bring her after all.
You wanna know a secret about angels?
Absolutely.
We're not always so good.
I'm not in a hurry.
Go ahead.
Can we see the picture ?
Just to be sure.
No.
No, that's... Not our Kylie.
Detective, may I
ask when you lost your faith?
I'd rather not talk
about my faith.
You don't have it anymore, do you Dear ?
But you used to, didn't you ?
You know, we have
a lot of people to get to so...
- If you don't mind...
- But you want it back, don't you ?
It's there, waiting for you,
if you want it.
Whenever you want it.
You know that,
don't you, Dear ?
I'm takin' a break.
I'm in no hurry. Go ahead.
It's a real freak show.
I did that thing you asked.
Went by that guy car,
his work and apartment.
Hasn't been seen
at either of them since yesterday.
I ran a list of his
known associates.
Want me to run out
some of them?
- No, I got it.
- Are you sure ?
Hey, whatever it is, man,
i'm okay with it.
Crews.
We've got another one.
We gotta go.
What was the deal with Stark?
He wants us to start a bowling league.
Just because the wings were fake,
doesn't mean she wasn't a real angel.
Isn't there an "off" button?
I know she wasn't an angel
on a cloud with a harp angel, but...
Maybe she was an angel in
the way we all might be angels.
We all might be angels ?
Crews, l'm gonna
tell you something.
You know, there're may be
a few things...
that I don't know about myself,
but...
I'm sure I'm not an angel.
You see, that's exactly the kind of
humble things an angel might say.
That was very hostile.
That was at close
to hostile.
The detectives are here.
Whose genius idea was this ?
What do you say, Reese ?
Write them up
and send them home ?
We all did things like these
when we were young.
You know, pranks.
I tried. Good luck.
You know what I was doin' before I
got the call to investigate this ?
I was investing a homicide.
What you have done is waist my time.
Throwing that off from the roof
was a crime,
but wasting my time is what
you both are gonna pay for. Take them in.
All right. Let's go.
That was hostile.
Maybe she isn't an angel,
after all.
It was a big responsability,
saving someone's life ?
It was a surprising amount of paperwork.
Several thousand pages.
Does he feel in debt to you ?
Charlie ?
Detective Crews,
he doesn't owe me anything.
He owes you his life, yes?
I was just doing my job.
So Detective Crews
was just one more client.
Hum.. N..no.
Of course not.
I would never say that.
Ah... No. I don't think I can break that.
No, I don't want change, Ron.
I want you to have it.
How do you know my name?
Oh, I know a lot about you.
I know you spent three years
up in Lompoc.
What, you're a cop?
No just now, I'm not.
So what do you want ?
I'm looking for your pal, Cudahy.
And don't tell me you don't know.
Let's not do that, okay, Ron ?
You celled with him for fourteen
months up at Lompoc,
and then after you had
a little business together.
Something about girls, right ?
I don't know where he is.
You broke my finger.
There's just kiddin'. Let's not exaggerate.
What do you think about thought?
I... I don't understand you.
Thought, Ron.
Often gets in the way of truth.
Pain, Ron,
clears the mind of thought.
Let all toughts,
flee your mind,
and let the truth
make itself know.
Look, i don't know
where cudahy is.
I can make some calls.
Let... let me make
some calls.
Is that the truth ?
Yeah.
There.
Good as new.
Better than new.
Because now, you have had
this experience.
Look, if i - if i find Cudahy,
Who--who should i say
is looking for him?
He'll know.
No i.d. on her or left in the room.
it's like she fell
out of the sky.
She fell out of a window.
It's like she's no one
No one is no one.
Now you sound like me.
Take that back.
Would it be so bad?
I'm in no hurry.
go ahead.
Reese, Reese.
Hey.
i know it's all about
the journey,
but, er... sooner or later
you're just gonna have to get
to the front of the line.
I know.
I--I know.
Detective Crews.
Detective Reese.
Your name is...?
Jasper.
Jasper Willens.
How come you've been
giving your space away, Jasper Willens?
'cause i'm afraid.
Afraid of what?
Afraid of the answer?
That's right.
There's an answer
at the front of the line.
if you never get there,
you don't ever have to know?
That's right.
You think it's gonna be bad news,
if you find out the truth ?
Truth usually is.
I'm that guy.
- Which guy is that ?
- The guy that gets the bad news.
But you came down here,
Jasper.
so you did want to know,
didn't you?
And now do you know
where you are ?
you're at the front
of the line.
I saw the...
photo on the news
of that woman
on the car.
and i think i know her.
How do you know her ?
She's Lena.
my wife.
I came home from work
last night,
and Lena always
has dinner ready.
She wasn't home.
And she never came home.
And then i saw the news.
She always had
dinner ready?
Every night.
She liked to cook.
May i ask what kind of work
you do?
I make glue.
I--i own a company that makes
industrial glues and adhesives.
We moved over $14 million
dollars worth of product last year.
That's a lot of glue.
Well, it's what
holds us together.
Oh.
That's our slogan.
"It's what
holds us together."
Do you know why your wife
was at the hotel ?
I have to ask, uh...
She was wearing wings.
Do you know why?
I never saw those.
I don't know why
she would have them on.
Do you know anyone who'd want to hurt
your wife, jasper?
He would.
He ?
He told her he'd take her
away from me if i didn't pay.
But i paid every month,
and he took her anyway.
Who said that ?
Tell us his name, jasper.
Then tell us
about your wife.
I--i met lena
about two years ago
at this bar
that i'd heard about, Ritual.
Where did you hear
about that bar?
It's where an older man
can find...
- What he needed?
- She was from russia,
and she'd had
a hard time there,
and she liked that
i could make her laugh.
And you had to pay
every month?
Not at first,
not for the first year.
And then we got married,
and... and...
I have to go now.
I--i just came to see
if it was Lena.
To see if it was her,
and i--
i need to go home now.
What happened
when you got married?
Is that door locked ?
You are in a police station.
What happened
when you were married?
We came home that night,
from that party and...
he was in our house.
Who was ?
Why was he in your house ?
He was sitting
in my kitchen.
Lena must have
given him the key
r the alarm code.
He said that i owed him
for the time that we'd already
spent together,
and that if i wanted her
to stay with me,
i had...i had to pay him
every month,
or he would take her away
and he would punish her.
He beat her like a dog.
He'd make Lena
live in a cage
like a dog.
Tell us his name.
I paid !
I paid $10,000 every month !
Why did he take her from me
if i paid ?
Why ?
Give us the name, jasper,
of the man who killed lena.
Roman...
No last name, just Roman.
That's it.
We're running it,
but Roman is like...
John in russian.
So the russian girl
is a natasha.
a Lena.
No, her name is Lena,
but she's a natasha.
It's what they call the scam
the russians run on american men.
Get them hooked on a pretty
russian girl,
get them married,
then come for the payment.
It's a long-term con.
Takes patience.
Sounds like you
admire them.
I respect
how good they are.
And you'll respect them too,
or...
Or...?
Or they will feed you
to their dog.
Industrial glue.
It's what holds us together.
A natasha.
That's one word for it.
She was a prostitute,
Crews, not an angel.
You can't be both?
Well, i'm pretty sure
that there's a rule
that says you can't be
a prostie and an angel.
I know a prostitute at pelican
bay whose name was Angel.
They have women at pelican bay?
No, she wasn't a woman woman.
And just to make it clear,
i didn't "know" her...him.
didn't know her-him.
But she did make
a nice carrot cake.
Maybe i should go in first.
It's some kind of
upscale pick up joint,
and, you know,
i'll go in and i'll...
And you'll...?
I'll get...
picked up.
I'll be ten minutes.
So i'm not too old,
i hope.
Ah, no.
Not too old.
Anyways, i don't like
all these young men in L.A.
I think i scare them.
Oh, yeah ?
Why is that ?
Because they're
so easy to read.
I can see how silly
they are.
They all want one thing,
you know ?
Can you read me ?
Do you want me to ?
I can tell...
you have money.
The watch told you that.
I can tell
it is new money.
Now, how did you know that ?
And i can tell that you do not know
what to do with your new money.
Do you know what else
i can tell ?
What ?
I can tell you're a cop.
I can tell she's one too.
Her name was Lena.
She was thrown
from a window.
I had seen her around,
but not for a long time.
Do you know
what a natasha is ?
You let her talk for you?
Do you know a man
named Roman ?
I know a lot of men
named Roman.
It is common name in russia.
Officer new money,
How come you let the woman
do your business ?
I can read people too.
and i think it made you sad
when Lena died.
I also think you know the Roman
my partner asked you about.
Know Roman ?
No one knows Roman.
All right, really...
What is it with this guy ?
What is with Roman ?
He's not what you american cops
are used to.
He was born
in russian prison.
He's been to hell and back.
Roman is not
like the rest of us.
Why is that ?
Roman has no fear.
Well, i'd like to ask him
about that.
Maybe you can tell us
where to find him.
Don't worry. If you're looking
for Roman, he will find you.
But you can't hold on to him.
When you reach out for Roman,
he's not there.
I saw the news.
So she wasn't an angel
after all.
She was just a...
a what ?
Just a lost girl.
Hey,
you didn't file a report
about Cudahy about what happened.
Oh, i'm done with it.
You're done with it.
Right, Charlie?
you're done with it.
Do you want to talk
about these boxes?
- Do you like them?
- Do you want to talk about
why you're packing books
Because it's what people do
when they're moving.
Pack books into boxes.
I'm going to need them
with me in New York.
I'm going to New York.
When ?
Tomorrow.
- For how long ?
- A while.
My firm has
a big case there,
and i'm going
to sit in on it.
New York.
City that never sleeps.
No, i've been there.
it sleeps a little. naps.
I need to go, Charlie.
I need to go away.
My husband...
I'm here with him,
but i'm away from him.
And you...
I'm here with you,
but i'm--
I'm not here with you.
I need to go.
Want some help
with those boxes?
No, my husband's on his way,
and he's going to help me...
...pack.
So i guess
i should take off then.
Yeah.
Okay.
Roman is Roman Nevikov.
We ran financials on ritual.
He doesn't own it.
A company that he owns,
owns a company that owns it.
LAPD has had this guy
on their radar for years.
Stolen dvds, identity theft,
gasoline scams.
Oh, keep reading.
He also loves the blood sport.
He's heavy into dog fighting,
anything that dies.
He said he'd make Lena his dog.
He said he'd make Lena
live in a cage like a dog.
That's what Jasper said Roman
would do to Lena if he stopped paying.
I mean, we've been after this
animal roman for years,
and i don't see one indictment
in his jacket.
Not one charge in here
that sticks.
"Uou can't hold on to him.
You reach out for Roman,
but he's not there."
That's what Julia said.
Well, i want you two
to reach out
and bring backup to make sure
you hold on to him.
Lena may not have been
an angel,
but she was a woman
living in my city.
If Roman killed her,
i want him for it.
Is he in there ?
Well, detective, we're not
actually sure about that.
Either Roman is in there
or Roman is not in there.
21-david saw him
enter the building,
23 and 25-david were um...
not able to verify.
An escalade has pulled up
to the building.
All units,
hold your position.
Is that clear?
Doors opening, no clear
sight of the subject.
This is 23-david,
we have eyes on the subject
entering the club.
Negative that.
this is 25-david.
Subject has left the club.
Subject is in the suv.
23-david, do we have a go
to enter the club?
We need instructions.
Do we enter the club
or follow the vehicle?
A little freaky,
right?
A little bit.
Okay.
Officer new money...
Cuff me.
Report came back from interpol.
Our new friend, Roman,is a person of
interest in five murders back in russia.
After he fled the country,
they found two hockey players,
cut up and buried in his basement.
Man, this guy is a sociopath.
So what's he doing
in this country?
How does Roman get into the U.S. ?
What are you thinking?
We started out looking for an angel.
And now we're staring at the devil.
How you doing?
Splendid.
I like this room.
- You do ?
- 12 years in prison,
and you're still walking upright.
Just between us...
You killed that family,
didn't you?
That belong to you?
Do you mean did I own her ?
We have a witness who pins you
to human trafficking.
You know what kind of time
that carries?
He won't testify.
- Why not?
- How's that rehab working for you?
Down time's the hardest.
You have nothing to do,
your muscles get all twitchy.
You can taste it
in the back of your throat.
Shut up.
All the way down there
In the back of your throat.
Shut your mouth.
You got hooked
working undercover.
Shut your mouth.
Took a junkie lover too.
What ever happened to him?
You look at me
when you talk.
You know what a Natasha is, Roman?
You think this girl
was a Natasha,
and I killed her.
Let me ask you a question.
If she was my Natasha,
earning my money,
why would I kill her?
I'm a businessman...
it's just bad business.
You have a good look.
If you ever want to make
some real money,
you should call me, okay,
Detective Dani Reese?
Now, in about two minutes,
my overpriced lawyer's going
to come in and tell you
that there's nothing to tie me
to this poor dead girl.
Then my lawyer is going to tell you
that he and i are leaving.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
And you, Detective.
What if it was one of them
who set you up?
Crews.
So where are we?
We're uh...we're back
at the beginning.
Okay.
So let's go back
to the beginning.
The hotel room
where she was thrown.
When Roman
said those things,
did you want to shoot him?
Yes.
Me too.
Did you see yourself
shooting him?
Yes.
Me too.
You lost your faith
because of the guy,
not the drugs.
My faith has been gone
for so long,
I can't remember
when it was that I lost it.
Or if I ever even had it.
So they were here,
but no one was registered.
So how do you get into a room
without registering?
You steal a key.
Or you buy one.
Stan, are your
employers here aware,
that you were fired from your
last three jobs for stealing?
Nothing's missing.
I didn't steal nothing.
No, you can't steal nothing.
Nothing does not exist.
To steal something
that doesn't exist...
Wait.
If it doesn't exist...
Then how can
it be something?
Ha!
I hate that.
Don't you hate that?
It's a brain fart, right?
Crews!
Nothing's been stolen, Stan.
But you do have a pass key,
don't you?
So you want us
to question you about this,
or about the murder
that happened here?
My buddy Oliver,
he does my ink.
I pay him with pass keys.
Look, no one
was staying here.
How is that stealing?
So what exactly is it
you do here?
Mostly tattoos
and airbrush stuff on cars and bikes.
We work in metal
and flesh.
What does Oliver
do here?
Oh, just the designs.
He designed...
He designed this.
It's good, right?
I have the same design
on my Ducati.
Metal and flesh.
That's right.
You want a tattoo?
Oh, I have some.
Come on.
When does someone
like you get tattoos?
It's complicated.
That's Oliver's
work station.
When was he last here?
I don't know, maybe a few days.
People kind of
come and go here.
You got a great view of Roman's
night club from here.
You wouldn't happen
to have
oliver's home address,
would you?
Do you really have
any tattoos?
You wanna see 'em?
Absolutely not.
Oliver Sanderson!
We have a warrant
to search these premises.
I have a pass key.
That's her, right?
That's Lena.
Art school graduate.
And lover of angels.
We find his car around the block
from the hotel,
where Lena died.
No calls on his cell phone,
or land line
since her murder.
Mail stacked up
outside his door.
No charges
on his credit card.
on his starbucks* card.
This kid is nowhere.
No one is nowhere.
Now you're sounding
like me again.
Am I ?
Okay.
Okay, that picture
with Lena in the wings.
She posed for that photo.
She put those wings on
and posed.
So that Oliver
could take that picture.
So you think maybe Lena...
put those wings on
for Oliver?
Now, who would Lena
talk to about that?
Where is Officer
New Money?
Detective New Money,
actually.
These russians are tough.
Sounds like you
admire them.
Julia...
Lena posed for that photo,
didn't she?
Yes.
Who'd she put
the wings on for?
For Oliver.
He said she was his angel.
Lena and Oliver were in love.
She was married
to that Jasper.
She was working for him...
Roman, but she was in love
with that punk kid Oliver.
She wore expensive dresses,
and she knew how to order wine,
but she was only
23 years old and...
and she wanted
to be young.
Yes.
How old are you, Julia?
22, but...
None of us are young.
Julia,
Did Roman know,
about Lena and Oliver?
I don't know.
But Lena was leaving.
Lena and Oliver were leaving.
She was leaving Jasper.
She was leaving Roman.
What would Roman do
to Lena if he found out?
He would kill her.
Even though she makes him
money?
He'd kill her
to set an example.
That's right.
To set an example.
And what about Oliver?
I die, you know,
as I say these things to you.
These words kill me.
We can protect you.
What would he do
to sweet Oliver,
for trying to steal Lena,
trying to steal his property?
Death would be too good for him.
You understand, don't you?
Is that door locked?
You're at a police station.
That's a lot of fear,
Jasper.
To be so afraid of someone in
the middle of a police station.
That kind of fear
doesn't come from a threat.
It comes from a beating.
When you talked
about the dogs, Jasper,
about what Roman would do,
did he do it to you?
Did he show you the cage?
Roman's going to kill
someone else, Jasper.
Someone Lena...
someone Lena loved.
Where are the cages?
He blindfolded me.
I can't tell you
where they are.
Do you remember anything?
Anything that might be useful?
It smelled
like gasoline.
Even with all those dogs,
it smelled like gasoline.
What about that gas scam
that Roman was never tied to?
Where did they
operate out of?
Gasoline.
No one fires.
Over here!
She was my angel.
Did Roman kill Lena?
He threw her out that window.
We met there.
We thought we were safe,
we thought nobody
could find us.
He found you.
She'd put the wings on
for me.
I'd draw her....
For me.
Roman found you.
Yes, she...
She told him
we were gonna leave.
He laughed at us,
he laughed at her wings.
She...
spit at him and...
And then?
Then he threw her
out the window!
Took me here,
to be his dog.
Will you testify to that
in court?
You will testify
that Roman killed Lena?
He made me his dog.
Ready?
Ready, ready.
Detectives Reese and Crews,
This is special agent Bodner.
Homeland security.
Oh, I don't think I'm gonna like
what happens next.
Well, i'd just say
lay back and get it over with.
But we took this seminar,
so now i don't talk like that.
- You took Roman.
- Detective, we've had Roman.
He's ours.
He's always been ours.
He killed a woman.
We have a witness
that'll testify to that.
I'm sure you do.
But you can't have a trial,
because you can't have Roman.
- Like I said, he's ours.
- He threw a woman out the window.
Roman Nevikov provides
information
about drug and arms shipments
between Russia, Mexico, and the U.S.
That untell can save
hundreds of lives.
Save hundreds of lives, you expect I'm
gonna believe you actually care about...
That's enough.
Detective, you have no idea
how the real world works,
- Do you ?
- No, but I know how guys...
like you work, and it's all
about the power, isn't it?
You... You close your mouth now.
And you.
Take your russian and get
the hell out of my house.
"You can't hold on to him.
You reach out for Roman,
but he isn't there."
Hello, Neil.
Oh...
I'm trying to forgive you,
Cudahy.
But what you did
to Constance...
I just wanted
what you got.
They paid you that money
just to shut up.
Why shouldn't they
pay me too?
I know I'd be a better person
if I did forgive you.
I just wanted
what you got.
I've called the police.
I am the police.
- Hey.
Hey, did you ever find
that guy you were looking for?
No.
No, I never did.
Hello?
Detective...
I have something you might be
interested in.
Oh, yeah?
What would that be?
The bank of Los Angeles
shoot-out.
How 'bout it?
You should ask your partner
about the bank of L.A. shoot-out.
That was 15 years ago.
I know.
You should ask your partner.
you should ask your partner
what happened
to all that money.
Good bye, Detective.
welcome to www.1000fr.com