Go back, go back.
That is God and a surgeon
working in harmony.
Here comes
the Schwarma girl.
Hey.
Hey...
Here you guys go.
Be careful, it's really hot.
I don't want to... for you
to burn your tongue on it.
Wow, 29 orders this month.
One more, and you'll get
a free baba ghanoush.
Oh...
I'm reaching in my pocket
for money, not for...
Hey, do you
have change?
Oh, she's...
Did you get it?
Fellas...
Oh, boy.
What are you guys doing?
Or have you forgotten
about Big Mike's pol
on "mammary cam"?
I don't know what you're
talking about, Chuck.
He doesn't know what I'm talking
about? That's so weird.
So, you didn't actually just
remove the offending video
from the camcorder and
then hand it to Lester,
who is now hiding it behind
his back?
What? Wow!
My feelings are hurt.
Charles,
after all these years,
where's the trust, my friend?
In Jeff's sweaty palms,
along with the amateur
consumer porn.
Look...
No, you look...
Hey, Chuck? Uh, can
I talk to you for a sec?
Move.
Awesome...
to see you, Devon.
Yeah, yeah.
What's up?
All right.
So, what's
on your mind?
Chuck, I was, I was hoping
to talk to you about Ellie.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Well, you know,
ever since, um,
ever since we've been dating,
I've come to think of you
as that little brother
I never had.
Don't you have
two younger brothers?
Indeed. Indeed.
But you seem like someone
who can offer sage wisdom
in confusing times,
and this is one of those times
I am really confused, bro.
I don't know how to put
this into words, really.
That's a bug.
What? What?
Spider, I hate those
fuzzy little bastards...
Oh, no. I think, uh, no,
you got him.
He was like...
and then poof! Gone.
Can you excuse me
for just one second?
I think I just saw a kid
climbing into an oven
over in Home Appliances.
Chuck!
Chuck, I need you to drop
some knowledge, bro.
Keep moving, Bartowksi.
Nothing to see here.
Not even if I had the time.
You're getting sloppy, Casey.
I understand that you have
some perverse desire
to listen to everybody,
but you really need to be more
careful when hiding your bugs.
What are you lip-smacking about,
Bartowski?
I just found this on one
of our product displays,
and not very well
hidden, I might add.
Normally, I'm a fan
of your craftsmanship,
if not your methods.
Look, all I'm saying is that
something like this discovered
by someone less in the know
than me could spell trouble.
You worry about that
supercomputer in your brain.
Let me worry
about the spy stuff, huh?
Don't you have a hard drive
you can go fix?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
There's best buddy of mine.
Yeah. What's up?
Okay, saw an Infinity Ward
mail in the trash,
and I'm guessing that means
you got a pre-release demo
of the next Call of Duty game?
Ah... Yeah, but the last time
I lent you a game sampler,
it ended up
all over the Internet.
So this one's gonna
stay in my locker,
and you can play it when
you get some adult supervision.
Adult super...?
Chuck, I'm almost at the age
where I should get my prostate
checked annually.
Okay? Surely I could be trusted
with an advance copy
of the next greatest video game
on the planet.
Have you seen Awesome?
Over by the Home Theater Room.
(muttering):
I think that's...
...really.
??
???
defrosting himself,
as it turns out.
So, uh, what, uh,
what's going on?
This is one of those
rare moments
when things are not kosher,
Chuck.
Oh, man.
This is harder than I thought.
Uh-huh.
Go... Go on.
I'm listening.
Right. Well...
I've been thinking a lot
about the way things are
between me
and your sister.
And you're the man in...
in Ellie's family,
so I was wondering...
Can I have your permission...
Can I marry Ellie?
Wow. That-That's quite...
quite a rock you got there.
Is that a yes? Dude...
Yes! Yes!
Sorry! I just...
You kind of--- waah!
You know, you pulled the blang
just right in...
Yes, you have my blessing.
Thank you. Thank you.
I mean, it's been in my family
for years.
This was my great-grandmother's.
(chuckles)
Ah, you think she'll like it?
Like it? She'll, she'll love it.
I, um, I'm just not sure
she'll be able to lift
her hand anymore.
Oh, one other thing.
Ellie is a bloodhound
when it comes to these
kind of things.
If I keep this in the apartment,
she will smell diamond.
Can you hold onto this,
just for a day or so, man?
I mean, just till I figure out
how to pop the question?
I don't think it's actually
a good idea...
Oh, thank you!
Thank you so much, bro.
Hey, pretty soon, I'm going
to mean that literally.
There you go.
All right...
We have a problem.
What do you mean?
Chuck found that
in the Buy More.
We have a problem.
BECKMAN:
The bug Chuck found is
a GLG-20, one of the most
advanced counter-espionage
listening devices
in the CIA arsenal.
This is a CIA design?
Figures.
The GLG-20 is
a low-power transmitter.
In order to avoid detection,
it has a maximum range
of about 20 yards.
Which means there's
probably a receiver
hidden somewhere
inside the Buy More.
GRAHAM:
We believe
it's recently become
a favorite
of the FULCRUM agents.
So, you're telling us the secret
government cabal that abducted
Bryce Larkin and came
within a hair of figuring out
that Chuck's the Intersect is
now skulking
around the Buy More?
We need you to locate
that receiver,
and find the person
who planted it.
BECKMAN:
You have 48 hours.
If you cannot identify the
enemy operative in that time,
we will have no choice
but to relocate Chuck
to a secure government
holding facility.
GRAHAM:
Bartowski's time as a civilian
may be coming to an en
For their own safety, his
family may never see him again.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
糊涂间谍天才蛋 第一季第13集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译:玺爷 任小猪 爱CHUCK的GRAY13
校对:酒囊饭袋
时间轴:小L
When are these young ladies
going to learn?
If they don't want someone
taking a picture
of their private business,
put some drawers on.
Hey, uh, you think
we should make a run for it?
You don't run
from the cops.
It makes you look guilty,
or shot in the back.
We are guilty.
Shh!
Bring me down
and I will cut you.
So, no locks broken?
No alarms set off?
Nope. It's clean.
Must be an inside job.
Thought of that.
You really think any of these
dummies can mastermind all this?
It's almost always someone
close to the operation.
When I find out
who robbed my store
and stole my fish,
I'm gonna break
my foot off
in his behind.
(whispers):
Oh, my God...
Shh!
Hi.
Hey.
What's with the police
presence outside?
They robbed the Buy More, man.
They took everything.
They took everything?
Everything.
Oh, please, God, no.
Please be there.
Oh, my God...
The ring.
They took Ellie's ring.
Oh, my God.
(panting):
Oh, oh...
Oh! Oh!
Hey...
Chuckles, what's up?
Dude, I figured out
how I'm gonna pop the Q.
The Q? What Q? What's a Q?
You know, the Q, the big Q
you only ask once in a lifetime.
Can't say right now... Mom.
Is that your mom?
Tell her
that I love that
kittens-playing-with-the-yarn
sweater that she knitted me.
You got it, babe.
I'm going to do it
while we're skydiving.
Really?
Do you think, uh...
Do you think
that's a good idea?
Not the first time we've been
in the mile-high club, buddy.
If you know what I mean.
Yeah, uh...
Listen: skydiving is a little,
it's a little risky.
Don't you think? I mean,
you could drop the ring.
Whoa. Hot call, dude.
Hate to lose
my great-granny's ring.
She gave it to me
right before she passed.
You know? She knew Ellie was
the one before I did.
Great, great, okay, so...
just, you know, let me know
when you figure
something else out.
Okay.
But, Devon, um...
take your time.
You got it, brother.
(thuds)
Oh...
Detective Conway here
is convinced
that this is an inside job.
And we intend to get
to the bottom of this.
Bartowski, get over here.
You're a suspect, too.
You all are!
When that pig
talks to you,
look him in the eye
and say nothing.
Zip it.
Nothing? Come on, that's
incredibly rude, Jeffrey.
Dead men tell
no tales.
Stop it.
Quit messing around.
Bartowski, where's Casey?
Don't you two usually
carpool together?
Yes.
Yes, sir, we absolutely do.
But, uh... not today.
Why don't you go find out
why his ass is so tardy.
Someone might
find that suspicious.
Sure, I can-I can do that.
CASEY:
What?
Where are you?
Big Mike's looking for you.
Yeah, well, he's going to be
looking for both of us.
Now get down here, we need you.
No, no, no, no.
Listen to me.
I need you, okay?
Someone cleaned out the Buy More
last night.
They took everything;
they took my sister's ring,
the one she's supposed
to wear forever,
even though she doesn't
know it yet.
Awesome is supposed
to propose to her,
he trusted me
and now it's gone.
Save it for your coffee
klatch, Bartowski.
Get down here.
We got bigger fish to fry.
You robbed the Buy More?
SARAH:
We had no choice, Chuck.
CHUCK:
No choice? Are you
out of your mind?
Do you have any idea
what's going on at
the store right now?
That bug you found,
it isn't one of ours.
What bug?
Who, ours?
SARAH:
The one you found yesterday.
Casey only installed EM-50s.
The one you found was a GLG-20.
It requires a secondary
recording device nearby
to collect the data.
What are you talking about?
Someone is spying on us.
What?!
Okay, listen carefully--
the bug you found was not ours.
It belongs to an enemy agent,
probably Fulcrum,
and they planted it
in the Buy More.
Why?
Looking for
the Intersect.
They're looking for you.
We found a total of
29 bugs just like it,
but we still haven't
found the receiver.
CHUCK:
Okay.
Okay, well, wow.
Uh, extreme...
extreme measures,
but, uh, decisive action
had to be taken.
Good luck schlepping all this
stuff back to the Buy More.
Uh, I'm going to get
back there right now
and pretend like I
don't know anything.
Got any good tips
for beating a polygraph?
Chuck, wait.
What? Ch...?
Oh, duh, yeah...
(chuckles)
Can I get my
sister's ring back?
You guys are pretty
damn thorough.
You should be more concerned
about not making it
to her wedding.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Hold on.
He can't hear it like that.
He won't process it.
How do you give a man
a life sentence
just for being
a good guy?
Okay, how about I
give it a try, gently?
No, I don't want to hear
your version of it
and neither does he.
It's a job.
How come you always
got to get your lady
feelings involved...?
It has nothing to do...
Agent Walker, Major Casey.
You might want to take
a look at this.
This is a surveillance tape
taken during
the robbery.
CASEY:
There's nothing there.
Bad guy disabled
the security system.
Wait.
CHUCK:
Hey, that's Jeff and Lester.
And they are apparently drunk.
It appears they've mistakenly
turned the camera back on.
Hang on a second--
who's that?
SARAH:
That's the spy.
He's the spy who
spies on spies.
CHUCK:
Why would a Fulcrum agent
try to steal Big Mike's fish?
CASEY:
Those two dilweeds
interrupted an actual
robbery in progress.
The receiver's in the fish.
Marlin, actually.
Technically,
it's a marlin.
Marlin.
You would call it a
marlin, right? Yeah.
Look.
See, there you go-- done.
My job here is done.
So now I'm sure you
super-agents can figure out
where the two
drunken pinheads
stashed the fish-- marlin,
four-foot marlin.
I'm going to stick
around here and try
and find my
sister's ring.
Hey, Chuck?
Chuck, no ring came up
in our inventory.
What do you mean no ring
came up in your inventory?
You guys robbed the Buy More,
didn't you?
What happened to Awesome's
great-grandmother's ring?
We kind of have some bigger-
picture concerns right now.
What could be possibly be bigger
than me ruining the chances
of my sister
getting married?
The receiver
may contain information
indicating that
you're the Intersect.
Say it.
Say what you're not saying.
If we don't locate the receiver
in the next 24 hours...
You'll be stored in an
underground bunker for so long
you'll forget what fresh air
smells like.
LESTER & JEFFREY:
One, two, three, four.
I declare a thumb war!
Oh! Come on,
Jeffrey.
Jeff, Lester, we got
to talk, it's important.
Yeah, see, this is
your problem, Charlie.
Why is your time
more valuable than mine?
Oh! He is taking
him over the top!
All right.
Ow! My thumb!
Hey. Let's go.
(fake coughing):
Narc. Narc, Narc. Narc. Narc.
JEFFREY:
Easy on the shirt, Narc.
Where's the fish?
Fish? What fish?
Okay, we can do this
the easy way or the hard way.
Easy way is I shove
his foot up your ass.
What's the hard way?
I use my foot.
CHUCK:
Look, we've seen the
surveillance footage, guys.
Okay? We know you were here
last night.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, no,
you two geniuses
thought you were
turning the cameras off,
but, instead,
you turned them back on.
We won't say anything
to Big Mike, I promise.
Okay.
Come on, wh-what's
happening?
Charles, would you give us
a few minutes, please?
Chuck...?
It was his idea.
What?!
The whole reason we snuck in
was to get your alcoholic ass
another drink-- you
were getting the shakes.
Not cool.
It's a disease.
You're a disease,
and you've diseased us all--
me, Chuck, this guy.
C-Calm down. Calm down.
Okay.
Look, Jeff, I totally
understand your plight.
We sympathize
with you, okay?
And we don't judge.
Just tell us
what exactly happened?
We were across
the street at Bennigan's
and I got
cut off again...
Jeff.
If you're going
to tell the story,
please...
don't butcher it.
We were at Benni's, enjoying
the deep-fried sampler,
and we decided
to come back to the store
for a nightcap in boss man's
private stash.
It's off.
(groans)
Rock and roll.
We have the store
to ourselves.
We should take off
all our clothes.
Don't make me uncomfortable
to be alone with you.
Go get it.
Bingo.
Yes.
No.
No, no, no.
Jeffrey!
It's a wasted mission now.
It's a wasted mission.
We've gotta do something
exciting while we're here, man.
We can burn it down.
I was thinking more along
the lines of a...
fishing expedition.
And that, friends...
is the story
of the missing marlin.
And where is the marlin now?
I'm afraid I'm going to need
a little compensation.
(cries out)
At Chuck's!
We took it to Chuck's pad!
What? My apartment? Why?
We didn't want to get busted
with Big Mike's fish.
LESTER:
I'm going to
need lotion.
SARAH:
We're pursuing the receiver.
We've got the location,
and it shouldn't be long
before recovery.
Stay with the receiver.
In the meantime we've decided
to extract Chuck.
What? But we don't know
he's in danger.
There's a chance
the identity of the Intersect
has been compromised.
We have to err
on the side of caution.
You promised we had 48 hours.
You know the game, Agent Walker.
The order has gone out.
Chuck is coming in.
Come on.
Chuck, you're looking
for a marlin.
Hey, hey, whoa.
Whoa, stop, stop.
I seriously doubt
that these geniuses
had time
to reupholster the couch.
It's got to be here somewhere.
Chuck?
Hey, sis.
John.
Hi.
What are you two up to?
What's going on
with the apartment?
I'll clean it up later.
Right now, we're
looking for something.
What is it?
Look, I-I promise you
whatever you want to talk
about is not as important
as what we're looking
for right now.
Okay.
What are you looking for?
A stuffed fish.
A fish?
Marlin, actually,
about four feet long.
Got a spear-like nose.
And a mouth. Yeah.
Okay, Chuck, I get it.
Besides, if anything
really important
were going on,
you have plenty of people
in your life you can
talk to about it.
Hey, Ellie, wait.
What?
Oh!
I love you.
Just in case.
Just in case of what?
Uh....
Just-just in case
I can't find the fish.
I suppose you haven't
talked to Morgan.
No. Why?
Because he left here last night
with a four-foot long marlin.
He's mine.
And you know nothing about
the stolen merchandise?
No, sir. Officer. Detective.
Where's my fish, Grimes?
Mr. Tucker, please.
The merchandise is insured.
That fish cost me 200 bucks
on eBay.
Wait, you bought that fish?
That will be
all, Mr. Grimes.
What did you use
for bait, PayPal?
CONWAY:
Grimes, out!
All right. Yes, sir.
You cracked,
didn't you?
LESTER:
You are so weak.
JEFFREY:
You are so weak, man.
How am I weak, dude?
I didn't say anything.
In fact, I told...
How am I supposed
to believe that?
Bartowski! You're up.
I got the scraggly troll.
I-I did not rob the store.
Did I ask you that?
Already he's talking
about stolen goods.
You might as well come out
and admit you did it.
Please.
Let me handle
the investigation.
Now, Mr. Bartowski,
we believe
this was an inside job.
None of these other imbeciles
could even tie their shoes
without Bartowski's say-so.
If there's a ringleader,
you're looking at him.
Where's my fish, Bartowski?!
Okay, start talking.
From the beginning.
Okay.
Um... I was born
a Cesarean section.
And I always felt
like I was robbed
of that headlong voyage
through the uterine canal.
Where's the marlin, moron?
Ah, the elusive fish. Sure.
That's a tale for the ages.
Start talking or I'll pull
each and every one
of these hairs out of
your face, one at a time,
starting with this one.
(groans)
Torture?
Hey, if you're trying
to get me to talk,
you are using
the wrong tactic, brother.
Really?
What's the right tactic?
My own personal kryptonite:
Grape soda.
On the rocks, please.
Conway.
Excuse me, I have
to take this.
I got this.
Ah.
You don't want to talk,
Bartowski?
We'll just have to turn the heat
up on you.
Mm-hmm.
There we go.
Ah. Proper.
So, it all started with
"The Next Call of Duty" game...
Now, I don't really
consider it stealing,
since I see Chuck and I
as being life partners
and therefore,
community property.
Using my own personal entrance,
I went into Chuck's room
to play the game.
Yessss!
And when I reached
into the bag, I discovered a...
I found a, uh...
I can't go on.
This is just getting
a little personal.
All right, new tactic:
You finish the story
or I put your head
through the wall.
Okay, someone wasn't hugged
enough as a child.
Ugh.
That's horrible.
It's better on the rocks,
that's why I told you to...
Anyway, there I was...
staring at the most horrific
object the world has ever seen.
Noooooo!
What?
Morgan, you scared me
to death!
What is wrong with you?
No, no,
no, no, no...
no, it's Chuck.
Well, what is it?
What happened?
We've lost him, Ell.
We've lost him
forever.
You better sit down.
Um...
I don't know how
to say this.
He's gone.
Morgan, what are you
talking about?
I'm talking about this.
Chuck's going to
propose to Sarah.
And that's pretty much
the whole story.
More or less.
Ellie and I bonded
over the fact that,
you know, he didn't include us
in this life decision.
But, hey, who cares, you know,
he's got you now, so...
What does that have
to do with the fish?
F-Fish? Who cares
about the fish?
John, Chuck's getting married!
Pitas are here.
Hey.
You've had 29 deliveries,
so I dropped in
your free baba ganoush.
Really?
29 deliveries.
Uh-huh.
29 bugs.
Wait a second.
Oh, lunch!
Thank you.
Ooh!
Hey, buddy.
I-I smell falafel.
Yeah, of course
you do.
What do you got?
I got the chick...
I'm just going to,
let me just have a...
No, no.
You're going to
finish the story.
Back to the story.
Ooh!
Come on.
"Boobies."
Jackpot.
Gotcha!
Good thing Jeff
and Lester are pervs.
I can see you're sweating it.
So...
you ready to tell us what
happened here last night?
I'm telling you guys,
I have no idea.
Fine.
There's other ways
to make you talk.
Time to send you back
to gen pop.
He sung like a canary!
Thanks for the
info, Chuck.
John Casey! You're next!
One sec.
What? Can't fit the police
into your social schedule?
Get in here now,
or you and I are taking
a trip downtown!
If you have a second,
Mr. Casey,
we'd appreciate it.
LESTER:
I can't believe
you told Casey
you put the marlin
in Chuck's room.
What?
Don't worry.
I moved it
into the freezer at
the Wienerlicious.
Wow, I'm impressed
with you.
Thank you.
Bye.
What? Where you going?
Where you going? Where
you going, Lizzie?
Lizzie? Where's she going?
Can I help you?
Yeah.
I was wondering
if I could get something
out of your freezer.
Oh, uh, I'm sorry.
It's company policy.
The kitchen is usually off-
limits for non-employees.
Okay, then I'll have to use
my special pass...
You're no hot dog maker.
Bring it on, pita girl.
We're closed!
Where's the fish?
We need to talk.
It's an emergency.
Oh, listen, no, hey,
hey, hey, Chuck, Chuck,
it's okay, man, I know
about you and Sarah.
Man, and how she's more
than just your girlfriend.
What?
Morgan, stay.
But I...
Sta... stay!
Hello.
After careful consideration
of all potential proposals,
I have made a decision.
Oh, let me guess: Naked 2K run?
Dinner, Chuck.
Romantic, candlelit dinner,
just the two of us.
The coup de grce...
Wow. Good.
molten lava cake with a
two-carat diamond ring filling.
Ellie will really
love that.
Look, Devon,
just-just promise me
that you'll take care
of my sister
if anything were to happen.
What's gonna happen?
Oh, hey,
cake hits the oven in two hours.
Don't be late.
What am I gonna do?
Do nothing.
You haven't given Sarah
the ring yet.
Dude, there's plenty of time
to call this whole thing off.
Sarah? Ring?
Yeah, the ring
you got Sarah.
The one I kind of took
out of your locker.
You mean...
the ring that Awesome
got for Ellie.
Oh, thank God, man.
Are you kidding?
I thought I lost you, pal!
Morgan... where is the ring?
It's kind of
complicated but...
It's in the freezer
at the Wienerlicious.
I put it in
Big Mike's marlin and I...
I was gonna put it back.
Ow!
Slide it to me.
Now!
Hey!
Hi, S...
No...
No, no!
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
(distant):
Help!
Sarah?
Lizzie's the mole.
She got the receiver, Chuck.
Oh, my God, Sarah, it's over.
They're gonna stick me
in some tiny cell
with no windows.
Okay, Chuck,
I need you to focus.
We can get Lizzie
if you can get me out of here.
How?
I keep a backup piece
in the jar of horseradish sauce.
Horseradish?
Who-Who-Who puts horseradish
on hot dogs?
Chuck!
Got it. Right.
Hide it someplace nobody
would look-- good.
Great. Okay.
Oh! Whoa.
I got it. Okay.
Okay, now shoot
the lock.
Um, look, Sarah,
I've never really fired
a gun before, okay?
And I've actually
done this on purpose
to avoid any unpleasant
side effects
like shooting myself
or others.
Just shoot the lock
or I will shoot you
when I get out of here!
(gasping):
Okay.
Get back. Ready?
Ready? Get back.
One...
Two...
Take the safety
off first.
One, one sec...
just a little problem.
CONWAY:
Bartowski, Big Mike told me
I'd find you here.
Drop the gun, Bartowski!
Now!
No, no, no,
no need to shoot.
It's not my gun, it's not
my gun-- my girlfriend
is locked in the freezer,
and if you let her out
she can explain
everything.
Okay, let's go.
She's right...
Come on, move.
Okay, okay.
Just look in...
Nice try.
Go, go, go!
Look in the freezer, please!
Just look in the freezer.
She's right there.
You're taking this thing
a little seriously.
What kind of
cop are you?
Where's Big Mike's fish?
What are you now, huh?
Big Man's personal Gestapo?
Come on, you can't
break me, fool.
At the Wienerlicious.
SARAH:
Help!
Sarah.
Stand back.
The delivery girl
is the mole.
The detective took Chuck.
Where are you, Chuck?
I need the ring.
This is not awesome.
MAN:
And the package, HQ.
This is Long Shore.
You're not a cop.
We've identified
the enemy agent.
She was posing
as a Pita Parlour
delivery girl.
Code name Lizzie.
BECKMAN:
So she escaped
with the receiver?
Yes, but she made a phone call.
We're currently tracing
the cell signature,
and we can triangulate
her location.
We just need more time.
GRAHAM:
As soon as you locate her,
take her out.
Uh, one of us
needs to go
and get Chuck out
of police custody.
He was arrested just...
BECKMAN:
The Intersect
is no longer your concern,
Agent Walker.
I... I don't understand.
BECKMAN:
Detective Conway is CIA.
GRAHAM:
Chuck is on his way
to the extraction
point right now.
We've decided to transfer him
to lockdown immediately.
Is there a problem?
Uh, no.
No. I just thought
I would handle his transfer.
Forget about Chuck,
Agent Walker.
Focus on catching
that FULCRUM agent.
We're on it.
We, meaning,
I go get Lizzie
while you find Chuck.
Well, don't make me
change my mind.
So...
this is it, huh?
Going to get my own padded cell.
Do I get a bed, or is
my whole room
kind of like a bed?
It's not as bad as it sounds.
The underground complex
where you
will be living
has state-of-the-art
security and amenities.
You'll even be allowed outside
to visit controlled locations.
Hold on.
I-I... I can't leave
without telling Ellie something,
a reason for going.
What should I say?
Nothing.
It's safer for them
if you just... disappear.
CONWAY:
Asset is ready for extraction.
Send in the chopper.
Long Shore!
Is there a problem,
Agent Walker?
Sarah,
thank God you're here.
Listen, I-I don't...
I don't want
to go yet. I...
It's okay, Chuck. Agent Casey
is tracking the
FULCRUM mole.
He should have her
in custody soon,
so we can hold off
on the Chuck transfer
for the time being.
If there was a change
in the operation,
I would have been contacted.
I have my orders.
We don't have to do this.
This is a judgment call.
Okay, we can just hold Chuck
here until we know for sure.
His cover was blown.
He's gone.
No. I will take
full responsibility.
Chuck is my asset;
he's my guy.
Just... Just give us
more time, please.
CHUCK:
I'd appreciate it.
I really would.
Please don't do this.
CONWAY:
Okay.
You've got one minute.
One minute.
I'm not ready, Sarah.
I'm not ready
to disappear.
No. I know,
I know.
I need you to talk to Ellie
and to Morgan and my friends,
and-and-
and-and tell 'em...
I don't know. I...
Look, if I'm supposed
to be dead, just say something
that will make it okay,
that will make 'em
feel all right.
Just make sure they know
how much I love 'em.
You can do that, right?
Course you can. You're Sarah.
You can do anything.
And, hey, there's a silver
lining to this, too, you know,
'cause we're not working
together anymore,
which means,
we can go on a date.
You can come by my cell,
and we can hang out,
and you can tell me
who the president is.
And maybe, uh...
...maybe we can see
how we really feel.
Time's up.
Good-bye, Sarah.
Chuck?
I'll save you later.
(gunshot)
Oh!
Chuck, get down.
(gunshot)
Go, go, go!
I listened to the receiver.
BOTH:
She knows.
Do you know
how many agents are looking
for Bryce Larkin?
And all this time,
the Intersect was here.
Wait till
I tell my superiors that.
Okay, look, what if
I surrender, and you run?
I mean, I'm going
in a cell anyway.
What's the difference?
Torture.
Okay, no surrender.
I only have one question, Chuck.
Who's the ring for?
She has Ellie's
engagement ring?
Try to distract her.
What?! How?
Chuck, I'm not gonna
to go away.
Okay... okay,
look, look, look.
You really... You really
want to take me in?
You're going to have
to sweeten the deal
a little bit for me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Uh, look.
Look, the CIA--
they're offering me a nice
padded cell, real cush.
Can you beat that?
I'm a guy who enjoys
a... a good steam.
Can you do...?
Can you do maybe a
steam room or something?
I don't think you're really
in a position to bargain, Chuck.
I have two guns.
What do you have?
Me.
Don't break the ring.
Whoa!
Oh! Oh!
Hey! Bartowski,
get out of the way.
There's really
some serious spy
fighting going on.
CASEY:
Get down, Bartowski.
Sarah!
(grunts)
I had a feeling
that girl was dirty.
Norman.
The power of positive thinking.
This was an amazing night.
As it always is with...
But, sometimes, I know life
isn't always awesome.
What I'm trying to say is that,
when things get rough,
I want to face them together,
the good times and the bad..
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Ladies' feminine products.
That's not good.
Are you, uh...
Are you sure tAre yo
Are you sure that Lizzie
didn't have the ring on her?
When they took her away,
all she had was the receiver.
Oh, then it's got
to be here somewhere.
You know, Chuck, if
we can't find it, we
can just replace it.
Look, look, look, it-it was
Awesome's great-granny's ring,
and it's going
to be my sister's, okay?
Even if its covered in coffee
grounds and miscellaneous DNA.
I have a ring, I have
the blessing of your brother.
Will you do me the honor
of becoming my wife,
Eleanor Faye Bartowski?
CAPTAIN:
Ooh. Almost woke her up.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Ah! Hey!
Oh, I found it!
Let's go.
I'm so sorry...
but it might be
a little dirty.
Way to go, Chuck.
I always knew you could
handle my family jewels.
So to speak.
Uh, when she's sleeping
really hard like that,
sometimes, if you pinch
her nose, it'll wake...
Right.
I'm going to...
Oh, okay.
Mission accomplished.
I can't believe
we pulled it off.
That'll make one hell
of a story at their wedding.
Which I'm never allowed
to talk about under fear
of death-- understood.
I have other material.
You want to?
What, spy? You?
She looks so happy.
Yeah, she does.
I couldn't
leave them yet.
You don't have
to worry about that.
You're safe.
Yeah, safe for now,
though. Right.
I mean... they keep
getting closer.
Eventually, they're going
to figure out who I am.
Don't you think you should
go in and congratulate Ellie?
You want to
come in with me?
Oh, it's family time.
I know.
Well, good night.
CHUCK (laughing):
Hey!
Hey, buddy.
Yeah.
Hmm.
We can only keep him here
for so long.
You realize that,
don't you?
I love you,
sweetie.
I love you.
I'm sorry I had to keep it
a secret for a little while.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入