You woke up this morning
got yourself a gun
your mama always said
you'd be the chosen one
she said
you're one in a million
you've got to burn
to shine
but you were
born under a bad sign
with a blue moon
in your eyes
when you woke up
this mornin'
all that love had gone
your papa never told you
about right and wrong
but you're, but you're
looking good, baby
i believe that
you're a- feelin' fine
shame about it
born under a bad sign
with a blue moon in your eyes
so sing it now
woke up this morning
you got a blue moon
got a blue moon in your eyes?
?
Yeah
you say you
woke up this morning
the world turned
upside down
lord above, things ain't
been the same
since the blues
walked into town
but you're, but you're
one in a million'cause you
got that shotgun shine
shame about it
born under a bad sign
with a blue moon
in your eyes, yeah
woke up this morning
got yourself a gun
come on. Come on, dog.
Come on, come on, come on.
Go get it.
Look at this.
Look at this plastic.
And there's weeds.
It looks like
tobacco road.
Nobody gets down here.
Anthony!
Those dogs are wild dogs.
Cemetery dogs.
They'll take your hand off.
Come over here.
Say a hail mary
for your grandfather.
Lay off. He's a kid.
So he should
neglect his elders?
Just like his father.
Yeah, real scamp.
Yeah, my son,
the mental patient.
Remember those trips
to the shore?
Me and tony used to
ride the waves?
- I taught him how to bodysurf.
- My son was brought up right.
He needs a psychiatrist
for what?
To talk about his sex life?
Enough.
I hate it
as much as you do.
Anthony!
Those dogs could start
foaming at the mouth.
Hey, grandma. How come
youse not supposed to
breathe in the cemetery?
Who says?
It's a joke, for christ's sake.
Say "why?"
'Cause you'll make
the dead people jealous.
Pick it up! Pick it up!
Who's got the ball?
- Who's got the ball?
- Oh, my god.
Meadow, look out!
Come around, come around!
Up, up, up!
Cover'em through!
- I can't watch.
- Yes!
- Atta girl, meadow!
You're a brick wall, baby!
Brick wall!
Good save! Come on, now!
Come on!
That was close.
Pretty good.
Look at you
at girl's soccer, tony.
What do you want from me?
My only son's a couch potato.
- Red, five!
- What are you,
yellow card happy?
Rough play, my ass!
Oh, come on!
Hi, honey.
Got get'em, baby.
This fat kid is such a sneak
with that elbow!
Coach says next year
chiara is gonna be
one of his stars.
Come on, falcons! Let's
pull it out, for christ sake!
Heather dante!
- A hundred bucks for a goal!
- What's with ally today?
She's sleepwalkin' out there.
She eats at our house
three nights a week.
I know she's got the energy.
That tackle was all ball,
asshole!
Yeah, zebra,
i'm talkin' to you!
You blow that whistle
one more time, i'm gonna
stick it up your fuckin' ass!
Get off the field! Now!
Get off the field or your team
is gonna forfeit the game!
I'm goin'.
You fuckin' son of a--
get off the field!
You're a hell of a guy.
Falcons!
Falcons, heads up!
Red 42, 42! Push!
Ally! Come on.
Come on, al!
Yes, yes, yes!
Did i tell you?
He's a brilliant coach.
He's a beautiful,
brilliant genius.
Yeah. You in love
with him or what?
Frankly, yes.
If he steers chiara through
to a college scholarship,
i'll blow the guy at midfield.
Oh, you will?
How's cheffing at dimples?
You gotta come sample
the salad bar. We got
a special chemical brightener.
Keeps the lettuce crisp.
How nice.
Oh, yeah.
It's beautiful.
The offer's still there.
You wanna make a little money,
you put some out on the street,
at two points,
we split the interest.
Nice.
I can't do the math,
ton'. I'm an artiste.
Get outta here.
Good job, girls!
Absolutely, yeah.
You do that so well, coach.
Thank you.
You did a hell of a job,
coach.
Welcome to the bada bing.
Everything's on the house.
Brandy! Come here!
I want you to meet somebody.
- This guy coached college.
- Get outta here.
Division 1- a!
Nay, that's boonie state.
Besides, art, the time
has come to stop moving
my wife and deena...
like pawns every time
somebody ups the ante.
Anyway, now many chances
does a man get to coach
his own daughter?
What do they say?
"Money isn't everything."
Hear, hear.
- It's the kids
that are important.
- Cheers to the falcons.
Continued success.
Brandy, why don't you give
the coach a deluxe tour
of the vip lounge?
What?
Oh, guys.
Jesus,
we said a beer.
Oh, whoa-- no, i--
uh, thank you, but
i don't think so.
Aw, jesus christ.
Okay, brandy, go, uh,
sit on a tuffet.
Coach,
it's on the house.
- What the fuck are you
doin' here?
- Who's he?
My girl's soccer coach.
You got somethin' for me?
For one thing, every car you see
in your rearview mirror
is not a fed.
Mikey palmice went out
and got a major manhattan p. I.
Mikey palmice thinks
someone here is rattin'
for the government.
What else is new?
What else?
My colleague over at
organized crime task force...
gets chatty after, uh,
caffeine drinks.
Names of people
whose fiscal interests
intersect with your own.
Shit.
I'm still trying to find out
if you've been named.
But these people, they are
keeping these indictments
very, very internal, tony.
For all i know, they got
a folder withmyname on it,
and if i was smart,
i wouldn't be here.
I rest my case.
As it is, i'm up the street
on a rape/homicide.
What i need now, is to see
a liquor license, sir,
if you don't mind.
So anybody wonders
why i was here, or
for the lie detector test--
cha- cha, show him
the liquor license.
Don't touch the girls.
How you doin'?
Bada bing. Arthur bucco!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hello?
- What, you gonna stay
in that bar all day?
I'm shootin'
a little pool.
I'll rack'em up for you.
I thought we were supposed
to be painting the trim
on the patio.
I bought the primer
and i've been scraping.
- You have.
- Arthur, i could really
use your help.
All right. Sure.
Honey, i'll be right home.
This fuckin' guy lays down
the law, ton'.
Fuckin' blisterin'.
I'll be right home, honey.
I've gotta be
getting home too.
Shelly'll be looking for me.
It's quite the lifestyle
you got here, though.
See you later,
coach.
Okay.
Different strokes.
Melvoin, frolov, schneider
and archide.
I'm sorry.
He's in a meeting.
Can i take a message?
What's goin' on with the feds
and their fuckin' indictment?
Just put it
right down there.
Here's the bill.
The book is off
from the 14th ward.
I don't wanna minimize
your position, corrado.
Two prior convictions.
That places you in jeopardy
of sentence...
under the
habitual offenders statute.
I'm payin' you four an hour
to hear shit that's already
eatin' my insides?
Who had the peppers
and eggs?
Over here.
That's what i should've had.
I'd be happy
to surrender mr. Soprano?
You can be assured
of my full cooperation?
You'd rather they kicked in
your front door
in the middle of the night?
It's a target letter,
corrado.
I wasn't getting anywhere,
so i asked them point blank
what your status was.
Just testing. That's what
a good lawyer would do.
- They'd let me know
when it was appropriate.
- I may just start paying taxes.
- Fuckin' funny. -
i'm sick and tired
of sittin' around here
on my hands.
I'm gonna get outta here.
Down to boca
with your lady friend?
- What the fuck you know?
- Works for the joint fitters
union, didn't somebody say?
Runs their, uh,
labor management fund
outside the fed's oversight.
If you can't get
your friends jobs, what's the
purpose of attaining success?
The wheels of justice
turn slowly.
Take her to florida.
Develop a tan.
- Where's the key
to the partners' crapper?
- Top right- hand drawer.
Junior, we're working out of
our fuckin' lawyer's office.
Is that right?
I didn't want to say anything,
but this government's case?
If there's a leak,
it's in tony's boat.
You wanna tell me...
my nephew's in bed with
the justice department,
just say it.
Don't stammer around
like a fuckin' spastic.
There's something
fucking wrong with that guy.
I feel it in my gut.
I'm worried about you,
skipper.
I'm sorry, mikey.
You're a good boy.
Fuck this.
I'm goin' to boca.
Deena, when you guys showed up
to verbum dei last year,
i thought,"soccer.
Give me a break."
But your dad makes it seem
like this, i don't know,
metaphor.
Yeah.
Yeah, dad's pretty cool.
You guys, where's al?
She was supposed to
loan me a cig.
I'll come with.
Al?
Ally!
Al!
If you're smoking,
you owe me five dollars!
Al?
Ally?
- Ally, what are you doing?
- Ally!
Oh, my god! Ally!
Ally! Oh, my god!
Her parents split up.
That's why she spends
all her time at our house.
But the kid was born
with a silver spoon.
Teenage girls are
under a lot of stress.
I know this kid.
She's great.
Was it a genuine
suicide attempt, or was
it a suicidal gesture?
"Small cutting"
is the clinical term.
What's "large cutting"?
O. J. In the missing tracksuit?
It's a cry for help.
Ah.
Her mother says she...
tried this before.
A couple times.
What else is going on
in your life?
Life is putting
the prozac to the test.
It's all that business that
keeps popping up in the news?
I'd rather talk about
my daughter.
Principal says girls in sports,
they do better.
They don't take the drugs,
they don't get knocked up.
But now this shit.
If my daughter ever tried
to kill herself--
oh, god!
Last week
i called you a whore.
I might've been...
overstatin' the case
a little bit.
Oo- hoo.
Mr. Soprano.
Miss sanfillipo.
I have a check here
for you to sign.
Twenty grand.
For research
and development...
into furthering
the art and science...
of metal and ceramic
joint fitting.
Where does our research
and development
take us this time?
I was thinking
boca raton.
My, my.
You read my mind.
I'm all packed, baby.
I gotta talk to my cousin.
Uh, mr. Soprano?
What?
I was waitin' to talk to jerry
about how i could use some, uh,
wiggle room...
on this mall job i got
in north bergen.
Then i saw you here.
And i thought,
"what the hell?
I may as well
ask the man himself."
Let's you and i meet.
I can pass my recommends
onto my cousin.
Hey, mama livia, how are you?
Do you remember me,
larry boy barese?
Well, i know
who you are!
You lit an apartment house
on fire...
and scared your mother
half to death.
Mama's moving in here
on the fifteenth.
I like your shoes,
larry boy.
Mama hasn't been well in
her mind. Last week she threw
a jar of artichokes at me.
She better not throw
any artichokes at me!
Ma, how you doin'?
- Remember larry?
- Water under the bridge.
Yeah. We're gonna take a walk.
We'll be right back.
You should get some shoes
like his.
I'll tell you somethin',
tony. You've always been
a fuckin' genius.
But this last move is
the best move you ever did.
The feds are never gonna
surveil an old folks home.
That's why i got six truckloads
of bootleg polident comin' in.
Hey, jimmy.
How you doin'?
There he is.
Did you get your mother
settled into a suite?
They're not sure they're
gonna accept her.
They wanna see my
financial statement again.
So this office supply chain
comin' up from virginia.
What's the deal on them?
I spoke to them.
I think they're gonna listen
to reason on minority hiring.
You been to games?
What've they got?
What the fuck?
Hup! Hup! Hup!
Hup! Hup!
Knees high, colgiavani!
Eyes ahead!
Energy, girls, energy!
I know we're all upset about
all that's been going on, but
we still have a season left!
Come on!
Let's go!
Hey, coach.
Hey, fellas. Uh, sorry,
but practice is closed today.
I'm trying to
keep the team focused.
What're you doin'?
You're leavin' us?
After two fuckin' years?
I told that reporter
to wait until after sectionals
before he put that in the paper.
Coach, look at my little girl
out there.
- You're breakin' her heart!
- Believe me, art.
I am hugely conflicted.
But rhode island
doubled my salary!
They're giving my daughter
a full ride!
What could i do?
- They made me an offer
i couldn't refuse.
- You haven't heard ours.
Come on, sil.
Look, buddy,
i got a family too.
I happen to have a daughter
who loves playing soccer
very much.
Just kiddin'
about the offer thing.
Hey, nobody blew a whistle!
Let's not get lazy
out here! Come on!
- Why don't you
go fuck yourself?
- Excuse me?
Hey, med, want me
to tell your father--
this is my field.
Why don't you give me
ten laps around the goals!
Whatever.
Make that 20.
Anybody else
wanna mouth off?
Good! Come on!
Let's circle up
for keep- away!
Let's go! Over here!
Get in a big circle!
Go! Come on! Move it!
Out here!
I need some people out here!
Come on! Let's go!
Gimme your glass.
Who would've ever thought
we could've been
this contented?
I did. As soon
as i saw you, i knew.
You're a sweetheart.
If only they knew
the other side of you.
They'd eat me
for breakfast.
Mmm.
I've been lookin'
at some real estate.
Some nice houses on the market.
Maybe you'd like
something bigger.
No, corrado.
This is our place.
You know how long
we been comin' here?
Sixteen years.
And every one of them good.
How's junior, junior?
Hmm?
He's catching some shuteye.
Oh. You're such
a powerhouse.
When you kiss me
down there,
you're like
a great artist.
You got a real instinct
for it.
Pass me the red peppers.
You know the thrill
you give?
Just keep it to yourself,
okay, roberta?
Yeah.
All to myself.
Corrado?
Yeah?
Why the big secret?
About what?
Oral sex.
What's so terrible
about pleasing a woman?
You always have to
talk about everything.
I wanna know why!
It's complicated.
Yeah.
But why?
Why?
Because they think
if you'll suck pussy,
you'll suck anything.
Oh, you're kidding.
It's a sign of weakness.
And possibly a sign
that you're afinocch'.
A fag?
That's ridiculous.
How would the two
even translate?
What are you gonna do?
I mean, i don't make the rules.
Hey, it's not big
lifestyle choice, shylockin'.
My aunts quintima
and gemma.
They got money out
earnin' on the street.
It's like bein' a banker.
You help people.
Chiara broke down in tears
when she heard the coach
was leaving.
You don't wanna
talk about it, fine.
No, i--
i gotta go pick up
carmela at her sister's.
Let me ask you a question.
Why does your wife hate me?
Charmaine doesn't hate you.
Yeah.
You lie
like i play the french horn.
What?
Look at the fuckin'faccim
over here. Wearing a cap
in a nice restaurant like this.
That's one of the things
i hated most when i had
my restaurant.
It's values today.
Standards are crumbling.
Would it have killed
this coach to stick around
until my kid graduates?
Then let him stay four years
for chiara.
Hi.
That burns my ass.
Where you goin'?
That would be great.
- Take your hat off.
- Excuse me?
They don't sell hot dogs here.
They took the bleachers out
two years ago.
It's my hat.
I'll wear it where i want.
How you doin'?
- Thank you.
- Look at him. Douche bag.
Good for you!
Um, send them a bottle
of montepulciano.
And, uh, get the license plate
of these two guys
sittin' behind artie.
Get the valet to do it.
They look like cops.
I hear a voice
well, look who's here!
Hi!
Tony, look who's here!
Alphonse, how you doin'?
Good. Yeah.
You feelin' better?
Gonna miss that
left foot of yours.
Tony.
No, it's okay, mr. Soprano.
I'm gonna play.
No shit.
Pardon my french there.
You sure, ally?
Yeah, i-- i had a long talk
with coach hauser and--
i'm gonna play.
That's all.
- I told her she didn't have to.
- Just said she wanted to.
- Yeah.
- Did coach pressure you,
ally?
No, mrs. Soprano.
He would never do anything
like that.
How's he gonna pressure her?
He didn't have thecoglione
to stick around.
Dad.
What?
It's what we all wanted.
Okay. Right?
Long as everything's, uh--
look, we're trying
to watch this, guys, okay?
Kick ass, girls.
Right?
Good night.
Listen, roberta.
What i said earlier?
Mm- hmm.
I'm serious.
You discuss that with anyone,
we're gonna go ten rounds.
We just skimmed 20 thou
off the development fund,
and you're worried about
a littlelecca fica?
Will you keep it down?
All right.
I'll tell everyone
you're a good kisser.
I just won't say where.
That's my reputation
you're playin' with.
Honey, my lips are sealed.
Not too sealed, right?
Visual on corrado soprano
and female travel companion,
2200 hours, boca lounge.
Hey, hey, hey!
How's my boy today, huh?
Go, go, go!
I'm lookin' for, uh,
coach hauser?
That's me. Petey!
Come here!
A little somethin'
from your friends
at the bada bing club.
Brand new, surround sound,
hdtv compatible.
- Well, tell them thanks, but--
- this fucker's gettin' heavy.
If this is about rhode island,
tell your friends it's
a done deal. I already signed.
I don't know what it's about,
but the tv stays here.
Put it down.
No!
I mean it! Pick it up!
Get the goddamn thing
off my property!
Look, pal, i don't think
you quite understand.
Oh, i understand
only too well.
You tell your friends
i know all about them.
If you did,
you'd do what they want.
Is that a threat?
How quickly things change.
Let me tell you something,
guido--
my name is clarence.
I have friends in
law enforcement, and they
would call this extortion.
Come on.
You tell those assholes
don hauser will not be
intimidated!
I will not be threatened
or bribed!
I go where i want to
when i want to!
Hey!
All day, every day,
85 and not one drop of rain.
Oh, and those nights.
Bobbi, you are so lucky
with this guy.
You have no idea.
He's a sweetheart
underneath it all.
I wish i could get lou
to be like him.
More sensitive,
if you know what i mean.
That coral looks good.
I don't understand why i always
have to ask him for oral sex.
Not like you
and your corrado.
Bebe, listen.
I know we always used to
yak about our sex lives.
I think it would be better
if we didn't anymore.
Okay.
I mean it.
Sure. It's just
you're lucky, that's all.
- So, ma, you gonna come
to the big game?
- Game?
What game?
Miss meadow's soccer team
is goin' to the sectionals.
- Nobody tells me anything.
- Everybody hear me just tell
my mother about the game?
Can anybody
think of anything else
to talk about except soccer?
All right. Uncle jun',
how was boca?
Wonderful.
I don't go down enough.
That's not what i heard.
About what?
Nothing. I'm sorry.
I-- i don't know
what i'm talkin' about.
- Last time, aunt bobbi
bought me a live piranha.
- You believe that was a piranha.
That woman is not your aunt!
Livia, i warned you.
Stata zit'.
Bobbi's a sweet, sweet girl.
- What the hell's
the matter with you? -
what did i say?
This wife of yours.
She's got the giggles.
- Can i be excused?
- We just sat down.
- How are you gonna play
tomorrow, you don't eat?
- He's right. You need protein.
- No, i don't because i quit.
- You quit.
What are you talkin' about?
With ally back, you can
go to the state.
A girl slits her wrists
and you can think about
is a game?
It wasn't like friggin' cobain.
It was just a little
suicidal gesture.
- Come back here!
- You're not excused!
Oh, let her go.
Go ahead, honey!
Ma!
Why don't you butt out?
Only time you act like
a grandmother is when
you wanna score some points.
I will not eat in this house.
Junior, take me home.
- I'm not finished.
- Youmangia, uncle jun'.
She'll come back.
The stukas and messerschmitts.
They have command
of the skies.
The stuka is quite
a formidable weapon.
I don't know.
I'm glad meadow quit.
That coach pushes them
to the brink.
It's unhealthy.
Well, what do we mean
when we talk about commitment?
And that asshole.
He thinks he can just
walk away?
Watch it, cowboy.
Don't start.
What was with you
and uncle jun' tonight?
You better not get
in that coach's face.
Tell me about uncle jun'.
No, no, stop it!
Stop it!
I can't, i can't.
Yes, you can.
I know you want to.
All right. Okay.
Gabby dante's cousin and bobbi
go to the same nail parlor.
And--
your uncle-- no, i shouldn't
say. I shouldn't!
Come on.
Okay, okay! Okay.
Well, let's just say...
your uncle has acquired
a taste for her.
Uncle jun' gives head.
World- class.
The old man's whistlin'
to the wheat field?
Don't be disgusting.
He's a bushman
of the kalahari!
That's why i don't tell you
anything. 'cause you
don't know when to stop.
Oh, my god,
if this ever gets out.
Like you don't do it,
or any of your friends.
Bunch of hypocrites.
Hey. What goes on
in this bedroom stays here,
and you know that.
Once a year?
I can resist the urge
to gossip.
Arthur? You're home?
The grease in that "fryolater."
I'm gonna smell like
a cheap french fry
for the rest of my life.
So this is why we scrimp
and save to send our kids
to that school, huh?
So that you can have our name
just dragged through the mud?
What?
Shelly hauser called me
this afternoon.
Your friends sent somewayos
down there with a stolen
tv set...
to try and bribe the coach.
From your friends
at bada bing.
As if a tv set is gonna
get somewhere with a man
like coach hauser!
A tv set?
Arthur, do you
honestly believe that
they're gonna stop there?
They tried
bribing this man.
What's next?
Always with
the extreme scenarios.
No, come on, arthur.
Tell me. What's next?
You grew up
in the neighborhood.
Don't pretend
like you don't know what
tony soprano is capable of.
Who is it?
I found your dog.
What?
No, you're mistaken.
My dog is upstairs.
Golden retriever,
blue nylon collar?
Honey, who is it?
Evenin', ma'am.
He has our dog.
Where's petey?
I thought he was locked in.
Yeah, come get him.
I wouldn't want petey
to get hit by a car.
Petey, petey!
You okay? Come here.
What, no reward?
Just kiddin'.
I'm an animal lover.
You okay, boy?
Med, you can cheer up
about the coach,
'cause i got a feelin'
he's gonna reconsider
the big move.
- Tony!
- Did you do something?
What could i do?
Point is...
he's gonna stick around
and finish what he started
with the girls, that's all.
That's it.
Well, did i tell you?
You need to develop
some appreciation'cause you
got people all around you...
tryin' to help you and
all you do is bitch and moan!
I see this coach tryin' to
abandon his team. I see
your friends gettin' worked up.
So i try to do somethin'!
Is that why you think
we're so upset, dad?
Because a coach that most of us
can't even stand is leaving?
So, w- what difference
does that make? You don't have
to love him to be successful.
Catfish hunter
hated billy martin.
Bill parcells, his guys,
they can't stand him
till they start to win!
Coach hauser had sex
with ally!
What?
That's why she cut herself.
That's why i've been
practically living at her house.
All right,
hold on a minute.
Maybe--
with ally?
Meadow,
this is horrible. This is
also a very serious accusation.
- What exactly did ally say?
- That they had sex!
More than once! That she's
not a virgin anymore!
All right.
Ally's a very...
pretty girl.
Maybe there was--
maybe there was some confusion.
Maybe she wanted to...
look like she was sophisticated
in you guys' eyes.
Dad!
What?
Tony! What if
this had been meadow?
What kind of confusion?
A girl that age, the coach
should not have been
in any position...
where there's even
a remote possibility
of confusion!
I'm losin'
my fuckin' mind here.
Tony, go downstairs,
will you, please,
so me and meadow can talk?
Jesus fuckin' christ!
God, now what did i do?
Meadow.
Mom, i only told so he wouldn't
make coach hauser stay here.
Meadow, this is
a horrible, horrible thing.
Mom, she's in love with him,
but he won't leave his wife.
Leave his wife?
Meadow!
Now, meadow, he didn't
touch you, right?
No, but what about deena?
If she finds out
about her father,
it'll totally destroy her life.
Just tell dad to let him go
anywhere he wants, okay?
Come here. Oh.
Moldonado and his brother,
they'll handle it.
Mal owes me a solid.
No. No hired help.
This is personal.
Very glad to hear you say that.
I'll give him a real
after- school special.
You outta
your fuckin' mind?
What?
I know you
kidnapped the coach's dog
and all that other shit.
But if you
do one more thing--
aw, shut up, arthur.
You know, you're
five fuckin' time zones
behind your own ass.
No, i'm fuckin' serious.
You hear me, tony?
- You're serious?
- Yeah.
You wanna hear serious?
You wanna know what your
wonderful fuckin' coach did?
He fucked little
ally vandermeed and who
knows who else he fucked.
What are you talkin' about?
"Fucked"?
- That's crazy.
- That's why that kid slit
her wrists, youstunad'.
And my daughter should know
this shit, should have to
think about that filth?
No.
That self- righteous prick
put his dick in my little girl's
soccer teammate.
She's in eleventh grade,
for christ's sake.
Oh, my god.
Chiara. He drove her home from
the supermarket one night.
- Oh, my little girl.
- Fuckin' degenerate
son of a bitch.
He deserves to die.
Betrayin' children?
Artie, believe me,
he ain't gonna be
doin' that shit no more.
I guarantee you that.
He's in the pro shop!
I don't need a cart!
Nobody told you to put
my nephew under surveillance.
I know, junior.
I know.
I just wanted to be
on the safe side,
and i'm glad i did.
Because your nephew
is not just hangin' out
at that titty bar...
and goin' to his daughter's
soccer games.
Go ahead.
Twice last week...
he goes toward
the medical center,
then they lose him.
A girlfriend.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
He's seein' this
russian slit, very open.
Your nephew
is talking to the feds.
Where else would he be goin'
where it would require
such precautions?
And what the fuck else
would be the big secret?
What am i, a swami?
Hey.
Silvio! You're lookin'
good. I like that hat.
Mikey palmice.
How you feel?
You shanked it, sil.
I still got the coach
on my mind.
We got fresh air,
sunshine, a beautiful day.
Forget about that shit.
- Thank god for golf some days.
- I'm trying to concentrate
here.
- Did you get any golf in
down in boca, uncle jun'?
- Fuckin' manners! Please!
So you play, uh, manatee
or what's the name
of the other one?
Will you let the man tee off?
You yap worse than six barbers.
If you'd have shut up
during that game
against mountain lakes,
you wouldn't have missed
that fuckin' fly ball.
I was ashamed
to face my friends.
Good mikey. Better.
What do you mean,"better"?
Well, you know,
it's...better.
- Whoa, junior!
- "Whoa, junior" what?
Uncle junior's into muff.
What?
Oh, did i say "muff"?
I meant "rough."
Good shot.
What's that smell?
Did you guys go to a sushi bar?
What the fuck's
he talkin' about?
I don't know.
I thought you were
a baccala man, uncle jun'. What
are you doin' eatin' sushi?
You're fuckin' runnin' off
at the mouth, you know that?
South of the border?
Down mexico way
listen, my friend.
At least i can deal...
with my own problems,
unlike some i know.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Take it however you want.
Don't bullshit with me.
Guys, guys.
We here to play golf or what?
Come on.
South of the border?
Where the tuna fish play
arthur.
Everybody's just so upset.
The mother's on sedatives.
She's completely
unable to deal.
The father was
in europe somewhere.
They haven't reached him.
The little girl, ally, she
thinks it's all her fault.
Lousy bastard. He's not
gonna get away with this.
You got that right.
What?
Hand me that bottle
of bug be gone,
will ya?
Arthur, what?
Somethin' goin' on,
artie?
Your mobster friend
gonna do somethin' crazy?
If i had any balls,
i would do it myself.
Arthur, you do have balls.
That's why you're not like him.
Fuck it. Fuck the world!
Artie, this isn't makin'
some slob take his hat off.
This is beating a man to death
or cutting his balls off
or what?
You can't tell me coach hauser
doesn't deserve it!
Okay, but-- listen to you.
Think about what you're saying.
Yeah, you tell me.
Who's worse? Tony soprano
or that child- molesting fuck?
I trusted him.
I'd like to rip his heart
out of his chest!
Jesus christ, arthur.
I cannot believe you only
think about yourself!
Myself? Myself?
I resent that, charmaine!
Junior, what the fuck?
What's the matter?
What? That bullshit
with the sushi?
Nah, i-- i don't know
what he was talkin' about.
He, uh, he babbles.
What was that?
You're another one!
Me? Hey, he completely
lacked respect.
Sick and tired of having to
make excuses for him
all the time.
- It isn't right.
- It's'cause he's
a fucking mental weakling.
- I know.
- You don't know shit, mikey!
He's seein' a psychiatrist,
for christ's sake.
How about that, huh?
My nephew
is seein' a psychiatrist.
Makes me wanna cry.
- No shit?
- Indictment's being prepared.
He's spilling his guts.
- I fuckin' knew it.
- No, you didn't
fuckin' know it!
I just told you.
God knows how much of
our family business he airs.
If the place is bugged--
that stuff's not admissible.
It's that, uh, that, that
doctor/patient privilege,
just like us and melvoin.
Melvoin's a lawyer.
He's in the fuckin' ballpark.
Suppose this shrink
gets scared or somethin'?
Do you remember those fuckin'
escovedo brothers, whoever
the fuck, in california?
They whacked their parents?
Their shrink was in
a fuckin' witness chair.
Shit.
Anthony wants to play games,
okay.
I taught him games.
I taught him
how to play baseball.
You talking
about clippin' him?
Nobody would slap my wrist
if i did.
There's guys in prison
that have done half the damage
this prick has.
The judicial system has gotten
much better in dealing with
sexual predators.
Oh, yeah.
Let's impeach him.
If you're telling me of intent
to harm this person,
i must warn you of my duty
to alert law enforcement.
I don't know why
i tell you anything.
I'm interested...
in why you feel punishing
this man falls upon you.
- Well, it sure doesn't
fall upon you.
- What do you mean?
What would you do?
You'd call the cops,
who'd get some judge
who'd give him
psychiatric counseling.
So maybe he could talk about
his unhappy childhood...
and we could have sympathy
for the fuck'cause he's
the real victim here, right?
You know what you do? Stick
your head in the sand'cause
that's what people like you do.
Discredit psychology
all you want,
but i continue
to ask the question:
Why do you think
you, anthony soprano,
always has to set things right?
Hey, paulie. Is tony in?
Tony!
- Artie!
- Hey, ton', i gotta talk to ya.
- Kinda busy right now.
- I gotta talk to you.
All right, we'll, uh,
finish later, all right?
Come on in.
Hey.
It's about, uh, the thing.
You know what?
Nothing's happened yet,
has it?
Just gotta make the call.
I'm savorin' the moment.
- You gotta call it off.
- Don't worry about it.
You got nothin' to do
with it. You don't
go nowheres near this.
I don't care about that!
It's wrong, tony.
You can't do it.
It's wrong?
Oh, what he did isn't?
I'm beggin' you.
I hate the guy too.
What do you wanna do,
artie?
You wanna call the cops?
Here. Here's the phone.
They'll arrest him, right?
He'll get out in two fuckin'
years, move to saskatchewan.
Then you know what he'll do?
He'll teach girls' soccer,
and he'll start all over again.
You don't think
i wanna rip him apart
like a fuckin' chicken?
I drove by his house.
I almost got out.
But you didn't.
Something happens to him,
who's it gonna help, huh?
His daughter?
That girl? No, you, tony.
And silvio and me and whoever.
It's just gonna
make us feel better.
So don't even think about
calling this justice.
Leave it to the cops.
Let me ask you a question.
Who the fuck do you think
you are comin' in here,
talkin' to me like this?
Now your boyfriend
is finished.
You deal with it.
Okay?
Tony, don't do it.
This is me asking you.
Why don't you
get the fuck outta here?
Come on.
Get the fuck out!
Go!
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Oh, yeah
oh, yeah
dewayne, dewayne
woke up
yeah
dewayne
corrado.
I was worried! You usually
call me when you're this late.
I bought us some
barbecued chicken, some salad
and some lemon meringue pie.
But i got so hungry,
i had a piece.
Did i tell you
to keep your mouth shut?
What?
Did i tell you to keep
your goddamned mouth shut?
No, corrado, don't hit me!
You stupid, fucking,
blabbermouth cunt!
I don't understand.
Get your pencils
and your crap and
the rest of your shit...
and don't be here tomorrow!
Oh, no, corrado, don't leave!
I love you!
I am so sorry!
No, corrado!
Yeah.
You there at the place?
Is he in the house?
Yeah.
Fuck it. Walk away.
Just fuckin' walk away.
Don't do it.
Fuck!
All right.
Leave it alone.
Yeah, no problem.
Son of a bitch.
Lynn, we are here live
as colleagues and neighbors...
were shocked to hear of charges
brought against donald hauser,
coach of the
verbum dei high school
girls' soccer team.
Alerted by a student friend
of the alleged victim,
whose name cannot be revealed
because of her age,
police issued a warrant for
hauser's arrest this evening.
Tony.
In my hometown
tony, jesus.
Where i live
you smell like
lord calvert.
Tony.
We don't talk
we all get together
any kind of weather
and we do the camel walk
what is with you tonight?
Tony, what is this?
Oh, jesus.
Mixed with alcohol.
Oh, tony, that's wonderful.
- Happy trails.
Here, let's get you to bed.
- Carmela.
Carmela.
I didn't hurt nobody.
Call the shrink.
Tell her the town's gonna go
to the fuckin' mormons.
I hear a voice
from the back of the room
i hear a voice
cry out
you want something good
yeah, come on a little closer
by the front of the stage
i said come on a little close
wanna see your face
you see, i met a devil
namedbuena buena
and i feel all right now
i have to tell ya
i thinks it's time for me
to finally introduce you
to thebuena, buena, buena
good, good, good