O.K. Good,
children good...
Remember to feel the clay
Be one with the clay
nice...
Put more clay on the balls.
Boys!
What is that?
A reindeer?
You know, I've had it!
You four boys never
take art class seriously!
What a crime.
You think art is not important?
Weelll, art is just kinda...
for gaywads.
I love our class!
See?
Do you think this is funny?!
Do you think this is funny, huh?!
Well, you four can just spend
your afternoon after school here
making new pottery!
You can't do that!
I certainly can!
I'm your teacher!
You're an art teacher!
Make it two hours!
Mrs. Dreible thinks she's so cool!
How dare she talk
to us like that?!
(Yeah, how the fuck is that?!)
We can't let her get away with this!
I think tonight we need to do something drastic.
Like what?
Like find out where
Mrs. Dreible lives,
and go over there, and...
TP her house.
(Yeah!)
TP her house?
Toilet paper!
Cover her house in toilet paper.
What's the matter, Kyle?
You chicken? Ugh!
Quiet, boys. This isn't playtime,
you're being punished!
Fine! But we'll have the
last laugh tonight, artwhore!
Yeah! Payback time,
you ugly skank!
D'you think that's enough?
Should be fine.
Don't you guys think
this is a little suspicious?
We should buy something
else so it doesn't look obvious.
Okay. Here we go,
pack of chewing gum.
Hello boys.
Find everything you need?
Yep. All set.
Mokay, let's see here.
Toilet paper Toilet paper...
So, what are you
kids up to tonight?
Oh, we're just gonna watch
some TV, maybe play a board game.
Nice relaxing night at home, huh?
Toilet paper Toilet paper
Eh, hey. Now you kids be
careful with this chewing gum.
Don't go sticking it
under tables.
Okay. Toilet paper
Toilet paper Tooilet paper..
You know, son...
I dont remember you comin' in last
week and buying this much toilet paper.
Heh yeah,
that that's right.
You TP'ed a house
last week, Cartman?
No. Last Thursday
night was fajitas night.
Is this the right house?
It's the right address-wait!
Look there!
There's Mrs. Dreible!
This is the place.
Oh wait, wait,
there's kids inside.
So?
So we're not TP'ing
a house with kids inside it!
Kyle, we all
agreed to do this!
We didn't say nothin'
about no kids, man!
Kyle, you're bein' an asshole!
Now let's do this thing and get out of m'yeah.
Here's what I think of your
art class, you God-damned bitch!
(Yeah! Fuck you!)
Come on, let's go!
What have we done?
Let's go, Kyle!
We're, we're in trouble.
We're in sooo much trouble.
Aw man,
that was sooo awesome!
How can you say that?
Did you see what we did to their house?!
It'll take them days
to clean that up!
Who cares??
Well, YOU don't, because you're
a non-caring asshole, Cartman!
Me? There's toilet
paper on your hands, too, Kyle.
Cartman's right, Kyle.
We're all in this together.
Noo! No. Noo!
Honey, what is it?? Oh,
Jesus no! Our house!
Mommy! Mommy!
Whyyy? Whyyy?
Ah! Oh God!
Oh God!
Hey, uh, you guys here
what happened last night?
Mrs. Dreible's house got
covered with toilet paper.
Yeah. They say it's gonna
take three weeks to get it all down.
Yeah? Well, Ol' Mrs.
Dreible probably had it comin' to her.
I don't know. I don't think
anybody deserves that kind of brutality.
Well, I understand the
people who did it weren't caughts,
so-o...
Looks like nobody will ever know
the geniuses who
masterminded that perfect crime.
Okay children,
let's take our seats.
Oh, uh, Stan, Kyle, Eric, and Kenny,
the counselor wants to see you in his office, now.
Damn!
Oh God!
How the hell did they find out
it was us that TP'ed that house?
Will you relax, Kyle?!
They have nothing on us!
As long as we all stick
to our story, we'll be fine.
We'd better go over our story
again so we don't screw it up.
Okay. Last night, all four of us were at
the bowling alley until about 7:30,
at which time we noticed Ally Sheedy,
the Goth chick from the Breakfast Club,
was bowling in the lane next to us,
and we asked her for her autograph,
but she didn't have a pen,
so we followed her out to her car,
but on the way we were
accosted by five Scientologists
who wanted to give us all personality
tests, which were administered
at the Scientology Center
in Denver until 10:45,
at which time we accidentally
boarded the wrong bus home
and ended up in Rancho de Burritos
Rojos,south of Castle Rock,
and finally got a ride home
with a man who was missing
his left index finger, named Gary
Bushwell,arriving home at 11:46.
I'm confused. Did Ally Sheedy
take that personality test?
Yes, dude!
Kyle, it's very simple:
we followed Ally Sheedy
out to her car,
but on the way we were
accosted by five Scientologists
who wanted to give us all
personality tests, which were administered
at the Scientology Center
in Denver until 10:45,
at which time we accidentally
boarded the wrong bus home
and ended up in Rancho de
Burritos Rojos,south of Castle Rock,
and finally got a ride
home with a man who was missing
his left index finger,
named Gary Bushwell,
arriving home at 11:46,
you got it??
-Ah, Ah I, ah I thought...
-Oh, for Christ's sake!
Look, Kyle, just let Cartman
do all the talking, okay?
He's better at being
in trouble than anybody.
Thank you, Stan.
Sh sh, here they come,
here they come.
And so I said, 'That's a terrific
joke, Wendy. Tell us another one.'
Oh, hello, Mr. Mackey.
Are you ready to see us now?"
We're gonna talk to you
one at a time, boys, m'kay?
Kenny, will you
step into my office, please?
(Me??)
Come on, Kenny,
let's go, 'k?
Touché, Mr. Mackey,
touché.
Why are they doing us
one at a time?
They want to see
if we mix the story up,
and see if someone will rat out
the other three for a better deal.
I can get a better deal?
Kyle, so help me God,
if you Jew us out on this one,
I will fucking kill you!
There we go.
That should be about the last of it.
Ex- excuse me, uh,
wha-what are you doing?
Crime scene investigation!
There are several
footprints in the snow.
Perhaps more than
one perpetrator?
Ah... look, we really don't wanna
make a big deal out of this.
Is that the toilet paper there?
I'll need to take those bags as evidence.
Lo-ih ih it's just not
that big a deal, I mean,
I toilet-papered houses
myself when I was a kid.
You?! So where were you
last night at around 9?!
I was here.
Aha!!
Got you!
Officer, why would
I TP my own house?
Insurance?
It wasn't me, okay?
Now, if you don't mind, I just wanna
get my yard back to normal.
Now you listen to me!
Whoever TP'ed your house is
still out there roaming the streets.
It's only a matter of time before another
house and another family is victimized!
I have to stop that
from happening.
You really have nothing
better to do, do you?
No I do not.
Noo! No.
Noo!
Oh, Jesus no!
Our house!
Mommy! Mommy!
Whyyy? Whyyy?
Whyyy?
Oh God! Oh God!
I have to tell the truth!
Mooooomm!
Hello, Kyle.
Going somewhere?
I was... I was just
going to get a drink of water.
No need.
I have one for you right here.
Oh. Okay. Thanks.
Is there anything
else I can get for you?
Noo, I'll just...
be... going back to bed now.
You do that.
Goodnight, Kyle.
Josh Meyers TP'ed over six hundred
houses in less than a year.
He's a real monster.
I just need to talk to someone
who knows how toilet paperers think.
Just remember: he'd toilet-paper
you in a second if he had the chance.
He's the last cell on your left.
Hello, Josh. My name is Officer Barbrady.
I'm with the South Park police.
That's a terrible cologne you're wearing, officer.
You should try something more... casual.
I was hoping you could help me
solve a toilet-papering case?
And why would I do that?
Because I'm such a charming fella?
Uh please, I need your help.
What would you want in return?
Due to the harsh nature of my crimes they
don't allow me to have toilet paper in my cell.
You can imagine how
bothersome that becomes.
You... know I can't
give you toilet paper, Josh.
No, but it was worth a try,
wasn't it?
Tell me something, officer: why is it that you
police such a small town.
You must have had
larger inspirations.
What happened to those...
big-city dreams?
Well,
that's kind of personal.
Quid pro quo, officer.
Tell me what I want to know.
And I'll help you catch whoever
toilet-papered that house.
Look kid, I have very little time to
catch whoever toilet-papered that house.
Tell me what you know.
Are those the crime scene photos?
Let me see them.
Yes. Yes.
Not bad work, not bad at all.
These toilet-paperers are professional,
at least one of them is.
So you think there
was more than one. Why?
Tell me something first.
When you went to the academy
you had something to prove.
You wanted to protect and serve,
but mostly you wanted to protect yourself.
Who were you protecting
yourself from, Officer Barbrady?
Oh all right, all right, my uncle
Charles used to hit me with a belt!
Thank you. Your toilet-paperers
are most like males
between the ages of 8 and
10 and probably virgins.
Parents notice that
much toilet paper missing,
so they would have
to have bought it themselves.
Find out where the toilet
paper came from, officer,
and you just might catch your man.
Stan, Kenny, can I talk to
you guys for a second?
I think we have the counselor
and the principal fooled,
but we need to talk about Kyle.
What about him?
Come on, you know.
He's losing it. He's gonna crack.
(I think so too.)
Kyle can't take the heat;
he's gonna sing like a canary.
Then we're all gonna take
the fall for what we did.
Ha-ey fellas.
Butters.
Look you guys, all it takes
is for one of us to crack,
and we all know who
the weakest link is!
So what should we do?
We have no choice.
We have to kill Kyle.
-Dude, we're not killing Kyle!
-(Yeah!)
Why not?
Kyle's not gonna
say anything, alright?
He almost spilled the beans
in the counselor's office!
He can't even keep
the story straight!
I'm telling you guys,
he's weak.
He's weak, and he'll be
the end of all of us.
You wanted to see me,
Officer Barbrady?
Yes, thanks for coming,
Mr. Bell.
A house was TP'ed in South
Park and I need to see
if you can identify the toilet paper
I recovered from the scene.
I'm...
sorry I have to do this.
Oh my God.
Is this toilet
paper from your store?
It's... difficult to tell,
it's... so decayed, I...
wait a minute, yes. Yes,
I recognize the floral pattern now.
Positive ID on
the toilet paper.
Who would...
do this to toilet paper? Who?
Mr. Bell, do you remember
anyone suspicious
buying toilet paper in
the last few days?
Suspicious like how?
Well, like someone who was black
or Mexican or Middle Eastern.
Nnoo, the only Mexican guy I recall
bought toasted tarts and chips
and... we don't allow Middle
Eastern people in the store.
Oh my God!
What's this all about,
Cartman?
I just wanted to see how
you're doing, Kyle.
Why don't we go out
for a little boat ride?
A boat ride?
I just thought we should find
a private place to... talk.
Well, okay.
Could you help me put this cement
block and chain in the boat?
Okay, let's go.
So how are things,
Kyle?
Terrible. Every time I close my
eyes I see the house we TP'ed.
I see the tears of our art teacher and
hear the screams of her daughters.
And you feel like
you have to confess.
I don't know what to do.
Part of me feels like
I wanna end it all now.
Tell people what heppened.
You know, I never knew how
beautiful this pond was before.
So cold.
The world can feel like that.
So calm on the outside, as if
nothing bad ever happens.
What the hell are you
doing, Cartman?!
I'm killing you.
But unfortunately
I could only afford a Wiffle ball
bat, so it's gonna take a while.
Cartman!
Don't fight it, Kyle,
it will only take longer.
Just slip into sweet
unconsciousness.
You wanna kill me?! Fine!
I can't live like this anymore! Go ahead! Do it!
Won't be long, Kyle.
Josh, I need your help.
The answer is right in front
of you, but you can't see it.
How do you mean?
Tell me, the toilet paper.
Was it quilted?
Yes.
Single-sheet?
No, two-ply. What?
What does that tell you?
Why does one
toilet-paper houses
To get revenge.
No, that is incidental.
Your toilet-paperers wanted to
transform the art teacher's house,
thus transforming her
entire occupation.
What do you mean?
Your uncle, who hit you with
a belt. Was he a large man?
I don't have time for this, kid.
Did he stink like bayer when
he came home from work
all powoor from playin' down
at the pool hiyouse?
Alright alright my dad dressed me
up like a little girl on poker nights
and he made me sit on
all my uncles' laps!
Uh, oh. Thank you.
Your toilet-paperers are most likely
students in the art teacher's class,
students who aren't
very good at art.
Oh. Of course!
One of her students!
Fly along now, Officer Barbrady.
You've got some arrests to make.
Fly fly flyyy.
Josh, were you doing the silly
voice for the policeman again?
No, sir.
Cartman, what are you doing?
I'm getting rid of our problem.
Kyle will be dead in a matter of hours.
You don't have to kill Kyle, dude.
The police made an arrest.
And the person confessed!
-They did?
They say they got the guy that
did it down at the police station.
Who confessed?
That doesn't make any sense.
But can I still kill Kyyyle?
Hello boys.
How are you?
We heard that you have the person
who TP'ed the art teacher's house?
Is that true?
It sure is!
Uh, can we see them-him-her?
Right over here.
Yeah, we interrogated the
suspect for over forty hours,
and he finally cracked.
Hey fellas!
Butters?
Yep. I'm in jail.
You con-fessed?
Uh huh. Unh, they said
I TP'ed the art teacher's house.
I don't seem to remember it,
but they're pretty sure it was me.
I just can't get
my behavior under control!
His parents are on
their way down now.
Yeah. And boy, are they gonna uh
let me have it!
Just wait till
my father gets here!
You guys,
we can't let him do this!
What are you talking about?
This is a gift from God.
An early Easter present all wrapped up
in a pretty ribbon from Jesus Christ himself!
Well I'm just a little asshole,
is what I am.
When God made me, he must have
not been payin' very close attention,
'cause I turned out wrong!
Just plain wrong!
Officer Barbrady,
Butters didn't TP that house.
Why do you say that?
-Because it was-
-Wiffle ball, anyone?
Anyone care for
a nice game of Wiffle ball?
You know, it's not my parents I'm
worried about. It's my girlfriend, Karen.
Why, she lives in Michigan.
But when she finds out about this,
woooo smokey, is she gonna be sore!
She might even break up with me.
And it would serve me right, too.
All right, boys, visiting time is over.
Thanks for stopping by.
You see guys,
it all worked itself out.
Tadow, tadow, how you like me now?
Feel a little silly now, Kyle?
Tadow, how you like me now?
I still feel bad, Cartman
What? Hu- How can you feel bad?
Somebody else is gonna pay for our crime.
Yeah. That makes it even worse.
Kyle, you don't seem to understand.
We're we're not gonna
get punished for this. Ever.
I know.
So... so then,
how can you feel bad?
He feels guilty for doing it and for
letting someone else pay for it.
...But he's not gonna get in trouble.
It doesn't matter if you get
in trouble of not, you can still feel bad.
I think you're right, Kyle.
Maybe we should confess.
(Yeah, maybe we should.)
What?? Eh... hey you guys!
There's nothing to feel bad about!
We're, we're off scot-free!
We feel bad for other people.
For oth-er...
ih, is it that ...you think
you might get in trouble later?
Tomorrow in school we'll all tell
the teacher it was us,
and let her decide
what to do. And Cartman,
if you had any thread of a
conscience at all, you'll do the same!
Eh buh... eh... eh...
Freakin' weirdos, man!
Well well well!
I had to see it to believe it!
Hi, Dad.
Don't you "Hi, Dad" me!
Look at you! Standing
behind prison bars! Again!
Yeahhh.
What fibs have you been
telling this policeman, Butters?!
You know damn well you
didn't toilet-paper that house!
Butters was with us all night,
Officer Barbrady.
Butters, what have we told you
about confessing to crimes you didn't commit?!
We have had it, mister!
Well, he kept
accusin' me for hours,
and then he shot me up
with sodium pentathol.
And that's your excuse?!
Well, looks like I made a mistake.
I... guess I'd better let you out now.
Just wait till we get you home,
you little fibber!
Officer,
can I stay in jail, please?
Come on, you guys!
Hurry! Guys, hurry!
What is it, Cartmam?
It's over this way!
Come on!
So how are things, guys?
Cartman, we're confessing
tomorrow in school, and that's final.
I'm afraid
I can't let that happen.
You can't kill
all three of us, Cartman!
Can't I?
Excuse me, everyone.
I have someone with me
who can tell us all who
toilet-papered the art teacher's house!
Josh insisted he be able to tell you
the names of the toilet paperers in person.
Uh, that's nice, Officer Barbrady,
but we actually don't need to know-
Hold it! Principal Victoria,
Mr. Mackey, Mrs. Dreible.
We have something
we need to tell you.
All right. Will you people
stop barging into my office, please?
What's the matter, Principal Victoria?
Was your mother abusive?
Did she spank your thighs with cold
cuts and stick umbrellas up your ass?
Get him out of here!
Uh, Policeman Brown,
will you take Josh outside, please?
Polceman Brown,
never quite made officer.
Why is that, Polceman Brown?
We have to confess that
we were the ones that-
It's too late, boys, m'kay?
We already know everything.
You, you do? How?
Hi guys.
Cartman??
I told them everything,
you guys. It's over.
Luckily for us, one of you had
enough of a conscience to come forward.
My consciences
just caught up with me.
That's not fair!
You all get two
weeks of detention,
except Eric, who gets
one week for being brave.
But, but he's lying!
He doesn't have a conscience!
Well, I guess my
work here is done.
After all this,
I'm gonna need a long vacation.
This was supposed to be my story!
My coming to terms with a
guilty conscience! This isn't fair!
Okay, Josh,
time to go back to the... Oh no!
He... He was too fast for me.
He ran out the door!
Couldn't you
have gone after him?
Well, ah I'm covered in toilet
paper. I'd look silly.
Welcome to detention.
You will be here till five o'clock,
so make good study use of your time. M'kay?
Wugh! Two weeks of this!
Yeah. But I have to say,
I feel a lot better now.
I know what you mean, Kyle.
I realize now that even though you
might not get caught doing something bad,
you can still get caught later.
Oh Jesus!
I didn't feel bad before,
but now I just feel terrible.
You just feel bad for
yourself that you're in detention!
Right. I guess I learned
today that sometimes you-
Oh, stop it, Cartman! You didn't
learn anything! Not a God-damned thing!
Police station.
Hello Officer Barbrady.
Josh? Josh, where are you?!
I'm afraid that giving away my location
might be harmful to my freedom, officer.
I just wanted to thank you
for helping me get out of that dingy cell.
Josh, you have to go back to Juvenile
Hall. You only have a three-week sentence.
Sorry, officer, gotta run.
There's something I've been
meaning to do for quite some time.
Ciao.
www.tvsubtitles.net