Torchwood
outside the government, beyond the police
fighting for the future on behalf of the human race.
The 21st century is when everything changes...
and Torchwood is ready.
* So who can you trust to transport your goods? *
* Harwood's! *
* You won't be sorry with a Harwood's lorry! *
Good morning. Today sees an improvement on the weather we've been having recently.
Yeah, Ruth. Did you hear it?
I wrote the last bit.
What sort of accident?
Yeah, I know it.
Yeah, I'll get over there now.
Stay back, please.
You'll have to move your car.
I'm Rhys Williams, manager of Harwood's Haulage.
You can check on the vehicle later.
Bollocks! I know the driver.
Is he...?
Didn't make it. Sorry.
Can you give me some details, sir?
It's Leighton.
Er. . . Leighton Reynolds.
- Next of kin?
- Yeah, he's got a wife.
Jen.
Just had a baby, man.
- Do you know the address?
- Yeah.
54 Keppoch Street, Roath.
I give him a lift to football.
Thank you, sir.
Er, right. I'm gonna need to
arrange to move the lorry.
Not yet. There's something suspicious in the back.
It's just meat.
Leighton was taking it to the abattoir.
Yeah, well, Torchwood want to look at it first.
www.1000fr.com Presents
Meat
Torchwood S02E04
Capture:evarin
Sync:”Í‰Ï@FRS
Argh, it stinks!
No bones. just dense flesh.
It's not like any flesh I've ever seen.
What is it?
Well, as there haven't been any giant cow sightings,
I suggest we take a sample back to the Hub.
We need to confiscate the contents of the van
till we've done further investigations.
Do you know where it came from?
No, but it's a Harwood's lorry so they should...
Oh, that's Rhys's firm.
- Right, done.
- Let's go.
Sorry, sir, you can't come this way now.
There's evidence of a vertebral column
but its genetic make-up isn't compatible with any known animal.
- Any idea what it is?
- I have to scan it.
But whoever's farming this meat knows it's dodgy. See this?
Official vet stamp fit for human consumption'. It's fake.
It's good, but it's fake.
Tosh, get onto the haulage firm.
Find out where the meat is from
and where it's heading.
Why did it have to be Rhys's firm?
It's too close to home.
Want to stand down?
No, to find out what's going on.
Thank you, Ianto.
* Harwood's! *
* You won't be sorry with a Harwood's lorry! *
Catchy.
Do you think the haulage firm are in on it?
Rhys? No.
He just hires the vans out.
- Driver must have seen it loaded.
- That doesn't implicate Rhys.
He's the most honest man I know.
Have you got his direct line?
Harwood's Haulage. How may I help you?
It's the police.
Hello?
Yeah, speaking.
Yes, I'm aware ofthe accident.
'It's a firm is called Harries and Harries.
They came to us two months back. It's a weekly contract.'
- 'Are they licensed?'
- 0f course they're licensed!
Could you give me their address?
There's no address here.
There's a pick-up point.
They said it was hard to find.
'Hello, sorry. All I've got is a service station on the Al?70,'
15 miles from Cardiff.
Do you have a contact number?
No, there's no contact number, either.
Can you tell me where your driver took the meat?
Yes,he was taking it to Caerwen Abattoir.
'It's a processing plant.'just general meat suppliers.
What time did the driver leave base?
'Signed out at ten to one.
Can I ask what this is about?'
I can't release that information, sir.
'Thanks for your cooperation'
Yeah, but I'm the manager...
Brilliant!
Leighton was their regular.
Apart from that first booking, they just went through him.
Yes, but now it looks like I'm hiding something.
Got him!
There he is, coming back 40 minutes later.
Let's say it takes 20 minutes to load...
We are talking a ten-mile radius.
- Jack!
- Yeah?
The scan shows it's definitely alien meat.
Where would they get it from?
If it's going into the processing plant
that means it'll be going into pies, burgers, pasties - everything.
That means people have been eating it for months.
Well, the DNA traces are stable.
There are signs of animal sedative but no diseases or residues.
My guess is it's good to eat.
Would YOU eat it?
Pizza's arrived.
I presumed it would be a late one.
- What did you get me?
- Usual. Meat Feast.
Lovely
I've narrowed it down to three potential areas.
Only one warehouse is unoccupied, just outside Merthyr.
Makes sense.Who knows what goes on there?
We have to shut the operation down,
neutralise whoever's doing this and identify the alien meat.
Tosh, you co-ordinate.
I have to slip home and check on Rhys.
Good idea. Find out how much he knows.
That's not what I meant.
Hiya
I got your message.Are you all right?
Er. ..bit of a tough day.
Had an accident at work.
One of our lorries crashed.
- Anyone hurt?
- Leighton.
One of my drivers died.
Oh, no!
Only 24.
Were you close?
For God's sake, Gwen, you met him!
Small, dark hair,played five-a-side with me.
Sorry. I can't place him.
Well, then I hear that the, er...
that the police have taken the meat out the back of the van.
You any idea why?
How would I know?
You work for them.
I don't deal in traffic accidents, so. ..
Well, they phoned the office and...
they asked loads of questions.
Thing is, all I do is hire out the lorries, so I. ..
Then there's nothing for you to worry about, is there?
Must be something dodgy going on,though.
If there was, you weren't to know, were you?
- No, of course not.
- No.
I wish I didn't have to go back to work now.
Hardly worth you coming home.
Yes, it was.
To see you.
I'm sorry.
I'll see you later.
Go and have a pint. Call Daf.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe I will.
Like I thought.
He has no idea what's going on.
Would you care to accompany me to the slaughterhouse?
Have you ever eaten alien meat?
Yeah.
What was it like?
He seemed to enjoy it.
'Ianto,Owen, we're on our way.
'How are things looking at the slaughterhouse?
Are you in position?'
'It's all quiet.There's a deserted access road.
We won't get noticed.
I'll direct you in.'
Ianto, nearly there.
Take the second turning.
Park on the left. No-one will see the car there.
There's a main entrance at the front.
It's the only one open.
The rest are padlocked and alarmed.
How many are in there?
It's difficult to tell, there are no windows.
I have blueprints of the warehouse.
The stock has to be in the central area.
Having fun?
You don't know what you're missing.
According to the sensor, there's a heat signature across the entire building.
That's a lot of meat.
Answer the phone, Gwen!
'You two take the sides,
Gwen and I will go in the front.'
We don't want any casualties.
We stun-gun whoever's in there
and put a stop to what they're doing.
Let's go.
There's someone there.
It's Rhys.
It's Rh... What's he doing?
Did you bring the alarm de-activator?
Well, that's one way of doing it.
He must be in on it.
Don't bother running, mate.
Never. No.
Greg? We've got a bit of a problem, bruv.
How else do you explain that?
Ianto, Owen...
'Stand down. Repeat, stand down.'
He told me he didn't know what was going on.
He wouldn't lie to me.
He also said he didn't know where they were based.
But he did.
There's something wrong.
There has to be.
Gwen! No. No!
No!
Come with me.
- I just have to get him out.
- By charging in there?
What then?
You gonna knock them out?
Look, lads...
I don't mean any harm, honestly.
You can't just go in there.
You have to do as I say.
We wait until he comes out.
Boys, you should've waited for the ketamine injection
before doing that.
What about the hoses?
That's lidocaine. It's not strong enough.
If you care so much, go and work for the RSPCA.
Or don't they pay as good? Oi, you.Through here.
Shift!
I want you and one of those with me, now!
- Who sent you?
- Come on. Don't waste our time.
No-one sent me.
I came on my own.
- I'm looking for the boss.
- You're looking at him.
Ignore my little brother.
I'm, er...
I'm from Harwood's.
Harwood's Haulage.
Leighton... Er, Leighton, your driver. ..um. ..
He sort of told me what was going on, like.
Mouthy git!
He was paid to keep quiet. Ssh!
Yeah, well, he's dead.
- Lorry crashed.
- With the goods inside?
What happened to the meat?Did anyone see the meat?
No, no, no.
I. . .er. ..I picked it all up and
took it all to be incinerated.
You see, um...
I was hoping maybe I could
pick up from where he left off, boys.
How do we know you won't report us?
I'm here, aren't I?
So what exactly did he tell you?
Everything.
You know, that you were...
cleaning up old meat.
0h, it's a lot bigger than that.
What's that noise?
What is it, boys?
No idea.
But the beauty of it is,
it just keeps growing.
No matter how much we cut it.
He'll get used to it.
I don't get it.
Come on.
Let's go.
- What were you doing at that warehouse?
- You lied to me!
You were at the crash.
What are you talking about?
Stop pissing me around,Gwen!
You're so used to lying and fobbing me off
like the idiot I obviously am!
Those blokes paying you?Why you were there?
No. I'm asking the questions, all right!
I followed you, OK?
Yeah.
So that bloke, the tall bloke in the coat.
You fucking him or what?
All I ever asked was you trust me.
What?Like you trust me?
It's a two-way street, Gwen!
There's stuff you don't understand,Rhyes.
Oh, I'm just a big, dumb animal,aren't I?
I mean, what's so secret you can't even tell your own fiance? ???
Why ARE you marrying me, Gweny?
What am I, a habit you can't be arsed to break?No.
- Then tell the truth!
- No. All right!
All right. My job...
the special ops thing...
it's a lie - a cover story.
Thank you! At last!
God, what's that taken?About a year?
That's one lie down.How many more?
Is there anything in your life based on truth?
- Us.
- Us?!
Us?
Us is crumbling, Gwen!
Us is falling to shit!
You think I enjoy keeping this stuff to myself?
Then why did you?
Because I'm trying to protect you!
Have you ever stopped to think about that?No!
No. Because you prefer to blunder in without thinking or looking.
Good old ham-fisted Rhys. His heart is in the right place but
but his brain is a million miles fucking back.
Come on, let's have it all.
What exactly do I need protecting from?
I catch aliens.
- Piss off!
- You piss off...
If you won't take it seriously...
This is why I couldn't tell you.
I hunt aliens and I scavenge the stuff they leave behind.
- Sometimes I don't believe it.
- jesus Christ!
What's getting into you?
Have you been brainwashed?
Is that what's happened? Cos you are talking high-grade shit here.
Every word is the truth.
Rhys...
The things I have seen...
The times I have wanted to tell you. ..
Aliens.
In Cardiff.
Have you never seen something so mad, so. . extraordinary. ..
..that, just for one second, you think there might be more out there?
Prove it.
Well, this is unprecedented -
the fiance finding out.
Mainly because we're all sad and single.
Speak for yourself.
I am better off without all that kind of hassle.
Maybe the answer is to go out with someone who knows what you do.
Look around you, Tosh.
Only we know what we do.
I saw you here earlier.
With him -
that bloke.
He appeared out of nowhere.
It's an invisible lift.
Oh, it's too complicated to explain.
Come on. Trust me.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Who'd have thought this was here?
- That looked so real.
- It was real.
- They're extinct, Gwen.
- No, boy.
In your time line,yes.
Captain Jack Harkness.
Thanks for dropping in, Rhys.
This is the rest of the team.
Owen and Toshiko. Ianto.
Pleased to meet you.
Welcome to our headquarters.
It's a bit bigger than mine.
So, Gwen tells me you catch aliens.
That's right.
A rift through space and time runs through Cardiff
and stuff slips in from other time lines and planets.
It's our job to monitor it.
Are you sure they're not some kind of weird cult?
You saw that alien in the warehouse.
Come on.
What did you see?
It was this huge, shapeless beast, filling the space.
Like a mound of flesh.
So it's one entity as opposed to several organisms.
The tests reveal high levels of chloride, so it probably lives in the water.
I reckon it came through the rift,into the sea and beached itself.
Like a giant alien manatee.
But how did they get it there?
That warehouse must be 50 metres long.
Maybe it was smaller when they found it. They said it's growing.
It's not dead?
No. It's breathing. Its eye opened.
So the protein chains regenerate despite the mutilation.
Not only is it replenishing its own flesh
but it's increasing it, giving them a brand-new meat supply.
It will last for years.
If we knew how it worked, we could feed the world.
We could release a single.
Before we get ahead of ourselves,
we're talking about dodgy pies in Merthyr, OK?
And the fact that they're cutting it up alive,
which we could have put a stop to if it wasn't for you.
I thought my fiancee was in danger.
Well, Mr Caveman, she wasn't.
- She can handle herself.
- Jack...
All you did was mess things up.
Now we have to think of a way to get back in and,
thanks to you, they'll have tightened security.
Well, what if you stopped and asked me what I saw in there,
instead of showing off around the place...
- Do I show off?
- Just a bit.
..you'd know I got out by saying I wanted a job as a deliveryboy.
So rather than cock things up, I've found you a way to get in.
But if you can't handle that, big boy, then you can stuff it!
- This is quite homo-erotic.
- No, no, no. jack, he is not getting us in.
Team meeting. You,too.
Jack
That's where the thing is.
That's the sedatives room.
That's where they pack the meat.
- That's good to know.
- Yeah, that is good to know.
but he's not driving us in.
They're expecting me.
You lot can hide in the back of the van.
What is this? Scooby-Doo?!
Absolutely no way is he getting involved.
When it was you to decided to get involved,
did you give me a thought?
0h, joy A domestic.
Rhys is right. He is our best way in. Stun guns only.
We've handled bigger than this.Why don't we
storm in, guns in the air, and arrest them?
Those men aren't organised criminals.
If we go in, guns blazing, they'll kill the evidence and run.
I wasn't suggesting blazing,just waving.
The last thing we need is a bloodbath.
- Point taken.
- I know that. ..
Once Rhys has loaded up, he can clear.
You don't have to come. You can stand down.
It might be better. You love him.
Makes you vulnerable.
He's not going in there without me.
- That's your decision.
- Yes, it is.
You both have to live by it.
Come on. You and me - a team!
Damn it, Rhys!
This is for real. Do you understand?
This is for real!
And if you mess up, I will kill you!
So...after we've stun-gunned the workers,
we put the creature out of its misery.
No. We're gonna save it.
Stabilise it, wait for the rift to open and. . .
send it back.
Guess who'll have to look after it in the meantime.
Tell me how are we going to use it to arm ourselves against the future?
Hide behind it.
Why shouldn't we save it?
Because it's an alien?
It needs our protection.
You didn't hear its cry. Heart-breaking.
Listen to Ahab.
- Jack, it's growing.
- Well, we'll find a way to stop it mutating.
We are doing this. That's an order!
- Fine.
- I'll stock up on plankton.
So you do have a heart.
We see enough death.
What's that?
0h, it's just an idea of what it looks like.
I had it made up from the genetic make-up.
It looks lovely.
You're just a big softie, really, aren't you?
I'd better get on with that report.
I brought you some sandwiches.
- Thanks, Tosh.
- It's OK, just cheese and pickle.
I can keep you company.I'm not tired.
In that case, maybe you can do it.I'm knackered.
That's another big lump out of its habitat.
Makes you realise, maybe it is possible to do this job and have a relationship.
Do you fancy a game of pool sometime?
We're always in here, slaving away.
It might be nice to, I don't know, kick back and have some fun.
Yeah, why not?
- When?
- I'll check with the others.
We could have a Torchwood tournament.
Thanks for the sandwiches,Tosh.
I thought you were anti-terrorism.
That was bad enough, but knowing you're in this much danger...
Yeah, you'd feel like I do now.
Worried sick.
You don't have to do this to prove anything to me.
I'm not leaving you with all these sexy young men.
There's only one from where I'm sitting.
- Sure about this?
- Yeah.
Cos once they ring, there's no turning back.
Moring.
- You just missed the advert.
- Yeah?
just popped in for my jacket and to sign for a van.
Here's your tea. And I got you a Danish, your favourite.
I'm in the wrong job.
We have got job vacancies.
Maybe you could fit me in.
I'd be delighted to.
Would I need a licence for trucking?
Yes. Takes four weeks, and then you can go long distance.
That wouldn't be a problem.
It's them.
OK. Yeah, hello?
Why her? 0f all the women you could have chosen...
She chose us.
- Kinda stumbled upon us.
- So did I.
Doubt you'll be asking me to join.
We needed someone with police skills.
Could have chosen anyone.
Did you ever think about us?
You know, me, her parents, people who love her, who want her safe?
No, I'm sorry.We needed her.
0n her first day of work,
she told me off for being too clinical.
She doesn't hold back, mind.
- Stubborn as hell.
- Tell me about it.
Yeah, she's an amazing girl.
I'm a lucky man, Jack.
Yeah, you said it.
I just wish you were a bit uglier.
Not gay, by any chance, are you?
Brought you a Danish, your favourite.
I know what you're like on an empty stomach.
Cheers.
- Get out as soon as you can, remember?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Now, stop fussing, and get in the back of the van.
I'll prepare a ketamine antidote so we can start weaning it off.
Gwen, Tosh and I will take the main area.
Owen,Ianto, cover the corridors and the small rooms. You OK?
- What do you think?
- He'll be fine.
He's a good bloke.
Let's go.
Yeah.I just need your boss to sign this, mate.
I don't want any questions asked.
You couldn't get us a cup of tea, could you?
Yes.
Where do you want my autograph?
Er...just on there, mate.
Here's a oner for your trouble.
Count it,if you like.
No, it's fine, mate. I trust you.
When you get to the abattoir, ask for Graham.
Him and the boys clean it up and process it.
All right.
Oh, my God!
It's amazing!
How did it get here?
Imprisoned, chained and drugged.
Welcome to planet Earth.
It heard you.
It's sentient.
Oh, that's disgusting.
What have they done to you?
What have they done to you, my poor friend?
Everyone...they're armed.
Rhys.
Gwen.
Stay here.
Where have you been? That injection was due ten minutes ago.
I needed more ketamine. I've had to up the dose.
The thing's in agony.
It's meat. It can't feel anything.
You going soft, or what?
Get inside and play nurse, if you're so bothered.
We've got work to do.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hang on.
There's only 12 bags in here.
He's supposed to have three more.
Come on, hurry up!
Hello. I have a...thingy here somewhere...Hell of a day.
I should be getting off, mate.
I've got jobs backing up, you see?
Well, they'll have to wait.
Dale,we've got a problem.There are people in the building.
You want to answer me?!
- Ianto, did Rhys get away?
- I'll check now.
Hey, hey, hey!
You looking for someone? How many more of you?!
Just us.
You thought the two of you could take us out?
Nah, you're not that stupid.
Dave, get some ropes, tie their hands.
I want every door locked, inside and out.
Nobody leaves the building till this is sorted.
- Move it!
- They've got Rhys and Ianto.
Gwen!
Gwen. Listen. Hey! It will be OK.
- Locked.
- They must know we're here.
This way.
What is it?
The lads call it the Cash Cow.
Dale, what are you doing?
They couldn't bear to see us making money.
Fancied some for yourselves, eh?
Thought we'd be a pushover?
Mate, you're so out of your depth.
Funny, I was just thinking the same about you.
Dale, don't be an idiot!
Show yourselves or I shoot the delivery boy!
OK!
There's no need to make any threats.
Just the two of you, is it?
Gun down.Kick it over.
- I don't have a gun.
- He had one, so you must have!
OK!OK.
Any more of you?
And before you answer, have a proper think,
cos if you lie, I will shoot you.
It's just me.
Get against the drum.
We can help you, Dale.
Yeah, help yourselves, more like.
Stand next to her. You, too!
Dale! Two more. Far corner.
They can't get out. It's locked.
Kick out your weapons, stand where I can see you!
Drop your weapons.
Do you know what you've got here, Dale?
- Shut up now!
- It's an alien.
A creature from another galaxy.
It came through a rift in time and space,
and it was unlucky enough to find you.
No. No way.
Did you really think it originated on this planet?
Have you ever seen anything like it before?
It can't be. Can it?
Look at it.
- It's just meat, that's all.
- You're carving up a sentient creature,
- and you've got to stop!
- And then what have I got?
I'm making money here! This is my business.
For the first time in my life, I've actually got something for myself!
Dale, stop. You can still walk away from this.
No.
You lied to me.
No!
Die!
Shit!
Ianto! Go! After them!
Owen! Rhys has been shot!
The creature's coming loose.
We need that sedative now!
Open your eyes. Come on.You can do this.
Open your eyes now.OK?
Yeah, I'm on it, I'm on it.
Owen, we need you!
The creature's breaking free. If we try and get past, we'll be crushed.
Come on.
It wasn't me!
I never wanted to be a part of this!
Sedatives won't work now.
If it's got loose, you're never gonna stop it!
We've gotta help them.
It's out of control.
Change of plan.
You went and shot him, bruv.
Come on! Go, go! Fill the other one.
I'm going as fast as I can.
Pray they survive.
Bloody hell!
I'm sorry.
He's OK.
Owen, you're making it worse!
Open your eyes!
You can do it.Come on.
It's working.Yeah, it's working.
What did you do?
Mercy killing.
Rhys, Rhys, listen to me, listen to me.
That's it, you're with me, OK?
I've got you tight.
Keep your eyes nice and open.
Gwen, let me look at him.
OK.
Soft, soft, soft.
I'm going to rip this.
I want you to keep the pressure on, OK?
OK.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Here he is.
Hero of the hour.
- Hey.
Are you all right?
???
Sorry.
Next time, let her take the bullet.
Never.
What happened to the blokes?
We gave them amnesia pills.
They'll remember who they are but not what they did over the past few months.
So they got away with it?
It would never stand up in court of law.
And the creature?
Incinerated.
So there's nothing left.
It was never there.
Gwen, I need a word.
Sure.
Rhys has to forget too, you know?
At least let me give it to him at home.
Let's not go home just yet.
Rhys, you've just been shot.
I know.
Come on,
Let's go for an ice cream.
Look around us.
Nobody else knows what we've been through.
Or what else is out there.
The sky won't be the same to me any more.
I used to look up and think,
'Ah, looks like rain, man.'
But now,
oh, now I'll...
I'll look and I'll think of all the other worlds and the planets
and stuff spinning around out there.
And I got to be a part of it all!
Fantastic!
Which puts worrying about unsigned dockets into perspective, I can tell you.
You've got some ice cream on your chin.
Have I? Gone?
I want to know about all of it,
about every alien you've ever seen.
You could take photos.
I'll keep a scrap book.
Wouldn't show no-one, no way.
No,because you won't be keeping one.
And you know...
I'm even cool about Jack.
All right, he's handsome, enigmatic,saves the world and all that.
But it's me you come home to at the end of it all.
And I always will.
Hey. Daf! All right?
0h, nothing much.
Same old, same old.
Yeah!
What?
No way!
I'm not doing it.
- I won't drug him.
- You have to.
You can't allow him to remember.
It's the rules. But none of you have any partners outside of this.
But we understand how you feel.
No, you don't.
No, you don't, Jack!
You all think it's cold and lonely out there.
But it isn't for me because I have him. He matters.
And I've lied to him for long enough.
What he did today was so brave,
braver than any of us
because we signed up for this. But he didn't!
He did it because he loves me,
and I won't take that away from him!
I won't!
And if that means I have to quit
or you retcon me or whatever, then fine,
fine.
You really think you could go back to your old life before Torchwood?
I wouldn't know anything different.
I would.
Give Rhys my love, and I will see you tomorrow.
If he comes after me again,
I'll kill him.
I love me.
Oh god. Say something.
- You OK with that?
- I've been for the last three years.
I killed three girls.
And it felt so good.
- Would you die for me?
- Yes.
How did you come here?
I'm the one you can confide it, remember?
I bury the memory of 150 years ago.
- Great.
- My little brother.
I can't afford to remember.
Drop the gun Jack.
And you always remember what you killed.
- Don't you, Jack?
- I let go of his hand.
It was the worst day of my life.
Capture:evarin
Welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net