and who am i?
that's a secret
i'll never tell.
you know you love me.
x.o.x.o., gossip girl.
sync by honeybunny @addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
(missing persons)
?you ask yourself ?
?where do we go from here?
?life is so strange ?
?destination unknown ?
?when you don't know ?
?your destination ?
?and something could change ?
(woman) rhodes records.
rick rhodes' office.
Hi. is he in?
It's lily.
Who?
His daughter?
Oh. ahem.
one moment, please.
Thank you.
thank you very much.
(click)
(man) hey, lil.
long time, babe.
Hi, dad. i know,
um, which is why i was hoping
That we could, like,
catch up or something.
There's so much
to talk about.
Is there any way
that you can, uh, have lunch?
You're in l.a.? why aren't you
in santa barbara?
In school?
well, we can make it a dinner
if that's better for you.
I'm leaving for london.
but, lil, what's going on?
geoffrey's?
your regular table?
Great. okay, see you then.
love you.
(horn honks)
(man) mrs. bass?
We're here.
Oh, yes. thank you.
Serena's been in jail
for over four hours.
She's already served more time
Than nicole richie
and lindsay lohan combined.
She's a socialite mistakenly
accused of stealing a bracelet.
I doubt they're working her over
with the phone book.
When i called lily,
she said she was on her way.
Where is she?
i just can't believe she had
her own daughter arrested.
I mean, who does that?
someone
who's never been arrested.
Hello. i'm lilian bass.
I'm here for my daughter,
serena van der woodsen.
So was lily blown away?
well, not really.
Yeah, he never actually, uh...
proposed. minor detail
in a proposal.
Kinda the key ingredient
to the recipe.
so he came home
and went into his room.
Uh, we haven't
seen him since.
ahem. hey, dad.
Oh, so prom tomorrow night--
What do you say? we stay in,
watch some scary movies?
the scarier the better.
Absolutely.
you guys are
the "gossip girl" generation.
Don't expect me to believe
you're not interested
In this gossip.
uh, nope. only interested
in my nim chow.
So to add to the lily intrigue--
or possibly help explain it--
I got a weird call
about your investment.
The money's gone. it's over.
really? 'cause, uh, serena had
a plan to get it all back.
It's--
no, lily had
a plan of her own.
Well,
that's what i was hoping.
yeah,
she had serena arrested.
What?
w-why?
I suggest you kids
stay out of it.
Let these van der woodsen women
fight it out themselves.
Wow.
(camera shutter snaps)
(jail door slams)
(sighs)
You forced me to do this. i just
hope you learned your lesson.
That my mom's crazier
than i ever imagined?
Well, no crazier than you,
my daughter,
Thinking you could fix
this situation yourself.
i was fixing this,
But then you were too worried
what people would think.
when you're a mother,
You will understand
that you have to make decisions
That don't always win you
points for popularity.
When i'm a mother,
i will be nothing like you.
Yes, you say that now,
but just wait.
I would rather give my kids
up for adoption
Than end up like you.
Oh, wait. you did that.
I came down here
To drop the charges
and put this behind us.
Please show a little respect,
and i will stick with my plan.
I'll just stick to mine.
If you didn't notice,
you weren't my phone call.
oh, so who was?
She called me, darling.
Ironic, isn't it?
If only she knew.
(serena) hey, grandma.
for those who complain about
the youth of today,
if you think we're bad,
you should've seen
our parents.
(camera shutter snaps)
I don't care how much
ahmet wants to give him.
The guy can't sing.
I'll pay for his publishing.
good-bye.
Hey, beautiful.
you get lost?
I'm sorry i'm late.
i couldn't find parking.
That's what the valet's for.
right, but it also costs $2,
and i just spent that on gas.
Here to hit dad up
for some cash?
what?
(laughs)
no.
So, um, christmas was weird
without you.
You know how important
the fourth quarter is to retail.
Somebody's gotta keep
tower records in business.
But i was sorry
i couldn't be there.
Yeah... um, about that...
I'm not a headshrinker
or anything,
But i do think
the sudden uprooting
Of my family from new york,
Coupled with my parents'
tumultuous divorce
May have contributed
to some recent difficulties
That i might be having.
you got kicked out
of boarding school.
what? wait, wait.
how did you know that?
she told me.
Mom.
Hello, lily.
what are you doing here?
If it was up to your father,
They'd stop me
at the county line,
But santa barbara's really
only a prison in my mind,
good to see you, cece.
wish i could say the same,
richard.
you hung up the phone with me,
and you called her?
You didn't even give me
a chance to explain.
That's because
he would have to parent,
And we know he always leaves
"bad cop" to me.
Punishing loved ones just comes
so much more naturally
To some people.
excuse me. may i have
a gin and tonic? no tonic.
I come with some good news.
You're letting me
live with dad? no way.
That's exactly what i was gonna
say. my bags are in the car.
And can i have the room that
overlooks the tennis courts?
I love that room. thank you for
coming all the way down here,
Mom, but i think this is
all worked out, right?
richard?
Lily, that sounds so good.
it's just--
Actually, your father did make
a call to the school.
I told 'em what had been
happening at home,
About your sister taking off,
your mother and i splitting up.
I explained that it was
An isolated, uncharacteristic
act of rebellion.
They're willing to turn your
expulsion into a suspension.
what?
you can be back on monday.
but i wanted to get expelled.
Lily, whatever for?
that school has everything.
Everything except for dad.
You're living
this amazing new life here,
And i'm just scared that
by the time i graduate,
I won't be
a part of it anymore.
And what if you forget
about me?
Lil, you do not have
to ever worry about that.
I just have a lot going on
right now with work.
I can't give you the time,
the--the supervision
That you need.
just like clockwork.
Okay.
Dad.
I'm late. i've gotta pack,
get to the airport.
Put lunch on my account.
i'll talk to you soon.
dad, no.
Why do you always
have to do that?
Dad.
(sighs) thank you.
Please don't walk away.
You need to be
with your mother, lil,
Out of the city, in school.
We can't let you turn out
like your sister.
Carol? yeah, i think we can
all agree on that front.
She ran away from our family,
and for what?
To become an actress, which is
a completely unrealistic goal.
I mean, yeah, she was
pretty good as abigail
In "the crucible," but what was
that, like, 11th grade?
Anyway, the point is--
is i'm not carol.
I don't crave adventure
or the freedom
To walk my own path.
i'm perfectly comfortable
With the path that you guys
have laid out for me.
go home, lil.
(kisses)
dad, you have a giant house.
i won't be any trouble.
I'll call you
when i get back from london.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Lily, it's over.
Let's go home.
I'll follow you back.
See you at home.
(engine revs)
(elevator bell dings)
eric and i had
the most invigorating walk
From the hotel.
you know, grandma is
deceptively quick.
Oh, she's probably racing back
to that bottle of gin
She has hidden under the sink
in the bathroom.
zing.
Good morning to you as well.
what are you doing here,
mother?
I don't remember inviting you
as our guest.
I know i haven't called you,
and i'm positive you haven't
So much as received
a christmas card
Or fruitcake at the holiday.
well, you can be thankful
for the last one.
What have i done to earn
your ire, my dear?
well, let me think
for a second.
Maybe telling rufus
about our child?
I'm sorry
if i thought it appropriate
That rufus learns he has a son.
Uh, you mean "had."
He died.
Oh.
I had no idea.
Imagine, something you don't
know. now if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to take serena
breakfast in bed
so i can start the healing
with my daughter.
uh, you might want
to put a hold on the healing.
Serena's not in her room.
what? i thought she was coming
home with you. where is she?
Why are you still in jail?
(serena) it's my choice.
Oh, god. you're not
gonna come out of there
With a mullet and a girlfriend,
are you?
my mother didn't think
that i was old enough
To make my own decisions,
so i decided to stay in jail,
And i'm not leaving
Until she agrees to let me
live my own life.
so it's a war of attrition.
(exhales deeply)
so to speak.
Except she gets to wage the war
from the comfort
Of her penthouse
while you remain behind bars.
look, don't worry about me.
enjoy prom with nate,
Like you always planned
In that scrapbook
that you kept under your bed.
(scoffs) please.
i don't remember that.
I was a child then.
I should go. i don't want
to abuse my phone privileges.
The fact that you're
on an actual pay phone
Has me beyond nauseous.
Stay strong, s.
What's this for?
strength. you will need.
I have good news and bad news.
which do you want?
Good news first, always.
There is replacement.
what are you talking about?
It makes more sense
if you pick bad news first.
Your dress for prom.
The dry cleaners--
they ruined it.
This body bag.
corpse not pretty.
But there's a replacement.
back to good news.
This morning it arrived
from paris.
Just like in scrapbook.
(laughs and gasps)
Oh! it is.
Oh! just like my scrapbook
i don't remember keeping
And haven't looked at
since i was an early adolescent.
Oh, i-it must be from daddy.
Tonight is
going to be magical.
(laughs)
You know, prom hasn't exactly
been going as planned.
The florists lost
blair's corsage.
Someone bought up
all the peonies,
And when i called
to confirm my limo,
It had been rented out by
a bachelorette party in jersey.
(inhales sharply)
the heart quickens.
Yeah, well, my hotel room
was mysteriously canceled,
And now i just found out
blair's dress has been ruined.
how tragic.
I gotta ask...
am i sabotaging
your dream prom?
The answer is no,
nathaniel.
And i don't know
how many times
We need to have
this conversation.
Blair is yours.
Okay.
Oh, what a restorative nap
that was.
I feel so much better.
Well, i'm afraid that moment
is not going to last.
Eric out of earshot?
i sent him to a movie
with jonathan.
So no one can hear me scream.
you're gonna what, lily,
Hack me to pieces,
suffocate me with a pillow?
i am simply--
and for the last time--
Gonna ask you to leave my home
and never come back.
"never" is a, uh,
very long time, darling.
You are toxic.
I'm your mother.
and a memorable one at that,
so much so it seems
That try as i might,
i can't help turning into you.
well, maybe that's 'cause
You finally are starting
to see the wisdom of my ways.
You blame me for everything.
and you accept responsibility
for nothing.
You know,
maybe carol's right.
The only way to have a normal
life is without you in it.
your sister was rebellious
And ungrateful for my love,
and look where she ended up.
From where i'm sitting,
it doesn't look so bad.
I don't want you meddling
With my family
or with my love life anymore.
I want you out. now.
Hi. i'm looking for
my sister carol. carol rhodes.
Uh, i think that
she works here. is she in?
I'm covering four extra tables
today, so that'd be no.
Flaking on work--
that seems like carol.
Do you know
where she might be?
(dishes clatter)
Hey! watch
where you're going, spaz.
You almost got udon
all over my gucci.
Personally, i don't see it.
See what?
The family resemblance.
to carol?
wait. you know her?
Yeah.
Well, do you know
where she might be?
Trying to work here.
well, you missed a spot.
(taps counter)
it's kinda sticky.
I'm sorry. i'm sorry.
I've had a really rough day.
i got kicked out of school,
My dad doesn't want me
to live with him,
I can't stand my mom, i spent
the last $9 that i had on gas,
And so now i'm broke
and i'm homeless,
And unless i can find my sister,
who i basically
Haven't talked to
in, like, a year,
I'm gonna have to become
a prostitute.
and i don't even know how
to be a prostitute.
I mean, really,
how much small talk is required?
And--and where do you even go?
and are b.j.s a must?
Because if that's the case,
i am so not doing that.
Not that any of that information
is relevant
Unless you're a john.
not a john. owen.
Lily.
There's a gig
at the 6-0-7 tonight.
Chances are your sister
will be there.
My friend's kinda dating her.
if you wanna go...
On a double date?
with a guy
That i just met five minutes
ago? you could be a psycho.
My shift ends in ten.
probably see your sister.
Don't want to come,
i'll give her your regards
And summarize the whole,
uh, prostitute thing.
I could change.
I have my suitcase
in the car.
Yeah. i'm just guessing,
But i don't think
that's gonna work.
You should try
something like this.
Your sister's always changing
for auditions and stuff.
(taps locker)
Wow.
She's really changed.
I can't believe
that she has this.
we went ice skating
at rockefeller center.
she snuck me
out of the house.
we took a bus across town.
my mom was so furious.
It was so much fun.
We were, like,
Best friends.
You can go now.
already out the door.
(cell phone rings)
Oh, hello, daniel.
Hey. so, uh, look, i'm really
sorry to bother you,
But i can't leave serena
one more message
And still call myself a man.
Not that it's exactly manly
to be calling her "mother,"
But i-i-i-i
really need to know,
Uh, how mad is she?
Oh, i-i wouldn't worry.
She hasn't gotten
your messages.
They take your cell phone away
when you're in jail.
Wait.
She's--she's still in jail?
(billy idol's
"dancing with myself" playing)
Hey. i think i need
a dress for prom.
Okay. but you're gonna
have to wear your own shoes.
?on the floors of tokyo ?
?a-down in london town's
a go-go ?
?a-with the record selection
and the mirror's reflection ?
?i'm a-dancing with myself ?
?oh, oh, dancing with myself ?
?if i had the chance,
i'd ask one to dance ?
?ow ?
?oh, oh, oh, oh ?
?oh, oh, oh,
dancing with myself ?
?oh, oh, dancing with myself ?
Get out, perv!
sorry.
You're taking long enough.
(sighs) do i looks like
i'm wearing a halloween costume?
No.
You look good.
Is this the moment where
you fall in love with me?
Oh, it is, isn't it?
You're totally falling in love
with me right now.
are you coming or not?
?if i had the chance,
i'd ask one to dance ?
Hello. i'd like to drop
The charges against
serena van der woodsen.
There's been
a terrible misunderstanding.
well, you can talk to someone
about the charges,
But your daughter's gone.
?oh, oh, dancing with myself ?
?oh, oh, dancing with myself,
oh, oh ?
?stand and deliver! ?
(applause)
?i'm the dandy highwayman who
you're too scared to mention ?
?i spend my cash ?
?on looking flash
and grabbing your attention ?
?the devil take your stereo
and your record collection ?
?the way you look ?
?you qualify for
next year's old-age pension ?
?stand and deliver ?
?your money or your life ?
?try and use a mirror ?
?no bullet or knife ?
?i'm the dandy highwayman
so sick of easy fashion ?
Wow, you're, like,
really popular around here.
Yeah, when you don't have
a lot of family at home,
You gotta find it
somewhere else.
?...nothing is worth taking? ?
?it's kind of tough
to tell a scruff ?
?the big mistake he's making,
stand and deliver ?
?your money or your life ?
It's kinda cool, right?
Sure. yeah, cool place
to catch hepatitis.
Owen!
(can clatters)
missed our set, man!
it was awesome.
It was like... (howls)
it was wicked! ha ha!
shep, hey.
Hey, who's the betty?
this your new girl?
no.
No. we're looking
for her sister.
no time to talk, guys. your
needs are gonna have to wait.
I have a plan. actually,
you know, it's more than a plan.
It's a mission.
but it's not just about me.
It's about my lady.
she's been wronged,
And i'm gonna make it right.
(snaps fingers)
What did they do to your lady,
tattoo the wrong butt cheek?
(woman) randy walter sheppard!
My 20s are ticking away
as we speak,
And we gotta go now!
Carol!
carol?
Lily?
What are you doing here?
What are you guys doing
with my sister?
whoa. wait.
she's--she's your sister?
she's your lady?
kind of.
No! lily, oh, my god.
it's so good to see you.
How do you know owen? i'm so
sorry i haven't written more
Or called, like, ever.
are you totally mad?
Wait. what are you doing
in l.a.? is something wrong?
Is everything okay?
yeah. no, not really.
i have--i have to talk to you
About something,
and it's kind of major.
okay, and i wanna hear about it,
i mean, totally there for you,
But right now i have to handle
something, and it cannot wait.
i know.
(lily) neither can this.
(carol) we'll talk in the car.
(shep) to the impala.
(lily) to the what? where?
(owen) the mission is
on the move.
oh, my god, lily.
it's so good to see you.
I've missed you.
are you wearing my dress?
?stand and deliver ?
?your money or your life ?
(playing swing version
of "stand and deliver")
(indistinct conversations)
(blair) oh, my god.
look at this place.
I've always tried
to make my life
Resemble the movie in my head,
And tonight, no effort required.
voil? (laughs)
Vote for prom king and queen?
We don't do prom queen.
that's for suburban schools
And the lame teen comedies
that are set at them.
We're doing it this year.
there's a tiara and everything.
A tiara?
But if you don't want
to vote for yourselves...
We were nominated. (laughs)
let's see.
I mean, of course we were.
(isabel) aw, you guys, i think
i'm getting sentimental.
it's true. this is
probably our last huddle.
Yeah, if you do this stuff
in college,
People think
you're pathological.
Come on, ladies.
let's commit election fraud.
I can't wait
to see blair's face
When she loses prom queen
to nelly.
(giggles)
And look, i-i know
this thing with your mom
Took on a life of its own,
but i just want to say
That i'm sorry for starting it
in the first place.
it was just really upsetting
That--that you went to her
without giving me a warning.
I know, and normally i would
never do something like this,
But lily is not like
other parents.
with good judgment, morals
and maternal instinct?
And when she said that she was
gonna take care of it,
I never imagined that
you'd end up incarcerated.
the most frustrating part is
She thinks she did
take care of it.
Hey, soldier,
eyes up front.
Well, i'm, uh, i'm glad
you let me bail you out
Or let me call cece to,
'cause missing your prom
Just to spite your own mother
is--is kinda--
something
only she would do, yeah.
Thank you for--for getting me
to see that,
And thank you for
breaking the cycle of crazy.
(laughs)
So what happened to the beemer
that mom and dad got you?
Oh, i sold it.
For this?
As if.
i gave it to this guy.
He had
this really amazing idea.
It goes around your waist
like a belt
So you can put stuff in it,
like a purse.
Wow. that's
a really sound investment.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing. nothing. (scoffs)
It just--your life isn't
exactly how you described.
You told mom that you were
making it out in l.a.
i am making it. this is
what making it looks like...
Before you've totally made it.
Carol, i've always thought
That you were
really, really talented.
It's just--
is it really worth...
Living your life,
you know...
Like this?
well, it's not forever.
Not once we get
shep's music video on mtv.
I'm totally the star. a music
video equals national exposure.
It's the birth
of a new art form.
really? shep's band?
Okay, i know you probably
wouldn't think so
Having met shep, but they're
actually kinda great.
Well, if they're so great,
then why don't you
Give their demo to dad?
because he's dad,
and i'm doing this on my own.
(turns volume up)
(lowered voice) listen, don't
tell anybody about who we are.
Especially them.
why do you care
what they think?
And besides,
being us is awesome.
all that money comes
with strings attached, lily.
People treat you differently.
Yeah, better.
Wow. (laughs) could you
sound any more like mom?
Of course i sound like mom.
She's the only female role model
i've had since you bailed on us.
Hey.
I think we're here.
(sighs)
I never wanted
to be like my mother.
I wanted to be open to life
and--and fearless
And not always thinking three
steps ahead--and consequences
And what would people say
or what would my father think.
Well, you have,
for the most part,
With a few notable exceptions.
That beautiful dinner
you made--
You were gonna propose,
weren't you?
But you didn't.
Because what i did to serena
made you fundamentally question
The kind of person that i am.
you're unpredictable,
that's for sure.
When i was younger,
that was damn exciting.
You were
always surprising me.
I'm just doomed to repeat
my mother's mistakes.
why do you always
have to do that?
dad, wait.
please don't walk away.
Our mistakes are ours alone
to repeat... or correct.
I should forgive serena
for defying me.
Or first maybe you need
to forgive cece.
oh, my mother
doesn't need forgiveness.
She needs electroshock therapy.
you've got good reason
to be angry with her--
those messed up values
she passed on to you.
i'll follow you back.
Until you let it go,
How can you move forward
with your own daughter?
Cece's never gonna change,
lil.
But you still can.
Thank you, rufus.
(sighs)
I'm glad we can talk,
but as for everything else,
I just don't know
where we stand right now.
Even after 20 years,
You're still not sure
who i am.
It's not that i'm not sure.
It's just, i think
you're still figuring it out.
Ah.
And she sticks the landing.
So is information
on this mission
Revealed
on a need-to-know basis?
Because i really need to know.
carol.
The so-called director
of our music video
Took our money
and then jacked up his fee,
And now he's holding
our video hostage,
And i am
a hostage negotiator.
yeah, just 'cause this dork's
uncle is john landis
Doesn't mean
he's above the law.
No richie rich film school kid
rips off me and my girl.
shep, i'm not your girl.
Right. she's--
she's more like my muse.
Oh, sweet hand towels.
So are we, like,
breaking and entering?
Seriously?
the window was unlocked,
So really,
it's just... entering.
And i thought investing
in purse belts was a bad idea.
thanks, lily.
Since i know how much
you love following the rules,
Why don't you just stay here,
far away from the party,
Where people are
actually having fun?
Owen, can you keep an eye
on her?
(toilet flushes)
(sighs)
What? just because my idea
of a good time
Isn't getting arrested for
breaking into some guy's house,
I'm automatically
a stuck-up goody two-shoes?
It doesn't exactly make you
the life of the party.
Where's the bar?
I think it's this way.
(swing music playing)
You made it!
yeah! there was
a last minute change of plans.
Yeah, i sprung her
out of the pokey.
You can--
you can thank me later.
well, i just spent ten seconds
talking to you,
So consider yourself repaid.
have fun.
(laughs)
(chuckles)
So, you know,
Not that i imagined, uh,
much about my time at prom,
But, um... it measures up.
Did you ever imagine yourself
dancing at prom?
That i did.
well, i am here
to make dreams come true.
Come dance with me.
bailing you out of prison
And dancing with you at prom
in one night? that's...
Yeah, i'm here
to make things interesting.
?
(men without hats)
?we can dance if we want to ?/i>
?we can leave your friends
behind ?/i>
?'cause your friends don't
dance and if they don't dance ?/i>
?well, they're no friends
of mine ?/i>
?i say, we can go
when we want to ?/i>
?a place where
they will never find ?/i>
?and we can act like we come
from out of this world ?/i>
?leave the real one
far behind ?/i>
?/i>
(inhales deeply) hey,
van der woodsen, you want some?
(depeche mode's "just can't
get enough" playing)
(carol) hey, keith!
Surprised to see me?
Carol. hey.
Wow. you, uh,
You look amazing.
Really? even more amazing than
in the video you won't give us?
Look, i'm sorry about that.
i just, uh,
I couldn't think of any other
way to get you to call me
So i could explain--
you have a girlfriend.
nothing else to explain.
I just want the video.
Hey. who is this?
Is she available?
Nah, man.
Nah, she, uh,
she was just leaving.
No, i wasn't.
?we walk together, we're
walking down the street ?/i>
?i just can't get enough,
i just can't get enough ?/i>
?it's getting hotter ?/i>
?it's our burning love,
and i just can't seem... ?/i>
Oh!
?to get enough, ah ?/i>
Oh, is this the moment
where you fall in love with me?
It is, isn't it?
You're totally falling
in love with me right now.
(chuckles)
?/i>
(glass shatters)
(carol) spare me, keith!
(blair) this is low,
even for you.
I can't believe you did this,
chuck.
You know how important
prom is to me!
blair, what's wrong?
I caught him with these.
they're all marked
With nelly yuki's name.
he's sabotaging me.
My missing corsage, my dress,
the limo and hotel?
(carol) we paid you 500 bucks
to shoot that thing.
we were friends then.
i was giving you a special rate.
Our relationship's
changed now.
You can pay me
the balance in cash
Or... i don't know...
What are you doing
saturday?
Gross. my sister
would never sleep with you.
yeah, 'cause she's dating me.
Shep, we're not dating.
we were never dating.
Well, both of you don't know
carol very well,
'cause, yeah,
she totally slept with me.
(clicks tongue)
pretty fun, too.
You slept with
your music video director?
i didn't know
he had a girlfriend,
And i broke it off
as soon as i found out.
But what he wants
to charge us?
Might as well be
a million bucks.
And i know you probably think
i should ask mom and dad
For the money, but...
Whatever. i'll think
of something. it's fine.
No, carol. it's not fine.
Hi. i'm lily rhodes,
and that's my sister,
And no one treats us
this way.
Okay. we already called
the cops, so...
You guys are trespassing.
It's cool, okay?
we're done here.
Finally.
Take the trash
back to the valley.
(scoffs)
what did you just say?
Don't you have
anything better to do,
Like get your butt tattooed?
The only tattoo i'm getting
tonight is your face on my fist.
Ladies, come on.
no need to fight over me.
Okay. okay.
How about we just fight you?
(grunts)
(boy) i got him.
(carol) lily. come on.
(boy) go, go, go. get 'em!
(carol shouts indistinctly)
Where do you think
you're going?
(boy grunts)
(owen grunts)
Carol!
(grunts)
aah!
(owen grunting)
(grunts)
Oh! hey! leave him alone!
(keith) aah!
(lily grunts)
(guests) oh!
(microphone feedback whines)
Students, if i could have
your attention, please.
For the first time ever
at constance,
Our prom queen is...
I can't believe you're not
even defending yourself.
(blair) lie to my face!
blame someone! something!
I'm sorry. just one moment.
(whispers) seriously?
(whispers) i know how to count.
(normal voice)
our prom queen is...
Blair waldorf.
But that's impossible!
(applause)
Oh, my god. i won.
This is my moment.
I own prom.
(penelope) and our king--
nate archibald.
Oh, my gosh!
This is so great!
(gasps) thank you!
Oh. thanks.
(microphone feedback whines)
Thank you, everyone.
Oh, i can't believe blair won.
yeah,
who even voted for her?
Me. about 150 times.
I wasn't putting
the nelly yuki ballots in.
I was taking them out.
but what about what she said
you did to her limo
And hotel and her corsage?
her new dress looks better
without it.
(camera shutter snaps)
Give this to her.
It's to the penthouse
at the plaza.
You didn't think
you were the only one
Who knew about
the scrapbook, did you?
(camera shutter snaps)
Chuck, i...
I can't believe
i'm saying this, but...
That was really sweet.
I just wanted to make sure
she had the perfect night.
(cheering)
your 2009 king and queen!
aw, who knew the mother-chucker
could also play
fairy godmother?
but if c. just made
b.'s dreams come true,
why does it feel like
our queen is standing
with the wrong king?
You can't use the one
You already have on file?
(camera shutter snaps)
Wait. let me
at least fix my makeup.
(camera shutter snaps)
(telephone rings)
(woman) are you ready
to do the workout?
(women) yeah!
beginner's workout. stand with
your feet a little more...
Jail?
you're in jail?
(voice breaks) i know, mom.
i'm--i'm sorry.
you know,
if i was a better mother,
I'd leave you in there, teach
you a lesson. you ran away.
You just abandoned me
at the side of the road.
you know they only give you
one phone call, right?
Oh, lily, the hopes and dreams
i have for you--
An ivy league education,
life on the upper east side,
Married to the richest man
see, that's the thing, mom--
Those are your hope
and your dreams, not mine.
I need to figure out what--
what i want, what i need.
Like a parole officer?
i'm getting in the car.
You need to be far away
from your sister's influence.
Why? what's wrong with carol?
the fact that she's independent?
That she thinks for herself?
that she does what she wants
And not what other people
tell her to do?
How about your spare me
the heartache
And yourself the humiliation
And give up on this failed
experiment in rebellion?
What if this is not
an experiment?
What about if this
is me growing up?
Enough soul searching. i'm
calling your father's lawyer.
We need to keep this thing
out of the papers.
(crying) please, mom,
i don't need a publicist.
I need my mother.
I'm trying to talk to you here,
and you're not...
Hey, mom. got a sec?
Carol.
This is your chance
To be a big sister
And finally offer some actual
guidance to lily, advice.
Her future's at stake.
Which is why she needs
to be far away from you.
This is how it's going to be,
mom.
Lily's staying with me
for a while.
carol, just be reasonable.
We both know the first time
that she breaks a nail,
Rides a city bus--
Or god forbid--actually steps
foot in a public school,
She'll come running home.
well, that's really up to lily,
now isn't it?
Just tell her to--to sit tight.
i'm coming for her.
No, mom. you sit tight.
she'll call you later.
(whispers) oh, goodness.
(normal voice) mother. mom.
Don't tell me you're
chasing me out of town.
I'm fleeing as fast as i can.
Well, please stop.
i'm not going to apologize,
But i love you,
and i know you love me.
Well, of course i love you,
My daughters,
my grandchildren.
My only motivation is love.
on the contrary.
Your motives are quite suspect,
selfish even.
And you haven't always done
what's best for me.
Well, i've done
the very best i could.
You think serena's a handful?
I would rather have
20 dan humphreys from brooklyn
Instead of that boy you loved
from the valley.
Well, you took care of that,
didn't you?
And you ended up
with serena and eric
And the life you deserve.
it wasn't up to you to decide
what kind of life i should have.
What else does it mean
to be a mother
Than to make sure that your
child fulfills her destiny?
Well, i wanted to create
my own destiny.
But that would have meant
losing you,
And i was always too afraid
to do that.
until this afternoon,
evidently.
(sighs) mother, please,
i'm just asking you to stay.
You know, being a mother myself,
i've made mistakes
That rival
if not outshine your own.
And i forgive you.
Lucky me.
You throw me out of your home,
and i get forgiven.
Mother, just say thank you
and give me a hug.
I most certainly
am not gonna thank you
For the terrible things
you said.
And as far as the hug goes,
Well, you've always done exactly
as you pleased, haven't you?
(fountain of wayne's
"prom theme" playing)
Hey. you okay?
This is supposed to be
the happiest day in high school.
So why do i feel so sad?
Like something's ending?
Well, something is ending--
High school.
Not just school.
You're my first love.
(sighs) going
to my senior prom with you
Is something i've wanted
since i was 12 years old.
And here we are,
Like it was meant to be.
Yes.
this was supposed to happen.
I'm sure of it.
But now it has and--
Why are you talking
in the past tense?
We're still here.
I know.
But this night already
feels like a memory.
(sighs)
Just hold me...
Until the song's over.
Let's not waste these last
moments talking about it.
(whispers) okay.
?but tonight we feel
like we're stars ?/i>
?we'll play our air guitars,
'cause we're 18 ?/i>
?it's a perfect night ?/i>
?to sing our prom theme ?/i>
Hey.
There you are.
Where's the prom king?
We broke up.
What?
But--but everything was
so perfect.
It w--it was like
a fairy tale.
It turns out fairy tales
end when they do for a reason.
I really wanted to go to prom
with my high school boyfriend.
And... now that i have...
He feels like
your high school boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
Me, too--
That you almost missed prom
Because your mother
had you arrested...
(laughs)
And your quasi
half-brother/ex-boyfriend
Was your prom date.
(laughs) you know, i actually
had a lot of fun tonight.
Dan and i made up, and i know
that whatever my mother did,
She--she did out of love.
And right now, i am with exactly
who i want to be with--
My best friend.
(lily) so thank you.
Well, it's the least i can do
Since i got you arrested
and everything.
I didn't know
you were such a brawler.
Neither did i.
I learned some things
last night...
The biggest one being...
That i've really missed you.
You are high school to me--
All of the boyfriends
And mean girls and--
and tests and teachers
And our crazy mothers...
We--we went through it
together.
We raised each other.
You're my sister.
(chuckles)
So where's your car?
How do you think
i got you out of here?
You sold your car?
What are we gonna do?
we're gonna walk?
Walking in l.a.? wow, sis.
I have so much more
to teach you. come on.
It's us. we travel in style
no matter how we travel.
(freur) ?doot ?
?doot-doot ?
?doot ?
shoulder pads may come and go,
but a b.f.f. is forever...
because even when you're not
sure where you're headed,
it helps to know
you're not going there alone.
(cell phone alert beeps)
no one has all the answers,
and sometimes the best
we can do is just apologize
and let the past be the past.
other times,
we need to look to the future
and know that even when
we think we've seen it all,
life can still surprise us,
and we can still
surprise ourselves.
x.o.x.o., gossip girl.
www.tvsubtitles.net