Gossip Girl here,
your one and only source
into the scandalous life
of Manhattan's elite.
I love you. That's not really
the reaction I was hoping for.
- What is it?
- It's from my dad and it's been opened.
You don't get
to judge me ever again.
Tell me that you didn't sleep
with him.
I did kiss him, but that's all.
You have the wrong idea.
I'm not some sort of trophy husband.
It's okay. We all sacrifice
our independence for love.
- You took the wrong boat.
- No,
this is the one with the cash.
Mine had the "E" in it.
I spent 18 years accepting the fact
my mother was dead.
Your real mother would never turn
her back on a chance to now you.
- I don't have a real mother, Blair.
- It doesn't mean you're alone.
We should try to take this slow.
I was thinking the same thing.
This wasn't a date.
If you want one, you'll have to ask.
Épisode 313:
The Hurt Locket
.: Arcadya Global Team :.
www.arcadya.net
www.sous-titres.eu
Get up and go at it,
Upper East Side.
I hear Little J. is
having foreign relations
with a handsome attaché.
We always knew she had friends
in high places.
But how low will she go?
What are you even doing here?
Your stepmom doesn't get up
before noon.
But if she doesn't, you'll be spending
the day in my closet.
Kinky.
All right, I'll go.
Are we still on for tonight?
Oh, yeah I was thinking Italian.
Maybe Morandi or Il Buco?
If you don't want to go downtown,
we could just walk over to Tony's.
Not that I don't love popcorn
and a movie,
but it's Saturday night.
I wanted to go out.
We are.
In fact, we have half a dozen deliveries
to make at some parties.
- Again? You're the only dealer in town?
- No rest for the wicked.
I'm gonna have to leave these here
for the day if that's cool.
Jenny's drug way station.
I guess that's the good thing
about my parents' huge fight.
I can think of others.
Hey, don't you wanna answer that?
Hello, father.
No, I can't this evening.
I have plans.
Just a friend.
All right,
shall we take care of this?
What?
Nothing.
Since when do you cook?
I didn't even know
we had a fridge until this morning.
We're not heathens.
Stop.
- I told you I was good in the kitchen.
- The olives I could've done without.
- Not really a breakfast food.
- I'm still hungry.
Doesn't Rufus make brunch
on Saturdays?
I prefer this breakfast.
Oh, God!
- Oh, God.
- Chuck!
Of course. Not to be outdone.
God forbid.
Yes! That's it! God.
Yes!
Oh, don't stop! God, Chuck!
- Oh, God, that's it! Yeah!
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
- Chuck?
- Where are you?
- Early meeting.
I forgot my cell.
Can you stick it in my briefcase?
- Blair is sort of in there right now.
- Which is why you need to grab it.
She can get curious,
and this is not a good time.
Yeah, man. I will do.
Great.
Yes! God, Chuck!
God, Chuck!
Yes!
- Oh, God, Chuck!
- Blair?
Yes, right there! Oh!
- Haven't you heard of knocking?
- I did knock, but you didn't hear me.
- We heard you, though.
- I'm sorry.
- Was it awkward?
- Are you trying to prove a point?
Yes. But I shouldn't have to.
I'm just glad I got
Chuck's couch scotchgarded.
Now if you'll excuse me,
Louis Vuitton is doing
metallic booties for spring.
Talk to me.
Tell me what's wrong.
Chuck and I aren't connecting
right now.
You mean...
Not just like that.
But thanks so much for
the constant reminder.
Sorry.
He's shutting me out
in his head all the time.
Normally, I'd chalk it up
to just him being him.
But last week he
went through something,
and...
If he's still upset, I just want him
to be able to talk to me.
How do you usually
pull these things out of him?
Pretty much what you just heard,
sans fashion magazine.
I've tried all my tricks.
He's not interested.
I just wanna make him feel better.
Bit overdressed, aren't we?
I have an extra pair of board shorts
if you want to join me.
Hit Ocean Drive?
Maybe some other time.
Listen to me.
All right, I know I screwed up,
and I don't blame you for
not returning my calls.
But I miss you.
And what I said at the hospital,
it was as a friend, only as a friend.
- It's cool. You don't have to explain.
- No, I really do
I want things to be like before.
We hang out today, remind ourselves
how normal it can be between us.
- The dorm's throwing a party tonight.
- Great, I love parties.
- And I'm going with Paul.
- I love Paul.
Don't you think
that it would be weird?
- Weird? No, I'll bring a date.
- What date?
If you would've returned one
of my 10,000 phone calls,
you'd know that I'm seeing someone.
It's not serious at all, but...
It'll be fun and normal.
Fine. The party starts in an hour.
All right.
Wait.
What's her name?
Melissa.
It's a good name. See you soon.
Hey, do you know
a girl named Melissa?
Everybody decent in here?
- Got it.
- What are you doing?
My phone's dead.
I was gonna use Chuck's.
There's a phone in the living room.
- I know. I wanted to check a tweet.
- Wait.
Chuck asked you to grab his phone
when he called, didn't he?
- Chuck called?
- No.
I mean, yes.
He doesn't want to forget his phone,
he asked me to put it in his briefcase.
I miss that.
- What?
- Dating someone who's a horrible liar.
So much easier.
Chuck didn't want me to see his phone.
Hand it over, Archibald.
There's half a dozen calls
from a number
I've never seen,
and... a message.
I was just going out for a coffee...
Hi, Lily.
You're up really early.
You remember Damien, right?
He just stopped by.
What is going on here?
Or do I even have to ask?
Lily, I'm...
I'm so sorry.
Please, don't tell my dad.
Please.
I want both of you
in the living room now.
You, get dressed.
I shouldn't.
I turned over a new leaf,
a new, non-meddling leaf
from the trust tree.
If he want keep secrets, then...
But he shouldn't.
Something is bothering him,
and he's not telling me about it.
What am I supposed to do, right?
Blair, put the phone down,
and talk to him when he gets home.
What?
It's this number. It's the same number
he called me from this morning.
Charles, it's me again.
I know I keep calling,
but you haven't returned,
and there are things you need to know,
things I need to tell you.
I'm still at the Algonquin
but I'm checking out today.
I hope you'll change your mind.
Elizabeth Fisher was staying there.
- Who's Elizabeth Fisher?
- Her name used to be Evelyn,
and she's my mother.
And just like that,
we get the mother of all questions.
Chuck, how is that even possible?
Bart told you your mother died.
He also told me kids
wear suits to kindergarten
and that blue chip stocks
are great for birthday gifts.
He told me
what he wanted me to believe.
Chuck ran into a woman at Bart's grave
and tracked her down.
She told us she was just
one of Bart's friends,
but I guess...
- You okay?
- Why wouldn't I be?
You're not excited.
After this time of thinking your mother
is gone, now you have a second chance.
A chance for what?
Why even come back?
She's here now. Who cares why?
I've got a pretty good idea
what her motivation is.
Throw this away.
- Chuck, no.
- Serena, just...
You have no idea what happened
20 years ago, why she stayed away.
- You have to at least let her explain.
- No, I really don't.
I'm going to the bar for a drink.
If you're planning on doing
any more sleuthing behind my back,
I can leave you
the combination for the hotel safe.
- He's gonna be fine.
- He's being crazy.
- What are we gonna do?
- Nothing.
You didn't see him
when he confronted this woman,
and she sent him away.
He's had enough pain in his life.
If he doesn't wanna hear her story,
then I'm gonna respect that,
and so will you.
I'm gonna take off. I don't really feel
like playing the scared boyfriend role.
No one's asking you
to play the boyfriend role.
Okay, Lily, what's so important
that you couldn't tell me on the phone?
Well, Jenny had a friend
stay over last night,
and I thought it would be
a good idea for us to talk about it.
So how long have you and Vanessa known
each other?
We've been best friends
since we were kids.
I was talking to Paul.
Right. Of course.
Paul and I met at a cabaret
last semester.
And the theme was fairy tales,
so it's only appropriate that I met
- my prince charming.
- Actually, Dan was prince charming.
- Where did you and Dan meet?
- In the hallway. He...
I was lost.
This building can be very tricky
when you don't live here.
- Let's go hit a beach ball around.
- Yeah. Sure.
Are we gonna talk
about what's going on here?
More drinks first.
I'm sorry.
But...
A Blair Waldorf apology
without a caveat?
Sounds serious.
Which is why I'm here
if you wanna talk.
Or if you don't.
Even if she is my mother,
she isn't.
It doesn't change anything.
The past belongs to the past.
I think we should go
to Bart's grave one last time,
drop that of and never look back.
Come here.
Where do I even start?
How could you let this happen?
I didn't let anything happen.
Jenny is not Serena.
Contrary to popular belief,
children need boundaries.
Excuse me, sir.
The truth is,
we fell asleep watching TV.
I know that sounds like
"teenage excuses for dummies."
I appreciate
that you're a concerned father...
The worst part of being
a father of a teenage girl
is remembering when
you were a teenage boy.
- Pack your bags You're coming with me.
- What? Where, dad? I live here.
- Not anymore. You're back to Brooklyn.
- Dad, you can't do that.
- Pack your bags or I will.
- Okay, fine. I'll do it myself.
- Rufus, can we please talk about this?
- No, Lily, we can't.
While she's packing her stuff,
maybe I'll go grab what's left of mine.
- Where's Melissa?
- Uh, oh, she's salsa dancing. Paul?
She seems nice.
- I knew this was gonna be weird.
- How so?
We're not
in a friendship groove here.
- There's too much pressure.
- Too much? There's no pressure.
Problem solved. What could be friendlier
than taking a mock photo?
Come on.
- Photo?
- Huh?
- Right. That was...
- You know, it's...
it's all these mojitos,
the confined space and the heat.
Right. Miami.
Um, so photo?
We come in peace.
We're here for ya.
We made reservations at Kellari.
Greeks know how to do comfort food.
What do you say?
I guess I could use the walk...
And some food in my system.
- You sure we're doing the right thing?
- It's his mother.
You know Chuck. He just
needs a little push.
Careful, S.
You may think you know what's best,
but this time, you might
just be pushing your Chuck.
- What?
- Nothing.
Our drinks would be nice,
maybe some bread for the table.
You haven't eaten bread
since middle school.
So, buddy, uh, how you
holding up? You good?
Yeah, I'm fine.
No, it wasn't me.
- We called her.
- We think you're making a big mistake,
one you'll regret for the rest of your
life. Why not just listen?
- That's it. Let's go.
- Blair, you know I'm right.
No matter what he says now, he'll always
wonder, and it will eat away at him.
She's here now,
and she wants to talk to you.
Whatever she has to say,
it's better than not knowing.
Fine.
- I forgot our drinks.
- Melissa and I already grabbed some.
And we got to talking.
He was surprised to find out
- we just met this morning.
- This morning?
Right before you called and told me
you wanted to get back together.
Back together?
How do you feel about salsa dancing?
I can explain.
Can you just wait one second?
No, we get it, even if you don't.
And whatever's going on between you two
either do something
or don't do something about it.
But, please, don't bring normal
people into whatever this is.
This was a mistake.
I was brought here
under false pretenses.
Your friend Serena told
me that you know who I am.
"Friend" is a pretty
loose term right now.
- They're talking.
- See? I knew if they got together
Eat your spanakopita.
- I don't know where to start.
- If it's all the same to you,
why don't we skip
to the end of the story?
I'm... I'm sorry?
- What's he doing?
- Oh, Chuck.
I know why you're here.
Yes, to-to talk.
Really? Well, we'll see
how much you want to talk,
because...
I bet it's not as much...
as this.
She doesn't want the money.
She won't take it.
She just wants to talk to him.
- I'm going over there.
- Serena, sit your ass down.
No judgment, no strings attached,
but one.
I don't want to know your story.
I want to know you'll leave
and never come back.
This is really what you want?
I'm sorry, Charles.
You're right.
An expensive lunch, but it was worth it.
By the way, you were wrong.
What are you still doing here?
Do you want my dad to kill you?
Right. Well, I assume you're
not leaving without these.
I will be taking these, but...
I actually came to say goodbye.
Okay.
Well, goodbye... friend.
That's what you called me
on the phone to your dad, right?
- So?
- So I'm getting exiled to Brooklyn
because of our relationship,
and I don't even know if we have one.
You're in high school.
- Your father's not out of line.
- Okay.
You know, wait a second.
I'm not gonna go write your name
in a heart on my binder, okay?
But you cannot expect me to
start world war III with my dad
without even giving me
something to fight for.
What difference does it make?
Your father won't let you see me again.
Okay, now who's in high school?
I fight with my dad all the time.
Last year I ran away.
- I'm not afraid to stand up to him.
- Jenny?
What are you doing?
Whose are these?
They're mine.
Watch your step, little J.
Damien may be your drug of choice,
but it looks like this
love could be bad medicine.
- Look, I can explain.
- Oh, believe me, you will.
Right now.
- Did you know about this?
- No Rufus,
I did not know
about a giant bag of pills.
What are you doing?
I may be a bitch, but
I'm not a little bitch.
I told you I wasn't afraid.
Are you taking these or selling them?
I want the truth.
They're for a friend.
- Please don't make this worse.
- Okay I don't get what the big deal is.
You didn't spend
years on the tour bus reading.
There's a huge difference between
sharing a joint with my bassist
and getting caught with
a sack of narcotics.
This is serious, Jenny.
Okay.
So let's just get it over with
then. Am I grounded for life?
- Military school? What?
- Probably both.
This goes way past that, Jenny.
See, I look at you
and I don't see my daughter anymore.
The drugs don't belong to Jenny.
They're mine.
Actually, they're my father's.
Chuck, wait.
You were looking for
a fairy-tale ending.
Next time rent a movie.
Leave me out of I.
I just wanted him to have answers.
Please. You and I both
know why you did this,
and it has nothing to do with Chuck.
You're right.
I'm sorry. I should go.
Hey, I'll go with you.
Nate, I need to be alone right now.
What do you mean, it had
nothing to do with Chuck?
Sorry, Nate.
- We need to talk about this.
- What?
- Our... our kiss.
- What's there to discuss?
We both had too many mojitos.
Why did you lie
to me about dating Paul?
Because I knew
you had feelings for me,
and I didn't want things to be awkward
between us. And if I was dating Paul,
- then you won't get hopes.
- V, don't...
No, don't get all Dan Humphrey on me.
Melissa? Really?
All right, fine.
It's clearly not my best plan.
I shouldn't lied to you, but I was
trying to protect our friendship.
I don't want you feel weird.
That stopped being an option the minute
you old me you had feelings for me.
I wish you'd never done that.
I think I need another mojito.
I'll see you around.
So after my mother left,
I thought my father just
wanted to have a good time, but,
of course, it escalated,
and he started going on
these benders.
One day he disappeared for two
days. I thought he was dead.
You didn't tell anyone?
I had no one to tell.
My mother certainly wasn't an option.
Then he came back in, filthy,
with a broken arm and no recollection
of what had happened.
- Oh, my God.
- The good news was
I think it scared him enough
that he got sober.
And I got my father back,
or least I thought I did, until I saw
these this morning in his room.
That's when I came
over here, to see Jenny.
Jenny's really been here
for me lately.
And wile we're clearing
the air, I want you to know
I didn't spend the night
in your home last night.
Jenny was just trying to protect me.
By letting me believe
that Damien slept here?
I was distracting
you from seeing the pills.
I don't understand
why you brought the drugs.
I know it was completely reckless,
and I'm sorry for putting you...
and Jenny in that position.
I just thought if I got the pills
away from my dad...
that everything would be okay.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to talk?
Or...
No talking.
Well, that was certainly
a crazy story.
Where'd you get that intervention?
It sounded real.
They totally bought it.
Yeah, there's nothing to buy.
It's true...
Oh, Damien, they're upstairs.
They can't hear you.
Except for the part about
my dad getting sober.
I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
No one does.
I'd leave except
I feel like if I disappear,
he'd have absolutely
no reason to ever come home.
I'm really glad you told me.
Well, the pills have been flushed.
It's time for Damien to go, and us, too.
Just be happy you have a father
who actually cares what you do.
Thanks, dad.
I really liked Damien,
and he liked me.
You're young. You'll get over it.
Get your suitcase.
I'm sorry. I need to leave.
Can I just have a moment
of your time, please?
Charles was pretty clear
about his feelings.
It's not for him. It's for me.
Well, S., looks like Chuck's mom
isn't the only one with baggage.
My dad left when
I was a little girl.
I don't know when or
if I'll ever know why.
But I want to know why you left.
I know it must not be easy, but
I don't think you would have come back
if you didn't want
to tell your story.
I was 19 when I got pregnant,
nowhere near ready to be a mother.
We agreed I'd give the
baby up for adoption.
But I saw a picture of you
holding Chuck in the locket.
You couldn't go through with it?
No. It was Bart who
couldn't go through with it.
Once he saw his son, that was it.
He even asked me to marry him.
- You weren't married?
- Oh, no.
And I wasn't about to be.
I didn't love him. I told him that.
So he blackmailed you
then told you that if you left,
you'd never see your son?
I'm the one who told him
to tell Charles I was dead.
It was the only way I knew that
he'd never come looking for me.
And that way
I could go on with my life
as if he never happened.
But you must have had regrets.
And knowing Bart, he wouldn't have
made it easy to come back. Right?
Bart sent me money every
year to keep me away.
But truth is,
he didn't have to.
I didn't doubt my decision.
I know...
This wasn't what
you were hoping to hear,
but now you know why it's better
if I just leave.
My son wants to hate me.
I don't blame him.
You know, I've known
Chuck my whole life,
and he's better than anyone
I know at pushing people away.
I don't care what he says
or does, but there's no child
that doesn't want
to know their parent.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Yeah. Excuse me.
Look, you're right.
I lied to you about Paul and
then kissed you because...
I have feelings for you.
I'm scared, because I don't
want to ruin our friendship.
- And neither do I.
- We're in this no-man's-land.
We aren't hooking up
because we want to stay friends,
we aren't friends
because we want to hook up.
No one'swinning.
It's like we're so cautious
that we're ruining everything.
We're hurting our friendship
by-by not hooking up.
I think we should just throw
down and see what happens.
- If we go up in flames...
- at least we know we burned trying.
I'm scared.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I know that I'm probably
grounded until I go to college,
but please, is there any way
that Damien can have visitation rights?
I understand that you like Damien,
but you can't see him anymore.
- Dad...
- You lied to us to protect this boy.
And whatever's happening
in his home life.
I can't have you spending time
with someone mixed up with drugs.
Lily, please. You get it, right?
Jenny, I'm sorry.
Your father is right.
Okay, you're just taking dad's side
because you guys are in a fight.
This has nothing
to do with Lily and me.
Lily's sleeping till noon every day,
and you're hiding at the loft,
because you finally found
something that you guys can agree on,
- it doesn't mean that you're right.
- Where are you going?
I'll be waiting for you downstairs.
Let's just get this over with.
I wish you and Jenny would stay here,
and we could work through as a family.
Jenny needs a break from this world,
to be back in her old room,
her feet on solid ground.
And I think I need that too,
at least for a while.
I'm sorry for not telling
you about Elizabeth calling.
I wasn't trying to shut you out.
Then what was it?
I was hoping I could
find out who she was
without ever knowing
why she did what she did.
Writing the check was just a test.
But I wanted her to pass, not fail.
As soon as I handed it to her,
I didn't want her to take it.
It's the front desk.
Hello?
Okay, Patricia, hold on.
Elizabeth Fisher is in the lobby.
She wants to come up.
All right, you ready to go? Jenny?
There comes a time
when every father learns
you can't keep a bad girl down.
- Nate, what are you doing here?
- Well, I thought you'd be here.
Where'd you go?
I went to see Chuck's mother.
Why?
Because of my dad.
I've been trying to find him.
I just
want to talk to him,
to understand why he left.
I've come close to finding him.
I tracked him down last summer.
But, he didn't want to see me,
and he wrote me a letter explaining.
He was with my mother.
That's why you've avoid your mom.
And I felt like
somehow his letter meant something.
You know? But the truth is,
he knows who I am now,
and he hasn't come to find me.
I think talking to Elizabeth
made me finally realize
that he just doesn't
want to be found.
Why didn't you tell me?
Things have been
so good with us, so fun.
I didn't want to bring
any heaviness into it,
you know, ruin things.
Yeah, I mean, this time
has been incredible.
We broke my dresser.
And I'm enjoying every minute of it.
I want to be that person
you can bring anything to,
the good and the bad.
Me, too.
Did you ever think that maybe...
if that's the way your father feels,
he's not worth finding?
I know it's probably not
the story you wanted to hear,
I wanted you to know the truth.
And I thought my father was
the heartless one.
You have every right to hate me.
- But I want to be in your life.
- For a price, of course.
I don't want this.
I thought it would be better
if you could hate me,
but it's better if you know me.
I've decided to stay in New York.
I'm willing to wait
as long as it takes.
I want to know my son.
Wait.
It seems like all that money...
should at least buy you a drink.
I was worried that it wasn't gonna be
as good without Olivia.
Yeah, it's almost like she
brought us down, I would say,
- if I had to grade us.
- "A" minus?
All right.
Well, I was gonna say "A" plus.
Well, minus for the first time,
due to the elbow incident,
but after that, plus.
Plus, plus, plus.
The reason,
I was freaked out when you told me
was because with us,
it feels like it's all or nothing.
Yeah, I know. If we hooked up,
then it puts everything in fast-forward.
Like we'd have to be married
before graduation.
All of our friends would be getting
their first STDs,
and we'd be celebrating
our first wedding anniversary.
Let's just take it
one day at a time?
Keep being friends?
Yeah.
As long as we can keep doing this.
You're gonna be in a lot of trouble.
Yeah. You'd better make
my punishment worth it.
So my dad
might have flushed your stash,
but I raided Lily's medicine cabinet.
- She sometimes gets headaches.
- It's a hell of a headache.
We could go to the party
and sell those instead.
Or...
We could skip the party.
And do what?
No, miss Lily. It's me.
Is that Rufus' scarf?
It was turned in, lost and found.
He wasn't wearing it today.
I did not want to say
this, but Dorota insist.
Miss Holland say...
Rufus left this at her apartment.
I'm sure he was just down there
talking about rooftop garden.
Thank you, Vanya.
I'm sure that was it.
Hey. It's me. Serena.
I still don't know
if this is your number,
but I wanted you to know that...
I'm not looking for you anymore.
I thought
maybe you wanted to know me.
But now it's me that
doesn't want to know you.
I'm done.
See you tomorrow.
Enjoy your talk.
Call me in the morning.
Thank you. I will.
Spotted... Chuck Bass
breaking bread with his mother.
Looks like our little boy
lost is finally found...
- What do you want to know?
- Everything.
For now, at least.
X.O.X.O., Gossip Girl.