Gossip Girl
Here-- Your One And Only Source
Into The Scandalous Lives Manhattan's
I Love You, Nate Archibald.
Ways Have, Always Will.
I Love You, Too.
At Is Wrong With You? This Is Not
Who You And Those Girls Are,
But I Know Who,
And I'm Not Gonna Forget That
St 'Causehang Out Wit
To Talk, Remember?
Can't Help Myself. I Never
Should Have Let Yolelet Me Go.
I Will Not Base My Personal Life
On Your Preferences.
Dan Is My Boyfriend.
Would Rather Be
Chuck's Stepsister Than Dan's.
Ly, Would You Do Me
The Honor Of Being My Wife?
He Propod D Before We Left,
And I'm Going To Say Yes.
Take Care, Rufus.
How Glad Are You To See
Our Families Merge, Sis?
So Glad Atat If You Ever
Call Me That Again,
It'll Be The Last Thingu Ever Say, Chuc
Unless You Want Ar Nathaniel To Know How
You Lost Your Virginity To Me In The Back
Of A Moving Vehicle,
I Encourage Patienced Restraint.Isn't
You Can Torture?
Ok, I Know
You're Friendsitith Blair,
But If You Know Something...Well, Blair
Really My Friend.
...So, Yeah, There's Something
You Should Know.
What A Bitch.
Oh, My God. She Is Such A Slut!
Made Aececisionwas In No Condi
To Do With You, Blair.
It's Over.
You Held
A Certain Fascinatio
When You Were Beautiful
And Untouche
I Don't Want You Anymore,
And I Can't Seewhy Anyone Else Would.
What Are You Doing Here?
I Was Just Leaving.
No, Stay.
Consider Yourself Dethroned,
Queen B.
Jenny, If You Walk Away
From Me No I I Will Ruin You.
How Are You Gonna Do That?
My Whole Life Falling
Stay And Fight.
We'll Get Through This
Together.
Promise?
Promise.
And Who Am I?
That's A Secret
I'll Never Tell.
You Know You Love Me.
Gossip Girl Season 1 Episode 14
- The Blair Bitch Project -
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
Cat?
Cat!
Cat.
You Don't Have A Cat, Jenny.
My Name Is Blair.
You Don't Have Anyone.
But I'm Blair.
I'm Blair!
Ms. Blair. Ms. Blair.
. Blair.
Wakey, Wakey,
Upper East Siders.
Spring Break Is Done,
And I'm Starved For The Dish.
Were You Sunning In Capri
Or Sinning In Croatia?
Give Me The Deets.
Oh, What's Happening?
You Have Bad Dream,
D D You're Sleeping
With Your Chocolates.
Oh, Lady Godiva,
My Only Friend.
And Has Anyone Spotted
Our Ex-Queen B.?
Wheredoes
The Dethroned Royalty
Vacation These Days?
Club Bed Is Over.
First Day Back To School.
I Can't, Dorota.
I Don't Elel Very Well.
Serena Come
To Get You Soon.
Call Her And Cancel.
And Cover My Mirrors.
M In Mourning
Fomymy Former Life.
Uck, I'm Serious!
E You Done Yet
This Is My Bathroom!
It's Late,
Anand Not To Mention
Disgusting.
Chuck!
What Are You Doing?
L Right, Ladies.
My Sister Needs To Shower.
Make Room.
I'm Just Msising With You.
Can't Believe You Lit Up My Bathro.
Well, If I Lit Up In Mine,
En The Folks Would Know
It Was Me, Sis.
, Okay.
Let's Get One Thing Straight--
Our Parents Mabebe Insisting
On Blending Our Households,
But I Am Not Your Sister.
I Do Not Share
Any Of Your D.N.A.,
Nododo I Ever Wish To.
Then I Suggest
You Get W W Hand Towels.
Okay.
It's Imperative
That I Bathe.
Can You Just Get Out?
U Know What?
Fine. Just Forget It.
Xt Year, We're Doing
Spring Break In Maldives.
Skiing Is Too Dangerous.You Broke Your A
T The Spa.
, Here, Hazel.
Thanks For Letting Me Borrow It.
At Is This?E Bracelet
You Lent Me In Aspen?
Oh, Yeah. You Know
You Could've Just Kept It,
D I Would've Forgot
I Had It.
Girls,
How Excited Are We?
Rty Tomorrow Nightfor Jenny At Sociali
I Know!
It's Gonna Be
My Best Birthday Ever.
I Heard The Mojitos
Are Amazing.
Itilill You Get Your Moutharound A Mini
Oh, I Don't, Um--
It's A Sandwh.H.
Oh.
Wardrobe, Ladies?
Ferragamo Clutch
D Whatever Dress I Buy Today Go With
????????????
Oh, I've Got Some Dresses
On Hold At Bendel'ere's An A.T.M.,
You Said You Wanted To Hit It.
U Know, To Pay Penelope
Back For Brunch?
Oh, Uh, Yeah. $120, Right?
Ah, I Don't
Feel Like Stopping.
You Can Get The Next One.
What Areouou Doing?
I'm Hiding From My Valet.
Wanted To Put My Socks On
For Me This Morning.
Ur Servantse Very Atten
New Latvian Maid.
No. No, No, No, He Should Not
Meet Brigita. He's 14.
Avoid This Person.
May I Remind You, Serena,
That You Used To Have
A Sense Of Humor?
No.
- Morning, Father.
- Hey.
- Morning, Kids.
- Morning.
D How Islilily Von Bulow Today?
Oh, I Have A Headache.
Had A Very Frustrating
Conversation
Th The Wedding Planner
This Morning.
Ll, May I Say
Aggravation Becomes You?
You May,
But I Won't Believe It.
So... First Day
Back At School, Huh?
Ney, You Didn't, Uh,
Want To Shower?
I Have To Go Meet Blair.
Eric?
You Go Ahead.
'L'll Take The Limo.
As My Best Man,
I Expect You To Keep Things
Smooth Until The Wedding.
Best Man?
Uh, Um,
I'd Be Honored, Sir.
To Family.
I Can't
Straight From The Airport
Take Jenny To School,
And She's Already Gone?
E Slept At Hazel'sst Night.
Oh. Who's, Uh, Who's Hazel?
R New Friend,
The Girl Whose Famil
She Went With To Aspen.
Ah, I Was Actually
Surprised You Let Her Go
D Cancel On Mom Likehahat.Ll, Your
Complete Support Of It.
Nny Was
Very Well Taken Care Of.
Spoke To Her Every Day, Twiceom The, Uh
Prprivate Plane?
It's The Best
Early Birthday Present
We Er R Could Have Given Her.
Oh, So You Paid For It?
Well, I Gave Her
Pocket Money.
Yeah, Jenny's Happier Than
She's Been In A Long Tim
Hey, Whenever You're Done
With That "I'd Do Inings
Differently" Look, Two Things--
E--I Can't Seem
To Nail Jenny Down
On What She Wants To Dofor R R Actual Bi
I'll Get It Out Of Her.
Good. And, Uh, Two--
At The Hell
Are You Still Doing Here?
Mm. Thank You.
At Least You Get To Wake Up
From Your Nightmare.
I'm Living With Mine.
Ank God I Have
Plans With Dan Tonight.
Finally, The Return
Of Some Normalcy!
B., What Are You Doing?
Giving Homeschooling
Some Serious Consideration.
Look, I Know You Think
Erybody's
Still Talking About You,
T Your 3-Week-Old-Scandal
Is Ancient News.
D You Even Hear The Dirtat Happened
Heard It From? Dorota?
Ll,
After Much Concerted Effort,
Ya Finally Made It
Into Brody Jenner's Cell Phone.
, And Kati's Dad
Ved Her Entire Family
Back To Israel. Yeah.
And Cotatance's
Bad-Girl-Turned-Good...
Serena Van Der Woodsen...
Moved In With Chuck Bass.
Yeah. So You're Thinking
Is Whole Thing
Could Have Blown Over By Now?
Come On.
That, Too.
Don't Worry, B
The French Revolution
Had Keke.
Come On. Let's Go.
The American Revolution
Had Tea.
T Looks Like The Overthrow
Of Blair Waldorf,
Well...
O Said You Need
A Silver Spoon
To Dole Out Just Desserts?
Can't Believe Th..Oh, My God,
That Was So Perfect.
At Was So Perfect.So Funny.
Hey, Jenny.
Can I Talk To You
Just For A Second?
Up
With You Guys, Okay?
Hey, So I May Have
Told Birir
U Told Me The Truth
About Heanand Chuck,
And I'm Sure She Didn't
React Well To That.
T You Don't Know
What You're Dealing With Here.
I'm Not Scared Of Blair,Te.
No, M M Not Talking About--
I'm Talkingout Your New Ciriririririr
M Talking
About Your New Circle.
I Mean, They've Been
Friends With Blair Forever,
D Look What
They're Doing To Her.
U U Fall Out Of Line,
At Do You Think's
Gonna Happen To You?
Ll, Then I Won't
Fall Out Of Line.
I'm Not Saying
You're Gonna...
It's Just...
U're Not Like
Those Girls, Jenny.
That's Weird, Nate.
Since They're My Friends,
Okay.
Well,
I Will Give You This--
You've Got Good Aim.
Can't We Eat Somewhere Else?
Ok, I Know
This Is Hard For Youb.B.,
Buyoyou Can't
Let Them Beat You.
You're Blair Waldorf,
Remember?
Ght. Right.
These Are My Steps,
And I'm Not Gogg
To Relinquish Them
Without A Fight,
Though It Would Be Helpful
Maybe There Was
One More Person In Our Crowd.
Only Old People
And Children And--
Ugh, There's Chuck
Th A Blond Mini-Chuck.
He T Trying To Torture Me.
.. I Can't Believe It.
I Know.
Does Little J.
Actually Think
At She's Anything
But Eieir Lackey?
Hey.
Y.Hi.
So Since When
Does Nate Archibald Have
Much To Say
To Jenny Humphrey, Hmm?
Why?
You Guys Don't Like Him?
Penelope's Only Dd
A Historic Crush On Him
Since The 20th Century.
Nce You And Nate
Are So Tight,
Ybe You N N Broker That.
Yeah. Maybe.
They At?
Ey're Taking Her
Out To Dinner
For Her Birthday
Tomorrow Nig----
Table Service
At Socialista.
So Jenny Humphrey Is Officially
Being Inscribed On The A-List.
Wait. Hododo You Know This?
Because They Invited Me,
Butsaid No
Out Of Deference To You.
Just Thought
I Could Have Dinner
With Her And Dan
And The Wholfafamily.
????????
Cause I'm Nice.
You Should Try It Sometime.
Come On. Um, Compliment Me.
Tell Me My Hair Looks Beautiful.
But Your Hair Looks Disgusting.
Did You Even Shower?
B., I Say This Out Of Love,
But Your Being A Bitch
What Got Dairy In Your Hair
In The First Place, Okay?
Nice And Neutral, And Things
Will Swing Back To Normal.
You're The Que B B., So Just
Let Nature Take Its Course.
M Going To Model U.N.,
But We're Dining Tonight, Right?
Tter, 7:00., Um, I Don't Know
If I Can Go Out Again Tonight.
Y? What Are You Doing?
Do We Have A Reservation?
Yeah, Doesn't It Take,
Ke, 2 Weeks Get A Table There?T If
The MaîTRe D' $100.
Oh, And Don't Forget, J.--
You Owe Me.
U Know,
Veve Got A Better Idea.
At Does She Think
She's Doing?
????????????
E's Giving You The Perfect
Opportunity For Niceness.
Come On.
No.
S.
Serena, I Know
That You're Dog G Something
With D T Tonight, But, Blair,
Um, We're All Going To Butter,
D I Was Wondering You Wanted To Joi
Yes! Butter.
Great.
Great!
Ve N Nice.
Ank You.
Who's There For You
When You're Ldld And Alone? *
* The Teenagers,
E E Teenagers *
* We're Playing Our Songs *
Ve You Always
Looked This Good?
You Look So Good To Me.
You Look So Good To Me,
- D You Smell...
- Mmm, So Clean.
Mm, You're Not Gonna Tell Me
The Chuck Shower Story Again,
Are You?
No.
Good.
Dan.
Uck. How Are You?
Excellent. Enjoying
Having Famy Y Around.
Can Yojujust
Get It Over With, Chuck?
Y Whatever Pervy Thing
You're Gonna Say And Just Leave?
The Wedding Caterer
Is Presenting A Tasting
To The Family.
I Was Coming
Call You To Dinner.
Okay, I'll Take Off Then.
No Need.
Already Asked The Staff
To Set A Place For You.
*Ou And I,
Loining Like You Never Cried *
I Have To Y Y I Prefer
The Chestnut Pappardelle.
Yeah, The Foie Gras
Is A Bit Rich.
U Know, I'm--I'm, Uh
Slanting Heavily Towards
The Venison Fellow.
It's Fallow.
Fallow. Fallow, Exactly.
Fallow.
Oh, For Me?
Ank You.
O's It From?
I Don'knknow...
But It Says "Open Immediately."
I Have To Refrigerate It?, It's Not
I Don't Know.
.Oh, Don't Put Your Dtyty Package
On The Table.
I Had A Dimefor Every Time I Heard Th
That's Enough, Chuck.
Porn And Handcuffs?
Really?
Oh, My.
W.
This Is Low, Chuck,
Enen For You.
What?
I Didn't Send This.
Excuse Me.
Uh, Could You...
Oh, Yeah. My Pleasure. Uh,
It's Not--That's Not What I--
I Didn't Mean That.
It's, Uh...
It's Trash.
I'll Throw It Out.
Spotted--Blair Waldorf,
Alone At Butter.
I'm Sorry, Miss,
T It--It Looks Like
Your Friends Aren't Coming.
Humiliated--Party Of One.
Can't You Just
Picture Her Sitting There?
Every Time
Memeone Comes In The Door...
H... It's Not Them.
Ooh, No, Not Them."
Not Going To Butter
Ch Better
Thanoioing To Butter.
New Nanette Lepore
For Jenny's Birthday.
Gorgeous.
Right?
What's
The Birthday Girl Wearing?
Oh, I'm Still Deciding Between
O O Dresses At Bergdorf's.
I Thought
You Said Bendel's.
Bendel's. Right.
Oh, It's My Dad.
Is,Rere Youwearing Your Black
Hello?
Which One?U Know, I Never
Wear The Same Thing Twice.
Mommy Taught Me Well.
Hey, Dad.
You Missed Dinner, Kiddo.
Oh, Yeah, I'm Studying At Hazel's,
And I Guessi Lost Track Of Time.
Um, I'm Not Mad.
I Just Feel Like
I Haven't Seen You In A While.
We Haven't Evediscussed Your
Do Something With My Friends...
Oh. That's Great, Honey.
But Since
I Have Nothing To Wear,
Don't Think
That's Happening Anymore.
Well, If You Want To Be
With Your Friends,
We Can Do The Family Thing
Over The Weekend.
Sweetheart?
Uh, Yeah.
I'll Be Home Soon, Dad.
Okay. Bye.
* You Drive Me Crazy *
Llo? Hi.
Oh, No Check, Honey.
The Drink's On Us,
Unless
You Want Something Else?
Yes.
Another Bellini,
E Seared Squab,
And A Bus Person
Toepeparate The Tables,
Please.
One May Be
The Loneliest Number...
Information.
What City And State, Please?
Ooklyn.
I Think That's In New York.
But Sometiss
Only The Lonely Can Play.
Wake Up, Little Jenny. The Bitch Is
I Thought You Said
You Didn't Have Anything Else.
Well, I Found Sometutuff
In The Back Of My Closet.
-Hmm. Do You Want
To Go With Cash Again,
Or Do You Want To Bu
Your Sewing Machine Back?
Neither.
I Want That Dress.
Hohoney, This Is $1,200.
Ll, This One's...
Quite Lovely.
Ah, Well,
That's More My Color.
I I Say We Take The Jet
To Croatia,
Where Young Eric Here
N Exploit
The Lesser Age Of Consent--
M Invited The Bachelor
Brother, Please.
D Then Head West
To Monte Carlo
For Some All-Night Cards
At Metropole,
En Swing By Giza
St To Watch The Sun Come Up
Over The Pyramids.
At Do You Think, Father?
I Think We're Here.
Uh, See You At Home, Bart.
Chuck Will Catch Up
In A Minute.
You Almost Ruined Things
Between Me And Lily Once Before.
I'm Not Gonna
Let That Happen Again.
At Are You Talking About?M Talking Ab
Stunt You Pulled At Dinner.
Didn't Send Serena
That Package,
And Quite Frankly,
R Violated Virgin Mary Act
Is Getngng Pretty Old.
Thought Making You
My Best Man Would Help.
What Is That
Supposed To Mean?
Inspire You
To Valuey Y Happiness
Ove
Your Own Childish Agenda.
Things Seem To Be Working Out
For You At That Club, Victrola.
I'm Thinking You Might Like Me
To Invest More In The Place,
So You Can Have
Momore Control?
In Exchange For Good Behavior,
Of Course.
You're Bribing Me?
So We Have A Deal Then?
Hey, Why Aren't You School
I'm Taking The Morning Off.
Volunteering To Help Those
Less Fortunate Than Myself.
Wow.
You're In A Good Mood.
Tter With The Girls
Must Have Gone Well Last Night?
I Didn't Go, Actuall
For My Forgiveness.
Hey, Dan's Not Hanging Out
In Brooklyn Again This Morning.
'S Wityoyouat School, Right?, No, No
But He'll Be Here Soon. Why?
Just Tell Him I Say Hi.
Okay.
Hi.
Nny's Dad?
We Met Briefly
At Thanksgiving.
Ah, Ye..
Hi.
Got Reree Cases Of Champagne
For Serena Van Der Woodsen.
. No, No.
I-I'm Serena Van Der Woodsen,
But Those Aren't Mine.
Ll, The Purchase Order
Never Lies. Salud.
Y, Guys, I Just Got
This Incredible Dolce.
- You Wanna See?
- It's Unbelievable.
You Can't Turn Your Back Your Own Hou
Talking About?
Mother'vavalentino
Was Stolen.
Oh, My God.
It Was Made
Especially For Her.
It Was The Same Year
He Did, Uh,
Jackie O.'S
Lace Wedding Mini.
Ll, Did Someone Break In?Noanand The Ma
Swore To The Police
At She Didn't Take It,T She'll Prob
Wait, Police For A Dress?
'S Worth, Li, , $15,000.My Mother Told I
If She Returned It,
Ey Could Work Something Out.
Like She'll Bring It Back.
Well, You Never Know.
I Mean, It Could Turn Up.
Ght, 'Cause Really,
Where Is She Gonna Arar It?
I'm Really Glad,
Because When I Spoke To Her,
E Mentioned The Plans
With The Girls Falling Through.
Ll You The Truth,I Didn't Really Bel
Why?.
Thought
She Was Just Conflicted
Out Oooosing Friends
Over Family.
Ll, You Know
That's The Biggest Struggle
With A Girl Her Age.
Memory Doesn't Serve...
Yiying To Reconcile
Who You're Becoming
With Who You Used To Be.
E's Beenununning
Herself Ragged, Mr. Humphrey.
Ddddling Two Worlds?Ll, I Know She Wa
Running Herself Ragged
Trying To Get Into
One Of Those Wldlds--
Picking Up Dry Cleining,
Gowns For Masked Balls...
Ll, It's No Easier
Once You're In.
She Needs Some Relief.
Ll, Then That's What
Shshe'll Get.
Whatever I Can Do To Help.
Oh, Thank God.
Betty?
Hi. Excuse Me. Um...
Uld You Pardon Me
For A Moment, Plea??
I Need To Trade Back
All Right, You Can Keep
The Scarf And The Shoes,
I'm Sorry, Buthahat'sst Not Gonna Be Po
What? Why?
U Know, When You
Leave Here With An Item,
You're Agreeing
To Its Value.
The Dolce Sold At $1,200.
The Valentino...
Is Seven Times That.
Easelolook,
This Has Sentimental Value,
And I Didn't Realize--
No, I'm Sorry.
A Couple Of Hours Ago,
This Dress Was Mine, All Right?
Doesn't Even
Have Tags On It Yet.
Look, It's Not My Fault
That You Don't Kww
What A Valentino's Worth.
Hello?
Nate, It's Jenny.
At's Going On?Listen, I Wouldn't
Be Calling You
I H A Anyone Else
To Turn To,
But I Made A Mistake,
And I Need To Fix It,
D I Really Need Borrososome Money.I
Jenny, Just Slow Down.
I Promise I'll Pay You Back.
Is Everything Okay?
Ah, I Just-- I Madea Mistake,
And I Nee Well, How Much?
,000.
$8,000? Jenny, What Do You
Need That Kind Of Money For?
You Know What? Forget It.
M Sorry E
The Price Of Fitting In
Might Have Gotten
A Little Steeper...
But Little J. Still Knows
'S What's Underneath
That Counts.
Well, We Coulpuput
This One On A Mylar Tablecloth
And Pretend
It's A Bar Mitzvah.
Oh, There You Are.
I Have A Date With Dan.
Could You Excuse Us?
You're Gonna Say Something Worse
Thanhehe Bar Mitzvah Remark?
Rena, I Think We Should
Talk About Any Feelings
You Might Be Having
About My Upcoming Marriage.
Ay, But You're
Asking Me This Now Because...
Cause I Got A Call
From Your Headmistress
O Said
That There Was Something
About A Case Of Alcohol?
Well, I Thought
You May Be Acting Out.
Ght, Mom. I Actually Woke Up
This Morning, And I Thought,
Mm. I'm A Little Uncertain
About My Mother's Wedding.
"Why Don't I Invite
The Entire Junior Asass
Out To The Courtyardfor A Champagne Toas
Things Like Thisefefore.
Obviously, Chuck's
Master Plan Is Working.
Can't Believe You Think
Chuck Is Doing Thesehihings.
Looking Good To Everyone
In My Life Isn't Enough For Him.
He Has To Make Me Look
Bad Or Cra..
Ll, Chuck May Be Eccenicic,
But I Doubt He's Diabolical.
What's He Done Now?
I'll Tell You
What He's Done.
Surprise!
Wow.
Happy Birthday, Jenny.
Um, Dad, I Ca--I Can't
Believe You Did All This.
And, Uh, Blair's Here.
This Is So Great
That All Of You Are Here
In My House.
, , I Should Go Change.
Uh, You Got It? Okay.
Don'ththink
She Was Surprised.
What's Blair Doing Here?
I Don't Know.
This Party's Kinda Weird.Eird"?
It's Time For Its Induction
To The Birthday Hall Of Lame.
So Not What I Pictured
En The Guy On The Phoneid "Loft Pa
We Gave Up Our Table For This.
Mint Mojitos At Socialista,
Mint Milanos
With Jenny's Dad.
He's Kind Of A Hottie.
Yeah, A Hottie Dad.
How Long
Do We Have To Stay?
Rice Krispie Treats?
You Can't Believehow Mad Bart Was
Yes, I Can,
'Cause You've Told Me
About Three Times.
Wonder What
They're Gonna Do To Him.
Sh Could See His Face.
Hey, You Know What?
I've Got Some Stories, Too,
Uh, About Seeing My Mother
For The First Time
Since She Left At Christmas.
I'm The Worst Girlfriend., You're Not.
No, You're Not.
D There's The Funny Visit
To My Grandma
At The Old Folks' Home--
Two Women, A Sponge Bathd A Bedpan.
You're Right.
I Wanna Be Here
Right Now With You.
And--And Nate.
What?
Hey, Guys.
Y.Y.
Sorry To Interrupt. Your Mom
Told Me You Guys Were Here.
N I Speak With You
For One Second, Dan?
Uh, Yeah. Yeah, Sure.
All Right. Okay.
Y, So Have You Spoken
With Your Sister At L L Today?
, No. Why? What'wrwrong?I Don't Know
She Just Called Me.
E Was Really Freaked Out,
Didn't Know Where To Turn.
She Asked To Borrow $8,000.
What? Why?
Yeah, I Don't Know.
I Tried To Get Her
Tell Me What Was Going On,
But She Wouldn't Say Anything.
Ease? Dad, Just Get Out, Oka
I Need To Change!
Ney, Can't You Tell Mewhat's Goi
Just Leave!
Y Are You Crying?
Are You Upset About The Party?No, I'm No
Talk About This Later, Okay?
Really Just Need
To Get Out Of This Dress.
Uhh, It's Stuck!
Okay, All Right.
Just Help Me, Okay?
Help Me Get It Off.
Nny,U Have To Calm Down.
No, Hurry Up.
D You Get It
I Need A Pair Of Pliers.
Dad...
Sorry. Sorry. We Were
Just Looking For Our Wraps.
I'll Get Them.
Oh, My God.
That's My Mother's Dress.
, You Guys, I Got Th
At--At Resurrection.
Remember,
I Was Telling You
Out The Really Great Dressbought?R Mo
One-Of-A-Kind Valentino
At Jt T Happened Disappear From Her
And Forgotten Or Something.
Are You Calling
Myauaughter A Thief?
Well--
Excuse Me.
This Feelsririvate,
So I'm Gonna Head Out Now.
I Have A Table At Butter.
Servation's Under Waldorf,
In Case There's An After Party.
Otted--
Jenny In A Red Dress
With The Red Hands To Match.
Is The Name On The Label.
Blair Said They Told You
The Original Party
Had Faenen Through
That They Could Surprise You
With A Better One.
Blair's A Liar.
You Got Played.
She Also Said
That You Were Afraid
E Girls Wouldn't Accept
Everything Aboutouou.
Like You Had Nothing
To Be Ashamed Of.
Was That A Lie, Too?
Where Did U U Get
E Dress?
And I Know
You Didn't Make It,
Cause Your Sewing Machine
Is Gone.
U Have No Idea
How Hard It Is, Dad.
I Sold
My Sewing Machine, Okay?
What?Ah, And A Lamp
And Some Jewelry.
Why?
Because I Had To.
D, You Think That You Can
Just Send Me Off To School
Th A Plaid Skirt
And A Metrocard,
And Everything Will Be Okay.
I Am Not Apologizing
For Not Having A Private Plane
For You, Jenny.
U Think I'm Ashamed
Of Where I Come From?
No, Dad,
What I A Ashamed Of
Having To Bring
A Brown-Bag Ncnch To School,
D, You Know,
Eat It In The Bathroom,
And Then Go Out
With My Friends
And Pretend
That I'm Not Hungry
When I Go To Lunch
With Them.
U Don't Have
To Do Those Things, Jenny.
You're Making A Choice.
Why D Don't You Get?
Do You Want Me To Choose
To Have No Friends?
Ll, Clearly,
I Mean, That's Not Even
A Choice Anymore,
Because That's Just Done.
I Should Probably Get Back.
Well, Thank You
For Staying With Me
Ile I Hid Outfrom My House Of Horrors.
Oh, No Problem.
, Do You Think Jennyll Be All Right?
Yeah, Dan's A Good Guy.
He'll Take Care Of Her.
U Are, Too,
You Know, A Good Guy--
A Forgiving Guy
Who Can't Pit Himself
Against Blair Forever.
Good Night. M Sorry
You Gave Me An Opening.
Couldn't Resist.
I'm Just Saying.
How Are You Doing, Man?
Night.
Hey.
Where Have You Been?
Therapy.
For Four Hours?
, Well, Before I Was--I Was
Playing Wii Tennis With Chuck
At This Guy
Named Brantfthth's House?
Y Are You Hanging
Out With Him?
Brantforth?
Chuck Is Fun, Okay?
He's Cool To Me, And He Doesn't
Treat Me Like Some Freak
At Just Out
The Ostroff Center.
Who Treats You Like That?
, Guys At St. Jude's,
The Girls At Constance,
A At The Korean Deli
On 75th Street.
Eric...
And He's Not--He's Not
Always Caref A Around Me,
Like--Like One Bad Thing,
And I'll Break Or Something.
Besides,
I Always Wanted A Brother.
I'm Trying It Out,
You Know? Here.
At's This?
Uck Said It Came For Y
This Morning.
Thought You Might Want
To Open It Out Of The House,
Just In Case.Y Didn't He Bring It
To Me Himself?
Cause He Thought You Wanted
Him To Stay Away From You.
Is That Coke?
How Do You Like A Brother
Who Usesouou As A Drug Mule?
Serena, I.
Hey. Who Turned 12?
Oh, Please Don't Rub It In.
Dad, What Happened?
Hey.
You Okay?
You Wanna Tell Me Why
You Needed To Borrow $8,000?
Not Really.
H, I Can't Believe
Nate Told You.
Well,
He Was Worried About You,
At You Might Be Turning Into
Some Hideous Upper Et T Cyborg.
He Said That?
No. No, I Did.
Just Got In
Way Over My Head.
U Know, I Thought
I Could Trade The Dress
D Wear It That Night
And Return It,
But Just...
Look, Uh...
It's Your Birthday,
I Think
We Should Get Some Ice Cream,
And  C Can Talk About
All This Stuff Later, Okay?
Okay.
I'll Just Let Dad Know
What We're Gonna Do.
Jen,Ouou--You Have
So Much More To Offer
Than The Things
That Those Girls Have, Really.
U've Got So Much More
To Bring To The Table.
You Just Need To Find
A Way To Believe That.
What The Hell
Is Your Problem?
Specify The Context.
You Disgust Me, Chuck.
How Dare You Involve Eric
In Something Like This?
No Wonder You're Friendless
And Girlfriendless.
En Your Own Fatherpects The Worst From
Well, You Saw To That.
Listen, If We're Gonna
Exist Under The Same Roof,
I Am Laying Downme House
No Need, Princes
Bart Already Kicked Me Out.
What?
I'm Moving Back
To My Suite.
Bart Thought
It Would Be Best
There's A Line Outside.
U Ready To Give Up
You're Table Yet?
No. My Party's Coming.
They're Coming!
These Seats Taken?
Any Good General Knows
U Never Let Your Soldiers
See You Sweat.
Look's Like Thisatattle's
Ending At Butter,
And The Win Belongs To B.
Victory Is Sweet.
??
I-I Know, Dad, But Is,S,
You Know, It's Her Birthday,D I Kind Of Promised
.Ll, Since You Don
The Decisions Around Here,
E'll Just Ha T To Take Thatth A Gr
So What Are You Gonna Do?
Are You Just Gonna
Keep Her Locked Up?
I Don't Know.
St Week, Aspen.
This Week, Prison?
Yeah, Well, Spring Break
Is Over For Everyone,
Including Mylflf.
Really Took My Eyes
Off The Ball.
, So--So Wtt
Do You Want To Do?
Why Don't We Just
Celebrate 15
Th Some Jenny Cake
In The Kitchen?
Ay. All Right.
I'll Go Tell Her.
So, Jen, W--
She's Gone.
What?
She's Not In There.
She's Gone.
Y.
I'm Sorry For Calling You
Like That Earlier.
I'm So Embarrassed.
Anan, It Was Stupid
And-- And Inappropriate--
No, No, No, No. Listen,
I'm Just Glad You're Okay.
Yeah.
Um, Okay, Well,
I Do Have A Favor To Ask You.
I Mean, It's Not Money,
But I Just Really Don't Want
To Be Alone On My Birthday.
Oh, For Me? Thank You.
Oh, My God.
What's Wrong?
Nothing.
I'll Be Back.
Kylie Minogue's
"Rippin' Up The Disco"
Excuse Me.
Cuse Me!
I'm Going To The Bar.
What?
Bar!
We'll Be Rightacack.
Metallically Reflecting
Your... *
Where
Are All The Hot Guys?
I-I Don't Know.
, They Don't Exactly Servetea And Cupcak
2020 Minutes.
Is This Really Happening?
Penepepe,
You Know Nate, Right?
Of Course. Hi.
Hi. Uh, How Are You?
He Kills' "Sour Cherry"
Hazel,
I Think Maybe Your Mom
D Give Away
That Valentino.
Yeah, She Is Always
Cleaning Out Her Closet,
And That Ativancan Really Play With Her Me
*Hout When You Wanna
Get Off The Ride *
*Houthehen
You Wanna Get Off The Ride *
*Hout When You Wanna
Get Off The Ride *
*Ake My Heart
Beat Double-Time *
On Your Fruit Stand,
The Onlright? *Herry *
*M I The Only Sour Cherry
On The Fruit Stand? *
Hey.
I'm Really Sorry, Chuck.
Know It Wasn't You
Who Sent Me That Stuff.
Never Thought I'd Say This,
T It Turns Out
Chuck Bass Is Innocent.
Who D Nd S.
All Those Naughty Gifts?
Why Don't I
Make You A Drink?
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-