Gossip girl here
- Your one and only source
Into the scandalous lives
of Manhattan's elite.
How's your mom doing? My
dad left her for another man.
Something about uh-Uh, mom and a
neighbor? Yeah. It's complicated.
Mom's having an affair.
It's easy for me to say it.
It happened one time,and it's over.
Then why did our daughter have to
go to Hudson and drag you back here?
I'm sorry i kissed you,
but i did it because
I thought he should know
how it feels to lose you.
So when can we go public?
My kids have to know first.
My friend Vanessa-She moved
away to vermont last year,
And now she's back.
You guys just have
everything in common,
And, um, i'm just getting to know him.
This thing between us
- It's over fogood.
Nate is a gentleman. He
would never cause a scene.
Where to, mr. Bass? The airport.
And who am i?
That's a secret i'll never tell.
You know you love me.
X.O.X.O.³מוישו®<font
color="#4096d1"> µתע»¼¾µת11¼¯
- =זאדנצה»י=-
·­עכ&נ£¶פ:נ° ך±¼הצב:ךר»¤ללך¹ ¾זהע·¹
* santa, baby, a '54 convertible, too *
* light blue * * light blue *
Hey, upper east siders.
It's christmas in new york,
And along with the season
Comes the constance
billard/ st. Jude's bazaar,
Where the only thing bizarre
are the donated items for sale.
How about an antique butter churn?
Oh, my gosh. That would
go so well with my loom.
I know what i'm getting you
for christmas now. All right.
Oh, for when i move to siberia? No.
Come on. New york hardly
even gets cold anymore,
And it never snows.
Who wants chestnuts roasted on an
open fire when it feels like florida?
Okay, global warming grinch.
I'm just saying, christmas
should be white and snowy.
I'd even settle for
Manhattan slush. Mm.
There you are.
Hey, Vanessa. What are
you doing here? Hey.
Merry christmas.
This is a copy of "the new yorker. "
Thank you, but you know i
already have a subscription.
There's something else
What does it say, serena?
"Dear mr. Humphrey, we
are pleased to advise you
"That we would like to
publish your short story
In our summer fiction issue
featuring '20 under 20.'"
It's a contest for young unknown
writers, and i might have...
Oh, my god! Submitted you.
I'm gonna be published in
"the new yorker. " That-Oh.
This ca-This can't be real.
Is-Is this-Is this real?
This is so great.
I haven't even read
one of your stories.
Oh, don't worry.?
I swiped this one out of his drawer
on the pretense of borrowing a stapler.
Slick. You never did return
that stapler, by the way.
Mnh-Mnh.
Let's see. You story
is called "10-8-05."
What's that date?
Vanessa, thank you. I
don't know how you did this,
But this is the best present ever.
* so hurry down the chimney tonight *
* hurry tonight *
* santa, baby *
I can't believe we
just took a cab for $32.
Well, i can't believe you were gonna
wait an hour for another subway.
They said another train was on its way.
Uh, excuse me. Pardon me. Oh.
Oh. Rufus, alison, hello.
Hi.
Oh, rufus.
Uh, you remember my
friend bartholomew bass?
Hi. From, uh, eleanor's? Yeah. Hello.
Eleanor's? Oh, this is my wife alison.
Hi. How do you do?
Well, it's lovely to see you both.
Excuse us, please.
I guess lily's targeted
her next billionaire.
Actually, i think she's had
him in her sights for a while.
Well, that was awkward.
It wouldn't be if you let people
know what we were doing together.
I'm just starting?
And the only reason you
didn't trust me last time
Was because of a misunderstanding.
Yes, and to avoid another one,
That if it doesn't work
out between us again,
I'm gonna feel twice as humiliated.
Not telling people about us
ensures that we don't work out.
Look, when i committed
myself to you, i meant it.
You know i am in love with you.
What are you waiting for?
Blair.
Oh, happy holidays.
Happy holidays-Mwah-
Ms. Van der woodsen.
Mr. Bass, i didn't think
that you were still in town.
I figured that you were
with... with charles? No. Sadly,
I am stuck here on business while he
suns himself at my hotel in monaco.
I have my staff keeping an eye on him,
And i'll join him for new year's.
Oh, right. I
- I, uh, was wondering
Why he'd been so quiet, and
monaco answers my question.
Yeah.
Lovely to see you two. Bye. You, too.
Blair, there you are.
I- I can't talk right now,
serena. I'm late, and i have-
A huge sweet tooth?
They're for my dad and
me. We get them every year,
And he landed om parar 27 minutes ago.
Oh, then vite, vite!?
Come on. I said vite!
Hey!
Nice holiday spirit, scrooge!
Oh, gosh. So it's gonna be
a real waldorf christmas?
Well, a real waldorf christmas eve.
Eleanor drew the line at christmas day.
That's only for me, her and dorota.
Well, you still have?
No, it'll be more than
just a couple days.
I'm gonna convince him
to stay in new york.
What about paris and roman?
Roman is a phase. My
father belongs here with me.
He only left new york to
ride out the scandal. Oh!
Time to come home, don't you think?
Hey, did you want to ask me something?
Yes, a gift idea for dan?
The most thoughtful
dan-Like present ever.
Why don't you just buy
him? And call it a day?
Thank you for being
totally not helpful at all.
See you tomorrow night.
Bye.
Hi! Blair-Bear!
Oh! Oh, look at you.
Mm. More beautiful than ever.
Uh, sweetheart, you remember roman?
Blair.
Ah. Mm.
You are still perfection.
Delicate, yet full with flavor,
Like a macaron.
Imagine my surprise when
the elevator door opened
And out popped both of 'em.
Well, i didn't think you'd mind.
It's the perfect opportunity for you
two to get to know each another better.
Absolutely. It's for you.
Oh, sweetheart, you remembered.
It, uh, our tradition.
That's for you.
Merci, blair.
My pleasure.
My son, the writer.
(Alison) published writer.
Yeah, you got your dream girl and
your story in "the new yorker. "
(Jenny) maybe you should just die now.
That's true. I may have peaked.
This one is from the smiths.
"Season's greetings. "
That's very original.
Their name's smith. They
don't have to be original.
This one is from, uh, alex.
What?
"Alison, meet-Meet me on
the 24th for-" No, dan.
And that's not a christmas card.
(Lowered voice) why
is he writing to you?
Sending cards to the
house? Asking to see you?
I don't kn. W
Guys, we're-We're still
here. We can hear you.
Rufus, it's over with alex, okay?
I- I-I'm home now
with my family.
Good.
Let's all rewind and just pretend
this never happened. (Clears throat)
This is not gonna
ruin our Christmas.
I can't believe you're okay with
this. Who said i am okay with this?
What am i supposed to do, make a scene?
Behave like some
pathetic, scorned wife? No.
(Speaks french) roman does
not even know how to ice-Skate.
Can't you escort him out of the park
On your way to the meeting?
Maybe drop him at a nail salon?
I cannot bother myself trying
to wrestle roman away from you.
I have to mentally prepare.
I am meeting with the C.E.O.
Of victoria's secret, after all.
Victoria's secret?
Yes, i'm- I'm
designing a line
Of retro-Chic sleepwear
and lingerie and i-
I'm looking forward to the samples.
We're all very proud.
In fact, mom, why don't
you tell roman all about it?
Oh, yes.
I'm sure he'd be fascinated.
It's so good to have you here.
Well, it's good to be here.
Now where's the handsome Nate?
Am i gonna see him tonight?
Well, he's in connecticut with his mum.
He said he would try to catch a train
And make it to the party
tonight. Yeah, well,
Another New York
institution that i miss.
You know, you don't
have to miss any of it.
I wish that i could be
in two places at once,
My dear, but impossible. Sorry.
You know that chateau near
lyon that i told you about?
Mm-Hmm. Roman and i bought it.
You bought that place? Yes.
And with roman?
The house is flooded with light.
The fireplaces are big enough.
I mean, you can walk into them.
The gardens are incroyable.
Uh, pardon me. I'm
taking my niece skating,
And i can't seem to locate the rink.
But it's- It's
right over there.
Of course. The throng
of children in mittens
Should have tipped me off. Thank you.
You're welcome.
The handsome man was
just flirting with you.
That's absurd. He was
not flirting with me.
Roman, it is going to be so dull for you
To sit and watch them skate.
Yes. Why don't you go to the petting zoo
And feed the sheep?
Or why don't i join you
on the rink? It looks fun.
Wonderful.
Yes. Super.
I'll get you skates. See you there.
Super.
You're not autographing those
and selling them on ebay,are you?
No. No, no.
I'm just checking out some
of the previous publishees,
And i'm-I'm in great company
here. It'sthe new yorker. "
V., how can i top this?
I can't, really,
Unless i rig the oscars for
one of your documentaries.
You got in on your own merit.
The only gift i gave you was
to lick a stamp, and as for me,
The annual Dan Humphrey
christmas cd mix
Is more than enough. All right, yeah.
Hey.
What's in the bag? Perfection.
Look, i know it's not christmas
yet, but open it, please.
I can't wait. I'm too excited.
Oh, my.
I noticed the other day
that you don't wear a watch,
And then it occurred to me it's
because you don't have a watch,
And you're gonna need one to
be punctual for all the meetings
With editors and publishers
now that you're a fancy
And apparently, self-Important writer.
You don't like it. You
want the brown band.
No, no, no. I love the band.
I love the whole thing.
It's-It's the most amazing
watch i've ever seen,
But i can't accept this.
What? Oh, yes, you can.
Look, it's more of a gift for me
Because i had so much fun
picking it out for you.
You have to.
Serena, i buy a book for
my dad every christmas.
I think the most elaborate
gift i've ever given
Has been a pair of rubber
boots from I.L. Bean.
So then i overdid it?
I think even your underdoing it
Would be overdoing it.
Look, um, let's-Let's-
Let's set some rules,
Maybe some helpful guidelines.
Fine.
Deadline?
Um, tomorrow morning.
Price limit?
50 bucks.
All right. May the best gift win.
(Lowered voice) hey, um... hey.
If it's any help, i can tell you
dan's favorite used book shop.
That's okay. I think i got it.
Are you alex? Who are you?
Rufus humphrey.
Unless you want to be
carried out of here,
You're gonna stay the
hell away from my wife.
Calm down now.
You sent a letter to my wife
At my house where my children live?
Whatever you had with her is over.
Why don't you sit down? She
told you to leave her alone.
I'm sorry.
That's not what she told
me a couple days ago.
Excuse me. You...
You spoke to her?
(Mcguire sisters) * "c"
is for the candy trim *
* around the christmas tree *
* "h" is for the happiness *
Damn it. You can do it. You can do it.
Look at all these children.
They're skating around
fearlessly. Come on.
They got a lot shorter way to fall.
Blair, will you help us here?
Just a second. My laces came undone.
Only 1 question:how did
you fake ur virginity for n?
(Harold) now here we go.
Ready? Now go to blair. Okay.
You can do it! Blair!
Come give us a lesson.
Spotted spinning
at wollman rink-
The blair capades. All the
grace of nancy kerrigan,
But packing the punch of tonya harding.
(Harold) pauvre roman.
a va?
Are you all right?
I'm so clumsy. My foot got
caught behind the skate. Oh.
(Harold) oh. Here. Let me help you.
(Elevator bell dings) i cannot believe
that daddy decided to stay with roman
Instead of having tea
at the carlyle with me.
The E.R. Doctor said he
would make a full recovery.
Everything is ruined.
Why wod you say that? You
and i had a marvelous time.
Well, i'm sorry, mother.
It's just not the same.
I don't understand how that
french fox stole my father
And your husband and always seems
to come off like a-an innocent lamb.
Roman was not always
so innocent, you know.
Really? What's his story?
Mm, well, when i first met him,
He was going out with
this model named freddy,
And freddy was a horrible scoundrel.
Roman would actually?
Into him? He was-He was
absolutely infatuated with him.
Freddy had him under
some kind of spell.
I was the one who got
him to break out of it
And turn his life around. Don't
mention freddy to your father.
It is a sore subject.
Okay. What was freddy's last name?
Hey. Where were you?
I tried to call you,
but your phone was off.
I kept your date for you with alex.
He's actually a pretty cool guy
Other than the fact that
he's in love with my wife.
He told me about your phone call.
He... felt that i owed
him an explanation,
And he was right.
And you didn't tell me that because...
Because there was nothing to tell.
I told alex that i
was back with my family
And to stop calling.
Would you have come back...
If jenny hadn't shown up to bring you?
If i hadn't, would
lily be here right now?
I guess by turning our
backs on these other people,
We thought we could fix ourselves.
Maybe other people aren't the problem.
Maybe we changed.
And at what point do we admit
That no matter how much we
want it or how hard we try...
It'sujt t not rking.
I know it's been maybe ten
minutes since i last asked,
But are you still sure you
don't want to talk about it?
Dad said he didn't want?
That's what i'm trying to do.
Hey, well, just in case?
You're here. I know.
Okay. How about this?
At least you know it's
something serena doesn't have.
A year of cheese for $600?
Are these people kidding?
I could buy a cow for that much
money and make my own cheese.
You just said "make my own cheese. "
That's disgusting.
I'm never gonna find this
gift for serena.
Yeah, and your gift needs to be?
To make up for the
rest of her christmas.
What do you mean?
Well,she's living in a hotel.
You know, how homey can it be?
It's not exactly festive.
Eric told me they
don't even allow trees.
(Chuck) leave a message,
and i might listen. (Beep)
(Scoffs) chuck, you are
not answering my calls,
To torture me, i am sure, but
please, for the love of god,
Do not tell anybody about us, okay?
Please? Please.
Hey. You told me to come right away.
Is everything all right? Yeah.
Why aren't you with your dad?
Uh, i need your log-In?
From your modeling days.
My modeling days?
I did one print ad
for gap when i was 12.
What,are you holding an
open call or something?
I have one specific look in mind.
Uh,okay,well i don't know
If it'll still even be in here,but...
Well,look at that.
Addresses and phone numbers. Perfect.
You know,i called you an
hour ago. B.T.W.,you're late.
Um,you're lucky i'm even here at all.
It's christmas eve,and i still
haven't found a gift for dan.
Now all the stores are closing,
and i'm totally screwed.
Do you have any idea what you can buy
For under $50 these
days? I don't know.
A single entrיe at a
mid-Priced restaurant?
Three-Quarters of a dvd box set?
Maybe a pair of wolford stockings.
Oh,stockings. Yes,great idea for dan.
Blair,please, this is serious.
I don't know. Why don't you
buy him a gold money clip
From cartier,say it's $49.99?
He won't know the difference.
What are you doing anyway?
I'm booking me a model.
Hey.
I come to you hat in
hand, tail between my legs
And off my high horse. (Chuckles)
I spent the entire day searching
for the perfect gift for dan.
Now all the stores are closing,
christmas day is looming,
And,um... i need your help.
I could take this opportunity to gloat,
But i actually like you.
So let's get down to business.
What do you have so far?
Um,i found a first
edition J. L. Hall book,
Original italian poster
of the "400 blows"
And a montblanc fountain pen
All very thoughtful.
And all exceed $50.
Right.
Well,dan's not really that into things.
Which makes shopping
for him kind of hopeless.
The only thing he wants
for christmas is snow.
It's not like i can give him that.
You sure?
(Eleanor) happy holidays.
Welcome. Welcome.
(Lily) oh! Hi. Hi. Hi. I
don't know if you've noticed.
We're doing things a little
untraditionally this year.
I don't know if you've heard.
I'm desiining a ne of
lingerie for victoria's secret.
I walked into the store,and
i fell in love with this tree.
Isn't that lipstick clever? Isn't it?
Good. Have some eggnog.
Hello? (Rufus) hey. It's me.
Hey. So,uh,running into each
other at the school fair-
Kind of awkward.
I suppose so,especially
after our last phone call.
Rufus,we really shouldn't be speaking.
No,i know.
But if there's something
you want to say,
You should go ahead and say it
Is there something you want me to say?
Rufus...
Why are you calling?
Oh,i...
Just wanted to say merry christmas.
Hope you have a good holiday.
Yes,well...
I'm,um,flying to anguilla
with bart tonight,
So i'm expecting it to
be a-A great holiday-
One for the ages,in fact.
Good night,rufus. Good-Bye.
(Whispers) anguilla.
What is the matter with me?
(Laughs) i don't think so. Oh.
Oh. Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
Well,i was hoping to see you again.
I thought it great good fortune
that roman tracked me down
At the skating rink and
extended an invitation.
Oh,well...
En-Enjoy
the party.
Hmm.
How dare you invite a
strange man into my home.
Jack came?
Go talk to him.
Bring vodka. Roman...
(Whispers) you practically
picked him up off the street.
And then i googled him.
His name is jack roth.
He owns a prominent hedge fund
With offices in london and barcelona,
And he finds you very attractive.
Well,that's no excuse,
And-And-And i
am doing just fine
Without your romantic help.
Are you?
Eleanor,we've been
friends for a long time...
Since before marc
jacobs went into rehab.
Friends don't steal
other friends' husbands.
Is nate there?
Oh. A few hours ago?
Chuck bass didn't call for him, did he?
Uh,never mind. Did nate
say where he was going?
No,no. Don't-Don
disturbrb mrs. Archibald.
Um,i'm sure he's on his way here now.
All right. Thank you.
Dorota's gonna kill you if
you get glue on that comforter.
Sorry we've turned your
room into an art studio,b.,
But the clock is
ticking. (Computer beeps)
I'm done.
(Laughs) oh,my gosh.
Wow. That-That's
amazing.
Thank you so much,vanessa.
This is gonna be... incredible.
Good. I'm glad i could help.
I think he'll really love it.
Vanessa?
I think i'd like to help
with this little project.
Would you come and help me
find another pair of scissors?
It's so nice what you're
doing for your friend dan,
Helping his girlfriend
make his christmas present.
Serena is so grateful
Because she likes to
see the best in people.
I like to see the truth.
Yeah? And what's that?
I think you like dan a little too much.
Just thought i should let you know
Someone's watching.
Merry christmas.
I'm taking off. Call
me when you're done?
Okay. Where you going?
I'm gonna go check
on my daddy. I thought
You were gonna help?
I think my work's done here.
Oh,hello.
Hi. Good-Bye. When you two
are done hiding up here,
I'm taking you both out for
dessert. Can't,mom. I'm busy.
But this is important for our family.
It'll just be the three
of us. Mom,anytime you say
It means you're dating
someone new. Whoever it is,
I don't care. I'll just meet
him at the wedding. Fine,fine.
Then i will just tell you who it is,
Because you're gonna be
seeing him around from now on.
It's Bart Bass.
(Eric and serena) Bart Bass?
Mom,you cannot date bart bass.
You just said a moment ago you didn't
care who it was. That was before
He only has one facial
expression. He scares me.
And he raised chuck.
That scares me.
Oh,serena,as usual, you're
being overly dramatic.
I'm not marrying Bart.
This is very casual,
And regardless,i'm not
asking your permission.
You know when i suggested this plan,
I didn't know that it would
entail a robbery. Hey,hey,hey.
I left a donation,
So it was more of a
rescue than a robbery.
You know,those abandoned
trees in that lot
Were just gonna be kindling
the day after christmas,
And this tree that we have here
is gonna be loved and admired.
Oh,yeah,you have a real talent
for spin,my brother. Okay.
I wish i had more talent
for heavy lifting. Oh.
Oh. Yeah,well,what you're doing
for serena is really romantic.
I wonder what mom and dad
Are getting each
other for christmas.
I thought that if i got
them under the same roof
That things would go
back to the way they were.
They haven't,have they?
I think there's a real possibility
That they might split up.
If i hadn't brought her back, though,
We could've just kept pretending
That she's just in Hudson
doing her art.
You did the right thing, jen.
Really,you did, 'cause
whatever happens now,
At least,uh,we're not
living in a fantasy,you know?
Wonderful party,eleanor.
So you... ice-Skate?
Occasionally, with my niece,
But she's much more talented than i am.
(Clears throat) well, i
haven't skated since ages,
But i used to love it when i was a girl.
You must have been very beautiful out
there on the ice. (Elevator bell dings)
Oh,thank you.
Excuse me.
Merry christmas. Merry christmas.
(Chuckles) excuse me.
Freddy,what on earth are you
doing here? Oh,roman invited me.
(Eleanor) what?
Freddy,what... what are you doing here?
He said that you invited him. What?
Freddy.
Roman,explain this.
I can't.
And so true. How does one
explain the indescribable pull
To see an old lover,to feel
that jolt of electricity?
So you couldn't last two days
in town without contacting him?
I can't believe you'd trust
appearances and not me.
Harold,dear,i- Roman
did not invite freddy.
I think blair did.
Blair?
Freddy...
If you want to be the featured
model in my spring catalog,
You'd better tell us the truth.
She might have offered
to buy me a cruise...
Oh.
And renew my gym membership.
(Chuckles) well,you might
as well take that cruise,
Because you'll be
featured in my catalog
When hell freezes over.
Now please,get out.
Thanks for the champagne.
Merry christmas.
Looks like daddy's little girl
Isn't sugar and spice and
everything nice after all.
I wish you would just
slow down for a second
And let her be. Well,i
just can't believe
That blair would do something so cruel,
And roman,who's only ever
been completely kind to her.
It isn't roman blair's
lashing out at-It's you.
She was so looking forward to
spending time with you alone,
And then you show up at our
doorstep with your lover,
Without a word of warning. How
did you expect her to react?
Well,i hoped that once
we were together,
It would all work out.
I suppose that was pretty naive.
Blair learned scheming from her mother
And unrealistic
dreaming from her father.
She tries really hard
to act all grown-Up,
But don't you be fooled.
She's still a little
girl who needs her daddy.
(Grunts) okay,stop,stop,stop. Ow.
Okay. What now?
Now you go in there,
You distract dexter, the
humorless concierge... okay.
While i try and sneak this into an
elevator. All right,um,who's gonna
So you can carry this thing by
yourself? (Groans) i did-I did not say
this plan is fool-proofed,
(Jenny) yeah.
Hey,Ms. Van der
woods- Lily,hi.
Dan. Jenny. Tree. Hi.
Yeah,um,they don't allow
christmas trees inside,
Which is why we're out here.
Which is why dan's about
to ask you for a favor.
Ah,does it involve distracting dexter
And sneaking into the elevator
Why? Would that work?
No. Never. He has the eyes of a hawk,
And he takes his job very seriously.
So i've noticed.
But bobby at the
service entrance-
I think he could be bought.
Come.
I just sent him a text, and
dan's on his way. (Squeals)
Thank you so much.
It's really no problem,
And since there are no
problems,i should go.
Oh,no,no,no. Stay,please.
You don't need me. We talked
about how to turn everything on.
No,i know i can do it,but i
just want you to see dan's face.
I've really gotta get going.
Okay. Well,i'll tell
him how much you did.
Please don't. It's your present.
Just... enjoy your night.
(Nate) hey,this is nate.
I can't come to the phone (Beep)
Can i come in?
Our flight leaves in a few hours.
I wanted to say good-Bye.
Please forgive me,blair.
I should have told you
that i was bringing roman.
I knew that having him
here would be hard for you,
But i love you so
much, and i love roman,
And i was hoping that if
we were all thrown together,
That something... perfect would happen
And that you would love him,too.
I was gonna convince you
to move back to new york,
But you bought a vineyard
In france with roman.
What's next, a commitment ceremony?
(Scoffs) great.
There's no room in your
life for me anymore.
Sweetheart, there is
always room for you.
No matter where i am,
no matter who i'm with.
I,uh...
This is part of your christmas gift.
(Blair) yourouse in france.
It's very nice,daddy.
I'm sure you and roman
will totally enjoy it.
And so will you,
Because this... (gasps)
Is your room.
* i hardly believed it at all *
It's beautiful.
We're having it decorated just for you.
(Chuckles) a cat.
A cat named "cat," like
in your favorite movie.
It was roman's idea.
* plants and animals *
So... merry christmas, sweetheart.
We're hoping that you'll
spend the whole summer with us.
* was coming on *
* only for *
* you *
Merry christmas.
Do you like it? Do
you think it's cheesy?
No.
No,no, it's-It's
incredible.
How did you do this?
Well, i had help from my elves.
* that i know *
* and running a blender
in a lightning storm *
* disguised as a blessing, i'm sure *
Your present is waiting
for you at home,
But,um,i did bring a
little pre-Present for you.
* up here *
* there comes a fork in the road *
* the pants have gotta go *
Wait. This is your story.
Yeah,it's the original.
It's right out of the spiral notebook.
I'm kinda scared to read it.
What happened on october 8th,2005?
Well, i was accidentally invited
To a birthday party where i met a girl.
She only spoke two sentences to me,
But i've never forgotten her.
Wait. Your story's about me?
* gna wash my bones *
* in the atlantic shore *
* only for *
* you and me *
Are we really gonna do this?
Yeah.
The arts and crafts were impressive,
But how did you manage the real snow?
I'm well-Connected. (Laughs)
This is,without question,
the best christmas ever.
Ever in the history of christmas.
I hate to break the spell,
But,uh,we better get home
before our families wake up.
(Whispers) eleanor... hmm?
You are a marvel.
Oh,stop it. Mmm.
(Whispering) who knew
there were men like you
Wandering around central
park,lost? (Laughs)
(Normal voice) oh.
Eleanor,good morning,
And,jack,nice to see you. Good morning.
Yes,wonderful.
The flights were all canceled
because of the weather.
I wanted to tell blair in person.
Do not worry.
We-We have a room at the pierre.
No,it's nonsense.
You-You'll stay with us.
Thank you.
You'll call me later?
Oh,yes.
I'll be spending christmas
with my... family.
Bye.
What's going on?
We're back for christmas.
Well,roman, you are in for a treat,
Because a waldorf
christmas is like no other.
Come on,you.
Oh.
Whew. Merry christmas,dad.
You're up early.
And you're getting in awfully late.
Oh,yeah,well,
I left you a message.
Saying the tree shenanigans
were taking all night,
But i didn't think you
meant literally all night.
Oh. Yeah... yeah,the tree.
It was a big production.
Uh,luckily serena's mom was
there to help with the plan.
Lily was there?
I thought you mentioned she was out
of the country. No. No,they're here.
They're gonna go see
"the nutcracker" tomorrow.
Do i smell Chocolate chip waffles?
(Rufus) with hot caramel
sauce. Your father's
Christmas specialty.
Good morning. (Giggles)
after breakfast and presents,
I need to go to the
gallery... (alison) mm.
To take care of some
stuff. On christmas morning?
Well,yeah,you know, art never sleeps.
But you know what?
The three of us could hang out together.
It'll be great. We'll drink
hot cocoa and watch a movie,
And then when your dad comes
back,we can all go for a walk.
Hear those silver bells?
It's christmas time in the city.
Some families actually
do make the yuletide gay,
Managing to leave their
troubles far away...
Mom. Oh,it's beautiful.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh,look. You look like a
brunette catherine deneuve.
Quelle magnifique.
(Blair) it's so gorgeous.
Merry christmas,dorota.
It's so we can text.
Do you like it? Thank you,miss blair.
Other families have a
merry little christmas
Even when their troubles
aren't so far away...
So what did dad have to
do at the gallery,exactly?
Uh,paperwork,i-I think.
(The weepies) * carols
'cross the water *
You're going back to
Hudson, aren't you?
* all that i want *
Yeah.
But,hey, we are gonna be okay.
Come here.
* above the rooftops *
We know.
I'm sorry.
* golden spoon *
* i wait on clip-Clops *
Some presents might end
up getting returned...
I know how you like florida.
Yeah. Wow.
Uh,number one fan.
You know,i'm-I'm sorry i
didn't get anything for you,
Mr. Bass,but,uh,i didn't know
you'd be coming for christmas.
Ah,no worries,eric. Please,call me bart.
But some gifts are for keeps.
For you. Thank you.
Eric,serena,
I just want you to know
That i have deep
feelings for your mother.
Mom,your phone.
Oh. Uh,lily,you're not gonna
want to interrupt this moment.
Other presents come
when you least expect em.
* the world grows older *
Hey,lil. You know everything's
closed on christmas?
Diners that claim
to be open 24/7-
It's false advertising.
* all that i want *
And everyone knows
The biggest present
comes in the smallest box.
So,uh,alison's leaving.
She's spending time
alone with the kids.
And i seem to have walked
all the way from brooklyn
To your doorstep
Without a jacket, in the snow.
So what the hell?
I miss you...
And i have been
missing you for a while.
* all that i want *
Lily...
Would you do me the
honor of being my wife?
(Eleanor,roman,dorota) fromage! Cheese!
Ah,perfect.
Then there are those boxes
You wish you had never opened...
(Eleanor) oh,i
like the pa-
Don't worry, b. Who would i tell?
Have a holly jolly christmas. (Beep)
X.O.X.O.,gossip girl.