Your One And Only Source
Into The Scandalous Lives
Of Manhattan's Elite. I Remember
The First Time I Ever Saw Him.
I Knew. He's The One I Wanna Marry.
I Think You Dropped
This At The Ball.
I Hate Secrets More Than Anything.
You're Dismissed, Jenny... For Good.
Something About Uh, Uh, Mom And A Neighbor?
Yeah, It's... Complicated. Mom's Having
An Affair. It's Easy For Me To Say It.
Mom, It's Time For
You To Come Home.
I Was With My Friend Vanessa.
We're Very Close, And She
Moved Away To Vermont Last Year,
And Now She's Back.
You Said You Love Me.
Dan, Hungry?
Hello. Hi.
Hi. Nathaniel, I'm Shocked.
I Thought You Were Strictly An
Herbal Man. The Drugs Were Dad's.
I Mean, I Guess He Thought
It Would Be Easier On Everyone
If I Took The Hit. I Have To Say,
Every Time I Look At Anne's Finger
And See Blair's Future
Engagement Ring... Ah.
I Can Hardly Contain My Joy. It Seems
Your Father Is Facing Some Other Charges.
For What? Embezzlement And Fraud.
You Should Deal With Your Father.
He Needs You. I
Don't. Where's Nate?
I Think We Just Broke Up. What?
I Don't Wanna Talk About
It. I Just Want To Escape.
That's What This
Place Is For, Right?
And Who Am I?
That's A Secret I'll Never Tell.
You Know You Love Me.
X.O.X.O., Gossip Girl.
According To The Catholic Church,
Mortal Sin Can Only Be Absolved
Through The Sacred
Act Of Confession,
But It Looks Like A
Certain W.A.S.P. Princess
Has Recently Found Herself
Desperately In Need Of
A Little Unburdening.
And Who Is The Man
Upstairs To Discriminate?
Forgive Me, Father,
For I Have Sinned.
It's Been...
A While Since My Last Confession.
What Troubles You, My Child?
After Being Broken
Up With My Boyfriend
For Exactly 20 Minutes, I...
Succumbed To Inebriation,
Performed At A Speakeasy
And Surrendered My Virtue
To A Self-Absorbed Ass.
The Only Good News Is
That He's A Total Pig
Who Will Act Like It Never
Happened. Thank God. Ahem.
Sorry. Truthfully, I'm Not
Even Catholic. You Don't Say.
But Losing My
Virginity To Chuck Bass?
None Of My Friends
Will Ever Understand.
I'm Ready For My Punishment.
Whatever You And
God Think Is Fair-
Flogging, Fasting,
Putting That Thing With
The Teeth Around My Thigh,
Like Silas.
How About Some Food
For Thought Instead?
Don't Drink.
Keep Your Clothes On.
Try Avoiding Those Who
Might Cause You To Stray.
Oh, I Plan To.
Thank You, Father. It
Was Very Good Advice.
You Don't Grant
Birthday Wishes, Do You?
I'm A Priest, Not A Genie.
Well, The Next Time
You Talk To Him,
Would You Ask Him To Send
My Boyfriend Back To Me?
Mm. I Gotta Say...
No Need To Say Anything.
God, I Hate People In Love.
Wow.
Awkward.
Vanessa?
Serena. Dan.
No, No, No, No, No,
No. Vanessa's Here.
Ah. Lovebirds Ready To Order?
Oh, I'll Take 'Em. Hi.
Hi. So, Uh, You-You Work Here Now?
I Did Mention That, But
You've Been Distracted.
Vanessa. Hi. Nice To See You.
This Time You're Seeing Less Of Me.
Sorry About That. Walking In
When You Were, You Know... Yeah.
So You Guys Are Up Early.
What'd You Do Last Night?
Oh, My God. I Totally
Didn't Mean To Pry.
You're Not Prying. Why Would
You Think You're Prying?
No Reason. Did You Tell Her?
What? No. What's To
Tell? I Know Nothing,
But If You Guys Did The
Thing I Know Nothing About,
Then I Would Totally Support
That. Thanks, Vanessa.
Good To Know In The
Event That Should Happen.
Oh, Meaning It Didn't Happen? Meaning I Don't
Even Know What We're Talking About Right Now.
I Know I'm Lost. And
I Should Get Lost.
First Day. I Have Lots Of Tables.
Clearly.
So Vanessa Works Here Now.
Yeah, We Should Make
This Our Regular Spot.
Well, This Is The Last
Place I'd Expect To Find You.
Go Away, Chuck. I've
Been Given Orders
Practically From God Himself To Avoid You.
Would You Consider Avoiding Me Over Breakfast?
Sorry, But As Is Tradition
On The Day Before My Birthday,
I'm Heading To The Jeweler's
To Put Some Pieces On Hold
For Eleanor And
- Nate? Oh, I Don't Think
He'll Be Singing "Happy
Birthday" This Year.
No One Knows That
Nate And I Broke Up,
And It's Gonna Stay That
Way So I Can Fix This,
And I Don't Think Your Best Friend
Would Still Be Your Best Friend If He Knew
- If He Knew How Much I Enjoyed The Removal
Of A Certain Chastity Belt In The Back Of
This Very Limo? From This Moment Forward,
The Events Of Last Night
Will Never Be Mentioned Again.
Is That Clear? Not As Clear As The
Memory Of You Purring In My Ear,
Which I Have Been Replaying Over
And Over. Well, Erase The Tape,
Because As Far As I'm
Concerned, It Never Happened.
I'll See You At Your Party Tonight.
You're Officially Uninvited.
Never Stopped Me Before.
Speak Of The Devil,
And He Doth Appear,
Wearing His Trademark Scarf.
Careful, B.
Hell Hath No Fury Like
A Chuck Bass Scorned.
Hey, Dad.
Hi, Honey. How Was Hudson?
Your Mother Must Have Been
Kind Of Surprised To See You.
Yeah, She Was.
Hi, Rufus.
Alison.
What Are You Doing Here?
Well, I Asked Her To Come.
You Know, I Thought
You Guys Could... Talk.
Ahem.
Or Not.
Okay, Dad, I Know
It Wasn't My Place
To Ask Mom To Come Back... Jenny.
It's Your Life. I Get
That, But It's My Life, Too,
And It's Dan's, And I Just Felt
That Nothing's Ever Gonna Change
If Someone Doesn't Do Something.
Jenny! Stop. Breathe. I'm Not Angry.
You're Not?
Not At You.
While You Can't
Get Un-Angry At Mom
If She's In Hudson,
And You're Here, Dad.
I Mean, Nothing's Ever Gonna Change
If You're Not In The Same Room.
Can't You Just Give It A Chance?
Not On An Empty Stomach.
Come. I'll Make Us Breakfast.
Who Wants Waffles?
I Mean, You Do Still Like
Waffles, Right, Rufus?
You Know Me, Al.
I'm A Loyal Guy. Once I Commit
To Something, I Stick With It.
Ahem.
I'll Get The Syrup.
Hey, Mom. I Just Got
Back From The Jeweler's,
And I Have To Say
- Have You Seen This?
Since When Does
Drunk And Disorderly
Get This Much
Attention? Since Never.
The Captain Is Being Charged
With Embezzlement And Fraud.
This Is An Absolute Disaster.
It Must Be Awful For Them.
I Meant For Me. The Captain
Is Supposed To Represent Me.
The Contracts Are
About To Be Signed.
What About My I.P.O., Huh?
What Is Gonna Happen To My Bendel's
Deal? Nate Looks So Helpless.
I Have To Call My Attorney.
I-I Have To Put An End
To This Deal Before
It Goes Any Further.
I Have To Talk To Nate.
I Don't Know Why
Everybody's Making Such
A Big Deal Out Of This.
It's Just A Misunderstanding.
It'll Be Cleared Up In Time.
Yes, It Will, At Your
Trial. This Is Real, Howard.
The Only Reason You're
Not Behind Bars Right Now
Is Because Your Wife Could Afford Your Bail.
And I Would've Paid Ten Times That Amount.
You're Not Going To Jail. And
We're Gonna Do Everything We Can
To Make Sure That Doesn't Happen,
But In The Meantime, This Is Not
Something To Be Cavalier About.
It's Clearly A Setup. Someone's Got A Agenda.
Dad, Would You Just Shut Up And Listen To Him?
Nate. Look, Sir, What
Exactly Do We Need To Do Here?
Remain Calm And Give Them
Nothing But A United Front
As We Fight This. Well,
What About Some Sort Of, Um,
Some Sort Of Plea?
A Plea? You Think I'm Guilty?
Dad, It's Just A Question.
How Would That Work Exactly?
It Wouldn't. Nate, I'm
Sure You're Very Tired,
And This Is A
Conversation For Adults.
Why Don't You Go Get
Some Rest, Sweetheart?
Hey, Dad.
Jenny.
And-And Mom.
Hi, Honey.
Well, Look At This. The
Whole Family's Together...
Eating Waffles.
Want One?
You Bet.
Just One Question.
Am I The Only One Who Thinks
This Is Extremely Weird?
I
- I Mean, Given Everything.
Dan, Just Forget About It.
If Dad Can Let It Go, So Can
You. What Do You Mean, Let It Go?
You Know, The Guy In
Hudson. You Told Her?
No, Of Course I Didn't Tell
Her. Rufus. I Would Never.
I Overheard Dan And Dad Talking.
He Heard Us Arguing On The Phone.
Yeah, If You Want To Keep
Secrets, Maybe We Should All
Abandon The Loft And Move
To A Place With More Walls.
It's Always Gogood
To Give Him A While.
Yeah, No, I Knew-I Knew That.
I Can't Believe He Told Her
You Guys Were Gonna Do It.
Well, I Told You. That's
Different. I'm A Girl.
Yeah, Well, So Is She. Exactly
My Point. But Even If She Wasn't,
When You Get A Boyfriend,
You Become The Best Friend,
And The Best Friend Becomes
The Second Best Friend.
That's Just How It Has To
Be If It's Ever Gonna Work.
Hey, You Still Haven't
Told Me How Nate's Doing.
It's All Over The News.
Uh, When I Talked
To Him This Morning,
I
- I Told Him To Focus On His Family Today.
But He's Still Coming To
Your Party, Right? Here.
Uh, I Told Him Not
To Worry About It.
I Mean, Only If He's Up To It.
You're Such A Good
Girlfriend, B., Really.
Hey, Um, I'll Just Pick You
Up, And We Can Go Together,
But I Really Hope Nate Can Make It.
* We'll Walk Around * Nate, Here You
Are. I've Been Looking Everywhere For You.
I Was Up In Your Room.
I Was Calling Your
Name For 20 Minutes.
Hey, Take Your Earphones Out.
Take Your Earphones Out.
Nathaniel, I've Been
Calling You For 20 Minutes.
I'm Sorry. What Is It?
Blair's Birthday Party
Is Tonight, Isn't It?
Yeah.
I Was Thinking Maybe You Should
Give Her Something Special.
I'm Sure She's Already
Picked Out Something
At The Jewelry Store
And Put It On Hold.
Something More Special Than That.
Mom, That's A Family Heirloom.
I'm Not Giving It To Blair.
It's An Engagement Ring.
I'm Not Asking You To
Propose, But It's Important
That Blair Knows How Much
You Value Her Loyalty.
Her Loyalty Or Her Mother's?
Eleanor's Lawyers May Have Called.
What Difference Does It Make?
One Day We'll All Be Family,
And They Won't Have A Choice In These
Matters. Blair And I Broke Up Last Night.
Well, Then Get Back Together.
I Don't Think So. May I Remind
You It Was Your Own Rash Actions
That Got Us Into This Predicament?
We're In This Predicament
Because Dad Has A Drug Problem.
I Was Trying To Help
Him Then Help Him.
Your Father's Acting The Way
That He Is Because He's Scared.
He Needs You So Much Right Now,
More Than He Ever Has.
We All Do.
Whoever Thought Monarchy Was Dead
Didn't Realize It
Just Changed Zip Codes.
So What Will It Be, Nate,
Blair Waldorf's Hand
Or Your Father's Head?
Hi. Are You Okay?
Uh, I've Been Texting You All Day.
Yeah, I'm-I'm Fine. Thanks.
I, Um, Just Been A Little Busy.
I Just Wanted To Check On
You, See If You Need Anything.
Yeah, I Kinda Do.
Oh?
Um... Blair, Do You
Think We've Been A Little-
A Little Hasty With
The Whole Breakup?
I
- I Don't Know, Nate.
Um, It Was A Pretty
Difficult Decision.
Yeah, Look, I-I
Totally Understand.
I'm Sorry. I, Um, I
Shouldn't Have Brought It Up.
Uh, But We Do Have A
Lot Of History Together,
And, Uh, It Was In
The Heat Of The Moment,
But You'd Have To Be Willing
To Really Work For It.
Yeah, Yeah, Of Course.
Listen, We'll Just Take It
Slow And See How It Goes.
And, Um,
I've Got A Birthday
Present For You.
It's, Uh, Something Special.
I Can't Wait To
Open It At My Party.
I'll See You There.
I...
Hi. This Is Blair Waldorf.
I Was Wondering If Any Of
The Pieces That I Put On Hold
Were Picked Up Today.
The Diamond Necklace? Really?
Okay.
Thank You.
Thank You!
Hey.
Can We Talk?
Well, That Depends. Are
You-Are You Back For Good?
I Don't Know.
Your Father And I Haven't Really
Had A Chance To Talk, So...
Well, Do You Want To Come Back,
Or Do You Wanna Live In
Hudson With, Uh, Neighbor Guy?
Okay, Look, Dan, I Understand
That You're Mad, All Right?
And I'm Not Gonna
Defend What I Did.
No, You-You Don't Get It, Do You?
You Think I'm Only
Mad About The Cheating?
Okay. What Else?
Maybe That You Promised
You Would Be Home
By The End Of Summer,
And Then You Weren't.
Maybe The Fact That
You Left At All.
I Asked If You Were Okay With
Me Going Away, And I'd Hoped
That If There Was A Problem,
You Would Say Something.
Like What? "Your Daughter's
A Freshman At A School
"Populated By Mean
Girls And Date Rapists?
I Think She Needs Her Mom. "
Or Maybe "My Father Is
Madly In Love With You
And Will Probably
Never Get Over This"?
Why Should I Have To Tell You This?
Where Are You Going?
Out. I'll Call Later.
Well, That Went Well.
You Know, I Was Thinking
Of Going Out Also.
There's Something I Kinda Need To
Do. Oh, Yeah. You Need Some Help?
Can I Help You? No,
I'm Good. Thanks.
Come On, Man.
I Can Hear You Breathing On
The Other Side Of The Door.
Is She Anybody You Can Get Rid Of?
I Just Really Need To
Talk To You, Man. Please.
Nathaniel.
Where's The Girl?
In My Dreams. I Was Trying
To Get Some Shut-Eye.
What's On Your Mind? It's My Mom.
Sounds Freudian.
She Wants Me To
Give Blair Her Ring.
What? You Guys Broke Up.
Yeah, I Know. I Mean,
Uh, Wait. How Do You Know?
Predictably, Your Ex
Ran The Old, Uh,
Grill-The-Best-Friend Play.
Tried To Find Out
Where Your Head Was At.
So, Uh, Where, Uh,
Where Is Your Head?
Spinning.
I Mean, My Mom Wants Me
To Get Back With Blair
So Eleanor Doesn't Pull
Out Of Their Business Deal.
It's All Because Of My Dad's
Whole Trial Thing, You Know?
Yeah. I'm Sorry About All That,
But Look, If You're
Done With Blair, Be Done.
Don't Cave To Your Parents' Wishes
If They're Not Your Desires.
Excuse Me? Where's My Boy?
"Seal The Deal. Tap That Ass.
Money Marries Bigger Money"?
Look, I Care About
Three Things, Nathaniel-
Money, The Pleasures
Money Brings Me And You.
I'm Just Trying To
Have Your Back Here.
Your Parents Have Been
Controlling You Your Whole Life.
If It Doesn't End
Now, When Will It Ever?
Oh, My God.
Hey, Guys!
Hey, Serena! Blair! Happy
Birthday! Happy Birthday!
Oh, My God, Kati. Your
Brother's Place Looks Fabulous.
Yeah, I Know, Right? I Know. It's
Incredible. Come On, Guys. Let's Check It Out.
Hai. Douzo.
Arigatou Gozaimasu.
Douitashimashite.
Thank You. Hey. So Where's Nate?
Um, I'm Sure He'll Be Here Soon.
What About Dan? Oh,
Uh, He Said He's Coming,
But I Haven't Talked To
Him Since This Morning.
Well, You Better Check In On Him.
Make Sure The Best Friend
Hasn't Whisked Him Away
To Do Some Friendly
Activity. Oh, Shut Up.
Oh, There's Chuck. I Bet
He Knows Where Nate Is.
I Think Nate Probably Just
Snuck In While We Were Dancing.
Chuck.
Well, Thanks For Listening To Me
Complain About My Family All Afternoon.
Oh, Look, I Know It's Hard Right Now...
But Your Family's
One Of The Good Ones,
And Your Parents
Really Love Each Other.
They'll Figure It Out,
And In The Meantime, You've Got Me.
Um, Actually, I Was Gonna
Go Meet Up With Serena.
Oh, Sure. Have Fun.
I Will. What Are We Doing?
I Thought You Said We
Weren't Doing Anything.
I Like Serena, And I Like
You, And She Likes Me,
And You Like Me, So How-How
Can You Not Like Each Other?
It's Mathematically Impossible. Who Said
I Didn't Like Her? I Just Don't Know Her.
Yeah, And You're Making A
Real Effort To Change That.
I Mean, Why Spend Five Minutes
Trying To Be Nice To Serena,
When I Can Spend Day After Day
Forced To Choose
Between The Two Of You?
Okay, Fine. You Want To
See Me Get My Nice On?
Let's Do It Tonight. Just
You, Me And Serena. Um...
Tonight-Tonight Is Blair
Waldorf's Birthday Party.
Uh, I Think We Might Want
To Start By Dipping A Toe
Rather Than Diving Off Of A Cliff,
Headfirst, Into The
Rocks With The Sharks.
Why? We All Know
How To Swim. Come On.
You Want To Do This, Let's Do It.
Are You Ready For Your Present? Ow!
If You Wanted To Play Rough,
All You Had To Do Was Ask.
Hi. Hi. Hello There.
Happy Birthday To Me.
You Nauseate Me.
All This Talk About How
You Have To Be With Nate
Or The World Will End.
Face It. It's Over.
You Sound Like A Jealous Boyfriend.
Yeah, Right. You Wish.
No.
You Wish.
Please. You Forget
Who You're Talking To.
So Do You.
Do You...
Like Me?
Define "Like. "
Oh.
Uh, You Have Got To Be
Kidding. I Do Not Believe This.
How Do You Think I Feel?
I Haven't Slept. I Feel Sick,
Like There's Something
In My Stomach, Fluttering.
Butterflies?
No, No, No, No, No, No, No.
This Is Not-Not Happening.
Believe Me, No One Is More
Surprised Or Ashamed Than I Am.
Chuck, You Know That I
Adore All Of God's Creatures
And The Metaphors
That They Inspire,
But... Those Butterflies
Have Got To Be Murdered.
Fine. It Wasn't That Great Anyway.
Thanks.
Jenny.
Oh. Hi, Nate.
Hey. I Told Blair, And I
Shouldn't Have. I'm Sorry.
Oh, About What
Happened At The Ball?
It's, Uh, It's Not Your Fault.
So... How Have Things
Been Between You Guys?
Uh, Strange,
But Again, Not Your Fault.
So You Gonna Go Inside?
I Was Planning On It, But Now
That I'm Here, I'm Not So Sure.
Yeah. Me Neither.
Blair Invited Me Before Our Fight,
And I Was Gonna Run In
And Give Her This Card,
Which Says "I'm Sorry,
" Like, 30 Times.
Maybe You Could Just
Deliver It For Me, Though?
Uh, Do You Wanna Go
Take A Walk Or Something?
With You?
Um, What Would Blair Think?
Well, Blair's Up There.
Unless, Of Course, You Wanna Go.
It's Up To You.
A Walk Sounds Good.
Thank You.
Dan, You're Here!
And, Um, And You Brought Vanessa.
Hey. Good To See You.
Um, Kati And Is, You-You Know Dan.
Uh, Blair, This Is, Um,
Dan's Friend Vanessa.
Wow. You Didn't Mention
They Were So Nice.
Now I Get It.
Oh, Sweetie, You Did Not
Tell Me She Looked Like That.
This Is Such A Problem.
Rufus, I'm Sorry.
I Know That You're Upset.
You're Getting That, Huh?
Can You Please Talk To Me? Please?
I Only Have One Question,
And I'm Pretty Sure
I Don't Want To Hear The Answer.
It Happened One Time, And I
Wish It Hadn't, And It's Over.
Then Why Did Our Daughter
Have To Go To Hudson
And Drag You Back Here? Because
When We Spoke On The Phone,
I Didn't Really Get The Impression
That You Wanted To See Me.
I Thought I Should Give You Some Space.
This Family Has Had Way Too Much Space.
You Never Should Have Left. Can We
Not Go Through This Whole Thing Again?
Please. You Know
That I Wasn't Happy.
Yeah. You Happy Now?
In Some Ways, I Am. I Know
You Don't Want To Hear That.
Look, Please Don't Act
Like You Care What I Want.
Rufus.
I Was There For You When You
Were All About Your Music,
When You Were On The
Road For Months At A Time
And Everything That Went With It.
My Whole Adult Life
Has Been About You.
And Now I'm The One
That's Screwed Up.
I Guess I Was A Late Bloomer.
I Just Need You To Care
Enough About Me To Try.
Alison...
I Care.
Whoo!
Stalk Me Much?
What Are You Still
Doing Up Here All Alone?
I Don't Know Where Nate Is,
And He Always Calls Me At Midnight,
When It Turns Into My Birthday.
Well, I Wouldn't Count On It Tonight.
Doesn't It Strike You
As, Uh, Just A Little Bit
Of Coincidence, The Timing Of
Everything? What Do You Mean?
Well, Nate Suddenly Decides
He Wants To Get Back Together
Just Moments After Your Mother
Puts The Brakes On Her
Deal With The Captain?
So You're Saying That Nate
Is Only Pretending To Like Me,
And That He's Actually
Using Me To Get To My Mother?
He Wouldn't Do That.
Yes, He Would.
If It Was To Help His
Family, You Know He Would.
Nate Loves Me.
Whatever He's Doing,
Wherever He Is,
He Will Call At
Midnight. You'll See.
Care To Make A Wager?
If He Calls, I'll
Leave You Alone Forever.
If He Doesn't, You
Spend The Night With Me.
I Will Not.
I Thought You Were Sure.
You're Gonna Lose.
He's Never Missed My Birthday.
Careful, B.
There's No Safe Wager
When You Bet On A Bass.
You Just Might Lose Your
Shirt And Your Pants.
So You Brought Vanessa As
Your Date To Blair's Party?
No, No, You're My Date.
I Just Thought It Might
Be A Good Opportunity For All Three Of Us
To Hang Out. Oh, Yeah, 'Cause It Was So Fun
And Not Remotely Awkward
At Breakfast This Morning.
Fine. You're-You're- You're
Right. I Actually Thought
This Would Be A Very Bad
Opportunity For Us To Hang Out,
But I Kind Of Suggested To Vanessa
That She Wasn't Making An
Effort To Get To Know You,
So, Uh, She Decided
To Start Tonight,
But If It's Weird,
I Can Go Talk To Her.
No. No, No, No, Don't Do That.
Look, Tell Me Something
Vanessa Likes Besides You,
And I Will Make An
Effort To Bond. I Promise.
Oh, Thank You.
So What Now?
Ever Play "Guitar Hero"?
Yeah!
Thank You. Thank You.
Oh, She Owned You, Serena.
Yeah, You Went Down Almost As Hard
As Britney At The V.M.A.S. Okay,
You Know, You're Good, Vanessa.
I'll Admit It, But I Have
Been Holding Back Until Now.
There's A Little Birdie
That's About To Be Free.
And You're Rockin'.
That's My Girl!
That's It. Right There.
Thank You. Thank
You. Who Got On Now?
Not Bad, But Skynyrd
Is Meat And Potatoes,
And I'm Bringing Dessert,
So What Do You Say
To A Slice Of "Cherry Pie"?
No Pie. I Say No, I Beg You. Come On.
There's Nothing Like A Little '80s Hair Metal
To Put A Smile On Your Face.
After The Day You've Had?
The-The Day You've Had? What-
What Kind Of Day Have You Had?
You Didn't Tell Her?
Uh, No. No, Not Yet. Not Yet.
Um, It Was Kind Of An Odd
Day At The Humphrey Loft.
Uh, Actually, Jenny
Brought My Mom Home.
Your Mom's Back?
Yeah.
Excuse Me.
I Can't Believe You Didn't
Tell Me Your Mom Came Home.
I'm Sorry, Really. Uh...
What? You Didn't Think It Was
Important? No, No, Of Course It Is.
Why Bother? You
Already Told Vanessa.
I Tell Vanessa Everything, All
Right? I Have Since I Was 6.
Well, You're Not 6 Anymore, Dan.
I Just-I Was Just Hoping
That I Would Be The Person
That You Would Wanna
Tell These Things To Now.
I Want You To Be That Person, Too.
Really, I Do.
This Whole Girlfriend Thing
Is Very New To Me, You Know?
I
- I Just...
I Don't Know All The Rules Yet.
Well, Blair Says In A Relationship,
The Best Friend Is
- Serena, You're Really Taking Relationship Advice From Blair?
Good Point.
Look, I Just Don't Want To
Have To Compete With Vanessa.
You Know, With
"Guitar Hero, " Okay.
I'm Way More Awesome, If
You Didn't Happen To Notice.
But, Um, Not With You.
That's Fair.
All Right, So Tomorrow, You And I
Will Go Somewhere Together,
Just The Two Of Us,
And We Will Talk About My
Family In Excruciating Detail
Until You Are
- You're Just So Bored,
You're Begging For Vanessa
To Take Over, All Right?
How's That Sound?
Perfect.
All Right.
Come On. It's Almost Midnight.
What Happens At Midnight?
I Heard About Your Dad.
I'm Sorry.
Well, If It Makes
You Feel Any Better,
My Family's Not Doing That
Great Right Now Either.
You Know, I Actually Didn't
Want To Come To Blair's Party
As Much As I Just Wanted
To Get Out Of My House.
Yeah, I Know The Feeling.
Blair's Birthday Present.
Your Mother's Ring.
Blair Told Me About It.
Wow. It's Beautiful.
I'm, Uh, Supposed To
Give It To Blair Tonight.
I'm Guessing That Wasn't Your Idea.
Blair And I Broke Up,
And I Know It Was
The Right Thing To Do.
I Mean, We Just Shouldn't Be
Together Right Now, You Know?
Sounds Like You're
Pretty Sure Of That.
I Am, And As Much As I
Wanna Do The Right Thing
And Help Out My Parents,
It's Just-It's Not Fair.
I Mean, To Me Or To Blair.
I Just Think That If I Do This Now,
When Does It Ever Stop?
It'll Only Stop When You Stop It.
12:01. I'm Sorry.
No, You're Smarmy.
There's A Difference.
If You're Coming To
Collect, You Can Forget It.
Turn Around.
You Get Grosser By The Second.
You Get Older. Look.
Happy Birthday!
Blair, Blow Out
Your Candles. I Know.
Make A Wish, Blair.
It Already Didn't Come True.
Happy Birthday To Who?
Forget Cake And Ice Cream.
I'm Saving Room For Just Desserts.
Looks Like Chuck's
Wish Might Come True.
Hey.
So I Don't Know How It Was Possible
Given How The Day Started,
But, Um, I Actually Had
Kind Of A Good Night.
Your Parents Won't Be Mad You're
Coming Home So Late, Right?
Oh, No, They Think
I'm With A Friend.
Huh. Well, They Think Right.
I Had Fun.
Me, Too. You Have A Good Night.
Spotted-Nate Archibald
Depositing A Mystery Girl
In A Taxi After Midnight.
All We Know About Her For Sure?
She's Not Blair Waldorf.
Did You Guys See This? I Can't Believe
Gossip Girl Would Do This To Her
On Her Birthday. You Know
What? Maybe She's Wrong.
It Wouldn't Be The First
Time. Blair, Hey, I'm So Sorry.
I Never Would've Thought That This Would
Happen. I Hope The Slut Gave Him Herpes.
Cheater Totally Deserves Herpes.
He Isn't Cheating.
We Broke Up, Okay?
He Was Gonna Get
Back Together With Me,
But Only So My Mom
Would Help His Dad.
You Satisfied?
Blair.
Blair, Stop, Okay? Talk To Me.
We Ended It.
I Wanted To Tell You, But-But
Part Of Me Thought That
If I Didn't Say It Out Loud,
Then It Wouldn't Be True.
Shh. Shh.
It Was My Birthday Wish
For Us To Get Back Together.
Now I Think It's Really Over.
Oh, Blair, Shh.
Is It Okay If I Just Wanna
Be Alone For A Second?
Nate, Hey. What Are
You Doing Home So Early?
It's After Midnight. We Just
Thought You'd Be With Blair.
How Did She Like Her Gift? I
Didn't Make It To The Party Tonight.
Well, Her Actual Birthday Is Today.
You Can Call Her In The
Morning, Maybe Take Her To Lunch.
It's A Good Plan. Really
More Special This Way.
Dad, I Know You Think
Blair Will Help Save You,
But I'm Not Doing This.
It's Over.
Nate.
There's Nothing In This World
I Wouldn't Do To
Protect Our Family,
And I'm Sure You Feel The Same.
I Need Your Support
Here, Son, And Your Trust.
Well, You Better Hope For Your Sake
They Don't Call Your
Son To The Stand.
Hmm.
God, I Have Missed Your Smile.
Mm. I Have Missed Everything.
Mm.
Please Tell Me That Is Someone
Coming To Rob The House.
Hey, Mom.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, Jenny.
As You Were.
Is Your Friend Gonna Be Okay?
Um, I'm Not Sure.
She Just Broke Up
With Her Boyfriend,
And Then They Got Back
Together And Then, Um,
I Don't Know What Just Happened.
Well, She's Lucky To Have
You. Being A Good Friend Is...
Challenging At Times?
Hey, If I've Been Acting
However I've Been Acting,
It's Just 'Cause I'm
Protective Of Dan.
And I'm Protective
Of Our Relationship.
I've Never Actually Had One Before.
You Guys Just Have
Everything In Common,
And, Um, I'm Just
Getting To Know Him.
So, You Know, It Can Be
A Little Intimidating.
Talk About Intimidating.
You Just Admitted That
You Find Me Intimidating,
So How Cool Does That Make You?
I Think You Forgot To Mention
My Superior "Guitar Hero" Skills.
No, I Didn't Forget That.
And At The Next Party,
I'm Asking For A Rematch,
'Cause You Were
About To Get Smoked.
Oh, Really? Well, I Think
The Only Thing Getting Smoked
Is Your Pale Imitation Of A Guitar
Player. Hey, I Am A Golden God.
Oh, Really? Are You Now? Hey.
Am-Am I Interrupting Anything?
Um, Actually, You Are.
I'll Give You Guys A Moment.
Might That Have Been Bonding
That I Just Walked In On?
A Little Bit. Yeah? What
Were You Talking About?
Nothing You Need To Know About.
Oh, So You Have Secrets Now? I See.
Well, Listen, Um, If You
Want To Get Out Of Here,
Vanessa Can Only Fit Two On
Her Vespa, But I Can Walk.
Oh, Well, You Know
I Love Me A Vespa,
But, Um, I Think I Gotta
Stay Here And Be With Blair.
You're Not The Only
One With A Best Friend.
Yeah.
I'm Not In The Mood, Chuck.
This Is Pretty Much
The Worst Birthday Ever.
Maybe It Can Be Salvaged.
Is That Our Sex Tape?
It's The Erickson Beamon Necklace.
No, I Couldn't.
Yes, You Can.
Something This Beautiful
Deserves To Be Seen On
Someone Worthy Of Its Beauty.
I Really Am Sorry.
-
=Http:/Www. Ragbear. Com=-
Spotted
- B. Turning A Year Older,
But Not Necessarily Wiser.
Guess Chuck's The Gift
That Keeps On Giving.
Blow Out Your Candles, B.
This Will Be Better In The Dark.
X.O.X.O., Gossip Girl.