Gossip girl Here,
Your one and only source
Into the scandalous lives
of manhattan's elite.
You got into brown. The letter came while
you were away. Congratulations.
You said you could
call in a favor at n.Y.U.
Did you mean it ?
- I can only get you an interview.
It's gonna be up to you to wow him.
You got your money.
That's all that matters.
- Now you can go to Yale.
- Well I'm going to NYU now.
Great. Then i'll see you
next year.
Oh, my god.
You're nate archibald.
and you're bree buckley.
It's good to see you again.
I made some new friends,
one in particular.
Oh. So you are dating someone ?
His name's scott, and i think you guys
Would really like each other.
Yeah, mom,
everything's great.
I have been waiting all summer
for reed to start,
And tomorrow's the day
i get to do what i came here for.
I know secrecy
is a lot to ask for,
But i really can't risk making my family
more upset right now. Don't worry.
I'm good
at secret relationships.
What if your dad didn't want
to see you ? Who cares ?
Who the hell is he
not to want you ?
I would've stayed all summer
with you.
Vanessa, i'm--I'm not changing.
I don't care if you're rich,
which you aren't, by the way.
If you're gonna be in this world
be yourself in this world.
- Is there anything else ?
- I'd like to request a roommate--
Blair waldorf.
She's my best friend, and i just
can't wait to live with her.
Gossip Girl Saison 3 Épisode 02
** The Freshman **
Every fall,
confident high school seniors
Transform into
nervous college freshmen.
They leave their parents' homes
For the hallowed halls
of higher education.
And like any new venture,
Starting college
holds the promise
Of limitless opportunity.
The opportunity
to conquer a new territory...
Or to try and be
a little less lonely...
But just because
the opportunity
Presents itself...
Have a safe drive up to Brown.
So proud of you ! XO Mom
doesn't mean
everybody is ready to take it.
Mmm.
You're so sweet
to see me off.
I can't believe n.Y.U. Orientation week
Is finally here.
I have to object
to you living in the dorms.
Fluorescent lighting,
communal showers,
Public school girls ?
There's a place for that,
And it belongs
in the back of a video store.
It's not for long.
I can't rule the n.Y.U. Masses
from the upper east side.
I need to spend time in the dorm
to establish myself as queen.
It's not constance, blair.
The only queens at n.Y.U.
Are the ones with tickets
to see liza at carnegie hall.
Chuck, i trust
that when you say,
"Never drink absinthe
with daniel baldwin",
You know what
you're talking about.
But when i say the first week
of college means
Scared, vulnerable freshmen
needing someone to guide them,
That i know what
i'm talking about
And i'm very excited
for you.
So you haven't called vanessa yet ?
No, she's the one who's out of line.
She's gotta call me.
Or you could just get over it.
After all these years,
You guys are finally gonna
be at the same school.
I guess you're right.
It's probably not the best idea
To be avoiding my only friend
at n.Y.U.
For the record, dan,
i don't think
You're gonna have any trouble
making friends there.
Right, because The world of
greenwich village intelligentsia
Is dan humphrey's
natural habitat.
You're so lucky. N.Y.U.
Is exactly the right place for you.
Like brown is for you.
Serena ?
Um...
Sorry. Uh, yeah.
You know what ?
I should finish packing.
But good luck, dan.
Hey, i'm sorry.
Are you dan humphrey ?
Uh, yeah.
- Like the dan humphrey who was published
In the "20 under 20" issue
of "the new yorker ?"
Uh, yeah.
Large coffee, please.
I'm katie, and i'm not usually
an eavesdropping stalker.
It's just that i read
your piece, and it was amazing.
What ? Really ? Wow.
That's--That--Thank you.
Yeah, well, at first i hated you
because i also submitted,
But then i read it
and i was like,
Okay, fine. I accept defeat
at your hands, dan humphrey.
Anyway, i have a writer's group.
We meet every week.
We're meeting here at noon
tomorrow. You should come.
car's downstairs. You ready ?
As i'll ever be.
- Today's a big day,
You and dan
both off college.
Yeah, i know. I know.
Uh, i should get going.
Your mom's so proud of you.
So am i.
Hey.
Uh, scott, you remember dan.
Dan, this is scott.
Yeah. No, it's, uh, it's good
to finally officially meet you.
Uh, so are you two dating now ?
Last i heard you were just friends.
Yeah, you actually have to call me
To find out what's going on in my life.
Oh, well, okay.
I didn't realize we were speaking.
- oh, god.
- of course she's in a limo.
Ew.
Let's make it clear
from the start.
We don't know each other here.
- Works for me.
- Me, too.
Well, hello, sis.
I assume you need a few ounces
of study aid for brown.
No. I need a place to stay.
I'm not going to brown.
yes, we may all be freshmen and
new to n.Y.U. And the dorms,
but that doesn't mean
We have to embarrass ourselves.
I can tell from looking around this room
that none of you are From new york city.
Actually, i'm from--
Riverdale doesn't count.
Anyway, i won't be holding
The sad truths of your hometowns
against you.
In fact, i want to help you.
For example, who can tell me
Which is the only club to be
seen at on a saturday night ?
I read marquee.
Wrong. You should never be seen
at a club on a saturday night.
It's strictly bridge and tunnel
on the weekends.
You're welcome. Now dorota and i
have put together some gift bags
Filled with essentials
for everyone.
I think you don't need week
to run school.
You do it in one day.
I know. This is going
even better than i'd hoped.
And the best part is
i seem to have a single.
Sorry i'm late.
Blair ?
Blair waldorf ? Oh, my gosh !
Oh, my gosh. I can't believe it !
We're roommates !
Rah rah, sis boom bah.
Georgina's pulled
a coup d'état.
Welcome to college, b.
This is gonna be a blast.
Following me to n.Y.U ?.
Becoming my roommate ?
I'm gonna have dorota file
a restraining order.
I mean,
you're overreacting.
The roommate thing is
just a coincidence.
Besides, my parents said it was
either bible camp or college,
So go, bobcats !
- So you're not in love with jesus anymore ?
Oh, i still hold him
in my heart,
But jesus and i have
redefined our relationship.
You mean he dumped you because
he found out you were satan !
This could actually
be a good thing, blair.
Look. Manolos.
Size 7, just like you.
Let me know if you want to borrow.
I'll win, you know.
I ruled at constance and i will
rule here, And you can't stand in my way.
Are you still playing
this tired old game ?
Oh, please. Like you're not ?
No, i'm not. I'm actually here for a fresh start.
Oh, no.
Vanessa, you're in our dorm, too ?
Yay !
Your dorm ? Yeah, um,
my room's just down the hall.
So, uh...
That's awesome.
Oh !
Isn't this so pretty ?
I'm gonna hang it up.
Oh, miss blair.
What are we going to do ?
Call police ?
No.
We're going to throw a party.
I go to masa,
see if they will cater.
Pardon me.
I was packing and talking
to blair about her classes,
And then it hit me.
I wasn't excited
about any of it.
I don't know
what i want to do yet,
And--And going off to
a new place to figure that out ?
I don't know. I'm just--
I'm not ready for that.
Look, sis,
for people like us,
A college degree is
just an accessory,
Like a malawi baby
or a poodle.
Well, it's an accessory my
mother really wants me to have.
So you want to hide out at the
bass cave Until you figure it out.
Yeah, if it's okay with you.
Nobody knows about this,
Not even blair. Blair would be
even more upset than my mother.
I couldn't help but notice
you and carter baizen
At the van der bilt
polo party.
This doesn't have anything to do
with him, does it ?
No, absolutely not. I haven't
even seen him since then.
Good. Just one favor--
I'm having a meeting here tonight,
So if you can clear out for a few hours.
Chuck, i don't mind
if your dealer comes by.
Jesse is in st. Barths
this week.
This is something
more legitimate.
You know
the old art deco bank
On 72nd between madison
and park ?
The one that went
under last month ?
I want to make it
into a speakeasy.
In the front--
An elegant restaurant,
But down in the vault--
An after-Hours locale
Devoted to indecency,
Disreputable behavior
and all manner of debauchery.
A kind of homage to the last
time the market crashed.
The harder the times,
The harder people want to party
and forget about it.
Chuck.
this is really a great idea.
I-I can't believe blair
hasn't told me about this yet.
She doesn't know.
Nobody does.
I just wanted to wait till i was
sure it was going through.
You know, my father
turned his first profit
By the time he was 22.
I hope to do it
by the time i'm 21.
Let me guess.
women in literature,
professor schweik ?
You know i'm a sucker for
stories about scorned women.
I got the same. I think the universe
is trying to tell us something.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I should have called you.
No, it's--It's okay.
I wouldn't have wanted
to call me either
After the way i came down on you
at the party.
Um... so... scott ?
Yeah, he's--He's so great,
And he really wants
to get to know you.
Oh, my god. I have so much to tell you.
You are never gonna guess
who lives in my dorm.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh. Oh !
Sorry to interrupt. I just
saw you, and i thought, um...
So i really just want
to apologize
For everything
that happened in the past.
I've got my meds straightened out,
And i'm really in a much better place now.
So i come to n.Y.U.
Hoping for a fresh start,
And who do i get as my roommate ?
Blair waldorf.
What ?
i told you we have
so much to catch up on.
I mean, i wish i had some
other friends here, you know ?
You guys are--Are really
lucky to have each other.
Anyway, i should go.
Okay,
this is probably too much,
But would you guys want to have
a cup of coffee with me ?
Uh...
Look, georgina,
I appreciate that you want
a clean slate,
But i think it would
kind of be too much. I'm sorry.
No, of course.
I-I mean,
i-I totally understand.
I'd feel the same way.
I'll see you around.
Maybe we were
a little bit too harsh.
- What ? It's--It's georgina.
- And you're dan.
And you're vanessa.
This is a fun game.
I'm sorry. I just thought you were
A little bit more forgiving
than that.
Are you--Are you really trying
to make me the bad guy here ?
No, it's just we want a fresh
start and--And so does she.
Okay. I know you're new
to the whole school thing,
But you don't want georgina
as your friend.
I mean, she's gonna scare
everyone away.
- Georgina.
- Hey.
What's gonna happen next week
when we start classes ?
That's why we have
my family's apartment.
And plus, you know,
all this sneaking around,
Making sure the doorman
doesn't see you,
Not answering the phone
when my mother calls--
I mean, you know it adds
a layer of hotness.
What are you saying ?
That our hotness is
only purely circumstantial
And that if we were
out in the real world,
We'd like each other less ?
Mm. You know that
if we really started dating,
After a few months,
You'd realize that you hate
the way that i laugh,
I couldn't stand
the way that you chew,
And then we'd break up.
That's a very romantic story,
you know,
But... it doesn't have
to be like that.
Care to make a bet ?
I got an idea.
I will hole up with you
for the next 24 hours,
And we can fast-Forward through
the entire relationship.
Leave the seat up,
sing timberlake in the shower.
Ah, watch tv shows
you really like
As opposed to ones
you're supposed to like ?
What do you say--
You, me, this apartment ?
Let's get sick
of each other.
Okay.
As you can see, the restaurant
would be elegant--
Seasonal menu,
extensive wine list.
You know, the space is big, But i want
it to have a more intimate feel.
And how would you be using
the vault space ?
It's perfect for storage.
I have to be honest.
Give your reputation,
when you made your bid,
The board was
very concerned.
I completely understand.
The neighbors don't want
some raucous club coming in
And disrupting the quiet.
And believe me,
I wouldn't want to bring
that element to the area.
I'll be right down.
Sorry. I'm not here.
my heel broke.
Stepsister. I apologize.
My lawyer. Excuse me.
Sorry for interrupting
your meeting.
Not at all. We were
just finishing up anyway.
Oh, are you--Are you leasing
chuck the bank space ?
Mm-Hmm.
He has a real vision.
I know. Turning the vault
into a club--It's genius.
Serena.
excuse me ?
Thank you.
Cool party. I'm amalia.
I'm glad people understand The concept
of being fashionably late,
- But this is ridiculous.
- I think everybody's
Down the hall,
watching a movie or something.
What ?
Please.
Ease up on the toro.
He has to answer to a board,
serena.
And board members tend
not to approve
Of clubs with coat check girls
who give happy endings.
It was an honest mistake.
When he was talking about
your plans--
why do you think
i asked you to go out tonight ?
Because i knew something
like this would happen.
Fine. Then i'll go.
Train wreck.
great job, vanessa.
That was awesome.
Oh. Hey, blair.
Oh, my god. We just finished
watching vanessa's documentary
About this community garden
in her neighborhood.
It was amazing.
- No, it wasn't.
Yes, it was. I-I mean, vanessa,
tears. Actual tears.
When that gang member picked up
his first carrot--
Okay, screening is over.
The cocktail party has
officially begun
In the common room.
Sake-Tinis.
And is that my invitation
being used as a coaster ?
Um, thanks so much, blair,
But we actually just scarfed,
like, four pizzas,
And vanessa's about to show us
Her bootleg michel gondry videos.
- Georgina, please.
Nobody wants greasy pizza
and vanessa's home movies
When there's a sushi and sake
party right in the other room.
Did i mention wasabi facials ?
Okay, then.
And shut the door ?
Spotted--Blair waldorf
going from v.I.P. To v.D.
Poor blair. How are you
going to cure this one ?
morning.
Hey.
Thanks for letting me
crash here last night.
Harboring an ivy league fugitive ?
I'm your man.
I made you breakfast.
I have to go, but remember,
we don't have any servants here,
So if you see anybody else
in the loft besides me,
Call the police.
It's not the chef.
Good to know.
So did classes
start already ?
Uh, no,
just orientation stuff.
But, uh, i did join
a literary group.
More people have talked to me
at n.Y.U. In one day
Than my entire four years at st. Jude's.
Well, i'm not surprised.
I can totally see why people
would love you there.
Oh, about brown Uh, you really
should think about talking to my dad.
He might ramble a lot, he might
nervously strum his guitar,
But, uh, when it comes
to fatherly advice,
I don't know, he's pretty much
the best there is.
do you want one ?
Thanks.
Come to the party.
Come to the party. Thanks.
It's gonna be really fun.
- we'll be there.
Oh, fantastic.
Oh.
So if you're not trying to
sabotage me, then what is this ?
First you deliberately ruin
my sushi party,
And now you're making your move.
- This paranoia has got to stop, blair.
I am not paranoid.
I'm right.
Why else would you have formed
an alliance with vanessa,
The one person i may hate
more than you ?
It's not an alliance.
It's a friendship.
Unlike you, vanessa's cool
and people like her,
More than the weird girl
who threw the fish party.
Sushi. There was toro.
Face it, blair.
Once upon a time,
in a far-Off land,
You were a queen.
Here you're just a loser
who will never fit in.
So you won't be
needing that.
Hey, guys. Do you want
to come to my party ?
You can have one, too.
You're really pretty.
thank you.
Rufus ?
Hello ?
What are you doing here ?
Rufus and i were
just catching up.
But i have to prepare
for a meeting tonight.
Thank you for the waffles.
Look, i...
I don't know what kind of
twisted spin Chuck put on things,
But i actually wanted
to talk to you about this.
Rufus, i'm having doubts
about going to brown.
Well, i'm sorry about that,
But to lie about leaving
for college ?
I mean, between the show you put
on for the paparazzi all summer
And the craziness at the polo
party last week and this,
I don't know
what's going on with you.
I know. I'm sorry i lied. I just
didn't want to upset my mom.
at least we agree
about that,
Which is why you can repack your
things and go to brown today.
I'll have a car here
within an hour.
As long as you're in it, there's no
reason Lily ever has to know about this.
Or what, you'll tell on me ?
Wow. I feel really
emotionally supported
In making this life-Changing decision.
- It's not a decision. It's a mistake,
Which is why i'm--I'm trying
to get you not to make it.
By threatening me.
do you know you're more
afraid of my mother than i am ?
You know what, rufus ?
Go ahead. Call her.
You can let her know
i'm not going to brown.
Thanks for the talk.
What do you want ?
Hey. I was wondering
if you want to go out tonight.
- I thought you were at brown.
- No, i'm not.
In fact,
after i hang up with you,
I will be withdrawing
my admission.
There's nobody
i'd rather celebrate with.
So are you in or out ?
See you tonight.
no, i'm telling you,
I learned everything i need to know
about women From judy blume's "forever".
Can i talk to you ?
Uh, yeah. Yeah. What's up ?
I was wondering...
Do you have a date
to georgina's party ?
Forget the four horsemen.
The real evidence our world
is coming to an end--
Blair waldorf needing
dan humphrey
To rescue her
from social extinction.
You okay ?
I just feel like i got off
on the wrong foot here,
And i want to start again.
So... thanks for bringing me,
humphrey.
Oh. Uh, yeah. Well, you know,
i-I would just like to think
That if i needed it, somebody
would do the same for me.
Although, let's be honest,
we both know it wouldn't be you.
Oh.
No headbands in college,
okay ?
- Katie.
- Hey, guys.
Blair, you, uh,
you remember katie ?
Yeah. Cute necklace.
Thank you. I love your...
How--How about i get us all
drinks and you two talk ?
Just not about high school,
please.
What's up, dan ?
So was everyone
at your high school
Totally jealous of dan for
being such a great writer ?
Dan's a writer ?
Oh. Hey, dan.
Hey. Um, listen.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I-I was out of line.
Please don't Don't even worry about it.
I mean, you have every right to be upset.
I'm just really glad you're here.
- Thanks.
Okay, so am i really drunk,
Or did i just see you
walk in with blair ?
look, you wanted me
to give you a second chance.
Don't you think you should
give one to blair ?
She's not looking
for a second chance.
She's looking for a way in.
People like you here, dan,
and blair sees that.
I'm sorry. I've been the person
not welcome at parties,
And if i'm now
on the other side of things,
I'm--I'm not gonna treat people
the way i was treated,
Even if it's blair.
I'm just trying to look out for you.
Trust me.
You're being used.
Have fun.
Gross !
With your mother's
l.L. Bean catalog ?
Ugh. A cargo short fetish
Definitely goes
in the "minus" column.
What are you talking about ?
I was, like, 12 years old.
Speaking of pants,
pass yours over here.
- What do you need my pants for ?
- Because i want to see what's in them.
Come on. Show me
all your secrets.
- Have a look. It's just normal stuff.
- Normal stuff, huh ?
All right.
- See ?
- hmm ?
Keys, cell phone.
A boarding pass...
From london.
don't tell me That you've been wearing
these pants since we met,
Because that really would be gross.
- No, i...
if you must know, i kept it.
Ah.
And he has
a sentimental streak.
Hey, i thought
your theory was that
If we really got to know
each other, we'd break up.
Maybe i'm revising
my theory.
To you.
Brown's loss is my gain.
Thank you.
You know, when you called,
i tried not to answer.
Great. Chuck bass.
Let's get out of here.
- No. Come on.
Since when do you run away
from chuck bass ?
It looks like he's having
a business meeting.
This could be fun.
No way.
Serena, carter,
this isn't a good time.
Well, then let's make it one.
What's wrong, chuck ?
Aren't you happy to see us ?
- You know, carter and i were
Just sharing our favorite
chuck bass stories.
There were so many we had to
break them into categories.
What were we up to,
international affairs ?
Oh, there was a time when, uh, chuck
And the italian ambassador's
son
Were asked to leave an amsterdam brothel.
Now that's an accomplishment.
Simple misunderstanding.
None of us spoke any dutch.
Oh ! My gosh. Is this--
Is this a business meeting ?
I'm--I'm sorry if you sense
any tension.
Those two don't like each other
that much
'Cause they share
the same taste in women.
Sometimes they share the actual women.
- That's enough.
So what's this business meeting
about, bass ?
Still trying to fill your
daddy's shoes ?
Yeah, chuck, come on.
Tell him your idea.
- I'm opening a restaurant.
- Yeah, that's what he's telling people,
But downstairs, in the vault,
he's creating a club.
What did you say ? You wanted
to redefine decadence ?
You wanted to ruin my deal,
So you came here and brought
carter baizen as your wingman.
I told rufus about brown
Because i was
actually concerned for you.
I'm sorry to have wasted
your time.
Are you insane ? "Battlestar"
kicks "t.N.G.'S" ass.
What other show on the history
of the planet
Has been asked to speak
at the u.N. ?
Oh, perfect. An organization
that condemns terrorism
While secretly funding it Hosts a panel
for a show that glorifies terrorists.
Dude, i can't even look at you right now.
- Fine. Don't look.
What do you think ?
Trust me.
You don't want to know.
I do. I do want to know.
Oh, thank god.
Man, i'm really glad you
decided to come to the party.
Oh, thanks, man. That's...
Vanessa cares
about you a lot,
And i know that
she was hoping you'd come.
You know...
- yeah, yeah, i know.
there he is.
Oh, speak of the devil. Hey.
To, uh, to fresh starts.
I'm happy you're here,
humphrey.
me, too.
So, scott,
you are in big trouble.
I cannot believe you told
vanessa to take professor rifkin
For art in the world.
- Why ? I mean, i liked him.
Dude, he's totally old school,
not to mention just plain old.
i mean,
His lecture notes are literally
turning yellow with age.
Please do tell. What other
professors are you recommending ?
Yeah, let's hear it,
because katie's gonna have
To weigh in from now on.
- I-I'm at a party.
I really don't feel like
taking a test right now.
excuse me, everyone.
Can you please stop
with that noise ?
Hi, everyone.
- What the hell ?
most of you don't know me.
My name is blair waldorf.
But a lot of you know
My roommate, who threw
this amazing party--Georgina.
georgina !
Yeah, i know.
Georgina rocks, right ?
I mean, it's funny,
'cause i never knew
That a jesus freak
could throw such a good party,
But i guess i was wrong.
So, everyone, raise a glass
Or a... plastic cup of foam
To the coolest christian
i know--Georgina sparks.
Oh... my god.
This is a conversion party.
I can't believe it.
Georgina threw this party
And invited all her friends here
To convert the vulnerable freshmen.
It seems that blair waldorf
has finally found jesus
And invited him
to crash georgina's party.
- Carter, wait.
- So that's the whole reason
You wanted me to go out with you tonight
You knew i'd help you screw over chuck.
Chuck had screwed me over or--
Or at least i thought he had.
I wanted to get him back.
Serena, listen to you.
What's your deal ?
You're acting out
'cause daddy doesn't love you ?
Is that why you skipped out
on brown, too ?
Please.
No. I told you how i felt,
and you blew me off
Until you needed someone
to do your dirty work.
It's time to find
a new bad habit,
'Cause it's not gonna be me
anymore.
V.I.P. V.I.P. Room
at the monkey bar.
Monkey bar. Can't wait.
The limo's waiting downstairs.
We were worried about you.
We missed you so much.
I can't tell you
how my heart filled with joy
When we got your call
inviting us to share his glory
With all of your new friends.
I didn't invite you here.
We thought our little lamb
had been lost for good.
I am lost for good.
V.I.P. Room at the monkey bar.
Hope i see you there.
Monkey bar. limo's downstairs.
- Wait. What the hell are you doing ?
Georgina was turning everyone
against me.
You were just a casualty in
the battle for social dominance.
But don't worry.
Your loyalty's been rewarded.
Your name's on the list
at monkey bar. Yours isn't.
Georgina wasn't turning people
against you, blair.
You tried to bribe people
into being your friend
With sushi parties and gift
bags, and nobody liked it.
I don't need these losers to
like me in order to follow me.
Fear works better anyway.
Dan, you've experienced
social siberia.
If you want to try something
new, i'll see you at monkey bar.
I didn't know there was
a cool crowd at college.
Uh, i think you and i were
the only ones dumb enough
To believe that.
- Hey. So some of us were wondering
If you're gonna go
to monkey bar.
You know, just because
someone has to be on top,
Doesn't mean
it has to be blair.
Now when you get downstairs, You'll find
limos waiting to take you to the club.
And no sticking your head
out the sunroof.
This isn't
east ridge high school prom.
- Bye.
- hello. Hey, uh, excuse me.
Could i get
everyone's attention, please ?
Hey. Hi. Hello. I'm dan. I just
want to let everybody know here
That, uh,
blair waldorf over there
Invited some people
from georgina's past
Just so she could embarrass her.
But you know,
We're--We're all starting
college here, and college is
Supposed to be a place
where you're not judged
By what you believe
or--Or the friends you make.
You're here to make new friends
and start over, right ?
So last time i checked,
i mean, i think--
I think this--This party's pretty fun ?
- yeah.
Yeah, okay. So...
who wants to leave with blair ?
All right,
and who wants to stay here
Thank you.
You didn't have to do that.
Yeah, i did.
Let's get a beer.
Uh-Oh, b. Looks like your
new flock was just led astray,
And by dan humphrey no less.
I guess they know a false
prophet when they see one.
Hi.
- You mind if i join you ?
- It's your home.
Dan told you i was here ?
I was...
Glad you felt like
you could come here,
That you felt like
this was a safe place.
I'm really sorry, rufus.
I never meant for it
to get this messed up.
None of it was your fault.
Well, i didn't help matters.
I shouldn't have blown up at you
the way that i did.
So... talk to me.
Well, um...
I called brown
And deferred for a year.
Okay.
It may have been for
the wrong reasons at the time,
I-I think.
Well, no, i-I know that
it was the right decision.
I would have just been going
because my mom wanted me to go,
And while that's a good reason,
that's not good enough.
You know,
i did the same thing.
Well, it was rutgers,
not brown,
But i got in and i realized that if i
didn't pursue music, I'd never do it.
I wish i had
that same sense of purpose.
But i hope that if i--If i take
this time, that i'll find it.
Gosh.
How am i gonna tell my mom ?
Maybe i could help you figure that out.
I know i'm not the first guy
That your mom's brought
into your life,
But if you and eric
will let me,
I'd really like
to be more to you than...
Than just
lily's most recent husband.
Let me help you with this.
Wow. I, uh...
I would really appreciate that,
rufus.
I'm sorry, mom.
It wasn't my intention
to embarrass you or daddy.
i wouldn't be
doing any of this
If i didn't feel the way that i do.
I really, really like him, and...
Mom, please, don't be like that...
Mom ?
I guess we didn't fool
the doorman.
So you told your mom
the truth ?
I didn't want to risk
everything with my family
For some fling
that wasn't gonna last.
But ?
if your family can accept us together,
Maybe one day mine will,
too.
And if not ?
It's a risk
that i'm willing to take.
There's a reason
we never went downtown--
It's awful.
The minute you cross
14th street,
People forget
there's a class system.
B, you will find your place.
Just give it time.
No, i found my place,
and it's at the bottom.
It's a point of pride
now that i see who's on top.
Anyway, it's all turned out
for the best.
If i hadn't
been so distracted,
I would've been able
to force you to go to brown.
That's sweet, but no,
you wouldn't have.
I am sorry i pulled
a disappearing act on you.
I'm sure you'll find a way
to make it up to me...
In the handbag department
at bendel's.
Now normally i'd be
more worried about brown,
But you actually seem a lot
better than you have in a while.
I really am.
It was so much easier
When it was just about where
we sat on the met steps.
Yeah, but we've...
We've been here, done this.
But i was so good at it.
Well...
Then it's time
for a new challenge...
For both of us.
I'm glad
you're not going to brown.
I need you here.
Same.
Bye.
Bye, you.
I'm sorry i'm late,
But i have a good excuse.
What is this ?
A review of all the professors
i had this summer.
And look,
i even gave 'em grades.
Wow. This is amazing.
I'm sorry...
For that weird moment
with katie last night.
I think i got a little,
um, overwhelmed
From meeting
all your friends.
That's okay.
That was kind of the least weird
part of the whole night.
yeah, when dan--
He got on the mike
And he convinced everyone
to stay at the party, That was insane.
Is he usually like that ?
No.  dan is more of
a corner-Of-The-Party guy.
Should i call him,
see if he'll join us ?
Call him later. I just want
to be with you right now.
What do you want,
serena ?
There's a reason i always
come back to you, carter,
And it's not because you're my bad habit.
- What then ?
You're the only one who understood
Why i needed to find my father.
You were there for me during
all of that, and i trust you.
Anyone would have done
the same thing.
No, they wouldn't have.
And i don't want anyone else.
I want you.
Mm.
You were right
about the dorms.
The lighting is awful.
Are you okay ?
Mm.
I am now.
Hello ?
Hey. Do you want
to meet me and scott
So we can download about
the epicness last night ?
Mm. No, you know,
i'm still a little wrecked,
So, uh, i'll--
I'll call you later.
Okay. Bye.
Apparently,
higher education
Doesn't make
for smarter decisions.
So take out your notebooks
and sharpen your pencils, kids.
Gossip girl's going to college,
And this class has
a lot to learn.
~ Arcacadya Global Team ~
www.arcadya.net