Gossip Girl, here.
Your one and only source
into the scandalous life
of Manhattan's elite.
I can't have you spending time
with someone messed up with drugs.
Everyone'll be happy to know
that Damien and I broke up.
You touch this dress,
you'll never set foot in here again.
- You should do your own clothing line.
- I can model them. You can do this.
I didn't know you'd be such a thief.
Agnes, give me my dresses!
What are you doing?!
Hiding these feelings is killing me,
'cause I want totell how happy I am.
I think you should tell people.
I want to be as much a part
of your life as you'll let me.
I need someone to take over
operations of my hotel.
other people who'd do a better job.
They aren't my mother.
- Do we have ourselves a hotel?
- We do.
Subber East Siders
.: Arcadya Global Team :.
Season 03 Episode 16
The Empire Strikes Jack
www.arcadya.net
www.sous-titres.eu
They say the clothes make the man,
but who makes the clothes?
On the Upper East Side,
it's Eleanor Waldorf,
and we hear
her new line is to die for.
So, where are we going? I thought
everyone was coming over for brunch.
It's the first
since you're back at Lily's.
As hard as it is for me to admit,
some things are more important
than waffles.
And you're not gonna another day
sulking in that apartment.
- You grounded me.
- And I won't be able to unground you
until I know you're okay.
That's why we're going to Eleanor's.
- Wait. What?
- I was talking to Serena,
and she said that Eleanor is having
something called a pop-up fashion show
for her new junior line.
So I asked her
if you could help out.
Dad, the last time I worked for her,
it didn't exactly end well.
Remember?
But I also remember that my daughter
used to love working in fashion.
Listen, just give it a shot.
Your room's not going anywhere.
This isn't so bad, is it?
Thanks, dad.
I'll see you at home tonight,
after the show.
There's something about waking
up on the day of a fashion show.
The smell of fresh pleats
wafting through the city...
Nothing quickens your blood
quite like couture.
Ride with me uptown? My mother
would love to see you for breakfast.
I have a breakfast with my mother.
I'm so proud of you for
opening up to Elizabeth.
She earned my trust, and I, hers.
And she seems to be faring well
at the helm of the mighty empire?
She's a natural.
Have a perfect day.
Nothing says luxury quite
like your own private army.
Victor, is everything all right?
Mr. Bass, you need
to vacate the premises...
immediately.
I think you've misunderstood.
I may have put my mother in
charge for the time being,
but I'm not leaving the hotel.
Actually, sir,
these orders come from her.
My, look who's risen from the dead.
I just wanted to say thank you
so much for this opportunity.
And I've learned a lot
since the last time we worked together,
and I won't let you down.
Well, despite our troubled past,
as I told your father,
I am a firm believer in second chances,
so I even rehired your friend.
Hi. How are you?
90 days sober in A.A.
Good for you. Now come on.
What are you waiting for?
Get Agnes fitted.
I like to see my elves busy.
Clock's tickin'.
You ready? 'Cause this is it.
I'm ready. It's time.
We're just gonna go in
and tell them we're dating.
Exactly. It's no big.
Hey! It's the lovebirds.
He told you, didn't he?
She can read my mind.
Come on.
You couldn't wait to tell.
Speaking for everyone else,
I think it's great.
Now that the happy couple
is here, let's go eat.
Come on.
I have some very exciting news.
Mr. Conwell is flying in
from Salt Lake City
to see the show tonight.
Mr. Conwell?
He is the C.E.O.
of Conwell's department stores.
Blair, it's the biggest
retailer in the entire country,
and my first choice to
carry the new junior line.
What about Barneys or Saks
or Bloomingdale's?
No, my dear,
high-end has fallen on hard times.
Mr. Conwell can put my line in over
5,000 retail locations.
Where Bristol Palin shops?
Feed the masses.
Eat with the classes.
Although you do raise
a very good point.
My usual crowd of uptown socialites
and boho fashionistas
might give Mr. Conwell
the wrong message.
We need to surround him
with wholesome American girls-
the kind of girl
that he wants to shop at Conwell's.
I just had the most inspired idea.
Dessert at Momofuku after the show?
You should invite
all of your college girlfriends
to see the show tonight.
Mother, it's very last minute.
Miss Blair keep girls
on busy schedule.
Must beat drum, she says.
Baby beat dorota's stomach
like Lars from Metallica.
I need a gaggle of pink
sheet college freshmen.
Just bring 10 or 20,
no more than 30.
Tell them how important it is to you,
to me. I need Mr. Conwell to say yes.
But, miss Blair,
you have no friends.
Even N.Y.U.
minions very second-rate.
Actually...
There is one person at N.Y.U.
Who could help.
Did you send security
to kick me out?
Just listen. I- no.
Let me.
Morning, nephew.
What is this leech doing
stuck to my hotel?
Your hotel?
This is Elizabeth's hotel.
You're just a guest who's
no longer welcome here.
I'm sorry, Chuck.
You need to leave.
What? Wait.
What the hell is going on here?
Isn't it obvious?
You've been played, Chucky,
from the very beginning.
Now...
It's check-out time,
and we need to get your room ready
for, well, me.
Stop.
We hear Chuck's hotel is hanging
on by a thread...
And Jack's pulling all the strings.
Vanessa, I'm seriously
so happy for you guys.
Thanks. It's been really great.
It's been so easy to be with Dan,
knowing someone your whole life,
like you and Nate.
Yeah, it definitely
has its advantages.
When you've known someone so long,
you know, you're just
more comfortable. Nate and I
have no problem trying new things.
Not like that.
Just keeping the romance
and mystery alive.
You don't ever want
to fall into a rut.
I'm sure you and Dan...
Yeah, we always try new things.
So since you guys are out of hiding,
what are your plans tonight?
You should come
to Eleanor's fashion show.
Oh, no. Actually, we're gonna be
doing dinner at the loft.
- Vanessa's cooking up some,
- private dinner, Hmm? Sounds romantic.
No, it's not like that.
We're just, you know, watching movies,
cooking up some noodles.
Uh, it's kind of become
our Saturday tradition.
Agnes, can you put
your arms down, please?
Both arms.
Look, Agnes, I'm sorry for
how everything went down.
I shouldn't have gone behind your back
and cut you out of the fashion line.
I was gonna quit anyway.
Those dresses were lame.
Agnes, I'm trying to apologize.
You trusted me, believed in me,
and I betrayed you.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for torching your dresses.
Truth is, they were amazing.
Over it?
I missed you, bitch.
What is it?
Nothing.
Ugh. Well...
Truth is I was dating
this guy named Damien,
and he was a lot of things,
one of them being a dealer.
The sid to your Nancy.
That's awesome. What happened?
Well, when I didn't want to, uh...
Whatever with him,
he bailed. Now he just keeps
texting me for his stupid pills.
Sweetie, you can't let
him treat you like that.
I know, but whatever. Spin.
Hey, Damien?
- It's Jenny's friend Agnes.
- What are you doing?
Yeah, she wanted me to
call you to set up a swap.
We were thinking the
Waldorf pop-up show?
- Love it. Kiss.
- Agnes.
What? Chill out.
This is your payback, okay?
He's gonna show up tonight.
You're gonna wave the baggy
in front of his face and then
flush it down the toilet.
No one gets hurt, and you
get to show him who's boss.
Gotta take back your pride, babe.
All right. I'll admit that's
actually kind of brilliant.
We're total bitches.
I want to do something
special for Dan tonight.
Vanessa, I'm sorry.
I hope I didn't make you feel...
No, not at all. You were right.
Noodles and movies?
I mean, I just don't
want it to feel like
his one-millionth dinner
with the same girl he's
- known his whole life.
- Two words: role-play.
You know, that's-
that's not a terrible idea.
Why don't you do a date night
inspired by one of his favorite films?
He would definitely
not be expecting that.
So, I'll see
you at the loft at 6:00?
6:30 maybe.
Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- What's wrong?
We have to find Chuck.
You hate it?
I had forgotten how
talented you are.
I want to close with this.
And after the show is over,
you and I need to have a
talk about finding you
a more permanent position
with Waldorf designs.
Yeah. Wow. Eleanor,
thank you so much.
Yeah.
Treats were in your dresser,
just like you said.
Grabbed this clutch to hide 'em.
The eagle has landed.
Thank you, kali.
I'm sorry, Agnes...
I don't think I wanna go
through with this.
It's just that it's the
first time in weeks
that I've been able to
not think about Damien
and the first time in even longer
that I've actually been happy.
I don't know I forgot
how much I love this,
and I don't want to do anything
to mess it up, you know?
I'll just text Damien and, uh,
- tell him to forget it, okay?
- It's okay. I get it.
I was just trying to
help out an old friend.
Are you okay?
What's going on?
It would appear
we've all been players
in a Jack bass plot.
The reappearance of my mother,
the lawsuit...
it's all been part
of an elaborate ruse
to get me to sign over
my hotel to Elizabeth.
You have to admire his handiwork.
Have you spoken to your lawyers?
There's gotta be a way.
It turns out my lawyer was in on it.
Regardless, a suit to regain
control would take months,
in which time Jack would
have bankrupted the hotel,
making it easy pickings for
whatever vultures he has lined up.
My only hope is to talk
to Elizabeth alone,
convince her to sign the
hotel back over to me.
What makes you think
she's gonna do that?
This isn't her idea.
Jack has something on her.
I just need to figure out what.
I'll call you.
And all this time, we thought
Chuck got his dark side from his father.
- Maybe his mother's the evil.
- If she is his mother.
The story Elizabeth told me,
how do we even know it's true?
Chuck did a d.N.A. Test.
It was his guy at the N.Y.P.D.
But he probably
sent it out to a lab.
I wouldn't put it past
Jack Bass to fake it.
Whatever the truth is,
Chuck isn't ready to hear it.
In the meantime, I have to
get ready for a fashion show.
It's in 2 hours,
and I have 30 friends coming.
What? What friends?
Excuse me. Miss brandeis?
Can I help you?
I'm dorota.
Miss Blair would like to know,
what is your hourly
and if you have any friends,
like, 30?
30?
Jenny, can you help me get
these racks downstairs?
- Don't worry. I can watch your stuff.
- Thanks. Okay.
Careful, J.
The show's about to start,
and it looks like Eleanor's line
is going to bring a whole
new meaning to high fashion.
Like taking candy from a baby.
Helen, thank you so much for coming.
Storey, you look adorable.
B., I know what Chuck said,
- but shouldn't we...
- Do nothing.
He says he wants to handle
it on his own. We let him.
You don't think it's killing me?
- Oh, my God. Brandeis is here.
- Finally.
- Serena.
- Brandeis.
How's Congressman Wade?
- He's polling very well these days.
- Okay, so there's your target...
The guy over there talking
to my mom, Ed Conwell.
And remember, you guys
are my BFFs from NYU, so...
We got it, Blair.
We're closed for businessmen.
What? My mother said she wanted me
to pack the crowd with
wholesome American girls.
So you hired escorts?
B., you couldn't just tell your mom
you don't have friends at NYU?
Prostitutes are people, too,
and they have a lot
of disposable income.
Who are you?
Good evening, Daniel.
Hungry?
This is, this is just like...
"Rear window." I know.
Come on, people.
Trish, the girls look great.
Are they ready?
Show's in five minutes.
Agnes, where did you get that?
What? It's not like you're
gonna do anything with it.
It's just a little party.
What about your 90 days?
Look, I need the
waldorfs of the world
to think that I'm working a
program so I can get hired.
I'm not gonna let you risk ruining
- the entire show.
- What are you gonna do?
Waltz up to Eleanor and tell her that
your drug dealer dumped your virgin ass
and now the rest of her
models are high on his stash?
I will tell Eleanor
exactly what happened.
You know, this is my second chance.
And you don'twant to change your life,
but I certainly want to change mine.
I need to tell you something.
Not now, Jenny.
The show is about to start.
- Come on. Get the girls in line.
- But, I...
My goodness, getting models
to do anything, it's like herding cats.
Yes, but I really...
Jenny, go.
You know, I think it's time
for little J. to say good night.
I thought you wanted to
wait till the after party.
No. Let's put her to bed early.
I thought I was being
taken to the empire.
Elias and a few other
employees are still loyal.
I don't know how much my
Uncle has promised you,
but I'll double it if you
give me my hotel back.
Chuck, this was never about money.
Then what does Jack have on you?
'Cause it must be something
for you to do all this.
I love him.
I know it's very difficult
for you to understand...
Jack isn't capable of love.
He is using you.
He is stealing my hotel and
then he will leave you.
I know he's not perfect,
but he understands me.
He doesn't judge me.
Underneath it all,
he's a kind, loving person.
What kind of loving person
would convince you to do this to me?
When we started the game,
I told myself...
That you were just a stranger.
But I didn't know how much
I'd come to care for you.
So help me.
Give me back my hotel.
I can't.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry? That's it?
I need Jack.
And I believe he needs me, too.
He... he loves me.
If you believe that...
Then you deserve
whatever happens next.
Wow. I didn't realize Blair
had so many friends at NYU.
Yeah. Though at $300 an hour,
they don't come cheap.
Oh, it's Chuck. Hey.
I couldn't get through to Elizabeth.
What happened?
She thinks she loves Jack.
It's over.
The empire's gone.
I don't know. Um,
what do you say, Brandeis?
About five minutes? Uh, yeah.
Five minutes.
Maybe not. Hey, can you get Jack
to Eleanor's fashion show?
So? Uh, it was great.
It was great.
I'm not really a
shellfish kind of guy.
The little middle green
parts kinda, you know,
but the wine was amazing.
- Montrachet, just like...
- What grace Kelly brought Jimmy Stewart
That's right, yeah.
But a part of you wishes
we'd had ramen.
No. What? No seriously,
Vanessa, this was amazing.
In fact, I got you
a little surprise.
The student union is running
a mizoguchi marathon tonight.
That sounds amazing, but I thought
we'd do something different tonight,
break out of our rut.
Our rut?
We just started dating.
What do we do now that we didn't do
when we were friends?
Are you serious?
Obviously, besides that.
Is this what that whole "good evening,
Daniel" bit over there was all about?
I was just trying to put
a little mystery in our relationship
but if you'd rather just
do the same old thing,
Sorry.
I was just gonna pick up my 12-string.
No, why don't you stay?
I made dessert.
No. This is clearly a date.
You don't want it to be like
the nights the three of us hang out.
Really?
Because that sounds
exactly like what Dan wants.
- What's going on?
- I'm not sure.
Don't you just love the line?
Everybody looks good in it,
even the people
who shop in your store.
The clothes speak for themselves,
but, unfortunately,
our stores will never carry
your mother's line
if this is the type of clientele
that will be attracted to Conwell's.
What?
It attracts all kinds.
Everyone is here.
Yeah, I can see that.
Apparently...
Even prostitutes.
Eleanor wanted to congratulate
you on a great show
and say thanks
for all your hard work.
Thank you.
Last year she congratulated me herself
with a toast.
You deserve it.
We hear Eleanor's show
brought down the house.
Did you give her one or two?
Three.
Sounds like a night to remember...
if you can.
What's the matter, J.?
Champagne go to your head?
Did you put something in my drink?
Ever since I saw you at Eleanor's,
all I could think about
was payback for last year.
Then Damien's party favors just
happened to fall into my lap.
I wasn't gonna stand around
and watch Eleanor kiss your ass?
I was gonna have
my own fashion line.
Things were gonna change for me.
And then you had to go ahead
and do it all your way.
So here's to you, J.
Cheers.
Nate, I heard my nephew's
ready to cry Uncle. Where is he?
You can wait by the bar.
Now we just need Jack to be Jack.
Vanessa, this is fantastic.
I didn't realize you made flan.
I got the recipe off the Internet.
Did you do something to your hair?
Excuse me.
Son, I have to tell you,
this date is a disaster.
What's going on?
She thinksthat we're stuckin a rut.
A rut? You just started dating.
Yeah. I know.
You need to talk this through.
She's Vanessa. You're Dan.
You guys are best friends.
Did she just leave?
You whore and a half.
You couldn't just
keep it in your pants?
Conwell was about to buy
my mother's junior line until you-
Blair, I didn't cruise Mr. Conwell.
Then how does he know
you're a prostitute?
He doesn't. He knows Julian is.
He's supposed to see
him tonight, in fact.
Julian and Conwell part
every time he flies into town.
I'm really sorry, Blair.
We had no idea there'd be clients
here tonight. It was a total surprise.
I bet it was.
Brandeis, my apologies.
I'll be right back.
Mr. Conwell, a moment!
Your special friend, Julian,
wanted you to know that he's running
a little late tonight.
Blair, I have a family.
So do I, Mr. Conwell.
And when you love your family,
like we do,
you never want to see them
get hurt or disappointed.
What?
You want to take another
look at my mother's line?
Of course you can.
So we photograph Jack with a couple
of hookers and show it to Elizabeth?
Yes, and then she signs
the empire back to Chuck.
Okay.
You've only got one shot.
Evening.
Serena. Nate.
This is Jessica and Bethany.
Were you hoping to catch me
in a compromising position?
A little High School,
don't you think?
Leave the plotting to the experts.
Bethany, what were you saying
about sustainable energy?
- I'm gonna call Chuck.
- I'll find Blair.
Wait! Wait.
This little one's
not going home just yet,
we're gonna go see if we
can get this girl laid.
Pile in, bitches.
Spotted, little J.
passing out in a taxi.
Looks like somebody
better call the fashion police.
Is this where the bachelor party is?
- Yeah. You here to join us?
- Me? No.
But, my friend here,
she's ready to party.
Make sure you guys
show her a good time.
Thank you, Amy.
This is my first review
for "teen vogue." I'm very excited.
Mother!
Great news.
I just wanted to tell you
that Conwell's would be honored
to call itself your
exclusive retailer.
That is marvelous news,
isn't it, Blair?
Congratulations.
Of course we need to
make a few alterations...
hemlines, necklines.
You understand.
We could certainly discuss it.
Is that all?
And we'd like to change the name.
"Eleanor waldorf" sounds a
bit uppity and New York-ish.
Excuse me.
For the last 28 years,
every piece of clothing I have sewn
has carried the name
"Eleanor Waldorf."
My clothes are me.
My store is me.
Manhattan is an island
in more ways than one.
What works for you and yours
doesn't necessarily
translate to me and mine.
Mr. Conwell, I think you're
forgetting about something or someone.
Blair. I want to thank
you for your time,
but I do not think I will be
doing business with Conwell's.
Enjoy your flight back to Salt Lake.
Mother, what are you doing?
We could close this.
It was a stupid idea to begin with.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I would rather lose the
deal than lose myself.
Never hide who you are,
you remember that?
Everyone at NYU hates me.
- What?
- I have minions, of course, but...
They're hardly even
worthy of the name.
No, I don't understand. What about
all your friends from school?
They'll be anyone's friend...
For the night.
I was scared to tell you about NYU,
because I didn't want you
to be disappointed in me.
I did everything to try and fit in,
but I hate it there.
My girl.
One of the things that make
Waldorf women so special
is that we don't fit in everywhere.
But I don't feel like
I fit in anywhere.
That's 'cause you haven't found
the right place yet. You will.
One more round
and we're out of here.
Maybe I should stay and,
take care of blondie.
We'll tell the bartender
to call her a cab.
All right, first, shots!
Hello?
Hey. Where are you?
I've been calling you for...
I don't know where I am.
- I feel sick.
- Okay, Jenny, hold on one second.
Listen, just stay put.
- All right, I'm coming to get you.
- Hurry, please.
Can we talk?
So, uh,
Look, what happened tonight?
Don't you worry that we do all the same
stuff we did when we were best friends?
We go to movies,
we play scrabble with Rufus,
we go to coffee shops and make fun
of people. We are the exact same.
- Yeah, well, except...
- yes, I know. We have sex.
But I wanted to do something to say,
we're more than friends with benefits.
No, I was going to say except,
uh, it's not the same.
And if you give me a chance,
I want to take you
on the most romantic second first date
you've ever had.
Where?
Well, that's a surprise.
I hope you didn't bring me here
to gloat over your boyfriend's loyalty.
Chuck, I called you because...
This afternoon, I didn't
have the courage to tell you
that I... I signed the
hotel over to Jack.
Seeing you made me
realize what I'd done,
and so then I told him
he had to make a choice,
me or the hotel.
And what did my uncle say?
My flight to Zurich leaves at 10:00.
I wanted to say good-bye.
I'm sorry.
I tried.
Stay...
Not for Jack or the hotel.
Stay for me.
I already lost my mother once.
I'm...
not your mother.
I don't know if your real
mother is alive or not,
but I'm sure she loved you very much
and that she's nothing like me.
You're right.
Because my real mother could never
have done to me what you did.
Andy better be calling
that chick a cab, man.
That girl looked about 12.
Hey. Where is she?
Want to get out of here?
I live real close. Come on.
Where's Nate?
Is Nate your boyfriend?
'Cause he really
shouldn't have left you.
No, I don't...
- Who the hell are you?
- Get off her.
- I was helping her.
- Yeah, sure you were.
It seems chivalry
isn't dead after all.
Lucky for this damsel in a dress,
some things never go out of fashion.
How you feeling?
Steadier. How do I look?
I don't want to worry my dad.
Yeah, play the exhausted card, okay?
Hey. How was the show?
I thought you'd be
back a little sooner.
Yeah. Sorry I'm late.
The show was great, though.
Yeah, there were no cabs,
so I just figured I'd walk her back.
Yeah. I'm so tired.
I'm just gonna crash. But thank you
so much, dad. I love you.
- Thanks for seeing her home.
- Oh, yeah.
Good night.
So I finally told my mom about NYU.
B., I'm very proud of you for
telling your mother the truth.
Why? What good does
the truth ever do?
My mother can't help
me make friends.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Blair Waldorf?
Yes. Sorry to bother you.
But we're freshmen at
Columbia and, well...
We thought you were dead.
We haven't read about you
on "Gossip Girl" in forever.
What? You read "Gossip Girl"?
Of course. Everyone
at Columbia does.
I love your louboutins.
But...
The bow goes on the right.
Thank you. Bye.
S., what do you know about Columbia?
Hey, you forgot your purse.
You okay?
What's wrong with me?
Nothing is wrong with you.
What are you talking about?
Like, how did I end up here?
Jenny, look at me.
Okay, things...
Haven't exactly been
so easy for me either.
Now...
I'm with Serena, and I'm so happy.
Things will turn
around for you, too.
What if you're wrong, Nate?
What if everything we just-
It's Eleanor.
"Great job today. You're hired.
Lunch tomorrow."
See?
And I hope
you learn from this, okay,
mostly that I'm always right.
Oh, God, Nate,
thank you so much for tonight.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here. Try the bryndza.
Come on, swap.
The cabbage is my second favorite.
So this was your big romantic date,
having pierogies delivered
to my dorm room?
- Tell me you're not having fun.
- I am, but this isn't a date.
- This is what we always do.
- Except now we get to do this.
And it'sbeing friends with benefits.
No. No, because for me,
the benefit is that even though
we're doing the same things
eating pierogies and going to see Ugetsu
for the sixth time-
- We've only seen it four times.
- Well, now...
I get to do them with
you as my girlfriend,
which is why just
sitting here with you
is the most romantic
date I can imagine.
Humphrey, you just earned
yourself some extra benefits.
If you are what you wear,
you better dress the part you want.
A few lucky ladies can do no wrong.
Their look's perfection,
and they've got
accessories to match.
But most girls
get tired of the same old look,
and they'll do
about anything to get
the hot new piece on their arm.
And then there are
those with no vision of their own-
thieves of fashion
who'll steal the shirt off your back.
Did you change your mind?
I was hoping you changed yours.
Perhaps you need to see
the view from up here.
People really do look like ants.
How did I ever love you?
Fair question.
But if love won't tempt you,
how about money?
I'm leaving,
and I don't want anything.
Where are you gonna go?
You destroyed your
relationship with your son.
Who else do you have besides me?
I told Chuck I wasn't his mother
and that he deserves
someone better than me.
I'll warn you you're taking off just
when it's about to get fun.
I'm starting over.
I'm going to try to be
the person I forgot.
And always remember,
appearances can be deceiving.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Elizabeth?
Is dead to me.
She's gone.
- And the hotel?
- Lost.
What?
Sorry?
Don't be.
I'm not.
I've come this far without my mother.
I'm not backing down now.
Well...
If it's a war Jack wants,
then it's a war he'll get.
But whatever you wear,
always dress to kill.
X.O.X.O., Gossip Girl.