Previously on Sons of Anarchy.
Load the M4's and
Glocks in the truck, huh?
Torch it.
- Saw a lot of boot prints.
- Shit-eating Mayans, man.
- The M4's.
- Gone.
As are most of the Glocks.
- You got to see something else.
- Goddamn.
Get rid of the bodies.
Don't want this shit
hitting ATF's radar.
Found a box of his old shit
in the storage unit.
Just, like, pictures and journals,
things I never knew about him.
When you and Dad hooked up,
he ever talk to you about his vision,
about what he wanted from the club?
Jax is going through some shit.
He's asking me: did he want
to get into running guns?
He asked me if I thought
we needed to rebuild the factory.
I just want to make sure he's following
in the right father's footsteps.
We'll have all the Mayan intel
by the morning. We'll get our guns back.
Put the guns in the van.
Wire this shit hole up.
Got the good shit.
There we go, boys.
These muffins are great
with tequila, Bobby.
Shit is addictive.
Turning me into Fat Bastard.
Turbinado sugar, organic flour,
no processed shit.
Not that any of you give a damn.
You put hash in them?
You know my rule:
no bud before 9:00 a.m.
- I don't have that rule.
- Morning, kids.
Deal with the Niners
has officially closed.
Spoke to Laroy, and he is giddy
- about his new assault rifles.
- We're all about racial harmony.
Spend it wisely, boys. Might be a while
before we see any more gun green.
I love the green.
All about the Benjamins.
I just got an update
from my city hall snitch.
Looks like Hale's got a warrant
to search our warehouse.
Shit.
You're a little outside
your jurisdiction, aren't you, Hale?
Something blows up
this close to your town,
it would be bad law enforcement
not to look into it.
This is county property.
Sanwa sheriffs can handle this.
You know this guy?
Rodrigo Carpio.
Found him in the debris basin,
three bullets in his back.
Bluebird Supply business card
in his wallet.
From his rap sheet, I'm guessing
he was employed as security.
- No kidding.
- He died 50 yards
inside Charming.
Bluebird warehouse is part of my murder
investigation, and that's a warrant.
In case you'd never actually seen one.
- Glad your boy's gonna be all right.
- Yeah, thanks.
I'm sorry about last night.
Should've had that place leveled
before the Mayans ever got there.
Made a shit call.
Yeah, I'm the one who should've
been there blowing the shit up.
Should've never gone to Tahoe.
Everything happens for a reason.
If we hadn't hit that warehouse,
we never would've known
about the Nord-Mayan hookup.
Right.
I got to get this shit to Rosen's guy.
Need a big Jew brain to figure out
these Bluebird losses.
Not this big Jew brain, baby.
I can barely count my own fingers.
- Gonna go see the kid later.
- Yeah, I'll be there.
And I still want to do that dinner.
Maybe tomorrow night.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Did he say anything about
what he found in storage?
Doesn't matter.
Not his old man, stop worrying.
Hello.
Right.
That was Unser.
Got a protection run tonight.
What?
I got to tell you something, man.
I mean, it could be bad.
It already is.
Those two dead Mexicans in
the warehouse hole, I was hitting them.
Jesus Christ.
- Both of them?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Kind of a taco twofer thing.
Tell me one of them doesn't have
a belly full of Tigger juice.
Afraid they both do.
You did time, shithead,
you are in the DNA database.
Forensics team gets ahold
of those bodies...
I'll go pull them out of there.
Hale will be watching
that warehouse day and night!
Maybe Trammel can sneak me in.
He's a county sheriff,
he outranks the local PD, right?
You're just gonna stroll out of there
with two dead Mexi whores
- draped over your shoulders.
- I'll gut them dead bitches.
I'll flush their bellies with bleach.
No DNA.
What kind of nasty shit
did your mama do to you?
What do you mean?
Enough ammo in here
to give Halliburton a hard-on.
Holy shit.
Jesus Christ.
Tape it off.
Nobody enters.
Get me the ETA on that forensic team.
Mr. Bluebird just flew
into a brand-new cage.
Episode 102: Seeds
What were you thinking... brother?
I was thinking about getting my dick
sucked twice.
All anybody can prove is that
a couple of brownies swallowed your chum
and died hiding from the fire.
You didn't kill anybody.
It's not about the manslaughter rap.
The CSU team tests those bodies,
Tig's DNA puts the gun factory
at our doorstep.
And then ATF takes up permanent
residence in our collective rectums.
That warehouse sits on county property.
Hale will have to wait days
to get San Joaquin to shake loose
a forensic unit.
It's a local case.
County won't get involved.
Hale'll just wind up borrowing
a crime scene unit from Lodi.
Big Otto's sister still works
for the A.D.A. in Lodi.
Call her. See if there's a forensic team
heading this way.
I gotta have a talk with Unser.
Maybe I can convince the chief to...
put a leash on his hyperactive deputy.
Unser's just waiting
for the clock to run out.
That old boy's a lame duck.
So your boy, not really a team player.
I've made several gestures
of friendship. He's declined every one.
Hale's not interested in friends.
He thinks Charming's stuck in 1969.
Wants to bring it into the 21st century.
Hale is a half-bright clerk
with a Wyatt Earp complex.
Hardly seems like a guy with a vision.
Don't underestimate him.
He's tight with city council
and his old man's
got deep political ties
in Northern Cali.
Yeah. But you're the boss, right?
Come on, Clay.
Since they found the cancer last year,
I got one foot out the door.
I mean, the squad's his now.
Be official in a few weeks.
This uptight piece of shit
is gonna make our lives miserable.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
There's nothing I can do about it.
The doctor and my wife,
they're making me step down.
I'm sorry. It's done.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
This doesn't mean we can't keep
our business arrangement.
Me and you, we had a good thing
going for a lot of years.
We need each other.
Yes, we do.
What's the run?
Got Blu-rays and iPods
heading down to San Jose.
Goddamn niggers have been jacking
the shit out of them.
Keep your eyes open on this one.
I'll make sure they get
where they're going.
How you doing, Jax?
Heard about Wendy and the baby.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
You know, I took a ride out
to the streams today.
Saw that warehouse that burned down.
Outside your jurisdiction, ain't it?
You ever hear
of a Bluebird Supply Company?
Apparently they hold
the title on that parcel.
Never heard of them.
Whole area was littered
with casings and gun parts.
That warehouse was a weapons depot.
No kidding?
Chief Unser's retiring
at the end of this month.
I'll be stepping into those shoes.
Unser's always had a look-the-other-way
policy with the Sons of Anarchy.
- Unser's a lazy drunk.
- I will not look the other way, Jax.
Just a friendly heads up.
We're all free men,
protected by the Constitution.
You look any way you want, Chief.
- He's moving around a lot more.
- Yeah. All his vitals are up.
Any permanent damage?
Because of the drugs, brain or anything?
Can't know for sure,
but everything so far
points to full recovery.
How long's he gotta be in that thing?
Could be weeks.
But
he'll be in the NICU
for at least two or three months.
Hey, look...
I'm sorry about last night.
- I wasn't...
- I really don't want to know.
Right.
What?
Just figured you'd land
a million miles from this place.
You always hated it here.
Oh, I didn't hate Charming, Jax, just...
me in it, at the time.
Looks like Wendy's gonna be okay.
Define "okay."
We're taking her through sedated detox.
She'll be out for a couple of days.
You two...
Are you together?
No, I filed over a year ago.
She got clean about ten months back,
we tried to reconcile.
Didn't work out too well.
Looks like one good thing
came out of it.
Yeah, I guess it did.
I should get going.
Yeah, I'm late for rounds.
It's good to have you back.
I'm gonna need the truck.
Why can't you take the wagon?
We're three months behind.
I got to lock it in the garage,
or they'll repo it while I'm at work.
I don't know how to get
in front of this shit.
Getting buried here, Donna.
I'll pick up some weekend work.
You'll get that pay bump soon.
We're going to make it through this,
baby.
I promise.
We'll figure it out.
Shouldn't you be at the mill?
I'm on my way. I gotta ask a favor.
What's up?
Three months behind on Donna's
car payment, they're gonna repo it.
- I hate doing this.
- If you ask me for money,
I can't help you.
I just made the quarterly
insurance payments.
I'm going to be tapped
until the end of next month, okay?
Look, I'm sorry, son.
That's all right.
Thanks, Pop.
Clay
is making a protection run tonight
for Unser.
It's low profile shit. You ride along,
- scare off the bad guys, huh?
- I think I'm on Clay's shit list.
Doubt he'd put me on it.
- Then why don't you make it right?
- I don't know.
I don't know
what the hell's wrong with you.
Why don't you quit whining,
grow a dick
and take care of of your business?
Jimmy Cacuzza called.
The Italians want to place an order.
- I didn't know what to say.
- How about the store burned down,
they missed the fire sale?
I talked to Otto's sister,
and Lodi Forensic Team will be here
first thing in the morning.
And the shit keeps piling on my head.
Only one thing is gonna stop
that Lodi forensics team
from getting to our warehouse.
And that's another murder in Lodi.
I don't know.
Hale's on red alert. Mayans, Nords...
everyone's twitchy as hell, man.
- It's not a good time to kill things.
- It never is,
but we talk about protecting Tig here.
And staying out of ATF's crosshairs.
We hit the projects,
we find ourselves a scumbag,
a dealer...
We should off a couple of Nords,
Clay, is what we should do,
all right? We should just do that,
then we'll dump the bodies in Lodi.
It buys us some time to get
those Mexicans out of the hole.
It sends a message to Darby...
Kill two birds with one crow.
Very clever,
with the cops eyeballing the warehouse?
- Doesn't matter.
- I'll handle that. You set it up.
What if I could do this
without spilling blood?
This isn't me tripping some guilt shit
because of my kid.
This is about one of us
thinking straight.
Brains before bullets, right?
Let's hear it.
All we need for a murder
are bodies and a crime scene.
Jackie boy, now you lost me.
Skeeter. He's always got more
gambling debt than he can handle.
I'll make it worth his while.
- The cemetery guy?
- Cash for cadavers. I like it.
I give a Lodi a front-page murder.
We don't stir up another shit storm
to bite us in the ass.
What about educating Darby?
I'll figure that out.
The important things is to keep
your DNA out of the Petri dish.
Protect the club.
Path of least resistance
always best, right?
We'll do it your way, VP.
All right.
Don't make me regret this.
- They really cremate bodies here?
- Yeah, we do.
Hey, guys, what's going on?
- Need a favor, Skeeter.
- Christ, man, now's not a good time.
Got a supervisor crawling up my ass.
Relax. Not here to make a deposit.
Actually, it's a withdrawal.
Need two bodies, fresh.
You serious?
For what?
Well, I could tell you, then
I'd have to stuff you in the furnace.
Two dead ones?
That's, that's crazy shit, man.
I'm sure you took a beatin'
at the Golden Gate this weekend.
No, I stopped the ponies, man.
I stopped it all.
Gambler's Anonymous three-three,
three months now.
You're kidding.
You don't want the money?
Working a program, you know?
Jesus Christ.
Something
you might be able to get for me.
What's that?
Emily Duncan.
She's one of our Friday night whores.
She loves a good punch up her knickers.
Yeah, no kidding.
I've been trying to push up
on that for a long time.
You want to hook up with the crow-eater,
I'll make it happen.
Shit, you got a deal.
I'm not cremating anything
till the end of the week.
- Need two by tonight.
- I'm prepping a closed coffin.
Some phone guy took
a header off the top of the pole.
White guy?
I'll take it.
- Need a Mexican guy, too.
- Buried one this morning, cheap seats.
- Should still be fresh.
- What do you mean?
- That we got to dig it up?
- Who said anything about "we"?
This is so wrong, man.
This is so wrong.
Hey, Darby. Here, I got you a tamale.
I never should have led you
to their gun warehouse.
I knew stealing those M4s
was a bad move.
None of my moves are bad.
I lost my best guy,
niggers got their gats back and
you're out three men and a warehouse.
What the hell would you call it?
Insurance covers the warehouse...
and I've always been
about survival of the fittest.
If any of Clay's guys
recognize Whistler,
they're gonna come at me...
hard.
We need to combine forces now.
Strike first.
Let the asshole sweat.
Spin a little doom about what they saw.
We'll learn from their next move.
Their next move is gonna be putting
a bullet in my goddamn dome.
Now we made a deal: we work...
Our deal was me getting the guns
Sam Crow keeps feeing my competition.
I get the gats, I cross the Niners.
- Starting a war's not smart.
- I got a news flash for you, La Bamba.
I don't give a shit about
some wetback-nigger beef.
The only reason that I'm at this table
is because I need muscle
to put Sons of Anarchy
the hell out of Charming.
Now you comprende that?
I'll give you some guys to watch
your back in case they retaliate,
but we've got to let this shit
calm down before we make our next move.
And don't worry.
We'll both get what we want.
Where's my goddamn Suburban?
Who the hell is that?
That, me ol' mukker,
is 130 pounds o' cock-ridin' gidy.
- Hey, Jax.
- Hey.
Chibs said you were looking for me?
I'm Emily.
Right! Shit. Sorry.
Come in.
Sit down.
- Nice room.
- Yeah.
So,
I need you to do a favor
for the club, Emily.
Really? Sure. I mean,
what do you need?
What can I do?
You know Skeeter, right?
Yeah, that guy's been trying
to get in my pants since high school.
Need you to let him in.
Are you serious?
Dude, that guy burns dead bodies.
He creeps the shit out of me.
I know, but we need Skeeter
to do us a good deed.
And the only thing he wants in return...
is the hand of beautiful
Emily Duncan.
- I'm not some whore.
- Come on.
- It'll be our secret.
- Yeah.
Cross my heart.
I need you, Emily.
Oh, boy.
You do me, I do him.
Fair enough.
- Do me a favor?
- Absolutely.
Put your cut on.
I'm all about the service, darlin'.
That's great
Not only do you stink,
but you're a fat bastard, too.
Beware the zombie bikers!
Jesus Christ,
you scared the piss out of me!
- Who's your friend?
- I hate this shit.
It's really bad karma,
digging up a grave, man.
Nah, as long as it's not your grave,
karma's just fine.
So, how are we gonna get him out?
I think we're gonna need a tow truck.
Jesus Christ, these guys stink.
We'll leave Darby some good
dead Mexican stench.
Dude, I... look,
I tell them I lost it in battle,
all they want to do
is wrap their patriotic lips around it.
Shit!
That asshole!
They made me spill my beer!
Gemma.
- Abel seems better. Stronger.
- Yeah, he's a lucky kid.
Both he and his mom
escaped death in the same night.
I heard about Wendy.
Very sad.
I can't say I'm surprised.
Guess you wouldn't be.
- Something on your mind?
- No.
Something weighing on yours?
Junkie tell you something?
No, she's still sedated.
But I talked to her
after that baby was born.
She was crushed.
She hated herself,
but she wanted to live.
No, somebody else
popped her with that needle.
Or at the very least
gave her the loaded gun.
Guess you think I'm that somebody?
Guess I was the one shooting it
into her fingers and toes
the whole goddamn time
she was pregnant, too.
No, that sin's on her.
If I were a cop, I'd call that motive.
Thank God you're only a doctor.
We'll see what Wendy says
when she comes out of detox.
Or maybe I'll bounce
my theory off of Jax,
see where he lands on it.
That's how you'll win back his heart,
accusing his mother of trying
to murder his ex-wife?
- Come on, you are smarter than that.
- I am not trying to win back anybody.
No?
Then why'd you come back to Charming?
Because of the job.
Which one, doctor or detective?
You still think you can just say
or do anything you want
in this town, don't you?
Everything comes round, Gemma.
No one is untouchable.
You want to touch me, sweetheart?
That make you happy?
You're an idiot, it's not gay.
I've been shaving my shit for years.
- It's totally gay.
- Whatever.
Shit.
He spotted the smashed front end.
Cops run those bogus plates,
they're gonna search
that SUV from top to bottom.
We got two dead bodies in there, man.
Lodi's got a sky team.
We'll never get away
knowing this piece of shit.
Put the gun away.
What's up?
Jesus Christ!
Get back here!
Come on, piggie!
Come on!
Run, prospect, run!
Get in, you faggots!
Run, baby!
Run, boys! Get in!
Bye, copper! Bye!
Thanks.
I haven't had a chance to talk to you
much since you got out of the joint.
Not much to say.
You know what it's like.
- Takes a while to adjust.
- Yeah.
Hear Donna's having a rough time of it.
Think it was easier for her
when I was inside.
She knew what to do then.
Gets that way.
Sometimes the people we love
just don't know the right move.
Crippled by all the shit
they're afraid of.
Donna's not crippled.
She's pissed.
How about you, Ope?
You pissed?
I mean, guys get locked up,
they resent the loss of freedom,
start doubting the choices they made,
the right and wrong of it all.
I got no resentments.
Attaboy.
Uncle Jimmy called.
I just got a heads up
about a hijack zone.
- Where?
- Coleman off-ramp.
Think we should go in the back way,
take 101 instead.
You sure you guys know
where the hell you're going?
You sound like my wife.
Okay, bring it forward.
Little more... little more.
Good.
That sounded nasty.
Someone call Greenpeace,
you're saving a Mexican whale.
Come on, Shamu.
Dude...
- Get the blood.
- Come on!
Make it look real.
You ain't icing a cake, prospect.
It's a crime scene.
Let's go.
I know, I know.
All right, let's do it.
What a beautiful thing!
All right, plant the gun,
I'll leave the message.
All right, let's go!
Circuit City, kiss my guinea ass.
I could move this whole load
for you in two days.
- Good.
- 50-50?
Just throw me ten percent.
It's my little gift to you.
We had a little setback
with the business.
Yeah, we heard rumors.
- Wetbacks, right?
- Yeah.
It might be a minute
before we're up and running.
I'd appreciate
if you and some of the other crews
would be a little patient,
give us some time to get on our feet
before you found another distributor.
We might need to go elsewhere
in the short term,
but I'll let the boys know.
They don't any big gun business
with anyone except the Sons.
- Thanks, Jimmy.
- Yeah.
Make it fall off the truck, boys.
You knew all this was going down?
Well, I had it in the works
but I wasn't sure till I got the call.
What about your deal with Unser?
We're supposed to protect the cargo.
Chief Unser needed a wake-up call.
We needed a goodwill gesture.
It'll all work out.
You wanted in, right?
Yeah, I did.
- Wait a minute. You see what I see?
- Aye.
That's that douchebag that cut us off.
Been a very long night, brother.
Come on, won't take long.
Pass me one of those Hostess dumb dicks.
What are you doing?!
Don't ever cut me off again, shithead.
- My store! This is my store!
- What are you doing?!
Why don't you come at me now, asshole!
You okay, Jackie boy?
Holy shit!
What the hell happened out there?
O'Brien Electronics
is my biggest account.
Probably the last time they'll use
Unser Trucking
to transport their precious cargo.
What are you doing, Clay?
Just keeping a good cop
on the job, is all.
You don't step down
for another six months.
You let us rebuild.
And keep Hale off my goddamn back.
If I say no?
Then I'll make sure every truck
leaves this yard hits a roadblock.
- Where's my driver?
- He-he's getting patched up.
We convinced him
to keep this incident in-house.
Jesus Christ.
This how you treat an old friend?
Nah.
It's how I treat an old cop.
Sorry, Mrs. Winston.
We can't take your checks anymore.
The last two bounced.
Okay.
I'll just pay cash.
- What's this?
- Rest of your groceries.
Opie's out now.
We don't need any more charity.
Thanks.
It was never charity, Donna.
It's what we do.
You're family.
I have my family back.
I don't need yours.
Look...
I know what you went through.
Been there, with two husbands.
Lose your man, kids lose their dad,
you get pissed off.
Want to blame the club.
But Sam Crow is not the enemy.
It's the glue.
The one thing that will always be there
to pull you through the ugly shit.
Got to stop fighting us, Donna.
You need us.
I married Opie.
I didn't marry the club.
You have no idea what I need.
We're having a little family
dinner tonight.
You and Ope should come.
Bring the kids.
You might actually have a good time.
Don't say anything else.
My Martha Stewart's wearing real thin.
You know where we live.
Why'd you pull my detail
off the warehouse?
I was paying overtime for six unis
to sit on a 20
that's not even in our jurisdiction.
This is my case,
and overtime is not really
your concern anymore.
I'm afraid it is.
Not stepping down yet.
What are you talking about?
That's already done.
No, it's not.
Gave city council a heads up.
I'll be keeping the badge
for another six months.
What the hell are you doing, Unser?
Right now, getting a haircut.
Bullshit.
You've always been in Sam Crow's pocket.
- This is about me.
- Stop talking, son.
One more wrong thing
comes out of your mouth,
and I'll rip that badge off
your puffed-out chest.
Sorry, Floyd.
That boy needs a hot shave.
Yes, he does.
"Most of us were not violent by nature.
"We all had our problems with authority,
but none of us were sociopaths.
"We came to realize that when you move
your life off the social grid,
"you give up the safety
that society provides.
"On the fringe...
"blood and bullets are the rule of law,
"and if you're a man with convictions,
"violence is inevitable."
I hope they looked better
than this when they blew you.
A little.
Jax?
Jesus, it smells like old socks
and pussy in here.
Hey, darling.
They're having a sale on toiletries.
I picked you up some things.
Thanks, Mom.
You okay, baby?
You look exhausted.
Long night.
That your dad's stuff
you found in storage?
Yeah.
Some pictures, a few Harley manuals,
a bunch of Nam shit.
'80s hair.
How hot was I?
Smokin' hot.
You said you read something?
A few journal entries, nothing much.
I'd love to read it.
Your father was a real good writer.
Always had a knack for it.
You know, I'm the one who bought him
that old Selectric.
- Didn't know that.
- Yeah.
Jax! Clay wants you.
Custom job.
Unser's not retiring.
What did you do,
threaten to rape his daughter?
That's a little harsh.
Maybe the old man's
not ready for the gold watch.
I just got back
from that Bluebird warehouse.
There were two dead women in the utility
hatch before my guys got pulled off.
They're gone.
They could've been napping.
You guys.
Cruising around here like heroes.
And you and I know the truth.
What truth is that?
You're white trash thugs
holding on to a dying dream.
That is so poetic, Chief.
I'm sorry,
I guess it's just Deputy Chief.
Right?
It doesn't matter if I'm chief or not,
you can't stop progress.
It won't be long before Sam Crow
is just an ugly memory
in the history of Charming.
So you enjoy the ride...
while you still can.
- You go get rid of those bodies.
- Yeah, a'ight.
Should we say a prayer or something?
You know any Bible passages
about lost semen?
And may the ray...
ray of sunshine warm your souls.
Amen.
Let's burn 'em.
Jax? I need some corn.
Subtitles: Michvanilly, Tagne