Previously on Sons of Anarchy
Found a box in the storage unit.
It's like pictures and journals.
- Things I never knew about him.
- When you and Dad hooked up,
he ever talk to you about his vision,
about what he wanted from the club?
Jax is going through some shit.
He's asking me,
did he want to get into running guns?
Tonight he said that maybe
we shouldn't rebuild the factory.
I just want to make sure he's following
in the right father's footsteps.
Sam Crow's been in this town
since I was a kid.
My old man was a county judge.
Saw some of the guys catch their due,
but for the most part,
Clay and the others keep slipping
through the legal cracks.
Been chatting folks up
last couple of days.
Most of them got pretty quiet
when I ask about Sons of Anarchy.
Clay's got some of the locals
convinced his brand of outlaw justice
- keeps away the corporate bogeyman.
- I'd say he's right.
Franchise development
in Charming's pretty much nonexistent.
Been jonesing for a Starbucks
since I got here.
Sam Crow isn't stonewalling
growth by themselves.
They're getting a lot of help,
some of it from inside
this department.
Got to bring it in through here.
Afraid the amped-up carb's going
to throw too much heat on the line.
Might.
That new Graytex cable can take
a shitload of heat, though.
We got troubles.
Want to tell me what the fed's
doing in Charming?
Showed up two days ago.
Chicago division.
- Looking into Sam Crow.
- And I'm just finding out now?
- How long is he going to be here?
- No idea.
He's collecting intel, fact-finding.
Didn't go into too much detail.
I don't want you out rogueing
with this guy, you hear me?
Stick to Charming business.
This fed wants anything,
he runs it through me.
Oh, of course.
You're the chief.
That's right.
I'm the goddamn chief.
We've taken every precaution
to stay out of ATF's crosshairs.
No busts,
no investigations for five years.
- We don't know this guy's here for us.
- Hale flagged Bluebird
as our gun warehouse.
He's pissed off we made Unser crush
the case and he called in the feds.
- I think it's got to be about us.
- Be my guess.
We got a garage full of 25-to-life.
Any legit place we store those guns
is a straight line back to us.
Can't Rosen get us
some storage short-term?
He's killing Bluebird, man.
He's setting up a dummy corp.
It takes a few weeks.
We got that call
from Jury last week.
Mayan's pressing the Devil's Tribe
to pay him vig,
to keep running book
and pussy out of Nevada.
Look, maybe I do head
to Indian Hills.
Offer Jury some advice,
he offers our AKs a safe house.
No, that's a risky run, brother.
Knowing Nevada's Mayan territory.
No, they're still looking to settle
a score from our little raid.
The Mayans know that
the Tribe's a brother club.
Part of asking for that vig
is about shitting on us.
They knew Jury would call.
- Theywill be watching.
- That's what I'm saying.
That's why just me and you go.
Under the radar.
We bring the guns in the same way.
And you think
you can bring Jury on board?
Shit, my dad saved his ass
in Tay Ninh.
He owes the Tellers a chit.
Look, man,
we're not going to go cowboy.
I promise.
Promise.
Low-profile.
I don't want no wetbacks
knowing we crossed into NV.
They pull this off,
I want you and Juice
driving the barrels.
Done. We'll need something big,
though.
I'll call Unser.
- Give me a minute.
- Yeah, I'll find you.
Everything okay?
I was hoping you could help
with the Cutlass.
It's in pretty sad shape.
Shit.
This is your dad's, right?
It was in the garage
under two tons of old newspapers.
Why don't you bring it in back.
- Have Lowell take a look at it.
- Okay.
Thanks.
I was hoping you could give me
a lift home.
Actually, I'm just heading out
for a couple of days.
Okay.
Anything come up with the baby,
who should I call?
He's out of the woods, right?
Just in case of procedural stuff.
Just let my mom know
if you need anything.
Everything okay?
Yeah, fine.
She's just here to get her car fixed.
- Could you give Tara a ride home?
- She's got to leave the Cutlass here.
- That's okay. I'll just take a...
- Love to give the good doctor a lift.
- Where you going?
- Visit Uncle Jury.
Nevada?
By yourself?
With Bobby.
- Does Clay know?
- Relax, Mom, it's going to be fine.
You sent him into Nevada?
It was his idea.
It's club business.
He has a ten-day-old kid.
He's distracted.
- You have to protect him.
- Protect him?
- From what?
- Himself.
He's fine. Relax.
And this one.
What's she doing here?
Anything she can
to get close to Jax.
Maybe she just needs a tune-up.
Didn't trust her then.
Don't trust her now.
- Hey.
- Hey, Gemma.
Back it up, prospect.
Come on. Back it up.
Lowell, my back tire needs air.
I gotta admit, Clay's old lady
gives me a serious MILF chubby.
Hey, I brought that car
out of the garage.
It's clear now.
If you need me
to clean it out again, I can...
Clip a truck from Muntz's tonight.
Make it look like you stole it.
Cancer boy wants deniability.
MILF chubby?
It's like a compliment,
you know, 'cause she's hot.
Stop.
What do we got?
Mayans.
So much for low-profile.
Episode 4: Patch Over
Two on three?
Hey, Doc,
got to sign these.
Thanks a lot.
Mind if I smoke?
And if I said yes?
Right.
Must be strange being
in that house alone.
Everybody gone.
Hard to get lonely.
My dad was a bit of a packrat.
Can barely turn around without
stepping on some piece of history.
Clay's the same way.
Never throws anything out.
Still has underwear from 1967.
Me, I hate clutter.
I get that.
Thanks.
Want to tell me why you're carrying?
The gun in your bag.
You went through my bag?
I spotted it.
I'm very observant.
I started carrying it
when I was in Chicago.
I lived in a rough neighborhood.
Haven't gotten around
to get rid of it yet.
Beretta's not an old tampon.
You don't just forget
it's in your bag.
- Is it registered?
- I have a permit. It's legal.
You know how to use it?
Yeah. I do.
Gimme the pre-pay.
So, Mayans spotted us.
Well, this forces our hand.
Can't risk bringing those AKs
in with the Mayans onto our visit.
- We need a bigger presence.
- Why don't the Vegas boys head up?
Oh, no, I'm talking
about a permanent presence.
It'll be months before
the warehouse is up and running.
Indian Hills could be really useful.
You talking patch-over?
I don't know, Clay.
Tribe might've started outlaw,
but now,
I mean shit,
they're bookkeepers and bouncers.
They're earning outlaw-sized money.
It's just a matter of time
before the Mayans push 'em out.
They need us
for their own protection.
Jury was a real good friend
of my old man's, Clay.
I don't feel right,
slamming a patch, no warning.
It's good for both clubs.
Now if you don't want to break it
to him, I'll tell him myself at church.
We're riding to Indian Hills.
Mandatory.
Patching over the tribe.
- What, you serious?
- Do I look serious?
We're-we're short, I mean,
Chibs, he's up North with McKeavy.
Anybody visiting?
Happy's down from Tacoma.
Doing an Autism Run.
He's got Lorca, Bully, Donut,
- couple prospects with him.
- Get 'em.
Okay, well...
Jury's got all that beautiful pussy,
man.
It's gonna be
a four-shot patch-over party.
Unfortunately,
you're driving the precious cargo.
No, no, Christ.
Clay, come on. You need me...
Last time you had free range on pussy,
you throat-pumped two brownies,
your DNA almost brought us down.
Besides,
you're the only one
I can trust to handle this.
Come on. Hauling barrels?
Let the prospect go with Juice.
What prospect?
Which one is it?
What are you an idiot?
Take the picture.
- Can't find the button. Sorry.
- Jesus.
Here, let me do it.
Holy shit. I...
- told him not to sit on your bike.
- That's all right.
Look like a guy who knows
how to get his way.
You do that to her lip?
- Bitch has a mouth on her, you know?
- Sure, I get it.
- So you like Harleys, huh?
- Yeah, they look good,
but I'm way into the slant bikes
for their speed, you know.
Right, right.
All right.
- Say cheese.
- Cheese.
Nice.
That's before.
Before?
You don't ever sit
on another man's bike, asshole.
- Holy shit.
- Shut up, bitch!
Little respect for the fairer sex.
That's after.
- Where you headed?
- No place special.
Me, too.
I'm Suzi.
I'm Jax.
Just don't ask any questions, okay?
I'll let 'em know you're with me.
You are the James T. Kirk
of the MC world.
Going where no man has gone before.
Let me tell you, brother,
I think every man's gone there before.
- Jackson Teller.
- Uncle Jury.
- You guys rember Bobby.
- Bobby.
- Needles, how you been?
- Bobby Elvis.
MC royalty in the house, folks.
Jax Teller and Bobby Elvis
of the Sons.
Welcome.
- Let's make 'em feel at home.
- Good to see you, man.
We got 'em all shapes and sizes.
I think I could be in love
with that perfect darkness.
Daytona,
come on over and say hi to Bobby.
Daytona? As in 500?
As in 1200.
A night.
My treat, brother.
Show me the way.
- That your old lady?
- Nah.
Picked her up at the border.
Little doe in the headlights.
Cherry.
This honey's with Jax.
- Show her the ropes, darling.
- Sure thing.
Come on, sweetheart.
I'll see you in a couple of days.
Call me. Let me know he's okay.
You know I'll drive out there.
- How embarrassing would that shit be?
- I'll call.
Started the sports book
with the escorts and strip clubs.
First stop over the border.
Must be churning some serious cash.
You got the Mayans circling
for a percentage.
They're jamming me up, Jax.
If I don't pay the Mexicans,
turn my business inside out.
If I kick up a vig up to 'em,
I disrespect you guys.
- Tribe attracts a good membership.
- 18.
Real good boys.
You still get along with local law?
Douglas County.
- Sheriff likes the girls.
- Right.
- How you doin', babe?
- I'm good.
Hey, girls,
the beers are warm.
We just pulled those.
I'll get those. Excuse me.
So, how we gonna handle the Mayans?
We're hoping actually maybe
you could help us out with a problem.
Sure.
Got a garage full of AK-47s.
Need a place to assemble
and store 'em
till we find a buyer.
It's a temporary thing.
Got a strip club off out on 95.
Huge basement. Private.
Sounds perfect.
Appreciate it.
You'll talk to Clay,
let me know
how to handle this Mayan thing.
You can talk to him yourself.
He's on his way.
Clay's comin' out?
Yep.
- It's about the future, Jury.
- Future of what?
The tribe.
Jesus, Jax.
Patch-over?
It's time, Jury.
This whole area is blowing up.
We don't patch you over,
Mayans will run right through you.
We get a foothold in Nevada.
You get status to protect
your business.
Best move for both clubs.
Lot of my guys aren't Sam Crow.
The ones that are cut out for it
will make it. Others will fall off.
I'm not a young man
anymore either, Jax.
I don't know how much outlaw
I got left in me.
You'll do fine, Jury.
Never throw
these guys any lip, okay?
I didn't. Just asked him a question.
Yeah, that's even worse.
Where's Bobby?
- Out front.
- All right.
So, how long you been his old lady?
- We just met.
- Yeah, that's what I thought.
You better pay close attention
to what I do, baby girl.
Whose old lady are you?
No one's yet.
But soon one of these guy will realize
what a fine old lady I'm gonna make.
How long have you been doing it?
It's about three years.
You and Jury get into it?
Didn't see it coming.
I don't know if the old man's going
to be able to hang a reaper on his back.
This shit don't feel
good to me, Bobby.
Clay's making a mistake.
Tribe ain't SOA material.
You all right, brother?
Yeah.
- Why?
- Just checking in.
You've been through a lot of shit
in the last couple of weeks:
baby, junkie...
Maybe all that noise in your head's
got you turned around a bit.
Noise in my head?
You got something to say, man,
just say it.
You been second-guessing Clay
ever since your boy was born.
Club's picking up on it.
You got to get right with that.
Next time this gavel slams down...
will be the last
for the Devil's Tribe.
History between our clubs...
Jury and John Teller
were in the same platoon in 'Nam.
Needles' brother's a 20-year member
of our Fresno charter.
We have a deep respect
for each other.
Now
it's time to become brothers.
I know some of you look forward
to wearing the reaper.
Others of you are afraid of it.
That's a choice
each man will have to make.
From this point on,
we're family.
Indian Hills, Nevada charter
Sons of Anarchy.
Congratulations.
It is my personal hope
that every one of you
wears this cut.
I know you got a lot to talk about.
I'll leave you to your business.
- Did you dose it?
- Triple dose.
Patch-over bash, man.
Makes Mardi Gras
look like a sweet 16 party.
With Jury's stable... shit.
Nothing but young,
tight,
perfect pussy.
Well, Fido's having his own party.
- Which one?
- Unser said take the cargo truck.
The keys should be in it.
Holy shit!
Run! Go! Go!
- Shit!
- Run!
Open the door!
God!
Damn it!
Shit!
I thought you said
you drugged the meat.
I did.
Look at him.
He's foaming at the mouth.
That thing should be dead.
I dosed it with, like, two grams.
- Grams? Grams of what?
- Crank.
You fed crystal
to a killer Doberman?
Are you retarded?
No.
Should I shoot him?
Drive.
Put it in.
Look at my ass.
- Hey, darling. Do me a favor?
- Sure, babe.
Guy distributes your stuff...
he still have access
to that federal marshal?
Think so. Been feeding his Pillsbury
dough girl fetish for years.
What do you need?
How do you think
this thing'll play out?
Half, maybe more will stay.
And that pack'll thin out
once the Mayans come a-knocking.
Which will be real soon.
You can't leave
these guys with no backup.
Vegas can hang.
Indian Hills is gonna have to learn
how to protect their ground.
Best way to thin out a herd.
Herd's already pretty thin, Clay.
I want to be here for Jury
when the shit goes down.
I ain't worried about Jury;
he can handle himself.
You believe that?
Looks like the vote's in?
We're in.
Patch-over party!
What's a patch-over?
Means things are about to change.
I have a cousin in Iraq.
He still have both his nuts,
but he's lost a couple buddies.
Yeah, you know, sometimes I feel
guilty I left after just one TOD.
You shouldn't.
I mean, you're a hero.
Can you still have kids or...?
Yeah, lefty's real potent.
- You ever been to Ireland?
- Shut up.
Look, man, it's not my fault
that you got bit, all right?
You didn't specify
what kind of drug.
I am not happy
about being here either.
At least you and I, we can try
to have a decent conversation.
What do you want?
You want to bond?
You want to get closer?
Fine.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna dunk my balls in your mouth.
You're gonna gag, I'm gonna laugh,
we'll be best friends forever.
- Why do you got to be that way?
- You ever been to Attica?
Shut up.
Pull your pants up.
You okay?
Want something?
I could get used to this.
Let's just take it
a night at a time, babe.
The brunette,
she anybody's old lady?
No, Cherry's just a sweetbutt.
- Good girl.
- How good?
What's mine is yours, brother.
Watch my stogie.
- Can I cut in?
- Yeah, sure.
Hi, baby.
Hi.
Come to Daddy.
I got to admit this one
gives me a serious chubby.
Look at this shit.
Hey, guys.
Here we go.
The first time I read Emma Goldman
wasn't in a book.
I was 16,
hiking near the Nevada border.
The quote was painted
on a wall in red.
When I saw those words,
it was like someone ripped them
from the inside of my head.
"Anarchism
"stands for liberation
of the human mind
"and the dominion of religion.
"Liberation of the human body
from the dominion of property.
"Liberation from shackles
"and the restraint of government.
"It stands for social order
"based on the free
grouping of individuals."
The concept was pure, simple, true.
It inspired me.
Lit a rebellious fire.
But ultimately, I learned the lesson
that Goldman, Proudhon
and the others learned:
that true freedom
requires sacrifice and pain.
Most human beings only think
they want freedom.
In truth, they yearn for the bondage
of social order,
rigid laws, materialism.
The only freedom man really wants
is the freedom to be comfortable.
Man!
I hate you.
- What's up, killer?
- I hate all of you.
- Morning, Cherry.
- Morning.
You want some coffee?
Whip up some breakfast?
Okay.
I thought you liked that guy.
I do.
Well, then why'd you sleep
with that old dude?
'Cause that's what we do.
You mean, you just sleep
with whoever they tell you to?
I take care of them
and they take care of me. It's a family.
And when I finally hook up,
I'll belong to that guy
and that guy only.
See, good old ladies,
they can make or break a club.
Come here.
- Hi.
- Car's ready.
Figured you'd need it for work.
Yeah.
You drove it here?
I'm thinking, me and you
got off to a bad start.
It's my way of saying sorry.
That's nice of you.
Thanks.
You weren't kidding
about the clutter.
Working through a room at a time.
Your dad was real handsome.
Kinda nuts, but cute.
- Yeah. Why are you here, Gemma?
- Your car.
Yeah, the good Samaritan
bit's not really playing.
What do you want?
You left Charming
because it was
incestuous, backward,
and small-minded.
It's pretty much an exact quote.
I don't forget.
You leave Chicago
to come back to this:
shit-filled house, mediocre gig
at a community hospital?
Needed to tie up family business.
People don't up-end their lives
to pack up a dead relative's house.
You seem to be spending a lot of time
and energy worrying about my life.
- Do I scare you that much, Gemma?
- I don't forget.
I'm not worried about you.
Just the people you touch.
Jax is in a real strange place.
He doesn't need any
outside voices in his head.
Stay clear of him.
We're not 19 years old anymore.
You can't dictate what he does,
- who he sees...
- I'm his mother.
And until I am dead and cold,
I am gonna do anything
I have to do to protect him.
And, I'm not sure
why you're carrying a gun,
but if you're gonna use one,
make sure to be safe...
No serial numbers.
Any problems?
Truck's out back.
It's all good.
He still pouting?
Who, Tiggy?
Why don't you give him the sweetbutt?
Nah, I'm good with Half-Sack.
That score's settled.
- Where the hell are you?
- Yeah, looks like Jury's gonna have
some backup
when the Mayan shit goes down.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm on my way back and I'm not alone.
Shit! Mayans.
- Where?
- Pack of 'em trailing Jax.
- Get rid of the goddamned truck.
- Got it.
- Mayans? What do you want to do?
- Weapons behind the bar.
- You two should get out of here.
- What's going on?
Let's go out.
- Why?
- Just go.
- What can I do?
- Girls all gone?
Open up the garage.
Move the bikes inside!
Everybody got a weapon?
Go! Go!
Jesus Christ!
Moby's doing good.
He likes school.
Yeah, he likes to draw a lot.
I don't see his mom too much, but...
Hey, I'm real happy
that Jax's kid's gonna be okay.
That's a blessing.
What happened to Wendy
should be a lesson to you, Lowell.
It is.
And I know.
I've been doing real good
with all that, Gemma.
You can ask Clay.
Good.
- Hey.
- Any luck?
Nothing really flagged.
No outstanding warrants.
She had a restraing order
a few months back.
- Against her?
- No, she filed it.
My guy said the name
was omitted from the report.
What kind of neighborhood
she live in?
Old Town.
Pretty nice, I think.
You really don't trust
this bitch, do you?
Cleared his book debt. We're good.
What happens now,
I'm probably gonna lose
more guys 'cause of this.
There won't be another hit
for a while.
That pop-off
was just about dick size.
They want to let us
know they're watching.
Vegas'll stick around for a while.
Appreciate that.
Brother.
Yeah.
- I'm sorry about all this, man.
- It's all good. It's all good.
You want to tell me
what happened out there?
I went for a ride to clear my head,
and the Mayans spotted me.
You saw the rest.
Juice will stick around
and watch over the AK assembly.
I'll have Vegas, you know,
bring up some illegals, help him out.
I got some helpers for you.
No, really?
- I love you.
- I know. You don't deserve this.
I love all of you.
Yes, I do. I love all of you.
Come on. One, two, three.
Look, I want to go back
to see the kid.
I'll ride back
with Happy and his guys.
- How's he doing?
- Hard to say.
I got anything to worry about?
Not yet.
Thought that bitch was with you?
Dr. Knowles, this came for you.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- Fine. Your mom's in there.
Where else would she be?
How was Nevada?
Uneventful.
Hey.
You okay?
I'm fine.
You think maybe someone
could have called? I've been sitting...
Hey, little guy.
Subtitles: Santiag Team
michvanilly, Tagne.