Previously on "moonlight"...
I want to help people.
It's why I became a P. I.
If I can help others, it might make up for what I am.
Have I got this right?
A stake in your heart will paralyze you.
I see it now--it's like your own little prison, isn't it?
This whole vampire thing?
You can't have anybody poking around--
a girlfriend, anyone who cares.
oh, is that your friend--the blonde?
This is beth turner for "buzzwire.
since you met that guy, screwed up has started to seem normal.
Please don't look at me.
what are you?
I'm a vampire.
beth.
Okay, I'm here--I'm here to talk to you about, um...
you.
Maybe you should come in.
I really need you to tell me that I didn't see what I saw--
what I think I saw-- the other night...
the blood, the fangs.
I heard what you said.
That I'm a vampire.
How am I supposed...
are--are you the only one, or, uh, are there other vampires?
A few hundred here in L. A.
How can people not know you exist?
We're extremely careful.
Sometimes people see things, but they dismiss it.
How can they?
Or no one believes them.
People have been hunting us for thousands of years.
So it's extremely important that no one knows we exist.
Do you understand?
So do you bite people's necks and s-suck the blood out?
Actually, I-I get most of my blood from the blood bank.
Oh.
The red cross does not mention that in their literature.
I don't think they know.
Do you--do you know how crazy this is?
I'm trying really hard to wrap my mind around what you just said and what I saw.
Hey, I get it.
It's a lot to... get.
So how does a person even become a vampire?
How did you become a vampire?
L. A. 1952
I'll love you forever.
Forever?
Forever.
nick?
I'm sorry.
I-I can'T. Not...
I'm sorry. You gotta go.
Were you bitten by another vampire?
Is that how it works--
one minute you're mick the human, and the next you're mick the vampire?
Another time.
What was it like?
What's it like to turn into a vampire?
As if there was some way to describe it.
What do you do when your whole world changes in the blink of an eye?
Sir?
Sir, can you hear me?
Sir, are you all right?
Okay, everything's gonna be all right. I'm a doctor.
Okay, I'm just gonna feel your neck a little bit sir, okay?
stay with me. Come on.
When suddenly, all the rules change.
-=www. ydy. com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-? ? ?
-=www. ydy. com/bbs=-
Moonlight
Season 1 Episode 03
hey!
What are you doing?
You have to pay for those!
I'm not paying for anything.
Something's wrong with your food!
It doesn't have any taste!
You're crazy!
you stay away from me!
You get back!
I mean it!
at this time, the police aren't releasing any details,
but earlier tonight, a store clerk was murdered at this downtown location.
We'll post further details as soon as we get them.
This is beth turner for "buzzwire.
And we are good.
I'll go to the van and upload your report to the archives.
Okay.
it's a bloody mess in there.
The guy was literally chewed up.
A wild animal maybe?
In a convenience store?
Maybe someone didn't approve of his choice of slushee flavors and--
and sicced his dog on the poor bastard.
Pit bull?
Like the one that mauled the woman in san francisco?
Maybe.
Best theory so far.
We'll see what the coroner says.
All right.
Let's call it a night.
listen, whatever you heard...
off the record.
I heard "bloody, chewed up body.
I said, I don't want you going out with this thing.
Then give me something.
Come on, carl.
It's me.
Just give me a little something.
Off the record, I swear.
Yeah, that's what you always say.
And I always hold the story.
Look, fine.
This guy in here was not just chewed up.
His blood was gone.
Somehow his body was completely drained.
jeez, guillermo, you're like a 12-year-old girl with the messages, the texting.
All right, I'm here. What's the emergency?
Came in a couple of hours ago.
Look at how the flesh has been just ripped away.
It's like something was literally trying to eat this guy.
What are the cops saying?
Well, for now, dog attack.
Yeah, right.
Not many vampire victims come into the morgue.
That's why I wanted you to get down here before the coroner took a look.
The vampire that did this must have been severely pissed off.
Or newly turned.
I can barely smell any decay.
but why wasn't his sire controlling him?
Maybe the sire changed his mind, deserted the newbie.
That goes against every rule we have.
A sire has to be responsible for whoever they turn,
help them through the transition.
I hardly remember anything from when I got turned.
I was too out of it.
I remember the rage,
the need to satisfy a hunger that I didn't understand...
and what it felt like to feed for the first time.
We've got a rogue on our hands.
The way to find this guy is to find his sire.
What are you doing here?
Word is something slashed him open and drained all his blood out.
"Something"?
What, as in something like me?
I didn't say that.
Whatever did this is nothing like me, okay?
Okay, fine. I believe you.
I want you off this case.
Why?
Because there's a vampire involved?
Oh, god, I can't believe I just said that.
Yeah, exactly.
Hey, I've been doing this job long before I knew about vampires,
and I'm gonna keep doing it.
I don't have to ask your permission.
It's gonna get dangerous, beth.
Then it's a good thing I got you around.
(Sighs) okay.
You still want to know how someone becomes a vampire?
Well, first, you have to reach a point near death.
Then the vampire, your sire, feeds you their own blood.
Your sire, like a parent?
Kind of.
So do they tell you what to do?
Are you close forever?
Like humans, some relationships are terrible, some are amazing.
It can go a million different ways.
There's no way to predict,
but something has gone terribly wrong with this one, that's for sure.
I'll go through the wire reports,
see if the cause of death matches any other recent murder victims.
Beth--
and will you ask the other vampires if they know anything?
There's not like a big clubhouse where we all hang out.
Oh, okay. Well, however it works.
I'll deal with the cops and the computers.
The other thing-- you're the expert.
Time was, I didn't even know vampires existed,
let alone being an expert.
But I know one thing--
a rogue vampire won't stop killing on his own.
The first thing a newly turned vampire needs to do is feed.
Problem is, if you don't know what you're hungry for,
you'll try anything,
when really you're only looking for one thing--blood.
city sidewalks are covered in all kinds of crap--
gum, bits of food, cigarette butts, spit.
but I can always find the blood.
that smell can't be mistaken for anything else.
And vampire blood smells like no other.
A vampire was here...
and then there were two.
This is where the rogue was sired...
poor guy.
Probably didn't know what hit him.
L. A. 1952
don't be afraid.
It's okay.
What have you done?
What have you done to me?
Don't be scared.
It's my wedding gift.
I freed you.
I freed you from death.
Tell me what you did to me.
I joined us forever.
but you don't understand.
I've given you a gift...
the greatest gift I can give.
But I don't want this.
I love you.
You made me into a monster.
I don't know. "Monster" may be a little extreme.
Yeah? You didn't see the body.
I gotta play with tiger.
Do you think tiger would be up for a little night putting?
It was pure carnage, man.
Yeah, well, the blood loss can be pretty heavy when you're first turned,
and you can really lose it.
I know I did.
Damn, those were good times.
You know, a newly turned vampire is like a feral kitten.
if you don't socialize it within the first few days,
it's never gonna be able to live with humans.
Well, if I were you, I would pay a visit to the cleaner.
She knows where all the bodies are buried, so to speak.
I've never needed a cleaner service.
However a lot of vampires *****.
but *************
she is necessary to mentain the balance.
Mick st. John.
Don't tell me you need you need a cleanup.
No.
What happened here?
Mr. Sloppy and mr. Stupid over there got a little carried away,
offed their midnight snack.
These two?
Accidents happen.
Everyone feels bad, but at least they called for cleanup.
Yes?
Let's take a walk.
Anything unusual about your recent calls?
We've been a little busier than usual--
couple of coeds on the westside last week.
The week before that, a gangbanger in torrance.
What about downtown, 1st and main?
Oh, yeah, last night.
But that was a false alarm.
What do you mean, false alarm?
Vampire called about an accidental kill.
I hauled my guys all the way from the westside,
but when we got there, no vampire, no kill.
I didn't even get out of the car.
So did you, uh, get the name on the vamp who called it in?
Come on, mick.
You know how it is.
All calls are confidential.
That's why the system works.
Really?
'Cause, uh, he left this behind.
I'm gonna find him eventually.
The reason there was no body there is because it got up and walked away.
A turning?
Gone rogue.
If I don't find this guy, there's gonna be a lot more cleaning up to do,
with no one to pick up the tab.
The vampire who called for cleanup is named gerald stovsky.
You find this sire, call me.
Damn it, josh, don't sneak up on me like that.
I didn't sneak.
Why are you so jumpy?
I'm not jumpy.
Oh, what is this about?
Oh, nothing.
What time is it, anyway?
Uh, it's late.
I know you usually forget to eat, so...
I picked up some chinese-- kung pao, extra spicy.
You're the best.
I still don't know how you can eat that.
I know that look.
No look.
It's just, you've been so busy, we...
never really talked about what's going on lately.
What is going on?
Shooting a guy, P. I.
Buddy, your new obsession.
Look, I know the last couple weeks have been crazy.
I've been juggling a lot with the new job.
But it has nothing to do with you, with us.
I promise.
I traced stovsky to the jet propulsion laboratory in pasadena.
Turned out he was a vampire and a rocket scientist.
hi.
Hi.
Yours?
My notes.
Oh, thank you.
I thought I'd lost them.
Corner of 1st and main last night, right?
Maybe.
I go by there every night.
There you go.
Were you alone?
Yes, you know, I-I think I've finally gotten used to my solitary existence.
Other vampires seem to avoid me, and my human colleagues are--
well, you know how that is.
Right.
Where were you coming from?
The empress pavilion.
I love their barbecue pork buns.
But we don't eat.
I know, but I sure used to love those buns.
Anyway, last night, after your pork bun, what did you eat?
And by, "what, " I mean, "who"?
What?
I found your pad in a pool of blood,
and since you're a vampire,
I figured it's probably not a coincidence.
That wasn't my fault.
As I said, I was just walking along when, suddenly,
out of absolutely nowhere, this car mows me over.
So you attacked the driver?
Oh, no, no, no.
I-I was in no condition.
Fortunately, a good samaritan came by.
So you fed on him?
Drained him, I'm afraid.
It was just an accident.
I don't ordinarily feed on humans.
I was just desperate and I...
look, I called the cleaner as soon as I got home.
She should've disposed of the body, so...
did you check if the guy was dead before you left him there?
Yes, of course I checked.
I-I mean, he wasn't moving.
Why wouldn't he be dead, right?
(Mick) you screwed up.
Some of your blood got into his system.
You didn't kill him.
You turned him.
Then you left him there by himself,
not knowing what he was and not knowing what to do.
Now he's out there killing people.
Oh, my. Oh, dear.
What do you remember about him?
Nothing much. I...
it all happened so fast. It was dark.
Ah, yes. He said something about being a, um, uh...
a doctor.
No--yes, a doctor, a doctor.
A doctor?
Yes.
Are you sure?
what?
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
what... everything is gonna be okay.
I'm a doctor.
again, the details are sketchy, but the police appear to be treating this as a homicide.
As of now, nobody knows who or what is responsible for the bloody crimes of the past few days.
This is beth turner for "buzzwire.
" And we're out.
Good job.
You really think this is related to the other murder?
There's only one way to find out.
Watch these people over here.
So what happened to holding the story?
I did hold it. This is a different crime scene.
Or are you telling me you think this is related to the convenience store murder?
Initially, we thought this was a suicide.
And now?
We decided it was unlikely that he chewed out his own throat before he took his leap.
Was his blood missing?
Listen, beth, we still don't know if this is a serial.
Okay, so don't you go giving this psycho a nickname.
You name him, all the wack jobs come out of the woodwork.
People start panicking.
Carl, would I do that to you?
Yes, you would.
This is beth turner for "buzzwire.
" I watched your report.
You don't know "what" did this?
I didn't say "vampire.
" Came awfully close.
In fact, by not saying it, I'm lying to people.
Well, keep it up.
Why do you think you can't trust me?
I found the rogue vampire's blood on the corner of 1st and main.
I need you to use your police contacts to see
if anybody has filed any kind of reports in the last couple of days.
You're a private investigator.
You don't have any contacts in the department?
It takes time to develop a contact-- years.
People age. I don'T.
Cops especially tend to pick up on those kind of details.
It kinda makes long-term reshtionlaips with humans difficult.
1st and main?
I'll see what I can find out.
Part of me felt bad for the rogue.
It's not easy being a newbie.
Trust me.
there you are.
Get away from me.
I know you're hurting.
I brought you something that will make you feel better.
No, take her away.
You don't really want me to do that.
Yes, I do.
Make it stop.
Make it stop, please.
I can'T. It's done, and it's gonna be so wonderful.
You gotta--you gotta kill me.
I wanna die.
No, you don'T.
You wanna live.
what in the world...
Jeff, what are you doing in there?
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
I needed some sleep.
You were sleeping in the refrigerator?
The cold.
Ah, it's nice. It feels good.
Where are your clothes?
I didn't need them in there.
Okay, honey, come inside.
You've been under a lot of stress lately, taking on all those extra shifts.
You're just exhausted.
Something's happening to me--
something that I don't understand.
Oh, jeff, please, honey, let me call the hospital.
You need help. You're sick.
I'm not sick!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm just...
so hungry.
I should be getting those police reports you wanted,
but there's no cell coverage here.
I'll try again later.
(Cell phone beeps) chip?
I got the ones without garlic.
I can eat garlic.
I mean, well, I could if I... ate...
food.
But I don't eat food.
Just blood?
Didn't we just cover that?
Can you fly?
Mm-hmm, just like superman.
-Really?
-No.
it would be cool, thoughdnwoul, 't it?
Yeah
So you know what you said earlier--
vampires really don't age?
Really don'T.
So how old are you?
It's not polite to ask people about their age.
That's just women.
I know you must be older, but you look about 30.
That's how old I was when I was turned.
Wow.
So when I was 2-- I looked 30.
When you're 82, I'm still gonna look 30.
So how old are you really?
I'm gonna be 85 this november.
(Chuckles) immortality looks pretty good to me.
Not from where I'm sitting.
Here we go.
"No police reports of a hit-and-run on 1st and main.
" No 9-1-1 hits, either.
Parking enforcement said they towed an abandoned car from that intersection
that's registered to a dr. Jeffrey pollock.
2810 hillside.
and "wait in the car" means...
yeah, 'cause that worked out so well last time.
What's that smell?
blood.
Stay close.
Is she dead?
Maybe she's not dead.
She's dead.
There's no heartbeat.
You can tell that from here?
Is she going to turn into a vampire, too?
No. He didn't turn her.
He just murdered her.
We need to figure out where he's gone.
With every kill, pollock becomes more dangerous.
His bloodlust will only get worse.
It was his wife.
He killed his own wife.
They look so happy.
You must've had a normal life before you became a vampire--
a job, friends, family...
I did.
But once I was turned, be I came a danger to them all.
I had to give them up.
Were you married?
Once.
What happened?
She died.
Did you try and turn her into a--
she's dead. Period.
Okay. Sorry.
You're not. Trust me.
He works at sacred angels hospital.
We have to get there now.
You think he'd feed on his patients?
New vampires crave blood.
Where better to find it than a hospital?
he's back.
stay here. Stay.
You didn'T...
it was her husband--
the vampire you turned.
Are you tracking him?
After you left, I realized I had to make things right.
I had to take the poor vampire under my tutelage--
help him through the transition.
You're too late, gerald.
He's out of control.
No, he's-- he's just confused.
He's not confused.
He's feral.
He's killed three people already.
He has to be put down.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't completely honest with you.
I did remember the doctor's license plate.
I am good with numbers, after all.
Please understand, I was never able to sire before.
This mistake has given me something I've never had--
a son, a companion.
I won't let you take him from me.
mick?
Mick, you still here?
Oh, my god.
Mick...
mick.
Mick!
take it out.
Oh, my god. You're alive.
Wait. What did you say?
(Weakly) the stake--
take it out.
Uh, okay.
maybe it's like a piece of glass. You're supposed to wait--
take it out.
Thanks. I'll take that.
I thought stakes were supposed to kill vampires.
No, they only paralyze us.
Are you gonna be okay?
I heal fast.
Did pollock do this to you?
No, it was his sire.
We have to get to the hospital.
Pollock, you missed it, man.
Didn't know you were working tonight.
Missed what?
Car wreck. Driver's radial artery was severed.
I mean, look at this.
I've never seen that much blood.
How much blood was there?
What did I just say? A lot.
You lucky guy. You were probably playing golf.
Anyway, I got a patient down in 304 I gotta check up on.
Can you cover the floor?
Yeah, sure.
Drpollock.
Do I know you?
We need to talk.
It's important.
Can't right now.
I'm on call.
Hey, you seen dr. Pollock tonight?
Yeah, he's up on four.
You can't go up there!
you're not my doctor.
I'm covering for dr. Duffy tonight.
I'm gonna need to take a little blood.
Doctor, I need to speak with you.
Who are you?
What do you want?
I'm here to help you.
I'm your friend.
I don't need any friends.
Doctor, please.
I can't stop him. He's insane.
You created a killer vampire and just left him?
What's wrong with you?
Gerald stovsky, we need to talk.
hey.
Back awaY.
Now.
I can smell you.
You're like me.
I'm nothing like you.
Yeah, you are.
We're vampires, aren't we?
The strength, the speed...
the blood.
I figured it out.
You need to come with me right now.
I'm not going anywhere.
can't you smell how delicious it is?
You don't have to kill to survive.
I like killing.
Come on!
I'll share.
There's enough blood here for both of us,
and they restock every day.
You can't feed here!
We have rules.
there are no rules.
I'm top of the food chain.
These are people.
They're human beings.
You used to be a human, remember?
Not anymore.
No, I understand now.
I'll stop killing.
I'll go back to my old life.
You can'T.
You destroyed it.
mick.
Some woman came and took gerald away.
Pollock--you found him?
And staked him.
Sh-should we call the police?
Suggestions like that are why you shouldn't be here.
But I thought you said a stake doesn't kill a vampire.
It only paralyzes him.
What should we do?
Not "we. "Me.
You can't just kill him.
He's already dead.
After all this?
No, beth, okay?
No.
The incinerator.
Damn.
Remind me to never piss you off.
I didn't have a choice.
Well, like I'm judging you.
I would've done the same thing, except I would have enjoyed it more.
You know, after all these years, I still don't understand you.
The bad guy was caught.
Justice was served, and you're sitting there like someone died.
Actually, four people died.
Mm, collateral damage for a greater good,
and pollock was a danger to all of us--
humans and vampires.
I could've been like pollock,
if coraline had let me go after she turned me,
if she hadn't taught me how to survive as a vampire.
Oh, don't tell me you're saying something good about the ex.
No.
But you're still thinking about her.
I'll tell you something I've learned in my 400 years.
Two buddhist monks are walking down a road,
and they see a woman trying to cross a stream.
The first monk picks her up, carries her across.
She says, "thanks, " and they go their separate ways.
But the second monk is spitting mad.
After a couple more miles, the second monk speaks up,
tells the first monk, "you violated the rules of our order
when you carried that woman across the stream.
And the first monk replied,
"I may have carried her across that stream,
but you've been carrying her ever since.
I have?
You stop carrying coraline around, mick.
You can't change the past,
and you can't let it stop you from going forward.
I know.
When you're asleep, you should be unconscious
and not even know there is anyone next to you,
but somehow, you do...
more than ever.
Hey.
Mick.
Do you wanna come in?
No.
I mean...
you wanna know how I became a vampire.
Yes.
Okay.
I told you I was married, right?
Well, she was a vampire.
I didn't know.
And on our wedding night, she turned me.
I went to bed a happily married man, and I woke up a monster.
You're not a monster.
Believe me, I was.
You must find it hard to trust anyone now.
You asked me if I trusted you.
You're the first human that I've told any of this to--
about who I am or what I am.
So, yeah.
I trust you.
-=www. ydy. com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-? ? ?
-=www. ydy. com/bbs=-
Moonlight
Season 1 Episode 03