(Metal Clattering)
We're not...
who...
we are.
We're not...
who we are.
lt goes no further than this.
lt stops right here...
right now.
(Gunshots)
Team captainJohn Richterhere.
It'sbeena couple
offrustratingmonths
butafteragreatdeal
ofstick-with-it-ness
we'reproudtoreport
thatas ofahalfanhourago
wesurpassedtheprevious record
fordrilling down
intoanicesheet.
All:Allright!
Mulder: This team ofscientists
made up the Arctic lce Core Project.
Theywere sent to Alaska
by the government's advanced research
project agency
nearly a year ago to drill
into the arctic ice.
The samples they removed
contained trapped gases, dust,
chemicals--
Evidence that could reveal
the structure ofthe Earth's climate
back to the dawn ofman.
Theirworkwas a success,
nearly completed.
No reports or indications
ofproblems ofany kind
until only a week later
this next transmission was received.
We'renot...
who...
weare.
We'renot...
who weare.
Itgoesno furtherthan this.
Itstops... righthere...
rightnow.
(Groan)
What happened up there?
Nobody's been able
to reach the compound
because ofbad weather.
Obviously they think
we're either brilliant or expendable
because we've pulled the assignment.
ls it severe isolation distress?
These were top geophysicists.
Theywere trained and screened
for this project
in everyway imaginable,
including psychological makeup.
We leave for Nome today.
We'll meet up
with three scientists
familiarwith the project
and then head north
up to the lcy Cape.
The National Weather Service
reports a three-daywindow
to get in and get out
before the next arctic storm.
Bring your mittens.
Radio:Fouts looks over
the Raiders'defense.
Here's thesnap. Raidersblitz.
Fouts dumpsitacross themiddle
to Winslow.
He'sat the 15! 10!
Touchdown San Diego!
Touchdown!
Fouts is God!
Sorry. My team scored.
There's no football on Wednesday.
Fouts retired in '87,
didn't he?
This is some ofmy all-time
favorite plays on tape.
You two F.B.l.?
Agent Mulder, Agent Scully. And you?
Danny Murphy.
Professor ofgeology, U.C. San Diego.
You get much ofa chance
to study ice down there?
just what's around the keg.
Dr. DaSilva?
Dr. Hodge?
Agent Scully, Agent Mulder.
Nice to meetyou.
Howyou doing?
Can l see some identification?
What for?
l just want to make sure
we are who we saywe are.
lt's me.
lt's you.
- lt's me.
- Thanks a lot.
Appreciate it.
lt's you.
Well, now that we know who we are
anybody care to take a guess
as to whywe're going?
Two agents, a geologist,
a medical doctor
and a toxicologist.
That should give us some idea.
l assumeyou all
took a look at the tape.
Something wrong?
Come on. You're F.B.l.
You have to know
more than we do.
You folks the ones
going up to lcy Cape?
Yeah.
Then l'm fying you.
My name is Bear.
The plane's across the way.
Provisions are loaded.
Grabyour gear.
Oh, could we see
some credentials?
Credentials.
The only credentials l have
is that l'm the only pilot
willing to fyyou up there.
You don't like
those credentials...
walk.
Bear... see ifyou
can get the power started.
Anything to get out ofhere.
Where do we start?
Body bags are on the plane.
Before we touch anything
we have to thoroughly
document the scene.
Scully: Flashing.
Mulder: That's what
theywere drilling for.
Quarter ofa million years
melting away
in a couple ofdays.
l want to preserve
some samples.
(Rumbling)
lt's the generator.
Oh.
Agent Mulder...
(Screaming)
(Barking)
Hold on.
(Groans)
Hold it down.
That will keep him
out for awhile.
You okay?
Yeah, he didn't break the skin.
Bear, you okay?
He got me.
Get thatjacket off.
Give me the stuff.
l'll do it myself.
DaSilva: ls it rabies?
l don't see any indications.
lfit is rabies
it's certainly not a strain
l'm familiarwith.
Scully:
Look at this. Black nodules.
Swollen lymph nodes.
Symptoms ofbubonic plague.
l'll do a blood test.
We'll take it from there.
This dog has got
a skin irritation
on its neck.
Murphy: lt looks like
it's been scratching off
its own hair.
Look at this.
Look at this!
What the hell was that?
(Groans)
From the autopsies
it's clear these men
killed one another.
There are contusions
around the throat areas
ofthree men--
evidence ofstrangulation.
Richter and Campbell
killed themselves.
l also found tissue damage
due to fever.
Did any ofthem have
the black spots the dog has?
No. None ofthem had
the black nodules.
So, uh, those spots
didn't have anything to do
with those guys
killing each other, right?
l wouldn't rule it out.
l just reexamined the dog.
The nodules are gone.
What could that mean?
lt could mean that the spots
are a symptom ofsome disease
at an early stage.
Danny?
Danny.
Sorry.
The play-offgame
against Miami, '82.
Helps to get my mind offstuff.
My interpretation of
satellite remote sensing photos
is a little rusty.
Murphy: All right,
this is the lcy Cape area.
lt approximates
the depth ofthe ice sheet
to be about 3,000 meters thick.
l also found this data
and ifl'm reading it correctly
the team actually found
the ice sheet
to be twice that depth.
That's very good.
The numbers indicate
the topography to be concave.
Looks like theywere drilling
inside a meteor crater.
Hodge: No, you're wrong.
l analyzed two samples.
What did you find?
There's a presence
ofammonium hydroxide
in Richter's blood sample.
lt's not possible.
Ammonia would vaporize
at human body temperature.
l checked all
the air filtration systems.
l found no evidence
ofany such toxins.
l have.
ln the ice,
and that's not all there is.
l found a high ratio
ofammonia to water
in the ice core.
The earth's atmosphere could
never have produced such levels
even a quarter
ofa million years ago.
Look in the scope.
Unless a foreign object
was introduced
into that environment.
Murphy: Tell me
that's not a foreign object.
Scully.
That same thing is
in Richter's blood.
What ifthat single-celled organism
is the larval stage
ofa larger animal?
That's kind ofa leap,
don'tyou think?
Scully:
The evidence is there.
Maybe the organism
in the ice core
somehow got into the men.
Come on.
Nothing can survive
in sub-zero temperatures
for a quarter million years.
Mulder:
Unless that's how it lives.
Why areyou squabbling
over some bug?
You said ityourself, Scully.
Your autopsy found
those men killed each other.
That's it.
Let'sjust get the hell out ofhere.
l agree.
We'll send the bodies
to a facility
where they can make
a definitive diagnosis.
ln the event that something
was missed, Agent Scully.
lfthose bodies are infected
we can't take them back.
We can't go back
without proper quarantine procedures.
We can't risk bringing back
the next plague.
Let's say
they came down with something.
We haven't, and l ain't
waiting around until we do.
l think it's safe to go back.
There's no reason
whywe'd be infected.
We took the necessary safeguards.
The dog did bite Bear.
ltjumped Mulder!
There's only one way to proceed.
A doctor eliminates
every possibility.
We must determine
ifany ofus is infected.
All right.
Parasitic diagnostic procedure
requires that each ofus provide
a blood and a stool sample.
A stool sample?
This kind oftravel
always makes that tough... for me.
Mulder:
Anybody got the morning
sports section handy?
l ain't dropping my cargo
for no one.
What l'm doing is getting
my gear, my plane
and fying the hell out ofhere.
You can't go.
The dog bityou.
l got hired to fyyou up here
and fyyou back.
No one said this might be
part ofthe deal.
So the deal is over.
Scully: We can't let him leave
without being checked.
Who's going to stop him?
We have to.
We can't risk infecting
the population.
lfhe gets on that plane,
l will too.
There's no time to argue.
Take a vote.
Who believes
we should confine Bear
until he agrees
to an examination?
All right.
Bear, wejust want
to checkyou out.
lfwe don't find any trace
ofthe parasite or the virus
we'll all go.
All right.
Give me the damnjar.
Murphy, get a rope.
(Bear Grunting)
(Groaning)
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Get my bag.
What areyou gonna do?
Cutting it out.
We know nothing about it.
lt's killing him.
Scully, help me hold the skin.
Hold still, Bear.
(Screaming)
Forceps.
(Moaning)
Hodge: Hold still, Bear.
just another second.
You're going to be okay.
(Groaning)
(Agonized Moaning)
This is the A.l.C.P.
investigative team
calling Doolittle Airfield.
Come in.
D.A.F. responding.
This is Agent Mulder.
We have a serious
biological hazard.
Request air pickup
and quarantine procedures.
Come in, Doolittle Airfield.
We copy.
Thisareais underaheavystorm.
Noaircraftcangetout
forthenextday.
Maybe themilitarybasein Kotzebue
cansetupa quarantine.
Adviseimmediate evacuation.
Thestorm isbearing
inyour direction.
We were told
we'd have three clear days ofweather.
Welcome to the top
ofthe world, sir.
ls Bear in any condition to fy?
lfwe don't get out ofhere
in an hour
we don't get out for days.
He's dead.
Hodge: lt's similar to a tapeworm
in that it has a scolex
with suckers and hooks.
You can deal with it?
What?
No.
Very different
from any organism--
at least that l know of.
Haveyou figured out
how it's transmitted yet?
Exchange offuids, touch, air,
all ofthe above?
l don't know.
All the other dead bodies
had the creature.
This is the only one
that's still alive.
Were they all in the spine?
No. lt appears theywere
in the hypothalamus gland
deep in the brain.
Murphy: Hypothalamus.
What was that again?
lt's a gland
that secretes hormones
although l don't know why
a parasite would want
to attach to it.
Hypothalamus releases acetylcholine
which is what produces
violent, aggressive behavior.
That might be a connection.
Everybody that's been infected
certainly seems
to act aggressively.
Maybe the worm feeds
on acetylcholine
which foods our capacity
to control violent behavior.
A parasite shouldn't want
to kill its host.
lt doesn't kill you
until it's extracted.
Then it releases a poison.
You're saying it's possible
the worm makes you
want to kill other people
which is maybe what happened
to the first team.
Orwhat could happen to us.
lt'sjust a theory.
We don't have definite proof.
Except five dead men.
lfthe worm makes people
violently aggressive
then why did Richter
and Campbell kill themselves?
Maybe they did it
to save us.
l'm just, uh...
double-checking.
Making sure l didn't miss anything.
just some sleep, right?
Sleep. l'm so tired,
l can't sleep.
We're all wired
and hypersensitive.
lt will be good to get
a fresh start in the morning.
l don't want to waste a second
finding a way to kill this thing.
l don't know
ifwe should kill it.
This area ofthe ice sheet
is formed over a meteor crater.
The worm lives in ammonia.
lt survives sub-zero temperatures.
Theorists in alternative life designs
believe in
ammonia-supported life systems
on planets with freezing...
No.
The meteor that crashed here
may have carried that type
oflife to earth.
Mulder, that pilot
developed surface symptoms
within a few minutes.
Within a few hours
that parasite had total control.
What would happen
ifthis got into the population?
A city the size of New York
could be infected
within a few days.
Exactly.
But what do we know about it?
This organism might be
lying dormant in another crater.
lfwe don't kill it now,
we run the risk
ofbecoming Richter and Campbell
with guns to our heads.
lfwe kill it, we won't know
how to stop anything like it
in the future.
Scully: Future!
(lndistinct Arguing)
Tell me it's hot in here.
Don't worry.
You don't have a fever.
Heating system's malfunctioning.
Outside, it's 40 below,
and in here it's sweltering.
Can you hear
what they're arguing about?
They're probably discussing
their little government secrets.
You think they knew what was here
before we arrived?
l'm sure ofit.
Scully:
...biological hazard.
You know, Bear's infected blood
did get on Scully.
lt also got on you.
How doyou know
it can't be contained?
lt can!
By extermination.
We should take
those bodies--
worms and all--
outside and incinerate them.
Something going on
we should know about?
Agent Scully, you all right?
Yes, l'm fine.
lt's nothing.
You seem a little stressed out.
What the hell
areyou saying?
Let's all settle down.
lt's been a hard day.
We're all tired and scared.
Let's not turn
on one another.
At least not
without a good reason.
Mulder: We should all
get some sleep.
You kidding?
You think any ofus
could sleep right now?
Guys, let's face it--
we got to check for spots.
Any person or persons
who has them should be confined.
Are we agreed on that?
Areyou going to do the exams?
No.
We do them in front
ofeach other.
No secrets.
Before anyone passesjudgement,
may l remind you
we are in the arctic.
Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
DaSilva: Yeah. Good night.
Good night, Mulder.
Good night, Scully.
At least everyone's okay.
Don't forget.
The spots
on the dog went away.
Ballon the three-yardline.
Fourthandgoal with only 15seconds
leftin thegame.
Hemoves overtheball.
Here's thesnap.
Hegoes over...
(Gasps)
(Door Closes)
(Barking)
(Dripping)
Mulder, what areyou doing?
Murphy's dead.
You killed him.
l found him like this.
l heard one ofthe doors close.
l came out
to check it out.
lt was one ofyou.
You could have done it
and not known.
He said he didn't.
l have no symptoms.
You checked him.
Six hours ago.
lt was one ofyou.
Stop it!
Shut up!
Put the gun down and let
Hodge giveyou a blood test.
He'll doctor the results.
l won't let him
stick a needle in me.
He has to be confined now.
Turn around and let us
take a look atyour neck.
l'm not turning
my back on anyone.
As far as l'm concerned,
you're all infected!
Hodge is right.
We ought to lock him up.
Mulder...
Scully, get that gun offme.
You have to understand.
Put it down!
You first!
Scully!
For God's sakes, it's me.
Mulder, you may not be
whoyou are.
ln here l'll be safer than you.
(Gasping)
What wereyou doing?
You know what l was doing.
l can't help thinking,
Agent Scully
you're the only one with a gun.
lfyou get infected,
we don't stand a chance, do we?
Okay.
Was there something there?
Hodge: You're okay, Nancy.
We're all okay.
Now is not the time
for the three ofus
to break down
and turn on each other.
There's four ofus.
Mulder isn't one ofus.
lf Mulder is infected,
it's not his fault.
We can't turn our backs
on him now.
He needs us to help him.
She's right.
Who knows
what prolonged exposure
to the parasite could do?
lt could damage him to the point
ofpermanent psychosis.
lfhe is infected,
he doesn't go back.
l won't risk
the possibilities.
This is A.l.C.P.
calling Doolittle Airfield.
Please come in.
(Static)
This is
the Arctic lce Corps Project
sending a general distress call.
Please respond.
(Static)
Nancy, put a drop
ofthe uninfected blood
on the slide ofthe blood
drawn from the pilot.
Run that by me again.
Put the uninfected blood
on the infected blood.
No! Damn it!
What did l just tell you?
You infected
already infected blood.
We have to start over again.
l made a mistake.
Don'tyell at me.
Wasted hours ofwork.
Maybeyou should do it byyourself!.
Damn it!
l'm notyour assistant!
Hodge.
What?
Come take a look at this.
The larvae from two different worms
killed each other.
An individual worm will not tolerate
another invading its host.
lt does to the invader
what it did to humans.
lt makes them kill.
Hodge: But the species needs
another to procreate.
Worms are hermaphroditic.
lt can reproduce itself.
Look at the evidence
in the microscope.
This thing does not like company.
What areyou saying?
The way to kill it
is to introduce anotherworm
into an already infected body?
(Whining)
lt sounds okay.
lt passed the worms
in its stool.
They're dead.
l want to talk to him first.
Try and make this voluntary.
What?
You can't go in alone.
lfanything happens,
you come inside.
l can't do this to him
until l'm sure.
(Door Opening)
lt'sjustyou?
Yes.
lt's one ofthem.
No one's been killed
sinceyou've been in here.
So?
We found a way to kill it.
Two worms in one host
will kill each other.
You give me one worm,
you'll infect me.
lfthat's true
then why didn'tyou
let us inspectyou?
l would have,
butyou pulled a gun on me.
Now l don't trust them.
l want to trustyou.
Okay.
But now they're not here.
This is the last one.
She's not going to let us
give it to him.
Well, she'll have to
ifhe's infected.
He'll convince her somehow.
l just examined him.
He's uninfected.
So is she.
Which means
that it must be one ofyou.
All right.
Let's go over
to the main building.
l'd like to check him myself.
Then he can examine both ofus.
You want to lead the way?
No!
Get the worm.
Don't!
Oh, my God.
(Screaming)
lt's her!
No!
Scully!
lt's DaSilva.
(Screaming Hysterically)
DaSilva: No!
Hodge! Now!
Mulder.
After this,
there won't be any left.
They're all going to be dead!
Do it!
(DaSilva Screaming)
No!
Shh, shh.
(Moaning)
lt's all right.
lt's all over.
lt all stops right here.
Right now.
Okay, lock her down.
She's being put in quarantine
along with the dog.
We'll keep her there
until we're sure
she won't infect
the rest ofthe population.
Our tests came back normal,
so we've been released.
Plane ready.
lt will takeyou as far
from the ice as you want to go.
l'm going back to the site.
This time l'm going fully prepared
with proper equipment.
There's a lot ofresearch to be done
on the genetic structure
on its origins...
Mulder, don'tyou know?
Know what?
45 minutes after they evacuated us
they torched the place.
There's nothing left.
Who did that?
The military...
the Center for Disease Control...
you ought to know.
They'reyour people.
lt's still there, Scully.
200,000 years down.
ln the ice.
Leave it there.