Man #1 : You're supposed to be
in charge here, Perkins.
Man #2:
I am in charge.
Man #1 : These men want answers.
Theywant to know whatyour plan is.
This thing could kill us all.
Man #2: We should have left
two days ago. No one would listen to me.
Man #1 : Nobody knew what it was
two days ago. Nobody knows now.
Somebody has to go for help.
What are the rest ofus
supposed to do?
Wait for help?
Someone has to chance it...
and hike out.
That person might not make
the road before nightfall.
Then what?
I saywe run for it.
Split up,
take our chances.
It's suicide, Dyer.
Fine.
You stay here.
Tell us how it turns out.
(Panting)
(Grunting)
(Labored Breathing)
I think it's broken.
You got to get up.
I can't make it.
(Groaning)
We got to keep moving.
(Grunting)
We're not going to make it.
(Distant Humming)
(Humming Growing Louder)
(Dyer Screaming)
Take a good look, Scully.
What am I looking at?
30 loggers working
a clear-cutting contract...
in Washington State--
rugged, manly men...
in the full bloom
oftheir manhood.
What am I looking for?
Anything strange, unexplainable,
unlikely, boyfriend--
I don't know.
I give up, Mulder.
Funny. That's what
the Federal Forest Service...
has done as well.
Why? What happened to them?
In a word, theyvanished.
Or so it would appear.
This is Doug Spinney
and Steven Teague.
They call themselves
"monkeywrenchers."
They drive spikes into trees...
sabotage logging equipment,
and make life miserable...
for lumberjacks
and lumber mills.
Ecoterrorists--
militant environmentalists.
Right. Two weeks ago...
the loggers radioed a message...
that Spinney and Teague
had gone on a spree...
sabotaging equipment,
causing general mischief.
One week later...
all radio communication
was cut off.
Do they know why?
No. The lumber company...
asked the Federal Forest Service
to look into it.
Two officials went in last week.
No one has heard from them.
It appears as if
these monkeywrenchers...
are doing more than
mischiefmaking.
That's what the lumber company
and forest service are accusing.
They've asked the FBI
to investigate.
I had to pull strings
to get the case.
An ecoterrorism case?
Do I dare askwhy?
In 1 934, long before anyone knew
what an ecoterrorist was...
a WPA crew...
working that same area
vanished without a trace.
None ofthose men was ever found
or heard from again.
And you suspect what, Bigfoot?
Not likely.
That's a lot offannel
to be choking down...
even for Bigfoot.
Come on. It will be
a nice trip to the forest.
Hi. Fox Mulder, Dana Scully.
We're with the FBl.
Larry Moore,
Federal Forest Service.
You can putyour gear
in the truck.
Must be pretty rugged
where we're going.
Yeah.
Is that a bullet hole
in yourwindshield?
.22 caliber.
Somebody shot atyou?
There's not much
to hunt around here...
with that ammo
except Freddies.
" Freddies"?
Employees of
the Federal Forest Service.
It's what ecoterrorists call us.
Is that whoyou think
shot atyou?
Let me get this
out ofthe way.
I have no quarrel
with ecoterrorists in principle.
I'm as concerned
for this forest...
and the environment as anybody.
It's their methods
I can't condone.
Doyou think
they'd kill a man?
There's 30 men up there
unaccounted for...
each with survival experience.
Something happened to them.
Sorry I'm late.
I was down talking
to Bob Perkins' wife.
He's one ofour missing loggers.
Hey, Larry.
Steve Humphreys,
head ofsecurity...
for Schiff-lmmergut
Lumber.
Mulder. Scully.
We've got a four-hour drive
ahead ofus--
Plenty oftime
to get acquainted.
Get the impression...
we've walked into
the middle ofa war...
that's already started?
Why do these men...
work so far up
in the wilderness?
That's where the trees are.
You're kidding, right?
No. Environmentalists
have made sure...
that all the land here
is untouchable.
We take our timber
where we can get it.
Even then, we plant saplings
for every tree we take.
So why do ecoterrorists
targetyou?
Tree huggers
are like the boys...
who went up to Canada
during the Vietnam War.
They're cowardly,
and so are their tactics.
Damn it.
Homemade tire spike.
Clear through the sidewall.
It's unfixable.
You got a spare?
Humphreys:
Right tire's history too.
Monkeywrenchers call it
a caltrop.
Roads back here
are littered with them.
Indiscriminate terrorism.
Can you imagine somebody...
spiking the roads
ofWashington, D.C.?
How much sympathy
would they get?
So how are we going
to get to the camp?
We're going to have to hike.
Anybody here?
Someone forgot
to clean their plate.
Scully: Looks like
they left in a hurry too.
They forgot to pack.
Find anything?
Party favors.
Vehicles have all been
monkeywrenched.
Power generator's busted.
Somebody really turned
this place upside down.
Whoever did it didn't want
the fact broadcast, either.
Radiators are all full ofrice.
Looks like sugar or sand
in all the crankcases.
They really did a number here.
The sun's going down
in an hour and a half.
Better look around
before it gets dark.
I'll see ifl can get
that generatorworking.
You were right
about one thing.
What's that?
Definitelywasn't Bigfoot.
Look at that.
Scully:
What is it?
Moore:
It looks like a hive.
Maybe a cocoon ofsome kind.
Made bywhat?
I don't know.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Got it.
Can you cut it down?
Yeah, I think so.
You all right, Scully?
Scully:
Oh, God.
It feels, uh...
it feels desiccated,
hard and dry...
almost preserved.
Like it's been embalmed.
No, more like the fuids
have been bled...
from its body.
Almost like it's been cured.
I think...
it's a male.
Barely.
I'd say it's some kind
ofspider's nest...
or insect cocoon.
What kind ofinsect
could have gotten a man...
all the way up
into that tree?
Itsy-bitsy spider.
(Creaking)
(Clanking)
Don't move.
Who areyou?
Doug Spinney.
I ought to shootyou.
Might as well
shootyourselftoo.
You're in a spot
to be testing me.
What happened to my men?
What men?
The men who were
working this camp.
I don't know.
Probably the same thing...
will happen to us
when the sun goes down.
What areyou doing?
This animal's Doug Spinney.
He's responsible
for all the monkeywrenching.
He's probably a murderer.
I'm no murderer.
You're a liar.
Let's hear him out.
Ifwe stand around,
there will be nothing left to say.
Think about getting
that generator started.
Darkness is our enemy.
What's he talking about?
Someone want to give me a hand?
Now he's giving orders?
I'm the one...
who fixed the damn thing.
Mulder:
It's all right.
Why did you say
that darkness was our enemy?
That's when they come.
When who comes?
I don't know what it is.
They come from the sky,
take a man right offhis feet...
and devour him alive.
I saw it happen.
Happen to who?
(Engine Sputtering)
(ldling Smoothly)
I need to eat.
I haven't eaten in three days.
What kind of B.S. story
is that, huh?
You believe that?
We found something
in the forest.
What?
A man caught in some kind...
ofinsect cocoon.
What happened here?
We camped two valleys over,
four ofus.
Three now.
More rats in the woodpile.
Our truck has a dead battery.
We drew straws to see
who would make the hike...
to steal one
from the loggers.
Why notjust hike out?
It's over a day's hike.
No waywe wanted to be caught
in the forest after dark...
not after
what happened to Teague.
That's the man you said
was devoured alive?
Yeah.
Why areyou out here?
Camping.
The kind ofcamping you do
is a federal offense.
just hold offa second, okay?
No, he's right.
This man
is an admitted felon.
He could be arrested.
What aboutyour offense,
my friend, huh?
What aboutyour offense
against nature?
We operate within the law.
We pay for the right
to take those trees.
Well, your logging crew
is taking trees...
that are marked and protected...
so don't talk to me
about breaking the law...
sir.
They've taken marked trees?
Yes, sir, marked in orange.
Old growth trees?
You know anything
about that, Steve?
No.
You going to take
this man's word...
over mine?
You don't want to go
out in the night.
Take myword on that.
It's out there.
Ifl go out that door...
something's going to eat me
and spin me in its web?
Yes.
It's too polite to come in here...
and get me?
For some reason,
it's, uh, afraid ofthe light.
It's afraid ofthe light.
There may be something
to what he's saying, Steve.
He's a murderer, clever enough
to make up a story like that...
even whip up that cocoon
to save a few trees...
and I'm going
to prove I'm right.
This is ridiculous.
Where is it, Spinney?
I thought it was going
to come and devour me.
Humphreys:
Here I am!
(Zapping)
Come out, come out,
whereveryou are.
Aw, don't be shy.
Come on.
Huh?
It'sjust like I told you.
There's nothing out here
but a bunch oftrees...
that this man values
more than human life.
I'm going to see him
tried on murder charges.
What doyou think?
I think
I'm going to suggest...
that we sleep
with the lights on.
(Sighs)
(Zapping)
You see this Douglas fir?
It's been standing here
since before time...
and your men cut it down.
Scully:
Who marks these trees?
Federal Forest Service.
You're only supposed
to cut trees...
with a blue X.
Mulder:
It must be hundreds ofyears old.
Scully: Must get a lot oflumber
from a tree like this.
Thousands ofboard feet.
Hell ofa lot easier...
than taking a lot
ofsmaller, younger trees.
Monkeywrenchers
like Spinney here...
are not above marking trees...
with their own paint.
This tree's 500 years old
ifit's a day.
Mulder:
Look at this.
What would this represent?
I don't know. I've never seen
a ring like that before.
Those center rings
are older rings, right?
Yeah. Every ring represents
a season ofgrowth.
And you see these?
These are 500, 600 years old.
They're a recorded history
ofrainfall and climate.
But this one, I don't know.
I should take a core sample.
We finished
with this nature walk?
What happened
to those loggers?
We're determining that.
Don'tyou think...
you should be
interrogating this man?
I don't think he did it.
I want him arrested.
He's not leaving.
No, not with a gun on him.
What happens
ifhis three buddies show up...
and do toyou what they did...
to those two federal
forest officials?
I just want to take
a core sample.
I got families who want
some answers about loved ones...
answers not found
in that tree.
The only crime is
the death ofthat tree.
Yeah, well,
we'll see about that.
Whereyou going?
I'm hiking down toyour truck...
and get some people up here...
who will take action.
Steve!
Let him go.
Let him find out for himself.
This is odd.
This yellow ring's
got something living in it...
some kind of...
tiny bug.
It doesn't make sense.
Why not?
Well, parasites attack
a tree in a variety ofways...
but they always attack
the living parts:
the leaves, the roots,
the new growth rings.
Even ifthey're borers
ofsome kind...
theywouldn't be working
so deep in the tree.
Maybe the wood
in this ring is different.
They seem to be
feeding on it.
Can you identify them?
It's a wood mite ofsome kind.
Could they have been living
in that tree for hundreds ofyears?
No. Inner rings
are dead wood.
The tree's vascular system...
is limited
to the outer few rings.
They need water to survive.
They appear to be hatching
out ofthe wood.
Maybe when you
drew out this core...
you tapped into a larger nest.
Spinney:
Can they build a cocoon?
Right after that tree was
cut down is when Teague died.
It's about the same time that
the loggers disappeared too.
You think these mites
killed the men?
Maybe they been dormant
for hundreds ofyears.
Maybe theywoke up hungry.
Damn it!
(Sighs)
(Humming)
All right,
you monkeywrenchers...
come on out now.
I know whatyou're up to!
(Humming)
(Horn Honks)
(Grunting)
(Screaming)
(ldling Smoothly)
Humphreys should have been
back by now.
These bugs
aren't moving anymore.
They're either dead,
or they're asleep.
It's the light.
They don't like the light.
Scully: Usually,
bugs are attracted to light.
Spinney: These obviously
are notyour ordinary bugs...
to say the least.
Doyou know insects, Scully?
Uh,just what I learned
in my biology courses.
They're the foundation
ofour ecosystem.
There are lots ofthem,
something like...
200 million per person.
They've been around a long time?
Yeah, something like
600 million years--
before the dinosaurs. Why?
This tree is what,
600, 700 years old?
Yeah.
These rings represent
a history ofclimatic changes...
which means that, in this year
in the life ofthe tree...
there was some strange event
that produced an abnormal ring.
Like what, exactly?
A volcanic eruption.
This whole chain ofmountains...
running from Washington
to Oregon is active.
Remember Mount St. Helens?
Yeah. How does that
explain the bugs?
After Mount St. Helens erupted,
there was radiation unleashed...
from inside the Earth.
Strange things started to grow.
There's this lake where
they discovered an amoeba...
that sucks a man's brains out.
Oh, a brain-sucking amoeba.
It's true. Spirit Lake.
There's documented cases...
ofinfected swimmers.
But an amoeba is...
a single-celled organism
that can be mutated.
An insect is a complex animal.
A mutation
would takeyears to evolve.
Maybe what we're dealing with
isn't a mutation at all.
What ifit's some kind
ofextinct insect larvae...
in that ring--
deposited during
volcanic activity...
brought up through
the tree's root system.
Ancient insect eggs...
thousands,
maybe millions ofyears old...
Iying dormant--
Until those loggers
cut down that tree.
That would be rather
poeticjustice, don'tyou think...
unleashing the very thing
that would end up killing them...
and your friend Humphreys?
And who knows?
Maybe us.
Sweet dreams.
Humphreys might
havejust hiked out ofhere.
We don't know that he didn't.
Maybe we're letting ourselves
get carried away...
with this bug story.
Yeah, maybe.
(ldling Smoothly)
Mulder:
Going somewhere?
No, I was--
Doing auto repair?
You're planning
on cutting out.
My friends
only had enough gas...
to keep their generator
running 20 hours.
They'll die
ifl don't get back.
Why sneak around?
The forest service guy
wouldn't go for it.
He'd never trust me.
He's got no reason to.
Neither do l.
I can save us all.
We've got aJeep.
It'sjust two valleys over.
It needs a battery.
I can be back in the morning.
We can all drive out tomorrow.
You got to trust me, man.
Mulder:
Radio's back up.
It's working?
I'm not getting
any reception...
so the receiver
could be trashed.
What about transmissions?
Can you send a message?
I could try.
This is a call for help.
Is there anyone
at this frequency?
This is Special Agent Mulder
ofthe FBl.
We have an emergency
and a possible quarantine.
Our position is--
(Generator Dies)
What happened to the generator?
I turned it off.
Turn it back on.
The radio's working.
Where's the gas can?
Spinney took it.
He took it?
You mean he's gone?
He left earlier.
He took a battery and gas.
He's coming back.
He gave his personal guarantee?
He gave me his word, yeah.
The man who gaveyou his word
has made an art out ofsabotage...
and defying authority,
and is probably the man...
who put that bullet
through mywindshield.
What would you have done?
We've got one chance,
which is one more than we had.
Or one less.
What doyou mean?
He let Spinney take
the last ofthe gas.
This generator's got
about a quarter tank left.
What about the trucks?
The tanks have been ruptured
or filled with sugar.
By the man we are trusting
to come back for us.
We got to get on the radio
and send a Mayday.
Every drop offuel...
is going to keep
this gennie powered tonight.
I don't want to wait...
hoping somebody heard
that transmission...
when this thing quits running
about 2:00 in the morning.
Doyou?
(Sighs)
(Groans)
Mulder--
It's done.
I shouldn't have let him go.
Let'sjust move past it, okay?
Fine.
What doyou suggest?
I don't know.
We'll think ofsomething.
I thinkwe both
have a good idea...
ofwhat happened
to those loggers...
and what happened
to the group in 1 934.
They only found one cocoon.
It's a big forest.
What would you have done?
Would I have made a decision myself
that affected us all?
Cut the sanctimonious crap.
What doyou want me to say?
We might die up here.
Ifwe're lucky, they'll find
our bodies spun up in a tree...
or they may not
find us at all!
You're right, and we're
wasting time arguing about it.
What areyou going to do?
Button this place up.
Ifwe got to spend
the night in here...
we got to do
everything we can...
to make sure the bugs
stay out there.
I'd be careful with that.
It's the only bulb that works.
(ldling Roughly)
I can see them.
You guys, look at this.
Look. They're coming
through the wall...
down where it's dark.
You see them?
(Gasps Softly)
They're on me!
Mulder:
It's all right.
Scully, Scully--
Get them offme!
Whoa! Watch it!
Stand still!
Stop it!
Can you see them?
Get them off!.
They're notjust on you.
They're everywhere.
That's what that residue is
over everything.
I thought we were safe
in the light!
We are!
I think the light
keeps them from swarming.
We'll be safe as long
as we stay in the light.
(ldling Smoothly)
Howyou feeling?
I'm okay.
They're oxidizing enzymes...
just like firefies.
Maybe that's why
they cocoon their prey--
so that they can oxidize
the proteins...
taken from the fuids
in the body.
What ifthe generator goes?
Will they swarm in here
and drain the life out ofus?
We got an hour and a half
till sunrise.
Then what? It's over
a day's hike out ofhere.
We won't make it on foot
by nightfall.
Maybe somebody
heard our transmission.
Help could be on the way.
You sent that call hours ago.
I mean, help would have
been here by now.
Well, I'm not going
to give up on Spinney.
He gave me his word
he'd come back to get us.
And ifhe doesn't?
We'll think ofsomething.
(ldling Roughly)
(Generator Sputtering)
(Sputtering lncreases)
(Generator Dies)
You got a patch kit
in your truck?
Yeah.
Maybe we can patch this
or get it to hold air.
With the truck's spare, maybe we
can limp down the mountain.
Ifnot, we can get on the radio
and warn them what's out here.
(Thunder Rumbling)
Moore:
See it?
Mulder:
Yeah.
(Low Humming)
Listen.
You hear that?
Moore:
It's a car.
No. It's aJeep.
We got to move.
Let's go! Let's go!
Wait!
What about the body--
Humphreys' body?
Leave it. I've radioed for help.
Where areyour friends?
They didn't make it.
We won't either...
unless we haul ass.
Let's go.
Come on.
Spinney:
Oh!
Damn it!
Moore:
I don't believe it.
You talk about
shooting yourselfin the foot.
(Yelling)
Get out ofthere!
Get in the car!
(Yelling)
(Groaning)
(Screaming)
We have an emergency
evacuation situation.
Requesting quarantine facility
for two...
possibly three victims...
with undiagnosed infection
or exposure...
to unknown biological vectors.
Repeat, that's an emergency
evacuation situation.
Two, possibly three victims--
How areyou feeling?
Better.
How did the tests come back?
Your respiratory charts
were good.
We were concerned...
about the damage
due to inhalation.
There were large concentrations...
ofthe chemical we determined
was luciferin.
Which is what?
The same enzyme
we find in firefies...
and other
bioluminescent insects.
Our entomologists
are still trying to determine...
the specific epithet...
ofthe insects
you encountered.
Scully?
How's she doing?
She's still not out of
the woods, so to speak.
She lost a lot offuids.
Two or three more hours
ofexposure...
she might not
have made it.
I told her it was going to be
a nice trip to the forest.
Howyou going to contain it
to the forest?
What ifthe swarm migrates?
The government has initiated
eradication procedures.
They're quite certain that,
by using a combination
ofcontrolled burns
and pesticides...
theywill be successful.
And ifthey're not?
That is not an option,
Mr. Mulder.
Imade this!