(thunder pealing)
(animal howling)
(neighing, mooing)
(animal roaring outside)
(growling)
(screams)
(growls, yells)
I'm not a killer.
I never meant
to hurt no one.
I'm tired ofmy cattle
being butchered.
That's the fourth one
this month.
Who orwhat
doyou thinkwas responsible?
That cow looked
like a piece ofpaper
that went
through a shredder.
No animal
could do that.
Then areyou saying
that a person
was responsible for this?
I want to remind you
Mr. Parker is free on bond
pending trial.
He's willfully speaking
solely in regards
to this incident
and not about other
litigation.
We can't talk
about Mr. Parker's case
against the Trego
lndian Reservation?
That's exactlywhat I mean.
Wait a second.
This ain't the time
for lawyer crap.
I want to get
this in the open.
You think I killed
an lndian
because we're having an argument
about where my land ends?
We want to settle
in court.
joseph Goodensnake is dead
with a wound from your shotgun.
All I'm saying, it was
no animal I know of.
But it damn well didn't
seem human, neither.
Take a look
at my boy's scars.
It was dark.
We heard a growl. We went
out to protect the cattle.
I could have swore I saw...
red eyes and fangs.
I thought my boy Lyle was...
Look, nobody--nobody--
was more shocked and upset
than I was
to find out
it was thatyoung lndian boy
but ifhe killed
our cattle--
I'm very sorry that we had
to find out about it that way
but as far as I'm concerned
that's the end ofit.
Can we see the corral?
I'll takeyou
out there.
Agent Mulder?
Yeah?
Agent Scully...
I suppose ifl were hearing
our side ofthe story
it might not hold up too well--
parts I don't understand
myself--
things my father could never try
to explain to a stranger.
What kinds ofthings?
For the last few months
wheneverwe'd go outside
at night to check the cattle
we never saw anything
out ofthe ordinary--
not a mountain lion,
not a coyote
not even anyTregoes,
Agent Scully...
but I can feel it--
something not human--
out there...
watching me.
The airwas more still.
The night animals
more quiet.
It was like nature herself
was terrified.
Gave me the creeps.
The creeps?
Yeah. The creeps.
Don'tyou ever get the creeps?
The victim was shot there
about three meters
from where Parker fired.
There's no way he could have
mistaken a person for an animal.
It's open-and-shut,
Mulder.
You know, I'm surprised
you volunteered
for this assignment.
Any Bureau agent could have investigated
this reservation homicide.
Why areyou
interested?
Well, there seems to be
nothing unexplainable
about this case.
Nope.
Not a thing.
This is so odd.
It's almost like a snakeskin
that's been shed.
I suspect the Parkers
knowingly killed Goodensnake.
They hardly seem the type
to skin theirvictim.
Police and coroner's report
make no mention ofsuch an act.
Scully:
We'll have to look
at the body ourselves.
Mulder:
The body's been transferred
to reservation authorities.
We're supposed
to get in touch
with a SheriffTskany.
Excuse me.
We're not from around here.
We're looking
for SheriffTskany.
Anyone know CharleyTskany?
Man:
Go home, F.B.I.
How did you know?
I could smell you
a mile away.
Well, they told me that even though
my deodorant's made for a woman
it's strong enough
for a man.
I was at Wounded Knee in 1 973.
What I learned
fighting the F.B.I. is
you don't believe in us,
and we don't believe in you.
I want to believe.
Whyyou here?
What areyou looking for?
You know
what we're looking for.
You tell me what I know.
We're looking
for information
on the homicide
ofJoe Goodensnake.
We're looking for anything
that can create human tracks
in one step
and animal tracks
in the next.
Parker. He found
whatyou're looking for.
He killed
whatyou're looking for, F.B.I.
Parker and his kid killed
my brother.
You're all too afraid
ofsome stupid lndian legend
to do anything.
Gwen!
The suits come
when theywant something
but when we need help
they're nowhere to be found.
SheriffTskany?
I'm Agent Scully
and this is Agent Mulder.
Goodensnake's body
is in my office.
Bill, Tom.
Let them through.
Come on, boys.
Who are they?
Guardians ofthe dead.
They escort the deceased
spirits to the new world.
I let them
as far as the front door.
I keep ancient beliefs out there
and police work in here.
The woman in the pool hall
said people were afraid
ofsome legend.
What do they believe happened?
I'm not a park ranger
here to answer questions
about lndians.
Whenever I need federal help
I never get it.
Since this case falls
under thejurisdiction
ofthe F.B.I.
you're entitled to examine
the body.
So let's get it overwith.
Mulder:
Was the woman in the pool hall
his sister?
Gwen. She andJoe
are primarily responsible
for fueling the boundary
dispute with Parker.
They felt
he had been grazing his cattle
farther and father
onto the reservation.
Parker probably told you it was
his idea to settle in court.
joe and Gwen
filed the suit.
Take a look
at that scar tissue.
Looks like he had been attacked
by an animal as well.
Tskany:
CouldJoe have been
attacked also?
Maybe the Parkers
did see an animal.
No. Those wounds
have been healing
for quite some time.
The shotgun wound indicates
point-blank range.
The pellets entered the body
in a single mass.
The assailant couldn't have been
more than three feet away.
We need to take a look
at Goodensnake's dental records.
These are the canine cuspids.
They're normal.
Could his records
have been switched?
The second incisor
is chipped
just like the ones
in his mouth.
These match
joe Goodensnake's.
There are cases
ofcalcium phosphate salts
developing abnormally
with age but...
That could account forwhatJim Parker
claims to have seen.
He was out that night
expecting to see
a mountain lion.
He gets rattled and the fashlight beam
catchesJoe here.
Parker saw what
he wanted to see-- an animal.
Lyle has scars
just likeJoe.
Doyou have a facility
for an autopsy?
Why?
IfJoe's teeth are abnormal,
an autopsy might reveal
abnormalities in the interior
ofhis anatomy.
I can't allow that.
I'm fully qualified.
No. The funeral is tonight.
It's a cremation.
After that we'll have nothing.
Tregoes believe that
the recent dead are unsettled
by their new condition
as spirits.
Any desecration ofthe body
angers the spirit
and keeps it haunting
this world.
A law enforcement officer
can't destroy evidence.
Don't tell me what I can't do.
Native Americans believe
there are laws greater than
that ofthe U.S. government.
Iftheywant
joe at rest
that's the way it's going to be.
Ifyou want
to make
an issue out ofit
with your authorities
go right ahead.
Charley, doyou believe
that the spirit
ofJoe Goodensnake
is in that room?
All I know is
tomorrow, the day after,
you're going to leave
but I have
to stay here.
I've got to answer
to these people.
You can continue
your investigation.
You're going to have to do it
withoutJoe Goodensnake's body.
(man chanting)
Scully: Since we've been here
you've acted
as ifyou expected to find
every piece ofevidence
we've come across.
What aren't
you telling me?
Why are we here?
A true piece ofhistory,
Scully--
The very first X-File
initiated by
j. Edgar Hoover himselfin 1 946.
During World War Il
a series ofmurders occurred
in and around the Northwest.
Seven here
in Browning alone.
Each victim was basically
ripped to shreds
and eaten
as ifby a wild animal.
However, many ofthe victims
were found at home
as ifthey allowed
their killer to enter.
In 1 946, police cornered
what they believed to be
such an animal in a cabin
in Glacier National Park.
They shot it
but when theywent in
to retrieve the carcass
they found only the body
of Richard Watkins.
Sounds like
the Parker scenario.
The murders stopped
thatyear.
Because the cases were unsolved
and so bizarre
Hoover locked them away
hoping that people around here
would forget about them.
This file indicates that
they started again in 1 954.
And '59, '64, '78,
and now again in '94
but...
Here it comes.
These animal-man
related murders
predate the oldest X-File
by 1 50 years.
Members ofthe Lewis and Clark
expedition
wrote oflndian men who could
change their shape into that ofa wolf.
What this folder describes
is called lycanthropy.
It's a type ofinsanity
in which
an individual believes
that he can turn into a wolf.
I mean, no one can physically
change into an animal.
How can youjust
dismiss the evidence--
the tracks in the mud,
the shredded skin
a man with the teeth
ofan animal?
Even ifyou're right
andJoe Goodensnake did somehow
have the ability
to transform physically
into an animal
he's dead.
jim Parker shot him.
In a couple ofmoments
his bodywill be burned.
End ofmystery.
Let's hope so.
You don't belong here.
Gwen...
You're around to wrap
upyour investigation.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry
aboutyour brother.
I feel sad for anyone who loses
a part oftheir family.
A part?
He was mywhole family.
I'm it now.
As a demonstration
ofsorrow
I'm supposed
to give away
all my brother's
possessions.
Gwen, I don't know
what to say.
It's no big deal.
He had more possessions
than he had friends.
I read the report
ofyour investigation
into the Goodensnake homicide.
It was very good.
It was thorough, professional.
But what I want to know
is offthe record.
What doyou think
really happened?
Your explanation,
Agent Mulder
is lying on
that burial platform.
Why don'tyoujust accept
that and go home?
Charley, doyou believe
in shape-shifting?
This is a funeral.
(drums beating)
(man chanting)
(group chanting)
(chanting)
(chanting continues)
- Get out!
- I want to show my respects.
I don't wantyour respects.
I wantyour heart to grow cold.
I wantyou to feel
what I'm feeling!
I thinkyou better
leave, Mr. Parker.
I wish your brother
could be here.
I wish that more
than anything else.
(faint growl)
(clinking)
(growling)
By the way
the body's been mutilated
I'd say he's been attacked
by a large predator
or somebodywanted it
to look that way.
Doyou think
this is retaliation
for the death
ofJoe Goodensnake?
I don't know.
Haveyou talked
to Gwen Goodensnake?
She seemed pretty upset
last night.
She's gone. Nobody has seen her
since the funeral.
I've put an A.P.B. out on her.
And what about Lyle Parker?
We can't find him either.
He could be dead
as well.
I'll take a look around.
(growling)
(growls)
(scully gasping)
That's not from any animal
I've ever seen.
Sheriff, I think
it's time we had a talk.
An exchange ofideas?
Scully: Mulder!
I'm taking Lyle
to the hospital.
He's suffering
from exposure.
When he's been checked out
I'm gonna question him.
What areyou hiding?
I thought it was over.
Over?
Is that whyyou wouldn't
allow an autopsy
onJoe Goodensnake's body?
You thought it would all end
when he was cremated?
What wereyou afraid we'd find?
I can't tell you
but I'll takeyou
to somebodywho can.
I'm ashamed
to say it
afterwhat happened
at the funeral.
I picked up some bourbon
and I don't remember a thing
after that.
Sometimes, when I'm down
I go out to where me and my dad
keep stray animals
that wander in on the ranch.
I just watch them, you know.
Keeps things in perspective.
Anyway...
my mom--
when she was alive--
was the one that started keeping
those animals.
I guess I go out there
and think about her too.
God, I must have
been reallywasted
to run around there naked.
You must have thought
I was one ofthose animals.
When you did go home,
did you talk toyour father?
No. He'd have been mad
I even went to the funeral.
I... I have...
an image ofhim
sitting on the front porch
but... I don't remember
talking to him. Why?
Your father is dead.
I'm sorry.
(sighing)
It appears as ifhe's been...
attacked by an animal, but...
I suspect it may be homicide.
Lyle, I lost my father
recently
and I know
how overwhelming...
Was it my fault?
By going to the funeral
did it anger them
into killing my father?
I don't know.
I can deal with death.
You know, living on the ranch,
being close to nature and all
you see how it all works.
Things are born. Things die.
Everything else
falls in between.
But ifl caused it...
Ifl brought it on
I couldn't, uh...
I... I...
I saw it once with my own eyes.
It was a long time ago.
It seemed like a dream.
I was a boy.
Was that 1 946?
The Watkins case?
I sense
you're different, F.B.I.
You're more open
to Native American belief
than some Native Americans.
You even have
an lndian name-- Fox.
You should be " Running Fox"
or "Sneaky Fox."
just as long
as it's not "Spooky Fox."
Tell me, lsh--
what did you see?
Watkins had been attacked
by an animal
when he was alone in the woods.
His scars healed.
It was forgotten.
Then the murders began.
The Tregoes--
we realized that Watkins
had been attacked
bywhat the Algonquins call
the manitou
an evil spirit capable
ofchanging a man into a beast.
To be attacked by a manitou
causes the victim to become one.
The healed scars
onJoe Goodensnake's body.
The manitou overtakes a man
by night, not by full moon
but when its blood lust builds
to uncontrollable level
the man changes
to a sickening creature.
It kills,
releasing a savage energy.
The man returns to his true self
unaware ofwhat has happened.
The cycle begins anew
the next day.
This continues until death.
One night
when I was 1 6 years old
I was coming back from fishing
in the Cut Bank Creek.
I knew a shortcut
behind Watkins' house.
There was a... a groan.
Not animal, but not human.
I looked into his window.
He was covered
in sweat and blood.
He was in a great, great pain.
His arm--
the skin ripped.
It tore up
and fell to the foor.
Claws sprang
from his fingernails.
He turned, screaming
and he saw me.
His eyes...
his eyes were still human.
They begged me to kill him
and ifl had been hunting
and had my gun
I'd have done it
without a second thought.
But being a boy,
and scared to death
I ran away.
Shortly after,
the police killed him.
But the manitou rose again.
Eightyears later.
But with Watkins dead
how could there have been
an attack by a manitou?
Watkins had a son.
It could be passed
along bloodlines.
Gwen.
IfJoe Goodensnake
was this creature
then perhaps it didn't originate
in him by the first attack
but was handed down
through the bloodlines.
Gwen could have it also.
Gwen could have killed Parker.
(low metallic clank)
(engine starting)
Gwen!
No, no, no..!
Charley:
You're under arrest
for stealing lsh's car.
What happened?
What areyou running from?
I saw it.
I saw it kill Parker.
Let her up.
I went there after the funeral.
I was going to mess up the kid.
So I waited.
Parkerwas on the porch.
Then this thing,
this animal--
Oh, my God!
(sobbing)
I've never been
so scared.
I ran, and I hid
in the woods all day.
I wanted to get out...
I wanted to get out ofhere.
I wanted
to get out ofhere.
Bring her inside.
(crying)
Thankyou.
Hello. This is DoctorJoseph.
This is Agent Mulder
from the F.B.I.
I was told I could reach
Agent Scully at this number.
We released Lyle Parker
from the hospital.
She's taking him back
to the ranch.
I can reach her there?
Uh-huh. Theyjust left.
There's something
I feel you should know.
I received the blood tests
performed on Lyle Parker
and there's something
rather unsettling.
What's that?
Traces ofhis father's
blood type.
It can only be there
through ingestion.
Power's out.
Yep. Happens to us
all the time
being out here
in the sticks.
I'll fire up
the generator.
(gasps)
You okay?
I feel sick.
Please, help me
into the bathroom.
Damn. Keeps disconnecting.
The mountains must be
blocking the signal.
How much farther?
About seven miles.
(gasping)
Lyle, let me come in.
Lyle, I want to takeyou
back to the hospital. Okay?
No! I'll be all right.
(gasping)
Lyle?
Lyle, answer me.
(gasping)
Lyle, areyou
all right?
(grunts)
(roaring)
(growls)
(yelling)
(gasps)
(whispering loudly:)
Scully!
(growls)
(growling)
(gunshots)
(growls)
Aah!
It's okay. It's me.
I don't know
what happened.
Somethingjumped me downstairs.
I lost my gun.
I heard it come up here.
Come on.
Okay.
(growling)
(gunshot)
You all right?
Oh, my God.
He was
in the bathroom sick
and then we were attacked
by the mountain lion.
Mulder:
It wasn't a mountain lion.
Charley:
It's still in a cage.
Where's Gwen?
She said she'd come
see us before we left.
She left last night.
Gave away all her possessions
to her friends.
just pulled up
and left? Why?
Her brother's gone,
no family.
Trouble with Parker
is all over.
Maybe she saw something that
she wasn't ready to understand.
Maybe.
Well, thankyou.
F.B.I.
Seeyou in about...
eightyears.
I hope not.