Relax. They'll be here.
Banks going to close
in five minutes.
Sure it wasn't a bogus tip?
It's real.
I've been on this long enough.
I know the difference.
Besides, I can feel it.
I'm inside their heads.
just as long as you keepyours.
Message received,
Agent Scully, loud and clear.
Position five.
It's Agent Willis.
Doyou copy?
What, areyou nervous?
Nope.
I just don't want
our luck to run out.
Baby, you are my luck.
No matterwhat happens
whenever I look up
at the stars
I knowyou're going to be
looking up at the same ones.
The same ones, baby.
You make every day
like New Year's Eve.
Get down!
Get down on the ground!
I want everyone
on the ground now! now!
Get down!
You too-- on the foor!
On the foor!
I'll execute all ofyou!
(woman screaming)
Put the money
in the bag now!
Move!
Freeze!
Drop the gun! FBl!
Drop the gun--
Now!
I need more saline
in here, stat.
Up to 360, now.
1 1 minutes, 55 seconds.
Clear.
Come on,Jack.
He's been fatlined
for over 1 2 minutes.
Another amp of EPI
and we'll go again at 360.
Clear.
(sighs)
I'm sorry.
You want me to pronounce?
No.
You can't give up on him.
It's been 1 3 minutes. He's dead.
Go up to 400.
We lost him. Let him go.
I'm a doctor.
Go up to 400
or I'll do it myself.
Clear.
Give him another amp
of EPI intracardial
and go up to 400 again.
Do it.
Clear.
Again.
Come on,Jack.
Clear.
We got a rhythm.
Don't ask me how,
but he's back.
B.P.'s 80 over 50
and climbing.
90 over 50...
Hello, Mr. Goldbaum.
How are we doing tonight?
(gunshot)
Anyword from Willis?
Still missing.
He hasn't been home or
checked in with the office.
I heard something
about a mutilation?
Yeah. Three fingers
on Dupre's left hand
were severed
by surgical shears.
We lifted prints.
They're Willis's.
He was chasing this guy
almost a year?
Yeah, he lived the case.
It was all he thought about,
talked about.
What areyou thinking?
That maybe this is some kind
ofpost-trauma psychosis.
Like the way soldiers
sometimes mutilate a dead enemy.
That still doesn't explain
why he would
just vanish.
Dupre's partner--
who was she?
Lula Phillips.
They met while
she was serving
a ten-year sentence
for manslaughter
at the Women's Correctional
Facility of Maryland.
He was a prison guard.
Until the warden found out
their secret.
According to Lula's cell mate
they carried on
quite a torrid romance.
It says she was released
on May 2, 1 993.
One week
before the first robbery
at Annapolis Savings and Loan.
The 65-year-old female teller
was pistol-whipped.
Died from
a subdural hemorrhage
because she didn't get
the money fast enough.
Lovely couple.
They took turns--
one pulling ajob
while the other one
drove getaway.
The two ofthem
have killed seven people
and gotten away
with close to $1 00,000.
That's a lot ofmoney.
Now she doesn't
have to split it.
We're putting
her face out there--
Iocal newspapers,
America's Most Wanted.
Am I boring you?
Theywere married.
Yeah, last May in Atlantic City.
So what?
I don't think this was a simple
necrophiliac mutilation.
Willis sliced and diced
those fingers to get
at the wedding ring.
Anybody here?
Lula?
Baby, baby, baby.
Damn.
Scully:
It's a left thumbprint.
You can see that whoever
held that cleaver
was using his left hand.
"Whoever"? It was Willis.
Willis is right-handed.
I checked his pistol grip
at the armory.
Bank surveillance tapes
show Dupre is left-handed.
I'm not sure
whereyou're going.
How long
did Willis fatline?
just over 1 3 minutes.
This is the E.K.G. strip
that recorded
his cardiac activity
at the time.
In your medical opinion,
what does that look like?
It could be anything--
an instrument malfunction,
electrical overload.
But what does it look like?
Two heartbeats.
Dupre and Willis
went into cardiac arrest
at the exact same time, right?
Right.
Which means for minutes,
both men
were technically dead.
Technically,
but we resuscitated Willis.
You resuscitated his body.
Mulder...
Two men died in that crash room.
One man came back.
The question is...
which one?
What can you tell me
about near-death experiences,
Agent Scully?
The usual stuff--
the tunnel, the light
people rising up and viewing
their own bodies.
How doyou account
for the phenomenon?
Some sort ofdissociative,
hallucinatory activity.
Did you know that
halfofall adults
who have had
a near-death experience
can't wear a watch?
The increased electrical
activity in their bodies
renders the watches
inoperable.
Now, I know
this sounds kooky
but as any biologist
will tell you
when cells die
and genetic material unfolds
tremendous energy is released.
Mulder:
Dr. Varnes believes
this burst ofenergy
is responsible for the
transformational nature
ofthe experience.
People do return
profoundly changed.
Changed how?
Personality shifts,
perceived psychic abilities
increased zest for life.
What about
the negative consequences?
They're rare, but apparently,
in the process ofdying
there is a window oftime during
which the body is vulnerable.
I don't understand.
There was a pilot
in my support group
who died
in a commuter plane crash
along with
his three passengers.
This was a fewyears ago.
He recalls foating up
and then feeling
an overwhelming need
to return to his body.
He was revived
in the ambulance--
the only survivor.
It was soon after that
that the visions started.
Visions ofmaking love
to his wife in ways and places
that weren't in his memory.
A dead passenger on the plane
was having an affair
with his wife.
The dead passenger's
consciousness
survived through the pilot.
What happened?
The pilot became
increasingly disoriented--
a schizophrenic,
his doctor claims--
until one day he strangled
his wife with an extension cord.
That's a nice story.
I don't discount
the near-death experience
because it can be explained
by stimulation
ofthe temporal lobe.
I sense a big "but" coming.
It's my best guess
jack's disappearance
can be explained
in psychological,
not supernatural, terms.
For instance?
The stress ofthe case,
the trauma ofbeing shot
jack's personality.
How well doyou know him?
We dated for almost a year.
He was my instructor
at the academy.
The plot thickens.
We even had the same birthday.
We used to celebrate
in some dive in Stafford
that had
a slanting pool table.
But it was always
so hard
forJack to relax.
It was impossible for him
really.
He was always so intense,
so relentlessly determined.
Doyou believe he's predisposed
to this type
ofpsychotic episode?
It's a long way from saying
jack had a near-death experience
to saying his body's
been inhabited byWarren Dupre.
A long way.
What the hell?
You're such a creature
ofhabit, Tommy.
Who the hell areyou?
Get out ofbed.
I ain't got no clothes on.
I don't want to shootyou
lying down.
Areyou the rent man?
'Cause I'm all paid up.
Come on,
you can go ask Cosmo.
Shut up.
Where is she?
Where's who?
Your sister.
Lula?
I don't know.
I was waiting to see her
on the news.
What I tell you?
Check it out.
The sound's busted.
Looks like
they'll find her
beforeyou do, pal.
Is that whatyou think?
That's not what I think.
I miss her, Tommy.
I miss her so bad.
That's why I came back.
Do I knowyou from somewhere?
Everything I see, I see her.
jesus, man, you're bleeding.
Even ugliness is beautiful
because ofher.
Okay, what areyou doing?
You set us up, Tommy.
You sold us out to the FBl.
Dupre?
(gunshot)
Neighbors heard a gunshot
but nobody bothered
to check it out.
The patrol guys
responded this morning
to an anonymous 91 1
and found him here
except the rats
found him first.
The victim's name
was Thomas Phillips.
That's Lula's brother.
There's not a lot
offamily resemblance left
between the rats
and the .45 he took
in the face.
Oh, I hate
this nicotine stuff.
What's his story?
He's single.
He's lived here alone
for seven months.
A few priors,
small stuffmostly--
B and E,
narcotics possession.
Nothing like
his big sister.
Was the television turned on
when they found him?
No. Why?
I don't thinkTommy
was a reader
since he doesn't own any books.
From the position
ofthe body,
maybe he
was watching the tube
when he was shot.
Print kit's over there.
Knockyourselfout.
Out ofmyway, ace.
Regulations state
to gain access to a crime scene
you got to show me l.D.
Looks like
you were right.
Excuse me.
jack...
(gunshots)
Is there a problem here?
No, I just don't have
any l.D.
and would you tell
this gentleman who I am?
This is agentJackWillis.
He's with the Violent
Crime Section
ofthe Washington Bureau.
Let's talk out here.
I wasjust doing myjob.
For God's sake, Willis,
what happened?
Halfthe Bureau's
been looking foryou.
Where haveyou been?
I don't know.
I just... wasn't myself.
I woke up in the street.
I'm taking you back
to the hospital.
I'm staying right here.
You're not ready to be here.
Who says?
You're recovering
from a major trauma.
It's a miracle
you can even walk around.
This is Tommy Phillips'
place, right?
jack...
Was he killed with a .45?
As a matter offact, he was.
That's Lula's weapon ofchoice.
I know these people.
I've been after them
for a long time.
We're halfway there.
You did open the book
on this one.
I'll be there when it's closed.
All right.
But as a colleague
and as a friend
I'm recommending you undergo
a medical evaluation--
physical and psychological.
All right, fair enough.
jack, good to seeyou
back among the living.
It's good to be back.
jack.
So what do we got here?
Mulder here found
a print on the TV--
a partial oblique--
and it's not
the victim's.
Good work, Agent Mulder.
I'm impressed.
That's fancy shooting.
Yeah, well, I got
to get recertified
before they give me
myweapon back.
I wouldn't worry
about recertification.
Is there anything else
you wanted?
Yeah. It's, uh,
Scully's birthday
and I was wondering
ifyou'd sign that for her.
Sure.
Be glad to.
I'm always glad to celebrate
the good times.
Hereyou go.
Happy birthday, Scully.
You're two months early.
It's from Willis.
I thoughtyou two
had the same birthday.
We do.
Well, that's
news to him.
I asked him to sign it.
You mean you tested him.
After I found out evidence from
the Phillips murder is missing.
What evidence?
The print we lifted.
Our best lead is gone.
Someone stole it before
the lab had a chance
to take a look at it.
And you thinkWillis
is responsible?
I'm not sure
Willis is Willis.
Can you
at least accept
the possibility that during
his near-death experience
some kind ofpsychic
transference occurred?
Can'tyou accept the possibility
that this isn't an X-File?
Aside from the expected level
ofpost-trauma stress
jack passed
both ofhis evaluations--
physical and psychological.
Anyway,
just because someone
forgets a birthday doesn't mean
that he's been possessed.
When I was studying
for my medical boards
I forgot my birthday too.
Did you forget
how to sign your name?
This is a copy ofthe automobile
requisition form
Willis filed the day
before he was shot.
Compare the signatures.
Like I said, Mulder, stress.
We both know it can
significantly affect
someone's cursive standard.
I'm afraid
this doesn't prove a thing.
(phone ringing)
Agent Willis here.
jack, where areyou going?
We got a break.
A landlord in Boyle Heights
thinks he's got our girl.
Hot line?
Yeah. Saw her picture
in the post office.
Can I askyou something?
Yeah, sure.
The print Mulder
lifted offthe television--
it's missing.
And?
And you were carrying
the evidence back.
Areyou implying
something, Agent Scully?
I don't know anything
about any missing print.
Now I'm ten minutes
away from closing
the biggest case in my career.
Areyou coming?
What's that
apartment number again?
Number 202.
Oh, yeah.
What's this guy's name?
Multrevich.
Multrevich?
(knocking)
Mr. Multrevich?
I'm from the FBl,
jackWillis.
We spoke
on the phone.
Oh, yeah.
Haveyou ever seen this lady?
Yeah. 207.
Two days ago.
First and last
month, cash.
Where's 207?
Down the hallway,
round the corner.
Mr. Multrevich, go back
insideyour apartment
and stay away
from the windows.
Where's our backup?
You called them, right?
Yeah, they should have been
here ten minutes ago.
She may be running
down a fire escape.
I'll call it in again.
Look.
That's her.
Where is she?
Where did she go?
I'll check back here.
Aah!
Face down.
Face down!
Hands behind your back.
Now!
She's all yours,Jack.
Yeah.
Like a dog
on a leash.
I already cuffed her.
They're foryou, Scully.
Put them on.
What's going on,Jack?
Put them on,
or I'll blowyou in half.
jack...
Shut up!
Put them on.
Come on, baby.
Come on, get up, baby.
I want to look atyou.
Your face
is all dirty.
Keepyour stinking hands
offme.
Baby, you ain't going
to believe where I've been.
Sure it's crazy.
You don't think
I know it's crazy?
This isn't my face,
these aren't my hands
but it's me in here.
And I knowyou.
I know everything aboutyou, baby.
Come on, ask me something.
Your birthday's April 7.
Your favorite color is red.
Come on.
Come on, ask me
something else.
Come on, ask me.
Okay.
Okay. What did we do
afterwe got married?
Right after?
After that.
Well, we went down
to the beach.
I took out my buck knife
and I sliced open my palm
and then I slit open
your palm...
and we let the blood
drip down in the water.
Then what did you say to me?
I said,
"This is so we can be married
in all the oceans ofthe world."
And then I madeyou
a solemn oath...
to never take this ring off
my finger.
Ever.
I mean to keep
that promise.
This is...
this isjust too weird.
I can't believe it's reallyyou.
Don't worry, baby.
It won't make any
difference in the dark.
We'll be in touch.
When do I get my reward?
We'll call you.
Now I'm worried.
1 2 hours with no word.
I don't get it.
Why's their car still
sitting out in front?
Why didn't Willis
call for backup?
Because it wasn't Willis
who answered the hot line.
You heard the recording.
It was Willis' voice.
Forget it, Bruskin.
Plus which, the manager
just l.D.'d him and Scully.
I said forget it,
Bruskin.
This isn't one ofyour
X-File theories, is it?
It doesn't matterwhat I think.
We're still after
the same thing.
(phone bleeping)
Mulder.
FBI centrex operator.
please hold.
Yeah.
Guess who, ace?
Willis?
That depends on whoyou ask,
don't it?
Where's Scully?
You're the FBI
you figure it out.
Let me talk to her.
Yeah. Sure.
Mulder?
Dana, areyou okay?
Don't...
Dana?
Okay. That's it.
Good-bye.
It's not going
to work,Jack.
You don't think so?
Bureau policy
prohibits negotiating
with kidnappers.
Butyou already know that,
don'tyou,Jack?
Stop calling me that!
Your name
isJackWillis.
You were born
February 23, 1 957.
You live at 51 Stanhope...
My name is WarrenJames Dupre
and I was born
in Klamath Falls, Oregon
in the Year ofthe Rat.
We spent a weekend
up at Pine Barrens.
You taught me how to fish
through the ice.
It was
your parents' cabin.
jack, try
to remember.
We drove up
in a snowstorm.
Come on,Jack.
Don't think I didn't see
whatyou did.
I was like a little slip
ofpaper up there
on that hospital ceiling.
I saw everything.
What did you see?
You left me to die
on that table
whileyou tried
to saveyour friend!
You are my friend.
Too bad he was gone already.
I watched him go.
just slipped away
down that long, black tunnel.
No. We broughtyou back.
You shot me dead!
And then you let me die.
No.
You won't kill me,Jack.
You call me that
one more time
I'll makeyou stone-cold.
Easy, baby, easy.
Notyet.
Remember,
she's our ticket.
Got any more
ofthis soda?
Lula:
Youjust drank
the last ofit.
Soda?
How much ofthat haveyou had?
What's it toyou?
jackWillis
is diabetic.
Which means you're diabetic.
Too much sugar in the system
could lead to hypoglycemia.
Maybe that's why
your stomach's hurting so bad.
Abdominal pain
is the first sign
ofimpending diabetic coma.
You need insulin.
Willis:
I feel myselfgetting
into their heads
and I'm scared
bywhat I'm feeling.
The intoxicating freedom
that comes from disconnecting
action and consequence.
Theirs is a world where nothing
matters but their own needs
their own impossible appetites
and while the pleasure they
derive from acts ofviolence
is clearly sexual
it also speaks to what
WardenJackson called
their operatic devotion
to each other.
It's a love affair
I almost envy.
A drug store was reported
broken into right here
on the corner ofOld Forge Road
and Madison
I'm betting Scully is somewhere
within this five-mile radius.
Am I missing something?
200 units of N.P.H. insulin
were taken
with a box ofsyringes.
Willis is diabetic.
Get me a census report.
Let's see how many households
we're talking about.
Quick, quick, quick.
My legs are starting
to go numb.
Hold on.
What the hell..?
Drop the needle.
Without this medicine, he dies.
Yes, soyou said.
Now, put it down
unless you want me
to putyou down with it.
What the hell
areyou doing, Lula?
I need that medicine.
You still haven't
figured it out, haveyou?
Figured what out?
It wasn't my brother
who setyou up.
You?
Yeah. Me.
How doyou think
I got away so clean, huh?
The minuteyou stepped
into that bank
I was out ofthere.
I got the money,
and I got rid ofyou.
At least I thought I did.
(groans)
(phone ringing)
Tactical room.
This is it.
Mulder.
Lula:
Listen carefully.
Where's Willis?
Oh, he's lying
around here somewhere.
Let me talk to Scully.
Not this time.
We don't deal
unless we know
Scully is alive.
She's alive.
She's not happy,
but she's alive.
You listen to me--
you lay one hand on Scully,
so help me, God.
Ifl wereyou,
I'd stop talking
and start passing
around the collection hat
'cause ifyou everwant
to see Scully again
it's going to costyou
a million dollars.
Have it by this time tomorrow.
I'll tell you when and where.
We got it.
It's a 202 number.
Great.
Get the address.
Forget it.
Why?
It's Scully's cellular number.
They're using her phone.
We can't trace them.
Lulu: She's not happy,
but she's alive.
Ifl wereyou, I'd stop talking
and start passing around
the collection hat.
That last part, right?
Yeah, but can you squelch
the voice even more?
Yep.
Done.
Ifl wereyou, I'd stop talking
and start passing around
the collection hat.
Yep, yep,
there's something there.
Definitely something
at the high end.
Let me throw on
an extra Z-1 4 filter
and isolate everything
over halfa decibel.
Ifl wereyou, I'd stop talking
and start passing around
the collection hat.
There.
That engine sound.
Let's clean it up some more.
Ifl wereyou, I'd stop talking
and start passing around
the collection hat.
Is that a small plane?
Taking off, by the sound ofit.
Give me a couple more minutes.
We'll guesstimate the altitude
within a couple 1 00 feet.
All right, people,
settle down and grab a seat.
Mulder says
he's got something.
What? An alien virus
or new information
on the Kennedy assassination?
Hey, Mulder's all right.
You should pay attention.
You might learn something
from the man.
We've identified what sounds
like light aircraft taking off.
Now, Washington County
Regional Airport
falls within our area,
just south ofthe state line.
Since takeoffs
are north to south
it's a fair bet
that our target area
Iies along this fight path.
For those ofyou
who remember ninth-grade math
that gives usjust over
three square miles to cover--
roughly 1 ,000 households.
With 1 00 law enforcement
officials at our disposal
at about 30 households
per man per hour
we should be able to canvass
the area in three hours.
Agent Bruskin
will grid the target area
and divide it
among the teams
and for those ofyou
who don't know already
this one's important to me,
so, uh, let's do it right.
Thanks.
Let me see Steinberg
Calder, and Westin.
Scully?
Hmm?
Huh?
Was there snow?
Yes,Jack.
There was lots ofsnow.
I can't...
It was December.
It was the weekend
afterThanksgiving.
I remember...
a red stove.
Yeah. That's right.
There was a...
there was a wood-burning stove
right in the middle ofthe room.
Cold.
Yeah.
So cold.
I remember I had
to wrapyou in a blanket
when the wood ran out.
Yeah.
No.
jack, don't
closeyour eyes.
Come on, keep talking.
jack, keep talking.
Come on.
Get down on the foor!
Get over there!
I'll execute all ofyou!
No.
(gunshot)
Shut up and do it!
(knocking)
just a second.
Who is it?
This is BrotherQuinn.
couldlspeak withyou?
What doyou want?
just a few minutes ofyour time.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
I wonder ifl can interestyou
in the word ofthe Lord--
Ieather-bound
in black or red.
Go away.
This is one-four.
Target sighted.
Well, I guess it's time
to make that call.
He's dead.
It's all on you now.
He's dead because ofyou.
Well...
guess it's over
Whoeveryou are.
Don't move.
jack!
Shut up!
I loveyou.
Don'tyou know?
You're why I came back.
This is Westin.
They battened down the hatches.
There's no clear shot
from this side.
Ditto.
Hold your positions.
Keep radios at two.
All right.
How do we look?
Backup's in
but we still don't know
what's going on in there.
We will soon enough.
I kept a bottle ofmedicine
in the other room.
I'll go get it.
I'll get it foryou.
Look, look, look
I loveyou.
I loveyou, baby.
No.
Listen, listen, listen.
We still have her.
We can get awaywith this.
I don't think so, baby.
Not this time.
jack, put the gun down.
You remember that...
Iight that I talked about?
No.
It's beautiful.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
(gunshot)
No!
All right, FBl!
jack!
FBl!
Areyou okay?
jack!
Hi.
I got this from the morgue
along with the rest
ofhis personal effects.
I thought
you might want it.
" Happy 35th, love D."
I got it for him
threeyears ago.
Next ofkin?
Uh... no.
jackwas an only child.
Both his parents died
when he was in college.
There's a kid
over in Parklawn.
jack's been his Big Brother
so I'm going to go
and see him tomorrow.
What am I going to tell him?
The official story.
Which is?
Fugitive Lula Phillips
died yesterday
in a shoot-out
with federal agents
which resulted in the death
ofSpecial AgentJackWillis--
killed in the line ofduty.
(sighing)
What am I supposed
to tell myself?
Good night.
It's not working.
It stopped.
At 6:47.
The exact time thatJack
went into cardiac arrest
at the hospital.
What does that mean?
It means...
It means whatever
you want it to mean.
Good night.