l'm here in Pasadena
with the NASA
mission control team
as they celebrate
scientific history--
the first close-up photographic
transmissions of Mars
from the Viking Observer
spacecraft--
photos that have created a stir
by revealing surprising
geologic information:
the presence of
large amounts ofwater
locked in Mars'
polar ice caps--
water that some speculate
could have possibly
sustained life
on the planet.
Even more controversial is
one image ofa land formation--
a formation that looks like
a sculpted human face.
However, NASA officials are
denying it as an indication
ofan alien civilization.
lt's nothing more than a trick
oflight and shadows--
a geologic anomaly.
The only sculptors at work
are the solarwinds that blow
across the surface of Mars
at 300 miles an hour,
ten months a year.
l'm seeing--
l've got--
How's it going out there?
There's something out here.
Can you repeat that,
Commander?
lt's coming at me!
Holy God!
Pickup terminalsequence,
M.P.S.
Youhaveago toproceed.
Boostyour
hydraulicpowerunits.
This is Shuttle Launch Control
with Tminus oneminute
fifteensecondsandcounting.
O. T. C. to C.D.R.
Howdoyouread?
Loudandclear.
Goahead.
Rogerthat.
Portsetup two zero.
Copy. Setup two zero.
C.D.R. Houston,
howdoyouread?
Loud and clear.
Sidehatch close out
andwhiteroom
configuration
is complete.
Retractingorbiterarm.
O.M.S. pressure on.
Cabin ventcomplete.
Roger, wesee that.
Allsystemsgo
forA.P. U. start.
Pre-startcomplete.
A.P. U. toinhibit.
Oxygen venthoodretracted.
Externaltankis
atflightpressure.
Lockyour visorsandinitiate
your O2 flow.
Y'allhaveagoodtrip.
Rogerthat.
T-minus20seconds
andcounting.
Go forauto-sequencestart.
Boosterhydraulicpowerunits
havestarted.
Go formain enginestart.
T-minus ten, nine, eight
seven, six, five,
four, three...
Abortliftoff.
System failure.
Repeat. Wehave
anabortedliftoff.
Scully:
What did the note say?
just that they
worked for NASA.
Theywanted to talk to somebody
from the F.B.l.
Why the cloak-and-dagger
routine?
l have no idea.
Think it's a crank?
lt's beginning to look that way.
My name is
Michelle Generoo.
Fox Mulder.
l sentyou the note.
Special Agent
Dana Scully.
l'm sorry to have
to take these precautions.
l few up from Houston
this morning.
l work
at the space center there.
ln what capacity?
l'm the Mission Control
Communications Commander
for the shuttle.
What brings you to Washington?
There may be a saboteur
at work inside NASA.
You have evidence ofsabotage?
l don't know. l may.
Two weeks ago
a shuttle mission
was scrubbed
three seconds before lift-off
when an auxiliary
power unit valve malfunctioned.
lfthe fight
had not been aborted
there was a great chance
the liquid fuel system
and the orbiter
would have exploded
on the launch pad.
This was sent to me
in the mail.
lt's a material analysis
that shows deep-grooved
scoring marks
inside this A.P.U. valve--
marks that could have
caused a malfunction.
Evidence oftampering?
That's what it looks like,
but...
According to the person
who gave meyour names
you have expertise
in unexplained
phenomena.
And what's unexplainable
is how anybody
could have done it.
How doyou mean?
The valve is made
offerrocarbon titanium.
To score that material
would take extreme
launch pad temperatures.
lf NASA looked
at that analysis
theywould say no one could do
that type ofdamage undetected.
Doyou have any idea
who sent that toyou?
No idea.
The official analysis
ofthe malfunction
was simple
mechanical failure.
Does anybody
shareyour suspicions?
lfthey do
they're not talking
to the F.B.l.
l believe in the space program
and the people who run it
but there's
another launch window tomorrow.
My reasons may sound selfish,
but my fiance
is a Shuttle Commander
on that mission.
Scully: Whywould somebodywant
to sabotage the Space Shuttle?
Well, ifyou were
a terrorist
there probably isn't
a more potent symbol
ofAmerican progress
and prosperity.
lfyou're an opponent
ofbig science
NASA itselfrepresents
a vast money trench
that exists outside
the crucible and debate
ofthe democratic process.
And, ofcourse,
there are those futurists
who believe the Space Shuttle
is a rusty old bucket--
a dinosaur spacecraft
built in the '70s
by scientists
setting their sights on space
in an ever-declining scale.
And we thought
we could rest easy
with the fall
ofthe Soviet Union.
Not to mention
certain fringe elements
who accuse our government itself
ofspace sabotage--
the failure
ofthe Hubble Telescope
and the Mars Observer
are directly connected
to a conspiracy
to deny us evidence.
Evidence ofwhat?
Alien civilizations.
Oh, ofcourse.
Look at that--
GeminiEight.
What?
The man we're seeing--
Colonel Belt--
nearly died on that mission.
Made an emergency landing
in the middle
ofthe Pacific Ocean.
You remember that stuff?
You neverwanted to be an astronaut
when you were a kid?
l missed
that phase.
Comein.
Colonel Belt.
l'm special agent
Dana Scully.
And this is...
Colonel Belt.
Fox Mulder. l'm a big fan.
lt's an honor
to meetyou.
You were a big hero to me.
Thankyou.
l stayed up all night
when l was 1 4
to watch your space walk.
Well, now it's like
a stroll around the block.
So... how can l helpyou?
This found its way
to the F.B.l.
Doyou recognize it?
Sure. lt's an auxiliary
power unit valve.
Doyou have
any reason to believe
that the damage done to it
was in an effort to sabotage
the Space Shuttle program?
No.
Any reason
to suspect sabotage at all?
No reason whatsoever.
And ifyou have any respect
for this program
and for the people who have
devoted their lives to it
you'll be careful
to whom you make
those accusations.
Looking at this evidence, sir
would you consider postponing
the shuttle fight
until a full investigation
could be conducted?
l don't know whereyou got
this specious artifact
but every precaution
has been taken
to rectify the problem.
We've been waiting
two weeks
for a window to initiate
this mission.
We've got a payload to deliver.
Has an internal investigation
ever been done on this matter?
The partyou have here
has been installed,
inspected, and designed
by over 1 00
highly trained technicians.
With the security measures
we take
it would be virtually impossible
for one man
working by himself
or two, or four men
to do what
you're suggesting.
l can assureyou
there isn't a person
in this facility
that doesn't want to see
that shuttle go into space
complete its mission
and come back
like winged Victory herself.
And in about ten hours,
God willing
you'll seejust that.
Doyou think
there would be a problem
with us watching the lift-off
from mission control?
Well, being thatyou'd probably
go over my head anyway
please, be my guest.
lt was an honor, sir.
Thankyou.
Didn'tyou want
to get his autograph?
Man: Where did you
sayyou got this?
Scully: lt came to us
anonymously.
This is an A.P.U. valve,
all right.
This doesn't make sense.
What doesn't
make sense?
This scoring here.
This valve is made out
offerrocarbon titanium.
You didn't order the analysis?
No, but we're
on outside contract to NASA.
They may have ordered it.
Wouldn'tyou order
a material analysis
ifa part malfunctioned?
Every shuttle has fown with
that same valve with no problem.
To do an analysis would delay
the program for months
not to mention
the cost.
ln order to avoid delays
is the program
being pushed ahead
without proper
safety precaution?
There are about 1 7,000 things
that can go wrong
with the shuttle
and about 1 7,000 people
who make sure they don't.
Who makes
the final determination
as to its safety?
We make a recommendation
but ultimately, the decision
is Colonel Belt's.
- Thankyou.
What doyou think?
l can't believe how much faith
we put in machines.
You think Colonel Belt
knows more than he's saying?
He lied about his knowledge
ofa saboteur?
l can't believe
Colonel Belt
would endanger the lives
ofthose astronauts
knowing that something
might go wrong.
He was
an astronaut himself.
Soyou think
this X ray is bogus?
God, l hope so.
This is Shuttle
Launch Control
with T-minus oneminute 45
andcounting.
Here we go.
This is Shuttle Launch Control
with Tminus oneminute30.
Finalapproachsequence.
Main engines ready.
Main engine check.
Switchingoff
groundsupply.
Roger, O. T. C.
Houston:Pick up
terminalsequence M.P.S.
O. T. C. to C.D.R.
Howdoyouread?
Charge capacitorenergy
storagebanksareallat241.
O. T. C. to C.D.R.
Howdoyouread?
Loudandclear.
C.D.R. to Houston.
Howdoyouread?
Loud and clear.
Sidehatch closeoutandwhiteroom
configuration complete.
Retractingorbiterarm.
Allsystemsgo
forA.P. U. start.
WehaveA.P. U. start.
B.B.S.R. powerdown
andready forlaunch.
Transfertointernalpower.
Main engines complete.
Aerosurfaces
in launchposition.
Militaryrecorder
is running.
Okay. Copy.
Oxygen venthoodretracted.
Externaltank
isatflightpressure.
Okay, C.D.R., lockyour visors
andinitiateyour O2 flow.
Y'allhaveagoodone.
Rogerthat.
Go forauto-sequencestart.
Boosterhydraulic units
havestarted.
Go formain enginestart.
Tminus tenandcounting.
9, 8, 7,
6, 5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
Zero. Ignition.
Wehave liftoff.
C.D.R. to Houston.
Greatjob.
Roger that.
1 0-4.
Roger.
Throttleback.
Main engine
at 65percent.
Roger.
Throttleat 1 10percent.
Roger, O. T. C.
l have to admit that l fulfilled
one ofmy boyhood fantasies.
lt ranks right up there
with getting a pony
and learning how to braid
my own hair.
You have to admit
that was exciting--
Mission control,
countdown...
Mulder! Wait!
Something's
gone wrong.
What happened?
Something's wrong
with the shuttle.
We had some trouble
with the solid rocket boosters
but we fixed it.
Got a phone call
20 minutes ago.
Communication with the shuttle
had gone down.
We've got to get back
to Houston.
They have a press blackout
in effect.
Chances are, the media
doesn't know about it.
Sabotage?
Things go wrong all the time.
But they usually fix them.
Usually.
She's turning.
Michelle!
l can see her.
Help!
You all right?
l'm stuck!
Can you move?
just get me out ofhere!
l'm wedged in.
You all right?
Come here.
Can you push with your legs?
Be careful.
just get me out ofhere!
Come on. Okay.
lt's okay.
Don't try to move.
Oh, l got to get back
to Houston.
What happened?
l don't know.
Something came at me
in the fog
and next thing l knew,
l was upside down.
Was it some kind ofan animal?
No. lt had a face.
lt was...
lt was grotesque.
l don't know what it was.
You okay?
Yeah.
Orbiter, this is Houston.
Doyou copy?
Your transmission
isbreaking up, Houston.
What's happening?
A malfin the O.M.S.
and R.C.F. systems.
They can't get the orbiter
into attitude rotation.
Cabin temperature is 1 03
and they have
downlink transmission...
What happened toyou?
l had an
accident.
What's their position?
just over eastern Africa.
Try patching them into the Seychelles
Tracking Station.
All right.
Hang in there, O.T.C.
The orbiter maneuvering systems
malfunctioned.
They need to rotate the shuttle
away from the sun
to keep the orbiter cool.
Drop in cabin pressure
21 kilopascals and declining.
They're going to burn up.
Where's Colonel Belt?
On his way.
What happened?
Backup system failed.
Can we auto-activate their
systems from down here?
We cannot.
lt's like
someone's screwing
with the uplink communications
from this end.
Can you trace it?
Digital processor.
They'd have to be
in the data banks.
Where's that?
Come on.
Scully:
Mulder?
l'm a Federal Agent.
Come on out ofthere.
What areyou
doing in here?
l work here.
Let me seeyour clearance.
There was a malfunction
in one ofthe processors.
Did you find it?
No.
Did you see anybody else here?
Call security.
l don't want anybody coming
in or out ofthis building
who doesn't have
proper clearance.
( garbledtransmission )
What's the attitude
ofthe orbiter?
They're fying
tail first, sir
belly towards the sun.
Flash evaporator system
is working
but it's not enough
to cool them down.
Cabin temperature 1 1 6.
Where's..?
Somebody'sjamming
our transmissions.
Somebody or something
is interfering with
our ground communications
and scrambling
our uplink telemetry.
The shuttle
is not responding
to override signals.
l'm cutting off
telemetry.
We might lose contact for good.
We have to give it a chance.
We have to bring them down.
We have to give them
control ofthe ship
to perform
that rotation maneuver
and deliver the payload.
What ifthey can't?
We could be stranding them.
Abandon telemetry.
Go to fy-by-wire mode.
They're cutting off
ground control to the orbiter.
The astronauts will be fying
the shuttle all by themselves.
ls it gonna work?
O.T.C., this is Houston.
How's the weather up there?
Sunny and warm, Houston.
What's the forecast?
O.T.C., we're going
to fy-by-wire mode.
We're going
to abort ground control
to see ifyou can bring
those systems back up.
Roger that, Houston
and leave the driving to us.
David... you take care.
Whatjust happened?
They cut offcontact
with the shuttle.
Generoo:
45 seconds.
lftheywere able
to execute
they'd have done it
by now.
Standing by.
60 seconds.
Go to reestablish
uplink communication.
Video signal's failed.
O.T.C., this is Houston.
Doyou copy?
Where areyou?
Howdy-do, Houston.
Looks like we fiinally
got thisbirdto flyright.
O.T.C., doyou hear that?
Music to ourears.
Cabin temperature
stabilizing.
O.T.C., this is Mark Belt
in Houston.
How's the crew holding up?
They're lookinggood, sir.
Y'all get some rest.
We'll get back to work
at about 0700.
Roger, Houston.
Let's get to work
on that telemetry problem.
We got a big day ahead ofus.
Belt: Let'sjustlet
the electronicpress
get their sound equipment set.
Are we set up in here?
Doyou want to test this mike?
( shoutingquestions )
l knowyou have
a lot ofquestions.
l'll get to them.
How did he know
it was going to work?
He didn't.
They could have died
and there would
have been nothing
we could have done.
They'd have been
a ghost ship
stuck in orbit.
Whywould he take
that risk?
Bring those men back
without delivering that payload?
That's millions
ofwasted dollars.
That's all congress would need
to shut down NASA.
Belt:
As of2200 hours
the crew has been conducting
on-board tests and tasks
and resting up for their
first full day in space.
l'm happy to say
after a beautiful night launch
the shuttle orbiter
has performed magnificently.
( reportersshoutingquestions )
So much foryour boyhood hero.
Colonel Belt?
Can l talk toyou
for a moment?
You want to know
why l lied to them.
You're asking yourself
ifthis means
l'd lie toyou.
You know what it means
to be an astronaut, sir?
You riskyour life
every timeyou get into
your spacecraft
for nothing more
than the good progress
ofmankind.
No argument from me.
You're true American heroes.
Heroes?
We made headlines
when we did ourjob right.
Now they buryyou
in the back ofthe paper.
Name me two astronauts
on the last shuttle.
You make
the front page today
only ifyou screw up.
They only know
your name
ifyou're the unlucky S.O.B.
sitting on 500 tons ofdynamite.
That's what they're
reallywaiting for.
Sir, l have to ask.
l'm sorry,
it's myjob.
Doyou think someone
is sabotaging the shuttle?
My answer toyou, sir, will be
to bring those men back
safely to earth.
Oh, God.
How's it going
out there?
There's something
out here!
Can you repeat that,
Commander?
lt's coming at me!
Holy God!
Houston, wejustheard
something weirduphere.
O.T.C. Houston,
can you describe it?
Sortofa dull thump,
likesomethingbumpedtheship.
Gotanyideasabout that?
( banging )
Thereitis again.
Pull it out?
Yeah.
That one
right there.
They've got
an oxygen leak
onboard
the orbiter.
Our O2 gaugesaregoing
allscrewy, Houston.
We got problems.
We've got an O2 leak
in the main tank.
What happened?
They don't know.
Theyjust said
it was a thump.
An astronomer
in Winnipeg
just spotted
a gaseous cloud
a mile long
trailing in our orbit.
That's the liquid O2
leaking into space.
This happened
to Colonel Belt
on an Apollo mission.
How much time
do they have?
We're doing
the calculations
but it will be
a guesstimate.
l need some answers.
And where is Colonel Belt?
He was due 90 minutes ago
to begin
payload deployment.
Houston? We're wondering
when wehave
tostartholdingourbreath.
We're working on it.
l need those calculations
and a worst-case scenario.
We don't know ifboth O2 tanks
are damaged.
Worst-case scenario!
And someone find Colonel Belt.
We'll find Colonel Belt.
They've got 30 minutes
ofbackup oxygen.
Why does she need Belt?
She doesn't know
how serious the leak is.
lt's an oxygen leak.
Even l know what happens
when you run out ofoxygen.
Colonel Belt's been
in the same situation.
He'll know what to do.
Where the hell is he?
Colonel Belt?
Colonel Belt!
l'm going to go
get security.
Colonel Belt.
Areyou all right?
Yeah. l wasn't feeling well.
They need you
at mission control.
There's been
another accident.
O.T.C.
ls your orbital maneuvering
system still operational?
Roger, Houston. We're ready
forreentry. Justsay the word.
How bad's the leak?
We have no way
to determine.
O.T.C., what's the condensation
on your cabin?
Windowsaregetting
alittlesteamy.
Carbon dioxide buildup.
Okay, O.T.C.
Everything's going to be fine.
l wantyou
to get in your spacesuits
and de-pressurize
your cabin.
And then l wantyou
to vent that CO2.
Andthen what?
l wantyou to stay
in your suits.
l wantyou
to prepare to use
your emergency oxygen systems.
And then
l wantyou...
to...
deliveryour payload.
Those are men up there.
You're out ofline.
You want to tell me
how to do myjob?
l've been up there
in that situation, Miss Generoo.
There's more
at risk here
than your
personal life.
lfyou can't
accept that
or operate effectively
in these circumstances
then maybeyou'd better
leave the decisions
to people who can.
O.T.C.
Doyou copy?
Roger, Houston. We're waiting
on those O2 calculations.
( sniffling )
Scully: Michelle!
They're going to die.
You don't know that.
lt's unconscionable
putting that payload
before those men's lives.
l think she's right.
He's losing it.
He saved
their lives earlier.
Did he, or did he put
their lives injeopardy?
lfhe can't deliver that payload
Congress kills
the space program.
Killing astronauts
won't have the same effect?
l think somebody must have
sabotaged the Space Shuttle.
l think Colonel Belt has known
about it from the beginning.
We've got to stop him.
We've got to pull them out
oforbit.
He doesn't want
those men to die.
He put them up there.
He may be the only person
who can get them down alive.
How can you be certain
that what he's doing
won't save their lives?
l need access
toyour records
in a hurry.
Mulder: l need everything
on the Hubble Telescope
the Mars Observer,
the Shuttle Challenger
and the current
orbiter mission.
That's tens ofthousands
ofdocuments.
What are we
looking for?
X rays, diagrams,
schematics--
any proofthat Belt knew
about a sabotage.
A needle
in a haystack.
Payloaddeployment
initiated.
Roger that, O.T.C.
Tracking it now.
Looksgoodfrom here.
Payloaddelivery
is complete, Houston.
We'reawaiting
yourorder.
System check for reentry
de-orbit burn.
HolyGod, there'ssomething
outside theship--
There'ssomeone
outside theship!
Can you repeat that, O.T.C.?
There'ssome
kindofghost
outside theship!
No!
( whimpering )
No, no, no!
( screaming )
Mulder
l found it.
This is the same diagram
that was sent to Michelle.
Ordered by Colonel Belt,
which means he knew
about the faultyvalve.
This is from the Challenger.
lt's the O-ring fitting
that failed.
lt's dated
one week before
the Space Shuttle blew up.
The analysis was ordered
by Colonel Belt.
You're saying
he might have known
about the Challenger defect?
Something weird
is going on
here, Scully.
Colonel Belt's collapsed.
He's in his office.
He wasjust here.
( whimpering )
Scully: Oh, my God.
Generoo: What's wrong with him?
Mulder: Get a doctor.
( whimpering )
Help me.
How can we helpyou,
Colonel?
He's having some kind
ofa seizure, Mulder.
Come on, come on!
Belt: lt's tearing me apart!
See ifl can get
a pulse.
( moaning )
Help me. Oh, help me.
l'm bringing
that shuttle down.
No!
lt's out there!
Easy, easy.
Belt: Spacesuits!
Give him
Diazepam.
No.
He's going to hurt himself.
He's trying
to tell us something.
Those men
are running out ofoxygen.
They don't have to die.
l wantyou to focus.
Focus your breathing.
Focus your pain.
Right here.
Blood pressure 1 74 over 1 20.
Vitals are rising.
Mulder
you're risking
an aneurysm.
Focus.
Nowyou're focused.
Right here.
Now, you're going
to save those astronauts
and you're going to tell me
how to do it.
The shuttle
can't survive reentry.
No. He's lying.
How doyou know
it can't survive?
The fuselage...
The fuselage is damaged.
The silicone tiles
are destroyed.
How does he know?
How has it
been damaged?
l'm responsible.
Did you sabotage the shuttle?
No, but l couldn't stop them.
Nobody can stop them.
Stop who?
Pulse 1 94.
You'll kill him.
Stop who?
They don't want us to know.
Who?
lt came to me.
lt lives in me.
It's comingatme!
( screaming )
And now--
Help me!
lt's coming back!
Generoo: That's the face
l saw in the fog.
We're losing him.
Defib.
Hereyou go.
Clear.
Hit it.
They're out ofoxygen.
They've got exactly
30 minutes left
in the backup system.
They're going to suffocate
up there.
l've got no choice
but to bring them down.
lt's the only chance l've got.
Again.
O2 standing by...
Hold on.
We've got vitals.
Scully: We've got to get him
to a hospital.
O.T.C., this is Houston
Mission Control.
Doyou copy?
Roger, Houston.
We'vegotsomespookystuff
uphere.
O.T.C., we're going
to bring you down.
We wantyou to instigate
de-orbit burn
and begin deceleration.
Roger, Houston.
I washopingyou'dsay that.
Activating
O.M.S. rockets.
Allsystemsgo
forreentry.
They're bringing
the shuttle down.
You said the shuttle
would burn up on reentry.
ls there anything
we can do to save it?
Change the trajectory.
Change the trajectory
to what?
Change the reentry trajectory
to 35 degrees.
We've got to change
the reentry trajectory.
Generoo: What?
Change it to 35 degrees.
30 seconds
to ionosphere reentry.
Belt...
l can't.
25 seconds.
lt's your only shot.
We'd have to change landing site
and inform them before blackout.
1 5 seconds to blackout.
What's the weather
in Albuquerque?
Are we go
for an emergency landing?
Weather in Albuquerque?
Landing conditions go
in Albuquerque.
T-minus five seconds
to blackout.
O.T.C., this is Houston.
Changeyour trajectory
to 35 degrees.
You'll be landing
in Albuquerque.
lonosphere reentry.
They get
that transmission?
Two minutes
to reestablish.
Damn it.
How much oxygen do they have?
1 6 minutes.
O.T.C., this is Houston.
Come in, O.T.C.
Come in, O.T.C.!
Anything?
What's the point
oftheir new reentry?
West of Hawaii.
Hawaii's picked
the shuttle up
on radar.
They made it.
Not necessarily.
Albuquerque, doyou have
radar confirmation?
Negative, Houston.
Nothingon thescreen.
O.T.C., this is Houston.
Come in, O.T.C.
O.T.C., this is Houston!
Come in, O.T.C.!
Houston, this is O. T. C.
Youknowagoodplace to eat
inAlbuquerque?
We couldmeet
fordinner.
- Whoo!
- O.T.C., welcome home.
You're looking real good.
Man: Yes!
The Space Shuttle
touched down today
at 1 0:56
Central Standard Time.
The orbiter delivered its payload
afterjust 1 3 orbits
and returned to earth
without incident.
We at NASA are looking forward
to our next shuttle mission
and to future successful
explorations ofspace.
For mankind
and for the future
ofmankind.
( beeping )
No...
No more!
( dooropens )
l just heard.
Something had possessed him--
something he must have seen
out there in space.
The doctors who examined him
said he was experiencing
severe dementia.
l don't think
he ever really knew
exactly how it was
working through him
or that he ever knew
that he was...
responsible
for his own actions.
He ordered those X rays
ofthe damaged parts.
l think he was trying
to warn her.
l think that he sent Michelle
those X rays
like he was trying
to reach out to her
without quite
knowing why
as ifhis own
instinctual impulse
was to save those men.
While simultaneously
trying to kill them?
Scully, we send those men
up into space
to unlock the doors
ofthe universe
and we don't even know
what's behind them.
l thinkwhatever it was,
he took it with him.
And in the end,
that was
the onlyway
he knew how to stop it.
There's an investigation,
you know.
They haven't ruled out
foul play.
He gave his own life.
He was an astronaut. That was
something he was prepared to do.
Colonel Marcus Aurelius Belt
devoted his life
to the exploration
and understanding ofspace--
learning its mysteries
and experiencing it
notjust for himself
but for humanity.
Lord, take
this man's soul
and let it rise up
toyour heavens,
higher than he could ever
go as a man.
Let him know the true nature
ofthe universe
that he sought
to learn.
Boy: l made this.