Here, let me do it.
Putyour number in,
then your card.
What's your number, Roland?
Three fifteen.
See how easy it is?
Engine efficiency?
- Ninety-four percent.
- We need more.
How's the back pressure holding?
What doyou think?
It's climbing.
Increase the blade inclination.
I said--
The inclination ofthe blade
is pi over nine.
We've reached maximum velocity.
No!
Let it go!
It will work.
It will destroy itself!.
I'm not going to do that.
It's not going to
destroy itself.
Come on!
We're almost there!
Our equations are wrong.
- What happened?
- Nothing. He pulled the plug.
I'm just protecting the baby--
and fouryears ofwork.
Fouryears that add up to zilch.
Unless we show some progress...
they're going to pull
the plug on us, Ron.
You should have
continued with the test.
Somebody's going
to crack Mach 1 5...
and I want it to be us.
I won'tjeopardize everything
becauseyou two...
can't wait to see
your name in print.
It's print that gets
the money, Ron.
Go down in fames together.
Fine, go ahead.
I'm going to do the math.
Good night, Dr. Keats.
What the hell?
Roland.
Open the door.
Open the door!
Roland, I wantyou to listen
to me very carefully.
We have to open
this door, Roland.
Stop typing!
Roland!
Roland, open the door!
What areyou doing?!
Open the door!
Roland, hit escape.
Areyou listening?
(screaming)
(splat)
How was the wedding?
The part where the groom passed out...
or the dog bit the drummer?
Did you catch the bouquet?
Maybe.
Is that whatyou couldn't
talk about over the phone?
The project everyone says
doesn't exist does exist.
The lcarus project?
The next generation
injet engine design.
Capable ofdoubling
current supersonic speeds...
using halfthe fuel,
at least, in theory.
And Ronald Surnow was
an aeronautical scientist...
who worked on it
here at the university.
- Yes.
- How close are they?
I'm not sure, but Surnow's
the second team scientist...
to die in six months.
But how is this an X file?
Mulder, you don't think...
this has anything to do
with U.F.O. technology?
There's something
unexplainable, Scully...
but it's not unidentifiable.
- Keats?
- There.
Dr. Keats?
We're with the F.B.I.
I'm Agent Mulder.
This is Agent Scully.
We understand you discovered
Dr. Surnow this morning.
What was left ofhim.
How doyou suppose he became
trapped in the wind tunnel?
Someone must have shut him in.
By computer?
We've already been through this
with the police.
Another member ofyour team
died recently...
isn't that correct?
Yes.
Arthur Grable.
He was killed in
an automobile accident in November.
I'm Frank Nollette.
I'm also on the project.
Areyou certain
it was an accident?
What areyou driving at?
Yourwork seems to be...
a perfect target
for industrial espionage.
Who wrote this?
Ron was working on it
when I left.
The handwriting here...
doesn't match
other handwriting on the board.
It isn't mine.
What about Roland Fuller?
Uh... Roland's the, uh...janitor.
According to the police...
he was the only other person here.
Roland didn't do that.
How doyou know?
Let'sjust say Roland isn't
exactly a rocket scientist.
Here.
"Tracy."
- (giggles)
- With stars.
Woman: Roland.
There are some people here
to talkwith you.
Uh-oh.
I went offthe paper.
Sorry.
That's all right, Roland.
Tracy?
Would you help me in the TV room?
Okay.
Hi, Roland.
Mind ifwe sit down?
Thanks.
Mind ifwe askyou
a couple questions?
Doyou rememberworking
last night?
Uh-huh.
Doyou remember seeing
anything unusual?
Seeing any strangers?
Did Dr. Surnow or Dr. Keats
or Dr. Nollette...
do anything unusual?
Nope.
You must like stars.
One hundred and forty-seven.
Sorry?
Stars.
You like numbers, too, huh?
Roland, let me helpyou.
One, two, three...
four, five...
six, seven, eight...
Roland? ls everything okay?
Roland, areyou all right?
Eleven...
twelve, thirteen...
What happened?
What did you say
to upset him so?
Sixteen, seventeen...
It's definitely the work
ofa fourth individual.
Surnow's, Keats' and Nollette's
cursive standards...
don't match whatyou found
on the white board.
Will you do me a favor
and try this?
What is it?
Something Roland
doodled at the home.
You don't really think Roland...
He was the only other person
in the lab.
Yes, but we're talking...
about a sophisticated
fuid dynamics equation.
Roland barely has an l.Q of70.
You saw his facility
with mathematics.
Some autistic individuals
display unusual abilities.
Yes, but even savants...
behave only as human calculators.
They can perform
certain functions...
but they can't tell
the value ofanything...
or the meaning ofa number.
I hate to take sides,
but the bottom line is no.
The terminal stroke on the six,
the roofon the five...
I'm sorry.
He didn't write it.
(gasping)
(grunting)
(loud music from earphones)
(beeping)
(door clicks)
(screaming)
(shattering)
(crunching)
(typing)
Scully: An organic object,
exposed to liquid nitrogen...
will become frozen...
exhibiting great tensile strength...
but is vulnerable to stress
from compression or impact.
Now, I've seen this
demonstrated on a fish before...
I don't think
they'll be performing...
this experiment on Beakman's World.
Has this been dusted?
Treatyourself.
Thanks.
Hey, Scully,
look at these files.
" KMAN" must be Keats.
His file was turned off
at 1 2:31 last night.
Scully: But look.
Someone else entered a file...
under the name "Arthur," after 1 2:31 .
And worked on it
for nearly five hours.
Well, it couldn't
have been Keats.
judging from the rigor ofthe body...
he was dead around 1 2:30.
You're saying someone came in here,
killed Keats...
and worked on
an old Grable file?
I can't access the Arthur file.
We're going to need
the password.
Try 1 5626.
How did you know that
that was..?
This is Arthur Grable's work...
on the same fuid dynamics equations...
the others were working on.
Look at all those entries.
Someone has been continuing
his work since he died.
How did you know
what the password was?
Woman:
Wave good-bye. Wave good-bye.
(child crying)
Say good-bye. Bye-bye.
Wave good-bye.
(door opening)
Roland?
Why did you sleep
in your clothes?
Well, let's getyou dressed.
You have visitors.
I'm not supposed
to talk to them.
Who told you that?
Remember that talkwe had
about being shy?
These are nice people, Roland.
Hey, Roland, you have
more shirts than I do.
I think this one would
look stylin' today.
What doyou think?
- The green one.
- Green one?
Please.
Mrs. Stodie...
can I talk toyou a second?
Seeyou later, Roland.
This one?
Hereyou go.
Soyou likeyourjob
at the college, Roland?
Yes.
I hearyou're
very good at it.
Doyou remember
howyou gotyourjob?
A man talked to Mrs. Stodie.
What man?
Dr. Grable.
Was Dr. Grable nice toyou?
Yes.
When was the last time
you spoke to him?
Last week?
Day before?
Dr. Grable died.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
People die.
They go away...
and they're not supposed
to come back.
Has Roland ever mentioned
the name "Arthur"?
That was Dr. Grable's first name..
but we only called him
Dr. Grable.
I doubt Roland even knew
his first name was Arthur.
Scully:
Mrs. Stodie, can I get a copy...
of Roland's file
and past history?
Our histories are confidential.
I understand...
but I have grounds
to obtain them.
The less time we spend in court...
the more time we have
to help Roland.
Roland Fullerwas hired
byArthur Grable.
He went to the halfway house...
specifically to find
a mentally challenged person.
Areyou suggesting...
Arthur Grable hired Roland
to use him?
Areyou suggesting
Arthur Grable is not dead?
Ifhe had intentions ofkilling
Nollette, Keats, and Surnow...
why not set it up to appear
the least likely suspect?
Yeah, but by the look ofthis,
he's hamburger.
Maybe he staged it.
That would explain why his work
is continuing on...
six months after his death.
This obituary says Arthur Grable
was born in Seattle.
His fatherwas a big banker.
His motherwas active
in a number ofcharities.
Only child.
Summa cum laude in physics.
Doctoral and postdoctoral...
in aeronautical engineering
at Harvey Mudd.
Brilliant future,
tragically cut short.
Roland's also from Seattle.
He spent most ofhis life
at the Heritage Halfway House.
The identity ofhis parents
has been sealed.
There's no information
on Roland before age three...
when he was put in the program.
Does it saywhen he was born?
july 1 5, 1 952.
That's also Arthur's birth date.
Don'tyou wish you could fy?
I can.
When I dream.
People can do anything
in a dream, you know.
Once, one time,
I had a dream we were married...
and lived in a house.
Doyou have dreams, Roland?
You can tell me.
Roland?
Who's Arthur?
I'm sorry, Roland.
I'm sorry.
Roland?
Go away!
Roland, what's the matter?
I don't want to hurtyou!
Go away!
Go away.
Mulder: ls thatyou?
Nollette: Yes.
What's the story here?
(sighs)
Um... a quantum physics
professor ofmine...
at Harvey Mudd funked me.
He challenged the tenets
ofone ofmy theories--
a theory I later published in Nature.
Anyway, to get back at him...
one afternoon,
we decided to take his car apart...
and put it back together
again in his office...
and left it running.
An egghead classic.
It was Grable's idea.
Scully:
ls that Grable on the chair?
Yeah.
Was he a practical joker?
Atop ofall his brilliance...
he had a genius for
executing elaborate schemes.
Could he be making it seem
like a man with a 70 l.Q..
is gaining access to and operating...
his old computer files?
Arthurwould still
have to be alive.
Could he have faked
his own death?
No.
The police report
on the auto accident...
that killed Grable
is woefully incomplete.
A dry road surface,
no mechanical problems found.
The bodywas never admitted
to a county morgue...
and there was no funeral.
Ifyou are trying to suggest...
that Arthur Grable
killed Surnow and Keats...
and is after me next,
you're way off.
Art could not have done the murders.
How can you be so certain?
Man:
This is Arthur Grable.
Because ofthe massive internal damage
to his body...
caused by the car accident,
we could only preserve the head.
Wouldn'tyour client
find it inconvenient...
to be thawed out, only to discover...
he had no functional mobility?
We believe that, by the time
science figures a way...
to revive our clients...
You'll also know how
to clone new bodies.
Exactly.
This technology is progressing faster...
than anyone thought possible.
Ask anyone here
at the university.
So, while for us,
the passing ofeach second...
brings our bodies closer to death...
for our clients,
it brings them closer to life.
These fuctuations in temperature--
Do they happen often?
No. We've had some problems
with this capsule.
Our technicians
have checked it...
but they've found nothing.
Could the brain
cause the fuctuations?
No, but we are looking
for the explanation.
The patient's in no danger.
He remains perfectly preserved...
as long as there's liquid nitrogen
in the capsule.
Maywe take a look
at Arthur Grable's records?
Thankyou.
Dr. Barrington...
in the future,
what requirements will exist...
to be an organ or tissue donor?
Same requirements
as there are today.
Compatible genetic makeup.
It's best ifthe donor's related.
Mulder...
Arthur Grable put down
only one donor.
Mulder: Roland Fuller and
Arthur Grable had the same birthday.
I think they're twins.
Older oryounger?
Same age...
just less hairy
and with better eyesight.
And the moustache?
Scully:
No. Lose the whole beard.
Next?
Close-cropped hair...
with a slightly receding
widow's peak.
Lose the glasses.
That's Roland.
Give or take a few pounds.
Tell me aboutyour dreams, Roland.
It's all right.
I won't tell anybody.
You know,
I had a dream last night.
I dreamt I was swimming
in this pool...
and I could see my father underwater...
but when I dove down,
the water stung my eyes.
Then there was another man
at the pool, watching me.
He upset me.
He was asking me questions
I didn't want to answer...
and I had to leave.
I couldn't find my father.
I can't tell you my dreams.
Why not?
Bad.
Your dreams are bad, Roland...
notyou.
You're a good person.
I hit Tracy.
Your dreams makeyou hit Tracy?
You know how to work
this toy, Roland?
Here.
You see,
the wayyou work that toy...
is like what's happening toyou.
You're the spaceship, Roland...
and your dreams
are the controls.
Who...?
Who runs the controls?
Haveyou seen this man recently?
Woman:
We have to say bye-bye to Roland.
(screaming)
Roland.
Roland!
Roland, stop.
Roland?
We need to keep
Roland under observation.
Roland?
(glass breaking)
He's trying to get away.
Roland!
Nollette's gone.
We should arrange
a security guard to find him.
No one's going
to provideyou with anything...
onceyou explain your theory...
on how Roland Fuller
is capable ofthese murders.
You've got a brother,
don'tyou, Scully?
Yeah, two.
Haveyou ever thought about
calling one ofthem...
and then all ofa sudden,
the phone rings...
and it's one ofthem calling you?
Does this pitch end...
with a way for me to lower
my long distance charges?
Evidence suggests psychic connections...
are stronger between
family members.
Particularly between twins
that shared the same womb.
Okay, but in this case...
one sibling has closer ties
to a frozen Fudgsicle...
than to his own brother.
Arthur Grable is not dead.
He's in a state ofconsciousness...
that no human
has ever returned from.
What ifthat state allows one
to develop psychic ability...
beyond the potential
ofthe conscious mind?
He could use that ability
to control his brother...
to kill those scientists.
But whywould he kill
his colleagues?
That's a question
only Dr. Nollette can answer.
Okay, let's go.
I have to call my brother.
Mulder:
We'vegot to fiindNollette.
Scully:
Let's talk to campussecurity.
Wego this way?
No, wegoleft.
Well, whereveryou are, Arthur...
I'm sureyou'll appreciate this.
Arthur and Roland Grable.
Born at Puget Presbyterian
to Mr. and Mrs. Lewis Grable...
onJuly 1 5, 1 952.
Arthurwas four minutes
older than Roland.
Identical twins.
Which means
they're the result ofa single egg...
fertilized by a single sperm.
I've read studies...
which suggest that, in some cases...
the identical twin arises
very early in the embryonic stage...
when a mutation in one cell
is rejected by the other cells...
as foreign.
So Roland's condition
is the result of...
a damaged chromosome rejected
by one ofArthur's cells?
In a way,
that would explain Arthur's genius...
and Roland's strange mathematical gift.
In a way.
(phone rings)
Agent Scully.
This is Larry Barrington
at the Avalon Foundation.
We've got a situation here.
Uh-huh.
Last night,
we had a break-in at the facility.
That's right.
It's Arthur Grable's storage unit.
His internalthermostat's
been compromised.
Well, is there any tissue damage?
We're trying to assess that now.
The temperature's still rising.
Something's blocking our access
to the cooling program.
Someone tampered with
Arthur Grable's capsule.
They're attempting
to stabilize it now.
Nollette.
What?
What is it?
(alarm ringing)
"Ifl have seen further
than other men...
it's because I have stood
on the shoulders ofgiants."
No.
This isn'tyours.
It's amazing.
There's this body sitting there...
in front ofme talking...
butyou're controlling it, Arthur.
You took mywork.
(snickers)
What good was yourwork
going to doyou?
You died before
you could finish it...
beforeyou could publish it.
It was mine!
And a brilliant piece ofwork too.
When I saw the writing
on the white board...
I knew someone had found the key.
Mach 1 5 was within our reach.
Our futures were guaranteed.
Ironic, isn't it?
You did all the work...
and I get all the glory.
No!
Yes.
Yes, Arthur.
I was here working
on the intake problem...
moments away from a solution
when you attacked me.
Fortunately, I was carrying a gun.
After the murder ofmy colleagues,
who could blame me?
No.
Oh, that's interesting.
(laughs:)
I've got it.
That's it.
I've got it!
(groans)
Arthur!
Arthur, open the door!
Arthur, how doyou stop this?!
Tell me how!
Arthur!
Wait!
Roland, we need you to help us.
Please, we need you to help us...
to stop the machine.
(child crying)
Try to remember how.
Roland, you've got to help him
or he'll die.
Wave good-bye, Arthur.
(screaming)
Mulder:
Come on, Roland.
Roland:
I can't remember...
(yells)
Scully:
He'll be held in...
psychiatric custody for evaluation.
Is he being charged
with a crime?
The D.A. hasn't made
that determination yet.
But we've recommended that
he be remanded toyour custody...
as soon as the court
deems it appropriate.
How could this happen?
Roland never exhibited
anyviolent tendencies.
It's my beliefthat he wasn't
acting under his own volition.
What doyou mean?
This is the work ofArthur Grable,
Roland's brother.
It's a new theory ofjet propulsion...
unfinished at the time
ofhis death.
In the last two weeks Roland has...
completed the calculations.
How?
We're not sure, Mrs. Stodie.
All we know is that Roland...
was somehow able to finish
his brother's research.
Roland?
Where areyou going?
Roland, don't go.
I have to.
Okay. Bye.
Tracy...
wait.
Keep my stars.
I loveyou.
Me too.