[ woman crying ]
Lauren,
l've been looking ev...
Areyou all right?
Doyou want some water?
No. l'm fine.
Oh, honey, it's been
a couple ofweeks now.
Doyou want to talk?
No. Really,Jane, l'm okay.
l just haven't known
a lot ofpeople
who have died, you know.
l've never known anybody
that killed themselves.
Maybe once everything
gets packed away
it will get easier.
There won't be
the constant reminder.
Here's your paycheck.
Come on. Go home.
Okay.
[ electronicbeeping ]
[ screaming ]
Oh, please!
l have no money!
[ screaming ]
Please, l have no money!
Let me go!
[ screaming ]
Food.
[ coughs ]
l think l'll pass.
Hey, l know a good place
to crash.
Up the fire escape
Through that window.
Come on.
l'll giveyou a boost.
Pull it down.
l can't get it down.
Come on, pull.
Come on! Come on!
Agent Scully,
Agent Mulder
Chief Blevins assures us
ofyour cooperation.
We regret any inconvenience
at this extreme hour.
We hopeyour expertise
in extraordinary phenomenon
will help us
answer some questions.
You're not F.B.l., areyou?
Haveyou ever analyzed
anything like this before?
Abnormal postmortem
muscle refex.
Both corpses
are still responding
to exposure to high levels
ofelectrostatic charge.
Any external lesions
or surface burns?
None.
Time ofdeath?
Well, it can't be long.
The body's still warm.
Somatic death occurred
sometime over six hours ago
but their body temperatures
haveyet to drop below 98.3.
Where did
you find them?
Look, at least
tell us
the time and mode
oftransport.
That might help us
determine why the bodies
haven't cooled.
You guys called us down here.
You want some answers
you got
to give some.
They traveled
60 minutes by air.
Thankyou.
The most troubling aspect
ofthe deaths
is the throat area.
Larynx, esophagus,
and hyoid bone--
all have been crushed
like chalk.
No abrasions, or evidence
oftissue damage.
lt's as iftheir throats
were crushed
from the inside.
Who are these guys?
Scully:
lfyou've done
your examinations
why areyou
consulting us?
Working on the X-Files
haveyou seen
anything like this?
No, never.
Well, thankyou very much
foryour time
Agent Mulder, Scully.
lfany inquiry as
to this meeting be made
we request full denial.
l'd sayyou people already
suffer from full denial.
You lied.
You have seen it before.
l can tell.
You lied to them.
l would never lie.
l willfully participated
in a campaign
ofmisinformation.
Who doyou think
theywere?
N.S.A., C.l.A.,
some covert organization
that Congress will uncover
in the next scandal.
lt's not important
who they are
but what they have.
l'm sure they have no idea,
because they called us in.
l have X-Files--
each case has an element
ofwhat we saw tonight.
Residual electrostatic charge,
internal mutilation--
none has the elements
combined in one case.
How can an esophagus be crushed
without the neck being touched?
Psychokinetic manipulation.
Psychokinesis?
You mean how Carrie
got even at the prom?
The Russians were
doing studies on it.
The Chinese still are.
Their findings
are kept secret.
Okay, l'm intrigued
but how can we investigate?
We have nothing to go on.
just getting in, Lauren?
Oh!
Mr. Graves used to letyou
get awaywith that
but Mr. Dorlund
is in charge now.
l was wondering
ifl could have
a minute with him?
Tomorrow... at 3:00.
[ sighs ]
Oh!
ls everything
all right out here?
Can l speakwith you?
Please.
Um, l'm here to give
my two-week notice.
Uh-huh...
Lauren,Jane told me
aboutyou crying
in Howard's office
and l wantyou to know
you're not alone.
As a matter offact,
we share something special.
Howard and l
started this company
ten years ago.
As long as l knew him
he had no interest
in anything besides work.
So, some ofus
became family.
l was his brother.
You were like a daughter.
So, ofcourse
l feel very
close toyou
and l...
l want to take care
ofmy family.
Stay, Lauren, please.
The company needs you.
Especially now.
l won't letyou leave,
Lauren.
What's wrong?
[ gaspingandgrunting ]
l, uh... l can't.
l have to leave.
l can't be here anymore.
You've got two weeks.
Mohammed Amrahlabi.
"Convictions:
lllegal possession offirearms
illegal possession
ofexplosives
falsification
ofexport licenses."
He has ties to
an extremist group in the U.S.--
the lsfahan
named after
the city in lran.
They're working
out of Philadelphia.
That's 60 air minutes.
l'll talk to the Philly P.D.
Officer:
This is where
we found him.
Who discovered
their bodies?
Nobody.
lt was about 1 0:00;
l was on patrol.
just saw them
hanging around.
No witnesses?
The kind ofpeople
who come around here
after business hours
don't witness
very much.
You know what
l'm saying.
We'll just question
everyone on record
who was at the machine
before 1 0:00 that night.
There.
l'll back up.
Lauren Kyte.
858 Franklin, Bensalem.
Whywould the lsfahan be
robbing someone of40 bucks
at an ATM machine?
Look at that.
Maybe it's another person.
Maybe. Maybe not.
Well, the resolution's
too poor.
lt won't help much
to enhance it.
That leaves us
only one person
we know we can talk to.
Oh, come on.
[ knockingatdoor ]
[ knocking ]
Hello?
Ms. Lauren Kyte, please.
l'm agent Fox Mulder.
This is
Agent Dana Scully.
We're with the Federal
Bureau oflnvestigation.
Maywe come in?
l was in the middle...
We won't be long.
Thankyou.
Haveyou ever seen either
ofthese two men before?
No.
Takeyour time.
l'm sorry.
l've never seen them before.
l'm afraid you have.
Can you tell us
what happened that night?
Um...
These guys, l...
l was depositing
my paycheck.
They grabbed me,
l got away, l ran.
l just didn't want
to file a report.
Theywere found dead.
Haveyou ever seen
this person before?
No.
l'm sorry. l can't tell you.
Does that mean
you know?
Uh... lt means l...
l can't tell you
who it is.
Well, when you
can tell me
this is the number
l can be reached
at any time, okay?
Mm-hmm.
A woman her size
breaking free
and outrunning those men?
Then somehow
crushing their necks?
Scully:
She knows who
the other person
in the photo is.
She's packing, running away,
but from what?
[ tiressquealing ]
What's happening?
What the hell's going on?
Mulder: Hang on!
Areyou okay?
Yeah.
Hi.
The paramedics
checkyou out?
Yeah. l'm fine,
although l do have
a standing-in-line-
at-the-DMV-sized headache.
Mine's more l.R.S.-sized.
Did they check out
the car?
lt's brand-new.
only 1 00 miles.
Then someone
tampered with it
while we were
in her house.
The mechanic says
everything's in proper order.
Nothing cut,
nothing greased.
Check out the lights.
They're on.
No. The filaments are heated
due to massive levels
ofelectrostatic charge
just like the bodies
in the morgue.
And isn't it interesting
that Lauren Kyte
was present
at both incidents?
She was in our presence
the entire time.
What ifit's possible
to raise the body's
electrostatic charge
to the levels
we've been seeing
and use that energy
to affect objects?
lfa person generated
that much energy
their body
would break down.
They'd glow
like those lights.
There's evidence ofthis
in the X-Files--
furniture moving untouched
objects levitating
unexplained
electrical discharges.
Frequently, people who have
psychokinetic power
are unaware
oftheir own capability.
Areyou saying
Lauren Kyte crashed our car?
Either that...
or a poltergeist.
They're here.
They may be.
Mulder, look at
the tangible evidence.
Two mideast extremists
were killed
trying to assault a woman
working for
a manufacturer ofparts
for the Defense
Department.
When we questioned her,
our carwas sabotaged.
ln both cases, someone else
may have committed those acts--
Maybe the same someone
from the ATM photos.
The mystery isn't
psychokinetic energy.
lt's her accomplice.
Excuse me.
She's clean. No arrest,
not even a traffic ticket.
The only thing is
she's in deep with her
credit card company-- 1 5,000.
What doyou think
you're doing?
Man:
l'm going to put that
on here.
No, no. l'll take care
ofthis, all right?
Here. l'll talk
to somebody.
Mulder:
A little upset over
losing a parking space
wouldn'tyou say?
Who is Howard Graves, anyway?
She was his secretary.
That's three people dead
in the last month
associated
with Lauren Kyte.
You won't find
too many people
at their boss' grave
who aren't dancing on it.
Look at this one.
[ watersplashing ]
Excuse me, sir?
ls there an office
where l can get some information
on those people?
Who? l attend
every funeral.
l'm the last person
to see them put to rest.
Doyou know how Sarah Lynn
was related
to Howard Graves?
His daughter.
Theywere at home one day
and he didn't latch
the pool gate.
She drowned.
His wife left him
a year later.
She's buried in a plot
in the northeast corner.
Thankyou, sir.
You're welcome.
She was only
threeyears old.
lfshe had lived,
she'd be Lauren's age.
Furtherinvestigation
into Lauren Kyte's
personalhistory...
revealsan estrangement
from herfamily.
Phonerecords confiirm
no contact withherparents
forthelast twoyears.
Heractions,
observedduringsurveillance,
indicateastrong relationship
between Lauren Kyte...
andheremployer,
thelate Howard Graves.
Was this relationship
somehowthemotivation
forhissuicide?
Howare theattack
andsubsequentmurders
ofthe Isfahanagents related,
ifatall?
Iam certain theanswers
to these questions...
lie in fiinding theidentity
ofLauren Kyte'saccomplice.
Enhance it by ten.
That's Howard Graves.
He's alive.
Not necessarily.
[ hissing ]
[ stairs creaking ]
[ muffledvoice ]
Man:Don'tdo this tome.
Howard.
Howard:No. Stop. No, no!
Please, no!
[ moaning ]
[ sobbing ]
[ panickedgasping ]
Lauren:Howard.
Theykilledhim.
l think Howard Graves
fabricated his own death.
Doyou know how difficult it is
to fakeyour own death?
Only one man
has pulled it off-- Elvis.
He and Lauren Kyte
are in on something.
Maybe an illegal dealing
through his company--
something the C.l.A.
was interested in.
You may be right.
Wait.
You think l'm right?
Sure. All you got to do
is prove Howard Graves
is still alive.
Howard Graves is very dead.
Maywe see
the autopsy report, please?
Knockyourselfout.
Uh... "Cause ofdeath,
arterial hemorrhage..."
Bledsoe:
Four out ofsix liters ofblood
down the tub.
Well, there seems to be
some blood work missing here.
We only do that
ifwe suspect homicide.
l don't supposeyou ran
any dental confirmations?
What for? lt was him.
How did you know?
lt said so on the toe tag.
Who made positive l.D.
on the body?
Um...
Lauren Kyte.
Mulder:
But he was cremated.
There's no way
to run a dental check
or get a DNA sample.
Yes, there is.
His body's tissues and organs
were donated.
Man:
Howard Graves
is in five different people.
They harvested the organs
immediately after death.
His kidneys
were sent to Boston
his liver to Dallas
and his corneas
to Portland, Oregon.
They've all
been transplanted.
Because ofhis age
we could only cryopreserve
the dura matter
in the membrane
ofthe spinal column.
We have Mr. Graves'
hospital records.
We'll extract a sample,
run a test
and in a couple ofhours
confirm the identity
ofthe donor.
l, uh, made them rush
soyou could haveyour check
beforeyou leave.
Oh. l'm going to miss you.
Oh.
Oh, what?
Here.
Good-bye.
[ doorcloses ]
You were going
to leave
without saying good-bye?
Well, uh, l came to say good-bye
and to wish you luck...
and to leaveyou
with this little thought.
l know Howard told you
and ifit ever gets out
l won't waste my time
trying to pin the source.
l'll go straight toyou.
And you'll do to me whatyou did
to Howard?
l knowyou had him killed.
Whywould you say that?
He told me.
[ telephoneringing ]
Mulder.
How soon can you
be at my house?
Why?
Please hurry.
The tests are conclusive.
The dura matter
does belong to Howard Graves.
He is, indeed, very dead.
[ knocking ]
just a second.
[ screaming ]
Go run the bath.
Get out ofhere!
No!
[ screaming ]
No. No!
[ choking ]
No!
[ Laurenscreaming: ]
No!No!
[ mangasping ]
[ Lauren crying ]
You know,
you're not under arrest.
You'rejust here
for questioning.
The sooner
you talk to us
the sooner
you get to go home.
What happened
to those people tonight?
Doyou have any idea
who they might be?
Why did they
attackyou?
Doyou know who this is?
Scully, Mulder.
He'll keep
an eye on her.
Come on. Now.
You've seriously compromised
our investigation.
We were following leads
pertaining to an X-File.
l want to know every detail
ofyour activities
concerning this case.
You're the ones
who have been
withholding
information.
Why don'tyou tell us
whatyou've got?
Then we have nothing more
to talk about.
Wait! We believe H.T.G.
lndustrial Technologies
sold restricted parts
to the lsfahan.
Serial numbers were recovered
in the wreckage
ofthe bombing
ofa navy transport van.
How is Lauren Kyte involved?
Your actions impeded
our investigation.
We don't have enough evidence
to hold her.
lfshe doesn't talk,
she goes free
and we lose our chance
to break this company.
l could make her talk.
My advice toyou:
don't get rough with her.
That was a waste oftime.
Your turn.
Lauren...
l won't talk
toyou either.
Okay. Then you're free
to go.
l can't go back
to that house.
Why?
Because of Howard Graves?
He's dead.
l know.
He's watching overyou,
isn't he?
Lauren:
l don't know ifyou've ever
been a secretary before.
Sometimes your boss can talk
as ifyou weren't even
in the room
which can hurt, you know.
Sometimes you're all he has
to talk to
which is how it always was
with me and Howard.
One night, late,
l went into his office.
He was crying,
more scared than sad.
The Pentagon contracts
were being canceled.
The companywas going under.
He felt personally responsible
for each ofhis employees.
Seeing and feeling
their fear every day
reallywore him down.
Then this one time,
Dorlund came with that group--
that mideast group-- lsfahan.
They'd buy parts
at an outrageous price--
notjust once--
for as long as they
could get awaywith it.
That night Howard was crying,
he hadjust found out
that lsfahan
had claimed responsibility
for killing a couple sailors
in Florida.
He was never the same
and l thought
that's why he killed himself...
but he didn't.
l saw...
Howard showed me how
Dorlund had him killed.
Made it look like a suicide,
'cause he could see
Howard was going
to put an end to the deal.
So now Howard
is protecting you?
lt sounds so ridiculous.
Butyou believe it?
He was closer to me
than my father.
l told him that.
l still feel his presence.
Sometimes...
l even smell his after-shave.
lfyoujust could have... seen
the things l've seen.
l just want all that to go away.
That's why l'm leaving.
Maybe he can move on.
That's not enough.
You have been given the chance
to tell him again.
Take it.
Tell him you love him
by showing him...
by... by helping us finish
his unfinished business.
Lauren,
how will you ever
be able to rest
ifhe never can?
Okay.
l'm a mess.
l'm going to, uh... wash up.
What areyou doing, Scully?
You don't believe.
Mulder, there's no such things
as ghosts or psychokinesis.
l'm sure there's an explanation,
but l believe that she believes
and my priority is to get her
to help us stop Dorlund.
Well, we may havejust
sacrificed our best opportunity
to observe spectral phenomena.
No, l'm giving us the chance
to solve a case that's tangible
instead ofchasing
after shadows.
[ dooropensandshuts ]
Areyou ready?
All right, everyone
we have a warrant
to search the premises
for evidence
pertaining to the sale
ofrestricted
manufactured parts.
The evidence
may be in the form
offalsified export licenses,
parts manifests, communiques.
lt could be on computer disk
or hard copy.
Once there,
ifin doubt, ask.
We need this to be clean.
This is the culmination
ofa yearlong investigation.
lfwe don't come out
ofthere todaywith something
proving a connection
to the lsfahan
this guy could walk.
Okay, let's go.
You okay?
lt will most likely be
in Dorlund's office.
We'll execute the search,
but we'll need you to guide us
soyou have
to be strong, okay?
Scully:
Everybody stay calm.
Federal Bureau oflnvestigation.
Ma'am, could you back away
from those files, please?
This is all we could find.
We don't have him.
He's not even
breaking a sweat.
Webster:
Our case is blown.
We've wasted a year.
This guy's going to walk.
Let's get out ofhere.
Mulder: Lauren, it's over.
we have to go.
What we're looking for
isn't here.
Dorlund:
She's no agent.
l've been more than cooperative.
She has no right
to destroy
my personal property.
What about that van that blew up
and killed those servicemen?
l don't know
whatyou're talking about
you stupid bitch!
Lauren, no!
Lauren: Don't kill him!
Help us find it!
[ lights explode ]
Mulder!
Oh, my god.
Mulder: l guess what we're
looking for is here.
The U.S. Attorney's Office
is going after Dorlund
with everything they've got
including the murder
of Howard Graves.
l'll come back
to testify.
Whereyou going?
Away from here.
[ enginestarting ]
Thanks.
Boy, she's in a rush
to get out ofhere.
Out ofhere, or away from
the ghost of Howard Graves?
Hey, Scully, doyou believe
in an afterlife?
l'd settle for a life
in this one.
You ever seen
the Liberty Bell?
Yes.
l've been to Philadelphia
1 00 times
and l've never seen it.
You're not missing much.
lt's a big bell
with a big crack
and you have to wait
in a long line.
I'dreallylike
togo.
Whynow?
Idon'tknow.
Howlate doyou think
theystay open?
Miss Kyte, l asked for this
25 minutes ago.
l know. l'm sorry.
Maybe that's the way
theywork back East
but here in the Midwest,
punctuality is a virtue.
We really have to find
a new office space.
Every time a truck goes by
the whole building shakes.
That's all, Lauren.