Melinda: previously
on "ghost whisperer..."
why do your friends shine?
Because they don't have faces.
they're made of light. but they're scared.
What are they scared of,
buddy?
Of the shadows.
what kind of shadows are those?
The ones they make
from the parts
that get left behind.
Parts of what?
people.
Broken people.
I've been trying
to protect you.
You and melinda.
melinda?
I've said too much.
protect her from what?
Is it the shadows?
Stop asking
so many questions!
Don't ask any
questions at all.
her name's julia miller
and she was a patient.
According to this,
she lives here
at the hospital
Her whole life.
No one can know
i'm here.
Why not?
if they find out,
Something bad will happen.
what?
Something really bad.
oh.
You scared me.
That's not easy
to do. um...
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for aiden.
Ok, well,
he's at school.
And you don't
belong here, so...
Have i seen you?
it's his closet,
And he said
i could stay.
Yeah, well,
technically it's my house.
And so i decide
who's staying.
Julia miller.
The girl practically
lived here.
Yeah, i knew she
looked familiar.
She had leukemia?
well, she died last week
Of pneumonia,
and her immune system
Couldn't stand
the cancer treatments.
Isn't she the one
who sent you those creepy
sally stitch emails?
One of the many
reasons i don't
want her near our son.
Ok, but i thought
you said ghosts
made her do it.
Well, 11 is a little old
to still be seeing ghosts.
But she was dying.
Maybe she was
sensitive.
No, i don't know
how to explain it.
There's just something
not right about her.
Says the woman
who just found out
Her son was
keeping a ghost
in his closet?
I have a bad feeling
about this one.
Very bad feeling.
Ok. never
a good sign.
Yeah.
It wasn't really
a secret.
I just didn't
tell you about it.
Yet.
ok.
But you know you should
have told us that
julia was here.
Right?
She didn't
want me to.
Well, then you
were keeping
a secret, bud.
That's how it works.
We just don't
have secrets
in our home, ok?
Just with other people?
Look, i know
that that can be confusing.
Um...
But it's not--
it's not good
For julia
to be stuck here.
You know? she's supposed
to be in the light
with other ghosts.
I'm sorry, mom.
hey.
Maybe you can
convince julia
to talk to mom.
Yeah.
She doesn't like
talking to mom.
Why not?
She says
you don't like her.
Why makes her think that?
'cause you don't
want me to learn
how to do magic.
Oh.
Um, you know,
i just--
I just don't like it
when ghosts hide in our house.
Right? but what else
is she doing here?
Besides teaching you
magic tricks?
I don't know.
All she wants
to talk about is magic.
Well, why don't you
just promise to tell us
Next time's julia's here, ok?
I love you.
Love you, too.
ok.
Bath time.
i don't want a bath.
Ok. all right.
We'll take some of this
into the bed.
Julia, will you please
just talk to me?
Look, i'm not angry
with you.
That is not helping.
What do you want?!
Child, whispering:
can you see us?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Julia miller?
isn't she the same girl
Who was sending
all those awful emails?
Well, that's why
i'm worried.
You know, what
if she's a bad
influence on aiden?
Mel, we do the best we can
to raise our kids.
At some point,
they're going to pick friends
That we wish they hadn't,
you know?
Living or dead.
Don't you remember
that ghost that got ned
To shoplift
from your store?
Exactly, but you didn't
believe me then.
Ok, well, i do now.
And i may not have
any advice how to stop
playdates with ghosts,
But i am telling you,
as a mother,
You've got to trust
your instincts.
You've got to cut it off.
Yeah, but what
if she's staying
here for something?
Or i can help her?
cut it off.
Hey. well,
she's here
right now.
Hey, mel, this is
david and linda.
These are julia's
parents.
hi.
Your husband said
that you wanted
to talk to us.
Something
about julia?
I'll be nearby.
Thanks.
thank you.
May i?
Sure.
I know about your loss,
and i'm so sorry.
It must be
very difficult for you.
Oh, thank you.
There's some comfort
in knowing
That our daughter's
finally at peace.
I don't know
what jim told you,
And i know that this
is going to sound
a little strange.
But i have a gift.
I can see ghosts.
Have you seen
our julia?
Yes.
She's attached herself
to my 5-year-old son.
Can we talk to her?
She sort of shut us
out of her life
these past few months.
She did?
Yeah. we don't know why.
The doctors say
there may have been
Some psychological issues
That resulted from being
alone in the hospital
For so long.
We weren't even
with her when she died.
Do you think that
maybe why she's still here?
Because she never
got a chance
to say good-bye?
That might be
a part of it,
But i feel like
there's some
unfinished business
That she's just not
telling me about.
What unfinished business
could an 11-year-old have?
You know, we're here to
pick up julia's things.
The nurses said that
She did a lot of drawing
and writing.
Well, i guess we could
look at some of those
if you like.
See if we could
find anything.
That would be great.
And if you find anything,
Can you just call me?
Thank you.
David: it will be
all right.
But i can still
do magic tricks?
Yeah, as long
as they're not
ghost magic tricks.
Julia, what's going on?
It's none
of your business.
Look, i understand
that this must be
hard for you.
If you just let me,
i can help you.
I need aiden,
not you.
Aiden, go upstairs
and play, ok? right now.
Ok. bye, julia.
Right now.
I saw your mom
and dad today.
They're very worried
about you.
Look, i get
how confusing
it can be to--
You don't get anything.
you're a grown-up.
Whatever's keeping you here,
i can help you.
Stop saying
you can help me.
You can't.
If you just
let me, i can.
Jim: hey?
what's going on here?
Julia's here.
And, uh,
Where is our son,
aiden?
He is upstairs, ok?
and he's playing
and he's fine.
We're just going
to work this out.
No. it's not fine.
no, we're not
Going to work
this out right now.
We're going to put
these knives in here,
And i want julia
out of this house.
Julia, can you hear me?
i want you out of my house
And i want you
to leave my son
alone, got it?
Do you hear me?
Jim...
Does that mean
she's gone?
For now.
You don't know
who you're dealing with.
So, was julia around
last night?
No. i think she's gone.
That's probably
for the best.
You understand that,
right?
Yeah.
Is it ok to miss her?
Of course it is,
sweetie.
Drink your juice,
it's good for you.
oh, my god,
aiden, don't drink that!
Aiden!
Aiden?
Jim, i can't find aiden!
hmm?!
Aiden?!
Jim: i'll check
outside!
Aiden!
Baby!
Jim: aiden! aiden!
Aiden, where are you?!
Aiden!
I can't find him
anywhere.
Oh, my god.
Jim, i have searched
every inch of this house.
Honey, honey,
calm down.
it'll be ok.
I'm going to call
the police,
we'll call everyone.
Hello?
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
My son is missing!
Melinda, honey.
Have you heard
anything?
No, nothing.
listen, i sent you
a picture.
If you could just
send it to everyone you know.
Ok, sure.
Where's jim?
he's, i don't know,
Driving the neighborhoods,
waking up people.
The police on their way,
and eli, he went straight
To detective blair.
all right.
Well, do you think
it's julia?
She took him. i know it.
the mcallisters, the taubs,
I went as far
as the playground.
nothing.
She's not going to take him
somewhere we've looked.
He's five. technically,
how far can he get?
I mean, can a ghost even
move him like that?
He'd be moving on his own.
Then that means
he's in walking range.
Why is he doing this?
he knows better.
He probably
felt sorry for her.
Or she tricked him,
i don't know.
But if i have to stay
in this house for five
more minutes without him,
I'm going to lose my mind.
Look, i'm going
to go to main street
And i'm going to go west
and south, all right?
You guys go south
and east, please.
I'm just gonna stay here,
In case the police come
or anybody calls.
I'll be here.
do you have your cell phone?
Yeah, in my purse.
Where are my car keys?
Mel...
not now.
Detective blair
needs to ask you
some questions.
Look, you have the photo
and delia and eli
Will catch you up
on everything.
Right now,
nothing else matters.
All right, well,
the police are
already canvassing,
But there are details
i need to hear from you,
Specifics that could help us
find your child.
He's with a dead little girl
who doesn't care
Whether he lives or dies.
Does that help you?
A dead girl?
A ghost.
Throughout the years,
the cases we've
helped you with,
The bodies we've found,
It's because melinda
can see spirits
and i can, well--
It's just a lot
to explain.
Ok.
Just give me a chance
to filter the right
information
To my officers.
thank you.
I don't understand.
Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
It's going to be fun.
I'm not supposed
to go anywhere but
school on my own.
You'll be home soon.
they won't even miss you.
When you show them
the things i'm going
to show you,
They'll understand.
I don't know.
I know some
really good magic.
You can do things,
things you don't
even know about.
Ok, come on.
you have to get on.
Does it cost money?
See that mom and those kids?
Go with them,
but stay right behind them.
The bus driver
Will think
you're with them.
come on, hurry.
He's not at school.
They checked the grounds
and surrounding areas.
He's on a bus.
A city bus. white,
With red stripes.
i couldn't see
a logo or a number.
Where did you see--
Please, don't ask me
how i know that.
I was going to ask you
where the bus was going.
If you saw where
it was headed.
Any direction,
any landmarks.
No.
I've got an update.
Check city busses,
driscoll county
transit line.
Aiden!
I'm talking about
any county bus
Within five miles
of this area.
Notify the drivers,
pull them all over.
I don't care.
We're looking for a boy
with a blue backpack.
Ned!
I'm sorry.
my cell was off
And i slept
on campus last night.
It's ok, honey,
you're here.
Did you hear anything?
no.
Well, there's
a couple outside
That are looking
to talk to melinda.
She just left.
Well, then i think maybe
we should talk to them.
Eli: are those julia's
things from the hospital?
Yeah, we--
ahh.
Julia did a lot of
writing and drawing
To keep herself
company.
Um...
It's hard to, ahh...
Um--
Why don't you tell us
What you found.
She wrote down
her thoughts and...
Some of them
were so dark.
She wrote about
something she did,
Something terrible
to a friend of hers.
She said...
Mrs. miller.
Aiden's been missing
for over two hours now.
He's five.
You have to tell us
what your daughter did.
She was so lonely.
she made things up.
Please. we need to know.
Um, she, uh,
She talks about this
one friend.
It was a girl.
she didn't say who,
But julia seems
to think that,
Um...
She claims
she killed her.
Excuse me.
Melinda?
Are you driving?
Pull over
for a second.
There's something
you should know.
Bus driver:
this is woodland avenue.
This stop for transfers
to green line, westbound.
Come on, aiden, hurry.
Where are we?
We'll just take
a shortcut.
Follow me, ok?
Do you know
a secret or something?
yes.
But first, i'm going
to show you something.
I'm going to teach you
how to disappear.
Officer on radio: dispatch,
this is one, zero, two.
Boy with blue backback
boarding green line
westbound bus.
I'm in pursuit.
President bedford?
Professor james.
What are you doing here?
that's a good question.
Wait, you know something
about melinda's son?
I don't know where he is.
I just know that
you're barking up
the wrong tree.
How?
I've spent some time
at that hospital.
Your mother.
you visit her every day.
And i've learned
a few things.
That girl, the ghost...
She's not what
you're up against.
I don't understand.
she didn't take aiden?
She did, but only
because she's scared.
She's a scared little girl.
She's watched too many
of her friends waste away.
And after they died,
Something she had to watch
even worse.
Worse how?
Eli, i warned you.
I warned you to stay
out of their business.
Who? the shadows?
What's all this
really about?
i don't understand.
The shadows
get you installed
As the university
president,
And they're responsible
for this dead girl
Somehow?
Melinda was warned
to leave julia alone.
She should listen.
What, the message
in her kitchen?
She tried to get
that girl to cross over
into the light.
Is that a bad thing?
what do the shadows
Have against
going into the light?
I'm taking a huge risk
just being here.
Hold on!
are you saying
the shadows
Had something to do with
what happened to aiden?
All i'm saying
is if you and melinda
Aren't careful,
they will.
They will.
If i'd have known
he was on his own,
I wouldn't let him
get on the bus.
Who did he get on with?
I saw him get on
with his family.
No, look,
i'm his family,
all right?
I'm his father.
this is my son.
See? you sure this is
the boy you saw?
Yeah, that's him.
I already
told the police.
Look, if it's
any consolation,
he seemed ok.
Thanks.
Except...
except what?
Well, at one point,
i noticed the seat
next to him was empty.
But he was talking.
To himself, i guess.
To be honest,
that's the only reason
I gave him
a second though.
But then, i've got
to keep my eyes
on the road.
Do you remember
where he got off?
did you notice?
I'm pretty sure it was
along woodland avenue,
The stop by
the highway.
By the on-ramp?
The stop's a way
from the entrance.
yeah.
There's not much else
there--another bus stop,
Some woods.
Oh, man. thanks.
Look, mister...
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
i'll find him.
Delia: have you
found anything?
Just kid's stuff.
a lot of poems about
Being alone, sick, angry.
She hated ivs.
And some of the nurses.
And all of her medicine.
How are we supposed
to do this?
Bit by bit,
until we find out
what's keeping her here.
What's keeping her here
is that she was a bad kid
Who hung out
with bad ghosts.
I mean, right here
it says that sally stitch
Was a real ghost
and that julia did
everything she asked.
And bedford said
this girl
Isn't the one we should
be worrying about.
Why are you taking
his word for anything?
I mean, look at this.
Julia goes on and on
about killing a friend.
And this whole journal
is full of the words
"it's my fault."
I mean, you tell me.
how do you get
A child sociopath
to let go of aiden
and go into the light?
Sociopaths
don't feel guilt.
Delia: yeah,
they don't have
friends, either.
Have you really
looked at these books?
It seems that
many of them
Belong to a girl
named lily.
I saw that name
somewhere else.
Here it is.
This weird food list.
Let me see it.
Like some kind of haiku poem.
This isn't a list.
This is a diet.
for lily.
Ned: "tuesday, ketchup.
wednesday, bacon."
Bacon and one lemon.
That's it?
for the whole day?
"thursday, cure berries
from the magic bush
By the dolphin
fountain."
That fountain's in
the back of the hospital
In the garden.
there's some bushes
back there,
But i doubt they're edible.
Cure berries.
Don't you see?
hello.
Delia: mel,
i don't know if you
want to hear this.
But maybe, just maybe
julia miller
Isn't as bad
as we thought.
Melinda: i would love
to hear that.
It's possible she killed
her friend by mistake.
By doing something
the shadows
asked her to do?
By making some kind
of potion to cure her friend
Out of bacons, lemons, and--
It's not important.
What's important is,
i think she might have
Picked the berries
that have killed
her friend.
Didn't you once
have a nightmare
Where you nearly
poisoned aiden?
I had a vision.
I could see a girl.
I don't know
if it was julia
or her friend,
But they had
gotten sick.
Eli: bedford
said something
about julia
Having a bunch of friends
at the hospital
Like, waste away.
Maybe she tried
to do something about it.
I hope you're right.
Aiden: how long
do i have to wear this?
Julia: not much longer.
Are we getting close?
Just keep going straight.
The ground's pretty flat.
We're almost there.
You can take off
your blindfold now.
I don't know
this place.
Are we at
the train station?
Sort of.
Is this a surprise?
Yeah.
Why did i have
to cover my eyes?
I, uh,
Just thought
it'd be more fun.
I'm hungry.
I guess you don't
have any snacks.
Why isn't there
anyone here?
I thought there'd be
kids here.
Kids love
this place.
It's happy.
Safe.
It's getting dark.
I want to go home.
We can't.
I can't.
We can find a grown-up
and call my mom.
She'll send me away.
Just to the light.
You'll like it.
it's nice.
You don't know that.
You don't know anything,
And neither does she.
Why is your voice
sounding mean?
I--i can't go home,
And i can't
go into the light.
If i do,
they'll get hurt.
Who?
All the spirits
that were nice to me.
The good ones.
Ghosts don't get hurt.
My mom says
they can't feel pain.
She's wrong.
We do.
How?
It's an uh-oh feeling.
you know, like when
You've done
something wrong.
It's all you can
think about.
The bad thing you did.
All of the bad things
you did.
And it grows
and grows until
that's all you are.
You're nothing else.
It eats you up
completely.
It's coming for me.
I know it.
This is it,
this is it. aiden!
Aiden, can you hear me?
Aiden!
The bus driver
said it was this stop.
Aiden!
Aiden, no matter what
julia said,
It's not all right to hide.
Aiden, if you can
hear my voice...
Damn it.
What the hell
is that?
Aiden?!
Aiden!
Aiden, i know
this is yours! aiden!
jim?
Hey! did you find him?
jim: no.
No, but he was here.
he was here by this bus stop.
Look, i just found
a little silver car
That he must have
just dropped.
I called the police.
Are you sure
it's his?
Yeah. because...
It's got the little
scratch on it
Where i showed him how
to use the sliding board
for a jump.
Honey, when we find him,
i swear...
I know.
You're never going
to leave the house again.
Where did you find
the toy?
Just at the edge
of the woods.
He must have been
playing with it
On the bus when
he dropped it.
She probably led him
into the woods.
You know, to keep him
out of sight.
All right,
i'm going in there.
Ok, well, just call me
if you see anything.
You know it.
i love you.
I love you, too.
What do the shadows
want with my son?
Carl: i don't know.
I don't
have time, carl!
I'm aware of that, melinda.
No, bedford
just told eli
That they
threatened my son
If i crossed julia
over into the light,
Which means they were
the ones who moved
that furniture.
What i don't
know is why.
I don't know, either,
melinda.
How can you
not know?
What the hell
are you seeing, carl,
When you're doing
all this watching?
Not the shadows.
i told you that.
Ghosts can't see
the shadows.
No one i know sees them,
except...
Aiden.
He sees those others.
The shinies.
And if those beings,
whatever they are,
Fear the shadows,
i'm guessing--
Guessing they co-exist
on the same plane.
Really? carl, that's
the best you can do?
we hear rumors.
We hear whispers.
What?
Whatever they are,
wherever they live,
These shadows
are very interested
In children, melinda.
Especially ghost children.
Why?
No one seems to know.
Are you telling me
That the shadows
want to turn my son
into a ghost?
I told you,
i don't know.
Then at least tell me,
Do you have some idea
where he went?
I can't--i can't.
he's hidden from me.
how?
I can't see clearly.
my vision,
It's filled with pictures
from my past.
Everywhere i look,
it's like an endless
slide show
Of every mistake
i made in my life.
It's like a sickness of guilt.
Is that why
you seem so weak?
Oh.
It's the shadows.
If that's true...
Do everything you can,
melinda,
Not to anger them.
I will do anything
to get my son back.
Just don't anger them.
I will do anything.
hello?
Jim: mel, i just talked
to detective blair.
She's going to send
a search party
up to these woods.
Ok, well,
did you find anything?
It's weird.
i found a little
yellow school bus,
And i'm pretty sure
that it's aiden's.
something else shiny.
What are you getting at?
Last night,
in the kitchen, um,
Everything was shiny.
You know, remember?
Remember, aiden said
that the shadows
and the shinies,
That they hate each other?
Well, what if julia
put all that stuff
out there because
She was trying
to keep the shadows away
And attract the shinies?
Wait, do you think
that's why
They brought
these toys with them?
I don't know,
maybe. carl--
Carl?
Wait a minute. oh!
Melinda,
i found another one.
It's a little
tiny train.
He's not dropping
that stuff on accident.
So what do you think,
he's leaving a trail
of bread crumbs?
He's trying to tell us
something.
The car, the bus,
the train--
It all has
to do with travel.
Wait a minute,
travel town.
Remember that place?
it's nearby here.
But it shut down
a couple years ago.
The ghost
wouldn't know that.
She's been in the hospital.
It is right
where i'm headed.
I'll meet you there.
Julia: don't go!
don't leave me!
I want to go home.
There must be a phone,
Or a grown-up
to ask for help.
It's getting too dark.
it's not safe.
This isn't
the train station.
What is it?
It's travel town.
I used to come here
with my parents.
Why didn't you
tell me that?
I didn't want you to know,
or your mom would find out.
How would my mom
find out?
She never told you?
She can see
what you can see.
It's like
she's spying on you.
I've watched her.
She can see it all.
Where you going?
There's a light
over there.
Aiden: hello?
Hello?
I don't
like it here.
I want to go
some place safe.
My mom says
ghosts are safe
in the light.
You should go in the light.
You sill trust her?
After she lied to you?
Just look around
and see if you can
find the light.
It's too dark
in here.
I can feel them.
They're here.
Stay close to me.
Aiden!
I'm scared.
I'm scared,
i'm scared!
I can't see them!
where are they?
Close your eyes.
I'm scared,
i'm scared!
Keep your eyes
closed.
What's happening to me?!
I can still see
everything!
All the bad stuff.
All the bad stuff
i've ever done!
It's everywhere i look!
It's everywhere.
I hate you
for putting me here!
I just want to die!
No!
Aiden: no! please, no!
It eats you up completely.
No! stop!
Aiden, get out.
And your backpack, quick!
Hurry, aiden, hurry!
Where are you?
Come on!
Julia:
what's happening?!
Aiden:
the shinies...
They won't come in.
they're too scared.
The other shadows
are keeping them out!
I need help!
Aiden: are you ok?
It was so awful!
Melinda: aiden?
aiden!
Jim: mel!
Aiden!
Mom, dad!
Oh, my god!
My baby!
aiden, are you all right?
Oh, little buddy!
we're so happy to see you!
Oh! honey!
Are you ok?!
Oh, you really
scared me, man.
You really had us scared.
I know. me, too.
Come here.
Oh, what were you thinking,
you crazy kid?
Cop: is he ok?
Jim: hey, officer.
yeah, we got him,
he's ok.
Melinda: it's safe
to come out now.
Are you sure?
Aiden says
there's no shadows.
And there's some people
that you need to see.
It's ok.
Mom and dad?
Linda: is she here?
They came to say
good-bye.
It's time
for you to go
into the light.
No, i can't.
i can't do that.
Because you were
told that something
bad would happen
To your ghost
friends if you did.
Did aiden tell you that?
He was worried
about you.
He saw what happened to me.
i know.
But i'm going
to make sure that
your friends are ok.
How?
By getting some help
from my friends.
I want you
to meet them.
Julia: what will you do?
Well, we have
some things
the shadows don't.
We have a book,
And we have lots
of ghost friends
of our own.
We'll find a way.
But right now,
we need to get you
into the light.
Julia, hi. my name's ned.
I hope you don't mind,
But we read some
of the things you wrote
in the hospital,
About lily.
Eli: and we pieced
everything together.
And we want you
to understand--
You didn't
hurt your friend.
Jim: julia, when
you were in the hospital
And you made those potions,
You weren't just
playing doctor.
You were trying
to make a real cure
for your friend lily.
I mean, something
the regular doctors
couldn't do.
But i didn't help her.
I made her more sick,
and then she died.
She thinks
that she made her
more sick,
And that's why
she died.
Oh, that's not true, honey.
You only think that
because she went
into the hospital
After you gave her
your potion.
But she was sicker
than you knew,
A lot sicker.
What do you mean?
She doesn't
understand.
Uh...
Lily had the same thing
you had, darling.
Lily had leukemia.
But you told me
she had a bug.
She remembers you
calling lily's
disease just a bug.
Darling, we--
We didn't know
that you'd given her
that potion.
We didn't realize
that you'd thought
you'd made her more sick.
But why didn't you tell me
she had leukemia?
She just wishes you could
have told her the truth
about lily's disease.
Oh, baby.
We were afraid
that you would think
You might die
like she did.
But i did.
But she did.
Yeah.
Not for years.
In all that time,
you had hope.
I thought lily had hope, too.
I thought i gave it to her.
She feels guilty.
She feels like
she gave lily
A false sense of hope.
Don't you know,
sweetheart?
You gave her something
better than hope.
You gave her a friend.
Lily's parents told us
That those last months
you spent together,
Those were
the happiest times
she ever had.
She sees it.
She sees the light.
I'm afraid something bad
will happen to my friends.
Julia,
look into the light.
Try really hard.
You might see
some of your friends.
Once you've crossed over.
aiden: really look.
You can make them
appear.
Just like magic.
There she is.
I see lily.
She's smiling at me.
Lily's there.
Go in, darling.
Wait for us.
We'll be there soon.
Bye, mommy.
Bye, daddy.
?seasons change ?
?treetops sway ?
She's gone.
?i am young today ?
?children play ?
?sidewalk games ?
?as i dream ?
?away ?
?that someday
i'll float away ?
Ok, now remember--
anyone, person
Or a ghost tries
to tell you
to do something
That you know
is wrong...
I know, mommy.
I won't.
It's important, aiden.
i know.
I'm sorry i scared you guys.
You really did.
But we're proud
of you for wanting
to help someone.
Just remember
that most of the time
Helping somebody is not
a little person's job.
It's a big person's
job, ok?
I get it.
all right.
Can i have my backpack?
There you go.
Percy. i didn't know
she packed percy.
Who did? julia?
But wait a minute--
Julia didn't want us
to find you, so...
If you didn't
pack your backpack,
Who packed the toys
that left the trail
for us to find?
The shinies.
They led us to him.
They--they knew you were
going to be in travel town.
They had to.
Because julia
blindfolded me.
So they couldn't see
the stuff i saw.
Like usual.
What do you mean?
Julia told me the truth.
That you can see
everything i see.
Melinda: not everything.
Just some things?
which ones?
I don't really
know how it works, baby.
I--i think it's just
the things i need to see.
But you said no secrets.
Why'd you
keep them from me?
I hated doing that.
i really did.
It's just,
sometimes moms and dads,
They--they have
to keep secrets.
You know, to make
the world feel
a little bit safer.
But it isn't.
Jim: hey, aiden,
mostly it's safe.
Really. it's just,
There are some
places that--
Like where the shadows live.
Yes.
Like where the shadows live,
and we shouldn't go there.
Not ever.
But what if we have to?
I hope we won't.
You don't have
to tell me.
Oh, ok.
Come on, baby.
Scoot down.
?straight for the stars ?
Sync by honeybunny