???
??
- ??
- ???
??
???
Where were you?
At the--The firehouse.
Oh, right. You told me that. I forgot.
Later.
oh!
If that's sam, could you just tell him
That i'm at the restaurant already?
'Cause I don't want him
to cancel on me again.
it's a telemarketer.
What is going on?
Well, it's just,
he's been acting weird lately,
You know, like something's changed.
Like what?
I don't know.
It's like he can't trust me,
which, Who can blame him?
I'm always running around after ghosts
Or hushed conversations with eli.
But you do know.
It's all about ghosts.
Melinda, you have to tell him about it.
I mean, at best he'll believe you,
At worst, he'll think you're...
eccentric. Like I did.
What?
Nothing.
It's just, I was gonna tell him
at dinner tonight,
But a part of me was hoping
That you would really talk me out of it.
Why? You tell people
you see ghosts all the time.
Yes, but it's not
usually followed up with,
"Oh, by the way,
"You're my husband's soul
in another man's body.
Could you--Could you
pass the salt?"
Are you planning on
telling him everything?
First i'm going to see
how he deals with my gift, you know?
Baby steps.
good night.
you didn't eat much.
yeah, I guess i wasn't hungry.
Well, i'm glad that
you got some free time.
Yeah, schedule's been crazy.
Look, I wanted to
spend time together, but...
Never mind.
Look...
I think I know what's going on,
And I just want to clear the air,
Because I hate having secrets.
Good. That would be great.
What's wrong? It's like
you've seen a ghost.
Actually...
what the hell?
all right, so
we got everything, right?
So, um, how long do we
have to stay at this hotel?
Oh, probably just the night.
If the events are as
frequent as you say they are,
I should know something by dawn.
John, devin, what's going on?
Oh, hey, melinda.
We were just, um...
Some weird stuff has been going on.
Uh, noises, things moving.
Then doors started opening--
Locked doors.
Yeah, we're at the end of our rope.
Yeah, see, I know you probably
think This sounds crazy,
And that's no offense to you,
But when the plumber and
the electrician couldn't help us,
We didn't know who
else to call, but--
Linus van horn,
Spi--Supernatural,
paranormal investigation.
Oh, here's my card.
What do you do, exactly?
Uh, well, spectral beings emit energy,
So I set up infrared
still and video cameras,
Ultra sensitive audio recorders,
Thermal measuring...
There are a lot of
non-Believers out there.
I'm guessing you're among them?
no, no, no. It's just...
- Really?
- Absolutely.
So if you ever need
a ghost hunter--
no, that's all right.
I'm already In hock to my, uh,
witch doctor, but thanks.
Witch doctors.
Ghost hunters?
Are people really this stupid?
The clients, or the ghost guy?
What's the difference?
I mean, this is nonsense. Ghosts?
Look, what you were saying
about clearing things up--
You know what,
i, um, i--Ugh,
I forgot to write a check
to the website guys.
I'm just gonna run back to the store.
I can go with you. That's ok.
'Cause i'm probably just
gonna do some other things
While i'm there, so i'll just--
I'll see you later.
Right.
I was this close!
You know, to coming clean.
And then this guy had to show up.
You know, how is sam
supposed to take me seriously
When there's a hearse
driving around town
With a big, giant ghost on top?
Well, what if there really
is a ghost in your friend's abode?
Well, then it needs
to be handled respectfully
And crossed over, you know?
Not tormented and photographed
by some guy Who has no idea
what he's dealing with.
Wait a minute. So these guys
Actually really can detect ghosts?
Yeah, some of them, but
that's all, you know?
They can capture recordings and sounds,
But they can't communicate with spirits.
So people end up spending All of this money
just to confuse and anger ghosts,
and make things worse.
All right, our ability should
be on a need to know basis.
Otherwise, we run the risk of
becoming a complete laughingstock.
Trust me.
Sounds like you speak from experience.
yeah. I was almost outed
by that shame the devil website.
So you come to me to do what, rant?
No, for help.
Oh, boy.
Please?
Ok, will you just go over there
And find out if there's a ghost,
and cross him over?
All right? And tell that guy To take
his carnival act somewhere else,
Because I really...
I really need to tell sam the truth
With just a little shred of dignity.
if you want to learn about ghosts,
You need the right equipment.
That's a k-2 meter.
That measures magnetic fields.
Theoretically, if used properly,
You should be able to get
ghosts to communicate with you,
You know, like 2 blips for yes,
One for no sort of thing.
Sounds primitive.
Have you communicated with any ghosts?
Uh, well, no, not yet.
But I have heard them, Through evp.
Electronic, um--
Voice phenomena, yeah.
And i've seen them, too.
Well, the recorded images.
Here, check these out.
Huh?
Look at that.
I used to use a t.I.D.C.
That's a thermal imaging digital camera.
Detects, you know, long wavelength Infrared,
you know, things are invisible
to the human eye.
But then I upgraded to the m.F.S.C.
I'm not gonna touch that one.
That's a multi-Frequency
sensitive camera.
And ever since I got
this baby right here,
I've been detecting ghosts everywhere.
They look like little specks of dust.
Uh, yeah, But they were
taken in total darkness
Where there's no light to detect dust.
I thought you said you were a believer.
Oh, I do believe--
With the skepticism of science.
Wow, that's a really hot ghost.
What?
Oh, no. I'm sorry. That's, uh,
that's my ex-Girlfriend.
And you got all this using your multi...
Frequency sensitive
camera, that's right.
This baby right here.
And not cheap.
What do we do now?
We turn off the lights and we wait.
no, no, hey!
Wait, shh, shh! Hey, hey, hey!
look at this, come here!
Oh!
There is definitely a presence.
Yeah, you can call it that.
This is so weird. Usually
when I pick up an e.V.P.,
Something comes up--
Stairs! Go towards the stairs!
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, there it is!
Wait, is that-- Is that--
It's that, really. Come on, come on.
I just saw my first ghost.
Yeah.
How did you know where it was?
can you see us?
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@´ó±¦
Sync:FRS@wdysai
GHOST WHISPERER S04E16
Are you listening?
I said I saw my first ghost!
Wait, so this ghost guy
is the real deal?
Only in that he can take pictures.
Nothing else is new.
Oh, really, miss I see
ghosts all the time?
Can us newbies bask a little? Please.
Ok, enough basking.
Did you talk to the ghost?
No.
But I kind of let it slip
that I could hear them,
So linus is extending his run.
Ugh, eli, you validated this guy?
No!
I merely heard
the ghost he photographed,
Which means he's legit.
Besides, won't this help you
prove to sam that ghosts are real?
Yeah, well, fuzzy orbs
wouldn't have swayed me.
Thank you. You know, eli,
You have to cross this ghost.
And get rid of this guy.
Just give me a little bit more time.
I don't have much more time.
I know. But when I tried to engage
her in a little one-On-One,
She realized she was
being videoed, she bounced.
Great, so she's hiding something.
It'd be so much easier
if you just came over there and just--
I can't, ok?
If I start hanging out at a house
with a plastic ghost in front,
Sam's gonna think i'm nuts.
Ok, look, i did my research.
Your friends bought
that house in a probate sale
From the estate of one evelyn bellsbury,
Senior citizen who lived there from 1972
Until she vanished a few years ago.
The case was never solved.
Well, then, solve it for god sake, ok?
Just find out what's keeping
this mrs. Bellsbury here.
Get her into the light
so melinda can tell sam!
I really, I just can't
take much more of this!
Ok! I'm on it.
Ok, hmm...
Melinda Gordon + Grandview
Come on.
Let's see who you are.
???
"Grandview antiques
dealer melinda gordon
Seems to be hiding a
very mysterious sideline."
???
Damn it.
trouble, no!
No! Hey, sorry,
but can't you read the sign?
uh, i'm actually Not selling anything.
Um, i'm--You're
jeffrey crockett, right?
I'm dr. Eli james.
Um, i'm writing a paper
On the plight of grandview's elderly,
And, uh, I was wondering
if you knew anything
About your neighbor, evelyn bellsbury.
Uh, a little.
We bought the house 10 years ago,
Right before she disappeared.
I was hoping to learn a
little bit more about that.
Well, yeah. She was, uh,
a really sweet old lady.
We called her mrs. Blueberry
Because she made
the most amazing jellies and jams.
Trouble! No!
I didn't realize she was married.
Well, she wasn't.
It was just her And her parakeet
as far as I know.
Anyway, we were shocked
when she went missing.
Do you remember anything about that?
Let's see, um,
she brought over these scrumptious
Blueberry tarts for the holidays.
I mean, the filling was unbelievable.
The pastry was like butter. It--
Trouble!
And then a couple weeks later,
There were cop cars out
in front of her house.
So she just left?
Well, nobody really knows.
I mean, her car was there,
Her keys were in her purse in her house
With her license and her passport.
There was still a bunch of
blueberry tarts on the windowsill.
Any chance that she could
have just wandered off?
I don't know how far
she would have gotten.
She walked with a cane.
Listen, I gotta
let the dog out, you gotta go.
Give me a 5 second head start, ok?
hey.
Sam, hey.
Um, i'm sorry, but melinda
Just stepped out for a while.
Um, do you have any idea
Where she might be?
Um, actually I don't, but
you're welcome to stay,
Or I can just tell her
that you stopped by.
Oh, ok, yeah.
She's pretty guarded,
isn't she? Melinda?
You know, where she goes all the time.
What she's doing.
Yeah, she's, um,
Kind of a private person.
Look, I don't want to seem
like i'm checking up on her, ok,
But I just can't shake the feeling
That there is more going
on in her life than...
Selling antiques.
She's, um...
Complicated.
I know. I get it, I do.
And that's cool.
Just lost her husband, and maybe
i'm asking for too much, too soon.
But if there is something
going on with her,
I just want her to
know she can let me in.
She will.
I know she will.
I hope so.
Sam,
melinda has got this huge heart.
And she's such a good person,
And she helps a lot of people,
And she just doesn't like to be
in the limelight or take credit.
Credit for what?
You just gotta give her some time.
Yeah.
And when she does talk to you,
You gotta keep an open mind, ok?
Like, wide open.
Here you go.
Coffee, and in honor of our ghost,
Blueberry pastries.
'Cause I did a little research,
And our ghost--
Is most likely evelyn bellsbury,
Who the neighbors
affectionately refer to as
mrs. Blueberry.
So you met trouble.
Yes, I met trouble, and
I brought him dog biscuits, too.
I really do my homework.
You know, if mrs. Bellsbury
Tells us what happened to her,
She could be--
She could be the one.
The one?
Yeah, I mean, people may think
That folks like you and I are crazy,
But if we can actually prove
that a ghost helped us solve
A missing person's case...
oh, she's here!
Hit the lights.
Come here.
Holy cow.
Talk to her.
Talk to her!
Evelyn?
Can you tell me what happened to you?
Whoa, she's on the move. Here.
Put these on.
She's moving
kind of slow because--
She walked with a cane.
Yeah.
Oh, look!
There it is.
Oh, my god.
It really is her.
This is awesome!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's the door the occupant
said kept opening.
Even when it was locked.
I got goosebumps.
Do you have goosebumps?
Mrs. Bellsbury?!
She's gone.
Sorry, sorry, sorry. My bad.
Cake mix?
It's empty.
Hey, look, there's
a false bottom to this.
13 cents.
It's an old savings passbook.
Look at this--
Right before she disappeared,
She withdrew everything she had in cash.
Do you think she hoarded
all of her money In these cake boxes?
Yes, I do.
But where's the money now?
Little old lady, living alone.
Withdraws all of her
savings, and then--
Wait, wait, you think somebody knew
That all of her money was here?
Could have been anyone.
Housekeeper or someone
Who followed her home from the bank.
- 'Cause the next thing--
- She disappears.
She leaves a fresh batch
Of blueberry tarts
just sitting on the
windowsill, Cooling.
What a waste.
???
murder!
We're talking murder!
Poor little mrmrs. Blueberry,
She put all her money into dry goods,
And they whacked her!
All right, keep your voice down!
God, what are you, in the mob?
Wait until you see the footage.
did he upload this
to his website already?
yeah, guy's gotta make a living.
And if linus cracks a murder,
He's on his way to
some serious ghost coin.
I thought you said
this was a passion for him.
It is! And after seeing my first spirit,
I'm thinking about
quitting my day job, too.
You were that inspired
By some shifting, grainy blob?
Don't call mrs. Blueberry a blob.
She's a nice, murdered little old lady.
How do you know?
She baked treats.
How do you know that she was murdered?
Ok, so, fine, she led
you to some stored money--
Uh, all of her money,
Withdrawn days before she disappeared.
One day it's gone, and so is she.
What?
What, you think she went to paris
and left her tarts on the windowsill?
I don't know.
The woman was 76 years old.
Maybe she forgot about them.
oh! I forgot about them!
Why can't this be murder?!
Are you jealous because
i'm playing with linus and not you?
look, if she
was killed by somebody,
Why wouldn't she
just tell you that?
- Sam!
- Hey.
Eli!
Melinda.
Eli.
Sam.
Yeah, I just, uh,
i thought i'd come by.
I saw you were home, and...
What is that?
Uh, that's--
That's the guy.
That's the ghost guy, right?
Yeah, uh, eli was just showing it to me.
Yeah, uh, I was talking to him.
I like people who are
different and stuff.
Wait a minute, what's that?
Supposed to be some kind of ghost?
I think so, yeah.
Yeah. How did he do that?
What makes you think he did anything?
What, you guys don't believe
in this stuff, do you?
Well, I mean, he recorded sounds
And some energy moving around.
Yeah, well, it's easy enough
to doctor footage, isn't it?
Well, yeah, I guess so, but the
neighbors did say that they heard voices,
You know, when nobody else was home.
Right, hearing noises,
like bumps in the night.
It's basically air and plumbing.
And energy moving around,
isn't that just when We forget
where we put our keys?
Well, what makes you so sure?
You know, I barely
know who I am right now,
So i'm not sure about much,
but the one thing I am sure of
Is that ghosts aren't real,
And i'm very sure that guys
like this who say they are
Are just preying on
other people's fears.
what's up with
jim's negativ-O attitude
About all things paranormal?
You'd think a ghost ate
his dog or something.
Yeah, it's weird. I mean,
jim was never like that, not at all.
When you told him,
he just jumped right in a believer?
All I know is, he--
He believed in me,
And somehow it's harder
for him to do that.
oh, wait, ok! Listen,
I really get the sense--
And this knucklehead,
He's not making it any easier.
what can you do?
Nothing! It's probably fine.
Look, you said a woman was murdered
in our house and she's still there.
How is that fine?
it's, uh--Oh, hi.
Hey, I was just coming by
to see how everything's going.
Honestly? Terrible.
Guess what? We bought a haunted house.
- Honey, i--
- You saw the proof!
You guys are talking about
the previous owner, right?
Mrs. Bellsbury? Did you ever meet her?
No. Did you?
No.
Did you actually--
Did you actually see her?
I mean, how did she
make her presence known?
Well, we started hearing clanging
And banging in the night.
And the jars would
rattle in the basement.
The jars?
You know, the sealed glass jars
People buy for canning.
She left hundreds of them.
Uh, look, we, uh, we have
to re-Register at the hotel
If we're going to stay another night.
It's good seeing you, melinda.
- ??
- And you,
you call us
if there's any resolution.
And I truly believe that spirits
Do not mean us any harm,
you know, They just want to be
heard and understood!
You didn't tell me about jars.
I didn't know about them, i still don't.
Ok, well, you said that she was
hiding her money in the pantry.
Then it's gone, what else is missing?
Um, her body?
The fruits of her labor.
Ok. All right, she was stocking up.
What year did she go missing, exactly?
Uh, I guess it was 1999.
So the last time that
the neighbors saw her,
It was christmas.
But what if--What if she
wasn't saving up for christmas?
What if it was for new year's?
Mrs. Bellsbury?
If it is you,
Can you please tell me
what happened--
Oh, no. No.
No, no, no. Hey, wait, wait, come back!
She's here!
Um, she's, um, she's here! She's here!
He's a psycho. Let's go.
what is that?
Do you hear that?
I don't hear ghosts. You do.
Oh, right.
Oh.
Come here,
Why is she making that noise?
No!
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute. What happened?
are you seeing this?!
It's mrs. Bellsbury!
I know that dress.
I saw it in a photo. Holy cow!
Hello, are you seeing this?!
I see it!
I saw it.
And?
Right body, wrong ghost.
The pressure latch jammed.
She got locked in.
Wasn't a robbery, either.
The police said they found
Her life savings down there.
Minus the 13 cents
we found in that cake box.
So much for robbery murder.
Yeah. I'm glad about that.
Look, i'm gonna try
and grab some more gear,
See if I can get in there.
The police might need my help, you know?
There's still a story to be told here.
And thanks to this puppy,
i'm the man to tell it.
I think mrs. Bellsbury's been
at peace For a long, long time now.
Are you sure you didn't see her spirit?
Not unless she was trans-Gendered
Or cut twenty years off her age.
What was she doing down there?
I think she was preparing
for the millennium.
I mean, the jars, the preserves,
The money that she was
hiding in her secret room.
A panic room.
She was making a panic room
because 1999 Was coming to a close.
Yeah, the whole world was freaking out.
You know, january first, 2000.
The computers were supposed to fail;
Banking systems collapse.
Life as we know it would cease.
She was a y2k nut.
But who's the ghost that led us to her?
I have no idea.
Neither does linus.
And mrs. Blueberry sure ain't talking.
Wait a minute.
Linus.
What if we're right?
What if the ghost isn't someone
in her life Or the new owners?
Who else does that leave?
Linus?
But I only said that
'cause you said it already.
Ever since he got his fancy equipment,
His very accurate fancy equipment,
He's been able to see ghosts everywhere.
I haven't seen ghosts everywhere.
Have you heard any?
I just assumed he was exaggerating.
What if he wasn't?
What if the reason he's
the only one who's finding ghosts
Is because he's the one who's haunted?
Anyway, as you can see,
there's a lot of activity here.
it's unbelievable!
I've gotten 3 calls
from reporters, 2 new clients,
and my website Is
getting slammed with hits.
Congrats.
You're the one that figured out
That mrs. B was canning for catastrophe.
You should be sharing
some of the credit.
I appreciate that, but I prefer
To keep what I do private.
Why? It's so cool.
Eli, you could change
the way that people think
About the dead, about the unknown,
About everything.
Yeah, well, it might change
the way people think about me.
you can't--
You can't be worried about that.
I--I--Yes, I know,
I paid the price for believing,
But it doesn't matter,
'cause it's important to me.
Why?
I mean, one day i heard ghosts,
I needed an explanation.
But you, you took a leap of
faith long before you had proof.
Oh, I had proof.
Believe me.
I grew up in a bad part of the city.
And when we were 9,
My friend, he got shot.
Just crossing the street.
It was pretty hard to feel safe
after that, But...
i did.
Why?
My grandmother told me
that he was with me.
Your friend who died?
Did your grandmother have the gift?
well, she can't see
or hear ghosts,
But she believes in guardian angels.
And she said that
I have one with me now.
And she must have been right,
Because how else would I
have gotten out of there?
Gone to college, graduate school.
All along the way, being guided
to people who would help me.
Well, like carrie.
Carrie? Who's carrie?
Is that someone who died?
No. No, no, no. It's my ex-Girlfriend.
You saw her picture.
Yeah. Even after she broke up with me,
She loaned me the money to buy that
multi-Frequency sensitive camera.
I mean, is that nice or what?
Um, mixed.
But i'm interested in
this guardian angel.
Is he still with you?
Sure, yeah, I guess.
Do you think it's someone other than
your friend Who died as a child?
Say a man, mid-Fifties,
you may have known?
That's pretty specific, eli.
Do you know anyone who died
who matches that description?
No, no, not a soul.
Why? Do you hear somebody around me?
Because i'm pretty sure that carrie
would have captured something like that.
Carrie, your girlfriend?
No, no, no, no. I named
my mfs camera in her honor.
Ok.
When you said carrie
picks up ghost images,
Basically everywhere you
go since you got it--
Her, There's a spirit around you.
Spirits are everywhere.
I mean, I just didn't see them
until I got carrie.
When was that, exactly?
He doesn't know anyone
who fits that description?
He didn't seem to, but I do know
when he started clocking spirit stuff.
Spirits, or this particular spirit?
That's for you to figure out.
I got papers to grade.
But it all started when his
girlfriend carrie gave him the boot
And a nice loan for his
fancy camera-- A rather large loan.
Eli, i'm not a jealous guy.
I mean, she and i haven't
been dating long enough
For me to even be jealous.
But, look, i have to say,
I do notice you coming in and out
of melinda's At all hours, I do.
We're friends.
I know that, And that's not
what i'm after here.
I don't think for a minute
that you guys are involved.
Not for a minute?
I mean, we're not, but...
a minute?
Eli...
I'm here about the bodies.
Excuse me?
The dead people that tend to surface
Every time melinda becomes
interested in something.
There was--There was the little girl
At the bottom of the well
She was suddenly fascinated by.
There was the sorority
girl lost in the woods.
She wasn't dead.
Nearly dead. And then there's
the old lady that they just found.
Look, eli, tell me, i know
you worked on this case.
Case? What are you talking about?
I'm a professor.
Yeah, but you're also
a clinical psychologist
Who consults with the police.
What makes you think that?
Because you told me
one night, over drinks.
I gotta quit drinking.
You had one beer.
That's pathetic.
I gotta quit bragging.
Look, I talked to delia
and she said, look,
Cut melinda some slack, ok,
because she does so much
For the community, You know.
She helps people.
Now you tell me, how does
an antiques dealer do that?
Well, you can do stuff.
Ah, you can't tell me.
All right, i'll say it--
She's a profiler, isn't she?
Well, if she was,
and i'm not saying she is,
Don't you think it should
be her place to tell you?
She lies to me.
And I just want to know why.
And if she's not working with the law,
Then what the hell is she doing?
Please.
Ok, look.
Her official title is criminologist, ok?
But she operates completely
and totally under the radar.
The fed insist on that.
Yeah.
So linus sent you to me for a reference?
Well, how did you know you were haunted?
I've, um...
i've sensed things around me,
I'm guessing that you
believe in what linus does.
What's important is that he believes.
He's not in it for the money.
When I was with him,
I had to push him to
even bill for his time.
Do you--
Do you feed the birds
like that every night?
no.
It's a baby raccoon.
I think its mother abandoned it.
Oh.
I guess i'm just
the patron saint of lost causes--
Like linus.
I'm guessing that
he wasn't having much luck
When you with him.
Finding ghosts, I mean.
No.
Not too many.
But did you see him
on the news last night?
He found this woman
who had been missing for years.
If only some people could see him now.
Who are we talking about?
My father.
He, uh, he died.
I'm sorry.
He was always so hard on linus.
You know, he thought he was
Such a loser and a kook,
A pile of wasted potential.
Not someone to build a future with.
And when the rent checks kept bouncing
And a fun date
Meant going to the impound
to get the boot off our car...
I caved.
And I dumped him.
But you missed him.
A lot.
Enough to buy some
new equipment for him?
Well, after my father died,
i didn't see the harm.
Do you--Do you have
a picture of him?
Your father?
Yeah, why?
I think I can tell you in a minute.
If I could just see a picture.
Ok, I have some on my phone.
He would roll over in his grave
If he knew what I did with his money.
Yeah, I think he's done
much more than that.
???
Well, I guess the linus
show is extended once again.
But what people don't realize
is the ghost h he's looking for
Is his ex-Girlfriend's father.
What is wrong with you?
You'd think as a shrink
i'd know what to do with my anger,
But look at me, my body is vibrating.
You're really that mad?
I mean, he's a ghost.
They lie to us all the time.
No, this is different.
Linus can't detect ghosts like us,
Ok, but that never shook his faith.
He doesn't deserve to be
deliberately mocked this way.
Wow, you really care about him.
Yeah, I do. He's kind of like my protÉG?.
He kinda looks up to me.
Aw, that's cute.
It's not cute, it's serious.
I hope this ghost creep
stays earth-Bound forever.
I'm just glad the old man
screwed up so bad
He made linus look like
an actual genius.
You just said that the ghost actually
Made linus look like a genius.
Yeah, his plan backfired, precisely.
What if that was his plan?
Ok? What if--
What if that ghost is
actually trying to help him?
Oh, great.
So now all of a sudden,
the ghost is a good guy?
What would be wrong with that?
What am I supposed to
do with my anger now?
Walk it off.
All right? We have to go talk to linus.
Go.
Walk.
With a full night to observe, maybe two,
I can confirm whether or not
your manifestations
Indicate a spectral infestation.
So this is for real?
Those machines can prove
we have actual ghosts?
Didn't you talk to devon and john?
Well, what happens after?
How do you get rid of them?
Uh, well, I mean,
there's a whole process.
Um, but detection is the first step
To elimination.
Could you excuse us for a minute?
Yeah, of course.
So I guess word of mouth
is good for business.
You know, it's like ever since
that mrs. Bellsbury thing,
It's like everybody who has
air in their plumbing Has a ghost.
It's not that i'm saying
that they don't.
It's just I feel kind of bad
taking advantage, you know?
So is that how john and devon found you?
Is you helped somebody they knew?
Actually, there's a funny story to that.
Both john and devon each said that
they found their browser
Open to my website.
And they thought that
the other one left it for them.
I've seen evidence of ghosts
interacting with electronics before, But..
it's almost like mrs. Bellsbury
Wanted me to find her, you know?
Yeah, it's a lot like that.
Ok.
Ok, you may be right.
The ghost may not be evil.
Yeah, which means he's been
leading you this whole time--
To the money stash,
the basement room, Everything.
But we did some pretty good
detective work. I mean...
And the ghost had us
look where he wanted.
Look, I wasn't suggesting
That you're not a good profiler.
You, either.
The best.
Yeah, except i'm not a profiler.
What?
Sam stopped by earlier.
Had some questions.
eli!
And I was a vault on
the whole ghost thing.
I didn't say anything,
not a word, not even a syllable.
The whole ghost thing?
Yeah. Sometimes you have to use
A smaller lie to cover the larger one.
What did you tell him?
He may have gotten the impression
That you sometimes
work for the government.
The government?!
Fbi, really.
Fbi?!
As a profiler, but
it sounds pretty sexy, right?
Hey!
- Oh, my god.
- ??
- Are you ok?
- I'm ok.
You were running so fast--
Jacob, honey, what happened?!
- I'm ok.
- You ok?
I'm ok. I just fell.
What are you scared of?
Why were you running?
He said there were ghosts!
He said that?
Is that true?
You told this child there
were ghosts in his house?
No, I was trying to explain to
the parents how this all works--
Wait a minute, how what works?
How your camera takes pictures
of things that aren't there?
Or how to make out the check?
Sam, listen, i think that
You don't understand the whole picture.
No, I think I do.
The credit this guy
Is taking for finding a dead body
actually belongs to someone else,
And none of this has
anything to do with ghosts!
- Well, actually--
- No, I know this.
I'm not going to tell you
how I know this, but I know it.
No, you don't!
Melinda, you don't
have to defend him--
Yes, I do!
Linus is telling the truth.
What? I don't understand this.
It's all real.
Linus, the ghost, the machines.
Melinda, I can make you a ghost
detector machine in 5 minutes.
You need batteries, diodes, and--
Yeah, except I don't--
I don't need the machine
to tell me that it's real.
I see ghosts.
I have since i was a little kid.
All right, if this is
supposed to be funny, it's not.
??
Come on, come on.
What took you? I got everyone here,
But i'm a little stuck without my eyes.
Is this ghost ready
for the big crossover?
Why don't you ask him?
Well, he's here, i established that,
I just don't know
what kind of mood he's in.
Better than mine.
Oh.
Ahh, that thing with sam?
Let's just get this over with.
That's the attitude.
Carrie, hi. Um...
Your father's here, and I think there's
something he wants to say to you.
Not only her.
I want to say something to linus.
And to linus.
I'm sorry that i doubted you
When you told me
what you believed about ghosts.
I don't know if I can do this.
I remember when linus first explained
Where his belief came from.
His guardian angel.
He remembers when you told him
about your friend,
The one that died.
That was the first i brought linus home.
Probably not the best way
to make an impression.
I thought he was weak-Minded
to believe in such nonsense.
Until I was dead, i never...
Understood how alone he must have felt.
Or how strong he was to believe anyway.
Nolan says he never appreciated
How hard it must have
been for linus to believe
When everyone doubted him.
And to think my not believing
Might have ruined
their chance at love...
I couldn't go on until I made it right.
Nolan couldn't stand the idea
That his doubt kept you two apart.
So that's when he found mrs. Bellsbury
And led linus to her.
He thought if linus got some
credibility for the case,
It would bring carrie back to you.
Is that about right?
Thank you.
You've given me the greatest joy.
He's crossing over,
and he says good-Bye.
Come here.
Why is it so hard?
What?
Believing.
Hey.
You got a minute?
You must hate me right now.
Hate you?
For making you feel
bad about...what you do.
Look, who the hell am I to--
It's not your fault.
It's just a sensitive thing for me.
Ever since i lost my memory,
and my life.
I try to latch on to
things that are solid,
And so it's made me allergic
to things that are...
Not so solid.
That makes sense.
It's funny.
Because some of the best things in
my life right now Make no sense at all.
Like what?
Like us.
We don't make any sense?
No, me waking up out of this coma
And the only thing i know
are my feelings for you.
I can't explain it. I--
I have to rewind the tape.
No, please, let's--
Let's not rewind the tape.
Right.
If you're looking for something solid...
What about ghosts?
Why would I let something
I can't see come between us?
Because this thing
that I do, it's--
it's a really big part of me,
And if you don't
believe in it, i--
Hey, you needed a little time
and a little space
To get ready to tell me this.
Let me have the same
to get used to it.
Take all the time you need.
all right,
thanks.
welcome to www.1000fr.com