Previously on Ghost Whisperer...
No!
I'll always love you, Melinda.
Please. not you.
You have to cross over.
I don't want to.
Jim, no!
You're back.
Do I know you?
I see the same guy that you see,
Different hair, nose, eyes.
It's not Jim. he's in there somewhere.
He just has to be.
You're not gonna tell me that you think
I'm your husband reincarnated.
Because you're the only sane
person I've met since I woke up.
It's not much. but maybe you
can help me finish my garage.
And you could live there
while you do the work.
Just until you figure
out your next move.
Do you know how lucky you are?
You are gonna get a second
shot at your one true love.
That's strange. I've
been hoping for a clue,
Something to tell me who I was.
Guess I got more than I bargained for.
I bought that less than a month ago.
Question is... who did I buy it for?
Hey!
Hey. you're looking
chipper this morning.
That's how a morning off effects me.
Oh, yeah. you got a little...
- Thank you.
- Yeah, sure.
Where you running off to?
The farmer's market. we're supposed
to meet Delia there at 9:00.
We are?
Oh, that's right.
Melinda, I'm so sorry. I gotta do a job.
Yeah... yeah. anything interesting?
Well, if you call making kitchen
cabinets interesting, then yeah.
Cabinets are great. I
mean, I love cabinets.
You found that... that ring...
Did you ever look into it?
Right. yeah.
- The ring...
- Right.
Did you find out anything?
You don't want to know. sorry.
Of course I want to know.
that's all I want... is to know.
Charlie used to say that. drove me nuts.
Jim never did. because Jim
was never a question dodger.
What does that even mean,
"you don't want to know"?
Well, with Charlie it either meant
that he didn't want to talk about it,
Or he didn't want me to talk about it,
Or that he actually wanted to
talk, but wasn't sure if I did.
Well, thank you. that's helpful.
So, what do you think Sammeant?
What else could he mean?
He found her... his girlfriend,
His soon-to-be
future wife.
That's why he blew me off today.
That's why he's been
so distracted lately.
Because he found her.
And he's probably gonna get on a plane.
He's gonna fly all the
way to Michigan or Paris
Or wherever it is she is right now.
Mel, I seriously doubt that Jim's spirit
Would have gone through all the
trouble of taking over Sam's body
Just to run off with another woman.
Please tell me nobody heard me say that.
Yeah. but he doesn't
even know that he's Jim.
I mean, what if he smells her perfume
And he gets confused or attracted or...
Honey, you are spinning.
I wouldn't have to if he
wasn't dodging my questions.
It's just too loaded.
I mean, I don't know
how to approach it...
Oh, you could.
That's perfect!
It's not perfect. it's bruised.
They all are. see?
No, not again!
I'm sorry. did I do that?
No, it happens all the time.
And you wonder why?
Well if I could get
some help around here!
I need to get home and cook dinner.
Well, maybe I can help you.
Oh thank god, finally
somebody with manners!
You know I have been
coming here every Saturday
for God knows how long,
All of a sudden he decides to ignore me.
I don't you how long I've been waiting.
How long do you think?
I... I'm not sure.
Let me guess, a ghost wants pie?
I'm not sure what she wants.
I don't even think she knows she's dead.
Wait!
Could I,get 4 of those? thank you.
They're for you. maybe I
could give you a ride home.
Oh, that's so sweet. thank you.
My name is Tammy. Tammy Gardner.
You... you did get the
organic ones, right?
You know what, I better go and check.
Did you just offer to give
a ride home to a ghost?
Only because she doesn't
realize that she's dead.
Hi.
Hi, I'm Melinda Gordon.
Are you Mr. Gardner?
Yes, I am. I'm sorry.
Like I tell all you
realtors, we're not selling.
Actually, I'm here about your wife.
My wife? oh, she's not
here. she's at the market.
Did something happen?
How long ago did she leave?
Over an hour ago. she was due back...
Ah, there she is now!
Hey, sweetheart.
Who's she?
I was getting worried.
Melinda, this is my wife, Elizabeth.
Unless you two know each other?
No.
No, the thing is I own
an antique store in town,
And someone left a vase on consignment,
And I was just trying to track her down.
Hmm. that wasn't me. I'm sorry.
You know, just so there are no mix-ups,
The woman who left the vase,
Her name was Tammy... Tammy Gardner.
Tammy, um...
Tammy was my first wife. we're divorced.
Oh. you wouldn't have a recent
address change for her maybe?
No, I'm sorry.
I haven't heard from her since
she walked out on me 2 years ago.
Wish I could've been more help.
Good day.
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you.
But I went by your
store. but it was closed.
And your address was listed...
So is my phone number.
I know, I'm sorry.
I wanted to see to you in person.
I need you to tell me what
you know about my wife.
When exactly did she leave?
Just about 2 years ago, October 15.
I remember that day because
it was our fourth anniversary.
At first I wasn't worried.
She'd disappeared before.
sort of a pattern for her.
But she'd always come back
after a couple of days.
When she didn't show up after 3 days,
I knew something was wrong.
I just can't understand
why she hasn't contacted me.
You said this was a
pattern? her disappearing?
Maybe in a way it's good
she hasn't contacted me.
Means she's probably
staying out of trouble.
What kind of trouble?
She had mood swings.
What did she do?
She couldn't stand feeling confined.
She'd run away, then come back,
Looking disheveled and confused.
That doesn't sound at
all like the Tammy I met.
That's part of the illness.
I mean, she could be
delightful and happy one day,
And then... and then
depressed and angry the next.
Was she ever diagnosed?
Oh, no. no. she refused to see a doctor.
I talked to plenty myself.
Said it was some sort
of bipolar disorder.
I loved her so much.
But it's so painful living with someone
You can't break through to.
I know what you mean.
Why didn't you tell that poor guy
That his ex-wife is haunting him?
Because I don't want
to make things worse...
Roger's already got a ghost
in his house because of me.
Besides, I need a little more
information, like how she died.
Do you still think there's a chance
that she could've moved on?
I can hope. something tells
me she'll be here soon.
Because this is where
I saw her yesterday.
Which would tell us she's
still stuck in the loop,
Still playing Suzie homemaker.
I'm just wondering if her
imprint has something to do with
mental illness and not her death.
She's stuck in a loop because
she's loopy? makes sense.
You're not helping.
No, it does. really.
People in the manic
stage of bipolar disorder
Often have trouble assimilating
anything negative...
Like being dead, for instance?
That's the fourth person
you let go before me.
I just need my husband's shirt...
It's the blue one in the plastic,
And I said no plastic.
Hi.
- Ok. 3 pieces.
- Thanks.
Somebody help!
Stop this thing!
Tammy! stop it!
Oh, I'm so glad you're
here!It's a blue shirt,
and Roger likes light
starch if you could just...
We are not gonna pick up
your husband's dry cleaning.
You don't need to take
care of him anymore.
It's time for you to move on.
I can't do that.
What would happen to my family?
I need to take care of them, of Roger.
No, you don't. they'll be fine...
Stop it. Don't say that. Roger needs me.
He has a new wife.
Ok? he's moved on.
You can let go now, really. it's ok.
Why are you being so
mean? You helped me before.
Why can't you help me now?
Make those people listen to me!
They can't. not anymore.
The day that they stopped hearing you
Was the day that you died.
Look, you know, don't
you? what happened?
Oh dear...
There was something...
It happened after I fell
asleep. I remember thinking
It was strange how fast
I was falling asleep.
And then what happened?
I was floating.
There was a big grassy field
And lots of tall trees below me.
My car was there.
And colors,
Lots of bright colors
flying all around me.
Oh, no... I have to get home.
Lots of colors? sounds
like a hallucination.
Yeah or maybe not.
She said that she was above a field,
There were tall trees.
She disappeared in October.
Is this what you saw that day, Tammy?
Kites? floating colors? Am I close?
Hot? cold? lukewarm?
Crap. need some dialogue here,
A little back and forth.
It's not so easy when you
have a client that's invisible.
Ok, I've hiked far enough.
And I draw the line at thistles.
What's that? look, I'm sweating now.
So if it turns out to
be another dead end...
No. no!
This can't be true.
I can't be dead. not like this.
I told my friend detective Blair
that I found the body hiking,
As opposed to breaking and entering,
Which is how I found the last dead body
That I called into her.
How many times can you do that
Before they haul you away?
Well, they haven't locked me up yet.
That's wildly reassuring. that's nice.
At least now we know
how and when she died.
Possibly why she's stuck
here... out of guilt.
Because she abandoned
her husband and kids?
Yeah. maybe that's why
she's trying so hard now
To take care of them.
I just don't understand
Why this ghost is so
hard to get through to.
I mean, she's seen
her husband's new wife,
Her own dead body...
You'd think that would bring
up something. but it hasn't it.
If she's drawn to that square,
Maybe something happened there
That she doesn't want to remember.
Like, an affair?
Roger said she used to disappear a lot,
Maybe she was meeting someone there.
Right, maybe she was seeing someone
And her husband never knew.
Yeah. or he did, and
didn't want to believe it.
Hey, Roger.
It's Melinda Gordon. I
was hoping we could talk.
So, call me. ok. thanks.
I don't know what's happening to me.
I see that woman in my
house. something's very wrong.
It's because you don't
belong there anymore.
And you know that somewhere deep down.
You left the house. and that's hard.
But you really have to remember why.
I remember... trying
to make Roger happy.
How I felt like it was
the most important thing
I could ever do.
And... and how I'd always
worry about my kids.
I don't... I don't have any kids.
But I used to feel that
way about my husband.
Spirits often don't remember things
because somewhere deep down,
They don't want to.
Why wouldn't I want to?
Usually guilt.
You talk about your family a lot.
Maybe that's what you feel
guilty about? Or maybe...
maybe you just need to say
goodbye to your children.
I don't know. God.
I can't think about it anymore.
I have to get home.
I can't be late.
Hey, what's up? Come on in.
Oh, thanks.
You look like you're running off.
Yeah, it's really urgent.
What is?
I have to get to the laundromat
before every T-shirt I own
starts standing up by itself.
Oh, so that's your...
You're not planning a trip?
No. why? You trying to get rid of me?
No... no, it's just that, uh...
My mom might come, and she stays here...
Here in the garage?
Allergy thing.
So if you were gonna plan a trip to,
I don't know, Paris or Michigan.
I would need a heads-up.
Ok.
Well, the contractor guy I
work for has got a spare room
No. No. No. Cause,
cause you know, she might not come.
You know what?
Your mom lives just over in Hamilton.
Right. Right. Which is why
she might not stay over.
So you should stay put.
You know, the doctors
didn't tell me if my
subtext decoder was
damaged in that accident
But are you're trying
to tell me something?
No.
Yes.
Yes. I just realized that
I have a washer and dryer inside.
And you could use them.
Thank you.
Delia, I was an absolute idiot.
No, there's no need to
coddle me, I was there.
I was an idiot.
I'm at Roger's house.
I just want to, I don't
know, feel him out,
See if he ever suspected
Tammy of any kind of affair.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
Listen, you know what?
I'll talk to you soon, ok? bye.
Excuse me.
Do you know the kids
who live in this house?
There's no kids there,
just that lady and her husband.
Oh. Do you ever remember there
ever being kids in this house?
Nope. Never. And we've
lived here forever.
Ok. Thanks.
This isn't a good time.
I'm about to be arrested.
Det. Blair asked me to come down.
I guess she wants to read me my rights
Yeah. There are no kids.
- Where?
- At Roger's house.
One of the neighborhood kids said
they've never seen any kids.
Wait. Tammy always talked about family,
I assumed...
Yeah, so did I. But
it never dawned on me
That they may not be Roger's kids.
I mean, maybe she was married before.
So where's the family
she's always been talking about?
That's what I was hoping you
could ask Det. Blair.
I gotta go,
If you don't hear from me,bring bail.
Have a seat.
I had nothing to do with it.
What?
I found another dead body,
You want to arrest me, admit it.
Look, you're a talented profiler.
You help me solve cases.
I don't care how it works.
Oh. Ok.
So, uh, was it a suicide?
Well, it looks that way.
The dental records confirmed
the woman was a Tammy Gardner.
Her husband's been informed.
What about her kids?
Do you have any records of the children?
No.
Says here the only family
she had was a Roger Gardner.
He filed the missing person's report.
But Sarah Evers had 2 children.
Who?
Well, that's why I called you down here.
The dental records also matched a woman
who's husband reported
her missing 6 years ago
Sarah Evers.
Wait. So, Tammy was also
Sarah? She had 2 identities?
Maybe more. We don't know yet.
So, does the first husband know?
Well, we're still trying to
track him, see what his story is.
Did Sarah's family live nearby?
Thomas Evers filed the missing
person's report from Lake Forest.
That's 3 counties over.
They don't know about their mom yet.
Haven't had the heart to tell them.
I never thought it would end like this.
Even after all these years,
I always thought she'd come back.
So, you said you were
a friend of Sarah's?
When she lived in Grandview.
Right.
I'll tell you what, when she left me,
I was blindsided.
I never saw it coming.
There were no signs of trouble?
No.
We were happy or so I thought.
Apparently everyone knew
what was really going on but me.
What do you mean?
After she left, the neighbors said
they'd suspected something.
We had an electrician,
did some work for us.
Said things that made them think affair.
Turns out, it was.
About a month later I get a postcard,
saying she's never coming back.
That must've been devastating.
You have no idea.
Especially for the boys...
7 and 10 at the time...
Their mother abandoned them.
I wanted to grow old with her so bad.
What did I do?
You ready?
I left them for Roger.
Sam!
Hey, Sam!
Sam, hi.
Oh, sorry.
I just, uh... I brought
this stuff by for Mel.
It's just got some fixtures
in it for the remodel.
Great. Thanks.
Sorry about the racket.
Oh, yeah. I understand.
You're just cranking it up
when the landlady's away.
Right. I know it's juvenile.
But it works perfectly when
you're trying to take
your mind of things.
You want some water?
Fruit juice? Anything?
Yeah. Sure. Some water.
And what kind of things?
Or is it something
you don't want to talk about?
I'm sure Melinda's told you
about this engagement ring.
Yeah. She mentioned it.
I really appreciate her concern.
But I feel weird
talking to her about it.
Because I know she's got
a lot going on in her life.
I think that she just
wants to make sure you're ok.
You know, I'm ok.
So are you thinking about
going to look for her?
Yeah. But what do I say
to her when I find her?
"Hi, I was about I was going to
propose marriage to you,
but I've got a serious head injury.
But by the way, was it chicken
or fish for the wedding?"
Yeah. I suppose that
would be kinda awkward.
I mean, I already
broke my family's heart
by not remembering them.
Do I really need to
add to the body count?
And besides, if this woman
is the love of my life,
How come she hasn't found me?
I don't know why I kept all this stuff.
It's hard letting go.
I guess some part of me
was hoping she was ok,
And that she'd want
her things back one day.
How is Elizabeth dealing with the news?
Well, it's been hard.
It's part of the reason I'm out here.
I figured it's time to put
the past behind us, you know?
So if this is about the vase,
you can go ahead and keep it.
No. actually it's not about that.
It's about Tammy.
I think it's time for
her to move on as well.
What do you mean?
I have a gift. I see earthbound spirits.
And I've seen Tammy. she's confused.
She has no memory about
what happened to her.
Is this some kind of joke?
I know how it must sound.
Ghosts that get stuck here like Tammy,
It's usually because of guilt.
I think hers has to do with the fact
That she left her
husband and boys for you.
Look, I don't know what you're after,
Or how you even know that.
But taking Tammy from her boys
is not something I'm proud of.
We fell in love. passionately in love.
Didn't mean to. just happened.
But lots of people get divorced.
Not so many flee in
the middle of the night.
Lots of people don't
have husbands like Thomas.
What does that mean?
Tammy made him out to be pretty awful.
But now, you know, I'm not
really sure about anything.
Because she left you, too.
Look. it doesn't matter
anymore. she's dead.
I tried to help her find
peace when she was alive.
I tried to give her a
good life. but I couldn't.
I guess nobody could.
He's all torn up. he doesn't
want anyone else to get hurt
So he's doing what men
do best... avoiding it.
So he hasn't found her? or
even started looking for her?
Nope.
Well, at least that buys me some time.
Although his fiancee could
still show up at any minute.
Hey, by then Sam will have
remembered that he's Jim.
And you will live
happily ever after. right?
Hey. hand me that box. I'll
take it out to the recycling bin.
I can see now... how I
left my boys, my family.
But I can't remember why. what happened?
You're the only one who
knows. try and think back.
You left Thomas, and
then you left Roger, too.
I know you say that, but
that couldn't have happened.
I'd never leave Roger.
Please. why can't I remember?
What happened? did
someone do that to you?
Sweetheart, you poor thing.
It's ok. I'm here now.
I don't know how that happened.
Was it Thomas?
Cause Roger said that he
didn't treat you very well.
Or was it Roger? or someone else?
No. Roger would never hurt
me. he always took care of me.
Ok. well, either way, it's
something Roger knows about you.
Maybe he talked to Elizabeth.
His new wife?
Well, she had to have asked
about you, about what happened.
You've been hanging
around the old house.
Is Elizabeth home right now?
No. she went out.
She's at the farmer's market.
Hi, I was at your house the other day.
Melinda, right?
Sorry to bother you. I know
this is a difficult time.
I'm sorry? what do you mean?
Well, Roger must be upset
about his first wife.
What are you talking about?
Tammy's dead.
They found her body yesterday.
How did... how did... what happened?
They're calling it a suicide.
But she had bruises on her wrists.
I think she was abused.
Did she tell you that?
No, she just looked really scared.
Like you do right now.
I'm going to tell you the
same thing that I told her.
You're not alone.
There are people that can help.
I can help.
It's safe to talk to me.
I'm sorry. I have to get
home. I can't be late.
Elizabeth!
You're starting to remember, aren't you?
I was just like her.
I was so scared. I was
in such a dark place.
You were abused, of course
you were in a dark place.
No. no.
I was in a really dark place.
Tammy?
I don't know how long I'd been in there.
It seemed like forever.
So, after you left your husband,
Is that how Roger would punish you?
No.
That's where Roger kept
me after he kidnapped me.
Thomas was working late,
I was up doing the dishes.
I thought Roger had gone
home. But suddenly he was...
standing right behind me. He
said he knew that I wasn't happy.
And that he could make me happy.
Was there something
going on between you two?
No! I barely knew him.
He was... he was just some
guy doing work on our house.
But the neighbors told your
husband they suspected something.
I remember seeing him talking to them.
I just... i just thought he was
just trying to round up more work.
So he wanted them to suspect
something to cover his tracks.
What happened after he locked you up?
I lost count of the days.
I thought I was losing my mind.
I remember hearing my boys' voices.
I couldn't tell what was real anymore.
Then one day, it all just changed.
Upsy-daisey. there we go.
Ooh, these are a little tight, huh?
Suddenly he was so kind and caring.
It's ok.
At first it was just food.
And then it was bigger things.
Like letting me go outside.
Eventually he let me take
trips to the market alone.
So you started to trust him.
Oh God, how could I have?!
You were brainwashed.
It happens. I don't know why.
It's called stockholm syndrome.
Did you ever try to get away?
No. no!
I couldn't.
He threatened that if I did, he
would kill my family, my boys.
So the only escape was to kill yourself.
No, I wouldn't.
Then what happened that day?
I was at the market.
For some reason I was late getting home.
Hey, honey.
I was worried about you.
Sorry, I'm fine.
No, you're not fine.
What's going on, darling?
Nothing, it's... nothing.
You know you can't lie to me.
Did something happen in town
you want to tell me about? Hmm?
No, I must've lost track of time.
After that he told me to
go upstairs and rest...
That he would make me something to eat.
We ate.
Then, I felt sleepy.
And I wanted to say something, but...
But the words wouldn't come out.
Roger always told me,
"I decide when you leave. "
I guess he decided it was time.
After he kidnapped and stockholmed her?
That's possible. Right?
I mean, I'm not making this stuff up?
No, what you're describing
is exactly how it works.
He grabs her. He locks her up.
He threatens to kill
her family if she runs.
She's scared out of her wits.
So what if he's doing the
same thing to Elizabeth?
You said Elizabeth seemed
scared, which is good,
That tells me she isn't
completely brainwashed.
Look, I want you to call
Det. Blair and find out
if anyone matching
Elizabeth's description
has gone up missing in the last year.
If she has a family anywhere,
we need to get them somewhere safe.
And what're you gonna do?
Just call me when it's done.
Elizabeth, are you here?
Roger spied on me sometimes.
I never knew when it would be.
So you're saying he could've seen me
talking to Elizabeth at the market.
Is someone there?
Help.
Oh, my God.
Are you ok?
I'm so sorry.
Stay away from her!
Don't do this! I love you.
Is that what you said to Tammy? is it?
Before you killed her?!
She told you that?! she's insane!
She says she sees ghosts!
Well, maybe she'll see yours soon!
That's enough!
Get out of the way!
Put it down, the police
are on their way. Ok?
He's gonna get his
punishment. Put it down.
Punishment for what? having a wife?
Who is gonna believe
that I was held captive?
They'll say I could've
run. He'll get away with it.
He thinks of everything.
Then you have to think of
everything... your family.
All right, if you kill him,
you're gonna get put away.
And you'll be kept
away from them forever.
Think of your family. Put it down.
Now you'll know what it
feels like to be a prisoner.
No, no, please. Don't leave.
Help me! Please! Elizabeth!
At least one of us got to go home.
Thank you.
I can help you talk to your family.
You could say goodbye.
No, they think I abandoned them.
And I almost did.
How could they ever forgive me?
You didn't abandon them, not really.
There was always a piece
of you that remembered.
I got your personal
effects from the station.
I almost missed this, it
was folded so many times.
That's my little boy.
That's Rich.
That's why I was late that night.
I stared at that picture for hours.
My heart just aching.
You must've put it in
your wallet that day.
Roger knew that you
were covering something.
He knew that he was losing control.
And he just couldn't let that happen.
Let's go home.
Do me a favor, get
your brother a soda, ok?
Thanks.
So you're saying you talked
with my wife's spirit.
That's why you came to me first.
That's, uh...
Crazy. Yeah, I know.
Um, Tammy...
Sarah, she needed some
answers about things.
She couldn't remember
what happened to her.
And now she does.
I'm so sorry, Thomas.
I wanted to grow old with you, too.
I wanted to see Joe hit
his first grand slam,
And Rich get his braces off
And I wanted to buy that
houseboat on the lake
And fill it with grandkids
just like we talked about.
She says there's so much that
she wanted to do with you,
The houseboat on the lake.
How did you know about that?
We had this joke.
We were gonna name
the boat, 2 old coots.
2 old coots?
She's really here, isn't she?
Oh God, she must hate me.
I just left her there!
6 years and I never went after her.
I should've looked harder for her.
All she went through. I did nothing.
How can I forgive myself?
You have to. please tell him that.
Roger kept me prisoner for so long.
He used guilt, fear,
remorse to keep me tied up.
Don't let him do that to you,
don't give him that victory.
I'm free now.
I want you to be, too.
She needs that to move on,
to know that you're free, like she is.
I love you so much. You were our world.
I know. I felt that.
She knows that.
And you did helped her
even if you didn't know it.
Hey, dad.
Will you make sure
that he tells them
everything that happened?
That I always loved them?
I see something.
It's a light.
That's for you.
Come here.
Thanks.
Anything good in there?
Yeah. Huge story.
Did you read about
that guy who kidnapped those 2 women?
Yeah. Crazy, huh?
What a happy ending for the woman.
Can you imagine what it was like
for her to see her family again?
Yeah. Thank God the
police got there in time.
She gets a real second chance.
Kinda like me.
I just can't keep
carrying this thing around.
I mean, I might have
somebody worrying about me.
Just like these women did.
And if you find that person, what then?
I don't know...