Commonly accepted methods
for communing with the dead.
As opposed to...
In my culture,
communication with the dead
Is taken very seriously.
Oh. Now you respect it.
You politically correct
trained weasels.
I expect the subject matter
to be taken very seriously.
Yes?
How come you never tell us
if you believe this stuff?
What does it matter?
We're studying trends,
Theories, systems of beliefs
that effect people.
Small subsets of people.
Like those who first believe
that the earth is round.
But it is.
Oh.
Been to outer space,
have you?
Seen the earth in all
of its rounded glory?
I'm just saying.
As per usual,
Some of you will
find this all absurd
And have a good laugh at it
over your next game of beer pong.
Others of you,
for whatever reason,
May find it
a little too real.
I told you,
I already have a t.A.
He's an econ major.
You need someone who's
serious about the field.
Here.
Look at this, ok?
Oh, wow,
nice spirit board.
Where'd you get it?
I scope garage sales for a
secondhand store I work at.
Yeah, it's rare.
I could have someone
look at it
If you're trying
to find a price.
It's a gift. For you.
It might be worth
something.
Sell it at the store
you work for.
I can't.
The woman who owns it,
well, let's just say
She's not really a fan
of this kind of thing.
Oh, an occult prude?
Not exactly.
But really,
you should have it.
Don't worry.
You're going
to ace this course,
So you don't have
to suck up to me.
That's not what I'm doing.
Then what
are you doing?
Is that a concert flyer??
Trey...
Where did you get this?
Get what?
This flyer.
Who put it on my door?
Oh, sorry.
I know you want messages
handed to you,
But it's not my fault.
I didn't see anyone
put it there.
Hmm.
Did you just do that?
No.
Did someone tell you
I like that band?
No.
But who would
know that?
Maybe the spirit
board knows.
For a clean-cut kid,
you're a little odd.
I know.
Come on in.
I've got it covered,
trey. Go.
Have you ever used
one of these before?
No.
But you must have,
right?
I mean,
in your course of study?
In eighth grade,
at a slumber party,
Marie antoinette told my friend
sintra she liked her clothes.
Did I mention sintra
was holding the planchette?
Why don't we ask
about the flyer?
Hmm.
Should professor avery
go to the concert tomorrow?
ned: Whoa!
Did you do that?
No.
Come on!
Look...
Somebody wants you
to go to that concert.
Somebody dead.
Office hours are over.
I'm sorry.
I didn't...
You can leave the board
if you want to.
So did you make
any inroads?
I still don't know why you
want this t.A. Job so bad.
I'd have access
to the faculty libraries.
Including
the copeland wing.
That's where the drake
collection was originally housed.
I can't even
go in there.
You have to be
with that department.
It's where we found
the book of changes.
Who knows what else
is buried in there?
So you want to do it to find
out more about the shadows?
I've been researching for
months trying to find something,
I mean, anything,
about whatever they are.
But I keep coming up dry.
The copeland wing...
Academics from everywhere
do occult research there.
Weird looking guys, too.
Some with accents,
funny hats.
Ok, I thought we were
talking about a ghost.
Yes, and if I can help get
it away from professor grant.
That's if the ghost who flipped
the spirit board even knows her.
Look, this spirit
could be anybody, ok?
That's the problem
with those stupid boards.
They upset ghosts who are
desperate to communicate;
Gets them frustrated,
and then you end up with...
Frustrated, upset ghost.
Exactly.
There's something
about that concert.
And professor grant
knew it, too.
She seemed
kind of freaked out.
She does have
a dead ex-boyfriend.
Fiancé, technically.
Car accident.
I thought
you didn't know her,
That you guys ran in
different circles.
Circles of guys
she hooked up with,
Briefly dates,
and then dumps.
I heard many sad stories.
Fine. What do we
know about her?
Well, I found a link
to her webpage.
Wow.
Tribute much?
Not to be insensitive, but this
is a shrine to her ex-fiancé.
I mean, piece of cake.
He's gotta be our ghost.
Am I right?
I'll keep
my eyes open.
Thanks for lunch.
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Hey, all right, yeah.
I don't have any money.
Listen,
This might be
a little awkward,
But I think we have more in
common than you might think.
Ned, we need
to have a talk
About a little thing called
"boundaries." ever heard of them?
What concert?
I did not put this
on my date book.
Do you see what's
happening here?
No more office visits,
no more bringing me presents,
And no more trying to get me
to go to this concert with you.
With me? I think
you have the wrong idea.
And what are you
even thinking?
With your spooky,
invasive magic tricks.
They're not
magic tricks.
The flying spirit board,
The flowers you left me?
I didn't do
any of that.
Then how did you find out
about my favorite band?
You're haunted.
My friends don't
think so, but...
I'm haunted?
What friends?
I think there's
a spirit.
The board awakened it,
And I'm sorry
for my role in that.
But I don't think it's
going to stop pestering you
Until you
acknowledge it.
You're nuts, and you need
to transfer out of my class.
But this is...
I'm asking you to leave.
>
You're nuts.
According to ned,
those were her exact words.
So she teaches
the paranormal,
But she doesn't
believe in it?
Hey, if I bought into every
psychological theory I teach,
I would have
murdered my parents.
Hey, how are they?
Honestly? Thriving.
I mean, for a couple
of dead people.
I think they're haunting
my aunt shirley in boca.
That's not exactly romantic.
You can't even
dance to it.
Well, maybe it was
something special
She shared
with her fiancé,
If he's even
the ghost.
The guy's sending her flowers
from the grave;
Setting up concert dates
with her.
Who else could it be?
Anybody,
Thanks
to the spirit board.
Ok, I get it,
you hate them.
Because they're like writing
your number on the bathroom wall
For the dead.
And maybe ned told avery
about the ghost too soon.
But he was doing it
trying to help us
Get into the copeland wing.
So we gotta help him.
That's her,
with the chair.
That's just academics.
Hey!
I resemble that remark.
No, I mean,
in this area.
Whether they believe it
or not,
They all think
they're experts.
And not only do I have
to convince them
That I can see ghosts,
But then they have to unlearn
everything they think they know.
hello?
I told you, I was
going to a concert.
Poor thing.
Whatever she said to ned,
she still came.
To meet her dead fiancé.
What faculty meeting?
With president bedford?
What wasn't it
on my calendar?
No, it wasn't.
All right,
I'm 10 minutes away. Oh!
Uh...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I used to have
one of these.
I hated mine, too, so.
There. You ok?
Better than
my phone.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I just...please.
It's fine.
Fine.
Set it up.
So you see ghosts
and you talk to them.
You're one of the friends
ned was talking about.
I know it's
a lot to process.
And you think that's why my cell
phone decided to take flight.
At the exact moment you were
thinking about leaving the concert,
Which a ghost went to a lot
of trouble to get you to.
What do you think
happened?
I tripped,
and it flew out of my hand.
Law of physics.
You don't teach physics.
Just because I teach
anthro of the occult
Does not mean I should buy
whatever it is you're selling.
I'm not selling
anything,
Especially to somebody
who doesn't want my help.
But you know what,
feel free to call me
When your ghost
comes back.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm listening.
Please, tell me
how this works.
First, we have to figure
out who the ghost is.
Logical place to start,
based on the behavior,
Someone who has romantic
feelings for you.
'cause all
the good ones
Are married,
gay or dead, right?
I should
have said "had."
Eli told me about
curtis, your fiancé.
Oh.
Well.
If you're just taking
shots in the dark,
You should be a little more careful
about throwing out names of loved ones.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
Nobody means to.
They just want me
to move on.
Register at some dating sight
and find another soul mate.
Well, I'm old-fashioned.
I think you get one.
I don't expect you
to understand.
I understand better
than you think.
Believe it or not, I think
this ghost is staying here
Because he thinks
you need him.
You have
to let him go.
But if curtis is here,
why would I let him go?
Because spirits
don't belong here.
They belong
in the light.
Who died and made you
the expert?
I know a few things
about ghosts myself,
Or did you forget that?
No.
No, I didn't.
Did I order this?
"the big lebowski."
At least someone
screwed up with taste.
Curtis?
What are you doing?
Popcorn?
Extra butter?
Curtis, if this is you,
You know I like
my popcorn plain.
I can't tell if this is
a seduction or a séance.
Ok.
Well, what's
that about?
You don't want
to watch the movie?
So what
do you want to do?
Talk?
You know how much
I hate texting,
But I'm game.
Curtis, I...
I've been talking
to you out loud
For the past 3 years.
And now, I'm about
5 cats away from crazy,
So if you can
talk to me,
I mean, really
talk back to me,
Now would be such
a good time.
Maybe that woman's right.
Maybe you do belong
in the light.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
I miss you so much.
Melinda: Don't touch,
I got it covered.
I'm...I'm just
trying to help.
Let me help.
Uh, no? Ok.
You know what,
I'm gonna go.
I'll clear aiden's stuff
out of the way.
No, no, he's in the middle
of a masterpiece.
Look, I already set
the dining room table.
Why don't you and aiden
go outside and play ball?
Right.
Ok. Turkey chili,
20 minutes.
We'll be there.
Hey! You know what,
If you want to talk
to me, just talk, ok?
No games.
Hey! Oh!
You know what?
That is just childish!
Why are you hiding?
No, no! Not my son's
art project!
Will you please stop?!
I just want to have a quiet
evening with my family!
You are ruining
everything!
Look, what I don't understand
is, how can you ruin everything
When you haven't
done anything yet?
Well, I told
dr. Grant and curtis
That they should
move on.
And you think
he has other plans?
Well, luring her
to the square
For a romantic concert,
Sending her flowers.
It's like he doesn't
want to let go.
And who am I
to say he should?
You know,
they're soul mates.
Hmm.
Like us.
oh!
Hospital.
Duty calls.
For both of us.
See ya.
Bye.
Avery, hi.
Is everything ok?
I think I owe you
another apology.
Something strange
happened last night.
I know
I should be happy
Instead of feeling
whatever it is I'm feeling,
But something about
the whole date night
Was just...Off.
And what was it?
I could really
feel him there,
And that was so amazing.
But... but he
wasn't really there.
Having him so close
but not being able
To really be with him...
I know it sounds ungrateful,
But...
It's just not enough.
It's torture.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe the only way
for both of us to heal
Is for curtis
to go into the light.
I can't believe
I'm saying that.
Hey, it doesn't mean that
you love him any less.
I know.
It's just that I have
a problem
With the whole...
Afterlife thing.
I mean,
before the accident,
I was kind of
a closet believer.
I mean, I always maintained
a very healthy,
Scientific skepticism
in public,
But I would go
in the copeland wing
And I would
read those books,
And they rang so true.
After curtis died, I waited and
waited for him to come back to me,
And...He never did.
So you're saying
that the hauntings
And feeling
his presence,
That just started
recently?
Maybe I shouldn't
question it.
Why would it
start now?
What's different?
Are things
worse for you?
Ever since you told me
that curtis was haunting me.
I mean, before that,
I could go the whole day
Or two without
thinking about him,
But now,
I'm more obsessed
with him than ever.
Curtis?
Curtis,
if that's you,
You don't really
have to use the board.
I can see you
and hear you,
So you could just talk...
Or we can
do it your way.
"curtis is..."
"gone."
that's the message
The ghost spelled out
on the spirit board.
If curtis is gone, then
who's controlling the board?
Maybe we have
the wrong ghost.
Wouldn't be
the first time.
That would explain
the message
I got on my new
board last night.
You got a new board?
It said,
"I'm not curtis,"
Which would
make sense if...
You bought yourself
another board?
Look, I know how you
guys feel about them,
But you don't understand
what it's like for me.
I'm not a sensitive,
And I just thought
if I could...
I don't know
what I was thinking.
You really don't, if you actually
wish you could hear what I hear.
But I guess it proves the ghost was
attached to grant and not the board.
Right.
Do you know anyone else
in her life who died recently?
Professor nettinger was her
mentor in the anthro department.
He died a few months ago.
But the guy was like 104,
So I'm guessing
he wasn't making
With the romance.
Wait, her grandmother.
How do you know that?
They were close.
And she died last spring.
And according to my friend,
Grandma was always
pushing avery
To get on
with her life
And date guys she'd only
kick to the curb.
Fits the profile
of the ghost.
I was thinking the ghost
couldn't be a guy.
How come?
Dude, the ghost
left a glitter note.
Ok.
My ghost consultants
now tell me
That I may be communicating
with you, nana.
Is that true?
Nana, you don't have
to use the board.
There's a lady in town
who talks to ghosts,
And, uh, she might be
my new best friend.
Or a complete whack job.
Possibly both.
I know you want me to go
out there and meet new guys.
How about this?
I promise to start
shaving my legs
And putting on lipstick
before I go to the market
If you promise
to go into the light.
But I can't promise
that I'll ever feel
What I felt for curtis.
Is this supposed to be
the silent treatment?
Ugh! Why isn't there
a star 69 on this thing?
Ugh! Ok, fine!
"the big lebowski," how did
this get back in the machine?
Clavus ferreus,
malleus ferreus,
Ferrum refilium,
ferrum nobilis.
My parents thought
my degree would be useless.
not so useless
now, huh, mom?
Actually...
I don't know.
Get this chucky doll
out of my life.
Professor grant,
Quince seed, sage,
spirit circles...
This stuff's
not going to help.
Well, your friend,
then, tell her,
Whatever potions she has,
Just to bring them on.
That's not
how it works.
This ghost wants to
reach you somehow.
Well, whoever's calling me,
My phone is off the hook
and I am not answering!
Hello?!
I was being
metaphorical!
What do you want from me?
It's the scratched disk.
I never returned it.
Maybe that's what
it wants you to do.
The ghost is trying to get
me to return an overdue dvd?
That makes no sense.
Not yet.
Not until we go to the store
and find out what else it wants.
I'm on my way
to the square right now.
Let me give you a lift,
And maybe we can put an end
to this thing once and for all.
There really should be
some kind of express line
For people
with haunted disks.
Got that right.
What does the ghost
expect me to find in here?
I already rented
every good movie,
Which is not a lot.
Look out!
Whoa. Are you ok?
Wait...
Uh-huh.
Wow.
Now, don't I know you?
I think so.
The concert
in the square.
You threw
your phone at me.
I didn't throw it at you,
It just kind of fell out
of my hands.
I can't explain it.
Well, I can explain it,
but never mind.
You're kidding me.
You're the one
who's late with this?
I've been waiting
for this.
You're here to rent
"the big lebowski"?
It's the best coen brothers movie ever.
Uh, best coen brothers comedy.
Aren't they all?
You may have a point.
Well, what are
the odds, huh?
Maybe not so bad.
No, not bad at all.
Excuse me.
All right.
surprise.
Hey, I was hoping
you guys would come by.
Oh, aiden twisted my arm.
I made this for you
at school.
It was really,
really hard.
Oh, it's really
beautiful.
You know what, I better put this away,
'cause somebody's
going to want to buy it.
What's that
doing here?
Ah, oh, it's another
one of ned's.
I made him leave it.
I thought those
were only for teenage girls
To scare themselves with
at slumber parties.
Uh, that, too, but
there's more than one thing
That can make
the pointer move.
Oh, really?
Other than the unconscious
muscle movements
Called ideomotor response?
You believe whatever you
want there, doctor man.
I used to,
but then I met this girl...
Aiden: Mom?
This board...
You know what,
baby, that's mommy's.
We're just gonna... we're
gonna put that away, ok?
It talks.
It talks?
What does it say?
It says,
It still won't
give her peace?
Give who peace?
Her.
All right, there you go.
Ok.
What, a girl with a
bloody head? How bloody?
She's a ghost.
But what does this have
to do with professor grant?
You know what,
Ned's out there, so let me
see if he knows something.
Right.
Oh, that's beautiful.
That's...that's funny.
This your doing?
No. It's the ghost,
whoever he is.
Oh, we got a problem.
You said you didn't really
get a chance to see it,
And, uh, I got...
Melinda:
You mean she.
Professor grant's grandmother?
She's here?
Not unless she had kids
at a very young age.
I don't know if you're going
to be able to watch it either,
'cause I think it's scratched. Oh, yeah?
I mean, maybe I could come
over and watch it, but...
That sounded so smarmy.
Um, there's something wrong
with my dvd player.
I was not inviting
myself.
Stop it, that was me.
I was angling inviting you
In my most smarmalicious
kind of way.
Really? 'cause it was
really awkward.
Why are you smiling
about it?
'cause I think you're just
as bad at this as I am.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
I need to get out
of the house more.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Ok, why do I keep feeling
like I've seen you before?
More than the concert
or the video store?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I know what it is.
The taj mahal.
Not the one in india.
Mini putt!
Mm-hmm.
I love that place.
The best mini golf
in the tri-state area.
Oh, the world!
You know, I know people go
there ironically and stuff,
But...It's beautiful
there at night, you know?
It's like this tiny,
perfect world
Where nothing bad
can ever happen.
Yeah.
It's not like here, huh?
No.
You want to go get
a coffee or something?
Ooh!
Why is there a tweenager
haunting avery?
And why'd she work so hard
to get those two together?
Nothing, nothing
was right at all.
And, you know,
we parted ways.
That's all.
But we still talk,
Sometimes.
Not so much.
Oh, god, how many rules
does that break,
Talking about my divorce
on the first date?
If that's even
what this is.
It is for me
if it is for you.
good.
Tell me a little bit
about you,
'cause honestly, I...
I can't believe
you're single.
Well...
The truth is, I don't really
consider myself single.
Mm-hmm. Why?
My fiancé died
in a car accident.
Oh, my god,
I'm so sorry.
A car accident?
Yeah, if it had been
a couple of weeks later,
We would
have been married
And I would officially be a widow,
Which maybe people
would understand better.
Mm-mmm. No, no,
they'd never understand.
Avery, the only people
that understand
Are people
that lived through it.
Did you?
My daughter.
Oh...
Also car accident,
3 years ago.
I was driving.
I'm so sorry.
You never get over
something like that, never.
Uh, the other guy was
wrong side of the road.
And this was
3 years ago?
And what road
was this?
Covington ridge.
Covington ridge road?
Mm-hmm.
That's the road
curtis was killed on.
It's those blind curves.
I mean, the other guy,
He was just...
he was killed instantly.
And, what was
his name? Um...
Henry c. Flood.
You said
your fiancé's name...
His middle name
was curtis.
Oh, god.
And you said...
January 12th, 8:28.
You were driving the car
that killed curtis.
And madison.
Who is doing this?!
What do you mean?
Who wants me
to feel this pain?
What do you mean? Avery?
Do you think this is
a coincidence?
I don't know. I...avery!
I'm sorry, I can't.
Avery, wait!
Eli: Pizza's here.
What do you want to drink?
Anything. I found it.
Thank god. I thought I was
really going to have to make good
On my offer
to help you inventory.
Ah, check it out,
I've ided our ghost.
Brian and his daughter
madison.
But it says they only
had minor injuries.
Ah, that's what
they thought at first.
But look at this piece
from 2 weeks later.
2 weeks after the accident
she got a headache
During a volleyball game.
By that night,
she was in a coma.
She died of an epidural
hematoma.
This is why we didn't come
up with her name before.
It's possible.
Not even avery knew.
Why would madison
haunt dr. Grant?
She wasn't driving
the car that killed her.
Hmm, first article, officials blame
texting and driving for the accident.
Curtis was answering a text
at the time of the crash.
What if it was a text
from dr. Grant?
Hmm, that would explain
why the ghost blames avery,
But not why the hauntings
just started recently.
Why good-bye?
Is somebody leaving?
Leaving how?
What does that mean?
Someone's going to die?
When? Does it mean that
somebody's going to die soon?
hello?
Avery, it's melinda.
Where are you?
I'm driving. What is it?
Where are you going?
I need to talk to curtis.
Avery, please
just listen to me...
Please just
leave me alone!
Where's my purse, and my keys?
But we don't know if the spirit
board meant it was dr. Grant
Who was going to die, or if
the ghost was threatening her.
Do you really want
to take that chance?
Of course not,
but how do we find her?
I don't know.
She said
she was in her car,
That she needed
to talk to curtis,
So where would she go
to talk to him?
Ah...
Wait a minute.
His obit said
he was cremated.
No service to bury
his ashes or anything.
Ok, so what else would be
a meaningful place for them?
I don't know, her website
listed dozens of places
They liked to go together.
Maybe she went to
the crash site
At covington ridge road.
I called 9-1-1!
Help is on the way!
Ok.
avery...
Brian!
Avery, it's you!
What are you
doing here?
Oh, god.
I was driving,
I saw dust and smoke.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
No, I don't think so.
You sure?
Yeah.
Ok. Ok.
Ok. You sure
nothing hurts?
No. I think I'm more
rattled than anything else.
Ok.
Come on. Ok.
All right, now,
I want you to move everything
Just to see
if anything's broken.
Ah, I'm fine.
Thank you.
You're all right.
It's ok.
Why were you
driving on that road?
What do you mean?
Were you...
following you?
No, avery.
This can't be
another coincidence.
It's not.
It's where
the accident happened.
I come here all the time.
Why?
Avery! Brian!
Is everything ok?
Yes. I think so.
Where did you get that?
From your shrine
for curtis up the road.
Why did you do this?
I didn't mean
for her to get hurt.
I believe you.
What?
is madison here?
It's gonna be
all right.
Ok.
Madison?
Nobody
is mad at you.
You don't have
to hide.
Sweet...sweetheart?
It's daddy.
We just want
to talk with you.
She's here.
You did this to bring
them together, didn't you?
I didn't. Fate did.
Fate?
You mean your accident?
No, I mean, like,
practically every day since.
I don't understand.
Ever since he started coming
to talk to me on that road,
I noticed
she'd go there, too.
She'd come the anniversary
of the crash,
And he'd come the
anniversary of when I died.
So they missed each other.
But I followed her,
and I started noticing
That she likes all the
same stuff you like, daddy.
And not just weird groups
and mini golf,
But you both hate
snow skiing
And people who take up
2 parking spaces,
And people who say
"supposebly."
She followed you.
You both have a lot in
common, and not just music
And movies
and mini golf.
But you both don't
like snow skiing
And people who take
up 2 parking spaces
And people who use
the word "supposebly."
Supposebly is not a word.
No. And people who take
2 parking spaces...
Should be beaten.
Plus, even the accident,
It only happened
because dad and her fiancé
Happened to be buying tickets
to the same bizarre concert.
The accident was
just a part of it.
You and curtis, you were headed to
buy tickets for the same concert.
Broken social scene.
It's my second
favorite group.
Honey...
Um, having a few things
in common with someone
Doesn't necessarily mean
the two of them
Should end up together.
Madison: I never said
they should end up together.
Just talk.
She just wants you
to talk.
You don't think I talk?
Till today, not hardly.
Not really.
Until today.
Because avery,
she understands.
That's the real thing
you have in common...
Me, her fiancé,
The wreck,
and how that feels.
Is that why you started haunting avery?
Because something reminded
you of the accident?
No. Daddy
was feeling so sad,
Like a new place
would help.
He was going to move.
And you were thinking
about moving?
Yeah. Yeah, she's right.
I mean, I was looking.
You were?
Yeah.
Then they'd lose
their chance.
I couldn't say good-bye
Till I made it
mean something.
What mean something?
Me being gone.
What?
She wanted her death
to mean something.
That's what
all this is for.
Sweetheart?
Oh, god, madison.
No.
Your life meant
so much to me.
It would mean
even more if you try.
Promise, daddy.
Just try.
She needs you to promise
that you're gonna try.
Oh. I...honey,
I don't know.
I can.
I can try.
Really?
I mean, you sure?
Mm-hmm.
Ok. I'll try.
Can you tell him
never to wear
The cologne
that mom gave him?
He thinks it makes him
irresistible. It doesn't.
Yeah,
I'll tell him that.
Sweetheart?
I'm going to miss you...
Every single day of my life.
And I love you so much.
I love you, too.
She's gone.
I mean, does our son
just imagine
That little elves
come out at night
And clean up
his toys for him?
I don't...no.
He probably imagines
that we come out and do it.
I really wish someone
would clean up my toys.
Sorry. I keep
taking these from ned.
What's wrong?
Nobody died.
That's a bad thing?
Well, no, it's just
that the board
Said that somebody was going
to die, and they didn't.
Good.
The board was wrong.
You're right.
No.
Does that mean that
somebody is going to die?
Is it someone we know?
>