Sure, I can cover your patient, too,
But, um, there she is.
Hey. Hi.
Look, first thing, I love you.
Well, that's good.
But this is going to be the third
time this week that I do this.
No! I know, I'm sorry.
But half the staff's got the flu,
Half's got some sort of respiratory virus.
I just can't get out of here.
Not even for lunch?
We can go to the cafeteria.
But I gotta work a double.
Is this even safe?
I mean, I don't understand
The medical profession,
and I feel like doctors
And truck drivers-- truck drivers?
And pilots, you know,
they should get the most sleep,
You know, not the least.
Well, we got vegetarian lasagna today, ehhh.
Help.
Somebody help me.
Hey, what's the problem?
Sir, did something happen to you?
He had a knife.
Why aren't you listening to me?
Lock the door. Lock the door.
Just lock the door.
Call the police.
You should definitely do that.
Sir, we need to examine you.
Yeah, let's do that right now.
Ok, why don't we examine you.
Just sit down. Help me get him to a chair.
He had a knife. He had a knife. Whoa!
He won't stop slashing!
He just kept slashing!
Let go of her. He won't stop slashing!
He just kept slashing.
Can we get security down here?
His eyes, his eyes!
Are you gonna be all right?
It's going to be fine, sir. Calm down.
Where is security? And the blood!
And the blood, you have to stop him!
There was an officer in peed's
talking with a social worker.
Call over there.
Just get someone who is armed.
Won't do any good.
They can't stop it.
Stop it? Do you know what happened to him?
They can't save him no matter what they do.
He's a dead man.
Child, whispering: Can you see us?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Hey. Why aren't you listening to me?!
Please, someone just listen to me!
How is he? I don't know.
The er doctor took over.
They want to sedate him,
but they say he's got to talk to police.
Ok, well, you should talk to him first,
Or get me in there.
Wait, did you see something?
Something and someone. I had a vision.
I saw someone with a knife.
Just like he said.
Except it was a woman.
She was screaming and bleeding.
Do you think someone else was attacked?
Did he say anything about a woman?
No, but, I mean, he's in shock.
Oh, boy. Right this way, officers.
He said someone is after him.
The patient's this way.
Did you see the person holding the knife?
I think it was a man.
Do you think you could describe
The woman in the vision to the police?
Dirty blond hair,
an intense cut on her forearm.
I don't even know if she's still alive.
All right, that's the something you saw.
What about the someone? Ghost.
In his thirties.
It was kind of hard to make out.
But he wasn't cut, he wasn't bleeding,
He just looked awful.
What is he, a third victim?
Or the attacker.
Maybe someone that the guy--
Robert, his name's robert.
Ok, maybe somebody that
robert killed in a struggle.
Wait, he didn't even know it?
I mean, like, he was being
chased and didn't know?
All I know is that the ghost said
there's nothing anyone could do.
And that your patient
robert is going to die.
Is he?
I don't know. It's tough to tell.
With a knife wound,
Sometimes you gotta open
them up and see the damage.
Ok, well, you need to get to him
before he gets into surgery.
That woman could still be out there.
Yeah, and she might still
be alive, right? Ok.
So he's stable. I'll notify the e.R.
Good. I'll be back, dr. Myers.
Hey, wesley.
What's going on in there?
Dr. Meyers is just finishing up the exam.
He's gonna be fine.
They're not going to open him up?
No, we checked him out.
He's got lots of abrasions
And some moderate lacerations.
Nothing that looks like a knife wound.
What about all that blood he came in with?
Well, like I said, he's pretty banged up.
Anybody know why?
He keeps talking about
some guy with a knife.
Maybe he got knocked around
pretty good trying to get away.
I really need to talk to him.
Those cops are waiting to
talk to him, too, you know.
Yeah.
I need to talk to him first,
So could you hold them
off for about 5 minutes?
You got it. Thanks.
Hey, mr. Wharton, how are you doing?
Who are you?
I'm a doctor. Well, actually I'm the guy
Who threw you in the wheelchair
when you first came in here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just, I'm so tired.
It's probably the adrenaline.
You know, it spikes
And then your body crashes.
They said there's nothing wrong with me.
No, not too much. Nothing serious.
Look, this attack you've
been talking about...
Was there anyone else who got hurt?
Anyone else?
Someone who was with you.
You know, a woman, maybe?
Ah, I don't know.
All right.
Mr. Wharton?
Do you mind if I call you robert?
Look, robert,
Someone saw a woman being
attacked with a knife.
Where?
Well, that's what I was
hoping you could tell me.
You came in here,
you haven't been cut by a knife,
But it turns out this woman was.
It wasn't a dream.
Wait, you know what I'm talking about?
This actually happened?
Robert... Who was she?
Who was she?
Can you tell me anything about this attack?
Look, where did it happen? Were you inside?
Were you outside, were you in a building?
Tell me any sounds you heard, anything.
The night was just so dark.
I just wanted to shut my eyes.
I thought, please,
could I just shut my eyes?
Hey, man, it's the middle of the afternoon.
This went on all night?
I don't know.
Who did this to you?
What the hell happened to you?
Robert, where were you before you came here?
Where am I now?
You're in the rockland memorial hospital.
Who are you?
My name's jim, I'm a doctor.
You don't remember coming here, do you?
I wake up in places,
And I can't remember how I got there.
Was I sleeping?
Just now, was I sleeping?
No, it's like you're blacking out.
Yeah.
I guess so.
I think so.
Robert, I'm going to ask you a
very important question, all right?
You came in here covered with blood.
Was that blood yours?
I don't know.
Robert, tell me. Did you hurt somebody?
Somebody you knew, anybody?
A woman? Did you?
No, no, I wouldn't. I couldn't.
I hope not.
Am I awake?
I mean, is this place real?
Are you real?
You see?
It's in him now.
It's in him now?
What does that mean?
Melinda wasn't exactly sure,
And the ghost didn't
stick around to explain.
Where is she?
She's giving eli the local ghost update.
What do I do?
I want you to find out everything
you can about robert wharton.
You mean, about people he knows who died.
Yeah, but especially the one we hope didn't.
The woman that she saw getting cut.
Yeah. So look at his friends, ok?
But don't rule anybody out.
And see if anybody's gone
missing in grandview.
If not, nearby towns, ok? I'm on it.
Thanks, man.
Hey, so is detective blair.
She must have gotten melinda's message.
All right, you hear anything, call me.
Ok.
Thanks, man. Take it easy.
So you're sure that this is the man you saw?
Yeah. That's the guy
I saw sleeping on the bench.
And you didn't see anyone with him,
Near him, menacing him?
No. But as he was curling up to go to sleep,
I noticed he might be hurt.
So I asked him if he was ok,
And he looked at me like totally lost.
And I pointed out the blood.
That's when he ran away.
When he realized you saw the blood.
Yeah.
Excuse me. Sorry, detective blair.
But I was here when the guy
You're talking about was brought in,
And he told us he was being chased.
Yeah, by someone with a knife.
I didn't see anyone.
And I'm telling you, the person
he was running from was me.
And then what happened?
I followed him. I lost him
For a few minutes, but then I saw him
Ducking into the hospital, and...
Here I am.
This guy walks into a hospital
Screaming he's been attacked
When he's the attacker?
It's a possibility, that's all I'm saying.
I've heard about throwing
suspicion onto someone else,
But come on, be smart.
Only do it after the police are onto you.
Or this guy robert could have had
some kind of psychotic break.
Yeah, and really believes
everything he's saying.
I really don't think he
has any idea what he did.
And, you know, we have no
idea what he's capable of.
All right, well, can you check his records?
Find out if he's under psychiatric care?
Maybe he went off his meds.
He had nothing on him. No wallet, nothing.
Only information we have is
his name and his blood type.
And the blood that was on his shirt,
they're testing it,
So if there was a second type...
Then he might have hurt someone else.
The woman you saw. Or the ghost, right?
I mean, there is one dead
person in this scenario?
The ghost said you can't save him.
Maybe he meant robert
should fry for what he did.
But even if he killed both of them,
that's unlikely.
So...Look, I'm not sure.
But I don't think this
guy meant to hurt anyone.
I mean, he seems like he wants to help.
Good.
'cause I want to talk to him.
We sent officers over to
robert's place of employment
And his apartment.
He was fired weeks ago. What happened?
Well, over the course
of the last few months,
He became erratic and aggressive.
Then he just stopped showing up for work.
That'll get you canned.
Did you find anything in his apartment?
Yeah, I mean, did anyone
see him with a woman?
A woman who he might have hurt?
The neighbor said he had a
girlfriend, helen reeman.
They lived separately,
but she stayed nights with him.
She was him all the time.
But no one has seen her in over a week,
Including the people at her job.
Yeah.
I don't understand.
If I'm not hurt, why am I still here?
Yeah, well, we think you're still at risk.
You said you've been blacking out, right?
I guess, but I don't--
Can't remember.
We're just going to run some
tests and see if there's
A medical reason for it. Or...Anything else.
like I'm crazy?
I mean, it's what you're thinking, isn't it?
Do you think you are? Could that explain
Some of the things you've done?
What have I done?
Who are you?
Hi.
Um, robert, this is my wife, melinda.
Sometimes she does special counseling
For certain patients.
I don't know what's happening to me.
Detective blair: What's happening
is your girlfriend is missing.
Helen reeman.
Do you know who we're talking about?
Helen? Yeah.
Of course.
You came in here talking
about a man with a knife.
The doctors think you may be delusional,
But I just think you might be confused.
And the man with the knife was you.
That sound right?
Oh, my god.
Helen.
In my dream, I saw a knife,
And it was slashing at someone.
There was blood.
I heard a woman screaming,
Saying, "stop!
Please stop, I'm begging you."
Then she said she loved me.
She was bleeding.
Then it was just so quiet.
Next thing I knew, I woke up
and I was covered in blood.
He killed his girlfriend,
and he doesn't remember it?
He must be out of his mind.
Yeah. Or out of his body.
Aiden! Hey.
Here's your snack. How was school today?
Good.
Is there anything you want
to tell me about today?
Maybe just one thing? Hmm, nothing.
Can I eat next to my game? I'm playing.
Sure.
Andrew wong got a crayon stuck in his nose.
Ooh. Is he ok?
Yeah, he's fine. It was purple.
Well, there you go.
Honey, it sounds like
you got your hands full.
The ghost, the murderer.
The missing girlfriend we
still haven't found yet.
And the demonic twin.
Tell her about that one.
Yeah, he's not a twin.
It was a vision, and it was that guy robert.
The patient and maybe murderer?
Yeah. He was holding a knife
And had this very hollow expression.
And goat's eyes. You know how goats
Have the slit pupils that go sideways?
Mm-hmm. They're satanic.
Ah! How did satan get brought
up in this conversation?
The ghost said it's in him now, right?
Maybe what's in our patient
Isn't some kind of psychosis.
Yeah, or maybe he was just in shock,
Or had some kind of brain tumor.
I mean, the delusional state
that he shared with me...
Or he's sick with something worse.
Something evil.
I don't buy it.
'cause you don't believe
evil exists on its own.
How do you explain the shadows?
The bad parts
Of people left over when
they go into the light.
Aiden's seen it. Ok, ned.
Stop. I know this is what you're into,
And I know you're studying the occult
because you're trying to help people--
I'm studying it because
I find it fascinating.
Because both of you
Showed me there's more in this
world than what you can see.
Why can't you trust what you saw?
Because ghosts are unreliable.
Look, I don't even know who this ghost is.
Let's just start there. Ok, who's the ghost
And how is it related to robert?
Ok, fine.
Robert isn't married.
He has no children, and his mother is dead.
What about his father?
61, and alive.
His name's rudy, and he works downtown.
Maybe he knows your ghost. Yeah, thanks.
Where is it? Oh.
Hello?
There's a jane doe in the morgue,
And she's got lacerations on her arm.
Maybe robert should identify her.
It was his girlfriend.
I think he's just trying to help.
They can't let him, it's police
procedure, he's a suspect.
Besides, he's just dehydrated
and confused, exhausted.
I can't believe he hasn't passed out yet.
I can't believe I haven't, either.
Yeah, what shift are you on?
I can't remember.
Why isn't robert passed out?
That's a good question.
Every time he tries to fall asleep,
or he's about to,
He gets agitated.
He goes in and out of being
confused, being himself.
It's strange.
So she either jumped off a
bridge or she was pushed.
So if she died from a fall,
Then why did the ghost
show me a knife wound?
Maybe robert went after her
with a knife before he...
Can I see her face?
It wouldn't help. She's unrecognizable.
Any of these wounds look familiar?
I saw one cut, but not
enough to identify her.
See anything else? Any visions?
No.
Her hair looks similar.
Lighter, maybe.
What's weird is if robert killed her,
Then where's her ghost?
I don't know.
Maybe she forgave him and crossed over
Because he wasn't himself.
A few months ago, this guy
had a girlfriend and a job.
And then he just loses his mind,
Starts blacking out and he kills her?
She wouldn't go out like that.
She'd be worried about people.
Maybe even robert. Yeah.
Hey, I'll be out in a second.
You can see me.
Who are you?
He's not dangerous.
Robert? Are you his girlfriend?
He wanted to be with her forever.
He didn't want to hurt her.
Hurt her?
Is that you in there?
Or are you just someone else
that he hurt and didn't mean to?
I'm still tired. Isn't that strange?
Other spirits say they can't feel anything,
But they're wrong.
'cause I can see how sad or lonely they are.
And they still love just as much.
I want to help you.
Really, I do.
114.
114, don't go in 114.
Is that an address?
Is that where you died?
You know, just talk to me.
Do you know robert?
Can you stop him from hurting anyone else?
He won't hurt anyone else.
He's going to die.
There's nothing anyone can do about it.
Wait, another spirit said
exactly that same thing. A man.
Do you know him?
You can see me.
He's not dangerous.
He wanted to be with her forever.
He didn't mean to hurt her.
Right.
114.
1...14.
How do you know that ghost even
Knows our ghost? Or our guy?
I don't even know if our
ghost knows our guy,
Much less that ghost.
Is it me, or does it sound like
We're rapping about a bunch of nut bags?
All these people,
And when I say "people,
" I'm including the dead,
Sound totally whackadoodle.
Yeah, I've dealt with crazy ghosts before,
But this one's different.
What makes you so sure?
It all happened so suddenly with robert.
The living nut. Right. A few weeks ago,
He was totally normal.
And then all of a sudden,
he becomes violently insane.
Define "normal."
I mean, you said yourself,
The ghost's girlfriend was totally nutty.
I never said it was his girlfriend.
Hey, guys. Hey.
What's going on?
Well, robert's being scheduled for an mri,
And we're going to check for
any kind of brain abnormality.
Till then, he's being
transferred to the psych ward.
I can keep an eye on him there.
Or you could talk to his father.
That was my next step. He's here.
He's signing commitment forms.
And, uh, he's not alone.
I was so worried about him.
That's robert's father,
And robert's girlfriend helen reeman.
Are you sure? Yeah. I met her.
They came in together.
They're both pretty broken up.
Was she injured?
No. She said he wasn't violent.
She said he was agitated,
But then he just shut himself off.
She swears he never hurt her.
So why couldn't we find her?
Where has she been?
Ah, looking for robert.
You know, he stopped returning phone calls,
and then about a week ago,
He's gone.
They had met in providence,
So that's where she was.
She was checking out old haunts,
Talking to his friends.
While he and his devil buddy
were roaming grandview
Getting bloody.
Look, I'm glad that she's alive,
But...
Is she's not the knife victim, then who is?
You know what, I don't think there was one.
The bloodwork came back on his clothes,
And there was only one type on it--his.
And there was this witness,
the skateboarder kid.
He said he saw a guy completely disoriented
Falling down, totally agitated.
Which would account for the blood,
But what about the woman?
And why was he running in the first place?
If he's in that state,
could he maybe see a ghost?
Well, let's not forget mrs.
Loopy down in the morgue.
Why are they both predicting his doom?
My guess is that mri's
Going to come back with a big,
honking death sentence.
Are the results in? Could it be a tumor?
He hasn't even been scanned yet.
You talked to his dad.
Is there any history of
mental illness in his family?
It's a dead end. Robert was adopted.
Nobody knows anything
about his birth parents.
So much for getting the
skinny from his family.
I'm not so sure about that.
The ghost said that we couldn't save him.
Maybe it wasn't a threat.
Maybe he was worried about him.
You're his father, aren't you?
Yes.
I wasn't there for him.
He needs me now.
You said the ghost was close to the guy?
Their foreheads were touching.
And jim said that the patient
had the same nightmare,
Of someone slashing a woman with a knife.
That sounds about right.
It sounds about right for what?
They call it threading.
I found 3 different references
to it in the library.
Why is it called threading?
It's when a ghost weaves images or visions
Into the mind of a civilian.
A civilian?
Someone who's not a sensitive,
like you or aiden.
It's supposed to be easier
with physical proximity.
How easy?
Well, you don't have to suppress
a person's consciousness,
Like with possession,
But it does take lots of energy;
The kind of energy you
need major motion to get--
Hate, anger, love.
Or guilt.
Well, that depends. How much guilt?
Well, in my vision, it was from
the point of view of the slasher.
If I had slashed someone,
I'd feel pretty guilty.
Then again, I'm not a slasher.
Maybe the ghost wasn't, either.
Which begs the question--
Why did he say, "he needs me."
Why would he need his son
to see him slashing someone?
And who was he slashing? I don't know.
It wasn't robert's girlfriend.
I don't think it was
The ghost I saw outside the morgue.
Why?
'cause she wasn't cut or bloody.
And you know what,
it was something else she said.
She said, "he didn't mean to hurt her,"
Not, "he didn't mean to hurt me."
Then who's the victim? Yeah.
Who's the woman outside the morgue?
Why are so many of them crazy?
No, I don't mind you asking at all.
Frankly, I wish the hospital
had sent someone sooner.
I know they're busy, but, you know.
God forbid you have an issue that doesn't
fit into one of their neat little boxes.
Like robert?
Yeah.
Here.
Have a seat.
Although, to be honest,
I'm probably more mad at myself.
For what? Well, I never asked
The tough questions until my son started...
Till things went so wrong with him.
Do you mind describing what happened to him?
Well, first it was simple insomnia.
It started a few months ago.
He couldn't sleep.
Nothing would help.
You know, exercise, pills, warm milk.
Nothing.
And then the nightmares started.
I heard it in his voice.
We'd talk all the time.
He was different.
And it affected his work.
Pretty soon, he lost his job.
He started to wander off,
disappearing from home.
Like he did when he
showed up at the hospital.
Helen, his girlfriend, she left her own job
To try and help, but it was no use.
The longer he went without sleep,
The worse it got.
You said you didn't ask the tough questions.
What questions were those?
I don't know if you have your own kids,
Biologically, I mean.
None that I know of.
Anyway, I have to imagine
It's different when you have your own.
You never worry someone will
come along and lay claim to him.
Was the adoption problematic?
No, I don't mean, you know, literal claim.
I mean, what if your child
Decides he wants to connect
with his own people?
And, you know, what if he discovers
He has more in common
with them than with you?
You were afraid of losing him.
So when we adopted,
They asked if we wanted to know
Robert's family's circumstances.
And I said, no, no, I didn't want to know.
That all changed when he got sick.
Of course, and I had to know.
I wish I'd known sooner.
Known what?
Robert's parents didn't
choose to give him up.
It wasn't up to them.
He was a ward of the state.
Was this, by any chance, because
robert's father had killed his mother?
How did you know that?
It's hard to explain, but I promise I will.
Do you have any paperwork I can see?
I understand that there are privacy issues,
But I was hoping you'd still
want to help the family.
You're forgetting that I'm retired now.
Especially considering
the gaps in your report.
What gaps?
Robert's adopted father is how I found you.
You were the social worker on the case.
Yeah.
Well, you left his birth
father's cause of death blank.
But then you said it was
listed in appendix d,
But there is no appendix d.
So maybe it fell out of the file.
That's when I realized that the
pages prove that nothing's missing.
See, appendix c is on page 13
And appendix e is on page 14,
Meaning that there was never an appendix d.
Was there?
What do you want?
I want to know what's
missing from the report.
What do you know so far?
His birth mother, marlene,
She died of uncontrolled bleeding
Due to cuts on her forearms. And his father,
Vernon, he was found on
the floor of a motel room
Babbling incoherently.
Yes, he blamed himself
One minute, he blamed his wife the next.
He also blamed demons.
Yeah, there was talk about demons.
And then he died in a psychiatric
ward not much after that.
Ok, you say you worked with the hospital.
Is robert sick? Yes.
Why?
Is he suffering from insomnia,
by any chance?
What else is missing from that report?
No one would have adopted that boy
If they knew the truth.
The truth?
That his father killed his mother.
That he was insane.
Because psychosis is genetic.
Because at the time,
it seemed like the worst thing
You could pass on to a child.
At the time? Was there something else?
The doctors didn't even know
that the disease existed,
Not until there was another death
in the family like vernon's.
A woman, robert's sister.
Extremely rare.
It's called fatal familial insomnia.
And if a parent has it,
You have a 50% chance of inheriting it.
So how is it treated?
It's not. There's no cure.
The body can't live without rest.
Yeah, for a few weeks,
Months at the most.
After that, psychosis sets in.
Organ failure.
And death.
It says in the obit lane dokes died
Of an undisclosed illness.
Yep.
That's robert's sister.
It's the ghost I saw outside the morgue.
She was 24.
Her father died in his early thirties.
Kids got split up after that.
She went into foster care
and robert got luckier.
Yeah, if you call that luck.
Coming down with a fatal
disease that I wouldn't wish
On my worst ex-girlfriend.
When she said he didn't mean to hurt her,
She was talking about the father.
When she said he wasn't dangerous...
She meant her brother.
Yeah. Obviously, she's still very confused.
That's what happens when
most of what you remember
From your final days is hallucinatory.
Poor dead looney tune.
Yeah, I have to tell robert.
Tell him what? "hey, good news,
"you probably didn't kill anyone.
"bad news is visions that
made you think you did,
"are little home movies of dad killing mom.
"oh, and by the way,
he and your sister went bonko
And died of a fatal disease
that you inherited."
I gotta call you back.
Wake up quick, before it's too late.
Hey, hey, hey, whoa.
Are you ok?
Depends on which melinda you're asking.
Sorry?
I'll explain later. What's going on?
Robert's gone.
Gone-gone?
Yeah, they searched the hospital.
He's nowhere.
He's disappeared.
His name is robert wharton.
I'm his girlfriend, can't you find him?
Thanks.
I just needed some air.
We're sorry to add to your worries.
There's no cure? You're sure?
There's no cure?
That's what we've been told.
And you think his father is haunting him?
Why?
Maybe to warn him. We're not sure.
What's awful is this is the
first thing I've heard in weeks
That actually makes sense.
When you get used to your
boyfriend's boss calling,
Asking if he's drinking for breakfast.
Do you mind telling us what happened
Before he disappeared?
You mean after he lost his job?
He started calling all times,
Day and night,
Asking strange, bizarre questions.
Sometimes he'd accuse me of things.
He sounded paranoid?
At first I thought it was
a bad case of cold feet.
Cold feet?
We'd just recently talked
about getting married,
Maybe even having kids.
Did he ever tell you about
dreams he may have had?
Hallucinations?
Yes.
A lot.
The second he would close his eyes,
Or sometimes even when
his eyes were still open,
He would see these creatures.
Uh, I don't remember what he called them.
Demons?
That's right. Demons.
Do you know what that means?
Vernon, his birth father,
said that he saw demons, too.
I thought they were all just delusions.
Are you telling me that they weren't?
Hey. Hey.
Did you find anything?
Yeah, robert's brain scans just came back,
And, um, they don't show any physical damage
Or abnormalities that would
explain the symptoms.
So he has it. It's in his blood.
How else would you explain the insomnia?
Look...
How long does he have?
Wait a minute, wait a minute, helen.
This doesn't mean that he has ffi.
We don't know that yet.
There are tests that can
better determine that.
But even if he has the disease,
There are remedies for
these kinds of things.
I mean, treatments.
Obscure stuff that no one knows about
Because the disease itself is so rare.
Look, there's always hope.
Excuse me.
You're making a bad mistake.
You need to leave him alone.
Your son is sick.
Those doctors will make him worse.
How?
They're gonna try to make him sleep.
He needs sleep. He's gonna die without it.
No. Sleep is what they need.
Who, the doctors or the demons?
Look, in my vision it said
That I had to wake up
before it was too late.
Is that because that's when the demons come?
They come when your guard is down.
They wake up when you go to sleep.
No, no!
Stop!
Uhh!
114.
That's the motel room where she died.
What were you doing there?
I wasn't myself.
Do you understand? That wasn't me.
Of course not. It was a sickness.
No. It was them.
They got inside me.
The demons?
My son needs me before he goes to sleep
And before they get him, too.
Forget your keys?
robert.
You scared me.
Why are you hiding like that?
You must be exhausted, too, huh?
So tired of this.
I was--I was so worried.
Why did you run away from the hospital?
I'm afraid.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
But you have to--
I'm afraid of myself, all right?
What do you mean?
I can't control it anymore.
What?
The things in my head.
Robert, there's something I
need to explain to you, ok?
Sit down.
So I am going crazy?
Because this thing?
But the doctors think
there might be treatments.
Which is why you have to
go back to the hospital.
No.
I don't like it there.
I don't...
Robert, please.
No, no. I don't want to hurt you.
I don't want to hurt you.
You won't. I know you.
Listen, I just--
I've got tea boiling and
I've got to grab my purse.
Just come inside. No, no.
I can't. I'm--I'm scared to
be alone with you in there.
Ok, then just wait.
Wait here.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You can end it, robert.
Just one step, take it, take it.
Hey.
I just talked to detective blair.
There's no sign of him.
So how long can he live without sleep?
Well, he may not have to find out.
What do you mean?
I did a little extra research.
It turns out that the root cause of ffi
Is a thing called a prion
protein in the brain.
It's related to mad cow.
But we checked robert's blood samples.
And it's not there?
Well, the test isn't conclusive,
But I'm starting to think this
guy does not have this disease.
Which of course raises the question,
Why the hell's he staying up all night?
I think our answer's right in front of us.
Well, in case it isn't,
I'm gonna keep checking
with our staff neurologist.
Oh, have you seen robert?
No, why? God. Where is he?
No, no, no. What happened?
I told him the truth about his disease.
No.
He promised me he would
come back and get help,
Then he disappeared.
If you know where your son is,
you have to tell us.
Even if you found him,
you couldn't help him.
What do you mean?
Think of his options.
Insanity and then death.
Or just death.
Is that what you chose?
You went to that motel
To cage your own demon, didn't you?
I don't understand.
I had a vision with demons,
But they were me.
Just like the demon that
was in robert's room,
It was a version of robert,
And you saw that, too.
You knew that something
wanted to hurt your family
And that's why you locked yourself away.
But you wanted to make sure
That it would never
threaten your family again.
And that's why you took the knife.
114.
You said not to go there,
But that's because you never stopped wishing
That your mother had stayed away.
How did she know where he went?
I remember her dialing...
And dialing.
She called all of our friends.
All of his family.
She called hospitals. She called the police.
I have to find...
And then she called the bank.
I tried the hospital.
And they told her
That was the last place
he used the credit card.
That's how she found you.
It's very hard to remember.
In my vision I saw you swing
That knife up and away from her, like you--
I didn't want her to take it.
I left the door unlocked and she came
And she saw me. Stop, please.
She knew what I was doing there.
give me the knife.
I need you to go!
Please.
She saw the knife
And she tried to take it,
And I didn't want her to take it.
I was just trying to keep
it from her, that's all.
Don't. No.
Stop.
Ahh!
Aah!
Oh!
I didn't know that I'd cut her,
I just wanted her out
So I could finish what I started.
And then I shoved her out the door.
After that, I'm not sure what happened.
She was crying.
And I wouldn't open the door.
I'd hoped that she'd gotten away from me.
Then she was finally safe, and with me gone,
We'd both have some peace.
I'd hoped that she was safe.
He didn't mean to hurt her.
No, of course he didn't.
You're right about that.
But what I don't get
Is if robert isn't sick,
Why did you suddenly start haunting him?
Because he wasn't sick yet.
He was talking about having children.
You heard him. And you thought--
He was worried our kids would inherit it.
And you wanted to make sure
that would never happen again.
Where's you son?
He doesn't have to die.
Robert, wait.
Please wait.
Stay away from me. Both of you.
You don't have to do this.
I don't want to. I don't, but...
What if I told you that
you're probably not sick?
I have to be.
Why else can't I sleep?
Because someone won't let you.
Someone?
Someone who loves you.
Someone who's been very
confused for a very long time.
Look, you thought that you
could keep your son awake
By threading images into his thoughts
That would keep the demons from
getting him like they got you,
But you're wrong.
And they never got you while you were asleep
Because you never slept.
No, I remember. I...
I'd wake up. I would have done things.
You may have had blackouts,
But you never slept.
You couldn't have. You had a disease.
Is my father here?
Yes.
And your sister.
Robert, please come off the ledge.
Please come back to me.
But the plans we made.
Even if I'm not sick, what about our kids?
This thing is still in my blood.
Don't you know,
One of the reasons I fell in love with you
Was hearing you talk about your family.
How thankful you were for having parents
Who wanted you so badly.
They didn't know what I was.
And I do.
And I...Love you.
Robert, I want what your parents wanted.
I want a family. And I want it with you.
Please.
Well, they're gonna keep
him under observation
For about 24 more hours.
And that's just to be sure.
Well, something tells me he's gonna be ok.
You two can do now if you're ready.
Say good-bye to him for us.
Mom's waiting for us.
They're gone.
That is beautiful.
What, all that love?
No, all that sleep.
you poor thing.
When's your shift over?
It should be over about now,
But I can't seem to read my watch.
You know what?
I'm busting you out of here.
Oh.
Delia said that aiden was an angel.
He only went downstairs
11 times after lights out.
And hopefully it'll get easier for you to...
Sleep.