Previously on Californication...
I'd like to introduce you
to Richard Bates, the writer.
- Big fan.
- Who wants to see me tuck
and do the pee pee dance?
We're really gonna do this,
sell the place?
- Isn't that what we want?
- Sure. I guess.
I just want to be done with it.
I want to sell this fucking house
and get on with the rest of my life.
You're saying just pack up
and leave L.A.?
the three of us
move back to New York?
Yeah, end of the semester, whatever.
So which one are you sleeping with?
- Excuse me?
- My bets are on the young,
voluptuous student.
This is so not fair.
I'm in love with you, Hank Moody.
I've never stepped
outside of my marriage before.
Please, go.
Something must be different.
That's right. You fucked my wife.
- There's that.
- What does that mean?
- You didn't tell her?
- What?
Becca's father and I
had a slight indiscretion.
She's got to be kidding me, right?
I don't want to hear about
Felicia and her midlife crisis.
- Wait, who else has he been fucking?
- You're a goddamn girl whisperer.
I can't believe
you slept with all of them.
- Will you live?
- I'm trying.
That's all anybody can ask for.
Check this out.
Lordy bagordy, we made
some fucking love, woman.
They should put us
in the joy of sex...
a nice little pencil sketch
of us doing it.
We're that good.
Who are you right now?
I'm not sensing
the same level of enthusiasm.
I... It was good.
Come to think of it, you weren't
quite as vocal as you normally are.
I mean, you've never been
a screamer per se,
but I can always count on you
for a little intense moaning.
Hank, stop it.
Thank you.
Thank you for that.
A woman does love a reenactment
of the most vulnerable moment.
But you got there, right?
Close.
I see.
It was, like, a tiny one.
- That happens. That's understandable.
- Not so much.
What?
Are you serious?
You mean not even a little one,
like a micro-orgasm?
- No.
- Are you sure?
This is upsetting.
The truth is, Hank,
we've been through some...
We've been through
some really hard times.
- I know that.
- So...
But we've always had
our fire and our passion.
Our beautiful sex organs
don't know about our problems,
and we should definitely
keep them out of it.
You got to give me another
chance to please you, woman.
We, we can't. It's too late.
It's not gonna work.
No, there's too much pressure.
No. Anyway, we have plans.
It's Saturday.
I can do this all day.
Felicia.
Your new friend.
She invited us for lunch.
- I know. I had to say yes, because...
- No, you didn't.
God, that woman is so annoying.
She's so irritating.
Yeah, that's good.
Like that, only louder and deeper.
I can work with that.
Me love you long time.
It's over.
I got to go.
I got to get ready.
All right.
Just give me a moment...
while I talk my testicles
into descending.
Guys?
Looks like there's some kind
of a book club or something.
Of a sort.
Oh, dear.
At least it won't be
a dull Saturday afternoon.
Welcome.
Hello. Come in.
- You shouldn't have. Thank you.
- No, it is you who shouldn't have.
This is quite a surprise.
- I think pleasure is the word.
- Or surprise.
They all heard
that I was having you over.
Guess the whole ya-ya sisterhood
had to get in on it.
We can't let you skip town
without a fond farewell.
Our last class was very unsatisfying,
since you didn't teach us anything.
This is Jill. She was Hank's
teaching assistant this semester,
And that's Jackie.
We met in class, right?
- We were all there...
- In a way.
Why don't I come with you guys?
We can hang out,
try on some lip gloss,
- you know, sparkly?
- You made your bed.
Now you're gonna have to lie in it.
Have fun, Hank.
Wake the fuck up, Runkle.
Open house time.
You know the house won't sell
if we're within five miles of it.
Give me ten minutes, ten minutes.
Come on!
We got to jet.
Buyers can smell our impending divorce
from the freeway.
Coming!
I'm coming.
You really are coming. Barf.
I told you.
And I told you.
She never fucking listens, am I right?
You must be Marcy.
I'm...
Getting your pants and getting
the fuck out of my house.
Now, please.
Thank you.
There's a good girl.
Off you go.
I'll call you.
Really?
The floor, that's your move?
You said not to mess up the bed
if we're showing the house.
Christ, Runkle!
I'm sorry
she's not a coke-snorting teen idol
or a big black rapist.
Not everyone can have
class up the ass.
No ass.
Just class.
I could take the stubbornness,
really I could,
and the substance abuse
and the lateness
and the "cooler than school and all
the rest of us ne'er do well" attitude,
but the thing that absolutely got me
was the unwarranted advice
about my biological clock.
But, you know,
he's fully qualified to do that,
because he has such
a deep understanding
- of womanhood.
- Shouldn't you be defending me?
You, talking up my good points?
Yeah. I will later.
Right now I'm really enjoying
this kind of appraisal
of your little idiosyncrasies,
you know, the things
that I have grown
to know and love about you.
The cracks.
It's how the light gets in.
More pimm's, anyone?
Hit me with that. You know,
it's not an act... this whole thing.
I'm very sensitive
to the pain and suffering of women.
I listen to them.
I'm aware of that shit.
OK. That's true.
In his defense,
I must say that he paid me
- tons of special attention in class.
- Not special.
No, Jackie.
He did not.
Jackie's writing's actually very good.
I read some of her short stories.
- You have.
- Yeah, sure I have.
I had to write her a recommendation
to the graduate writing program.
She couldn't very well ask you.
When is luncheon gonna be served?
That's why we're here, right?
And I'm curious.
I want to know how it's different
from actual lunch.
We have one last guest,
who's a late arrival.
- Here's the latecomer now.
- It's not a lady. Please not a lady.
Is that Richard Bates?
Yeah, Crack the sky, you know him?
- Know him?
- Yeah.
Karen, is that you?
You look exactly the same.
Exactly the same as what exactly?
I mean, even more beautiful.
I can picture you right now
standing under the arch
in Washington square park,
wind blowing your hair.
And you blowing me off, you asshole.
Asshole...
I like where this is going,
him being an asshole and all,
but you want to fill me in on
- the rest of this shit?
- You gave me a "c". I mean, like,
when you sleep with your professor,
isn't that, like, to get a "b"?
You slept with him?
The glorious "mangina" here?
This is my professor that I had
an affair with as an undergraduate.
I mean, I know it's, like,
100 years ago.
It feels just like yesterday.
- Worst day of my life.
- You look great.
Thank you.
- You're not with Bush league here?
- Fuck yeah, she... is.
- Well, kind of.
- Really?
Don't keep secrets
from the rest of the class.
You planted the seed...
that writer thing,
my attraction to writers.
Have a drink.
How'd you snag her, anyway...
the old "I'm an agent" spiel?
It's not a spiel.
I'm an agent.
She has a dream, she's a waitress.
In your language,
it means stripper. She's a stripper.
She is a cocktail waitress
with a screenplay.
An idea for a screenplay.
Still, I see potential,
and I just...
Please. You see blow job.
Do I detect a note of jealousy?
Like I could be jealous
of a food-service professional
with an idea for a screenplay
- and her boobs.
- You are.
Marcy Runkle is jealous.
I never thought I'd see the day.
Go with God.
I got mine. Only right you get.
I have said all along.
I still love you.
It's not what you say, Charlie.
- What do you mean?
- It's out of sight, out of mind.
See Marcy, want Marcy.
No see Marcy, want boobies.
Really? Still?
- I forgot to change my ringtone.
- Please allow me.
Eat my bent wang, Rick Springfield.
Wait, get that.
It's Sharon.
You're shitting me.
We have an offer.
Where were you off to
when you dumped me? Was it Nepal?
It was Egypt.
I etched your name in stone
atop the pyramid at Giza.
- I wish that were true.
- Bullshit!
Staying home is very nice too.
It's cozy.
You don't need a passport, no shots.
So overall you would recommend
to sleep with your teacher?
You see what you've gone and done?
You've set a bad example, woman.
You were just so sexy.
I can't exactly be judgmental,
because that is
how I met Chelsea's father.
I was in graduate school,
and I took one
of his ridiculous civil war classes.
Loved to teach, you know,
so passionate about what he was doing.
That's it.
You were so passionate.
That's what turns me on.
Yes, but that kind of passion,
that burns you out.
That kind of intensity, no bueno.
Look at him.
He's not burnt out.
The man had
a serious breakdown recently.
Public nudity and singing.
- Smuggling Dr. Johnson.
- Oh, my poor love.
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't be.
It was the best thing
that's happened to me in years.
For a man to be...
just broken down to his most naked,
most vulnerable self.
Just stripped of all irony,
all vanity.
I don't think I've ever been
so deeply in touch
with my feminine side.
- That's beautiful.
- No, it wasn't. It was queer.
And not queer as in gay...
It was queer as in odd.
Downright lunatic, as a matter of fact.
I had to step in for him at that point
with my passion, my intensity,
'cause I'm all about that stuff.
The guy who once fell asleep
during his own lecture.
One time...
I did that one time.
I was boring myself,
and I thought it was an honest
reaction to actually fall asleep.
Word on the street is you couldn't
teach your way out of a paper bag.
Where'd you hear that?
I may have lobbed
a few random emails here and there.
That sounds like Stacy.
That's odd.
Justice will be served!
Ladies.
I demand satisfaction.
Well, general Sherman,
nice of you to join us.
William Tecumseh Sherman, no.
Yet another sign
of your blazing ignorance.
Major general George Henry Thomas,
rock...
of Chickamauga.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
I don't know whether to shake your hand
- or to... your sword or...
- The day of reckoning is at hand.
It's time for you to answer
for your sins. You and I will duel
on this fine day...
Like men!
Men of what century?
Dear God, he's completely blotto.
How can you tell?
He must have gone out drinking
with those reenactment people.
- You mock me?
- Guilty.
I challenge you to a duel,
and this is how you respond?
Personally, I love a good duel.
You're back and looking good.
Let's go, Moody.
You've defiled my wife.
You've brought dishonor
to this house,
the university.
I'll stand for it no more.
And get your filthy car
out of my driveway.
Stacy, you might want to rest up.
Hank doesn't want to play these games.
- Hank don't want to play.
- They always lose, you see.
The union army gets defeated,
and then they go out drinking.
He held until nightfall,
preventing an even greater union defeat.
How? Because general Thomas
refused to surrender Horseshoe Ridge.
Was he the flashiest
civil war general?
Did he impress the ladies?
Was he a highly functioning
alcoholic like Ulysses S. Grant?
Maybe.
You know, you might want
to play along with him.
And let him bust
civil war-era cap in my ass?
I don't think so.
They're just blanks.
You won't feel anything.
- General?
- I'll be waiting in the field of valor.
For love and honor!
It's really quite fun.
We're gonna sell this house.
- To moving on.
- And to my favorite roommate.
And just think, we don't have
to be roommates anymore.
You can fuck whoever you want,
however you want.
Cowgirl, reverse cowgirl,
downward facing dog, whatevs.
I think that's a yoga term.
It is both a sex term
and a yoga term.
- I learned that from Rick Springfield.
- Please don't tell me any more.
That's the beauty of it.
I fuck who I want,
you fuck who you want,
and we don't have to discuss
the details.
I don't have to hear all your shit
about your pieces of class up the ass.
You know, not to go back on this,
but you actually did
offer me the ass one time,
- right here in this very living room.
- What was I thinking?
Dr. Drew says you could get
a prolapsed anus from that shit.
Once you hit 80, your ass is like,
"Why did you have to take it
in the pooper?
"Now you're gonna have to carry
me around with you all day."
And right over here?
The year that I got that UTK bonus,
remember? I came in.
I bent you over the couch and...
And gave me the worst
back pain I've ever experienced.
For years, I had a man
who liked to take it
out of the comfortable bedroom,
take it on the road.
- Great.
- That's right.
We really have humped
all over this house, haven't we?
Remember
the kitchen-counter encounter?
- Best night of my life.
- Not mine.
Days later, I was still finding
crumbs in my folds.
What about the powder room?
We never did it there.
That's true.
There's one room in this house
that was spared our unholy alliance.
Okay, let's go.
- Let's go, come on.
- Where? What?
We can't leave one room uninitiated.
We cannot leave that room pristine,
because that would be a tragedy,
and this is a happy day. Let's go.
You move it, schoolgirl.
You... Come on, let's go.
- No, you can't tell me what to do.
- Daddy's coming!
- You sure these aren't loaded?
- Oh, just pick one, Moody.
- So ten paces and then turn?
- I don't believe I have ever met
a bigger pussy in my life.
You slept with the man's wife?
The code of honor demands it.
What do you know
about honor, numb nuts?
Silence.
I'll have none of that filthy talk
on this field of valor.
My bad.
This is quite fun, Chels, isn't it?
Like the good old days
when we used to follow your father
around from battlefield
to battlefield.
Ladies...
- Come on.
- Start your egos.
For fuck's sake, Moody,
stop fucking around.
Come on!
Come on, let's do this thing.
- Come on.
- Come on, let's go.
- There, stand there.
- I hope he shoots him between the eyes.
You're not getting out of this one.
I'll let that slide
since this isn't a real duel.
One, two, five, six...
... nine, ten.
Damn it to hell.
Well, Moody, take your shot.
Wait, you want me to shoot you?
Nah, it's all right. I'm good.
I demand that you shoot me.
No can do.
This whole thing is way too gay for me.
Hold on a second.
You fucked the man's wife,
and now you refuse to shoot him?
You know something,
if it's all the same to you...
Is this what's supposed to happen?
Cool down, girls.
I guess I deserved that.
I'm sorry.
- I apologize.
- No biggie.
No, it was ungentlemanly of me.
The purpose of a duel
is to fight with honor
and decorum.
Nice one, Dean.
- You liked that?
- Yes, I did.
You know something?
You offend my honor.
You offend my lady's honor.
Your lady?
Are you so sure she's really yours?
Shit, Moody, you couldn't own
a woman like that.
Christ, I still remember the sound
of her approaching climax...
Fucking choir of angels.
I can't tell
if they're joking or not.
I think they're actually fighting.
Can I take you up on that drink?
Fuck your pussy.
- Fuck your pussy.
- Fuck my pussy?
Or your pussy is my pussy, or...
Shut up and pound me.
My back.
Holy mother of fuck!
Why did I let you sit on the sink?
The chick is supposed to sit.
That's bathroom boning 101!
I can't move,
I'm fucking drowning here.
You're drowning, really?
A person can drown in this amount
of water in certain circumstances.
You big baby.
Get over here.
Climbing the toilet bowl.
- We're almost home.
- Sit, sit.
Wait.
What the fuck is that?
You had my name tattooed
above your ass crack?
I was drunk.
I don't even remember getting it done.
- I'm getting it removed. I am.
- No, you're not.
- You like it?
- No, I don't like it.
It's fucking retarded.
Retarded and sweet...
Just like you, Runkle.
I guess I'd better take
my walking wounded home, right?
That's if he ever
comes out of the bathroom.
Are you... Are you okay
with Becca spending the night?
Yeah, of course.
It's no problem.
You know, it's nice for the girls
to spend one last sleepover together
before Becca leaves for New York.
- Good luck with that, by the way.
- Thank you.
Are you always so civilized?
The wife of a general
has certain responsibilities,
- you know?
- Of course.
I'll never be
as pretty as I once was.
And I'm peeing blood.
I got myself
more of a foot soldier...
Some cannon fodder, really.
What did I miss?
Look at that.
One semester ends, another begins.
- You gonna do something about that?
- What's the point, you know?
Nothing ever really changes around here.
It's the beautiful thing about academia.
None of us can really function
in the real world,
so that's why we end up here.
It sort of works for everyone, really.
We can't function
anywhere else but here.
You can't.
No, you can't.
- Ignore him.
- What's he saying?
Okay, I'm gonna go say
good night to Richard.
No, you can't.
- Go. I'm timing you.
- Thank you for lunch.
I hope we didn't give you
too hard a time of it today.
No, no worries.
I'm fine.
My ass is a little sore,
but that's normal for me.
It's all done with great affection.
You're a mess, you cause such chaos,
but I wouldn't change anything.
- You sure about that?
- Really.
It was a fabulous disaster.
Come here.
- Be happy in New York.
- There you go.
And the general?
You gonna let him back?
If you don't,
he's gonna call in reinforcements...
The cavalry, perhaps.
He does seem very determined.
Passionate, one might say.
I do like that in a man.
- I'm in a fever!
- I better go tend to the general.
- Toodle-loo.
My brow!
Did you ladies have fun
twisting the knife this afternoon?
- Absolutely.
- Too much fun.
I'm so happy that I could
give you a reason to come together
- and become friends.
- Yeah, we're like BFFs now.
She's gonna teach me
how to pole-dance.
Such a crying shame, Hank.
Just think of all
of the missed opportunities.
If I hear you've gone
and blown it with this gorgeous filly,
I will kick your ass
and make her my queen.
Ladies.
- Take care, Karen.
- Bye, have fun.
Bye.
- I can't believe I used to love him.
- You'll get over it.
Come on, soldier,
let's get you home.
You still have battles to fight,
realms to conquer.
The child...
What about the child?
The child is staying here tonight.
No wonder we never did it
in the powder room.
That was really not pleasant at all.
It wasn't great.
I don't mean the first part, of course.
I meant the second part.
I enjoyed the shit
out of humping you at first.
We could sleep
knowing we gave the next homeowners
a dirty sink and a plumbing problem.
Holy shit.
They came...
The divorce papers.
Big day, Charlie...
Signing time.
Well, I can't move.
You're gonna have to bring me a pen.
Hey, how was the first part
for you, Marce, hmm?
You never said.
What do you want me to say, Charlie?
The first part with you was great.
It's the last part
that ended in disaster.
Yeah, yeah, but it doesn't have to,
you know?
Because we could keep going.
You know, we turn the last part
into the middle part.
And what happens when we get
to the next shitty part?
There doesn't have to be
a shitty part.
There's always
a shitty part with us.
I appreciate the interest,
I really do.
- You do?
- Yes, I'm just...
I'm just not sure I'm...
in the Moody.
But I am.
I really am.
I mean, today was so exciting.
I could, like, totally just, like,
carry on from where
we left off this morning.
My mind and my body
are totally in sync.
I'm not sure that I like
the implication of that.
What? It's very sexy for a man
to fight for your honor.
Is it also very sexy to run
into some old geezer
you let bone you
when you were 19 years old?
It just reminded me
of being back at college again,
when life was so simple,
and he was so...
He was so passionate,
so full of enthusiasm.
I know, I know.
He was so big, actually.
Gross.
I mean, not that that matters
or anything, but...
You know, right?
- You saw. The whole deal.
- I saw nothing.
As far as I know,
the man is a hermaphrodite.
Really?
God, he was, like, the hottest
assistant professor on the campus.
Everybody wanted to sleep with him.
My friends were so jealous.
One time we were doing it in his office,
and there was, like, this line
- down the hall...
- That's it.
- I demand satisfaction.
- Yes, yes, it worked!
Good.
Are you gonna punish me?
You do know I'll have to live
with that image for the rest of my life.
I know.
I'm just not sure that my mind
and my body are in sync either.
The events of the day, all this fun
you've had, it's bruised my mind.
It's traumatized me.
It may very well undermine
my ability to please you.
Really?
No, not really.