My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice.
You're blacklisted.
When you're burned,you've got nothing...
No cash,no credit,no job history.
You're stuck in whatever city
they decide to dump you in.
- Where am I?
- miami.
You do whatever work comes your way.
You rely on anyone who's
still talking to you.
A trigger-happy
ex-girlfriend...
Should we shoot them?
...An old friend who's
informing on you to the fbi...
You know spies...
A bunch of bitchy little girls.
...Family,too...
Is that your mom again?
...If you're desperate.
Someone needs your help.
Bottom line... Until you
figure out who burned you,
you're not going anywhere.
Covert operatives have
a hard time dating.
Even if you find someone who doesn't
mind that you won't talk about your past
or that you carry a concealed weapon,
they usually want more
than you're able to give.
You're late.
What's that?
I said,"you're late."
watch the step.
I made you tuna with tahini...
Your favorite.
Good memory.
Oh,no.
No dossier at lunch.
You have had your head buried in this
thing every waking moment since you got it.
Come on,fi,it's not every day you get to
read a fictional account of your whole life.
Apparently,I sold secrets in lebanon,
code-breaking technology in jordan.
Who knew?
I got to figure out my next move.
I just can't believe it's the
only thing on your mind these days.
Fi,I know we haven't talked about
what happened the other night.
It was...
Well,you know what it was.
But there's a reason why
it didn't work before.
We were in a war zone.
This is miami,Michael.
Fi,beach is this way.
Actually,I got a little
errand to run first.
It'll only take a second.
What will?
Bagging a bail jumper.
I thought it'd be fun.
You're a bounty hunter now,fi?
Girl's got to eat.
There's this bondsman.
He gives me odd jobs.
Fi!
How often do I help you?
All the time.
Here's who we're looking for.
Thomas mckee.
I got a tip about an hour ago
he's staying at the victor.
Fi,I have a feeling this guy
is not gonna survive on the lam.
Is it always this easy for you?
Oh,hey,sorry.
Uh,there's your guy.
THOMAS MCKEE
FUGITIVE
Whoa,whoa,whoa,who is that?
WAYNE RAY
OTHER BOUNTY HUNTER
Wayne ray, bounty hunter.
I might have snaked
a few of his collars.
Mckee,get on the ground!
You take wayne,I'll take thomas.
That doesn't seem fair.
Ugh! Oh,dude!
Dude!
There you are.
Please,please,I didn't do it.
I'm innocent,I swear.
Get in.
Nice work.
Where do we deliver him?
We don't. He says he's innocent.
He's coming home with us.
Hi,I'm thomas.
Hey!
I told you this would be fun.
Hold it right there! Get back here!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-Ö¥Ê¿µ°¸â
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Burn Notice
Season 01 Episode 08
Beijing,london,the taj mahal?
Look at all these.
Bounty hunter.
The point is to collect the
bounty by turning him in.
The job is what... $4,000?
He's offering us $8,000 just
to clear his name,Michael.
Hear him out.
Hey,you have been,like,everywhere.
Yeah,I work a job,buy a snow globe.
Some people say I'm sentimental.
Tell us about your situation.
Oh,right,yeah.
I do liquor promotions for a
bunch of the hotels on south beach.
Now,I'm friends with a girl
who night-managed the victor.
A couple months ago,I'm
making a delivery,
and she shows me this,uh,you know,like,
you pin on your,um,you
know,what do you call the...
A brooch?
Right. They were holding it for a guest.
2 million bucks.
She showed it to you. why?
Because it's worth 2 million bucks,man!
I mean,it had a huge rock!
I mean,this thing was just...
Anyway,it gets stolen,and my friend
gets fired for showing me the brooch,
and the cops arrest me.
For just looking at it?
I'm guessing there's more than that.
Yeah,I had an access card for the
hotel office for late-night deliveries,
and I lost it.
And then I find out that somebody
used it to rip off the brooch,
and now everyone's looking at me like
I'm some criminal mastermind or whatever.
And you went back to the
scene of the crime why?
Investigating.
I was trying to find
out who did it,you know?
My trial was supposed
to start yesterday,
and my lawyer basically tells me,
before we go in,that I'm gonna lose.
I mean,I just...
I kind of freaked.
I mean,I know that you're
not supposed to skip court,
but,man,I can't go to jail.
I want to help him.
Do it for me,Michael.
Okay.
Between the cops and wayne and
all the other bounty hunters,
we're gonna have to stash him somewhere.
Why can't you keep him here?
You're okay with that...
Another guy staying at my place?
Yeah,it's fine by me.
Okay,then,it's fine by me,too.
Yeah,Sam,I need a favor.
Diamonds? Fun.
Buying or selling?
BARRY
MONEY LAUNDERER
Neither.
Looking for a $2 million brooch.
It's like a little spidey thing.
Yeah,the one that got lifted
from the victor two months ago.
****
That's the one.
You think it's on the market yet?
Doubt it.
A stone that big is easy to I.D.
It's like selling a fingerprint.
And if you cut it,the value plummets.
It takes months to line up a buyer.
*****
So,who does that around here?
Really only one guy in miami.
Don't ask me for an intro,though.
The guy shorted me on some
hot rocks a few months back.
It cost me a client.
We had words.
Give me a name.
Mike will see to it the guy
loses a few clients of his own.
Name's cristo...
Like madonna...
The whole one-name thing.
- Like charo.
- sting.
- Fergie.
- pel.
Spider-man.
Liberace.
Crap,I can't think of any more.
Anyway,cristo's got this
place on south beach,
but good luck getting a meeting
because he's,like,all
high-end referrals.
Well,you know Mike.
He's not gonna call
to make an appointment.
CRISTO
THE FENCE
You're out of salsa.
You okay?
That looked like it hurt.
Who are you?
Let's not talk about me.
Let's talk about what I want.
I'm looking for a piece of jewelry...
30 carats,platinum
setting,spider-looking thing.
Sound familiar?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh,we got to do this the hard way.
Selling stolen goods
is all about discretion.
You've got to be the kind of person
who can keep your mouth shut...
Gerald? He sounds nice.
Hey,hey,hey,what are you doing?
Shh! It's ringing.
The kind of person who never,ever shares
the numbers in their little black book.
Hey,gerald,man.
My name is paco.
I'm buddies with your fence,cristo.
Man,I'm in some legal trouble.
Cristo said you could help me out.
Can I stay on your...
That's rude. He hung up.
- Maybe vincent will be nicer.
- No,no.
I can do this all night.
Stop.
I got a call about the brooch.
The guy was an amateur.
He thought you could sell a
rock like that on the street.
He got all pissed off when I said that he
better hang onto it for at least six months.
I told him I will look for a buyer,
but he needed the cash quick.
I think he's planning
to move it in europe.
What's his name?
I don't know his real name.
I got his phone number.
That's all.
Okay,good enough.
I'll take it.
Oh,and,by the way,I should mention,
I went through your
fridge while you were out.
Do you know it's one of the most
frequently used hiding places?
Found this in the orange sherbet.
I assume you're holding it for someone.
I'll keep it until our job is finished.
Until then,you keep your mouth
shut about our little chat.
Even the most careful spy leaves
a trail that could get them burned.
A patriot making illicit
deals for his government
looks a lot like a traitor making
black-market sales for his wallet.
Somebody upstairs gets the wrong idea,
and suddenly you're
burned and out of a job.
Mike,piece of advice.
Ladies like attention.
They don't want to be
second to a dossier...
Not even a big one.
You've been talking to fi.
If by "talking to fi," you mean
"listening to fi," then,yeah.
So,look,I got ahold of
my contacts at the fbi,
about the guy who put your
little dossier together.
They were not very helpful at all.
They stuck me with the bill.
Did you get anything?
Everything I know about philip cowan,
who works for the
national security agency,
fits right here on the
back of the receipt.
I'll read it for you.
"He works counterintel
for the nsa." that's it.
That's all I got.
Is there any way to reach him?
Mike,you know these nsa
guys. They're like ghosts.
They got no phone number,no
address,no nothing.
Sorry I couldn't be more help.
Guess I'll have to find another
way to get in touch with him.
How's your jewel thing going?
I could use some more help,actually.
I need you to run down a phone number.
It belongs to a jewel thief.
Make you a deal.
I'll talk to my cop buddies,
you cover my little working lunch.
You want one?
They're awesome.
Thomas is a hell of a cook.
Playing catch?
He's teaching me baseball.
It's really nothing like cricket.
Sam's checking up on the real thief,
so thomas should be
out of here soon enough.
Oh,no rush.
I like having him around.
Thanks for suggesting it.
I need a favor,fi.
I need you to reach out to
your black-market contacts...
The scarier,the better.
Is this about the dossier?
It's about the man who burned me.
He's hard to reach.
I need to recruit some help.
How you gonna do it?
I've been accused of being
a major security risk.
It's time I started acting like one.
I know a few iranians
who are coming into town.
Let's avoid people who use "Michael
Westen" and "jihad" in the same sentence.
How about libyans?
I hear there's a group here talking
to some south american oil companies.
See if you can set it up.
Hey,Mike.
Hello.
Phone number you gave me
belongs to lawrence henderson.
Does he work at the hotel?
I wouldn't say "work." he owns it.
I mean,for now,at least.
He bet big on the victor.
Now he's got a cash-flow problem.
So,if you do the
math,it's a little screwy.
He's got 2 million bucks for a brooch,
but that's not gonna
bail him out of his hole,
but it might give him a year
or two to turn things around.
LAWRENCE HENDERSON
HOTEL OWNER, THIEF
Cops ever look at him?
No,they cleared him.
He had an alibi and a
fleet of lawyers to sell it.
A few years back,he had
a club in new orleans.
It was hit by,I guess you'd
call it,a very convenient fire.
Almost killed a busboy.
He got the hotel with
the insurance money.
Got a hell of a security setup.
He's a little paranoid.
Even paranoids have enemies,Sam.
You're living proof of that.
What are you saying?
Well,a little. I mean...
We should go.
The guy who owns the
victor did this to me?
I don't even know him.
It's not personal.
You handled the brooch.
You had easy access.
You're an easy fall guy.
So,what now?
I mean,can we go to the
cops with that guy cristo?
What do we tell them?
I broke into his house and
extorted information from him?
Meanwhile,lawrence ditches the brooch,
cristo denies everything,
and the only guys that
go to jail are you and me.
It's fine.
Hard or easy...Your choice.
Take thomas out the back.
- No,I...
- fi.
Right.
- You?
- Can we talk?
No,I'm done talking.
Watch your head.
Oh,damn.
When you're giving 5 inches and 100
pounds to a well-trained opponent,
it helps to know the
terrain better than he does.
That step is hard to see.
I did the same thing earlier.
Where'd they go?
I can't tell you if you keep choking me.
Italy was one of my favorites.
Thank you.
he has to stay with you.
With me,fi?
My place isn't safe.
We just left the world's largest bounty
hunter knocked out on my front lawn.
Guys,look,I don't
want to cause problems.
I can go stay at a motel or something.
No,don't be silly.
Cheap motels are the first place guys
like wayne are gonna look for bail jumpers.
Michael's fine having you here.
Yeah.
Well,you guys are the experts,I guess.
Seriously,man,thanks.
We'll figure this out,thomas.
Tell him about the plan,Michael.
The plan.
There's a plan?
Oh,yeah,there's a plan.
I'm gonna pose as a buyer,set up a sale,
get lawrence to bring the
brooch out into the open,
then the cops will arrest him.
And we will be celebrating your
freedom by the end of the week.
Hey,fi,can I...
Can we talk about the plan?
Just...
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything. We're working.
No,this is different,and
you know this is different.
I didn't think we were
in a relationship,Michael.
Do you want something to drink,thomas?
Maybe a yogurt?
Mixing romance and work is a bad idea.
Veronica...Just the other day,
she asked me if bullets
came in different sizes.
Isn't that the cutest
thing you've ever heard?
That is so adorable.
Sam,you gonna help me on this?
Yeah.
When have I ever said no?
Lawrence needs a buyer.
That'll be me.
You're the middleman.
Cristo is setting up an
appointment with you and lawrence.
So,what's my cover I.D....
A shady international business guy?
Yeah,something like that.
You're gonna take point on this deal.
Oh,that means I got to
shave and put on a suit.
It's 90% humidity,and I got
to come on all professional.
And paranoid...
Extremely security-conscious
so he doesn't have to be.
Veronica and I were
gonna go to the keys,Mike.
Sam?
Okay,okay,but I just
got to go on record.
I think this whole thing
with Fiona is unhealthy.
You got to go through all this crap just to
get some guy she picked up out of your place?
Okay,I'll break out the suit.
A good cover identity is a team effort.
If you want to meet someone,it's a
good idea to play a little hard to get.
Put people between
yourself and the target.
Make them come to you.
Yes,I'm looking for a mr. Henderson.
Ah,thank you.
Mr. Henderson?
Charles finley.
We spoke on the phone.
It's good to meet you.
Cristo said you were a good man.
He... He vouched for you.
Listen,can I get you a drink...
Some 20-year-old
single malt?
Thanks,but no.
I... I'm not a drinker.
Look,I'll get right down to business.
I represent a group of clients who deal
in merchandise that is bought and sold,
let's just say,quietly.
I understand that you have
something we might be interested in.
If I do business with a man,I
have to meet with him face-to-face.
I'm sorry,but that won't be possible.
For obvious reasons,discretion
is extremely important to us.
It's important to me,too.
If he would like to come
to my home,that's fine.
We could talk.
Otherwise...
No guarantees,sir,but I'll
try and make the arrangements.
Good day.
Hey,Sam. How's it going?
I got us a meeting for tomorrow.
We'll talk later. My
libyan just showed up.
Fine,but,from now on,
no cover I.D.S that involve
turning down 20-year-old scotch.
ANWAR
LIBYAN OPERATIVE
Who are you?
Well,hello to you,too.
My name is Michael Westen.
I heard you were in town.
Just wanted to say hi.
You're Westen?
I thought you would be taller.
You can put the gun
down. I just want to talk.
With you?
I've heard,people talk to you,
sometimes they don't live so long.
Well,that was then. Ask around.
My situation has changed.
My side isn't talking to me anymore,
so that leaves you guys.
Don't make up your mind right now.
Do your homework.
See what you think.
I'm around.
Are in their convertible
at the gas station,
and she had her baby in the back.
Am interrupting something?
Thomas made dinner.
Yeah,to say thank you.
I,uh,I did make some
for you,Mike,but,um...
We ate it because it was so good.
How'd it go with Sam?
Great. The meeting is set with lawrence.
If I can get him to bring
the brooch out into the open,
we can get him caught with it.
So I might get to go home soon?
Let's hope so.
He's locked down pretty tight.
He's either expecting
an armored assault...
Or he has something to protect.
Unfortunately,we only
have a few minutes.
We have some important meetings.
Well,thank you for coming,mr. Uh...
Smith.
Smith?
Yes. Typically,with this sort of deal,
we like to keep things not
so personal...You understand?
For security purposes.
Normally,I do not like
to do meetings in person,
but for a piece like this,I was
willing to make an exception.
Well,the way I see it,
you can't trust a man if you
can't look him in the eye.
Am I right?
Of course you're right.
Mr. Finley,you can wait right here.
It's important that I stay...
Charles,that's fine.
Well,the least I can do is...
I'll take care of it.
Something to drink,sir?
Yeah,water will be just great.
Thank you.
So how did you hear about me?
I've worked with cristo before.
And the people you've
contacted in europe
aren't being as discreet
as you might like.
Is that right?
Word is out.
None of my business,but
I would sell quickly.
It might not be long
before somebody tries
to take it off your hands
without your consent,
shall we say.
Well,let me worry about that.
That brooch isn't going anywhere soon.
Oh,don't be pessimistic.
Let me see what I can
do to pry it loose.
Brass tacks,then.
The item is worth $2 million.
I could give it to you
for $1.75 million cash.
For something I have to
cut up into little pieces?
Hmm,no.
$1.2 million is more than generous.
Then let's call it $1.6
million and be done.
Let me show you something.
Stolen from an armored
truck over two years ago.
I picked it up this morning
for 50 cents on the dollar.
Would you like to talk
to cristo about it?
$1.25 million.
I'm being very generous
offering $1.2 million.
Fine.
In cash...
Small,used bills.
Excellent.
Of course,I'll need to see it first.
Just because someone believes
you are who you say you are
doesn't mean he'll do
what you want him to do.
There it is.
Cute.
I'm serious.
Mr. Smith,this brooch
isn't coming out to play
till you come back with the money
in that little case of yours.
Fine.
We do the deal tomorrow,but not here.
We have to take the diamonds out to
an independent lab for authentication.
We do it here,where I can control it,
or it doesn't happen at all.
I'm afraid an independent testing
site is a deal breaker for me.
Then I'm afraid we don't have a deal.
Pity.
Lawrence needs the money.
He thinks it's too risky
to move the brooch now.
What do we do?
Convince him it's too risky to stay put.
I already planted the idea that
somebody might be trying to steal it.
We need to back that
up,push on his paranoia.
*****
I thought you said that his
place was impossible to get into.
It is...
Between the security
system,the guards,and the safe,
we'd need a small army. ***
We'll just have to make him
think we've got a small army.
Christ,this is turning into
a full psych-op campaign.
What are we talking about here?
Psychological warfare.
Give you an example.
U.S. Used to broadcast static
to soviet listening posts,
trying to get them to think
it was some new kind of cipher.
So they spent all kinds of rubles,
basically trying to decode white noise.
We need to convince the enemy
we're stronger than we are.
Yeah,except it takes forever.
Mike,I was supposed to go
car shopping with veronica.
We're talking cadillacs,you know.
You need to do it next week.
We got a lot of work to do.
You two scout it out.
I got to get ready for the meeting.
Clandestine meetings
are never fun to arrange.
It's a big part of the
job for a covert operative,
but it's never pleasant.
get in.
Where's anwar?
It's not so much the fear
of death that bothers you.
It's driving to the meet
with a bag over your head.
Sometimes they wash the bag.
Sometimes they don't.
Guys,you're really missing
out on the miami beach scene,
staying in a place like this.
Have you checked out the beach hotels?
They're surprisingly
affordable in the off-season.
Guys?
Okay,you wanted to talk.
Talk.
You checked out my situation,I assume.
Your own people turned on you?
Yes. So what?
Now you're working for us?
Why should I believe this?
Your government would like to know
who attacked your gas-supply
depot in ghadamis in 2002.
I could supply that information.
And why would you do this for us?
The u.S. And libya have mutual enemies.
This would be a win-win
situation for everyone...
Well,everyone except for the guys
who blew up the gas-supply depot.
Why don't I just make
you tell me,then kill you?
You could do that.
The information might
or might not check out...
Torture is unreliable,as you know...
And then you'd have to deal with Fiona,
who put me in touch with you.
More trouble than it's worth,trust me.
All right.
What do you want?
I'm trying to reach out
to the man who burned me...
Nsa officer philip cowan.
I just need you to mention
him as a friend of yours
when you know the
americans are listening.
A friend?
And say what?
I don't know.
Have the head of your secret
police send him a fruit basket.
Be creative.
He'll try to figure out
what the hell is going on,
and,in no time,he'll figure out it's me.
We'll think about it.
I love this part.
You ready back there?
Drive.
The thing about security
is that the very things
that protect you can
be turned against you
by someone who knows what he's doing.
It's tough to compromise a
well-thought-out security system,
but making someonethink
you can compromise it...
Well,that's much easier.
Take surveillance cameras,for example.
You can disable one by
shooting a laser at it
and overloading the
light-sensitive chip.
Cheap,easy...
...And exactly the sort of thing
a sophisticated criminal gang
with lots of resources would do.
Leave around some telltale
signs of surveillance,
like cigarette butts,a
forgotten camera-lens cap.
And the more security there is,
the more likely they are to think
they've got a very serious problem.
Even the security team
itself can be an opportunity.
The more employees you have,
the more you have to worry about.
Hello
- Can I help you?
- maybe.
You work at the hendersons'.
You're ted,right?
Yeah,who are you?
My name isn't important.
We've been watching you.
You look like you
could use a little help.
We'll be in touch.
Deliver some vague threats and a few
hundred bucks to a security guard.
If he's honest,he'll tell his boss,
who then wonders whowasn'tso honest.
For the cost of a nice dinner,
you can get a whole
security team canned.
- Here you go,rocky.
- Okay, man
Thank you.
Mike,I got to tell you,
this is more fun than I expected.
I mean,I haven't done
this sort of thing since...
Gee,since there was an east germany.
Glad you're enjoying yourself.
So,how are things at home?
A little strange.
Fiona likes to test relationships with
the emotional equivalent of artillery fire.
Does she even want this guy?
I don't know. I've never
been able to figure her out.
Well,I'm not one to tell
you how to live your life.
Hang on.
It's our buddy lawrence.
Charles finley here.
Yes?
Well,I'm not sure if
the offer still stands,
but I can talk to him.
No guarantees,but I'll do my best.
Bye-bye.
- How'd it go?
- Good.
I think we got him whipped
into a pretty good lather.
He wants to meet you at the hotel.
I'll let him stew for a bit.
Call him back when I'm
done with my slushie.
Mr. Smith,it's good to see you.
We can have our meeting in my office.
I was about to leave
town when charles called.
I'm happy to talk,but my
conditions haven't changed.
We just have some issues
with timing... Details.
It's right this way.
One of the dangers of any
kind of psychological warfare
is it can betooeffective and send
the target into a paranoid tailspin.
I have to thank you for
telling me to check my security.
We've had some problems at the house.
Happens all the time in this business.
Better safe than sorry.
I agree entirely.
That paranoia can be
useful... or deadly.
At first,I thought it might
be one of the europeans
I was talking to about the brooch,
trying to rip me off.
And then I thought
that didn't make sense.
So I said,"it might be cristo."
so I brought him in.
Listen,whatever he told
you,whatever you think...
He has said some very
interesting things about you.
5 pounds of pressure
on his carotid artery,
he'll bleed out in 20 seconds.
Let him go.
That's not all you have to worry about.
I could crush his windpipe
with the tie if I'm not careful.
Oops. Back off.
Back off.
Back off!
Next time,lawrence,go limp.
It's really hard to drag a human shield.
Jesus. I mean,he really
tried to kill you?
It didn't get that far,but it was
heading in that direction,yeah.
I mean,w- what are you gonna do?
I mean,h- he knows who you are.
No,he just knows I'm
not who I said I was...
A big difference.
He still thinks we're gonna rip him off.
He still thinks his security
system is compromised.
He's still got to move the brooch.
And we've still got to get him busted***
We just need to figure
out where he's taking it.
But how are we gonna do that?
I've got some friends.
There he is.
Hey.
How'd it go? You work your magic?
Magic was made.
You have something for me?
Michael wanted you to know that
that was compliments of cristo.
Tico,hit me.
Bloody mary.
Well... In that case,lawrence has
accounts at five banks in the miami area.
Only one with a safe-deposit
operation is dade trust,downtown.
Yeah,any good?
You kidding?
Best in miami.
Thank you.
If he's moving that
brooch,he'll go there.
Nice.
What else can you tell
me about dade trust?
You buying lunch?
You're the money
launder,for christ's sake.
Why doihave to buy lunch?
I know,I know,get in.
Can we do it without the head bag?
I hate the head bag.
So,this information you
have,we are interested.
And philip cowan?
Arrangements are being made.
That should give you what you need
to find out who the team was
that blew up your gas depot.
Don't be gentle on them.
They hurt a lot of innocent people.
The security services in my country
are not known for being gentle.
Michael,if you ever want
a job... Real work...
Let us know.
I'm flattered,but I've
got someplace to be.
The key to good security is
good systems...Consistency...
But those very systems
make you predictable.
Where will you take your valuables?
A bank you trust.
How are you going to get there?
With armed men in a big s.U.V.
When will you go?
When the bank is least crowded.
All good procedure,all 100% predictable.
Fi,they're on their way.
Yo?
All set,Sam?
I'm here. Good to go.
Looks like they're taking the highway.
They should be there in 5.
I'll call it in.
Yes,hello.
Is this the police?
Listen,I'd like to
report a bank robbery.
Yes,it's at dade trust,downtown.
I'm inside the building.
I can't talk loud.
There were men in an s.U.V. With guns.
Yes,they're here.
Oh,my god.
I have to go.
If you know someone's going to
be at a bank at a particular time,
it's not hard to make it look
like they're robbing the bank.
Shoot out a few
video-surveillance cameras.
Block off the street with a stolen car,
like they're preparing an escape route.
Fire up a spark-gap transmitter to
kill the security radios at the bank,
and they'll look like they
know what they're doing.
Mr. Smith,you're too late.
You sure?
Check the top floor of
the building behind you.
Gun!
You'll like prison,lawrence.
Drop your weapon!
They got a lot of cool security systems.
This is a mistake.
That's mine,that's mine.
*****
T- that's mine.
That's mine!
Quiet! Turn around!
All this to clear the
name of an innocent man.
That's noble.
You should be proud.
You know who I did this for,fi.
All right,I'm here.
What couldn't you say over the phone?
Bondsman won't have
anything to do with me now
that you've told him I
was aiding and abetting.
So I was thinking,when
you collect your bounty,
maybe we could split it.
Yeah,that's what you thought,huh?
I wouldn't be expecting a
check anytime soon. come on
Consider it a "sorry I brained
you with a snow globe" gift.
Why'd you wait to turn him in?
He was gonna pay us
off,but his check bounced.
You're all heart,lady.
Come on.
Mr. Bragin,wayne ray here.
I just collared mckee,and
I'm hauling him in right now.
Real cute.
You know,Fiona,next time...
Yeah,yeah,yeah.
Later,wayne.
I looked around for a washing machine.
I was gonna do the sheets.
Howdoyou do laundry,man?
I'll take care of it.
- Hello?
- You think this is funny?
Who's this?
This is philip cowan.
Nice to finally hear your voice.
You want to tell me what the
head of the libyan secret police
is doing sending me a fruit basket?
I got the fbi on my front lawn.
Yeah,well,welcome to my world,
and I'm just getting started.
I'd love to see what we can get the
north koreans to send you,or hezbollah,
and it doesn't stop until
you tell me why I was burned.
I was set up,and I want to know why.
Phil?
I'll be in touch.
Count on it.
Hey,man,if you got an important call,
I can just clear out.
No,it's fine.
My lawyer says my case is looking good,
but I got to go clear
it up in court tomorrow.
I would show up this time.
So,8 grand doesn't seem like
that much for what you guys did.
But here.
You're sweet.
Thank you.
You should go,thomas.
I'm not sure all the bounty hunters that are looking
for you got the memo that you're off the hook.
I wouldn't want you getting tasered
in the middle of our nice moment.
Well thanks.
I got you something,too.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-Ö¥Ê¿µ°¸â
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Burn Notice
Season 01 Episode 08