My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice on you.
You're blacklisted.
When you're burned,
you've got nothing.
No cash, no credit, no job history.
You're stuck in whatever city
they decide to dump you in.
- Where am I?
- Miami.
You do whatever work comes your way.
You rely on anyone
who's still talking to you.
- A trigger-happy ex-girlfriend.
- Should we shoot them?
An old friend who used
to inform on you to the FBI.
You know spies...
A bunch of bitchy little girls.
- Family, too...
- Hey, is that your mom again?
- If you're desperate.
- Someone needs your help.
Bottom line...
Until you figure out who burned you,
you're not going anywhere.
Bribery's a lot more difficult
than it sounds.
There's no way to shop around,
so you usually overpay
for whatever information you're after.
There's no money-back guarantee
if the information's bad,
and of course the only thing
that you know for sure
is that you're handing your money
to a thief and a liar.
I still can't believe you're giving
this money to some sleazy bank manager.
I went to a lot of trouble to find him.
I don't have a lot of options here.
Michael, he hid money for a man
who tried to assassinate you.
Which makes him a good person to know
if I'm trying to find that assassin.
You're going to this meeting unarmed.
You have no information.
It's a tactical risk.
Fi, I was warned not to meet you
the first time.
Yeah. I almost blew off your hand
with a block of C-4.
And I made a friend.
Maybe I'll make another one.
Watch my back.
Gustavo.
You have the money?
No small talk?
How was the flight?
Bad. All the way here,
I wonder why I do this.
You came here because I'm giving you
a lot of money for a little information.
I just want a name, a few numbers,
and you're back on a plane.
First, I need to know
how you found me.
Bank-secrecy regulations
in the Cayman Islands
are not easy to penetrate.
I have friends.
What friends?
I don't even know who you are
or why you want this information.
When someone's asking
for sensitive information,
it's basic security to make sure
that the person you're dealing with
is who he says he is.
An easy way is to change details
that the other person would know.
We talked about this on the phone.
I'm giving you $8,000 for a file.
Part of what that money buys
is privacy.
I don't care what I said
on the phone.
You don't tell me what I want to know,
you don't get this file.
$8,000, no $8,000.
The deal I made with Gustavo
was for $10,000, not $8,000.
He was very clear about that number.
And we never talked on the phone.
You want to tell me who you are?
I can explain.
Michael, what happened?
He didn't want to make friends.
Season 2, Episode 14:
Truth and Reconciliation.
Synchro VO: S@lomon
www.subbers-in-black.com
Hey, Mike.
Look what I got for you, huh?
My police buddy. It was his day off.
We went out on his boat.
Did you get anything
besides the fish?
I got a peek at a police file
from the Caymans.
Seems that the real Gustavo
was found dead in a bar.
I guess that's what you get
if you run payroll for an assassin.
- Where do you want me to put this?
- Sink.
- Did you catch it?
- No, buddy of mine did,
but I figured
you could use the protein.
Thanks.
So there was nothing
on my friend with the knives?
No, except that he's
as dead as that fish.
Probably got smuggled in.
Fi knows some people who make
extra-special travel arrangements.
I'm supposed to meet her
at the Carlito for lunch.
Bring the fish.
Maybe they'll cook it for you.
Mr. Westen?
- That depends.
- My name is Claude Laurent.
I need help. I found someone
who worked with you before.
He said that you were a good man
and once worked for the government?
Yeah, I was a government worker.
Please, please.
- I can pay you.
- What exactly do you need?
Several years ago, my daughter,
Veronique, was murdered in Haiti.
I am here to bring the man
who killed her to justice.
I'm not sure what you've heard
about me, but...
a murder in Haiti, that's not...
- No, I can't go there.
- No, please. Here.
See?
Jean-Pierre Duman.
He has a new name.
I have this, too.
It's from the inter-American
court of human rights.
We use it to make him come back
to Haiti and stand trial.
Duman was an official in Haiti.
Veronique spoke out against him.
He had her put in prison,
and then he had her killed.
Mr. Laurent, this is not gonna work
in an American court.
- Who is this man with the fish?
- The man with the fish is right.
You don't even have proof
of Duman's identity.
- No, no, no, I have found him, and...
- Claude, listen to me.
I'm sure Veronique
would want you to go home
and live out the rest of your life
remembering...
You know nothing...
of my daughter.
You do not deserve
to speak her name.
They said you were an honorable man.
They lied.
- What?
- Nothing.
Just waiting for Fi to show up.
You know, Mike, back in the day,
I had some buddies
who worked in Haiti.
Saw some of those prisons.
Bad, Mike.
Very bad.
A lot of guys got away
with a lot of bad stuff...
Evil.
Always wished I could do more.
Sam, he's got a worthless letter.
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
Probably just a...
big fat waste of time.
Just forget all about it.
A man and his daughter.
You want me to check out Duman?
Is that what you want me to do?
I made some calls
when I was taking a leak,
and I found addresses
of a couple places he hangs out.
- Yeah, mom?
- Michael, I need you to come over.
- There's been a break-in.
- All right. I'll be right there.
So, this was the break-in, mom?
I didn't even know
you still owned this car.
I park it at Mrs. Gartelman's.
They took the tape deck, Michael!
- What do you want me to do about it?
- Well, not you. We.
They're having break-ins all over here.
There's a real crime spree,
and I thought that the two of us
could look into it together.
Well, how about I get you
a new stereo?
It's not about the stereo.
I got the descriptions
of the boys who did it.
So call the police.
Yeah, right. They're not gonna do
anything about this, and you know it.
Could you at least give me
a ride to the store?
'cause the...
car won't start now.
Because the tape deck is stolen?
Hey, blame your father.
He installed the radio.
He wired the damn thing
to the ignition.
Spend enough time
in international hot spots,
and you learn that a lot of
the worst monsters on Earth
are just spoiled rich kids.
Mass murderers come
in many shapes and sizes,
but they tend to drink
the same brands of champagne.
That's the guy.
Jean-Pierre Duman.
His dad was a regional governor.
Damn near turned corruption into
an art form, died a few years back.
Jean-Pierre went into
the family business?
Yeah. Party boy there
ran the local prison.
Anybody complained, they went there.
Lucky ones were just executed.
After the election,
the whole family disappeared
with most of the island's GNP.
Disappeared till now?
Well, yeah, now he's Luc Renard.
He chases skirts, throws parties
at his place on Star Island.
Mike, I'm telling you,
we can do this.
You mean prove he's Duman?
Yeah, and you know how it is.
Nobody throws out everything
when they go off-grid.
We just got to get into his place.
Into his high-security place
on Star Island.
Nothing worth doing is easy, and nobody
loves easy more than me, but it's true.
Fiona, feel like coming to a party?
People love the sound
of their native tongue.
Even the most security-conscious person
often lets his guard down
when he hears somebody
who speaks his language.
If that somebody happens to be
in a designer dress...
What, I can't go in?
So much the better.
I will see you both later?
No. No, you won't.
And what do you suppose
I will be doing later?
I'll think of something.
I don't even know your name.
Luc Renard.
Claire Neville.
Come.
Party at my house.
Is this yours?
Yes. Do you like it?
Does it belong to your family,
or did you buy all this all by yourself?
You know, I don't like
to talk business.
Come, let me show you
the rest of the house.
Where does this lead?
This leads nowhere.
Come this way.
I have the biggest bathtub in Miami.
Well, if it's so big,
maybe we should invite a friend or two.
Give me a minute.
- Yeah, Fi?
- I'm in his office.
- There's not much here.
- Well, then, get out.
If Duman catches you, you're not getting
out of there with a stern conversation.
Well, it's a shame
to waste the opportunity.
I'm planting a bug.
This is the house
of Jean-Pierre Duman!
He murdered my daughter!
Come out and show yourself,
Jean-Pierre!
You cannot hide from your crime!
Our Haitian friend
just crashed the party,
and it looks like Monsieur Duman
is not too happy about his new guest.
Go and take care of him.
Now!
Go!
You have 30 seconds to get here
before Duman kills another member
of the Laurent family.
- You're driving my car back.
- No problem, Mike.
Come out, Duman!
Staying hidden isn't always
about sticking to the shadows.
Get in the car now!
In fact, if you're enemy's eyes
are adjusted to the dark,
there's no better place to be than
behind the brightest light you can find.
Why did you come?
- Why did you change your mind?
- Because that's the kind of guy he is.
He's an honorable man,
just like they told you.
He's just a little slow sometimes.
So...
- Where do we go from here?
- You go back to Haiti.
I am not leaving.
I am staying until it is done.
We have more experience
with this kind of thing.
I can help.
I found Duman
when no one else could find him.
Listen, Claude.
You've done your part.
Now let us do ours.
We'll get the guy.
How?
How will you do that?
By getting him to give us
evidence proving who he is.
Now, Mike is a very convincing guy.
Trust me.
You can count on him.
But you need to go home.
It's better for everyone.
You understand?
Yes.
I understand.
So, I asked around about
who might have brought your...
knife-wielding fake banker
into the country.
It was rough. I mean,
the Miami gun smugglers and the Miami
people smugglers, they don't get along.
And I've always been
more of a gun person.
- You're sure not a people person.
- You want to take over, Sam?
Oh, wait.
That's right. I forgot.
All your friends wear uniforms,
which makes you useless.
Hey, who found out about this guy
in the first place, huh?
Sam, Fi, just keep looking.
I intend to.
Good news on the Haitian front.
I got an angle on Duman.
His family used to do business
with Flintridge Industries.
It's a big multinational
that built all the prisons.
FBI's been nosing around them
for years.
You still in touch with those FBI agents
that were on the
"Follow Michael Westen
around Miami" beat?
Well, I could make a call,
but we didn't part on the best of terms.
Well, I think it's time
to mend some fences, Sam.
If you've spent time
working for the government,
you understand that it's a game
with its own rules.
If you want to make
the government work for you,
you have to understand
how the game is played.
An FBI agent might hate you,
but if working with you gets him out
of an assignment he hates even more,
you've got yourself a partner.
Hey, guys!
What's going on, huh?
She looks dangerous.
Cute, Sam. You know you're interfering
with a federal investigation?
What is she, like 80?
Did she steal somebody's dentures?
It's a racketeering case. Biggest
drug-smuggling family in South Florida.
Is she the boss?
Boss's grandmother.
Oh, man. You should check
the film speed in that camera.
At the rate she's moving,
you don't want to miss anything.
- What do you want, Axe?
- I come bearing gifts.
I have a peace offering.
A case that you guys can take back
to your office and be proud of.
You might even get a commendation
from the higher-ups.
This more crap like the stuff
you gave us on Westen?
I never lied to you guys about him.
Well, sure, I forgot some stuff.
What is it, Sam?
We've got work to do here.
He's an international fugitive
hiding in Miami under a new identity,
related to an investigation
you guys are already doing.
That's a whole different
department, Sam.
- Years in court.
- Listen, guys,
just check it out, all right?
We've had our differences,
but I know you FBI guys
bust your ass every day
to do the right thing.
I'll give you a time and a place.
Just check it out.
Watch out for granny.
You know, if you guys want me
to take her out, let me know.
All right. Good luck.
Being a fugitive takes work.
When you're being hunted,
hiding isn't something you can do
effectively without help.
So the best way to catch a fugitive
isn't to approach him as one
of the people hunting him down.
It's to approach him
as one of the people
who can help him stay on the run.
Ladies,
I'm terribly sorry, but I have a very
important meeting with Mr. Duman.
- Could you excuse us?
- Who are you?
Me?
My name is Owen Matthews.
But the more important question is,
who are you?
If you don't want to have
a very public,
very uncomfortable conversation
on that topic right now,
I'd ask these ladies to leave.
What do you want?
What makes you think
you can just sit at my table?
What gives you that right?
You know, I don't like to have
a meeting like this,
but when I find Jean-Pierre Duman
sitting in a restaurant
with FBI agents outside,
it is my obligation to sit down.
I've got a job.
The people I work for
pay me a lot of money
to make sure they don't land
in federal prison.
The people I work for
are very concerned right now
about the legal problems
of Jean-Pierre Duman.
I don't know what you're talking about.
My name is Luc Renard.
Luc Renard.
Call yourself whatever you like.
It doesn't matter what I think.
It matters what they think
because they're the ones
following you.
They're the ones who will be
asking you questions.
- This conversation is over.
- Just give me a few more minutes.
- You need to hear what I have to say.
- Speak.
The people I work for
were at Flintridge Industries
back when the company
was working with the Duman family.
I have been hired to sanitize
the record of those years.
- I am here to help you, Jean-Pierre.
- My name is Luc Renard.
No, it's not. Not yet.
There is still a trail that exists,
linking who you are
with who you were.
I am here to redirect
that trail, Jean-Pierre.
Until I do, everyone's in jeopardy.
You, my clients, everyone.
Let go...
of my arm.
I'm not the problem here.
I'm the solution.
Call me.
- Hey, Maddie.
- Hey, Sam! What are you doing here?
Mike said your ignition
need some work.
I'm already taking care of it.
I'm not helpless, Sam.
- You ever had your car broken into?
- No, mostly just broken.
Well, I told the police I want a list of
all the reported break-ins in this area
over the last six months.
Do you know these types of crimes
tend to cluster?
I read that.
Very impressive.
Don't pretend.
This is gonna take time.
I have a partner-stretching class
in half an hour.
Can you give me a ride?
- Sure, yeah, I can get you over there.
- Great!
'cause I need a partner too,
all right?
So you can hang out for the class
and then give me a ride back.
Partner stretching?
That sounds painful.
Boy.
Geez.
You all right?
This body was not built
for the hip-adductor stretch.
What? I got an inflamed bursal sac.
Got to ice it down.
Look, Mike, I think it's best
if you deal with your mom about the car.
... with the FBI.
They know my real name.
- Is that the bug in Duman's office?
- Yeah.
What do I pay you for?
To protect me,
to keep your eyes on things.
We found the license plate of the car
that was here at the gates,
- the man with the megaphone.
- So, who was he?
His name is Claude Laurent.
He's staying at the Golden Sunset motel
down by the beach.
Maybe he talked to the FBI.
Then why are we here?
Take me. Now!
Mike, Claude didn't leave Miami.
We got to get over there.
Before Duman sends him home
in a body bag.
Well, looky there.
Got our own little death squad
right here in the U.S. of A.
Hold on, Sam.
Stay here.
I'm pretty sure this is a two-man job,
you know, once the shooting starts.
I'm gonna see if I can keep
the shooting from starting.
Tell me you guys aren't this stupid.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- What do you think I'm doing here?
I'm here because
the guy in this motel
is pretty pissed at the Duman family
and causing problems for my clients.
But let me ask you, Luc,
what are you doing here?
Last we spoke, you hadn't even heard
of the Duman family.
- Get out of my way.
- You think that's gonna solve anything?
No, this is gonna solve nothing.
It is gonna cause us problems.
It's gonna make it worse.
Worse for me, worse for my clients,
- worse for you.
- Move!
You kill that man,
you validate everything he says.
That means news attention,
attention from the FBI.
I cannot let that happen.
You say you can change the past.
How?
Yes, I can change that.
I can take everything
that connects you back to Haiti,
every document,
every bank statement, all of it.
I can clean it and hand you back
a whole new you,
a Jean-Pierre Duman
who never has to hide again.
Now choose.
I can change your story...
Or end it.
Come to my house
tomorrow.
Your house?
Is that Jean-Pierre Duman's house
or Luc Renard's?
We will see.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You said you were going to leave town.
No, you said
it would be safer for me to go.
I said I understood.
And I do.
You put yourself in danger.
I...
do not want safety, Mr. Westen.
I want justice.
We said we would handle this.
Your daughter wants you
to get yourself killed?
That is what they said
when I wanted to go to the prisons
to find her.
That is what they said
when I wanted to go to the newspapers.
I failed her before.
I will not fail her again.
- You were not responsible.
- I was a coward!
But never again.
I will not leave
until Jean-Pierre Duman
is returned to Haiti
to face what he has done.
Working covert ops,
you learn to exploit weakness.
You manipulate greed, fear, pride
to make people do what you want.
But when you're dealing
with true believers,
those weaknesses aren't there.
All you can do is help
or get out of the way.
Wait.
You won't be safe at your motel.
I would like you to stay here.
It seems my people skills
are improving, Michael.
You found the guy who smuggled in
our fake banker from the Cayman Islands?
I found where he keeps his boat,
and he just arrived.
- Go easy on him, Fi.
- You're breaking up.
As a spy, it's usually best
to be unknown.
It allows you to adjust to any situation
and be whoever you need to be.
However, there are certain advantages
to being known.
A reputation can be a powerful tool.
- You leaving?
- I was just...
You just got here.
I forgot something. I have to go
get the thing that I forgot.
- Look, I don't want any trouble.
- But we haven't had a chance to meet.
- Fiona.
- Yeah, I know who you are.
You shot up Paco's boat, you set fire
to that guy's place up in Boca.
Well, they interfered
with one of my gun shipments.
But you wouldn't do that.
- We're friends.
- What do you want?
I need to know about a guy who came in
a few days ago, called himself Gustavo.
He liked to play with knives.
He's dead, Gary.
He fell off a parking garage.
I brought him in on a run-up
from the Caymans.
He paid cash. That's it.
You know, I got to tell you,
I'm a little disappointed, Gary.
I expect so much more
from my friends.
I brought him in.
I dropped him off at a storage unit.
I never saw him again.
A storage unit.
That's good.
You wouldn't happen to have the address
of that storage unit, would you, Gary?
Ma!
What, honey?
Have you seen dad's power sander?
What?
I've been to your place, Michael.
Your sander's better than your father's.
What, are you checking on my progress?
I've seen guided missiles
with simpler circuitry.
- Why don't you just let me...
- I can do this.
How's Sam?
Recovering.
Your stretching class
nearly killed him.
Well, what doesn't kill him
will make him stronger.
Believe me.
I know.
I don't think that applies
to cigarettes, ma.
You want to go
to the police with me?
They're gonna show me photos
of every burglar in the area.
No, I got to...
Michael, what is so important
that you couldn't do that with me?
I'm helping a man find justice
for his murdered daughter.
Well, if you need any help with that,
honey, you let me know.
I think I found the storage facility
where Gustavo kept his stuff.
Not too much damage done, I hope?
Oh, no. I didn't have
to lift a finger.
My reputation precedes me,
apparently.
You should think about moving into
one of these storage units.
Some have air-conditioning.
It would be a step up.
I'll keep it in mind.
Call the storage unit
and make some inquiries.
Let them know Gustavo passed away
and that you're coming by after-hours
to check on the unit.
I think I can handle that.
And you...
can say hello
to Monsieur Duman for me.
Most people have a hard time
letting go of their past.
The same guy who will burn a village
to the ground without a thought
often won't throw away
an old necktie
because it reminds him
of his high-school graduation.
If you know what you're doing,
you can hang him with that necktie.
Come in.
How does this work, what you do?
You give me everything you have.
Your passport, your medical records,
your financial records,
everything from the old days,
everything that ties you
to the name Jean-Pierre Duman.
And then?
We give you a new set of records.
The money siphoned from the government
turns into income
from overseas investments.
You get a new travel record proving
you weren't even in the country
when your enemies died in prison.
I handle it all.
My family left
the island of Haiti in a hurry.
These are some of the things
we thought we might need.
My father wanted to burn them,
but I thought perhaps someday...
You made the right choice.
No man should ever have to hide forever.
I'll take these and start cleaning.
Wait. First...
My father would like
to speak to you.
Your father?
- I've read that your father was...
- Was dead, yes?
Back in Haiti, we buried
another man in his place.
Oh, no. Daddy's still alive.
He's old-fashioned.
He wants me to sit in the house
and hide from the cameras,
but I told him about you.
He did not believe,
but I said that you would explain.
So...
This is the man
who can change the past.
I called some people I know long ago
at Flintridge Industries.
They do not know you.
Tell me.
Why is this?
Some big misunderstanding.
Let's clear it up, though.
Who did you talk to? Sam?
Because Sam is who I talk to.
Let me get him on the phone.
You know Sam.
He's got the big office
with the big windows,
south side of the building,
the glass doors,
you know, where you can walk
right out onto the balcony.
There is...
no such man.
Who are you?
Papa...
Wait, he said,
he knew about the prisons,
about Flintridge,
about the money, he...
How many times...
I tell you
to be careful?
But he warned me
that the FBI was investigating us.
Tell him!
It takes a lot longer to pull a gun
than most people think it does.
Almost five seconds, on average,
to draw and line up a shot.
Whether this is good or bad news depends
on what side of the gun you're on.
Get him!
The papers are gone.
They know we're looking.
- They'll have burned them by now.
- So that's it?
- Now we can do nothing?
- I didn't say that.
The papers were just a way
to get him to Haiti.
I assume there are people who can
identify him there without papers?
Yes, many people.
It's time for Duman to take
a trip back home. I like it.
Fi, can you get Duman away
from his bodyguards?
Sam, can you get us a truck?
For the chance to take these guys down,
I'll get us a convoy.
When you're abducting someone,
transportation usually
isn't the issue.
There is no trick to driving a truck
with someone hidden in the back.
The challenge is getting them
into the truck.
You can walk them in, drag them in,
or let gravity do the work
and drop them in.
Well, that should do it.
I just hope
it's not too comfortable.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
My guys in ties.
We checked out Duman.
Looks like the information you gave us
is good for once, Axe.
He's a real son of a bitch.
Thing is, there's not a lot we can do,
not without proof of who he is.
- Damn shame, really.
- Right.
But the thing is,
if you still want to help...
Come on, Axe,
you know as well as I do
we can't do anything official
unless we got warrants.
- The thing's got to go up the chain.
- Yeah, I figured.
But, unofficially,
what did you have in mind?
Spend time with corrupt, homicidal
third-world political figures,
and you hear a lot of self-pity.
What kind of man throws
his political enemies in prison
and tortures them to death?
Usually it's a guy who feels
so sorry for himself
he feels justified doing anything.
Killers, by and large,
are whiny losers,
but that doesn't make them
any less dangerous.
I do not want to be disturbed.
Understand?
Lie down on your stomach.
Close your eyes.
Most over-the-counter allergy medicines
contain mild sedatives.
In the right dosage,
they cause a pleasant drowsiness.
In the wrong dosage,
they cause dizziness, hallucinations,
and unconsciousness.
What was that?
My secret.
Mr. Duman?
Mr. Duman!
Mr. Duman,
open the door!
Mr. Duman, are you okay?
Mr. Duman, open the door!
Calm down.
Keep screaming all the way to Haiti,
you're gonna be hoarse for your trial.
I guess he can't change
the past after all.
You need to get going.
Sam has a friend with a boat.
He'll get you both back to Haiti.
You'll go now?
My daughter,
she would have liked you.
She was very brave.
Like her father.
What are those for?
Well, I thought I'd...
help you with the rewiring
of the car, if you needed it.
I did it!
Really?
You rewired the car by yourself?
I did it.
I went through some of
your father's old papers.
I found this diagram,
and I just put the wires back
where they were supposed to be.
It wasn't that hard, Michael.
I don't know what to say.
They caught them!
Teenagers breaking into garages.
I watched them come out
of Mrs. Hale's house.
I recognized the photographs,
and I called the cops.
You know why I think your father
wired the car the way he did?
'cause he thought if he was the only one
who could fix it, we'd always need him.
He'd be more useful, you know,
part of the family.
So, did you catch yours?
The guy who killed the girl?
Yeah, I did.
Good for you, sweetheart.
Hey, Sam,
your buddy's boat make it
back to Haiti okay?
Yeah, the coast guard kept clear,
thanks to you guys.
We have no idea
what you're talking about, Axe.
Yeah, right.
Well, I got a list of officials
who took kickbacks from
Flintridge Industries back in the day.
It's probably enough for you guys
to go after Papa Duman, too.
- A little bird told me.
- Little bird, huh?
He thought it would keep him
from being returned to the nest,
and I figured this could buy
some time away from granny.
Not exactly by the book, Axe.
Or I could send you a bouquet
with a nice card.
We'll find a way to use this.
Man, all this talking
makes me hungry,
but mostly thirsty.
Drinks on uncle Sam.
Come on, guys.
Cough it up.
Mojito!
- You call the storage place?
- The manager knows we're coming.
For the record, Michael,
I don't like this plan.
What plan?
You using yourself as bait
to see if whoever sent Gustavo
after you takes another crack.
That's what I would do.
You're gonna let me
back you up for real this time?
If you're right,
there's a good chance
he's waiting on a roof with a rifle
to take a shot at you.
That's what I would do.
I need him alive.
I need you alive.
You see anything, Fi?
Not yet.
Maybe it's time
we announced our arrival.
If you suspect
you're walking into an ambush,
searching for where
the bad guys are hidden
is probably going to get you killed.
Unless you get lucky
and find them in the first place
you look, you're dead.
If you can manage it, the best move
is to make it impossible to hide.
He's right above you.
He's on the move, Michael.
When you're in a foot chase,
the trick is to stay in visual contact
with whoever you're pursuing
until they run out of gas.
Of course, visual contact
doesn't do you much good
if you're separated by a 12-foot-high,
razor-wire-topped fence.
You should change
your workout, Michael!
You're not doing enough cardio.
Wait.
Did you see him?
Yeah. Turns out we've met before.