My name is Michael Westen.
I used to be a spy until...
We got a burn notice on you.
You're blacklisted.
When you're burned,
you've got nothing...
no cash, no credit, no job history.
You're stuck in whatever city
they decide to dump you in.
- Where am I?
- Miami.
You do whatever work comes your way.
You rely on anyone
who's still talking to you.
- A trigger-happy ex-girlfriend.
- Should we shoot them?
An old friend who used
to inform on you to the FBI...
You know spies, a bunch of bitchy
little girls.
- Family, too
- Is that your mom again?
- if you're desperate.
- Someone needs your help.
Bottom line...
as long as you're burned,
you're not going anywhere.
Previously on Burn Notice.
I don't know why you're willing
to meet Gilroy.
He sounds as bad as
the people who burned you.
He's worse.
This man is a freelance psychopath.
Westen.
I have to say,
I find you quite fascinating.
You and I have a lot in common.
- What do you say we work together?
- Tempting.
The gist is this.
You're to steal flight data
for every private plane flying in and
out of Miami for the next six weeks.
- What are you doing?
- I'm offering you a job.
You do it, you get paid money.
That's all you need to know.
This is another moment of truth.
Do we have a future together or not?
Double my fee.
Fair enough.
I may lose my seat at the table
if I don't come up with six weeks'
worth of private flight records.
- I was thinking the coast guard.
- That's a good choice.
This is every flight today.
Every day is exactly like that
except one day.
The 22nd.
Somebody needs a wide berth.
This is some serious black flight.
Originating in Chile,
fuel stop in Miami, destination...
Poland.
This is what
Gilroy is interested in.
You're a tad overdressed
for the jacuzzi, don't you think?
It's your card?
It's blatantly not six weeks
of flight plans.
Just the one that you want.
I need to know
what's going to Poland.
I suppose it's only natural
to be curious.
It's a weaponized plague
and a vaccine to match.
And they're worth a lot of money.
That wasn't so hard?
You're in?
I think you and I
have a bright future together.
- Learn anything?
- Only that he's a damn good liar.
When you need to locate a foreign
spy office, it's all about the food.
Spies like home cooking
just like everyone else.
Find out who serves
their regional delicacies,
tip the bartenders
and delivery boys well,
sand they'll usually tell you
who placed the big orders
on the last national holiday.
If some of these orders
head to an office with tight security
and scowling workers
with short haircuts,
you're in business.
You know,
some guys take girls to the beach,
concerts,
farmers' markets.
Ugly Polish
military-intelligence offices...
Not so much.
I'd rather be at a farmers' market
than bribing a bureaucrat
to tell me what's on a spy plane.
I have an idea.
Instead of working
with Gilroy the psychopath,
instead of sneaking around to figure out
what he wants from this plane, shoot him
- and be done with him.
- I've considered it.
But somebody hired Gilroy.
If I want to find out
what's going on and stop it,
I need him breathing,
and you know that.
There he is, right on time.
This guy Conrad
is the one to go after?
Low on the totem pole at work,
short on cash, bad divorce.
He's perfect.
We're meeting later today.
How's your Polish?
Rusty,
but his mom's from Moscow.
I approach him
as a Russian businessman,
buy him a few dinners,
and hopefully we end this quick.
Playing on people's loyalties
is an art,
especially when those loyalties
can be murky and malleable.
Poke around too much
and you'll look suspicious.
Sometimes your best move
is just to commit.
Thank you for meeting me.
It's better to do business
eye-to-eye.
What couldn't you discuss on e-mail?
Your office has information on...
covert flights
passing through Miami to Poland.
I need information on a flight.
- Why?
- I own planes.
I'm trying to get contract
on this flight.
It would be easier
if I knew what was on the plane.
It's a little thing
but worth a lot of money to me.
Russians.
Please let me get briefcase.
Commit too hard to the wrong side,
and there's not much wiggle room.
Instead of an instant ally,
you've just made an instant enemy.
Did you really think you could buy me,
that I would betray my country to you?
I was wondering why there is
extra security at office this week.
Easy, Conrad. Relax.
You sons of bitches
cost me everything.
My job in Poland,
my wife, my family.
Over there now.
You're going to tell me everything.
And then I'm going to cut out
your lying FSB tongue!
So much for an easy target.
You're seriously gonna try
to break into Conrad's office?
What else can I do?
I can't approach Conrad's co-workers.
What about a better angle on Conrad?
The guy who wanted
to interrogate me at gunpoint?
But we do know
that he can't stand the Russians.
That's our in.
Our in?
Are you volunteering?
I confess I am a little curious
about what a psycho like Gilroy
is so interested in stealing.
Probably best to approach
as American intelligence.
I'll need cash for this.
Deal.
Sam's has a job
he's been bugging me to take.
Fashion house that got robbed.
The lady who runs it needs some help.
- The pay is good.
- He talked to me about it, too,
but he sounded
more interested in the models.
Sam, you know that job,
the fashion gig?
So you're in?
Tell me that you're in.
- Is the money there?
- The money's there.
This lady is loaded.
You should see her fashion house.
It's in the Viceroy hotel,
and she is willing to pay.
All right, Sam, I'm in.
Thank you, Mike.
This covers Christmas,
my birthday present.
I'll swing by and pick you up.
When you're conducting surveillance
from a dusty cave in Afghanistan,
you daydream about air-conditioning,
swimming pools, and iced tea.
But spend a little time
waiting for a socialite
to hand off her tiny dog
to a canine beautician,
and that Afghan cave
looks a little better.
His usual pedicure,
of course the oatmeal shampoo,
and don't forget to rub his belly.
Colonel Peabody just loves
when you do that.
- Who doesn't?
- You're funny...
And cute.
My girlfriend said
you were a man of many talents.
You should do your own research.
Sam said something about a job.
One of your employees is stealing?
His name is Tim Hastings,
and we've been fighting a lot lately.
Now the numbers don't add up,
which means
that money's disappearing.
You would like us to find the money.
I need you to be discreet.
We'll keep it quiet.
How much do you charge?
Is $30,000 enough?
- That's too much.
- Please.
This might take a couple of days.
You won't be disappointed.
Recruiting an asset is about making
your target feel important.
Everything from the clothes you wear
to the location of the meeting
should communicate
how vital the mission is.
Wear the right outfit,
pick the right deserted bar,
and your target will be
ready to engage
in some good,
old-fashioned espionage.
We understand you were approached
by the Russians.
Are you from the Agency?
We have reason to believe there's
a Russian spy targeting your office.
He posed as businessman.
We need to figure out
who this spy is and what he's after.
Of course.
He asked me for information
about flight.
This flight is very important.
Security at my office has doubled.
We need to know.
I can't.
It's not my job to guard
this information.
It won't be easy.
You'll be taking a risk.
We know how important this is.
We will cover expenses.
Anything you need.
Some assets work for money.
Others believe in a cause.
The most effective incentive, though,
is a combination of the two.
All right.
Perhaps I can find this information.
But what about
this Russian cockroach?
I think we have a file on him.
Good.
Good news, Michael.
Conrad's enthusiastic.
I think we're gonna win
the Cold War.
He's in?
And then some.
Thing is,
I promised him the CIA file
on the Russian spy
he almost captured.
I think I'm gonna call your mom,
ask her for some pictures of you
in your military days.
Not my mom,
I don't want her involved in this.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
- You okay there, Mikey?
- I'm fine.
What's up
with this easy-money job of yours?
Bad news.
I had my fingers crossed that Tim,
the thieving vice president,
had a police record,
but he's either clean or careful.
Owns a gun, but it's registered.
No parking tickets, even.
You're smiling.
The fashion house is having a party,
and everyone's gonna be in the atrium.
That means one of us
can sneak into Tim's office
while the other one
keeps an eye on him
at the party.
Let me guess which job you'd like.
I'm partial to Isabella, models,
and mojitos, but I play fair.
I figured we'd flip a coin.
Call it.
- Heads.
- Cheater.
Quite a party.
Sam don't come?
He's using your access codes
to go through Tim's office.
If you're dealing with a operative,
there are hundreds of places
to hunt for documents.
If you're searching a jockey's office,
it's a far shorter list.
Before saying "in the cabinet", "behind
the bookshelf", "under the desk",
you've usually found
what you're looking for.
Which one's Tim?
I want to keep an eye on him.
- He's standing right over there.
- Now! Go!
Act casual.
Of course.
Let me have a word with you.
- Who is he talking to now?
- That's my business partner, Damon.
He started out designing,
and I was modeling.
This company's our baby.
I'm supposed to be at home
looking at his designs.
- Okay.
- I really should go.
You should go.
Go home. Do some work.
I'll call you later.
Spies are trained to keep track
of multiple conversations
at the same time.
Standing alone as you eavesdrop
is too obvious.
You need to engage in a cover
conversation near your target.
Hi.
Who are you wearing?
Black suit.
Love that dress.
I've never seen anything quite like it.
No one has, darling.
It's an Alexander Deschuno.
- I bought...
- Pure lip-reading
- takes years to master.
- Of course.
But confirming what you're hearing
by checking lips
is a much easier skill to pick up.
Don't get upset at me.
She said it.
You know what?
I'm gonna go talk to her,
- 'cause this is ridiculous.
- Good. I think that's a good idea.
You must visit my shop
in the design district.
Vintage Couture.
I'm talking classics.
That's great.
How's it going?
Jackpot. Found the books in his office.
Sent you a photo.
Good. Tim's heading over
to talk to Isabella at her house.
- She'll want to see that picture.
- Okay, good. Head over there.
I'll leave Tim's office
how I found it.
Ugly.
You were at the party.
- What are you doing, following me?
- I'm Michael. I work for Isabella.
- I think we should talk.
- I got nothing to say.
Save it for inside.
We found her financial records
in your office.
You were in my office?
That's illegal.
I should have you arrested.
It doesn't take long working
in combat situations before you start
paying attention
- to little things.
- Isabella?
Things that don't feel right,
like an open gate
or a pampered dog running around loose
often lead to much bigger things...
Oh, my god!
Isabella?
Jesus Christ.
What the...
... like a body in a swimming pool.
- We have to call an ambulance.
- Yeah, it's too late.
Or the police.
- Somebody already called them.
- Of course, knowing
something's wrong and being able to do
something are two different things.
Sometimes the damage
is already done.
That's my gun.
What the hell is happening?
You've been framed.
Somebody set you up.
No, no, don't.
Don't touch it.
Believe me.
I didn't shoot her.
Yeah, obviously.
- We got to go out the backyard.
- The backyard won't work.
There's a wall.
We'll be trapped.
I vote the backyard.
I told you.
We're trapped.
Want to head back?
Be my guest. Otherwise,
step on my hands.
We have to go get my car. If
they find it, they'll know I was here.
- They'll think...
- I know you want to chat,
but now is not the time.
Grab this.
Wrap it around your wrist.
Fall. When you do,
you'll be pulling me up. Ready?
1, 2, 3.
Easy-money gig?
I've been checking the scanner
since you called.
The cops are sending more units
to Isabella's house.
They found Tim's car,
but they didn't see you.
Whoever pulled the trigger must
have escaped before we got there.
We got to call the cops.
I'm gonna explain everything right now.
You know I'm innocent.
So...
if we go to the police,
- we can even take a lie-detector test.
- I know you're innocent?
You said you knew I didn't shoot her
back at Isabella's place.
You didn't shoot her.
Doesn't mean you weren't involved, Tim.
You had her books.
She knew you were stealing.
No, no, no, no, no.
Guys, listen to me, please.
All right, Damon was the one
who was stealing, all right?
I was trying to convince Isabella,
but he had her fooled.
I needed to find proof.
However the hell Damon did it,
there's no evidence in those books.
Every large money transfer
was authorized by Isabella, all right?
She signed them herself.
I kept telling her.
I kept telling her. She just...
- She believed everything he said.
- You think Damon killed her?
- I don't know.
- If he's behind, he had help.
- He was at the party the whole time?
- Yeah, he had the perfect alibi.
He told me to go to her house.
He...
said she was gonna fire me.
I've been fighting with her.
My car's outside her place.
The cops are matching ballistics
right now, even without your gun.
- He's got you pretty good.
- Pretty good? It's perfect!
I'm dead!
- It's over!
- It's not over.
If it was Damon,
someone pulled the trigger for him.
- We turn up the heat.
- Maybe find some evidence.
- We punch holes in their stories.
- You really think we can do that?
While I pay Damon a visit,
you're going to go pay cash
for a motel room,
and sit tight until we come get you.
I'll drop you in Hialeah.
We got snowed, Mike.
- We let Isabella down.
- She never saw it coming.
Whoever killed Isabella
sure did their homework.
When dealing
with a pathological liar,
don't bother looking for
signs of guilt.
True deceivers enjoy the lie.
They know how to look you dead
in the eye and usually shed a few tears.
If you wanna know
when they're lying, look for
the little smile that comes
when deceiving a roomful of people.
That bastard is giving quite
the performance.
He planned this whole thing.
Let's see how he does
when we mess with his script.
Thank you, officers,
so much for all the work you're doing.
Damon Belmont,
I'm Max, Isabella's Max.
- We need to talk.
- Excuse me?
We can talk in private or in public!
OK, we are on the clock.
We need to reroute all Italy shipments
through Paris.
Ministerial commission's
doing some search and seizures.
If you're planning on using
La Guardia...
Wait a minute, hold on.
First thing's first.
Who the hell are you?
She kept you in the dark.
I don't even know where to begin.
This is too big
to discuss this now.
Just suffice it to say I'm Max,
her other
business partner from L.A.
What the hell are you talking about?
I starch heroin
into Isabella's fabrics.
Production in Asia,
distro through Europe.
We're running about $4 million a week,
so we need to improve our communication
- here!
- When you make an approach as a spy,
you need to choose a role that puts you
in the center of the action
and explains
why no one's ever heard of you before.
Claiming to be a criminal
can kill two birds with one stone.
You throw around some names
and places and dates to confuse them,
show them some account books
to make real,
and make the dollar figures big enough
to play to their greed.
Did you say $4 million a week?
Now, about the cops
sniffing around outside...
If this little murder case
leads to a federal
narcotics investigation,
my new business partner
gets strangled to death
with his designer tie.
The police have this under control.
They already have a suspect.
One of our VPs.
He and Isabella
were fighting all the time.
- Did they arrest him?
- He's missing,
but they will find him.
They better.
Or they're gonna have another body
to investigate.
I shook the tree.
Let's see what falls out.
All right. I'll let you know
if Damon heads somewhere fun.
You want to look at
old pictures of Michael?
I realized just the other day
that I hadn't seen that many pictures
of Michael's past.
- Isn't that wild?
- It's wild.
So, have you kept any?
Sure.
Collecting dust in the garage.
Where's Michael?
You know, he's...
He's helping a friend.
But he was hoping
that we could borrow an album or two.
So, that's all there is to this?
You have so much time on your hands
that you want to just sit
and look at photos?
Sometimes, you got to take a break.
You hang on.
I'll go get them.
They've been in the back for a bit.
Couple of photos,
we get ears in that conversation.
And the cops will have
some new suspects.
Cover the front.
Like a blanket.
Contact microphones pick up
sound vibrations through walls,
allowing you to eavesdrop
on conversations.
Pair one
with a wireless transmitter,
and you have a bugging device
that doesn't need to be
in the same room as your target.
We have got a serious problem.
Damon, calm down.
What happened to your plan?
We weren't supposed
to see each other for months.
to call each other.
That's because things have changed.
There's this new guy.
Damon, enough.
Stop freaking out.
Everything's going to be fine.
I promise.
No one's gonna find
anything anywhere.
Christ.
- What was that?
- Interference on the speakers.
Is your phone on?
No, I didn't bring my phone.
I think someone's here.
Of course,
bugging a room from the outside
makes it impossible
to see potential pitfalls.
Just as a cellphone reacts
when it's too close to your alarm clock,
a room full of speakers can create
radio-frequency interference
if you're spying on someone
with a wireless signal.
- You think someone's here?
- Shut up!
Better get out of there, Mikey.
He's coming out the back.
{\RIC
DAMON'S PARTNER}
What happened to your plan?
We weren't supposed
to see each other for months.
We weren't even supposed
to call each other.
How's Tim?
Well, he's keeping his head down,
but he's a bit of a wreck, you know?
He's a boy scout, so he doesn't have
experience with this type of thing.
- We miss anything?
- No, just two guys having an argument.
Wonderful.
So, checked in
with my buddy at the station.
Cops are running
a full-fledged manhunt for Tim.
So, besides his car
at the crime scene,
they just found
half a box of bullets in his garage.
Predictably, perfect match
for the rounds that killed Isabella.
Damon and his partner
have been busy boys.
Speaking of partner,
here's the guy, Ric Pederson.
He's a club deejay.
He runs the shop during the day.
Nabbed a couple of times
for dealing ecstasy,
had an assault a while back.
Let me guess. No paper trail connecting
him to Damon or the fashion house?
Nothing I can find.
Today was probably
the last time they meet.
This is two guys
covering up a killing,
so they're not exactly itching
to break the law again.
Well, that is exactly
what we need them to do.
Law-enforcement cover IDs
are tRicy.
Pose as a lead detective,
and you'll have unlimited access,
but a single call to the station,
and you're caught.
You need to think smaller.
Nobody questions the credentials
of a lowly crime-scene investigator.
Excuse me.
You guys are still here?
Detective Parks said you guys were done.
Yeah, we were, but, you know,
that's how it goes.
You get some detective with a theory,
and the whole department does a 180.
- What are you working on?
- Picking up some samples.
Look, I can't really get into it.
Wait.
Please.
Isabella was a dear friend of mine.
Well, look, it's not like
I get the big picture.
I'm just a lab tech, but...
sounds like they're talking about
two guys working together.
- What?
- You didn't hear it from me.
I'll probably be back tomorrow
with a whole new assignment.
Looks like murder...
is in style this season.
- Who is this?
- It's your business partner, Max.
You said the investigation
was almost over.
You lied to me!
I did not. It was.
It is.
Then explain why the cops
are crawling around the fashion house.
Do I have to burn that place down?
It is not my fault
that the cops are idiots, okay?
This is an easy case.
They have Tim's car.
Everybody here knows he did it.
Well, I might be able
to find out some more.
I'm down in the parking lot.
Get out here now.
- Merry Christmas.
- My god. What are you doing?
I'm being proactive.
The cops questioned
Tim's neighbors, too.
Turns out
Tim has a little girlfriend.
She lives down in Homestead,
and she's going to tell me
everything we need to know.
Where is Tim hiding?
I haven't seen him in days.
I swear. We weren't even dating.
He was just helping me with my book.
- I told this to the police.
- Honey, I am not the police.
And you sure as hell
don't want me to get upset.
Where's Tim?
He made a deal
with some guy at the docks.
They're gonna smuggle Tim
to the Bahamas.
- Where's the dock?
- On 64th Street.
They're leaving at noon tomorrow.
He said something about calling the cops
on some designer who killed Isabella.
Don't shut me in, please! No!
- You killed her and didn't tell me.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
There is no evidence
that leads back to us.
I don't care what Tim says.
I used a partner.
There is no connection to me at all.
- It was the perfect crime.
- Perfect crime?
Except for one little thing...
Tim got away!
Don't worry. You're gonna just
black out in about 15 seconds.
Wait a minute.
We can get rid of Tim.
We can kill him tomorrow.
Now that you've found him,
we can end this.
We can make it look like he got killed
trying to escape the country.
The cops will close the case.
This whole thing goes away.
- You can pull that off?
- Yes.
All right, listen up.
I'm heading to the Everglades.
I'm gonna feed the scream queen
to the gators.
You're gonna follow Tim to his boat.
- You put two in the back of his head.
- Okay, two in the back of his head.
You idiots will be tempted
to touch everything.
Don't!
Just steal all Tim's money
and leave.
It'll look like he met his ride
out of town,
- and they robbed him and shot him.
- Done.
You do this right,
and the cops
will stop investigating,
and my stylish new
business partner, Damon...
Gets to live.
You won't regret this.
So devious.
He infiltrates American defenses
and then slips away.
Did you track down
the flight information?
Please tell CIA...
File is locked
in steel safe at office
with guard night and day.
Whatever is on this flight
is a big secret.
It's very, very dangerous, so,
it is impossible for Russian to get.
I wasn't supposed to tell you this.
One of your co-workers
is working for the Russians.
There's a mole in your office.
What?
You must tell me.
I will find this traitor.
Not yet.
It'll compromise our operation,
and we're running out of time.
If this mole makes his move,
if we find out what's in that safe...
This will not happen.
I will find file immediately.
It's tough to get someone
to compromise their values
in only a couple of meetings.
The only way to do that is to compromise
a few values of your own.
- How are you holding up?
- I was doing okay,
considering I've been sitting
in a motel room for three days,
but let me get this straight.
We're having
Damon and his partner...
- try to kill me.
- They won't actually succeed.
We just need them to get caught
by the cops looking guilty.
So we rented you a boat.
You walk in
through the parking lot here.
Mike and I are gonna be
covering you from the roof here.
When you get to the docks, hide.
The cops come in,
get Damon and Ric.
There are a lot of things
grieving co-workers do,
but hunting with guns for someone
on docks, not one of them.
Won't the cops arrest me, too?
And then you'll have the opening
to tell them the truth.
That plus your gun
dropped into Damon's trunk
is all you need
to blow their story apart.
Relax.
It's almost over.
There's Tim, Fi.
You got him?
They're our guys.
Time to call the cavalry.
Yes, hello, police.
I'm down on 64th, and I just saw
two guys taking guns out of their trunk.
I think they're headed
toward the docks.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
They're not exactly heading
toward the docks.
And they're not pulling out guns.
- Fi, what are they waiting for?
- I don't know.
Something's wrong.
- That bench wasn't there this morning.
- They moved a bench?
Sam, we got a problem.
Guys,
they've got a detonator.
They're not planning
on shooting Tim.
If we don't do something quick,
Tim is gonna be part of a big boom.
I'd say take it out,
but more than one shot gives us away.
Then I can't miss.
Mikey, do it.
He's getting close.
He's still alive.
- Fi, pick him up.
- I'm on it.
Get over here!
Let's go!
Fi, get out of there.
They're closing in.
Freeze!
Put your hands behind your head now!
- I tried to grab him.
- I know. We saw, Fi.
The guy panicked.
There was nothing you could do.
So, how far are we gonna take this?
Are we busting Tim out of prison?
Are we letting them get away
with killing Isabella?
Damon and Rick
just screwed up the plan.
We can use that.
If that's screwing up the plan, how come
they got everything they wanted?
From where I'm standing, they won.
They haven't won
until they know that they've won.
- Any chance they saw Tim get arrested?
- No, he went around the corner.
Sam, what's the time frame
on the cops announcing the bust?
Well, they're taking him in now,
processing him.
- I don't know, a couple hours, max.
- Then we have a couple of hours.
We drive Damon away from Rick,
get them to turn on each other.
We give the cops another killer.
Max? No, we shouldn't be talking.
What the hell happened down there?
Everything is handled.
Don't worry.
Listen, I'm gonna lay low for a while,
so don't call.
Everything is handled?
Everything is not handled.
- What the hell was that? We talked...
- Everything's fine.
The cops showed up.
There's no way he escaped.
No, he did escape,
for the second time!
No. That's not possible.
You know, I'm starting to think
that he is the only one around here
who knows what the hell he's doing!
You meet me at your office immediately,
or you're a dead man.
Wait.
- What are you still doing here?
- I can't talk to you. Police business.
It's okay.
We talked the other day, remember?
Look, I told you, buddy,
my higher-ups never tell me much.
There they are now.
- Yeah, this is Finley.
- Does Damon know Tim got caught?
I don't think so,
but I'm following up on your leads.
Looks like that tip you got
was a good one.
He's listening in, isn't he?
Yes, sir.
I'll be right back down there.
- Were you listening to my call?
- I'm sorry.
I just really want them to find
whoever killed Isabella.
- She was a dear friend of mine.
- Shouldn't be too long to wrap this up.
It looks like our killer's plan
is coming apart at the seams.
No one comes in here.
I said two in the back
of the head, Damon.
I tried to follow the plan
just like we talked about,
but Rick said using a bomb
was safer.
You feel safe now?
Tim's probably talking to the Feds!
I know.
I just found out he called the cops.
What's our next move?
Besides you and I and Rick,
who else knows all about this?
No one else. Trust me.
That's good, real good.
We just have one little thing
to close the loop.
Do not kill me!
Look, I know we messed up.
That was unfortunate.
I have an idea.
- Of course.
- We put this on someone else.
- You tried that.
- Another someone else.
My partner.
He's the one who killed her.
No, Rick will talk.
He'll blame you.
He'll take you down, too.
That gets messy, and I don't want
anything getting back on me.
- We could kill him.
- The cops will investigate his murder.
We'll make it look like
he killed himself.
Now, that's interesting.
How would you do that?
I'll write a suicide note
confessing to everything.
I'll even scatter some of
Isabella's files around his office.
- You can shoot him.
- Nope.
I'll get you a gun.
One of the many weapons
in the spy arsenal is sabotage.
Your enemy can't fight back
when their vehicles won't drive
and their weapons won't fire.
If you're handing a bad guy a gun
and you need it to jam accidentally,
fatiguing the trigger assembly
to break under pressure
is probably your best move.
It's undetectable,
so nobody gets suspicious
and nobody gets hurt.
Here you go.
It was stolen.
Serial number has been filed off.
- Which means it's untraceable?
- Completely untraceable.
Keep the car running.
- How we looking, Sam?
- Cops are on their way, Mikey.
What are you doing here?
Do you remember in the club when
you said everything would go perfectly?
You said everything
would go perfectly.
Calm down.
Everything is fine.
Everything is not okay!
Tim keeps getting away.
- Did you want me to get caught?
- What are you talking about?
Nobody is gonna get caught.
I can't go down for this.
There's no other choice now.
You son of a bitch!
I hope he's okay.
That's gonna bruise.
Police! Stop!
He shot my friend!
Arrest him! He's the killer!
Well, it took
a couple of days of explaing,
and my lawyer's trying
to get his head around the details,
but once Damon confessed,
the truth was out.
That's all you needed.
We're selling the fashion house
to a label in Milan.
Isabella hosted benefits
for a local pet-rescue center, so...
- We're donating the proceeds to them.
- Sounds good.
- Take good care of Colonel Peabody.
- Yeah, I will.
Hey, thank you for your help.
- Yeah, Fi?
- Hi, Michael.
- Any progress with Conrad?
- I just got a message from him.
He's bringing me
the flight information today.
- And your mother's been calling.
- I'll head over there now.
Fiona returned the albums.
But some of the pictures are missing
from when you joined the military.
I think someone
must have stolen them.
So mysterious.
We'll bring them back, mom.
I thought we agreed that from now on,
you'd tell me the truth.
This was a small job.
Fiona had to put together a dossier
to prove that I was a...
A Russian spy.
Just a small job.
It's kind of a long story...
Which I'll tell.
It wasn't anything dangerous.
Look, the last time you and I
went through this, it was hard.
I just don't like
seeing you get hurt.
So, what, you kept me in the dark
to protect me?
You know how it goes.
These things aren't so predictable.
Well, she left one behind...
because it was special to you?
No, it's probably 'cause
there's writing on the back.
It was special to me.
It's one of the few times you sent me
anything to tell me where you were.
Well, actually,
I had already left the country.
I wrote that so that
you didn't know where I was.
Well, then, in the...
grand scheme of things,
I suppose
we're making some progress.
- You want some iced tea?
- That'd be great.
This information
Russian spy is after
is much worse than I thought.
You found out what's on that flight.
Not what, it's who.
Who's on the flight?
There's no names,
but he is maximum-security prisoner.
This document is instruction
on how to deal with him.
I'd translate it for you, but...
If Russian pig gets his hands
on this envelope...
He'll never get it, my friend.
Thank you.
We were right.
It's bad.
It's a rendition
to a black site in Poland.
Somebody's high-risk enough
to be flown alone.
"Do not engage in conversation
with prisoner under any circumstance."
Sounds like a sweetheart.
This kind of treatment is reserved
for world-class bad guys, Michael.
I know,
and somebody wants my help
to break him out.