Break.
Red dog, right! Red dog, right!
- Twenty-six!
- Come on.
Hut, hut, hut, hike.
Gotcha.
Nice. Bring it in strong.
Nicely done. Nice hands, Davies.
Thanks. Nice throw.
You two,
all day with the compliments.
Nothing wrong
with positive reinforcement.
Ah, yes. I'm sure that Montana
always got all starry-eyed...
...every time Rice hauled one in.
Kind of hard to tell
with the helmets and everything.
Okay, 48 red. Break.
Forty-eight red.
Hut, hut, hike!
- Whoa. Whoa.
- Ah!
- Are you okay?
- Ow.
- Penalty.
- I think I did something to my wrist.
Let me see. Let me see.
Well, it's not broken.
You know, you may have sprained
your radial carpal ligament.
Oh, check you out. That's good for
somebody who's just auditing med class.
Maybe you should sub out,
put some ice on it.
With just 10 short yards
between us and intramural glory?
- Not a chance. Let's do it.
- All right, tough guy.
Nice win, kids. Don't forget,
cram session later, the cadaver lab.
Nobody leaves till we make
the endocrine system our bitch.
- Oh, I'm gonna be late for work.
- I'm heading that way. Want company?
- Yeah.
- All right.
You swear you've never played
flag football before today?
- It was my professional debut.
- You're a natural.
And a hell of an upgrade over Tyler.
I swear this guy's got hands like stone.
- Tru?
- That bag.
- What?
- It's just like the one...
...Dr. Kendall used to have.
Our family doctor
back when I was a kid.
Whenever he made a house call,
he used to bring a bag like that.
- You knew a doctor that did house calls?
- Oh, he was the sweetest guy ever.
He was the first person who told me
I should be a doctor.
You should buy it.
I'm not a doctor.
I'm not even a real med student.
Yeah, but you will be, right?
Come on. Davis is probably
wondering where I am.
- Ow.
- Are you sure you don't want me...
...to put some ice on that wrist?
Yeah, thanks anyway.
I'm gonna run to the clinic.
Doing some volunteering this afternoon,
so I'll get some there.
Oh.
Hey, Tru, is that you?
- Uh, yeah.
- Oh, hi. Hi, Jensen.
Hey. Hey, Davis.
Uh, so I'Il... I will, uh... I'll see you
at the cram session tonight.
Yeah, you will.
- See you later, man.
- Bye.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
that you two were...
That's okay. Nothing happened.
Of course nothing happened,
because I walked in...
...at the worst possible time,
which is my greatest talent.
Hey, uh, Davis, can I ask you
kind of a personal question?
Yeah, go ahead.
Well, after your wife died, um, how long
was it before you...? You know...?
Starting dating?
- Uh, four years.
- Oh.
But that had more to do with
social deficiencies than anything else.
Look, I know it's been a few months
since Luc died, but you know...
...if you're starting to have feelings
about someone, you should accept it.
It just... It feels soon, is all.
Well, it's always gonna feel soon,
whether it's today...
...or tomorrow
or four years from now.
Well, how do you know
when you're ready?
You fall in love again.
Freeze. No one move.
Help me, Tru.
Please tell me...
Please tell me that you can fix this.
Ooh, what happened?
Uh...
Well, Dad made some comment
the other day about my hair.
He said, uh, "You look a little scruffy
to be an employee of a law firm."
So I said, "Hey, why don't I make
the old man happy...
...get a real haircut for once."
You can't get one of those
for less than 6 bucks.
Come on, Tru. You're a girl,
you read all those fashion magazines.
There's gotta be something
you can do, Tru.
Uh...
There. It's perfect.
There's a new suit?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I say, you know, what the hell,
might as well go all out.
Get myself some new threads.
Do you like?
It's very professional.
No, let's not kid ourselves, shall we?
We both know what they call a guy
like me wearing a suit like that.
- The defendant.
- Oh, come on, Harry. You're not...
I was crazy to think I could change.
I can't change who I am.
Let's face it, okay?
Hey, you can change.
You changed your hair.
- I'm just saying.
- Watch yourself.
Not now.
Listen, I gotta go.
- Thanks for the hat.
- Totally. You're welcome. Bye, Harr.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Not funny. It's not funny.
Harrison, you forgot your...
Avery, what's wrong?
He's dead.
What? Who's dead?
Jensen.
Jensen's dead.
Help me.
- Tru, I'm... I'm so sorry.
- I'm not here for condolences, Davis.
I'm here to fix this.
Please, before he asks, tell me
what I need to know to save him.
Okay. According to the police report,
there was a holdup...
...and Jensen got in the way.
He was shot once in the chest
at approximately 5:30...
...and he died en route to the hospital.
Where was the holdup?
A consignment store on West Broadway.
He went back for the bag.
There was this doctor's bag
in the window...
...and he knew that I liked it,
so he must have gone back for it.
I guess I should've
seen this coming, huh?
How could you possibly
see this coming?
Typhoid Mary, remember?
Everyone I care about gets hurt.
Everyone I love is in danger
just for knowing me.
- You're wrong about that.
- Really?
Because my track record
says otherwise.
In the past four months,
I lost Luc and Jensen.
- Even Harrison died once.
- Yeah, but you saved him.
All that means is I'm one for three
when it comes to people I care about.
Tru? Davis told me the news.
I just wanted to let you know
how terribly sorry I am.
She's a grief counselor. I thought
maybe you would like to talk to her.
- We could go up to my office.
- I'm not going anywhere.
Not when he needs me.
Maybe we should talk outside.
Okay.
Maybe this wasn't such a good idea.
No, you were right to call me.
She's clearly in denial over his death.
Yeah, but still,
we should give her some time.
Okay. Whatever you think.
- Hey. I'll be upstairs if you need me.
- Okay.
- It's Jack.
- It's me. I've got news.
How long has she been in there?
Four hours.
I should go. Jensen's parents' plane
lands in 30 minutes.
Gosh, you should've seen me earlier
when I called them to break the news.
I couldn't stop crying.
Some doctor I'm gonna be.
I can't even talk about death
without completely losing it.
I wish I could tell you it gets easier.
I'd better go, um...
- Take care of her.
- Yep.
Hey, I was thinking,
if you were hungry...
...maybe you'd like
to go down to the diner.
Not now, no.
- I've got things to do.
- Are you leaving?
It's been four hours
and Jensen hasn't asked for help.
Neither have any of the other bodies.
So it's time to face the facts.
If I want the day to restart,
I have to find some new dead people.
- How do you plan on doing...?
- Last time I checked...
...there were five other morgues.
I'll jog to every one if I have to.
- Yeah, but, Tru...
- I'm not gonna lose him, Davis.
Hi. Um, takeout for Davis, please?
That was fast. Thank you.
Word has it our girl hit every morgue
in a 20-mile radius tonight.
No need to fabricate a story, Davis.
I know about Jensen, and I know
exactly what she's trying to do.
The poor girl just doesn't have any luck
with boyfriends, now does she?
Yeah, thanks to you.
Oh, the Luc thing.
Yeah, that was my fault. I admit it.
But Jensen,
that's fate sending a message.
Well, lucky for him,
Tru has a knack for changing fate.
It's different this time.
She's not God, Davis.
She can't pick and choose
the people that she wants to save.
- They have to choose her.
- Why are you telling me this?
Two reasons. First and foremost,
I happen to think you agree with me.
Deep down inside, you know
what she's doing is wrong...
...but you're too damn loyal
to say anything.
Second, she won't listen to a word
I say, but she might listen to you.
You are right about one thing.
I am... I am loyal to Tru.
And if she needs help saving Jensen,
then she'll get it.
Fine. Just don't say I didn't warn you.
I know I can help you. I just...
I need a little more time.
Any luck at the other morgues?
I'm sorry.
- You're tired. You should go home.
- I can't.
Not until a body asks for help.
Tru, that could take days,
or even weeks.
I can wait.
Well, maybe you shouldn't.
- What?
- Look, I know you care for Jensen.
But the fact is,
is that he didn't ask for help.
Maybe we should assume
there's a reason why.
I don't care if there's a reason.
I can help him, and I will.
Maybe you're not supposed to,
you know?
Maybe it's a violation of some rule.
Aren't you worried about consequences?
I don't know about you,
but I didn't get a rulebook.
I didn't get a rulebook either, but that
doesn't mean there aren't rules, Tru.
City Morgue.
Yes. Okay.
- Someone just called for a pickup?
- Yes, Third and Ogden.
I know that it's difficult...
...especially with someone
with your abilities...
...but maybe you have to accept
the fact you can't help Jensen.
Is that what your favorite grief counselor
told you, that I'm in denial?
Well, she's right.
I am in denial. I deny this.
And you know what? I can.
Excuse me, I have a pickup.
The deceased escaped...
...from a work detail
at 11:30 this morning.
- He was a prisoner?
- Yeah.
He was doing the roadside work
on Route 101 when he busted loose.
Used a fork to unlock the monitoring
device on his ankle, and took off.
We lost him for a couple of hours...
...then he stole this SUV,
and a chase ensued.
I guess we know how that ended.
Was anyone else hurt?
The dinner rush hadn't started yet,
so the patio was empty. Thank God.
He was the only casualty?
Now he's all yours. Enjoy.
Tru, look, l...
I know that you're angry.
But if this body asks for help
and your day restarts...
...promise me you won't forget
what we talked about.
Don't worry, Davis, I won't forget.
Come on, please.
Save me.
Now, that's more like it.
- Hello?
- It's me.
You're lucky you caught me.
I was on my way to the morgue.
Good. I've got
an assignment for you.
Please tell me they caught the guy
that did this to Jensen.
- This is gonna be a tough one.
- Tell me about it.
Okay. Two bodies, two "help me's,"
two totally unrelated deaths.
Guess we've got our work
cut out for us.
How did it happen? Did one body
ask for help and then the other?
- Did they ask at the same time?
- Same time. It was like in stereo.
By the way, I'm sorry about Jensen.
I know you two were getting close.
Look, he's still alive, Davis,
and I am gonna save him today.
Oh, I know, I know. I'm gonna
make sure that that prisoner...
...doesn't escape that work detail.
Actually, I was gonna hand the prisoner
off to Harrison.
Foiling the escape means talking
to police.
Harrison's got a little more experience
in that department.
- Well, all right.
- While I'm with Jensen...
...find a way to close the consignment
store where he was killed.
Right. Make sure the store's not held up
so no innocent lives are in jeopardy.
- Thanks, Davis.
- Is that it?
That's it. If I need anything else,
I'll call you.
- Sorry.
- That's okay.
Hi. Wow, where's she off to
in such a hurry?
Um, she's gonna go play flag football
at the park.
She's, uh, quite the athlete.
- Yo.
- Harry, I need your help.
Can it wait?
I'm about to get a haircut.
Just because Dad called you scruffy
doesn't mean you're due for a makeover.
- So I take it someone's day restarted?
- Sure did.
- The haircut?
- Does not end well.
- So, what do you need?
- A prisoner's gonna escape...
...on Route 101
in less than an hour.
Later today, he dies in a car crash after
a whole big car chase with the cops.
Unless I put a whammy on it.
One problem. I never got his name.
I need you to point him out.
How do I do that
without looking suspicious?
- Tru? Hey, Tru, are you there?
- You'll think of something.
Just give me a description.
I'll see what I can do.
Break.
Forty-eight red!
Forty-eight red! Hut, hut, hike!
Sorry. Adrenaline.
You're out one play.
Remind me never to piss her off, huh?
That was nice, Davies.
Didn't know you had it in you.
Sometimes you gotta fight dirty to win.
You, of all people, should know that.
Let's cut to the chase, shall we?
You're planning to save Jensen.
I'm here to talk you out of it.
Considering you only see the lives
of people who ask me for help...
...how'd you know he died?
- Oh, there's plenty of ways...
...to find out about a murder. Watch
the news, listen to the police scanner.
I relive days too.
You can save the speech
about preserving fate. I've heard it.
It's bad enough you save people
that do ask for help.
But saving people that don't?
You're taking things
to an entirely new level of bad.
This from a man who pushed a woman
with leukemia off a building.
There's a bigger picture here, Tru.
We may be on opposite sides...
...but each side has its rules.
You break those rules,
and the repercussions will be severe.
Not just for you, but for Jensen.
- Is that a threat?
- It's a guarantee.
Believe it or not,
I'm trying to do you a favor.
Let me put his death back on track
for both your sakes.
If there are rules, you broke them
when you killed Luc.
I'm willing to do the same
to save Jensen.
All right, keep moving.
- Can I help you?
- No, sir.
But I can most certainly help you.
You see, I'm with a law firm.
Davies, O'Donnell and Cross, downtown.
I'm sure you've heard of us.
No? Well, anyhoo, um...
Well, one of my less-fortunate clients
is currently serving a 10-year stretch.
Now, he's looking to shave some time
off his sentence by ratting out...
...one of your guys who's planning
an escape this very work detail.
- Which guy?
- Don't have a name, just a description.
Late 40s, light hair, and he's got
a tattoo on his arm that says "Mandy."
If you don't believe me,
just check the guy for a fork.
He's gonna use it to pop
that little LoJack gizmo...
...they've got on their ankles there.
Wait right here.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
Everything's under control.
- The prisoner's safe?
- They're shaking him down as we speak.
- Thanks, Harry, you're a lifesaver.
- Tell tell me something I don't know.
Drop it. Drop it!
Put it on the ground.
Now, get your keys out.
Take that thing off of my leg.
Now!
- Is that your car?
- Yeah. Actually, it's, uh...
- Come on!
- Aw, hey.
Trust me,
you don't wanna do this, pal, okay?
- Listen...
- Get in the car!
- Okay, man. Let's talk about this.
- Now.
Come on, move it.
Let's go!
Nice win, kids. Don't forget,
cram session later, the cadaver lab.
Nobody leaves until we make
the endocrine system our bitch.
Hey, I've got my car today,
so if you need a ride to the clinic...
How'd you know I was volunteering?
Avery mentioned it. She said you
were that much closer to sainthood.
Davis gave me the afternoon off, so
if you think you could use extra hands...
Yeah, always. I just have to warn you...
...it's mostly lab work and filing.
It can get pretty boring.
Believe me, I could use
a little more boredom in my life.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Okay.
Whew.
So, um, what are you doing?
The cops are gonna be looking
for this car. I gotta ditch it.
Right. Right, I hear you.
Good idea.
I'm sorry about the gun, by the way.
I hope I didn't scare you too bad.
Aw, I've been there, done that.
Actually, I hate guns.
- Never held one before today.
- Wow.
Could've fooled me.
Thanks for the ride, kid.
This your suit?
- Mind if I borrow?
- Just happy to be alive here.
It's all yours.
Okay, okay. Think, Harrison.
Think, think, think.
Okay, what would Tru do?
Here's the thing. No one is more
hooked up in this town than I am.
So whatever you need
to get a clean getaway:
- Fake IDs, passports, bus tickets...
- No, thanks. I take care of myself.
Ah, but you might change your mind.
In which case, I should stick around.
No. I won't, and you shouldn't.
I hear you. I'm hearing you.
But call me crazy, but l...
You know what I can't figure out?
I let you go, and you're not going.
Look, here's the thing.
Let's just say I'm not a fan
of the cops.
Besides, you seem like a decent guy.
Now, really,
let me do something, please.
Try to keep up.
You know,
you are an extremely weird kid.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
This is Harrison. Leave a message.
Hey, Harry, I haven't heard from you
since this morning.
I wanted to make sure you're okay.
Call me.
- How you holding up?
- A couple of paper cuts.
- But otherwise, good.
- Nice.
Jensen, I need you to take
a medical history in Exam Room 1.
- Patient's name is Stan Kirby.
- Stan Kirby. All right, no problem.
All right, Mr. Kirby, let's get started.
Well, you're not Mr. Kirby, are you?
I somehow seriously doubt
that you're here...
...because your sciatica is acting up.
It's good to see you again, Jensen.
Likewise, Jack. You mind telling me
why you're here?
First of all, let me apologize
for sneaking in like this.
I only did it because I didn't
want Tru to know I was here.
- Because...?
- Because I need to talk to you alone...
...about Tru.
She's been keeping something
from you. Something important.
And I think you deserve
to know about it.
Okay.
You see...
...she lost someone close to her
not long ago.
- It was a boyfriend. His name was Luc.
- I didn't know that.
Of course you didn't.
Tru didn't tell you.
I can't really say I blame her.
I mean, "My last boyfriend died"...
...isn't exactly a mood setter.
But the thing is...
...Tru never got over Luc.
And since he died, she really hasn't
been able to get close to anyone.
- She keeps sabotaging herself.
- What do you mean?
Haven't you noticed
how secretive she is?
How she's always running off but will
never tell you where she's going?
Look, I think Tru is a fantastic girl,
and I can tell she's crazy about you...
...and that's why I'm here.
I don't wanna see her screw this up.
I appreciate that, Jack. I do.
There's other things you need
to know...
...but I'm late
for another appointment.
Why don't you meet me later on,
and I'll tell you everything.
For Tru's sake.
Okay.
Great. I know the perfect place.
I don't believe this. I'm five minutes late,
and you give my appointment away.
- Just spell your name for me, sir?
- Stan Kirby. K-l-R-B-Y.
That's odd. I checked a Stan Kirby
into an exam room 10 minutes ago.
Well, I'm Stan Kirby.
So whoever you checked in,
it wasn't me.
And, uh...
This isn't the supply room.
Which is why they have a big sign
that says "Exam Room 1."
Sorry.
Um, that's all, Mr. Farmer. The doctor's
gonna be with you in a few minutes.
All right.
I thought the nurse asked you
to see a guy named Kirby.
Oh, well they must have given me
the wrong chart.
- It happens all the time here.
- Oh.
Um, listen, I'm gonna get going.
I'm gonna see you later?
I was thinking we could get coffee,
kill some time before you hit the lab.
Uh, I wish I could,
but I gotta go to the library...
...for books for the cram session.
- You should just come to the morgue.
Davis is like the endocrinology king.
He's got tons of books on the subject.
Yeah, I don't wanna put him out,
because he...
Trust me, he'd be happy to help.
Really.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go.
I've gotta tell you, I've seen my share
of fugitive-from-justice flicks...
...and, uh, not one of them had a scene
where a guy on the run...
...would stroll through suburbia
in broad daylight.
- Somebody I need to see.
- Oh.
- Hello, Barbara.
- Travis.
I thought you were still...
- What the hell did you do?
- You can read about it in the paper.
Oh, you're unbelievable.
- Tell me where the wedding is. I'll go.
- No.
I'm gonna go
to every church in this town.
- You know I will.
- Don't you dare, Travis.
Don't you dare ruin this day for her.
Who is he?
- Uh, hostage.
- Yo.
A hostage.
You brought a hostage to my house?
The place looks great, by the way.
David a good provider?
Better than you.
You look great, Barbara.
Touch that car
and I'm calling the cops, Travis.
No, no, no. No cops. Bad idea.
Last chance, Travis.
The cops will hunt Travis down
like an animal.
Now that he's got wheels,
there could be a chase.
Innocent people could get hurt.
Just give me some time to...
Let me talk to him...
...try to get him
to turn himself in peaceful.
That car better come back
without a scratch on it.
You have my word.
I'd like to report a stolen vehicle.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah. I'm just, uh, waiting
on a phone call from Tru.
The two of you are thick as thieves.
Yeah, we have
a pretty unique relationship.
Oh. As in, you used to go out?
- No. No. God, no. No.
- What is it?
Um...
There's, uh, something about Tru
that you don't know about.
No one knows it except me.
- It's okay.
- She's not properly insured...
...to drive the morgue van.
It's my fault, really.
I didn't do the paperwork.
Hi. Hope we're not interrupting.
No. No, no, no. Uh, have you...?
Have you...? Uh, Jensen, this is Carrie.
- Hey. Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
We were hoping maybe
we could borrow some books.
Yeah. Any particular subject in mind?
- Got something for me?
- You should know...
...that the boyfriend's here
at the morgue.
He's supposed to meet me.
He may need prodding.
If you see an opportunity
to seal the deal...
- I will take it.
- Good girl.
So I take it
that was your ex back there?
Yep.
That whole wedding you mentioned...?
My daughter's. Mandy.
So that's why you busted loose today
so you can go.
So, what the hell are you gonna say
to her when you see her?
Nothing.
Mandy doesn't know I'm her father.
Her mom married David shortly after
I started my sentence.
Mandy was a little baby.
They never told her about me.
- That's pretty cold, don't you think?
- David gave her a good life...
...with all the things that I couldn't.
I'm grateful for that.
That's why all I want is a glimpse
of my baby on her big day.
After that, I'm gonna turn myself in.
- What's that?
- It's receipt from a florist.
I found it under the seat.
It's a big order.
It's going to St. Augustine's today.
Guess we know
where that wedding is, huh?
So, uh...
...if you don't mind me asking, uh,
what did they lock you up for?
I was a getaway driver.
Bank heists, mostly.
I started when I was about your age.
So before you got busted,
you ever think of going straight?
You kidding me? All the time, kid.
I learned pretty quick, though,
a man can't change what he is.
Oh, of course he can.
I know it's hard to believe...
...but, uh, I was kind of a...
A small-time scammer.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah. I'm serious.
And now I got a 9-to-5, and, uh...
Well, I'm kicking much ass,
I might add.
You'll slip up.
Guys like us always do.
Damn it. Hold on.
And last but not least,
Ampoule's Modern Physiology.
Oh, thanks. They're, uh, heavy. Good.
Can I have a word with you, please?
I'll just read these...
...books.
- Is something wrong?
- You tell me.
- You didn't check in with me.
- I didn't know I needed to.
I left you three messages.
You didn't call me back.
- Because I had everything under control.
- Two people asked for help last night.
That is a lot to handle, even for you.
If you're trying
to keep something from me...
...whatever it is, I can handle it.
I just wanna help.
Two people didn't ask for help
last night, Davis, only one did.
- And it wasn't Jensen.
- I don't understand. Jensen didn't die?
I'm saying he didn't ask for help.
Look, I'm sorry I lied.
I didn't think that you'd help me
if you knew the truth.
Tru, look, at the end of the day,
you're the one saving lives. I get that.
And if you ever needed me,
I'll always be here for you.
Especially today, Tru.
- Hey.
- Oh, is Davis...?
- Outside talking to Tru.
Oh, great. I'm telling you,
once those two get started...
...it takes forever for them to stop.
Really?
You look like there's someplace
you need to be.
Yeah, I'm supposed to meet somebody,
but I don't wanna interrupt, you know?
Oh, don't worry about it.
I'll just tell them you had to run.
I think there's another reason
you're keeping the truth from me.
I think, on some level, you think
there's something wrong with this.
That there's a reason
that Jensen didn't ask for help.
You think fate wanted him
to stay dead?
- Well, don't you?
- I don't give a damn what fate wants...
...because fate obviously
doesn't give a damn about me.
How can you say that,
you, of all people?
Look at my life, Davis.
Look at everything I've sacrificed
to do this job...
...to answer this calling.
I've lost friends, family, sleep, sanity,
you name it...
...all in the name of fate.
And how does fate repay me?
It takes the people I'm closest to.
First my mother...
...then Luc, and now Jensen.
I'm sorry, but enough is enough.
I'm not giving up Jensen
without a fight.
- Where's Jensen?
- Oh, he left.
He said he had to meet a friend.
Jack. It's gotta be.
The consignment store.
Jack must have sent him back.
But I talked the owner into closing it.
I even watched him lock up.
Well, knowing Jack,
he found a way to reopen it.
He was shot once in the chest
at approximately 5:30...
...and he died en route to the hospital.
All right, I'll try and cut him off.
In the meantime, keep dialing.
See if anyone's at the store.
- City Morgue.
- He's not here, Davis.
- The store's still closed.
- I figured as much.
- No one answered when I called.
- Jack's got him, I know it.
Yeah, but the question is where.
I know where Jack took him,
to the crash site.
Glad you could make it, buddy.
I saved you the best seat
in the house.
Well, might as well. Do you mind?
- I had a feeling it was you.
- Whatever you did, it didn't work.
That prisoner still escaped.
Now the police are after him.
Oh, yeah, well, I kind of got a front-row
seat, if you know what I mean.
- You're what?
- I'm in the car with the guy.
- How?
- I'd love to tell you the whole story...
...but I'm a little busy right now.
- I'm five minutes away.
Keep him away
from the Third Street Café.
That's where he lost control
of the car.
Oh, good news.
We're nowhere near Third Street.
Uh, you know that whole thing
about being nowhere near Third?
Scratch that.
Hey, before we get started,
would you like a beer?
- Yeah, actually, that sounds great.
- I'll take care of it. I know the bartender.
She always gives me free drinks.
You stay right there.
I can't seem to shake these guys.
Okay, how about we call it a day...
...and pull over for the nice policeman.
What do you say?
- My daughter's wedding. Not a chance.
- Okay.
Harry?
Harry, are you there?
Oh, God, watch out!
Oh, God! God!
Oh.
Harry!
Get out!
Jensen!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah. Thank you.
What the hell are you doing here?
Call it fate. Just wait here.
I'm gonna go check on the driver.
Are you all right?
Yeah, just a couple bumps and bruises.
Nothing to write home about.
We should get you to the hospital,
get you checked out.
No, no, no. Maybe later.
Something me and Travis gotta do.
She is something, isn't she?
Yeah, she's a stunner.
No doubt about it.
The question is...
...is she worth it?
- What do you think?
Uh, time for me to go, kid.
Here's hoping I never see you
around the yard.
Like I told you...
...I'm not that guy anymore.
You know, I think you're right.
I thought you might wanna know
we're two for two today.
Come on, Davis, you gotta admit...
...I saved Jensen,
and the world didn't end.
So it's okay to admit
that you were wrong.
I still think my concerns were valid.
But, having said that,
if I were the one reliving days...
...and Carrie had died on day one,
I probably would've done the same thing.
Hmm.
Oh, and speaking of Carrie, um...
...I think it's time
we tell her the truth.
- About?
- About what we do here.
- We don't even know her.
- She... You know, I care about her.
And I think she would be
an important asset.
You know,
if she had known about Jensen...
...she wouldn't have let him
leave today.
Davis...
Okay. All right. I don't...
I didn't think you'd go for it.
I just had to ask.
Well, I gotta go. I'm gonna be late
for my study session.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, there she is.
Nice job.
- Nice to see you, too, Av.
- Thank you, Tru. Seriously, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
I sort of let it slip
that you saved my life today, so...
If he had died...
I checked school policy...
...we all would've gotten A's for this
semester, which would've been nice too.
- Yeah.
- I'm just saying...
- Hey, you okay?
- Oh, yeah.
I think I sprained something
when you tackled me.
- Oh, God, I'm sorry about that.
- It's okay. Believe me...
...I prefer it to the alternative.
- Can I take a look?
- Yeah, go ahead, please.
- Ooh.
- What?
That's weird.
I'm getting this serious case
of déjà vu right now.
What, you feel like
we've done this before?
Yeah, but, like, exactly this.
Me, you, the wrist, everything.
- That's crazy, right?
- Crazy, yeah.