Is something wrong?
Lex, what's happening?
Lex, where are you going?
Come on, Lex. Pick up.
Lex!
- Lex!
- Stay there.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
Stay away from her!
- What are you doing?
- I'm preparing him.
No!
People have been buying airline tickets
long before computers.
So glitch or no glitch, there has to be
some record of us being on this flight.
Can I talk to your supervisor?
Actually, let me talk
to your supervisor's supervisor.
Lionel.
I thought you'd be on your way
to Washington by now.
Come in.
No. Unfortunately...
...thanks to the airline company's
cutting-edge computer system...
...the flight was canceled.
That's easily solved. The Luthorcorp jet
is free to take you this afternoon.
No, no. I can't continue
taking favors from you.
Don't make this personal, Martha.
It's business.
It's the way to cope
with an emergency.
The important thing
is that you get there for the meeting.
It's a national education summit.
There will be over 3000 people there.
I'll be wearing my inexperience
like a badge.
Well, experience is often overrated,
especially in Washington. You...
You've got integrity, Martha.
It's one of the rare qualities...
...you possess.
Hey. I was beginning to think
I was living with a ghost.
Not that it would be the first time.
- Lana, are you all right?
- I'm so scared, chloe.
- I knew he was getting in too deep.
- Who?
Lex. They took him.
Tell me what happened.
We were in a field...
...and there was this flash of light
and Lex was taken.
Taken where?
Into the black ship I saw
in the meteor shower. It's back.
Do you think Fine had something
to do with this?
Fine was there.
He said that he was preparing him.
I can't believe I let this happen.
Lana, you can't blame yourself.
It's my fault he was involved
in the first place.
Chloe...
...what if he's dead?
What, do you mean "taken"?
I mean, ripped from the earth
and sucked into the sky.
His abductor did leave
a calling card in the field.
From Lana's description,
it sounded a lot like Zod's symbol.
Lionel's drawings
warned of Zod coming.
Maybe it's actually happening.
What is happening? I don't get it.
I thought that Zod was trapped in that
Phantom-prism other-dimension thing.
That's what I'm worried about.
Fine knows I would not
release Zod willingly.
He's obviously changed strategies.
- So then Lex is part of plan B?
- Which means Lana's in the middle.
I know what you're thinking. She used
to come to you. That's different now.
And you know what?
That was your choice.
I don't feel like I've made any
of the right choices.
I've been so angry with Jor-EI,
I didn't listen to his warnings.
It seems every time you turn to Jor-El
something bad happens.
What if he's just trying to protect me?
What if he's trying
to protect all of us?
Hello, my son.
I had no other choice
but to come here.
I know you are still angered
by the loss of Jonathan Kent.
- He was my father.
- I am your father.
Pain is part of life, Kal-EI.
But you cannot let it blind you.
Fine has returned...
...to release Zod.
What am I supposed to do?
Fine is merely an extension of the craft
that can regenerate in any form.
If Fine is part of the ship,
then who is controlling it?
It's not just a ship.
It's the Brain InterActive Construct.
An advanced technology that will
stop at nothing until its master...
... Zod, has been released.
No, there's gotta be
some way to stop him.
There is one way.
Zod was imprisoned
in the Phantom Zone...
... for crimes that led to the
destruction of our planet.
Zod killed you.
And your mother.
And our entire race.
Just as he will do on Earth.
I won't let that happen.
Zod's physical body was destroyed...
... to prevent him from escaping
the Phantom Zone.
He can be freed if he finds a body,
a vessel to inhabit.
You must find the human vessel
and destroy it.
No matter who it may be.
I've heard of fathers demanding
a lot of sons...
...but asking you to commit murder?
- That goes way beyond domineering dad.
- Chloe, I'm not killing anyone.
Well, I hate to say this, but disobeying
Jor-El has had grim consequences.
There's gotta be another way.
Okay, well, what about...?
What about the vessel?
I mean, why doesn't this Zod guy
come fully composed?
All Jor-El told me was that Zod's spirit
would possess a human.
This is the Zod whose hobbies include
mass destruction and world domination?
Chloe, what if Lex is the vessel?
That's why the ship took him.
Lana said that Fine was preparing him.
If I'm right...
...then I gotta kill Lex.
You know, Clark...
...in certain cultures, when a father
presents his son with a knife...
...it represents a rite of passage.
How do you know this is from Jor-EI?
The glyphs on the blade,
they're Kryptonian.
What does Jor-El want you
to do with the dagger?
Clark...
...I came here to find you.
When I woke up this morning,
I found this.
Must have written it in my sleep.
It's another warning from Jor-EI?
Tell me what it says.
"Sacrifice the vessel."
The vessel? I don't understand.
Let me help you.
Clark, please.
You don't have to
make this decision alone.
There's nothing you
or anybody else can do.
Don't underestimate me, son.
Jor-El wants me to kill...
...the person who will be the vessel.
Zod will possess a human form.
Destroy Earth just as he did Krypton.
But I can't kill anyone.
You of all people should know that.
Clark...
...the real test of a hero...
...is knowing when the greater good
will be served by an evil act.
To save the Earth...
...the cost of one life
is the price that must be paid.
Even if that life is your son?
Lex is the vessel of Zod.
He was abducted this morning.
Out of Maier's field.
Maier's field, you say?
Lex?
Son.
- Are you all right?
- Everything feels different.
Clark told me they'd taken you.
What happened, son?
Are you hurt?
You tried to warn me about Fine,
but I didn't listen.
You never have.
No matter what I give you...
...the things you've always wanted
were beyond your grasp.
This time you've overreached yourself.
Did you come out here
to lecture me or to help me?
It's too late to do either, isn't it?
You made a deal with the devil.
He always comes to collect.
Lex.
Dad, are you okay?
What have they done to you, Lex?
What have they turned you into?
Lex.
I thought I'd never see you again.
It's okay.
What happened?
I've been given a gift.
Your hand.
There's not a scratch on it.
You need to know the truth about me.
They've turned you into one of them.
I have their abilities...
...but it's still me.
Lana...
...I'd never lie to you.
How could I keep
something like this...
...from the person I care about most?
Lex.
I overheard Clark and Chloe talking.
Now that you're back...
...Clark...
...he's going to try and kill you.
It's fear, Lana.
My father's infected him with it.
Like he used to do to me.
Clark can't stand the fact
that I'm different now.
- There's someplace I need to go.
- Take me with you.
No.
Hey.
Know that I'll always love you.
You're talking like
we'll never see each other again.
That's your choice.
If you want us to be together...
...meet me on the roof
of LuthorCorp Plaza.
I'll be there tonight.
You found Lex.
Yeah. He was...
...in the field. He's... He's not...
He's changed.
What happened to you?
Everything Fine has been doing is...
It was meant to prepare Lex.
Somehow he now possesses
the same powers as you, Clark.
You can't begin to imagine
what he's gonna do with them.
Why do you say that?
He wasn't raised like you, clark.
I taught him to survive at any cost,
to be completely ruthless.
Maybe that's what'll save him. There's
still a part of Lex that can fight this.
You see that in him
because you want to.
There's always been a dark force
at work inside him.
I don't wanna hurt Lex.
If Zod is as evil
as you believe him to be...
...it's easy to understand why
he chose Lex to inhabit as his vessel.
What about Lana?
Someone very close to you.
She's a big part of his life right now.
Be careful what you
decide to do, Clark.
Which one are you willing to sacrifice?
If you'll be 20,000 feet above the
ground, might as well do it in luxury.
Well, enjoy it while you can.
If our flight hadn't been canceled,
I'd never feel comfortable doing this.
Well, you might wanna start
finding your comfort zone.
This isn't gonna be the last time
you're invited to fly the Luthor skies.
This is just a friendly gesture.
Right.
Look, another friendly gesture.
Card's for you.
Lionel can be a very generous man.
I'm not interested in a relationship
with Lionel or anyone.
- Really?
- Yes.
Or are you just worried
about how Clark would take it?
Okay. Enough said.
Lex!
- You'll never find him.
- Lana, he's in trouble.
I suppose you're gonna tell me
you came here to help.
- I don't want anything to happen to him.
- Like what?
Having your best friend
turn against you?
I heard you and Chloe
talking about killing Lex.
I don't know how you knew
he was gonna come back different...
...but I guess
I shouldn't be surprised.
Lana, you can't stay with him.
He's not what you think.
He told me his secret and it doesn't
change the way that I feel about him.
What's happened,
it doesn't scare you?
I am not going to abandon Lex.
Neither am I.
Listen, Fine would not give him powers
without expecting something in return.
It's not over, Lana.
I can help him
if you tell me where he is.
How do I know you won't hurt him?
- You know me.
- No, I don't.
You have all these different sides to you.
I can't tell if any of them is the real you.
If you have ever
really cared about me...
...tell me what's happening to Lex.
- Lana, please.
- You don't trust me.
You've never trusted me, have you?
I don't know how
I could have ever loved you.
And to think her loyalty
could have been yours...
...if you'd been honest with her.
I'm sure Zod
will cherish her allegiance.
Leave Lana out of this.
It's your own fault, Kal-EI.
You were supposed to be the vessel...
...but your father's spirit
was too strong in you.
If you'd have released Zod
the first time...
...they would have been spared.
I'm giving you one more chance.
Nothing could make me
release a monster like Zod.
Except maybe your one weakness:
Humans.
They're so fragile. They'll never survive
without their technology.
No matter how crude.
Take that away, and they'll devolve
back to the animals they really are.
And you can't save all of them.
I'll never do what you want.
Then it begins.
Enjoy the show.
Chloe! Chloe?
- What's going on? Streetlights are out.
- You tell me.
It's already reached Metropolis.
- You know where it started?
- Smallville.
Fine did something
to one of Lex's computers.
Thought if anyone could figure out
what it was, it'd be you.
It's an electronic virus and it's
spreading faster than I can track it.
After it scaled every firewall and
knocked down all the communication...
...it's infecting the infrastructure.
All because of me.
I refused to release Zod.
Now Fine's trying to force my hand.
Well, he's definitely playing hardball.
Elevators, gas mains, subways,
the entire city is shutting down.
I mean, it's like Y2K on acid.
The complete and sudden collapse
of the city's infrastructure...
... has caused havoc and panic
throughout Metropolis.
Reports of scattered looting
and violence are beginning to surface...
Clark, if this continues...
...every major city in the world
is gonna be infiltrated.
Clark, there's no use.
You can't save everyone.
And I can't release Zod.
Well, what if Jor-El was right?
I mean, what if the only way
to stop Zod and stop Fine...
...and stop all of this
is to just destroy that vessel?
I don't wanna leave you here.
You have to.
Clark.
I don't know
if I'm ever gonna see you again.
Hello, Clark.
I heard you wanna see me.
You'd tell me if I had drool
all over my face, wouldn't you?
- What time is it?
- It's about 10 minutes to 9.
And we aren't there yet?
We should be strolling down
Pennsylvania Avenue now.
You're right. I lost track of the time.
We must have hit
some strong headwinds.
More like gale-force.
We should've landed an hour ago.
Lois, relax. There are a million reasons
why we could've been delayed.
I'm sure everything's okay.
I might have flunked geography
but the last time I checked...
...the East Coast,
it didn't look like this.
So, what did you decide, Clark?
Are you gonna kill me?
You can't blame me for this, Lex.
You did this to yourself.
Oh, come on, Clark.
You love it!
Since that day on the bridge...
...you've always seen yourself
as my savior.
The one thing that would pull me
off the dark path I'd started.
See, that's why you cling to the idea
that there's still some good in me.
You don't wanna face the fact
that you might have failed.
Or maybe I can't believe someone
would have so little willpower.
It's hard to compete
with the willpower it takes...
...to kill one of your best friends.
How did you know
I was gonna come back like this?
You don't realize
how much danger you're in.
I used to think you had
this strong inner core.
You were so virtuous.
And yet you lie...
...all the time.
To me, to Lana,
to all the people who cared about you.
What kind of sick person
would do that?
If you thought this friendship
was so doomed...
...then why did you fight to keep it?
- Because I wanted everything you had.
The family, the inconspicuous life,
the loyal girlfriend.
Well, at least I walked away
with the part you loved the most.
You're not yourself.
Or maybe I finally am.
I knew there was something
different about you.
Do it, Clark.
Let's see if you're really
your father's son.
What have I done?
You've opened the portal for Zod.
Lex?
You have your father's eyes.
Hello, Kal-EI.
- Where's Lex?
- Lex is dead.
Why are you here?
For the same reason as anyone
who'd been imprisoned like a beast.
Revenge.
Your father banished me
to an eternal hell...
...trying to save a doomed race.
And in the end, the only survivor
of his pathetic crusade...
...was his son.
Then this is between us.
- These people did nothing to harm you.
- No.
But you feel no pain greater
than to see others in agony.
I won't let you destroy this planet
like you did Krypton.
You don't have a choice...
...unless you join me.
I'll never join you.
Well, I hope that's a decision
you'll be able to live with forever.
Open the door!
Lois, I'm not feeling well.
- Neither am I.
- I can't breathe.
Wait a minute, Mrs. Kent.
The air pressure. We need oxygen.
Open the door!
Mrs. Kent.
Mrs. Kent. Wake up!
You have to stay awake.
Where do you think
you're going, huh?
No!
Help! Please let me in!
Help!
Get in.
Ron, get us out of here.
- Oh, my God!
- Ron!
Mr. Luthor!
No!
Lex.
You know...
...part of me thought this was
another one of your tests.
You've been abandoned and betrayed
so many times...
...how could you know
that I wouldn't be next?
Well, I'm not. I'm here.
In spite of everything
that's happening out there, I'm here.
I don't know what it is
you and I have...
...but I'm here
because I wanna find out.
Do you?
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
www.tvsubtitles.net