This engine won't start.
I don't know how to fix it.
You're home from school early.
Yeah, well, I sort of dropped out
for the rest of the semester.
Clark, how could you do that?
You need me here.
There's too much work.
- But...
- Mom, it's done.
The governor's office
wants to see me.
Something about
your father's senate seat.
It's the last thing I wanna do,
but I have to go to Metropolis.
While I'm there, I...
I thought I'd drop some of your father's
clothes off at the homeless shelter.
Maybe it's too early
to get rid of them, but I...
It's so hard seeing them in the closet.
I can still smell his after-shave
on the shirts.
You should take a look, see if
there's something you wanna keep.
No, I'm sure there's someone
who can use it more than I can.
I think your father would have
wanted you to have this.
L... I remember the day he taught you
how to tell time with it.
You should wear it.
Well, if you're going to Metropolis,
you should go before it gets too dark.
- Hey, lady, need some help?
- No. Thank you. I can manage.
Don't do that.
- No!
- Nice bling, red.
That was my husband's.
Crazy bitch.
Slit her throat.
I've been looking for you.
Hey, back off, freak...
...or I cut her.
Don't worry, you're safe now.
Hey.
The muses weren't helping me
with my astronomy paper...
...so I thought I'd come by
and talk you into a frothy cappucc...
I was on my way to the hardware store.
I gotta pick up some supplies.
Clark, are you sure it can't wait?
Because I was really hoping
we could talk.
Clark, I understand.
You and your dad were really close.
- Lana...
- You don't have to open up to me.
You just can't keep
bottling this up inside.
Thanks for coming by. I really have to go,
the hardware store closes in a half-hour.
I'm sorry.
No, you're angry.
And you should be,
but don't keep hiding behind it.
Trust me, I've tried.
I know you're trying to help.
Thank you,
but you don't have to worry about me.
I'm fine.
Mom? What happened? Oh, my God.
I was dropping off the clothes,
these two guys came out of nowhere.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm all right.
Clark, somebody rescued me.
But not before they...
They took your father's watch.
I just spent half the night
down at Metropolis PD.
Not one person can tell me
about who mugged my mom.
No, I've got that covered.
My mole at the precinct...
...said that he'd fax me the police report.
So your mom actually saw the vigilante?
Barely. She left
just before the police got there.
There have been rumors about her
flying around Suicide Slums for weeks.
But I couldn't get a confirmed eyewitness
until your mom.
Now this has front-page news
written all over it.
- The vigilante is for real.
- This is great, Chloe.
I let my mom go down to Suicide Slums
alone, she gets mugged...
...and you're cashing in on it.
Clark, I was just trying to help.
You don't have to bite my head off.
I should've accepted the watch
like my dad would've wanted.
I couldn't even look at it.
Now all I can think about
is getting it back.
I'm sorry.
- They are today's obits.
- Thanks.
I saw your car out front.
Looks like old habits die hard.
Mrs. Kent asked me to close up
for the night.
They're going through a lot right now.
Look...
- Lana...
- Lex, it's okay.
You already said, "I'm sorry."
Yeah, well, it means more
when it's coming...
...from someone who's not drunk.
It seemed you were pretty upset
with Clark that night. Things better?
None of that matters anymore.
I just wanna be able to help him
through this difficult time.
How's he doing?
Lex, we both know what it's like
to lose a parent. He's devastated.
Yeah, I tried to get ahold of him,
but he doesn't wanna see me.
Well, as much
as we both wanna help...
...I think all we can do
is really just be there for him.
He's... He's very lucky
to have you in his life, Lana.
But when the time comes
for you to lean on someone...
...you know I'm always here.
All right. Now, this
is what I need, Clark:
A catchy moniker
for our new crime fighter.
"Miss Death-Wish." No, that's lame.
"Dirty Harriet."
No, that's too derivative.
I got it. I got it, Clark.
So your mom said that she
swooped down from the heavens.
So how about
"The Angel of v engeance."
- Chloe, police report.
- Right. I'm sorry, clark.
Once I go Woodward and Bernstein,
I get carried away.
I'll go check the fax.
I heard you were asking around
about me.
Something tells me a front-page story
could be a little bad for my health.
- Let it go, comprende?
- Hey, what are you doing?
Stay out of my way.
I'm one of the good guys.
- Clark, are you all right?
- Yeah.
I guess round one
goes to the X chromosomes, huh?
How about that costume,
how cool was that?
A little over the top.
Police reports?
Oh, yeah, of course. You know,
chokehold and everything aside...
...I gotta give the girl props
for patrolling the street.
Now, I just wonder if we're dealing
with natural-born-ninja territory...
...or if she's just another
garden-variety meteor freak.
- Whatever she is, she's got issues.
- Come on, Clark.
You can't tell me
that you have never crossed...
...any boundaries
to protect your identity.
Looks like I'm gonna have to get
to know her a lot more than I wanted to.
No leads. Your Angel of Vengeance
might be the only one...
...who can ID the guys
who mugged my mom.
After the way she chop-sockied
you tonight...
...I wouldn't hold out
for an invitation to tea.
We might not have to.
- No! No. Please help. No. No. Help!
- Give me the purse.
No! Help me. Help me!
You know what? We've taken
this show on the road all over town...
...and this obviously isn't working.
Because you're not
screaming loud enough.
Clark, I have freaked out every alley cat
within a four-block radius.
Look, let's just go one more time.
One more, come on. Take it, come on.
- Ready? Go.
- No. Help. Please.
- Come on.
- No. Please. Help.
You gotta give it some feeling,
some passion.
Stop!
You again?
- I didn't come here for a fight.
- Well, I'm not wearing dance shoes.
If I'd known you wanted a duel,
I would've brought my own pistol.
Oh, no, this isn't a weapon, Lex.
This is a piece of history.
A gift
from a grateful overseas partner.
That's right, a duel would require you
to face your opponent.
You prefer to strike
when they least expect it.
Oh, yeah, the activity this morning
in the Asian markets.
Is that what you mean? I heard.
Brokers were buying up shares
of LuthorCorp...
...like they were half-price potstickers.
Come on, Dad...
...you're just using the chinese.
I know you're the one leading
the Apex Group's hostile takeover.
And I didn't think
you were paying attention.
I'm pleased to see
that is not the case.
Wipe that smug smile off your face.
I won't let it happen.
How you gonna stop it?
Leveraged recapitalization?
Your campaign directly compromised
Luthorcorp's assets.
There's not a single bank
that will give you the money you need.
So, what are you gonna do
for an encore?
- Put a bullet in my head?
- Don't be so melodramatic, Lex.
I would never fire this. It's priceless.
You know, General MacArthur wore this
when he came back to the Philippines.
What was it he said, son?
"I have returned."
Don't get ahead of yourself, Dad.
You haven't taken the beach yet.
You want a show-and-tell, meathead?
Why don't you go first.
I don't know.
I was born this way.
You're lucky. The worst part
is remembering...
...what it was like to be normal.
- But then how did you...?
- Turn into a freak of nature?
When I got a heart transplant,
six months ago.
A girl dies in a meteor shower...
...and suddenly I get a souped-up
second chance. You have no idea...
...what it's like to know that
someone's life has been traded for yours.
That's why I carry this.
So I'll never forget.
I'm kind of allergic.
To a rock? Okay, whatever.
So I guess you and Sullivan have
all the dirt you need on me now...
...to write your little article.
I'm not here to expose you.
I need your help.
You saved my mom earlier tonight.
Some guys were trying to mug her
outside the Eastside shelter.
- They took a watch.
- Sorry...
...but there are people down here
who need a lot more help...
...than finding some missing Timex.
Belonged to my dad.
You lost him, didn't you?
And you can't say goodbye.
- What makes you say that?
- Because I've never been able to.
My mom and I were coming home
from my gymnastics meet...
...and these two guys mugged us.
I didn't even feel the knife
go into my heart.
When I looked up...
...I saw her lying there.
And they walked away laughing.
Is that why you do this?
She dedicated her life
to this group, Acrata.
They fought the gangs, the dealers...
...even the suits who wanted
to tear down our homes.
She was this little woman...
...but she was a badass.
It's not fair.
It's not fair to have someone like that
just ripped out of your life.
I can help you get the watch back.
But that's not
what you're really after, is it?
- You want justice, just like me.
- Can you tell me where they are?
They're part of
the Thirteenth Street Gang...
...but the guy you want
has gone underground...
...and his gang's all packing 9 mils.
But I'm in if you're in.
- Mrs. Kent, what are you doing here?
- Looking for Clark. Have you seen him?
Yeah, about an hour ago,
he left me holding the bag, literally.
Hey, you know, I heard what happened.
It's good to see that you're okay.
Don't worry about clark.
I'm sure he'll pop up soon.
- Or blur in, or whatever it is he does.
- He's been gone all night.
He's not answering his cell phone.
It's not like him.
There's a lot
that's not been like him lately.
He's trying to find those guys,
isn't he?
Chloe, I know you have a lot
of secrets you have to keep...
...but this isn't one of them.
- He feels really guilty about the watch.
- And me.
Well, I think he's willing to feel anything
except for the pain of saying goodbye.
But that doesn't keep it
from being real.
The more he refuses to go through this,
the worse it's gonna get.
I know.
I'm trying to do everything I can...
...but I don't think denial's
that unusual.
But clark is. He's gotta take
all those emotions out somewhere.
- Or on someone.
- And when he does...
...I'm afraid of what might happen.
We both know what he's capable of.
Yeah, but clark's always managed
to keep things in perspective.
It's just that Jonathan
was always there.
He always knew what to say.
Mrs. Kent,
I don't think that he was the only one.
When he died...
...I really didn't know
if I could keep the secret by myself.
It's good to know you're here.
Thank you.
He's gonna be okay.
We won't let anything happen to him.
That's the guy he was with.
Sorry, this isn't a costume party.
Whoa there, Jethro.
Maybe you should put the brawn away
and let the brains handle this.
Looks like somebody got the best of you.
We're looking for that friend of yours.
You know, the one
with the serpentine-facial graffiti.
- So why you talking to me?
- Because he's gone kind of AWOL.
- And he's got something of mine.
- We want it back. Tell us where he is.
You know what? Just tell
him we're looking for him.
What are you doing?
So much for brains winning out.
Snake, it's Ono. That chick
showed up with some boy scout.
They said to tell you
they're looking for you.
Can you check the last number
he dialed?
Well, I guess my go-to status
has been reinstated.
For a while there,
I thought maybe I'd been replaced...
...by the leather-clad version.
- You always change in a phone booth?
- The janitor was in the bathroom.
I thought the glasses were fake?
Are you kidding? I'm blind as a bat.
Besides, the mask doesn't look
so good with glasses over it.
Acuvue to the rescue.
Those were some impressive moves
you used to jack that phone.
- I could use a sidekick more often.
- I'm not a sidekick.
We should find a reverse list.
Yeah, and then maybe we can
just bypass the log-on page.
Got it covered.
That's why you work here, isn't it?
Nothing happens in Metropolis
without going through the Daily Planet.
Way to put the pieces
together, Brenda Starr.
Unless Snake's real name is Beatrice
Krauss, I think he's using a stolen phone.
Can you pull up the outgoing calls?
Looks like he's a proud
supporter of Fantasy Fone.
More importantly, deep-dish pizza.
Yes, I'd like to make
an order for delivery.
My number's 555-0138.
1436 Stanton Street.
Yes, that's my address. Thank you.
Looks like it's time to call the police.
- No.
Clark, don't you think you're
a little too close to this?
Chloe, if I don't use my abilities
to stop lowlifes like this...
...what's the point in having them?
I really don't think
that you should be go...
Don't worry. I'll keep an eye on him.
How is it that trash like you
is still alive, and my dad's dead?
Better leave now or you'll be dead too.
You stole my dad's watch.
I want it back.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- I don't have it anymore. I sold it.
- It was my dad's.
What are you waiting for?
He deserves to die.
- Lf you won't kill him, I will.
- No.
I'm sorry. I have to do this.
You.
Is this the knife
you used to kill my mother?
No. He's not worth it.
You didn't have to kill her.
She gave you all the money she had.
It wasn't about the money.
I was told to make it look like a mugging.
- It was a hit?
- She was in their way.
Whose? Who hired you?
The suits. Those Apex suits, the ones
that are tearing down the slums.
I want a name.
Andrea.
All I know is, the guy that hired me
got a call from Lionel Luthor.
Don't.
No!
I see you've already moved in. Don't you
think that's a little premature, Dad?
The board doesn't meet
on the bid until morning.
I value efficiency, Lex. You know that.
I hear you ran
a hectic phone bank today.
Must be humbling to pull all those strings
and find out they're attached to nothing.
Especially when your father's
the one holding the scissors.
You left the company vulnerable.
Then I suppose
I should be thanking you.
If you hadn't tried to take it,
someone else would have.
Exactly. What good is having a family
if they don't watch out for each other?
On the off chance...
...that unshakable family loyalty fails...
...there's always those Luthor closets
to rummage through.
All right. Let's skip the prologue, Lex.
What ancient skeleton
do you think you've dug up now?
Well, it's not quite a skeleton yet.
More like a freshly laid corpse.
I wonder
how Martha Kent would feel...
...if she knew you had a secret meeting
with her husband right before he died.
Now, a transgression like that would...
...test the virtues of even
the most forgiving woman.
What do you want, Lex?
I hope you enjoyed your stay.
Sorry it was so short.
Snake?
You're a dead man.
You kicked people
out of their homes...
...so you could develop
Suicide Slums for profit.
My mother stood up to you,
so you had her murdered.
No one escapes justice, Luthor.
Not even you.
Listen to me. We're not as different
as you might think.
Like you know anything about me.
I do. I grew up on the same
treacherous streets that you did.
I lost my parents, just like you did,
to a senseless crime.
It wasn't senseless. It was calculated.
Andrea. Stop. Let the police do their job.
If he's guilty, he'll pay.
If your father was murdered...
...and you were face to face
with his killer, what would you do?
What if you're wrong?
What if he had nothing to do with it?
Andrea, listen to him. Listen.
Look, I know what's in your heart.
It's anger. I feel it too.
But killing him, taking his life
is not gonna change anything.
- Yes, it will.
- Andrea, stop. Think about your mother.
Is this what she would
want you to do?
Let him go.
Let him go and everything will be okay.
I killed a man.
And I know you, Clark.
You could never let me
walk out of here.
It's time for you to be the real hero.
Exceptional woman.
Grossly misguided.
She's been through a lot.
Why do I think you saved my life
for her sake, not for mine?
Whatever the reason...
...thank you, son.
Martha, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
It's all right.
I was somewhere else.
Yes. These days must be difficult
to get through. I understand.
When my wife... When Lillian died, I...
I thought I'd never
be whole again. I...
It takes a long time
to let yourself heal.
Well, I'm doing the best I can.
I hear the governor has asked you
to take Jonathan's seat in the senate.
I haven't even told clark about that.
How do you know?
I make it a point to know things. I...
I wanted to find out how you were.
I'm not sure I'm going to
accept the offer.
If you came by to sway me
one way or the other.
No, you're quite capable of making
that decision on your own. I...
I'm only sorry
that they burdened you with this.
You've got so much
to deal with now, Martha.
I know that Jonathan leveraged
a good part of the farm.
- That was his decision.
- That was his pride.
So he could pay back
the campaign contribution I made.
I can't accept it.
Jonathan and I let politics
and money come between us.
I don't want that
to happen to us, Martha.
If you need anything...
...please, I'm here for you, always.
As a friend.
Hey.
I found her desk like this
when I got in this morning.
I called her home, her cell.
Looks like she pulled
an Amelia Earhart.
She's never gonna let
anyone find her now.
I guess exile's the price
you have to pay...
...when you play judge,
jury and executioner.
Yeah.
Clark, what really happened out there?
I should have listened to you, Chloe.
You tried to warn me.
I had my hand
around that guy's throat.
And I thought that if I just kept
squeezing the life out of him...
...then it would make
everything right again.
God, Clark.
- But you didn't?
- No.
What made you stop?
My dad's voice.
This is gonna sound weird,
but l... I could hear him.
He was the one who always kept me
from going over the edge...
...when I was too close.
It's too bad Andrea
didn't step back in time.
I think Metropolis could really
use someone like her right now.
Do you think you could ever
do what she did?
Play the mild-mannered reporter by day
and a crime fighter by night?
Honestly, I'm kind of hoping
I can find a way...
...to not have to hide who I really am.
I searched every pawnshop
in Metropolis for it.
I can't believe you found this.
Lana...
I'm sorry for the way I've been acting.
I know I should be able to move on,
but life without him...
...doesn't feel real.
It's like you're frozen...
...and the whole world's
going on around you.
No matter how many people
wanna be there for you...
...you end up going through this alone.
It's not like he ever let me take
the easy way out either, huh?
Put it on.
It looks great.
Your dad would be really happy.
Here, go that way.
Make a figure eight.
Please be careful.
Don 't worry, sweetheart.
It's gonna be fine.
That's what you always say.
- That way?
- Hang on tight.
What, are you kidding?
This young man 's a man of steel.
Look at him.
- Make one more turn.
- Where you going?
I thought I'd show our son
the back 40.
After all, it's all gonna
be his one day. Right?
Clark, wave bye to Mommy, son.
Bye-bye.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
www.tvsubtitles.net