I brought gloves and a scarf,
like you said.
- I was afraid you weren't gonna come.
- Well, to be honest...
...I don't think that a mystery date's...
...exactly what our relationship needs.
That's why I called.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God. Your heart's racing.
Because I'm terrified.
What's going on?
Lana, the way you've been...
I can tell by the way you look at me
that I'm losing you.
- Clark...
- And it's not your fault.
There's something I should've shown you
a long time ago.
I don't remember
this place ever being here.
How'd you find it?
It was left here for me.
For you?
I rehearsed this like a thousand times.
Lana, what I'm about to show you...
...may change the way you feel
about me.
Clark, whatever it is, it's okay.
It's okay.
Do you trust me?
Oh, my God.
When you asked me if I believed in
life on other planets...
...you had no idea
how ironic that question was.
I'm from a planet called Krypton.
But you're just like everyone else.
This isn't the first time you've done that,
is it?
How many times have you been there
when I didn't know it, saving me?
It doesn't matter, Lana.
I couldn't let anything happen to you.
And no one knew.
There were so many days
I wanted to tell you.
What makes today any different?
I want you to know who I really am.
Will you marry me?
- That's the worst joke I ever heard.
- Come on, you liked it.
I didn't.
I thought you were gonna meet us
at the polls.
I kinda took a shortcut.
Get this loaded up
before the victory party.
I appreciate your confidence,
but I haven't won anything yet.
Mom, Dad, I have something important
to tell you.
I told Lana everything.
What?
Right before I proposed to her,
in the fortress.
So, what did she say?
I asked her not to tell me.
It's a lot to put on her at once.
Clark, have you really
thought this whole thing through?
If I was ever gonna risk sharing
who I am...
...I want it to be with her.
I'm proud of you, clark.
I know this has been weighing
on you for a long time.
Just like with this election,
any big decision has risks with it.
I guess it's just hard...
...Iooking over at your son
and realizing you're talking to a man.
A man who doesn't need
his father's advice anymore.
I'm always gonna need you, Dad.
Any exit poll results for the 39th yet?
Yeah, I know it's early,
but patience isn't my strong suit.
Okay. Call me back.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
I try to keep the junk food
so I can't reach it.
But some days
it's easier to reach than others.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm glad you're here.
The decorating committee can't bunt.
Can you grab that for me?
Okay, spill it.
It's nothing.
Three guesses: Tall, dark
and bumbling.
It's just...
Okay, what would you do
if you thought...
...you knew someone well...
...and it turns out that there's...
There's this whole other side to them?
Well, that depends.
Are we in arms-dealer territory...
...or are we talking The Crying Game?
Nothing like that.
Then I guess the question is...
...does it change the way you feel
about him?
Maybe.
Look, I don't know what's going on.
But I would be lucky to end up with
someone as honorable as Clark someday.
- You told Lana your secret?
- Yeah.
Okay.
God, and after all those years
of me yanking on your closet door...
...what's the reason
for this sudden coming-out party?
It was only a matter of weeks
before she broke it off.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
You guys are, like, meant for each other.
You're Kansas' Ken and Barbie.
Except they broke up, which is weird.
- You're fired!
- You can't fire me! I quit!
Well, I think I was pushing Lana
to the point...
...where I don't know
we could have come back from.
And I love her too much
to let that happen.
So how did she take the whole
"E.T. Phone home" thing?
Not sure yet. I was hoping
she would've called by now.
Hello?
No, this isn't Mr. Fu's Noodle House.
Sorry.
Clark, if Lana cares about you
as much as I know she does...
...I seriously doubt
anything's gonna change.
One thing might.
I haven't gotten my answer yet.
I asked her to marry me.
Well, that one wasn't on the Doppler.
Not even a blip.
I know what you're gonna say.
That we're too young,
there's a reason I hadn't told her...
- ...that there's too much at stake...
- That's funny...
...because what I was gonna say is,
there are few people...
...who really know what they want...
...and are willing to risk everything for it.
If anyone deserves to be happy, Clark,
it's you.
I thought I'd see you at the party.
I know.
But then there'd be all those people.
Do I look different to you now?
Clark, you look like the same
handsome guy I've always known.
Handsome as in,
"I want to spend my life with you"?
Or handsome as,
"I'm gonna let you down easy"?
As in, "Yes, clark, I'll marry you."
- Can you fix this necklace?
- Thanks. Let me get this for you.
One more district and you'll have
a new commute to Topeka.
Whatever the outcome, sweetheart,
the only victory that's changed my life...
...was when I won your heart.
Mr. Kent. Mr. Kent, sir, this way.
Man of the hour, Jonathan Kent.
- Thank you.
Mom, Dad...
Mr. And Mrs. Kent...
...I know that this is as much
a surprise for you as it is for me.
Lana, we couldn't imagine clark
spending his life with anyone but you.
We hope that you have
as many happy years as we have.
- Thank you.
- Let me see this.
- Everyone. Everyone.
- Ah, it's beautiful.
I just got the heads-up
from the newsroom.
And, ladies and gentlemen,
you are looking at our new senator.
We can call the tightly contested
Lowell County Senate race.
Jonathan Kent's been
elected to the Kansas Senate...
... in a staggering upset over
corporate mogul, Lex Luthor.
All right.
Okay, Mr. Kent, I need to wrangle
you guys over here for a photo shoot.
All right.
- Excuse me.
- Mr. Kent.
Oh, hey, oh, thank you, thank you.
Looks like the congratulations...
...are already coming in.
I'll be with you in just a second.
This could take a while.
Is this really happening?
Go do your photo op.
You okay?
You sounded pretty upset
in your message.
I probably shouldn't have called.
I shouldn't do a lot of things,
but I seem to do them anyway.
I'm sure you want to get back
to the party. So...
Lex.
I know how hard you worked for this...
...but I don't think you should
take it so personally.
You know how many people
are cheering right now...
...that the spoiled, rich kid lost
to some salt-of-the-earth farmer?
Well, since when do you care
about what other people think?
Since I was branded at birth
with the sins of my father.
Just once, Lana...
...I wanted to get out from under
his shadow, you know?
Earn something on my own.
Well, consider yourself lucky
you never had a father to endure, huh.
I think it's best if we talk about this
when you're not drunk.
See...
Now I've hurt your feelings.
Perfect.
Through this whole campaign...
...I've managed to alienate
everyone I care about.
I can't lose you too.
Lex.
Hey.
You aren't going to lose me.
Well, I guess it's a bigger day
than I thought.
Yeah. You know, it happened so fast.
We never really got a chance
to tell anyone about it.
Yeah.
So after all the lies he told you,
you still chose him.
- You don't understand.
- How many times have you come to me...
...wondering what clark's
keeping from you.
Why he disappeared to Metropolis
for months.
How he rose from the dead.
It's not like that now.
Really?
Come on.
Lana.
I know you.
You'd never say yes
with all the doubts you have.
Whatever it is he's been covering up
all this time...
You know, don't you?
Clark isn't hiding anything, Lex.
After everything I've done for you...
...how could you lie to me?
Tell me!
Lana, where'd you go?
Clark, I'm so sorry.
I went to see Lex.
And he was really drunk.
What happened?
He knows.
I don't know how he could tell...
...but he could tell
I was hiding your secret.
I didn't say anything to him.
- But he got really angry.
- Lana, that's okay.
Where are you now?
I'm on Route 40,
right before Loeb Bridge.
Oh, God.
- Oh, God, he's coming after me.
- Lana.
Lana! Lana!
Just pull over so we can talk.
Lana, watch out!
No, no. Lana!
Hurry, George.
- Come here, come on. Clark.
- Lana!
- Come here. Come on.
- No!
- Lana!
No!
There's nothing you could've done.
Nothing.
How could you take her away from me?
Human life is fragile, my son.
You knew a life would be exchanged
for yours.
Don't make her pay for my mistake.
If I hadn't told her the truth about me,
she'd still be alive!
You have to let me fix it.
Your powers on Earth
may seem extraordinary, Kal-EI.
But we are not gods.
This is not her destiny!
And you know that!
There has to be a way.
There has to be a way to...
To fix this.
- Please.
- There is one trial...
...you have yet to experience.
But you must heed my warning.
The tide of fate is impossible to stop.
Even if you are able to alter
one course of events...
...the universe will find a balance.
There is only one crystal.
Once you make this choice,
there is no second chance.
Decide carefully.
I have to save her.
I brought gloves and a scarf,
like you said.
You're here.
Of course I'm here, clark.
I'm just not sure a mystery date's...
...exactly what our relationship needs
right now.
So where are you taking me?
I just thought
we could spend the day together.
That part, I kind of figured.
But it was the quote,
"day that I'll never forget" ...
...that I was a little curious about.
Right.
Well...
I thought we could go for a drive.
Maybe up to the lake. And...
But you know, with this...
This cold snap we're having...
...the bridges are probably iced over.
So we should just stay here.
Don't you think I know by now
when you're lying?
Just... Just say something.
Anything.
You know, it wasn't a big deal.
Really, I mean...
- Trust me. It was...
- Clark.
You know that it goes both ways.
- Lana, l...
- Don't.
Unless it's the truth.
Clark, as much as I love you,
I can't do this anymore.
Lana, you don't understand.
- Lf anything ever happened to you...
- Like what?
What could be worse than losing
the person that you love?
Nothing.
I need a break.
From me?
No.
From us.
She's really done this time.
Done-done?
Or just on a downward slope...
...of the perpetual
Lana-Clark roller coaster?
Really?
- What happened?
- Ready to put on your Wall of Weird hat?
I've lived this day before.
I kind of went back in time.
Right. What'd you do,
spin the Earth backwards on its axis?
You didn't pick up the lottery numbers...
...while you were at it, did you?
You see these flowers?
- They're going to this secretary.
- Margaret?
She's a workaholic.
She hasn't had a date in like a year.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
And your boss, he's firing someone
right now.
Within the hour! You're fired!
You can't fire me! I quit!
Don't bother. It's a wrong number.
Chinese takeout.
Hello?
No, I'm sorry,
we're all out of egg rolls.
All right, McFly,
do you wanna start with how or why?
Jor-EI.
I went to him
to try to change things back.
Back to what?
The first time around,
I told Lana the truth about me.
And I asked her to marry me.
What?
What...? What...? What did she say?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
What...?
Well, what was my reaction?
A lot like that.
But listen, it was a big mistake.
- Lex was chasing her on Route 40 and...
- Clark.
There was an accident.
I didn't get there in time.
- Why was Lex chasing Lana?
- He figured out she knew my secret.
- It's why I've been afraid to tell her.
- This time you can warn her.
This doesn't mean you have to lie to her.
Chloe, she knew for less than a day.
Someone's always gonna be
trying to find out about me.
As long as we're together,
they'll be watching her.
Don't worry, clark.
We won't let her near that road.
What time is this supposed to happen?
11:02. Problem is,
she's not talking to me.
You could stay with her
and make sure that...
Fate doesn't get a second chance?
I won't leave her side.
Man of the hour, Jonathan Kent.
- Everything all right, Clark?
- Yeah, everything's great.
- Good luck tonight, Dad.
- Thank you.
Hey, you made it.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How's everything?
- Good. I haven't left her.
Tightly contested
Lowell County Senate race.
Jonathan Kent has just been elected...
- Wait, something's not the same.
- Senator.
Lois?
Lois!
Lois.
Lana? Lana?
Yeah. Hello.
I wanted to be the first
to congratulate you, senator.
There are a few things
I'd like to discuss with you...
...now that we've won.
You okay?
You sounded pretty
upset in your message.
I probably shouldn't have called.
I shouldn't do a lot of things,
but I seem to do them anyway.
I'm sure you want to get back
to the party. So...
I was kind of looking for a reason
to get some air.
Clark and I had our last fight.
Last, huh?
I kept waiting for that armor
to crack, but...
I thought that if I was patient enough,
he would finally let me in.
But I guess people
have armor for a reason.
Lana.
I hate to say this...
...but it's possible
clark's never going to trust you.
I don't understand.
Why would you lie
to someone you love?
I wouldn't.
- Wow, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't...
- It's okay. It's okay.
- I'm just gonna... I'm gonna go.
- I...
- Let's go.
- Do I really need an audience?
Back to the party. There's lots
of chocolate cake, nine cases of merlot.
You were out.
Have someone take a look at you.
Do you need to haul me to HMO-land
for committing a serious party foul?
Clark.
Clark, I've looked everywhere,
and I can't find Lana.
Lana. Listen, I'm... I'm sorry.
Can we talk about this?
I'm not gonna tell you again.
Watch out!
Lana.
- Lana.
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean what happened back there.
I was just coming to apologize and...
Lex, let's just forget it ever happened,
all right?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Senator Jonathan Kent.
And I didn't expect you
to duck out of your victory party tonight.
But I'm here.
And I'm alone, as you requested.
Good.
So why don't you come down here
and face me, you son of a bitch.
Perhaps a few lessons in tact, senator.
Now that you're gonna be
in the public eye.
Why don't you just cut the crap, Luthor?
I know my campaign accepted funds
from you.
But I also know I'm gonna pay them
all back. I won't owe you a thing.
I wonder how far that virtuous
stance will get you once you're in office.
I just wanna make sure you understand.
You don't have a puppet, here.
I should hope not. I didn't put
my financial and political clout...
...behind a candidate
who would be anyone's puppet.
I envision this rather as a partnership.
The day you and I become partners...
...will be the day...
- Careful. Careful. Careful, senator.
Don't forget, you and I...
...have a common interest.
One that both of us would...
...protect with our lives.
I have nothing but respect for a man...
...who would deliberately
hurl himself into the spotlight...
...with such a...
...dangerous secret
that must stay hidden.
I won't let you destroy my family.
We can withstand anything
you bring down on us...
...because we have each other.
That's what will always separate
the Kents from the Luthors.
Now, why don't you get...
Now, why don't you
get the hell off my property.
What's your dad doing out here?
What?
Dad?
Jonathan? Jonathan!
- Dad? Dad!
- Jonathan!
Dad? Just set him down over here.
Come on, Dad.
Come on. Here, just sit down.
No, Jonathan!
- Dad!
- Oh, God! Jonathan!
- Jonathan!
Dad?
No! Oh, please, not yet!
- No! Jonathan.
- Dad.
No, Jonathan!
I guess it's time, then.
I'm sorry.
Sit down.
Clark.
I know you're blaming yourself,
but this was not your fault.
How can you say that?
I went back to save Lana...
...and now Dad's gone.
Do you think
you could have chosen between them...
...if you'd had the chance?
Clark...
A heart beats only so many times
in a life.
Your father used his
more than anyone I know.
I just don't know how I'm supposed
to be the man he wanted me to be...
...without him here.
You're his son.
You know what's right and wrong.
Whether your father is here with us
or not...
...you're a man he's proud of.
A man he could look up to.
And something tells me
he won't be the only one.
Can I help you with this?
I love you, Mom.
I love you too.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
www.tvsubtitles.net