Take out your key.
You're out of your mind.
I wouldn't expect you to understand.
Look, just take out your key.
- No. No.
- Do it!
Tom.
- No.
- You know what to do.
Don't do it, Tom.
- I'll kill him.
- Don't listen to him.
We can't let this happen.
Tom, no!
On three.
- One, two, three.
- Don't do it! Don't do it!
I'm sorry.
Hey, Gabriel. I'm surprised MIT
even lets you converse...
...with us pedestrian
Met-Uers so early.
- Chloe, you have to get out of town.
- I've been trying since yesterday.
I had no idea "just the necessities"
would take so long to pack.
Listen to me, Chloe.
Pretty soon, it's all gonna be over.
I know it sucks to say goodbye.
But if Smallville managed
without their cyberwizard...
...I'm sure they'll survive
without their star reporter.
Chloe, you're the one person
who will understand why I had to do it.
You have to make people realize
it wasn 't my choice.
It's the only way.
Gabriel, what are you talking about?
How much time did I spend at the Torch
helping you chase the big story?
In one hour,
you're finally gonna get it.
What happens in an hour?
Smallville's finally
gonna be gone forever.
DEFCON 1. Countdown commencing.
Hi.
That was the best night's sleep
I've had in weeks.
Thanks for listening.
It's just about 6:30 on a sunny...
- Oh, God.
- Oh, my God.
How did we fall asleep?
I told you we should've
gone to the Talon.
How can that hurt so much?
All right, look. Okay, my dad's
not gonna be up for 15 minutes.
Then we gotta get out of here.
You gotta get out of here.
Sticking around
for breakfast sounds like fun.
What?
Pass me my shoe.
"We won't fall asleep, I promise."
What else are we gonna do
at 2:00 in the morning?
- Look, you're not mad, are you?
- I'm furious.
Come on.
Hey, Clark, what...?
Mr. And Mrs. Kent.
I can explain.
Clark and I made
this decision together...
...so if you're angry,
you should be angry at both of us.
We... We're not mad.
It... But this is an...
You're both...
...in new territory.
Lana, this is about a whole lot
more than just you.
So if you don't mind, I'd like
to speak to my son alone, please.
You sit down.
Just... Just remember, I am 18.
I've been in love with Lana since I was 7,
so it's not like we rushed into something.
Please tell me you were at least safe.
- Yeah, Mom.
- Safe?
Safe has got nothing
to do with this.
You shouldn't be doing anything
like this under our roof.
- Like you didn't do it?
- Clark.
There's a lot of conversations
we didn't have.
- I didn't think we needed to.
- You guys think I'm not normal.
No, no. It... It...
It's just that...
You're just so much
more vulnerable now...
...without your powers.
Knock, knock.
Okay, I just passed Lana
flying out of here.
What would she be doing here
at 6:30 in...?
So, chloe, clark said you're...
You're off to Met U today.
Looks like you're getting an early start.
Not without one last
"why me?" moment, though.
I got a cryptic call
from Gabriel Duncan.
The tech guy from the Torch?
Yeah, well, I guess
today's my lucky day...
...because he said that Smallville
is going to be history...
...in exactly 53 minutes.
Have you spoken to Sheriff Adams
about this, Chloe?
I think I've used up my limit
of "cry wolfs" with her.
Why don't you find Gabriel.
I'll speak to the sheriff myself.
Early morning or late night?
What the hell are you doing here?
I've been admiring your sketches.
I didn't mean to pry.
No, of course not.
You were just going through my things
to get better acquainted.
- You can't just come in here.
- I didn't mean to rattle you.
There was no answer,
so I started to get concerned.
Lex, I'm fine.
Are you sure about that?
Look, I just wanna talk about
what you saw that day.
Weren't you the person who told me
I was hallucinating...
...last time I mentioned a spaceship?
Lana...
...I might have appeared skeptical,
but I still believed in you.
That's why I sent
an expert to the site.
Whatever caused that crater
was not a meteor.
Have you talked
to anyone else about this?
Like Clark?
You know, when you start rambling
about spaceships and aliens...
...people kind of look at you funny.
Well, they must not have
the same faith in you that I do.
You're not crazy.
Sheriff Adams,
can I speak to you for a minute?
It's nothing to worry about.
It's just a routine drill.
It's a routine drill
at the Hamstead farm, huh?
What...?
Wouldn't have anything to do
with the missile silo in their field?
Why don't you go on
back to your truck.
It's no secret the government
put these things out here.
I just thought
they decommissioned them.
Mr. Kent, thank you, we've got it
all under control. Thank you very much.
Why don't you just relax, sir,
and let us do our job.
Officers can stand down.
There isn't even a missile in here.
This is a false alarm.
Not exactly.
That signal did not come from
in here. It was rerouted.
There are at least 15 silos
that are still active in the county.
He could be in any one of them.
Missile tracking unlocked. Enter revised
coordinates for new point of impact.
Gabriel.
It's locked.
We call it "plan B."
It's for those of us who can't
crush metal with our bare hands.
Hello.
Gabriel? Colonel Duncan?
Is anybody here?
Find anything?
Does the fact that Gabriel's father was
a not-so-retired military colonel count?
These briefs are only a few weeks old.
A colonel with an aerospace
engineering degree from Purdue?
Do you think that he might be
the lighthouse keeper...
...for the local nuclear missiles?
Wall of Weird times 100.
Well, looks like Gabriel was giving you
a run for your money.
Yeah, I'd say he lapped me
a few times.
Why would he be so obsessed
with meteor freaks?
Oh, come on.
Now, journalistic curiosity is one thing...
...but papier-mâchéing your walls
with them is another.
Call me conventional, but shouldn't this
have been a red flag for Gabriel's dad?
I just... If Gabriel was so determined
to go atomic on the meteor epidemic...
...why didn't his dad stop him?
Looks like he tried.
I expected results by now.
- Mr. Luthor...
- Why isn't this open?
That laser uses technology
so cutting edge...
...even the military doesn't
know about it. We've tried.
Luthorcorp doesn't believe
in finite solutions.
I'm not sure you understand, sir.
We've used every
chemical compound that exists.
Every alloy of metal,
every method known to man.
Which would clearly suggest
that this craft isn't known to man.
So I recommend you and your team
start thinking out of the box.
- I'm... I'm trying to explain...
- For every question, there is an answer.
Now, if you find
that task too challenging...
...I'll recruit someone who doesn't.
Find a way in.
Wait.
I didn't see this before.
That's because it wasn't there.
I don't know how they'll check
15 silos in 40 minutes.
Well, neither can you anymore, Clark,
if that's what you're thinking.
- It's rough being regular flesh and blood.
- Never stopped you.
Of all the people in Smallville,
you're the only one he warned.
- He just wants me to tell his story.
- Either way, he trusts you.
Maybe we don't need
to search every silo.
- Hello.
- Gabriel. Hi, l... I need your help.
I started to leave town, then I was
freaked out when I was driving.
And then this dog
ran out on the road and l...
Chloe, slow down. What happened?
L... I guess I must have overcorrected,
and I ran my car into a ditch.
And I can't get it started now.
I'm really scared.
- Can you help me?
- Where are you?
Route 87, near the old mill.
Okay, just hang on.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Tell me what the symbols mean.
I'm not buying it, Dad.
You're in there.
You've been obsessively
drawing these for weeks.
They're identical
to the markings on the ship.
You'll never open it.
Only he can open it.
Gabriel, I'm sorry.
Everything happened so fast.
- I didn't know who to call.
- It's all right. Come with me.
- You'll be safe there.
- Gabriel.
Which silos did you activate?
I trusted you.
Whatever your reasons for doing this,
killing's not the answer.
You're wrong, clark.
It's the only answer.
Clark! Clark! No!
- You can't just leave him, he's gonna die!
- Don't fight me.
- Clark! No!
- Chloe, you have to trust me!
No!
Farmer heard the shot
and found him on 87.
Male, 18, gunshot wound to chest.
Massive bleeding.
Vitals are unstable.
We need to intubate now.
Prep him for the OR immediately.
- Clark?
- How serious is it, doc?
Can't tell until I open him up.
It looks like the bullet pierced his lung.
- Bullet?
- Sorry, I'm gonna have to ask you...
...to stay in the waiting area.
Gabriel, Clark could die out there.
In 20 minutes none of it
will matter, Chloe.
Missile trajectory locked.
Latitude 37 north.
You're gonna kill
everyone in Smallville.
How could you do that?
It's not that difficult.
The fail-safes were programmed
back in 1979.
It only takes a moderate genius
to bypass them.
You don't watch your dad
do the same drill for 10 years...
...and not pick up a thing or two.
Don't look at me like that, chloe.
You're safe here, okay?
With me.
Besides, you're getting
what you always wanted.
The story of a lifetime.
You actually think
I care about that right now?
You should care.
The last meteor shower left 10 times
as much rock to infect people...
...than the last one.
Pretty soon, there's gonna be
more psychos running around this town.
This is the only way to end it.
It's my one chance to be a hero.
So you're exterminating
a few meteor freaks...
...by sacrificing
the lives of innocent people?
Innocent?
Every single one of those mutants
was innocent before the meteor showers.
My dad warned me
to stay away from the rocks...
...because they turned
people into mutants.
Your dad?
Were those his articles
on the wall?
He tried to warn people.
He said the meteors were
destroying the town.
No one would listen.
Then during the last one...
...he became one of them.
You know, a lot of people think
special abilities are a gift.
You didn't have to kill him
just because he wasn't normal anymore.
He asked me to.
No one wants to live like that, Chloe.
Pretty soon, no one will have to.
I don't even know
if you can hear me...
...but I need you to know...
...that from the first moment
that I saw you...
...I knew that no one could
make me happier than you.
But I also knew
that you'd never change.
You'd... You'd always be running around,
trying to save the day.
All those times I pulled away...
...it's because I knew
this day would come.
- You're not supposed to be in here.
- Please, you need to clear the room.
Charging 200. Clear.
Charging 300. Clear.
Three-fifty. Clear.
Okay, I'm calling it.
Time of death, 7: 18 a.m.
Oh, my God.
Miss Lang. Miss Lang.
Oh, no.
Mr. And Mrs. Kent...
...we did everything we could...
- No.
...but we lost him.
Doctor, we have a problem
with the Kent boy.
Two minutes to launch.
Lockdown initiated.
Seal outer doors.
Security level four.
Warning systems on.
Access denied.
Final launch sequence initiated.
Lockdown complete.
Sixty seconds to ignition.
Oh, God.
Why couldn't you understand?
This is the only way!
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six...
... five, four, three, two, ignition.
Hello, Kal-EI.
How do you know to call me that?
You're my son.
Jor-EI?
And I hope the time is coming when
you will call me father.
I was...
I was just at the hospital. How did...?
How did you get me here?
The portal in the cave.
When this body was activated
by the crystal, it became a...
An oracle of Kryptonian knowledge.
A vessel for me to inhabit
if ever you should need me.
That time was now.
Am I dead?
Your mortal journey is over, yes.
But your imminent destiny
is too important to be sacrificed.
You will return...
...with all your natural gifts.
Unfortunately, this rectification
does not come without a price.
The life of someone close to you
will be exchanged for yours.
No.
No, I would never ask for that.
You already did when you decided
to relinquish your powers and disobey me.
It was your choice.
Then just don't bring me back.
It's too late.
For everything in nature,
there is a balance.
The life force that has been returned
to you will soon be taken from...
From someone you love.
You're about to face
your darkest hour, my son.
But remember...
...the lessons
that we learn from pain...
...are the ones
that make us the strongest.
Always know that I love you.
Clark.
The hospital lost our son.
If I had any idea what happened...
...I wouldn't have to call the police,
now would I?
Listen, I want you to get ahold of
Sheriff Adams and send her over there.
- I have to call you back.
- Clark.
Oh, Clark. Clark.
Son. They told us you were dead.
Yeah...
I was.
- Jor-EI?
- Yeah.
He returned your powers, didn't he?
I'm not human anymore.
It was the only way
I could come back.
We heard about a missile malfunction.
You stopped it, didn't you?
It's not easy to sacrifice
the thing you want the most...
...to save other people.
We're so proud of you, clark.
The real sacrifice would've been
not coming back at all.
Son.
After all those threats...
...Jor-El just decided to offer
to give you your powers back?
He didn't ask for anything in return?
No.
Mr. And Mrs. Kent?
Clark.
Lana.
I heard about clark's resurrection.
You know, I've... I've never
really believed in miracles...
...but I've certainly done my share
of asking for them today.
Me too.
But I think that
we have different reasons.
It's clark's medical file.
That's confidential.
I heard you asked for it at the hospital.
All of his test results
came back normal.
When are you gonna realize, Lex,
that he is just like the rest of us?
Do you really believe that?
Or is that what you have to tell yourself
to stay in a relationship with him?
You've had doubts about him too.
You can't deny it.
I was wrong.
Believe me, there's nothing
unusual about Clark...
...except his ability to see the good
in people who don't deserve it.
I think you're
forgetting something, Lana.
Whatever new lie he told you...
...however he swept it under the rug...
...a normal person
doesn't rise from the dead.
Aren't you gonna
give your old dad a hug?
I was told you were missing
from Belle Reve.
Man, I don't understand.
You've been nearly catatonic for weeks.
Didn't I just overhear you say
you'd been looking for miracles all day?
Looks like I'm it.
So maybe now
you can tell me why you've...
You've been wandering around...
...mumbling things like
"Krypton" and "Kal-EI."
Krypton? Kal-EI? I don't...
The last thing I remember
is standing here arguing with you.
That was weeks ago.
Okay.
You don't recognize these?
Looks like something from the cave.
What is it?
I found you carving them
with a corkscrew.
Oh, wasn't I creative.
I wish that I could unlock
the labyrinth of my subconscious.
I'm sorry to disappoint you, son.
I have my father back.
What's to disappoint?
If anything, I'd say
this is cause for celebration.
When Kansas didn't merge
with Oklahoma today...
...I kind of guessed you were involved.
Looks like you're okay.
You don't look too bad yourself.
For a dead guy.
I heard what happened at the hospital.
You went and got your powers back,
didn't you?
I didn't have a choice.
I know how much
you've dreamt of having...
...a bland, mundane, generic life...
...but being normal is highly overrated.
And besides, it makes my whole
sidekick role a lot easier...
...if you can bring super-duper
strength to the table.
I mean, not that we didn't make
a great team out there today...
...minus the whole part where
I was kidnapped and you were shot.
So...
...are you healing,
or how does that work exactly?
Unscathed on the surface.
But that's not what's going on
underneath, is it, Clark?
I guess I'll never be able
to escape who I really am.
Back to the lies...
...and hoping no one
will ever ask to see the scar.
Namely, Lana?
- We've never talked about Lana...
- That's because we don't need to, clark.
I'm a big girl now.
I do have one confession.
I really liked being
the only one who knew all about...
...you know, you.
For lack of a cheesier word,
it just made it...
...special.
But if you honestly believe that you can
stay with Lana and not tell her...
...I think you're
seriously kidding yourself.
I don't have a choice.
I can't expect her to react like you did.
But don't you think
you owe her the choice?
I can't take that risk.
I've risked too much already.
And now someone else
is gonna have to pay for it.
Clark, is everything okay?
What's going on?
I never should've given up my powers.
Why didn't I listen to him?
Chloe, I think
I've made a terrible mistake.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
www.tvsubtitles.net