Mom?
- Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
We got you, didn't we?
Look. And Lois even made
her world-famous rum cake for you.
From scratch.
- Wow, I never would have guessed.
- You should have seen the first two.
Come on, presents before cake.
Come on, birthday boy. Sit down.
Open it.
Wow.
Not that you're
the "dear diary" type...
...but since you keep
everything to yourself...
...I thought it might help.
And since I'm on an intern budget,
I figured I could just...
...comp a couple of those IOUs
that you owe me.
Thank you.
That's Dad's handwriting.
I found it in his desk.
Two tickets to the Wolverines game
in Milwaukee.
- Right behind home plate.
- Yeah, your dad and his baseball.
There was no one in the world
he'd rather watch a game with.
Thanks for the tickets, Dad.
I just wish...
...that you were here to go with me.
Dad?
Listen, I'm sorry I couldn't be
at your birthday party...
...to see the kind of man
you're becoming.
- Dad, everything I am is because of you.
- Not everything.
There can be no more lessons.
You're gonna have to do this
on your own. I can't help you anymore.
You're gonna have to stop him.
Stop who?
He's much worse
than we imagined.
So many people...
So many people are gonna die.
I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Lionel Luthor.
What is he doing?
He's gonna do something terrible.
Tell me, Dad,
what am I supposed to do?
I'm sorry, clark.
But to save this world...
...you've gotta kill Lionel Luthor.
Goodbye, son.
Dad?
Dad, wait.
Clark, grief can
play tricks on the mind.
Mom, I know what I saw.
It was Dad. His spirit, his ghost,
whatever you wanna call it.
Sweetheart, I see your dad
all the time.
Every morning when I wake up
I feel him beside me.
But it's not him.
And it's not his ghost.
It's my mind wanting it so badly
I think he's really there.
Right now you're really angry
with Lionel...
...and maybe you want someone
to say it's okay to get back at him.
Mom, this isn't the first time
I've seen Dad.
It's a long story,
but Lana was in trouble.
I tried to save her and had
some sort of near-death experience.
I saw Dad. He was the one
who told me Lionel knew my secret.
That wasn't my imagination.
What if this wasn't either?
If that's true,
if it really was your father...
Then what Lionel's up to is worse
than just knowing my secret.
It would have to be, for your father
to suggest taking someone's life.
One drip, one extra-hot double cap,
no foam.
- Sorry about the mess-up.
- Don't worry.
I know how finicky
that steamer can be.
- Thank you. Lois. Hey.
- Hey.
- Running a delivery service?
- No. Actually...
...Chloe started short-circuiting so l...
- Save it, Lana. It's okay.
There's only one extra-hot double cap,
no foam in this town.
Runs by "Lex."
Walks in here like he owns the place.
Actually, Lois, he does own the place.
So are you his new assistant?
No, not exactly.
No way.
I guess if you're in the market
for a boyfriend...
...why not Smallville's
most eligible bachelor?
He's not my boyfriend.
Look, I know I'm not versed
in the whole girl-talk thing...
...but I do have an unbiased ear.
And, I know what it's like
to have a case of the bad-boy blues.
Okay, Clark, I am the president
of Ghost Believers Anonymous...
...but your dad Hamleting you?
- Chloe, I know how it sounds.
- Hand me a cloak and call me Horatio.
- Great.
Now what could be so bad that my Dad
would want Lionel dead to stop it?
Maybe it has something to do with him
knowing where you really came from.
That's a part of it,
but there's gotta be something more.
Well...
...if Lionel is hatching
some evil scheme...
...it would explain why
he's sitting on your secret.
Maybe something's already in motion.
Chloe, someone tried
to blackmail my mom...
...with footage of me using my abilities.
- What?
Guess which billionaire
came to the rescue.
All right, say this ghost
of your dad's is right.
And we dig through Lionel's closet
and we find a smoking gun. Then what?
- Depends what it was.
- Would it?
Is there anything we could find that
would make Clark Kent kill someone?
My helicopter's waiting, Dad.
What's so important?
Obviously something
you've got cooking in Honduras.
Although I doubt
it's the banana daiquiris.
You've been racking up quite a lot
of frequent flier miles, son.
Challenging upper management
often leads to a bout of unemployment.
The welfare of your workers
is the least of my concerns.
You're involved with Milton Fine.
I know he's been smuggling the deadliest
viruses in the world into this country.
- With your help.
- Well, don't worry, Dad.
We're not gonna put them
in any Halloween candy.
You're extremely nonchalant for a man
whose collection of microorganisms...
...could wipe out
more than half of this country.
It's under control.
Your business partner's a man
who seems able to appear...
...at opposite ends
of the Earth simultaneously.
How much control
do you have over him?
Your intel is impressive,
but incomplete.
Shut the operation down, Lex.
Shut it down now.
Wherever you're incubating
these viruses, you need to destroy them.
Milton Fine embodies a threat
greater than you appear to realize.
You taught me. Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
This is one enemy you don't know.
Not knowing who you're in bed with...
...can make for a very
uncomfortable awakening.
Well, I'll present that nugget
to the board...
...when they ask why I'm late.
Wait, Clark, the alarm.
I cloned the transponder
from Lionel's key port...
...so we could override
the digital cipher.
I need a night life.
Look for anything my dad
might warn me about.
Okay, it might take a minute.
I can't exactly search for a file
called "My evil scheme."
Have you thought that
if Lionel knows your secret...
...he might have told...
Lex?
Knowledge is power.
Lionel would never level the field.
I guess this is one rare time...
...when we have to put our faith
in the Luthor family dysfunction.
- Locked out.
- Check his calendar.
All right.
I'm multitasking as fast as I can.
- Leon Rowland?
- Who's that?
Lionel has an interview tomorrow
with the Inquisitor's top reporter...
...regarding something
called "The Weapon."
Then at the Pentagon.
Looks like the mysterious weapon
is the hot topic this week.
Maybe it's not so mysterious.
Wait, you think that you might be
the weapon Lionel's talking about?
I bought us coffees.
But after a three-hour conversation
with Lois, they got a bit cold.
I can't wait to read all about Lex
and Lana in tomorrow's early edition.
She's not like that.
Believe it or not, she's a great listener.
And with everything
that's been going on...
...she's been a wonderful
outlet for me.
It looks like I'm not the only one
who needs an outlet.
Lana, something's happened.
I've been wrestling with whether or not
I should let you in on it.
But, when all is said and done...
...you're the one person in the world
I can share it with.
I've been working on something.
Something bigger than either of us.
- Lex, whatever it is, I trust you.
- This isn't about trusting me anymore.
It's about trusting you.
It's about how deep you wanna get
involved, and knowing when to say stop.
Lana, what I'm about to show you...
...means you're all in.
A hundred percent.
What is this place?
The future.
I'd like you to be by my side
when it arrives.
You've been collecting viruses?
The most deadly on the planet.
What are you gonna do with them?
Change the world.
Lana, we've been able to
alter the viruses...
...transforming them into
the ultimate vaccine.
One shot of this, and theoretically
you'd be protected...
...from any disease
that could be unleashed.
Unleashed?
By whom?
Well, according to Fine...
...the CIA believes the black spacecraft
might be the first of many.
Listen, you need to keep this
between the two of us.
Fine doesn't know
we're developing the vaccine here.
I thought you two
were working together.
Why don't you trust him anymore?
Because I think he might be reporting
back to something a little higher up.
You found the ship?
I was tracking Fine
and he led me directly to it.
But that's not the intriguing part.
These two photographs were taken
a hundredth of a second apart.
Where did he go?
Oh, my God.
Do you think he came out of that ship
like the others?
That's why I was
going along with him.
I thought I could buy some time
to find his weakness.
But I'm starting to think
he doesn't have one.
He might.
After the meteor shower, when I found
your dad in that strange trance...
...he grabbed me, and he told me
how to stop them.
Hi, this is the Kent residence.
Leave a message.
Martha, it's Lionel.
I know things are strained...
... but something's going on
that Clark needs to know about.
Please. Call me
as soon as you get this.
Jonathan.
How long, Martha?
What?
How long have you had feelings
for Lionel Luthor?
It's not like that.
I want you to be happy, sweetheart.
I've always just...
Just wanted you to be happy...
...but not with him.
Jonathan.
You know you're the only man
I've ever loved.
It's been...
...so hard without you.
Your voice, your touch.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too, sweetheart.
Why did you have to leave me?
I'm sorry, Martha.
I didn't have any choice.
And soon, neither will a lot of other
innocent people.
Are you talking about Lionel?
What is it? What is he doing?
He's going to drown you all
in your own blood.
Just like he did me.
Like he did you? What...?
Martha, I'm sorry. But, you've got to
tell Clark there is no other choice.
Lionel Luthor has to die.
Jonathan.
He has to.
Jonathan?
He was standing right here.
Like he was still alive.
He said Lionel was gonna
drown us all in blood.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know.
Mom, I think it might have something to
do with Lionel using me as a weapon.
But, Clark, you would never
go along with that.
What if he found a way
to control me?
Maybe that's what Dad's
come to stop.
All this time I thought Lionel
was making up for his past.
Mom, it's not your fault.
Lionel has been manipulating all of us.
Clark, he said something else.
I think he meant Lionel
had something to do with his death.
We've tracked Milton Fine
to the Midwestern United States.
We're working to narrow
his coordinates. We'll let you know.
- Sir, please be advised unofficial data...
- Good evening, Mr. Luthor.
May I?
Please, help yourself.
Everybody else does.
Some say the toast came about...
...by a man who feared
that his drink had been poisoned.
But he was a quick-witted man.
He joyfully clanked his mug
with the mugs of his mates...
...sloshing his lethal beverage
into everyone's drink with cheer.
A simple tap, then,
must be a sign of trust.
I'm not really thirsty.
I thought we had an agreement.
You would inform me
of the virus's progress.
But I seem to be
shockingly cut out of the loop.
A fact you've probably
known for weeks.
Come on.
You must have assumed
I wouldn't inherently believe...
...your CIA bluff.
And that's why I chose you.
For your insatiable distrust...
...and your propensity
for covering all the bases.
I'm sure you didn't waltz in here...
- ...thinking I'd just roll over.
- No, not you.
Not without a bone.
I'll take the truth.
I assure you the vaccine
is processed and ready.
But I'd be foolish to hand it over
to someone...
...whose agenda is still up for grabs.
Lex, it's a vaccine.
What threat could it possibly pose?
Now, that's a question
I've been asking myself for weeks.
I'm hoping this will help me
get a few answers.
Close...
...but I'm not one of them.
I was only made by them.
Where's the vaccine?
Before I tell you this,
promise you'll keep cool...
...and backburner those
American Psycho instincts, okay?
Chloe, what is it?
I pulled up your dad's phone records.
Unless Lionel was selling
long-distance plans...
...he was desperate
to get ahold of your dad.
There are at least 20 calls logged
in those last few weeks.
Dad said he died
protecting my secret.
Maybe that's how he found out
Lionel knew about me.
When did the calls stop?
They didn't.
Lionel talked to your dad
an hour before he died.
Think Lionel was congratulating him?
Not unless he did it in person.
Lionel's call came through a tower
in Jansen's Field.
That's only a mile away
from your house.
Lionel was there?
Lionel was there
the night my dad died.
Clark.
I'm glad you called. Thank you.
We don't have much time.
Is this where it happened?
Is this where you met my father
the night he died?
Yes. Yes, it is.
I had to talk to him. It was important.
He found out, didn't he?
He found out about your plan
to use me as a weapon.
A weapon?
No. Clark, no, it...
What did you do to him?
Clark, I wanted to help him.
He needed an ally
but he took it the wrong way.
- You killed my father.
- No. Clark...
What happened, he wouldn't
go along with the plan?
You pushed. You pushed him
till his heart gave out.
- Listen to me, Clark.
- I will never be anyone's weapon.
- You're not the weapon. It's not you.
- Lies.
That's all he's gonna tell you, son.
Gonna have to kill him
before he gets the chance.
- Listen to me, Clark.
- Shut up!
Do it, Clark.
Do it.
- You killed him.
- Yes, he killed me.
So go on, son. Avenge my death.
Your father would never
make you a murderer.
Kill him!
Listen to me, Clark. Listen to me.
Clark, I know this
is very difficult for you...
...but you have
got to kill Lionel Luthor!
Clark Kent, kill him now!
You know...
...I asked you to do one simple thing.
This is what I get.
You're a tremendous
disappointment to me, son.
You're not my father.
Well, it looks like I might have
underestimated you, Kal-EI. Catch!
It would be so easy to snap your neck
just like a twig.
But I still need you.
Who are you?
I'm the guy that's gonna help
bring this world to its knees.
Don't touch me.
Don't do it. Don't do...
What...? What just happened?
I was fairly certain Milton Fine
was a Kryptonian...
...but I didn't realize
that shape shifting...
...was one of the Kryptonian's
miraculous abilities.
It isn't.
Then Fine's not a Kryptonian.
Clark, it is important to both of us
that we keep this from Lex.
Look, Fine was created by Kryptonians,
and he's already been destroyed twice.
Twice? Some sort of self-replicating
entity, it's incredible.
That's one word for it.
Why was he so afraid of you?
And how were you able to destroy him,
just by touching him?
L... I'm not sure. But...
I feel the answers
could lie somewhere...
...in here.
Where did you find all this?
I didn't find it.
I wrote it.
And whatever voice I'm channeling...
...I believe that what I wrote
is meant for you.
So hell freezes over
and no one bothers to tell me?
Chloe, listen.
Mr. Luthor has been writing these.
Seems to be some sort of warning,
but I can't decipher it.
Unfortunately my Kryptonian's rusty.
What about...?
I don't know what any of this means.
I am simply the oracle.
The answers could be found
with a visit to your Fortress.
Last time someone talked me
into taking them...
...it was a trick to release General Zod.
- I have plans this weekend.
So if we could protect Smallville
from Krypton's deadliest villain, great.
Ancient hieroglyphics were deciphered
by finding repeated...
Repeated patterns. I know.
So let me scan this
and see if we got any.
Why would Fine wanna
expose himself now?
He's afraid I'm going to help you.
To stop what he and Lex
are planning to do.
- Which is what?
- Fine has been helping Lex...
...to develop a virus so lethal, it could
bring humanity to the brink of extinction.
LuthorCorp scientists
completed the project today.
So the weapon isn't clark,
it's this virus.
Yes.
What the pattern
is trying to warn me against.
I have a strong sense that this warning
I have been entrusted to pass on...
...is related to something more terrible
even than the virus.
- Maybe the virus is just a part of it.
- Yeah.
- Do you have access to the lab?
- I don't know where it is.
I think we know someone who does.
What are you doing?
Smooth one, Smallville.
- Something I have to talk to you about.
- How did you get in here?
I think I just heard a keg being tapped.
I'm gonna go check it out.
I shouldn't be going through
your stuff...
...but you're involved
in something dangerous.
Worried I'm involved in it,
or in it with Lex?
No. Lana, this has nothing to do
with my feelings.
Lex doesn't know what he's gotten
himself into. Neither do you.
You break into my place
and you expect me to believe anything?
Lex is in trouble.
And if you care about him at all,
you'll tell me where that lab is.
Before it's too late.
Impressive.
Looks like I underestimated
your willingness...
...to tackle a non-profit venture.
Well, Luthorcorp doesn't take the threat
of an alien Armageddon lightly.
You were never gonna create
a vaccine for humans, were you?
Is that what you think?
It was gonna be your way of protecting
extraterrestrial guests when they arrive...
...and unleash
some horrible disease on us.
So you went behind my back,
mass-produced the vaccine for mankind.
I wanted to give my people a chance
before you got your dirty hands on it.
I applaud your noble efforts
to protect your species.
Unfortunately, it's all based
on faulty assumptions.
I never intended
to mass-produce the vaccine.
One dose is all I ever needed.
Let the rest of the world
find its own cure.
I'm not sure
what to tell you, Mr. Luthor.
Whatever you were injected with,
it doesn't appear to have had any effect.
In fact, you've never been healthier.
Well, I appreciate the vote of confidence.
Thank you, doctor.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
So I'm guessing that my father told you
everything that happened at the lab.
You know, Lex, if you had listened
to your father's warnings...
...none of this would have happened.
- None of what?
All the viruses were destroyed.
And now LuthorCorp has a technology
to create an extraordinary vaccine.
Lex, you were double-crossed.
- Where's Fine right now?
- I don't know.
My operatives are scouring the globe.
Clark, I was the good guy here.
LuthorCorp spent over $ 10 million
producing that vaccine.
One more thing, Clark.
Lana called me.
I don't wanna hear you were
rifling through her stuff...
...like a crazy roommate again.
If you want something from me,
don't go running to Lana to find it.
You really crossed the line.
All those years we were friends...
...were you waiting for me to step aside
so you could make your move?
I don't know, clark.
All those years
you told Lana you loved her...
...were you just waiting to walk away
and break her heart?
There's a natural tendency to blame
the person who's replaced you.
I get that.
But I didn't take Lana from you.
You lost her all by yourself.
Lionel?
What are you doing here?
I have to make
a confession to you, Martha.
Martha, the...
The night Jonathan was elected...
...l... I called him.
So it's true.
I told him that I knew everything
about Clark.
He was so angry, he...
He never let me explain.
I wish I had a heart as full of strength
and goodness as your son, Martha.
I don't.
But I want you to remember
that I was at least honest with you.
In time, maybe you'll
be able to forgive me.
I'm sorry if things got awkward.
I was hoping Clark
wouldn't end up in all this.
- I just don't wanna hurt him.
- I don't either.
I care about him too.
But then I have to remind myself...
...that clark's specialty
is barging in where he's not invited...
...and then somehow making you feel
like you're the one who should apologize.
Okay, I have a great idea.
How about a moratorium
on the Clark topic?
Twist my arm.
Don't tempt me.
You know,
I still can't make sense of all this.
Why would you be asked to produce a
super vaccine just to have it destroyed?
I don't know.
But then again,
I think like a red-blooded human.
Well, he was obviously
preparing for something.
What happened?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Never better.
I thought you'd be outside Lana's dorm
with your binoculars by now.
I appreciate the concern.
Lana and I are none of your business.
Please, Smallville, I've had three exes
put under military surveillance.
I'm hardly qualified to dish out
post-relationship tact.
But it's time for some tough love.
Lana's going to move on.
She already has.
With Lex.
And it sucks.
But you gotta trust your gut
that you did this for a reason.
Whatever reasons guys have for dumping
hot, smart, fun girls these days.
Look, give her some space.
Your whole night-stalker routine...
...that is gonna ruin any of the
good feelings Lana has for you.
If there are any.
Look...
...sometimes you gotta tuck your
feelings away until it's the right time.
Like stuffing dollars into a piggy bank
for a bike you can't quite afford.
Except, I can't imagine
there is anyone else out there.
You never know, Clark. Maybe when you
finally crack open that piggy bank...
...you'll find that
you haven't been saving for a bike...
...you've really been saving
for a Harley.
There are times when I think
you don't know me at all.
Others where I think
you know me better than anyone.
Well, that's what I'm here for,
Smallville, one save at a time.
And speaking of saving things...
- My cake.
- Hello.
Your mom thought we might wanna
share some of the leftover birthday cake.
Well, I'm sure there's a goat on this farm
that will appreciate my knack for batter.
You handled the whole party
thing really well, by the way.
Thanks.
The baseball tickets...
...they hit me harder
than I thought.
Yeah, but those tickets,
they weren't your dad's only gift.
I mean, it didn't come with a big,
pretty red bow...
...but your dad raised you
to be your own man.
That was his real gift.
And he gave that to you every day.
I thought you just came
to get tipsy off of rum cake.
Yeah. Actually, I came by
for your Kryptonian dictionary.
I ran Lionel's symbols in that program
and it came up with this pattern.
Three signs repeated 32 times.
What does it say?
"Zod is coming."
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
www.tvsubtitles.net