Previously on 90210...
Adrianna, this is Lila,
our bass player.
I joined the band to get over Navid,
now I have to spend every day
with the girl he's dating?
- I'm kicking you off the Blaze.
- What do you want? Name it.
I'll do anything.
Please. I'll do anything.
- Are you offering to sleep with me?
- What? No. I...
Because that would be
completely inappropriate.
You're off the Blaze.
I know this isn't what you want to hear,
but you were the one out of line.
I cannot believe you're
taking his side, Silver.
He said if I wanted back on the Blaze,
I had to sleep with him.
What?!
So, you want to go out on a date?
- Do you mind if I crash here tonight?
- Not at all. Tonight, tomorrow,
- as long as you want.
- I'm Laurel.
If I can't be with you,
- there's no point in living.
- Jasper, no.
I told you,
I don't know where he is.
I just hope he's not getting
into too much trouble
before his parents
come back to town.
Leave a message.
I need you to tell me
where you are, okay?
I'm just getting really worried.
Please call me back.
And please don't hurt yourself.
What are you doing up there?
- It's all pointless, Annie.
- What is?
All of it.
Life. It's a joke.
It's painful.
It's humiliating.
And I'm over it.
You still have not chosen a loofah.
- I think you should come forward.
- Liam, no.
What Mr. Cannon said to you
was sexual harassment.
I don't want to deal
with the aggravation.
Now, I'm assuming you're going
to go with blue, but
lavender could be
bold statement for guy.
I don't understand.
Why don't you report him?
This has been a really crazy year.
The feud with Annie,
the situation with Jen.
Jen has hurt you enough.
Don't let her stop you
from doing what's right.
What?
The truth is...
I'm a lot more like Jen
than you probably think.
You are nothing like Jen.
And if you were,
I wouldn't be with you.
I'll take an Arnold Palmer,
mostly iced tea.
Like, a quarter lemonade.
And just a regular
water for me. Thanks.
So, you notice anything
different about me?
You're taller?
Shorter? Wait. I know.
You shaved your mustache.
No. I got a haircut.
Really? Like, a hair cut?
Single hair?
You're just not very
detail-oriented, are you?
Just because I didn't notice
your emperor's new haircut...
Now, come here,
you totally transformed woman.
Hey! Dixon.
Hey, man.
How's it going?
Who you here with?
No one.
By myself.
You know what? I should set you up
with my mixed doubles partner.
No. Don't worry about it, man.
I'm serious.
She is totally hot.
Definitely not my type.
Thanks for looking out
for me, but I'm cool
doing my own thing.
See y'all later.
Jasper, please listen to me.
It's not pointless.
What's the point?
What's the point to life?
You don't love me anymore.
Do you?
Peach Pit team
www.forom.com
Season 02 Episode 17
Sweaty Palms and Weak Knees
Hi. We're looking for Jasper Herman.
He's our son.
I'll see if he's out of surgery.
Mr. And Mrs. Herman?
What's going on?
Do you know?
All we've been told is that he fell
off the top of the Hollywood sign.
Were you with him?
What was he even doing up there?
Was he filming something?
No, I...
Look, he didn't fall.
He jumped.
Oh, my God.
Listen, you should go home, Annie.
Get some sleep, and...
we'll call you if we hear any news.
- I can stay.
- No. Jasper's our son.
We'll handle this.
You should take care of yourself.
Okay.
I am sick.
- Cold or flu?
- Not that kind of sick. I just...
Why am I enjoying watching
you iron so much?
- I'm sick, that's all.
- You're a sexist pig.
- What do you think?
- Cute.
You're driving
us to the concert, right?
You know it.
- You're the best roadie ever.
- Roadie?
I was thinking more groupie.
That's possible.
It's very possible.
But you know what groupies
do for their rock stars?
What?
Their ironing.
Okay.
Wilson looks.
He shoots.
- Come on.
- Was it something I said?
- Do over.
- No way, man. I want my ten bucks.
Are you guys betting
on baby basketball? That's just sad.
I wish I could put
money on the Lakers.
Telling you they're about
to go on a roll I can feel it.
Sounds like someone's
got the gambling bug.
Bug? No. Gift? Yes.
Could you hook me up
with your dad's bookie?
- Yeah, sure.
- Cool.
I'm telling you,
I really feel good about the Lakers.
Put me down for 250 bucks.
You don't want to put it
on the Lakers.
My dad's got floor seats
and last night, he overheard his trainer
saying that Kobe's
going to sit out against the Spurs.
- His knee's bothering him.
- Really?
Then, I'm feeling really good
about the Spurs.
- Hook me up, all right?
- You got it.
Anyone see the Cavs last night?
LeBron was on fire.
Man, I missed it.
Naomi and I were...
Never mind.
Liam, what's your problem?
You can talk about Naomi
in front of me.
Dixon looks.
He shoots.
- Are you okay?
- Never been better. Why?
I don't know. It just looks like
you have something against those books.
I don't get why everyone keeps treating
me like I'm some loser or something.
- You're preaching to the choir, miss.
- Really?
Ever since Silver and Teddy's
been going out,
they've been treating me
like some... charity case.
Seriously?
Yeah. Teddy tried to hook me
up with some tennis girl.
He was like, "Let me call in a favor
to this ex-girlfriend of mine
to see if she'll go out with you. "
Like I need his hand-me-downs.
I hear you. I mean,
between you and me, Liam's practically
chewing my food for me
then regurgitating it
back into my mouth.
What?
He's patronizing me, he treats me
like I'm some baby or something.
Baby bird, yeah. I get it.
And you know what I mean, though?
It's kind of ridiculous. I...
As if I care that he's still dating
that giggling imbecile?
Like I'm supposed to care that Silver
changed her Facebook status to
"in a relationship. "
Why do you know
Silver's Facebook status?
Anyways, you want to hang out later?
I don't know, grab a burger?
Yes, that'll be cool.
I mean, it seems like
everybody else is coupled off.
And besides, I haven't
had a Beach Burger since...
yesterday.
- Peace.
- I'll call you.
I'm just saying... you can't let
Mr. Cannon get away with it.
That's exactly
what I've been saying.
Have you guys seen Alaina
Grossberg's collagen injections?
- You have to tell somebody.
- Honestly, it's not that big of a deal.
Seriously, her lips
look like an inner tube.
It is, and it's your responsibility.
Your moral obligation.
Think about it. What if Mr. Cannon
harasses some other girl?
Enough! Please! Just stop!
This has been really hard?
Yeah, it has.
This whole situation is...
it's too much.
Maybe you should talk to somebody.
Maybe Kelly.
It's a good idea.
You're struggling with this.
Fine, I'll talk to someone.
Not Kelly.
I don't trust this psyche to anyone
who costs less than $400 an hour.
- I'll see a real therapist, okay?
- Come here.
- Your chair, madam.
- Thank you.
Are those new shoes? I like 'em.
Thank you.
So did I when I bought them
in seventh grade. Nice try.
What did we miss?
Nothing. Teddy's just trying
to prove how well he knows me.
- He's crashing and burning.
- I am so not crashing and burning.
Hello, there. What can I get
you all to drink?
Maybe some water for the table.
Sure. Sparkling or flat?
What do you prefer?
How about... Teddy,
you want to tell him what I like?
Sparkling, because she has
such a sparkling personality.
Actually, I like flat,
because apparently I have
a flat personality.
I'll get a bottle of each.
I was close. It's not like you know
everything about me.
You know what? He's gonna have
an Arnold Palmer... three-quarters
iced tea, one-quarter lemonade.
Snap.
I guess so.
Great.
Let's go, right?
- What's up?
- Come here.
- Grab a fork, stab me in the jugular.
- Too late.
You guys wanna join us for dinner?
- Why not?
- Yeah, there's
plenty of room.
I can just sit in Liam's lap.
- Actually, we were...
- We're on a date.
All right!
You can do better.
Naomi, I can hear you.
Anyway, that's really great.
It's pretty great.
Anyway... we should go.
- Shall we?
- We shall.
Bye.
- Have fun.
- See ya.
What the hell was that?
That was crazy!
Yeah, kinda.
But kinda crazy awesome.
Really?
Hell, yeah!
Did you see their faces?!
So... guess you're my boyfriend now.
Guess so.
- After you, my lady.
- None of that gentlemanly crap.
Come on.
A lingerie Web site.
Montgomery,
has it really come to this?
I'm trying to find
a gift for Silver.
Good luck with that. One time
I bought her a leather bracelet
and she accused me of being
insensitive to cow feelings.
Cow feelings.
She's not exactly
the easiest to shop for.
Tell me about it.
Do you think maybe she'd like to...
You know what? Never mind.
It's cool, man.
All right, I moved on.
I really like Ivy now.
Hell, yeah.
In fact, I recently bought Ivy
a little gift myself.
What'd you get her?
I can't have you rip off my idea.
It's way too good.
You and Ivy.
- I did not see that coming.
- Yeah, I know.
Neither did I. See you later, man.
Later.
Hello?
Hi, Annie. Matey Herman.
I just wanted to let you know
that Jasper is going to make it.
Good.
He's okay?
He broke both his legs
and sprained his shoulder,
but, yes, physically
he's going to be fine.
Psychologically, mentally,
the kid's obviously going through
a rough patch.
Once he checks out over
here, he's going to be checking
into a psychiatric facility
for a little while.
A psychiatric hospital?
I mean, that's...
that makes sense.
- That's good.
- Yeah. We feel it's going to help.
And help get him talking, you know?
My brother's death
really affected Jasper, and
we just want him to talk to someone.
Open up. Stop hiding.
One more thing.
Jasper wanted to talk to you
before he goes away. Would you...
would you do that for him?
- You really didn't have to drive me.
- I wanted to.
- How long is your therapy session?
- I'll be done in about an hour.
I'll pick you up then.
Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
May I please get a nonfat
blended mocha for here?
And can I see a menu, too?
Great! Now, we're going
to be late to our own show.
When did they start
locking the school so early?
Maybe after somebody spray painted
"Beth Jennings is a whore"
- all over the courtyard.
- Why would anyone do that?
Cause she's whore-like.
Whorish, whore-esque.
Not that I did it.
I told you it was a stupid idea
to leave our instruments at school.
I told you guys we can't practice
in my parents' garage anymore.
They can't handle the noise.
- Your parents have no taste in music!
- What the...?
Why don't we just climb
up the fire escape
- and jump down into the courtyard?
- Can we do that?
Yeah, totally.
All right, let's do it.
- You are a genius.
- Just your number one groupie.
- Come here.
- Come on, guys!
Let's go.
Whatever.
Are you still mad?
I'm not mad. I didn't realize
we're still keeping secret.
I didn't either. I guess I'm not ready
to let people know yet.
- Awesome.
- Gia, I'm sorry.
I'm still trying to
figure this thing out.
Step one,
stop calling it "this thing. "
you guys?
So, how were we supposed to get
over the wall with our instruments?
I hadn't really thought
that far ahead.
Wait! Before we go in.
I got a little something for you.
What's this for?
Teddy was getting something
for Silver, so I just thought...
Right... of course.
You know...
for a second there,
I thought you might really like me.
What?
- Look, I'm sorry...
- Shut up, douche bag.
I'm kidding.
Give me the necklace.
Is this scrimshaw?
This is rad, Dixon.
If we were dating,
I would be all over you.
And that's exactly
what I want to hear.
Now, look, I'm not telling you
you have to wear it in there
and make a big fuss
about what a great boyfriend I am...
Prepare to be fussed over.
What's the word?
The word is that I got a great guy.
- Stop it. Come on.
- No, I can't, it's true.
Look what my little Poopy got me.
- I'm sorry, "Poopy"?
- That's what she calls me.
- Cause she's my little Stinky Pants.
- I don't even want to know.
Anyway...
Where's the band, guys?
Aren't they supposed to go on soon?
You know bands... notoriously late.
Someone's probably throwing a fit
or eating a bat or something.
- Anyway, should we get drinks?
- You got it... Poopy.
Yeah, that's me.
Can we do that in public?
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
So... I got you a little gift, too.
To prove how well I know you.
- You did not have to do that.
- I know I didn't have to. I wanted to.
Because I wanted to see your face...
when you opened it up.
What do you think?
Do you love them?
- Are they my girl's best friend?
- Yes, they...
are gorgeous and big.
Thank you.
- Let's see how they look.
- Yeah, okay.
Beautiful. Perfect.
Guys, there's, like,
a zillion people out here.
We're gonna rock this bitch!
- You okay?
- Ade, what's wrong?
I can't do this.
What are you talking about?
I have never sung
in front of a crowd like this.
And I can't even take
a drink to calm down.
Don't worry.
You're going to be amazing.
I'm sorry.
I just... I can't do this.
What do you mean you can't?
I just can't.
All right, girl...
We are going to be right behind you.
You've just got to face your fears.
Don't think about who's watching...
- Come on.
- I'm sorry.
Sing in my place.
- Please?
- No way.
No.
We're a band. All right?
It's all for one...
and all that crap.
She's right.
We do it together,
or we don't do it at all.
Guys, come on.
Not a chance.
There'll be plenty of other gigs.
The important thing
is that we stick together.
Put away the puppy dog eyes.
We're not gonna rock
this bitch without you.
Hi! We're The Glorious Steinems!
- Can I have a shot of tequila?
- Sure.
Mom. What are you doing here?
Guitarist's dad's an old friend.
Don't worry.
No one's going to know I'm your mom.
Cause if you call me "Mom"
in public, I'll sock you.
How about "Mommy"?
- Swift kick to the groin.
- Gotcha.
- So, who are you here with?
- Just some friends
from school.
- Not that jerk Liam?
- Mom, he's not a jerk.
He just has god-awful
taste in women.
- Don't worry, you'll get over him.
- I know. I...
Whatever.
Which one is he, anyway?
Looks like a square to me.
What's with that helmet hair?
- Thanks, Mom.
- Shh, not so loud.
I just wanted to make
sure you're okay.
Don't lie to me.
What are you talking about?
You're here 'cause...
you have to make sure I won't
tell anyone your secret.
That's not true. Okay?
Despite everything,
I actually care about what
- happens to you.
- But you don't love me.
I don't.
You should've just
left me there to die.
Stop. Okay, just
stop manipulating me.
- I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
You have been from the start.
Even the way we got together.
You were just preying on the fact
that I felt so guilty about your uncle.
- You should feel guilty.
- Don't worry.
I do.
Every day, I do.
But I don't owe you
a relationship because of it.
So then what incentive is there
to keep me from telling?
None.
Everything I did,
I have done it because I love you.
You have to know that.
I know that you think that.
But what we had
was all based on lies.
- It wasn't love.
- Yes, it was.
It was.
And that's why I'm not
going to tell anyone.
I'm never going to tell
your secret, ever.
I'm sorry, but...
visiting hours ended a while ago.
Thank you.
I really hope you get better.
Good-bye.
I thought we were still trying
to figure this thing out.
I just had to face my fears
and not worry about
who's watching.
And don't call it "this thing."
That was an awesome show?
You okay?
I need to talk to you
about something.
It's something I feel really bad about,
but you need to know.
Or maybe you don't need to know,
but I need you to know.
What is it?
I hate these earrings.
I'm sorry.
I know that they were a gift
and it's all about the thought and...
It's kind of the thought that
bothers me. These are just
so not me.
I know most girls love diamonds,
but I look at them and I think about
about slave mining, orphans in Sierra
Leone and these mistresses in Texas
with their hair- sprayed hair...
Why are you laughing?
Here's your real present.
I remember at the beginning of the year
when we read this in Matthews' class,
you went on and on
about how much you liked it,
and how amazing it
was that Flaubert could write
from a woman's perspective,
and how much that inspired you.
And I thought to myself,
"stay away from that girl.
She's way too much. "
That's what you thought?
So, this whole time, you were...
what, you were just screwing with me?
See, I do pay attention to detail,
and I do know you.
I definitely knew those
earrings would make you mad.
They're fake... by the way.
But I also know how cute
you look when you're angry.
I hate you.
No, you don't.
Trust me. I know you.
So, your mom seems cool.
- When did you...?
- I think it's absolutely wonderful
that you can be so open with her
about your love life.
Excuse me?
I heard you, loser.
I know you're still into Liam.
What are you talking about?
I'm with Dixon now.
I saw how quickly you let go
of each other's hands
- when you thought no one was looking.
- Cause our palms were sweaty.
- You're obviously not really dating.
- Yeah, we are.
- In fact, we're...
- Totally pathetic.
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Sorry. Naomi didn't believe
that we were actually dating.
We can't have that now, can we?
That was great.
She totally bought that.
Water?
Thank you.
So, you feel like
your therapy session helped?
- Yeah, definitely.
- Good.
And do you feel better about
coming forward with what happened?
When I was at therapy,
I really thought through
what will happen
if I do come forward.
Everyone at school
will talk about me, judge me,
maybe even blame me
for what happened.
I wish I were stronger, Liam,
I really wish I were.
The truth is, I'm not.
And I'm not ready. And I don't know
when or if I ever will be.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
I should be stronger.
I should be...
It's all right.
I hate that guy for putting
you in this position.
I hate him.
Mr. Cannon, I forgot my paper.
Can I run home and get it?
- I don't know.
- Please?
You know you're, like, my
favorite teacher, right?
Okay, go get your paper,
but don't be gone too long.
- You son of a bitch.
- Get your hands off me!
You're a piece of garbage.
What's your name?!
Okay, this is cool.
Thank you.
See ya.
Thanks for letting me
borrow your car.
Yeah, no worries.
Just return it with a full tank of gas,
- and no dents.
- Yeah.
That's Adrianna, right?
Sweet.
What are you doing? You can't
exactly just park the car here.
You park it, then.
I'm Ivy's mom.
I saw your show last night.
You were fantastic.
Thank you.
You're a music producer?
Until the powers
that be tell me otherwise.
I work with a lot
of talented musicians your age.
And I'm interested in signing you.
No, I mean, yes.
I mean, really?
Oh, my God.
I can't wait to tell the band.
I wouldn't rub it in their faces.
Because I'm not interested
in signing the band.
I'm only interested in you.
Okay, just get it out
of your system now.
Do you prefer the more
colloquial "Poops,"
or perhaps the more
formal "Señor Poopy"?
Very funny.
- Do you want your money or not?
- What money?
You didn't hear about the Lakers?
Kobe sat out, and they still beat
the spread. I owe you $250.
- It pains me to take this.
- It pains me even more.
But it's my own fault.
I should have trusted my instincts.
Anyway there's a
game this weekend, and...
I want to put
the rest of this on L.A.
Man, are you sure?
Positive. I got to build back up.
See you later, man.
Later.
It's an awful day
to be stuck in school.
How about we grab our
wetsuits and head up to Zuma?
It's tempting, but I can't.
I have a history test.
Square.
Okay, I'm going
to go take a history test,
which will be a lot more
pleasant than this encounter.
What's up, Stinky Pants?
What up, Poopy?
You know, just in case
Naomi walks by.
Gotcha.
- I like the way you think.
- Thank you.
Did you hear about Liam?
He's in the principal's office.
- What? Why?
- Apparently, he attacked Mr. Cannon.
Oh, my God!
So, Liam, what happened?
Why would you go after Mr. Cannon?
I don't even know this kid.
If you don't say something, I'm going
to have no choice but to expel you.
Why don't you head back
to your class, Miles?
Thanks.
- Is Liam in there?
- You know that kid?
- He's my boyfriend.
- Say good-bye to him for me.
He's about to be expelled.
What happened?
- Please, you can't do this.
- This doesn't concern you.
Yes, it does.
I didn't tell him
what this is about.
You don't have to say anything.
Yes, I do.
Principal Wilson,
this is all my fault.
The only reason Liam
did this is because...
because Mr. Cannon
sexually harassed me.
Peach Pit Team
www.forom.com