Previously...
Your mom called me, she has cancer.
- Navid told me that you're a dealer.
- What?
- You're pregnant.
- I'm gonna keep the baby.
- 'Cause you have a huge crush on him.
- I don't.
You're not pregnant.
Stay away from my son.
- Dixon, are you okay?
- Sasha called.
She had a miscarriage.
My mom died 3 years ago.
I knows what you're going through.
He propositionned me.
- Sorry I stormed off like that.
- You don't want to apologize
- for hitting on my girlfriend?
- What?
- You should go to a meeting.
- I just want the pain to stop.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Well, well.
Open sesame.
Serena, we need
to reestablish Alpha Base...
before we can proceed
with the mission.
How you feeling?
Any better?
I got some good news.
I talked to your coach.
I explained you've been dealing
with a lot.
Threw around some pretty serious
principal rank, and guess what?
You're back on the surf team.
Thanks, but...
I'm not going to go back.
Why not?
Because I missed the practices,
so I should suffer the consequences.
There were extenuating
circumstances.
Sasha was pregnant.
And instead of supporting her,
I fought with her.
I've been trying to call her
and see if she's okay.
She hasn't returned any
of my phone calls.
That's probably 'cause...
She's trying to move on.
It's because she's devastated.
I know it.
And I'm supposed to just go
on with my life like nothing happened?
Just go surfing
while she's suffering.
How is that fair?
Thanks, but no thanks, Dad.
The system is off-line and
a lockdown protocol is in effect.
If we rebuild,
the lockdown will end...
Honey.
I'm really starting to worry
about Dixon. He seems miserable.
He'd be more miserable
if he knew Sasha manipulated him
and lied to him.
He'd be heartbroken.
He'd feel like a fool.
- I don't know.
- I do.
I was right about Sasha, wasn't I?
- Yes, you were.
- So trust me.
It's only been a couple of days.
He'll snap out of it,
and then we can all just
move on and put this behind us.
Rosie really wants...
Blueberries.
Excuse me?
Rosie really wants blueberries.
Red, red, white, blue.
Of course.
Can't take it on
an empty stomach, though.
Here's some electrolytes.
And while you drink that,
let's go over tomorrow's schedule.
All right.
The nurse is going to come
at 8:30 and it's Janet.
I know it's not her day,
but I told Linda that she could
swap with her next tuesday.
Janet's gonna take
you to the oncologist at 11:00,
which is all written here.
You have a CBC to check your
platelets and your fibrinogen levels.
And for medications for tomorrow,
everything is written here
according to what you take,
what time and with or without food.
So if you have any questions
just refer to the binder. Sound good?
What?
When did you get so organized?
- I've always been organized.
- You?
Remember in fifth grade,
I organized a class trip
to the San Diego Zoo.
I passed around that petition
listing all the reasons why
we deserved to go see the giant pandas.
You've got to be organized
to be a stage manager.
I did stage manage every school
play since like seventh grade.
Sure.
The point is,
I'm organized, and it's helping now.
So, come on.
Rosie really wants her blueberries.
This history homework is killing me.
I'm so over the Battle of the Bulge.
If you were dating Jamie, you would
so not be over the Battle of the Bulge.
- You're disgusting.
- You're jealous.
Jamie wants to know if I
can to to his frat party. No, right?
You tell me.
It's your half-birthday.
What time is the party?
I'm not going to
have a half birthday party this year.
Everything going on with my mom,
there's just not a lot of time.
Look who's here.
Thank God.
I was getting worried.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, you.
How you holding up?
I'm actually doing a lot better.
That's good.
That's so good.
I'm sorry I was such a mess.
Are you kidding?
You had every right to be a mess.
You made a stupid mistake,
and you lost the guy you loved, and...
- I am not helping. I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
I'm okay.
That's good, Ade.
And it's good to see you.
I'll see you all at lunch?
- How's she doing?
- I don't know
She says she's okay, but she doesn't
want to celebrate her half-birthday.
What?
That would probably help
her take her mind off her mom.
Right?
Whatever. I'm not done
working on her.
No matter what, we have to
get her a gift. Maybe a massage.
That sounds perfect.
But I'm actually running
a little low on funds.
Don't even worry about it.
Pick up the gift
certificate, we'll call it even.
- What do you think?
- That's so cute.
It's silly.
- "Happy Half-Birthday."
- $150... that should do it, right?
- Perfect.
- Good to have you back, Ade.
It's really good to be back.
I want to talk to you.
I didn't hit on Jen.
And honestly,
that woman is a psychotic bitch.
- Enough.
- She is.
You know what, I'm starting
to think your stepdad was right, okay?
Maybe you are a bad seed.
John Campos dares me to eat
ten packets of butter this morning.
Don't mean to brag, but I ate 11.
The kid had five. I swear he
was gonna hurl all over the cafeteria.
That's great.
- Is everything okay?
- Just fine.
Really? 'Cause you don't seem fine.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Obviously it's something.
What's going on?
What is it?
Just back off.
You're not my girlfriend.
Another reason to have
your half-birthday soiree...
I just bought a ridiculously hot dress,
and you'll get to see me in it.
Tempting, but I'll pass.
Pass on what?
Seeing Naomi look ridiculously hot.
Silver's half-birthday party,
which she's trying to
cancel for the first time in years.
I got to go.
Jamie's here.
Just promise you'll think about it.
My dress is...
Picture lots of cleavage, excellent ass.
It's amazing.
We'll find another occasion for it.
Maybe bowling or something.
Half-birthday party?
You so don't seem
like the type of person
that would make
a big deal out of it.
It's a long story.
It's a long walk to class.
For my tenth birthday,
... all my friends and I were
gonna go camping in my backyard.
I was super excited.
Counting the days excited.
And then on my birthday
my mom got trashed
and I had to cancel the party.
She'd missed birthdays before...
she'd gotten drunk
or just forgotten...
but, this one,
this was the last straw.
I just gave up on birthdays
in general.
- Too many expectations.
- And half-birthdays?
If you don't have high expectations
then you can't get let down.
What does one get a person
for their half-birthday present?
A half-DVD?
Just special features?
A half-bottle of champagne?
I know.
A half-bikini.
Perv.
All right.
How about a half-spring break trip?
It wouldn't be so bad.
A one-way trip to Cabo.
Despite the recent overdose
at Malibu Canyon High,
the students are seemingly
apathetic.
Teen drug use has reared
its ugly head at West Bev before.
Was the case at Malibu Canyon
an isolated incident,
or an indication of a larger,
yet uncovered problem
plaguing the Los Angeles
school system?
I don't think we've officially met.
I'm Navid.
Why would you tell Annie
I'm a drug dealer?
- That's what I heard.
- From who?
A friend of mine.
She said you sold to a friend of hers.
I assume you didn't talk
to this friend of a friend?
No, but...
'Cause if you did, you would
have realized that it's not true.
Don't you check your sources
before you publish your stories?
- Of course.
- Of course you do?
I wish you'd give me the
same respect.
For the record,
I'm not a drug dealer.
I'm just a guy who doesn't have
a lot of friends here.
Never have.
I'm not a popular kid,
and because of that, people like
to spread rumors about me.
I guess I should be
used to it by now.
People gossiping, but...
It still feels crappy.
Peach Pit Team
www.forom.com
Season 02 episode 09
A Trip to the Moon
Hey, you.
I missed you all morning.
I missed you, too.
- You want to go to Quality for lunch?
- Sounds good.
I have some pretty big news.
Really?
What?
How do you think we
should get to Quality?
Beverly or Burton?
I was thinking Beverly, but Beverly
can get so busy this time of day, so...
Then, let's take Burton.
What's the big news?
Sometimes I take Olympic...
once in a while... and it's like
- smooth sailing, completely.
- What's the news?
That?
I cut a few scenes together from
my movie and showed it to my father.
Granted, the guy, he
produces big-budget movies,
most of
which are completely soulless.
- But?
- But still...
He... responded to it.
He liked it.
- That's great.
- But that's not even the best part.
- What?
- There's a Shia LeBeouf movie.
There's a small part.
My dad's producing.
And I got you an audition.
- My God. Are you serious?
- I'm dead serious.
You just have to promise me
that when you're a big movie star,
you'll still have time for me.
I promise.
'Cause, after all,
I'll still need someone
to get me coffee.
- What up, guys?
- What's up?
Where's Liam?
Is he coming?
Don't know. He was in a nasty mood.
Bit my head off earlier.
Is it true you downed, like ten
butter packets this morning?
- 11, actually.
- Eleven?
What do you
guys think's going on with him?
Who knows?
We've got curly fries.
I'm more of a tater tot man, myself.
You can't say tater tot
and man in the same sentence.
Did you ask him what was wrong?
- Why not?
- Liam's not the
"talk about
your feelings" kind of guy.
What if something's actually wrong?
I haven't smelled dead
bodies coming from his car.
- That is a good sign.
- This isn't a joke.
He's obviously really
upset about something.
It's sad that the people
who are supposed to be his friends
don't even really seem to care.
Excuse me.
I swear, every year, I
forget about the Santa Anas
and then one morning,
I'll wake up...
And I'm boring you.
Maybe a little.
I'm sorry. I'm nervous.
I know that you saw me with
Teddy, and I wanted to explain.
I wanted to talk to you about it,
but since your break-up,
the timing wasn't right.
Teddy and I are...
We sort of...
We're friends and I feel
so badly about that
because of everything that happened
between you two, but his mom...
She had cancer, too,
and he's been really helpful.
Sorry that I didn't tell you sooner,
but if you don't want me to be friends,
then I won't.
That's what I'll do. I will
stop being friends with him.
I just want you to be happy.
If being friends with Teddy
is going to help you deal with your mom,
- go for it.
- Really?
Really. I'm fine.
- Ade, thank you. Thank you.
- Of course.
I'll be right back.
I got to go to the bathroom.
There's no way that your office
can deliver the records to our house?
That's okay.
I'll figure it out.
I don't usually do home deliveries,
so this will be extra.
Your homework.
And a black coffee.
Thank you so much. I needed this.
Everything okay?
My mom has to see this new doctor
and she needs her medical records,
- but her nurse had an emergency.
- I'll pick them up.
That's sweet, but you can't.
I have to sign for them.
Then I'll stay here with your
mom while you go pick up her records.
I don't...
I have plenty of experience
with sick moms.
Trust me.
I got it covered.
30 minutes?
- Thank you so much.
- I'll just add it to your tab.
You okay?
Thinking about Sasha?
I just wish she knew how sorry I am.
I hear you.
Speaking of apologies...
Catch you later.
Fancy meeting you here.
I want the same stuff I got last time,
but I only have 20.
Could you just sell me a few pills
now and then I'll buy the rest later?
Sorry, this isn't
an a la carte service.
- Call me when you have the money.
- Wait...
Here.
That's more like it.
You know where to find me.
Really? So you don't like it.
Not this time.
You going to take it?
I think I will take my
chances on lady luck.
And it's a good thing I did.
Careful there.
Your suits are showing.
You're throwing down a six?
Bad move.
- Next hand, double or nothing.
- You are on, sucker.
- Hey, you.
- Your mom is going down.
- No way!
- How's that for bringing it, hmm?
What you got now?
Hello?
It's...
- I know.
- Right.
I didn't think you'd be calling.
- But I'm glad.
- Ade, I saw you buying drugs today.
What?
- Why would you start using again?
- I'm not.
I saw you in your car with Jasper.
Look. Whatever you think you saw,
you were wrong.
- Ade, are you serious right now?
- Why are you even calling?
I thought
I wasn't your problem anymore.
Come on.
I still care about you, okay?
I'll be back in about an hour.
I got to go run by Sasha's.
What?
I just want to go over there
and make sure she's okay.
Apologize face to face.
I don't think that's a good idea.
You know, it may not be,
but I still got to try.
You know, I got to let her
know that I'm here for her.
Well, that's all well and good,
but I think it's obvious
that Sasha doesn't want
to see you right now.
Because I was being a jerk
and I made her feel like she was alone,
- which is why I have to go apologize.
- But now is not the time.
We're about to sit down for dinner.
Okay, fine. Then I'll go after.
What? Why are you guys making
such a big deal out of this?
Dixon, sit down.
I have something to tell you.
Sasha didn't have a miscarriage.
What?
She wasn't pregnant.
I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
I had some suspicions.
A lot of what she said
didn't add up,
so I went to see her
and I caught her in some lies.
I guess she said she had
a miscarriage to save face.
So, she wasn't really pregnant?
No, she wasn't.
Wait. And you guys knew
about this all along?
Look, your father
wanted to tell you, but I...
I wanted to protect you.
I didn't want you to get
your heart broken and not trust women.
Well...
Now I know one woman I can't trust.
No, it doesn't hurt.
Why should it?
Go, go, have a great time.
I couldn't care less.
That was great.
You are incredible.
That's a lie.
I know I'm not great.
I wish you could see yourself
the way that I see you.
You'd never have a moment
of self-doubt ever.
No, I'm serious.
You're beautiful, talented, soulful.
Sometimes I just,
I can't believe how lucky
I am to have found you.
Okay, back to work.
Where were we?
"But I won't have a
great time without you.
"Don't you understand?
I'm asking you to come with me."
I love you.
That's not your line.
I know.
Oh, I'm sorry. I shouldn't
have said anything.
Clearly, you don't feel
the same way.
No, Annie...
It's just that I wanted
to be the one who said it first.
You scumbag.
Good morning to you, too, man.
I saw you with Ade.
I saw you selling to her.
- Whatever you think you saw...
- No, you went into her car,
and you came out with cash.
What else did I have to see?
I spotted her lunch money.
Told her it was on me.
She insisted she pay me back.
She's a nice girl.
Why'd you two break up?
You just stay the hell
away from her.
Or what?
I'll say it one last time:
I'm not a drug dealer.
But if I was, I wouldn't be
the kind of guy you'd want
- to mess with, would I?
- You threatening me?
Not at all. Like I said,
not a drug dealer.
Who are those guys?
I don't know. They must've heard
the waves are breaking out here.
This is our beach.
Better not get in our way.
- Dude, chill.
- You chill.
And can you not use all my wax?
Yo, everything okay, man?
Yes! I'm fine.
I tried.
Silver? I'm in here.
Happy Birthday!
What? I don't understand.
I missed so many of your birthdays,
I wanted to make it up to you
before it was too late. So, welcome.
You're seven, by the way.
When I wanted to be an astronaut.
Now come here.
Oh, my God, a fishbowl space helmet?
Really?
Put it on.
You might not think this is
as exciting at my age,
but it totally is!
Would you like a glass of Tang?
Kinda hard to drink
through the helmet.
Now I'm not sure the
constellations are accurate.
It's incredible!
There's so much more to see.
There's more? Are...?
Like I said,
I missed a lot of birthdays.
I must be 12, when I was
obsessed with the '80s.
Oh, radical, dude! Yes!
How did you do all this, Mom?
I had a little help from the nurses.
But the biggest help was Teddy.
He was here for hours
with one of his dad's
fancy-schmancy set designer friends.
I mean, this is...
This is all so, so wow.
I understand why you're upset.
My intentions were good,
but, but obviously, I was wrong.
I can't believe you.
Dixon, please?
Dixon, stop.
I just want to talk to you.
Come on. I know
you're upset with your mom.
Whatever...
It's not like she's my real mom.
So, what made you want
a camping party in the first place?
Horror movies.
In every good horror movie
there's always a scary camping scene.
I'll never understand where you got
your love of being terrified.
It gets you out
of your head, you know?
I mean, the scarier the movie,
the more I could just forget
all my problems.
Me...
You...
You were just never there.
Which was hard.
You not coming to the plays
that I stage-managed...
Worrying about you when
you didn't come home at night,
just hoping that you were okay.
Honey, I am so sorry.
Which makes up for nothing, but...
No, it does.
This does.
I was so scared that you,
that you would die
and I wouldn't have
anything good to hold onto.
And now I do.
Now I have my tenth birthday party
where we went camping.
Oh, honey...
Enough of this sappiness.
Eat your marshmallow.
Just remember to save your appetite.
Tomorrow is your official
half-birthday.
All your friends are coming over
for a big barbecue.
Are you serious?
You've been celebrating
your half-birthday for years,
and I am glad that I finally
get to be a part of it.
Me, too!
Cheers!
Awesome.
Hey! Didn't think you'd make it.
You've been a little M.I.A. lately.
I get alerts on my phone that
let me know how the waves are breaking.
So you know I couldn't resist
when I heard about these swells.
Plus, you know, I just had
to get out of the house.
Everything okay, man?
Turns out Sasha wasn't
really pregnant.
What?
She lied about the whole thing.
I wish I'd get alerts that let me know
when crazy girls are approaching.
They probably got an app for that.
And I bet it beeps nonstop.
What the hell, man?!
- You tell me, dude. That was my wave.
- Like hell it was. Don't push me!
Come on!
- Get off me! He's a punk!
- We're leaving.
- No, we're not.
- Yes, we are.
Dude, what the hell?
Relax!
- What was that back there?
- That guy was being a jerk!
You were the jerk!
What the hell's going on, man!
- Nothing.
- It's not nothing.
You nearly got us in a fight back there,
and you're gonna tell us why.
Back off, man.
Or what? You gonna hit me?
Try it. You can't take
both of us down.
Make that all three of us.
- What is your problem?
- We don't have a problem.
Liam, we're your friends.
Friends tell each other
what the hell is going on.
So come on. What
the hell's going on?
Someone's been telling lies
about me, all right?
- Who, Liam?
- Jen, Naomi's sister.
That super hot Amazon chick
from the N.E.R.D. party?
- Sorry, she wasn't that hot.
- What'd she say?
She told Matthews that I hit on her.
She told my mother
that I was stalking Naomi.
- All sorts of stuff.
- What?
- Why?
- Forget about it.
We'll wait you out, man.
And believe me,
we can wait all night.
Tell us why, dude.
Last year, at the after-prom party,
she was the person that I...
That I had sex with.
So, wait, so, so, it wasn't Annie?
- I told you it wasn't.
- I know, but I still thought...
- You had sex with Naomi's sister?
- It wasn't like that.
She told me she was her neighbor.
She's full of lies, this woman,
and she's be trying to destroy me
since last year.
- That's messed up.
- I'm gonna destroy Jen
before she destroys me.
I just don't know how
I'm gonna do it.
It's not how you're gonna do it...
It's how we're gonna do it.
Hell, yeah.
That Amazon bitch ain't
gonna know what hit her.
Get her right in the kneecaps.
You guys, you...
You don't have to do this.
We know we don't have to.
But we're your friends, remember?
Later, Liam.
What's wrong?
I just got the call;
I didn't get the part.
My dad is such an idiot.
I know you were so much
better than all those other girls.
Apparently not.
You ever hear of Johnny Weissmuller?
No? Exactly.
But Clark Gable, he lost
the role of Tarzan to him.
You will get your part, Jane.
- Maybe.
- No maybe.
You will.
You're a star.
You're an old-fashioned star.
You're so talented, it's incredible.
Not to mention beautiful.
You're an extraordinary
person, Annie.
You're so vulnerable
and yet so strong and...
So innocent, but also wise.
I mean, you're Annie.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
And...
And I... I want my first
time to be with you.
Are you sure that you're ready?
Positive.
So, look...
I owe you an apology.
Dude, I totally get
why you snapped at me.
- You've obviously had a lot going on.
- About what I said in the hall.
About you not being my girlfriend.
I know you don't think
you're my girlfriend.
No kidding. We're just having fun,
dude, that's all.
- So we're cool?
- Yeah. Totally.
Good.
Hey, do you maybe want
to grab something to eat?
See who can scarf down
the most ketchup packets?
Cute.
Maybe another time.
All right.
Catch you later.
You know what? I'm pretty hungry,
so what the hell?
What a you in the mood for?
Tacos.
Really?
Tacos and ketchup?
Thanks, anyway.
No luck, boss.
I just talked to my friend, the one
who said she bought drugs from Jasper,
- and she won't help us.
- We have to find a way to prove it.
I want to bring this dirtbag down.
Look, I just came to apologize.
I should have trusted you
when you told me...
Is this about the fact
that you called Jasper sketchy?
Actually.
Of course not.
Whatever. I don't even know
why I care what you think.
You're clearly not
a very good judge of character.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
Your girlfriend faked a miscarriage.
Sounds like a real winner.
Go to hell.
Hey, what's wrong?
I went to
the spa to buy the gift certificate
for Silver,
and I got out of my car,
and out of nowhere,
there was this guy.
And he grabbed my purse.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
He took everything.
You know, my credit cards,
the money for
Silver's gift, everything.
I don't care about the money, I care
about you. Did you call the police?
They came, and I filed a report.
But they can't do much
because I didn't see the guy.
It just happened so quickly.
It was so scary.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's going to be okay.
- Did I wake you up?
- Actually, yes.
Good. I wanted to be the first person
to wish you a happy half-birthday.
Thank you.
For everything.
Last night with my mom,
it was perfect.
I'm glad.
- So I'll see you at the barbeque?
- Yeah, can't wait.
Bye, Teddy.
Mom...
It's time to wake up.
It's my half-birthday!
Mom? Fine. You don't have
to get up 'cause it's my birthday,
you gotta get up to take your pills.
I need an ambulance.