Previously...
- Finn Court, please.
- Not here.
- Excuse me?
- Checked out about an hour ago.
You really should
be a little nicer to me
now that I'll be
handling your finances.
I know you can take this tennis
all the way. No more distractions,
no more girlfriends.
Break up with her, Teddy.
I believe in you, and to see you
all depressed and down on yourself,
it hurts... the worst
feeling in the world.
Seeing you happy-
that means everything to me.
A beautiful girl like you
doesn't have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
There's no one, no special guy,
no one.
What movie are we going to see?
Don't care, as long as it's not
some stupid pop culture piece of crap.
Just because something's popular
doesn't mean it's any good.
Sometimes,
it's the exact opposite. Lots of people
like cigarettes, but they cause cancer.
- Any idea what he's talking about?
- Stupid pop culture cancer.
- What is your problem?
- You want to know what my problem is?
You want to know what my problem is?
I'll show you.
This right here is my problem.
Javier?
Can you get out of here, please?!
I'm tired of looking at his face!
Aren't you guys broken up?
I know that already.
But maybe I don't want to be.
Have you told Ade that
you ended it with Lila yet?
No, I didn't.
That's the first step:
you're supposed to tell her.
And step two: let her
know you want her back.
And step three: cut a single,
become an overnight teen heartthrob.
Does he kiss like a teen
heartthrob or not?
I don't know. We've been on,
like, two dates.
If you guys come to my gig on Friday,
you can meet him. He'll be there.
Ade, it's your first gig!
I'm so excited!
Miss, do you have another card?
This one's been declined.
Why were my cards declined?
Fix this, please.
Let me take a look and see.
They don't work
because I canceled them.
You've been spending entirely
too much money and,
you're on a financial diet now,
consisting
of low-denomination greens...
that's fives and tens,
little sister.
Would you excuse me? I have to
sign a check for my shrimp vendor.
I'll ask if he's hiring.
Hi. This is Jay Boyd.
I don't know a Jay Boyd.
What are you doing?
That's my phone.
This really isn't a good time.
Can I call you back?
- What was that all about?
- None of your business.
Now that I'm in charge,
things are going to change...
a lot of things.
Frugal is the new black.
Do you really have to go
to Australia all summer?
I'm gonna really miss you.
You should come.
To Australia?
If you wanted to.
I want to.
Really?
Yeah, I really want to.
I've got an idea.
What if we start our presentation by
playing Vivaldi for, like, ten minutes?
Which means we'd only have to talk
about Vivaldi for, like, five.
I think Matthews had something
a little more interactive in mind.
But we could do an interpretive
dance while the music plays...
And I'm serious.
Bring the ballet slippers next meeting.
Peach Pit team
www.forom.com
Season 02 Episode 21
Javianna
When did you get
out of the hospital?
Couple days ago.
My doctors think I'm ready
to reintegrate into West Bev,
so here I am.
Reintegrating.
That's great.
- Are you...
- Better?
Yeah.
I feel better.
Or at least I will, once I say
to you what I need to say...
There's no excuses for what I did.
But I need to explain.
- You don't have to.
- I do.
I was always an outcast.
And then you came along.
And I saw how much my
uncle's death affected you,
and I took advantage of that.
I didn't think I was gonna
fall in love with you.
But I did.
And then, when you
threatened to leave me,
I panicked.
Whatever.
I'm not here to make excuses.
I'm here to apologize.
You're one of the good ones, Annie.
If there's any way that
you can forgive me,
- maybe we can be friends.
- Jasper, stop.
I can forgive you.
And I do.
You do?
But we can't be friends.
There's just too
much that's happened.
I understand.
Thanks for listening to me.
What's the difference between
a big tennis practice and a regular?
A big tennis practice comes
before a big tennis tournament.
Which I'm gonna win, by the way,
earning myself #1 rankings in nationals.
- Hold your applause.
- I can't. Look. I can't.
Then, you better go.
I should definitely go.
Go.
What?
Has Teddy dipped his pen in
the ol'inkwell recently?
- Dipped his pen...?
- Have you done the mattress mambo?
No, we have not had sex.
But I want to. I really want to.
The only time I've ever done it,
I was going through a manic phase.
Now... I feel like
I'm a virgin again.
I just want it to
be right this time.
But how do you know when
it's the right time?
I think you'll just know.
What are you doing here?
Every now and then I like to stop at
high schools and get a little ego boost.
I just wanted to see you.
Come. I have a special
night planned for us.
I am really not dressed.
I had my assistant pick up a dress
and shoes.
I hope that's okay.
Are you serious?
- Is that a yes?
- Yes. That's a yes.
- Let's go.
- This is amazing.
Miss You.
Thanks, man.
You're still pushing
your forehand a little.
Everyone's an expert
from the sidelines.
But I know.
You got a text from Silver.
Still having a little trouble
accepting it's over?
Actually, it's not.
Over.
I thought we decided you
were breaking up with her.
You decided.
I decided I didn't want to.
I love her, Dad.
I'm not breaking up with her.
You're not thinking straight. You got
to focus on your tennis right now.
I am focusing on my tennis.
I can do both.
- What?
- I don't know.
I thought you were different, that
you were going to be the one kid of mine
that was a success.
Is this a good time?
- Sure.
- What's going on?
Ivy and her mom are going
to Australia this summer.
Just for some fun.
- And, they invited me, so...
- Absolutely not.
Dixon doesn't deserve
a trip right now.
What do you mean,
he doesn't deserve a trip?
I mean, he's not going.
- Shouldn't this be a discussion?
- You know...
- It's okay.
- No. It's not okay.
I happen to think the trip sounds
like a really great opportunity
if there's parental supervision.
It's not gonna happen.
And in case you've forgotten,
I have a say in this, too.
Really, please...
- Just forget it.
- No. We're not going to forget it.
Your father and I will
discuss it like a couple.
And then we will get back to you.
Javier?
Where are you?
Isn't this theater amazing?
Please, sit.
What's wrong? You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Teddy, I don't think you're fine.
Come on. What's going on?
It's my dad.
He is such an ass, I swear.
Sometimes the only place I feel
like I can breathe is here with you.
I mean it.
You make me so happy, Silver.
Me, too.
You make me so happy, too.
I thought you wanted to wait.
I did.
Now I'm ready.
It just feels so right.
Can you believe Jen?
She sent my Mercedes back and is
making me drive that hunk of junk.
There was a lot of smoke coming
from the exhaust. I'll take a look.
I'm poor, Liam.
What is there to live for?
I have to get my money back.
I have to.
- I think Jay Boyd is the key.
- Who's he?
I don't know. There's
a dozen Jay Boyds in the phone book,
I've to find the right one,
who made Jen all jittery and suspicious.
Or you could just wait until you
turn 18 when you get it back anyway.
Are you insane? I can't live
like a pauper for six months.
- Come on, you're not exactly a pauper.
- I can't shop. I can't spa.
I might as well eat fast
food out of the trash can.
Come on.
I cannot believe
you're being so unsympathetic.
I need your support.
I need you to be here for me.
You have got to be kidding me.
All I am is there for you.
In fact, if anyone hasn't
been here, it's you.
What are you talking about?
The fact that you have no idea what's
going on in my life for the last month,
none.
So for you to say
that I'm not there...
Whatever, Naomi.
You ready for bangers and mash?
That's Australian for
sausage and hash browns.
You better get used to the lingo,
because if you can come up
with the money for a ticket,
you are going.
- To Australia?
- You got it, mate.
You going to talk
like that until I leave?
I'll give it a fair go.
- Thanks, Mom.
- You're welcome.
Wait, why is everybody
staring at me?
I don't know.
Could have something to do with the limo
that pulled up to school yesterday.
Which brings me to my next question.
Would you do an interview with
the Blaze about what it's like
recording with Javier?
Lila was going to ask you to do the
story, but she's laying low on the Blaze
since the breakup with Navid.
Wait, Navid and Lila broke up?
- Yeah.
- When?
I don't know... like a week ago.
Why wouldn't he tell me that?
Why would he tell you that?
You're right.
I guess there's no reason to...
What's going on?
Do you like Navid? Again?
It doesn't even matter.
No, it doesn't matter.
Navid and Lila have been
broken up for over a week
and if he liked me,
he would have told me.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Mr. Hollywood Sign.
Welcome back.
Really,
we've all missed you.
Not me, but I'm sure
some junkies missed you.
They put a straitjacket
on your tongue in the nuthouse?
He is crazy.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he killed his uncle.
What is wrong with you?
You're pathetic.
You two belong together.
- You didn't have to do that.
- I did.
Jasper, all of this,
everything that's happened...
It all started
with me and your uncle...
- It's not your fault.
- It is.
If I hadn't...
It's okay.
How can you say that?
You forgave me.
And I forgive you.
I forgive you.
Mr. Montgomery. Hi.
Spence. Please.
Are you looking for Teddy?
Because he's not here right now.
No, actually, I'm here
to talk to you.
Come on in.
Would you like something
to drink or to eat?
- I don't think I have anything...
- I'm fine. Thanks.
I'd like to ask you a question.
How long have you been
going out with my son?
Officially?
A couple months, I guess.
Do you know how long
he's been playing tennis?
Since he was four.
- That's a long time.
- Long time.
Now he's got this one chance
to go pro.
One chance.
Do you want to be the one
that ruins that for him?
Me?
Your relationship is
starting to get in the way.
He's losing focus.
So tell me something.
How much is it going to cost
to get you to walk away?
What?
$100,000.
$150?
No, I think...
I think you should leave.
Please.
If you love my son,
don't get in the way of his dream.
Looks good.
Thanks.
You were right.
I've been entirely too
wrapped up in my own life.
But I want to be here for you. I do.
I screwed up.
But I'm here now.
And I promise it will
not happen again.
Come on.
Tell me what's going on.
My dad came back.
- What? I thought he was in...
- He got out.
Early parole.
He just showed up here talking
about how he wanted a relationship.
He did?
What happened?
He took off.
I'm sorry, Liam.
Whatever. I'm fine.
I know you're fine.
I can't believe I
wasn't there for you.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
But like I said,
it won't happen again.
You can trust me.
Poor people tend to be honorable.
Dude, you've got to
stop torturing yourself.
"Romantic night for
Javianna."
"Javianna?"
Really?
- What's up?
- Nothing. I was looking for Silver.
She's not here.
Thanks.
So I hear you and Lila broke up.
That we did.
No, but it's cool.
You know, I'm glad to be free.
You know me,
I'm not one to be tied down.
So, how about you?
Javianna?
My God, you saw that?
No, I didn't.
No, I did.
Because Dixon showed it to me.
So yeah, I did see it,
indirectly.
Let me just say that I'm really
happy for you. I mean, Javier...
Javier... he seems like
such a terrific guy.
Talented, handsome.
He seems like one of
those guys with the,
washboard abs. Am I right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Dude, I knew it!
You go, girl!
Tomorrow is my first solo show,
so in case you want to come.
Cool.
I'll run it through the...
old calendario.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Did I let on that I
had too many feelings?
Not at all. You let on that
you have feelings for Javier.
- And his washboard abs.
- Dude, she...
She doesn't like me, all right?
See, how can I compete
with a guy like that?
I can't serenade her
in some fancy theater.
My rabbi made me lip-synch the
Torah portion at my bar mitzvah.
Look. I'm sorry.
But you have something that
Javier can't sing about, man.
You have a history with Adrianna.
Dude, you guys were in love, man.
So tap into that.
And, make your play already.
175.
Dude, I can't go any lower than 200.
Look, man. This represents
two years of my life.
Carefully cultivated.
All right, I got a playlist
for every occasion.
And I'm throwing in my dock,
dude. Come on.
Annie's Sweet 16 party mix.
Yeah, that was me.
What the hell?
Thank you, man.
What was that all about?
Making money, baby.
$600 in a day, to be exact.
- Why are you selling all your stuff?
- For our trip to Australia.
My parents said if I could come up with
the money for the ticket, I can go, so
- I'm coming up with the money.
- By selling all your stuff?
Look, honestly,
this trip to Australia
is the only thing I'm
focusing on right now.
With everything
going on with my parents,
going on this trip and,
spending my summer with you...
It means everything to me.
I'm so sorry.
I just lost my #1 ranking,
which means I just screwed
up my draw at nationals, which means
I just threw away everything I've been
working for for the past three years.
I shouldn't have lost.
I mean, I've beaten that kid twice.
Maybe he got better.
I shouldn't have stayed up so late
last night. I should have gone to bed.
This isn't working.
Our relationship. It's...
It's too much for me and...
It's gotten too serious.
It's not what I wanted.
I've been thinking
about this for a while,
and I just wanted to wait
until after your match. I'm sorry.
No. Silver, wait!
You're gonna knock 'em dead,
you know?
Thank you.
My God. Stop kissing or I might
take a picture and send it to Perez.
On that note, I should probably go.
Wait, what? You're not staying
for Ade's first gig?
Javier has to go to New York.
He has a gig tomorrow.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
It's a full house out there.
Really? Yes!
So...
Did Navid come?
I didn't see him, actually.
Navid again? Really?
No. There is no "Navid again."
I mean, he's moved on.
And so have I.
- What took you so long?
- I had to pick this up.
Listen. Navid, look.
I like you,
but me and Ivy,
we kind of got a good thing...
Just shut up.
It's for Ade, okay?
**** Bro.
Like you said, we have history.
I just need to remind her that
no one else knows her like I do.
So, here's the 11 and a six
because we first kissed
on the sixth of November.
And here's her favorite flower.
A little tulip.
And... her favorite food:
a little hamburger
with tiny, tiny pickles on it.
Cool.
Just do me a favor.
When you actually give it to her,
lose the baby voice.
Gotcha. But I'm not
gonna give it to her.
I'm going to put it
in her dressing room
while she's performing,
with a note on it that says,
"Meet me on the roof."
- Why the roof?
- Ade's favorite movie is
An Affair to Remember.
And there's this super-romantic scene
where they're meeting on
the roof of the Empire State Building.
How cute is this? A little, mini Empire
State Building.
Dude. The voice.
Yeah. Whatever.
Wish me luck, bro.
Gotcha.
What's wrong?
I've been thinking, and I really
don't think you should be selling
all your stuff to come to Australia.
It's a little extreme, don't you think?
How else am I going to get the money?
We're not all rich, you know?
And what do you mean by that?
Are you, like, implying that
I'm spoiled or something?
No. That's not what I meant.
That's kind of exactly what
it sounded like.
I'm sorry that my mom has money.
- And I'm sorry my parents don't.
- You see?
This is kind of exactly why
you shouldn't be selling your stuff.
- I'm sorry. What?
- What do you mean, "what"?
- Look at us. We're fighting.
- Because you're being all judgmental.
So now, all the sudden
I'm judgmental?
If that's what you think then you really
shouldn't be coming to Australia at all.
Fine. Then maybe we
shouldn't be dating at all.
So, for the visual
part of the presentation,
I thought we could
use some visual aids.
Obviously, we'll use a portrait,
but maybe we could actually
take one of Vivaldi's scores
and blow it up really big.
What?
I don't know
if this is my place or not,
but I saw you with
Jasper the other day...
- The guy is a psycho.
- No, he's not. He just...
He snapped.
But everything's okay now.
All right? He apologized to me.
- You can't really be serious.
- Look, please,
just let's not talk about Jasper.
I know what I'm doing.
So, will you, pull up
the written part on my laptop
- while I look through our notes?
- Yeah, sure.
- What'd you call it?
- "Vivaldi," I think.
Here's a untitled document.
What just happened?
Nothing.
Look, I don't feel like
doing work anymore, okay?
That's fine.
I'll just get out of here.
Having fun?
Not really. No.
Me and Ivy just got into a fight.
And I think we broke up.
Seems to be a lot
of that going around.
Me and Teddy...
We kind of broke up, too.
Really?
- I'm sorry.
- It sucks.
Yeah. It really sucks.
My man! Your music library?
It's friggin' awesome, dude. And I'm not
just saying that cause I'm drunk.
Good to know, man.
But I am!
I'm seriously wasted!
You guys want some vodka?
Sure. Why not?
Mademoiselle?
Sure.
- Cheers.
What are you doing out here?
Okay. What's wrong, hon?
I broke up with Dixon.
What? Why? Last I heard,
he was coming away with us.
I know. But, you know,
then he starts selling all of his stuff
to pay for his ticket, and...
And?
And I don't know. It suddenly became,
like, the biggest thing in his life.
It was all he could talk about.
What if we get to Australia and,
We don't even get along?
Then, we'll have to drive him
to the Outback and ditch him.
It's not funny.
Or we could take him to the airport.
- You freaked out?
- I totally freaked out.
I get why you're freaked out,
but, Ivy, sweetie,
instead of picking a fight,
you know, maybe you could
have talked to Dixon
about how you were feeling...
Are you sure the
bathroom is this way?
Yeah, for sure.
No clue?
Not a one. Not a one.
Oh, wait.
Here it is!
Ladies first.
Thanks.
One question, what's it about this place
that says "Ladies' Room" to you?
What?
It's a broom closet!
You sent me to go to the bathroom
in a broom closet!
Okay, guilty as charged.
Let's go.
Can I say one thing before we leave
our broom closet forever?
Forever!
Ivy's an idiot for
breaking up with you
because you, Dixon Wilson,
you are a great...
- guy.
- Oh, stop.
Thank you.
And, I mean,
I have to say, too, Teddy
is a complete idiot
because you, Miss Erin Silver...
you are a great girl.
Thank you!
No problem, no problem.
- Listen...
- This is a total... it was a mistake.
Total mistake cause...
We're both drunk.
Exact. Totally drunk, and,
totally idiotic.
- So it never...
- Yeah nothing. Never happened.
Never happened.
Ladies first.
Hey, Dixon, can I...?
can I talk to you for a second?
- I'll see you later.
- Sure.
Okay, look, I messed up, okay?
I know. I just...
I don't even know.
I guess I'm kind of this...
you know, no-strings-attached
kind of girl,
and somehow in my mind,
Australia just
kinda became like this marriage.
No offense or anything,
but to me, it was just a trip.
- Right.
- A chance to get away for a summer
with a cool girl and maybe
see a kangaroo or something.
I know. I just freaked out.
But...
I do really want you to come
if you still want to.
Come here.
Good job.
- You were great out there.
- Thank you.
Amazing!
What are you still doing here?!
I thought you had to catch
a plane to New York.
One of the perks of private planes.
I stayed for the first song,
and I just couldn't leave.
- Stop it.
- No, really.
Which got me thinking.
How do you like to come to New York
and perform our duet onstage?
You're kidding, right?
There's a car outside,
but we have to leave now.
- Now? As in now now?
- As in five minutes ago now.
What about my stuff?
My assistant will pack the dressing room
make sure everything is in the hotel,
and anything else you need
we'll just buy in New York.
- You in?
- Yeah, I'm in.
- I am totally in!
- Let's go.
We're off to New York!
Come out and see us there!
What's up, Dad?
How could you even ask if
you could go to Australia?
What were you thinking?
Look, I thought it would be
a great opportunity,
and Mom told me that you
and her talked about it...
We did, and, she said you could go
cause she doesn't know what happened.
She doesn't know about the gambling,
the breaking into school.
Then maybe
you should tell me about it.
- How's the surfing going?
- How's it going?
Yeah, I mean, have you learned
any new tricks recently?
I don't really do tricks.
What's all this interest in surfing?
Potential housekeeper.
I'll call her back after lunch.
What do you mean? We have Rosa.
Why would we need another housekeeper?
We had to let Rosa go.
What? Why?
She stole some coins from
Jeffrey's collection.
I don't think that could be true.
I mean, it can't be.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
Look, can I see you?
I really need to talk.
Yeah, listen, can we talk later?
I'm actually in bed.
I think I have the flu.
Are you okay?
Do you need anything?
Just rest.
I'll call you back, okay?
All right.
Up yours, loser!
Listen, I'm really sorry that I butted
into your business last night.
No I'm sorry I overreacted.
I was just in a bad mood.
No, it's fine.
It happens.
Listen, I could really
use your advice.
- Can we meet in the park?
- Of course.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
More to the point,
what are you doing here?
Oh, so you must be Jay Boyd?
Are you having an
affair with my sister?
God, no.
No offense, sweetie.
Naomi, this is my new assistant Leo.
Who's Jay Boyd then? Why'd you act
like you were hiding something
when he called you on the phone?
Dr. Boyd will see you now.
Okay, thank you.
Because, Naomi,
I was hiding something.
You got me.
Jay Boyd is my OB.
Surprise!
You're gonna be an auntie.
Peach Pit team
www.forom.com