Previously on 90210:
We have been dispatched to spread
winter cheer. And to tell you all...
The Winter Wonderland Dance is near.
- You don't want to go to the dance?
- Whatever. Sure, I'll go.
So what if I felt something when we
kissed? That doesn't change the fact...
You just said you felt
something when you kissed.
This is my sister back
from boarding school.
For the life of me,
I can't remember why I ever let you go.
Do you still have
feelings for Naomi?
- I do.
- I got a text from Ivy
saying I had to come here,
that you had something to tell me.
- I know this guy's a drug dealer.
- What proof do you have?
I've been buying from
Jasper for the last month.
Don't. Stay away from me.
Why? You've made mistakes,
but I don't judge you.
- What are you talking about?
- You accidentally ran over my uncle.
I'm gonna read War and Peace.
One of my New Year's resolutions.
Why not?
It's really long,
but it's not in Morse code.
- I can read it.
- Send.
You're so not listening to me.
Sure I am.
I'm just texting Liam.
For my New Year's resolution...
He's surfing.
And he misses me.
I have so much to tell him.
She just turned down La Cienega.
Somebody's text-whipped.
She's cute.
He is cute.
We're cute.
This is so exciting!
So nauseating.
"Irritating" is the
word that came to mind.
- Don't be a hater.
- I'm not being a hater.
I'm happy for you, actually.
I'm happy if you're happy,
all right?
Did Naomi say anything
about Silver in those texts?
What's up with you two, anyway?
I can't believe you guys kissed.
I know. It was out of the blue.
It was amazing, man.
Can't wait to talk to
her tomorrow at school.
I just really hope Dixon
feels the same way.
- See you later, boy.
- All right, brother.
Look at all this.
I figured we had cause to celebrate.
It's a new year.
Annie comes home tonight.
And did I tell you
that she called to say she missed us?
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
And last night on the phone,
she was even laughing.
And it wasn't that snarky,
derisive laugh.
It was the good kind.
- It's a miracle I still recognize it.
- Who knew Vegas was the answer?
Two weeks on the Strip
would've driven me crazy,
and that's even if my
mother wasn't living there.
Is this that same boosters
reception we went to last year?
I think it is.
Did you not tell me about this earlier
because you knew Kelly would be there?
I didn't want you
to be uncomfortable.
- Should I be uncomfortable?
- Sweetheart, of course not.
I've barely exchanged ten words with her
since we realized she had a crush on me.
Since you realized that.
But trust me,
I've done everything I can to avoid her.
I am not interested
in avoiding anybody.
And I won't let Kelly determine
what school functions I attend.
I'm going to this.
Just like I did last year.
Great.
And if I think about it, I can't even
remember why me and Silver broke up.
Wasn't it because she liked horror
movies and you're afraid of the dark?
Very funny.
Me and her, we both did our thing.
She's changed. I've changed.
Now maybe we can get back together.
I'm gonna talk to her
tomorrow at school.
Definitely before U.S.
History though.
Cause then she gets
hopped up on conspiracy theories
and then there's no talking to her.
You okay?
I'm really not looking forward to going
back to school tomorrow, that's all.
It's not going to
be as bad as you think.
You already did the hard
part and broke up with Jasper...
It's already better than it was.
I'll be right down.
Welcome Home I missed you so much
Love, Jasper
Are you sure I look tan enough in this
shirt? I swore this was a blue-white,
but now it's looking
like a yellow-white.
Yes, Naomi, you look incredibly tan.
In fact, you look tanner
than you did yesterday.
How is that even possible?
I may have gone to the
tanning salon last night.
I really want a "wow" effect when I walk
into Allison's sister's birthday party.
I wouldn't worry. Everybody's going to
be like, "Wow, you've got leather skin."
That's like 20 years away.
The party is tomorrow night.
It's going to be a total blowout.
She rented out the beach club.
- I cannot...
- Hey guys...
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to interrupt.
- You didn't.
- How was your break?
It was good.
Just laid low.
How about yours? How was St. Barts?
You look really tan.
- It was great.
- Tan-tastic.
That's great.
I should probably get going.
I'll see you guys later?
What did I tell you?
I didn't know if it was going to cold,
but it wasn't bad.
And I got the 3.
2, so it was all right.
- What's up, dudes?
- What's up, kid?
- So Northern California was cool?
- It was awesome.
I really like Berkeley.
Cool place, man.
I even brought this,
this really cool souvenir.
Navid, is that...?
What the hell are
you doing with cocaine?
Peach Pit Team
www.forom.com
www.seriessub.com
Season 02 Episode 13
Rats and heroes
I think you need to put that away.
- What's wrong with you?
- Will you just relax?
We will not relax.
What are you doing with...
cocaine?
You don't do drugs. At least I hope.
Of course I don't.
I was going to plant this in
Jasper's locker.
I was gonna call that number.
They'll find the stuff.
It'll be all buh-bye.
Just like the poster says.
I'm not a rat.
- I'm a hero.
- You're not a hero.
You're an idiot.
Seriously,
this is a really bad idea.
Worse than your Boys of
the Blaze fund-raising calendar.
Jasper is already a drug dealer.
I'm bringing that to the attention
of the powers-that-be. It's simple.
All right, fine. How do
you plan on getting in his locker?
There's this master list of
all the student locker combinations
on file in the principal's office.
Me?
Sorry.
I understand.
You wanna think about it.
No way. I'm not helping you with this.
It's stupid.
You're on your own.
- It's your funeral.
- It's not that big of a deal.
Did you get my flowers?
I really missed you.
Jasper, stop. We're not dating.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm breaking up with you.
- You don't mean that.
- Yeah, I do.
It's over.
Then I'll tell.
What?
I'll go to the police and
I'll tell them what you did.
All they need is a lead in the case.
They'll probably start combing
through your Internet history.
See if you have any...
special interest in the case.
I'm guessing that it's not
going to be that hard to find evidence.
You probably took the car to
a local body shop that night, right?
After you ran over my uncle.
Why are you doing this?
I love you.
You love me. I know you do.
We've both made mistakes,
but I want to put them behind us.
Just say you can do that,
and I'll keep your secret.
Come here.
If it isn't the
fancy Caribbean jet-setter.
That is me.
I want to talk about
what happened at the dance.
Me, too.
It was obviously a mistake.
Exactly. That's exactly
what I was going to say.
We broke up for a reason.
Like you said,
you could never be yourself around me.
That's what I said.
I think I was just
feeling vulnerable.
I was feeling rejected by Teddy,
and when I saw him with that girl, but,
the truth is...
Maybe I just jump to conclusions.
Maybe that girl was just his friend.
Anyway, I'm going to talk to him
and see if we ca figure things out.
That sounds like a good idea.
I'm going to let you get back to work.
And I'll talk to you later?
Hey, Ives.
What you reading?
The Violent Messiahs.
It's actually really rad.
It's Lieutenant Major Cheri,
who's apparently
a schizophrenic now,
and she's chasing down this
gnarly masked villain...
Spoiler alert.
I wanted to thank you for
sending me that text after the dance.
That was nothing.
- It wasn't nothing. You were together.
- Me and Liam? No. Please.
That was nothing serious.
And I knew he liked you, so...
It meant something to me.
And in appreciation,
a little thank you
gift from St. Bart's.
You really didn't have to do that.
Go ahead. Open it.
It was not easy shopping there,
by the way.
Everyone kept yammering
away in French,
but I found that if you spoke
loudly and slowly enough,
you could eventually get through to them
that you did not want their junk.
I hit the jackpot at Duty Free.
- Isn't this something?
- I hope you don't have one already.
Definitely not.
But I've always wanted a pocketbook.
It's a Fendi baguette.
But no worries.
But it's the least I could do.
Anyway. Thanks again, Ives.
I'm not saying, "kick him
in the groin," but near the groin...
would be great.
So, how was vacation?
- A blast.
- Time of my life.
Aspen, right?
We're really gonna pretend everything's
fine? I saw you kiss Silver.
At least man up.
That was a lame-ass move.
You know I liked her.
Come on.
It can't be that big of a deal.
I bet you got over it pretty
quickly in Aspen.
I didn't just get over
it 'cause I like Silver.
I thought I'd made that
fairly clear by the night of the dance.
If there's something going on between
you two, I think I deserve to know.
I'll be straight with you.
I don't think me and
Silver are over yet.
What happened the night of the dance?
It happened.
Will it happen again?
Probably.
We're trying to keep it on the DL,
but between me and you,
we're talking about getting
back together again.
Come on, man.
- How was your break?
- It was good. How was yours?
Too short.
I hear you.
We haven't really
talked since the dance.
Wondering what's going
on with you and Jasper.
Tell us you broke up with him.
- It's complicated.
- What's complicated about it?
- He's a drug dealer.
- He lied to you.
He's a really bad guy.
- And he's pretty greasy-looking.
- Stop.
Please just stop.
You don't get to do this.
Leave me alone.
It shouldn't be hard.
You've done it before.
Hey, you.
- Silver. What's up?
- Not much.
I want to talk to you
about what happened at the dance.
Because,
I thought about it a lot and I...
About that.
You were right about me all along.
"Once a player, always a player."
Your words, right?
I can't be tied down to one person.
- It's not in my DNA.
- Why are you telling me this?
Because you saw it before I did.
I can't even decide who to take
to this Beach Club party on Saturday.
Emiko's hot, but, Alisa's...
She's easy.
Dilemma, right?
I'm sure you're going
to figure it out, though.
How's it going, man?
Dixon! Wait! I need to talk to you.
- What's up?
- It's about Annie.
She's still dating Jasper.
What?!
I saw them holding hands.
I went to talk to her about it,
but she said it's not my right
to interfere. And she's right. It isn't.
But maybe you can do something about it.
You're her brother.
Maybe she'll listen to you.
Hey, you.
Hi, Gia.
I didn't know you were in AA.
That's sort of what
the "Anonymous" is about.
It was a joke.
I was kidding.
A couple of us always go bowling
after the meetings. You want to come?
I don't think so.
You sure? Last week we had
a down-to-the-last-frame match
with some dentists from Culver City.
- Very exciting.
- That sounds tempting.
But the thing is,
AA is a part of me,
but I don't want it to be my whole life.
I just like having friends around
who understand what I'm going through.
- I figured...
- My friends do.
Or... they did.
Things are kind of weird with
us right now, but I'm working on it.
Thanks anyway.
If you change your mind or if
you ever want to talk, give me a call.
I'll see you around.
Thank you.
Thanks.
This is great.
I've been planning
this night for a long time.
I wanted it to be perfect.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
- What was that?
- Sorry.
Nothing...
Here we are.
At last.
I know, right? Finally.
- How was vacation?
- How was St. Bart's?
- Sorry.
- No go ahead.
I was asking you about St. Bart's.
- Did you have fun?
- Yeah, it was gorgeous.
Did you go snorkeling?
How about parasailing? I hear
they have amazing parasailing there.
No, I really just kind of
laid by the pool the whole time.
- Sounds fun.
- Yeah. It was great.
- What about you? What did you do?
- I worked on the boat.
The hull's been planked and ribbed,
so I've just got to finish the framing,
sheathe the deck panels...
And this is boring.
It's not boring.
Deck panels are rad.
What's new with you?
I'm redecorating the house.
I'm working with this Feng Shui expert.
At first I thought it was
another Chinese scam like
Tai Chi or acupuncture.
But she's on to something. She's helping
me remove all signs of Jen, so...
That's good.
That makes sense.
- Sorry. I shouldn't have mentioned Jen.
- No, it's okay.
No, it's not.
I just want to really forget
about her and everything she did.
- I'm really sorry again.
- Can we not talk about it? Please.
Of course. Sorry.
Have you seen the waiter?
You will love this.
So, see? Now you shake,
and it's gone.
So dad can't bust me for reading about
Jude Law's latest love child
instead of writing my Hamlet Paper.
Though, technically, because Jude Law
is playing hamlet on Broadway,
can't you just argue
that it's research?
Not bad.
So, I heard through the grapevine
that you're
back with Jasper.
- Stay out of it.
- I just don't get it.
You don't have to.
That guy is bad news
you gotta see that.
Stop. Okay, seriously,
I don't want to talk
to you about Jasper.
And we've been getting along lately.
Let's not mess it up.
Okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I actually kind of like that
we've been getting along.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Good night.
- Hey, Navid.
- Dixon?
Yeah. It's Dixon.
About the Jasper plan?
I'm in.
What's up?
- So, how are things?
- Good, good.
Go on. How was the big
date with the big "N"?
- What?
- Nothing, just...
Isn't it kind of weird?
Can we talk about that?
Not for me.
Liam, get over yourself cause I did.
Seriously, what, you think I'm in love
with you or something? Get real!
Whatever. I'll just
ask Naomi myself.
You know she gave me a pocketbook?
Seriously?
We're, like, buds.
Between you and me,
the date didn't go so well.
You serious?
Yeah, it was awkward
and just... weird.
- I'm sorry, man.
- Yeah, it sucked.
Okay, but you know
you win some, you lose some.
It was worth a shot, I guess.
- Right?
- It was worth a shot.
I got it.
Mrs. List, do you mind if I go leave
a note on my dad's desk?
Go right ahead.
I'll wait right here for you, bro.
Nice blouse, mrs. L.
Files...
The paisley's really
working for you.
Have you seen Silver?
No.
Shoot. I really need to talk to her.
- Is everything okay?
- No, it's not.
What's going on?
Come on. You can tell me.
I had my first date with Liam last night
and it was terrible.
We had absolutely nothing to say
to each other. I don't get it.
How could things between such
good-looking people be so boring?!
You're probably nervous and he was
probably nervous. You both
- just wanted it to be perfect.
- It wasn't perfect.
It wasn't even passable.
I think we lost our spark.
Maybe we have no chemistry anymore.
Don't give up.
This is Liam we're talking about.
- You've waited so long.
- Maybe we waited too long.
- Maybe we missed our moment.
- I don't believe that.
I think there was just
a lot of build-up. That's all.
And if chemistry is what
you're worried about,
I think there's a pretty clear way
to test that out.
You could be right.
Thanks.
Of course. Anytime.
Silver and I are going to
Allison's sister's 21st birthday party.
I think you should come with us.
I'd love to.
Good.
Come to papa.
Look who's here.
Principal Wilson in the house.
Looks like you lost
some weight. Am I right?
Could bed a couple of pounds.
You look fantastic,
just... fantastic.
Well, yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
Hey, dad!
I was just about to leave you a note
tell you I was going to Navid's
house, but you know, you're here.
Guess I don't have to.
- See you later.
- Okay.
And we'll see you later.
You ready to do some sucking
up to the superintendent?
- I'd be delighted.
- Okay.
- Quite a turnout.
- Yes, this is quite a turnout.
Definitely.
I was just on my way to
talk to some boosters. So...
I'll see you guys later.
See? Thasn't so bad, was it?
No, it wasn't.
- But I'm gonna go talk to her.
- What?
- Can I take your coats, please?
- No, I'm fine. Thank you.
- Aren't you gonna be warm?
- I'd feel naked without it.
- Why?
- Because I'm naked without it.
- What?!
- Really?
Ade and I came up with this master plan
to test mine and Liam's chemistry.
- This was your idea?
- Not exactly
Did you even ask Liam
if he was coming tonight?
- Why wouldn't he be?
- Because he's not exactly mr. Social.
Something tells me Ade's plan
was not completely thought through.
Ade's plan?! I didn't tell her
to come naked!
Yes. You practically did.
- Shut up!
- Drinks!
To enforced dress codes.
- My God, there's rum in here.
- Yes, there is.
Sorry. Wasn't thinking.
- Are you okay?
- Totally.
I'm fine.
I mean, it happens.
So, no Liam?
No, I haven't seen him.
Shoot. I'm getting warm.
Keep the jacket on.
I'm going to run to the ladies' room.
I will be right back.
We'll be over here.
It's Adrianna.
Something just happened, and...
I was wondering maybe
you'd want to meet up
because I could really
use someone to talk to.
- Sure.
- I'm at a party at the beach club.
Well, you're in luck.
Nice sweater.
It's looks good on you.
- Everything okay?
- I don't know.
I accidentally drank some rum and coke.
Just a sip,
- but the taste... I'm freaking out.
- Of course you are.
It triggered something.
You start second- guessing yourself.
Did I know there was alcohol
in the drink? Did I want to screw up?
I took a sip and I'm still here.
It's not the end of the world.
Stop torturing yourself.
No, I should have
been more responsible.
This is my fault.
I'm at a party where
people are drinking.
This whole sober living thing...
it's a process.
It's going to take some time.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me. I'm so sorry to interrupt.
Can I borrow you for a second?
I would love to talk to you
alone.
Excuse me.
Let's talk about that little crush you
have on my husband.
There is no reason for you
to feel threatened.
No.
I'm not threatened.
I'm annoyed.
I'm sorry that you're annoyed.
That was not my intention.
Enlighten me.
What was your intention?
- What, to break up my marriage?
- No, absolutely not.
I've been through a lot
with my mom lately, and
Harry ended up
being someone that I could talk to.
Someone that I could lean on.
And you're right. I shouldn't have.
But you have to know that the minute
I felt that there was
anything like a crush...
I hate using that word...
I steered clear of him.
I did not want to cross that line.
You have to believe me.
I'm not that person anymore.
You see that buoy down there?
Damn. That was close.
Not really.
Okay.
- You try.
- I don't want to throw rocks.
Okay.
You want to go see a movie? They're
playing this bollywood movie "3 idiots."
No. I hate movies with subtitles.
- Since when?
- Since forever.
I like to watch movies,
not read them.
You should have told me.
We've seem so many foreign films.
Whatever. Now you know.
And just so you also know,
most of the movies that we have seen,
I actually kinda hated.
- What?
- Yeah.
I could barely keep my
eyes open for the most part.
I guess I was trying to impress you,
but I just found them
incredibly boring.
The plots are all convoluted
and pretentious and...
Just stop it. Just stop!
I know what you're trying to do.
You're trying to pick a fight.
But it's not going to work.
I'm not going to fall for it.
I just...
Annie...
I love you no matter
what movies you like.
Okay? Because we're not
like other couples.
We're soul mates.
And you know what that means?
Well, it means that soul mates...
they're forever.
Forever.
Wait, aren't you
forgetting something?
See you at school.
You know what we need to do?
We need to find you a nice,
available guy.
Preferably not an actor.
Or a teacher.
And ideally... Straight.
That's not gonna be easy.
There's this great yoga class
you should try.
I might go tomorrow
if you want to come with me.
- Sure, I'd love to.
- Good, because i think I have someone
you just might be interested in.
You work fast.
Three letters... wtf...
spring to mind.
- What?
- What the frick just happened?
It turns out her crush
wasn't about you at all.
- It had to be a little bit about me.
- Nope.
Could've been anyone.
Could've been you, coach Cooper.
Lou, the gardener.
Lou has the mind of a child.
It's not even the worst part.
Naomi, okay, she
unbuttons another button
because now she's sweating.
I'm, like, please do not
let the ac go off tonight.
This girl, I swear, she is...
Silver, you okay?
It's gonna be okay, all right?
I didn't see you at the beach club.
So, I figured I'd come here.
Cool.
Is it hot in here?
Maybe a little.
Let me see if the heat's on.
I can easily turn it off.
That was...
I know, right?
- Anyway.
- So...
- No, what were you saying?
- No, nothing.
You?
Nothing...
And if you like country music,
they have sober line dancing.
Plus, sober roller-skating
and sober bar hopping.
- Really?
- I'm just kidding.
Yeah, I was gonna say!
Are you feeling any better?
I'm feeling so much better.
Thank you so much for everything.
My pleasure.
- Oh no!
- What?
My ex-girlfriend just walked in
with the new girl she's seeing.
I can't believe this is happening.
She's totally flaunting
that she's moved on.
God, I must look like such a loser.
Trust me, you don't
look like a loser. But...
But what?
Your ex looks jealous.
I think she thinks we're together.
I'm sure she doesn't.
I bet she does now.
- Why'd you do that?
- I don't know.
You helped me out tonight,
and I wanted to help you.
I can't believe I was
actually thinking
about giving him another
chance after the break.
Why can't I just get it?
He's a player.
Silver, wait...
There's something I gotta tell you.
The truth is...
I like you.
What?
When I said our
kiss didn't mean anything,
I was lying.
Couldn't stop thinking
about it during the break.
Anything and everything I
said during the breakup,
just forget about it.
Because I'm crazy about you.
Can you just give me another chance?
I think you're gonna like Kai.
He's very cute, very available.
And very coming
towards us right now.
How are you?
I noticed you weren't in class
yesterday. Is everything okay?
It's fine.
Harry and I just had a function.
I want you to meet my friend, Kelly.
This is Kelly's first time here,
- but I told her all about you.
- Nice to meet you.
So, have you given any more thought
about the ojai retreat?
I think you could really
benefit from those classes.
I don't think I'm
gonna be able to swing it, but
- Kelly might be free that weekend.
- Cool.
I better start class.
Well, cute, right?
Totally, yeah, but he is
obviously way into you.
Don't be ridiculous.
He's a little touchy-feely,
but that's just his yoga shtick.
He does that with everybody.
Let's all take our
first position, please.
Arms to your side.
Let's close our eyes.
Breathe in...
Out.
Breathe in.
What's going on?
Apparently they're doing random locker
searches. Something to do with drugs.
Now what do you suppose
could have prompted that?
No idea.
31-25-32.
This one's clear.
143...
32-37.
- Found something here.
- Wait a minute.
- Is this your locker?
- But that's impossible.
You better come with us.
Come on
Let's go.
It's not what you think.
I can explain.