Previously on Nip / Tuck:
No!
We have an obligation
to this community, Christian.
We need to go out there
and show people how to stand up to him.
Repair one of
my masterpieces again and I'll kill you.
We found this next to
the carved face of a girl.
It's a dare.
He wants to know if we're going to fix her.
You screwed me when I was 12
and you said you loved me!
Did you sleep with him?
The only man I've been with
since I met you...
is you.
Tell me what you don't like about yourself.
Are you kidding? Everything.
My body's dropping so fast
my gynecologist needs a hard hat.
But seriously, I was sent to you
by Barbara Busberger.
She told me
you're the best surgeons in Miami.
Barbara also told me
to buy a condo down here...
without saying it's God's waiting room.
So, what exactly...
I wanna look like her.
Joan Alexandra Molinsky.
Born in Brooklyn, raised in Larchmont.
Graduated from Barnard Phi Beta Kappa.
- This is you?
- That's me.
Unretouched.
The face and the photograph.
- I want you to make me look just like that.
- Like a 4-year-old girl?
I think I want you to do the surgery.
- You haven't said what it is yet.
- Sign this first, if you don't mind.
Confidentiality agreement?
Ms. Rivers, everybody knows
that you've had a few procedures done.
A few?
My face has been tucked in more times
than a bed sheet at the Holiday Inn.
What I want you people to do...
I don't want the media to know about it
till it's finished.
That's why I came to Miami
instead of New York or L. A.
Once you unveil me,
we'll hit the talk shows.
I'll do Oprah, Larry King, Regis and Kelly...
and the cover of People magazine.
I know it will happen.
As long as we're clear that signing this
doesn't obligate us to do the surgery.
There's no obligation.
Just that you keep it undercover.
Great.
Okay. Here it is.
I've always wanted to have a twin
because I wanted to see...
what I would look like
if I never had plastic surgery.
But I don't have a twin. I just have me.
So I want you to put me back
the way I would look...
if I had never been Joan Rivers.
I'm confused. Are you asking us
to do a complete makeover...
- that will restore your natural appearance?
- Yes. It'll be career Viagra.
I can bring back all those jokes
I used to do about myself...
before plastic surgery.
I had great jokes. I was so ugly
that if I wanted to moon somebody...
I'd just show them my face.
Or, my body is dropping so fast...
I can have a mammogram
and a pedicure at the same time.
Ms. Rivers, with all the work
that you've had done...
it seems like a pretty extreme thing to do
for the sake of your career.
Well, it's not just my career.
It's also my grandson, Cooper.
We have the most amazing relationship.
It's probably the most...
honest relationship I've ever had
with anybody in my whole life.
He loves me exactly the way I am.
- So why change?
- I'm a goddamn lie.
Look...
I know I'm the one that brought
plastic surgery into the mainstream.
I know I'm the one that convinced
all those thousands of housewives...
if you don't like your face,
then do something about it, change it.
But now I want to send out
a different message.
My grandson is... He's so pure.
He's so happy with himself the way he is...
and I want him to stay that way.
I don't want him to grow up hating
the thought that he's gonna get older.
I don't want him to care if he gets acne
at 20 or if his hair starts to recede at 40.
I just want him to know
there's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's the natural order of things.
And, boy...
it will get me some magazine cover.
People. Oh, my God.
Before, after. No one's ever done
something like that. It's gold.
And I could use a cover. I haven't had one
since 1994. Those sons of bitches.
Come on, what about it?
I am offering you
the mother of all plastic surgeries.
Will you do it?
You never smile anymore.
Talk to me, Ava.
Tell me, how can I make you happy?
- We'll never be happy.
- Aren't we happy right now?
Here in our warm little cocoon.
But once we leave the safety of this nest,
they'll always be there.
Harassing us, judging us, tormenting us.
They'll never understand.
To them, our relationship is unnatural.
Let's go away, then.
Let's go away
and start a new life together.
Let's go to Paris.
My life is here, Matt.
We'll eat croissants all day.
We'll drink wine. We'll make love.
I can't. Adrian might come back.
You have a cell phone.
I have medical issues.
We'll find a doctor in Paris.
I'll get three months of your medications
from my dad's office.
Your whole life is ahead of you, Matt.
There isn't one without you.
You smiled.
Just say yes, Ava.
Say yes.
My God, when is this gonna end?
Four new victims this month alone.
The cuts on her face
look worse than the others.
He's getting bolder. Probably feels
he's not getting enough attention.
You're the one stealing his headlines.
Not by choice.
Why are you fixing his work again?
Because every other plastic surgeon
in town is afraid to.
It's my moral obligation.
I'd stop it if I could, but I can't.
15-blade.
Sean. How's it hanging, homie?
- What am I supposed to do with this?
- You started a war, Sean.
You're gonna need more than a scalpel
to finish it.
Hey, sexy. How's that leg?
What are you talking about?
You and The Carver, brother.
You remember what he said.
Fix his work again,
he's coming back for you.
You asked how to stop it.
I'm telling you. Cap his ass.
You, of all people,
know I can't use this thing.
15-blade.
Pussy.
Maybe what you really need
are some balls, bro.
I've got balls. You know I do.
You're in jail because of me.
That was your finest hour.
Truth is, Sean, I made you a man.
- You didn't do shit.
- I gave you the guts to pull a gun.
I gave you the strength to risk
killing someone to save yourself...
and your family. And your business.
I gave you character.
Where did it go?
And what's with this music?
I hate this shit.
Now that's more like it.
God, do I love the '80s.
Turn that down.
I can't operate under these conditions.
Hey. You think fixing her face
is going to make everything better?
You wanna restore real order
to this mess, Sean?
You gotta be ready to go one-on-one
with The Carver. Like you did with me.
I think she needs some more gas.
No. I won't do that again.
Yes, you will.
Because you got a death wish.
So repressed, our little Sean.
You gotta take this guy out.
Restore the order and kill The Carver.
Kill The Carver.
Don't tell me this guy scares you
more than me. I'm getting jealous.
Shut up!
- Make me.
- Gun.
Good. Ready? Aim. Shoot!
What the hell are you doing?
Nothing.
I was just...
Temesta?
You're stealing anti-anxiety pills?
Look, I've been upset, okay?
And I didn't feel like asking for them...
and going through the third degree.
Helix? Don't you know
it's dangerous to self-prescribe?
Come on. They sell this shit
at school to help you get through...
Get your hands off me.
Clomiphene citrate has nothing to do
with stress, asshole.
I'm sick of your goddamn lies, Matt!
I don't know what's going on,
but clearly these pills aren't for you.
So you tell me
why you're stealing these drugs...
or I will personally bring you to the cops...
encourage them to lock you up
and keep you...
- until you're too old to enjoy them!
- Okay, fine!
They're for Ava. I'm stocking up.
Why?
Because we're going away. Forever.
Go ahead. Turn me in to the police.
I'll deny everything.
Matt will support me entirely,
and all you'll accomplish...
is starting a criminal file
for your very own son.
Matt won't be arrested. You will.
Pharmaceutical drug theft is a felony.
Do your research
before you come into my house...
with your pathetic Chicken Little act.
Vodka, rocks. If memory serves...
you downed it last time you were here
barking similar hollow threats.
Drink up and then get out.
How barbaric.
Despite your doctor's degree
and your slick veneer of sophistication...
when it comes to women
and how to treat them...
you've crawled right out of a cave.
I'd watch my mouth if I were you.
Or what? You'll hit me?
If you were a man, after the hell you've
caused my family, you'd be on the floor.
And you'd be right on top of me,
wouldn't you, Christian?
Because you want me, don't you?
You lubricate acid. If I stuck my dick
in you, it would sizzle off.
Oh, it would sizzle all right.
Matt's not here. But you knew that
before you walked in here...
carrying your big stick
you're afraid to swing.
You're not upset Matt's seeing me.
- You're upset that you're not.
- You're crazy.
And let me make myself clear.
I'm not leaving this hell house
until you agree to stop seeing Matt.
I will kill you before I let you
take him out of this country.
Screw the petty threats.
You want me to stop seeing Matt?
Then make me.
You want me to stop?
Then there's only one thing for you
to do, Christian. Make me want you more.
Conquer me. You don't have the guts.
Neither does Sean or Julia.
I have the power, and I'm keeping it.
I see now.
You're just like the rest of them.
Threatened, kowtowed, spineless.
Terrified of the unconditional.
Of a woman
with mental and sexual intelligence.
You disappoint me, Christian.
In the end, you're all bark and no bite.
- Bite me.
- How hard?
You started it. You're gonna finish it.
No. Not that!
You wanna be conquered?
Consider it done.
What's wrong?
Am I too much of a woman for you?
No, Sean. I can't allow this.
- It's the only way to make him stop.
- When?
I don't know. End of the week?
Pull the security detail off.
Let him see that I'm vulnerable.
We're waiting inside the house.
No, he's smart. He'll sense that.
We don't tell anybody.
My family, my partner. No one.
I'll be alone with him. Just me.
And once he thinks he's got
what he wants, then you come in.
We're sort of
in the middle of something here.
It can wait.
- This had better be important, Christian.
- It is.
Ava's a man.
Anything?
Still checking.
Are you certain she didn't just have
a naturally shallow vaginal canal?
Believe me,
there was nothing natural about it.
You're plastic surgeons.
If this is true, I don't understand...
why you couldn't tell right away.
She's the goddamn Hope Diamond of
transsexuals. Flawless in every way.
I called Abe Ruckman at the
Avon Sexual Reassignment Clinic...
Stephanie Duncan at the
Gene Identity Center in Colorado.
Nobody's ever heard of her.
Ava Moore has never existed.
As a woman, you mean.
Look, Julia, I thought it was
a preposterous conjecture, too.
Then he gave me the list of drugs
Matt was stealing for her.
- This is Greek to me.
- The compounds are very specific.
Spironolactone for breast
and nipple development.
Premarin for vaginal dryness.
And all in amounts and calibrations
we've never even seen before.
It's quite brilliant, really.
No prescription to chase?
Nothing.
- We need to tell Matt.
- No.
If this is true, and he finds out,
he will never recover from it...
and he'll be sexually ruined
for the rest of his life.
And if he finds out
you screwed his girlfriend...
he will never forgive you for it
or trust you again, Christian.
What? She jumped me.
Bedroom cam's working great, Sean.
So's that one in the dining room.
What's that for?
It's just part of the new security system
I'm putting in.
- Thanks. We'll talk later.
- All right.
Not one match.
Let me see.
We can't just keep
barging into her house...
and confronting her
without indisputable proof.
We get one more chance at this before
she leaves town and takes him with her.
Well, at least she thinks like a woman.
Hermes?
Remember when Suzanne hired a private
investigator to follow her husband?
He told her about a site where you could
look up other people's credit accounts.
She has an outstanding balance
at the Hermes store in Vienna, Virginia.
How close is Baltimore
to Vienna, Virginia?
- How old is Adrian again?
- Seventeen. Matt's age.
Well, 17 years ago, if you wanted
a state-of-the-art sex change...
there really was only one place
in the world to go.
The person you need to see at
Johns Hopkins is Carol, formerly Carlos.
She's been there 10 years.
Why would showing up in person
do the trick...
when leaving five messages didn't?
Sofia says the transgender community
is incredibly protective.
They won't open up
to someone they don't know.
They need to see you to trust you.
Explain to me how two strangers
can build a relationship in five minutes.
For God's sake. You've charmed half
of the female population of Miami.
- Not to mention a few transsexuals.
- One transsexual.
- And Ava fooled everybody.
- Not everybody.
There was a reason
I wasn't attracted to her.
- What if charm doesn't work? Any ideas?
- Be empathetic.
Convince her that you're there
as professionals to help Ava.
That you're concerned in her welfare.
- I'm not sure I'm a good liar.
- I am.
Come on. We're late.
This one here's a Fillet Tarpon Bay
with a rubber handle.
Real good for securing the grip.
Real nice choice
for barbecuing or dressing meats.
This one's my favorite.
A Buck Nighthawk. Very stealthy.
Comes with a nylon sheath.
It has a 650 tool steel
drop point blade for a real long life...
no matter what the elements.
Any other questions for you today?
Yes. Which one would you recommend
if I wanted to gut something?
Dr. Davis,
telephone, please.
I went into a men's restroom yesterday.
I've never been so scared.
You've been living as a man now
for five years, J. T.
You've certainly used the male restroom
since your surgery, right?
So why the fear?
It was a trough urinal...
where all the guys pee in the open.
What if the guy next to me
sees it's a brand-new penis and...
he wants to beat me down? You know?
See, you know what? You just need
to learn how to protect yourself.
Does nothing make you afraid, Carol?
Is there nothing you fear?
Yeah.
Airports.
Making it through security as a woman.
Man, since 9/11, it's like...
It's like they scrutinize so carefully now.
Lord, if you can make it through
those security lines...
undetected and accepted,
it's like you're real.
You know?
This is a closed meeting. Can I help you?
We're looking for Carol Nelson
in Room 305.
And you are?
I'm Dr. Christian Troy.
This is my partner, Sean McNamara.
We've been trying to reach you.
Sofia Lopez gave us your name.
Listen. Now why don't we just take
a quick little break?
Go outside, have a little snack.
And I'll see you guys back in 10.
Thanks a lot, Carol.
How can I help you?
We're plastic surgeons.
We've flown from Miami because
we need medical information on a patient.
Really?
I guess as surgeons and friends
of Sofia's, you have to know...
that a gender-reassignment file is as
classified as a nuclear weapons program.
We are aware of that, Ms. Nelson,
and we're completely sympathetic.
- So who's the patient?
- The name she goes by now is Ava Moore.
My partner Sean was the surgeon
who performed Sofia's bottom surgery.
He also saved her
from a botched tracheal shave.
Well, that's touching. But it doesn't
change a thing, gentlemen.
You see, these people here?
They're fragile.
So why is it
that I should betray their confidence?
If Ava Moore wants her records,
why hasn't she contacted us?
Because Ava is afraid. Seventeen years
ago, when she had her surgery...
there was no community.
She needs help. She's had a weakening
of the reconstructed vaginal wall...
and the bladder is coming through.
For us to repair it, we need to see
her records, because she claims that...
she had an adverse reaction
to the anesthesia in her original surgery.
We're here to help Ava, Ms. Nelson.
We're not into taking risks with her life.
Well, you don't wanna talk to me.
You want to talk to her surgeon.
He's retired,
and he's taken her records with him.
Where is he?
Dr. Barrett Moore?
I've been expecting you, Doctors.
I understand you've met my wife.
Pollinator.
Hybrids.
The first orchid hybrids
were produced in 1858...
and since then the process
has accelerated. But because of their...
artificial and unnatural evolution...
they're unable to attract
a suitable pollinator...
and hand pollinization is so unreliable...
and time-consuming.
There are mysteries to be solved.
You retired from medicine
to become a botanist?
I retired from medicine
because my work was done.
Every orchid here has been altered.
Each one evolving right before our eyes
into new species...
changing their very identities.
You mastered the technique on humans.
Why turn to flowers?
Because they never leave.
And they rarely disappoint.
Humans and medicine are so...
fallible.
There was nothing fallible
in your transformation of Ava Moore.
She's the work of a medical genius
at the peak of his career.
Why stop at the height of your success?
Avery Tanner is responsible
for the success that I have.
He was a walker, which is to say
that he was an escort...
to some of the wealthiest society women
looking for philanthropic causes.
He was a very good-looking young man...
and unusually interested
in the unorthodox work...
of an inexperienced new doctor.
He would bring them
to my fundraisers...
and charm them
into giving large donations...
for a field of medicine
that they barely understood.
At first, I thought as a gay man,
he was drawn to the transgender world...
because of the possibilities for himself.
But he wasn't. He was drawn to me.
We became close,
but I couldn't be with him...
the way that he wanted me to.
That's not my nature.
One night, Avery came to me in despair.
Suicidal.
And he asked if I were to change him
into a woman, could I love him then?
And I believed that I could.
The resulting operation was...
perfect.
Thank you, Harry. You may go.
To an outsider, we were like
any other happily married couple.
But on the inside, sexually...
I could not forget.
She thought that a child
might normalize what wasn't.
So we agreed that my assistant
would be impregnated with my sperm...
and carry the baby to term for us.
After Adrian was born,
things seemed to be more comfortable.
But soon after, they deteriorated.
I couldn't give her what she wanted.
It wasn't her fault.
I was the failure.
I couldn't see... her.
I could only see my own work.
And so she left?
I came home one day
from a conference and they were gone.
And I've never heard from her since.
How is she?
She's given up philanthropy
for a career as a life coach.
The ultimate creature of transformation
transforming others.
There is some poetry in that, Doctors,
you have to admit.
Her behavior isn't poetic. It's predatory.
Ava Moore is sleeping
with my 17-year-old son.
And yours.
Sleeping with juvenile males makes sense.
They're not experienced enough
to spot a fraud.
I had planned on one last procedure...
to go in, reconstruct the vaginal floor.
Make it less constricted.
I thought maybe it would bring her
some sense of peace, some closure.
But I couldn't find her.
- It would help us if we could see her files.
- You know better than to ask that.
We need to confront her
with more than just a story.
You couldn't save your son from her,
Dr. Moore.
At least help me save mine.
Hey, can I come in?
Please.
I probably should have called first.
- Is your friend here?
- Kevin? Oh, no, he's teaching.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah. And I brought you something else.
Just in case.
You shouldn't need it,
but for when Kevin isn't here.
- You've got to stop doing this.
- Doing what?
Stopping by to give me Mace,
asking me to stay over.
You don't need to protect me.
You're the one who was attacked.
We may be separated, but I'm still
allowed to worry about you, aren't I?
- I'm the one who's worried about you.
- Why? I'm fine.
Don't do anything silly
to prove that you're brave.
Your courage
has already been documented.
Did Matt agree to see you?
- We're meeting him for lunch.
- Good.
Be direct but gentle.
Are you sure you want to handle Ava
on your own?
Yeah.
I'm the one who got her into his life.
I should be the one to get her out.
It's been a long time since I've seen you
as Julia, instead of my wife.
I like it.
- Who else knows about this?
- Three of us. Sean, Christian, and myself.
Angry villagers with torches, here to
drive out the monster the doctor made.
I don't think you're a monster.
I think you're a sad, lonely individual...
who does monstrous, selfish acts
to cope with conflict.
Be careful with your choice of pronouns.
Have some goddamn respect.
I am a woman.
I don't care what this file says.
Break up with my son
and get out of our lives.
- Or what?
- Or I'll tell him the truth about you.
And then your well-kept secret
will be out.
As you know,
secrets have a way of spreading.
Did you ever love him?
I loved that he loved me.
I love her, all right?
And I will always love her.
If this is another intervention
trying to make me see her...
for what she is, you're wasting your time.
I do see her, completely,
which clearly you don't.
We're done with threats.
That's not why we're here.
We're here to support you.
Unconditionally.
We'll respect your choice, whatever it is.
My choice is her. We're leaving next week.
You have until the beginning
of next week to break it off and leave.
And if you need money, help finding
a place for you and Ava to live...
we want you to know
that we're here for you.
You're serious. I don't believe you. Why
are you doing this now? What happened?
What happened is you grew up.
You're not a boy now, Matt.
You're a man.
And we're treating you like one.
If it works out with Ava and you find
a cool job that you love in Gay Paree...
- well, that's great.
- And if it doesn't?
Then you'll hurt like hell.
But you have someplace
you can come home to, if you want.
I don't have anywhere else to go.
I don't have Adrian. I have no one.
You have yourself. And from what
I've witnessed, you're a survivor.
And survivors reinvent themselves.
They rise from the ashes of their failures
like phoenixes...
and fly off to their next destination.
Well, Julia, we've come full circle,
haven't we? You're coaching me now.
The truth of the matter is, Ava,
you really were a good life coach.
And if it wasn't for you
and the truths that you forced...
I wouldn't be able to stand up to you now.
I'm not leaving that easily, Julia.
If you want me gone,
then you talk to your doctors.
What do you want them to do?
Finish me.
Correct the one flaw that gave me away...
so I'm never found out again.
This operation will take under an hour.
You'll be up and on your feet tomorrow.
The last vaginoplasty hurt like hell.
Will this one?
The final expander
causes minimal discomfort.
The ditch was already dug pretty deep.
Just not deep enough for me.
You think this is pretty funny, don't you?
I'm a despicable joke to you.
Actually, Ava, I think you're one of the
most fascinating people I've ever met.
Have you done
many of these types of surgeries before?
No. That's why we brought in an expert.
Hello, Ava.
You are more beautiful than ever.
How is Adrian?
Like you.
Smart, beautiful...
conflicted.
I would like to see him.
I don't know where he is.
Or if he'll ever come home.
I need to be done with this, Barrett.
I can't keep running anymore.
Don't worry. That's why I'm here.
To finish what I started.
Count back from 10 for me.
Ten, nine...
eight, seven...
Ava, I got them.
Hey, I've got them.
What?
I was just saying I got them.
Two first-class tickets to Paris.
Great. And I'm guessing you put
the $10,000 charge on my credit card.
That's what you said to do.
I thought, I don't know...
you might surprise me
and find a way to pay for them yourself.
- What the hell's wrong with you?
- You!
You eat crap like a grubby little slob
on a $25 a yard couch...
and then expect mommy
to clean up your mess. I'm sick of it!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make a mess.
But you did, Matt, and I get it.
Boys make messes.
They leave water marks
on the French lacquer dining table.
They don't do their own laundry.
They're helpless until they go off
to college and learn to be self-sufficient.
But I'm not going off to college.
I'm going off with you.
Oh, Christ!
What?
Another water mark!
Did you do this, Matt?
I don't know, Ava. Are you on your period?
Look, you're stressed and you're upset.
And I get it.
You just need a vacation.
I got us a travel backgammon set...
and a crossword puzzle book.
I don't like backgammon.
And I'm not going to Paris with you.
It's such a cliché, anyway.
What happened
between the time I left and now?
This just doesn't work for me, Matt.
I was a mother once. I don't want to have
to do it all over again with you.
The pretense that you're a man
when you're not...
has become wearisome for me.
I need a genuine companion.
There are things I've been denying myself,
things that come with age...
which you can't possibly understand.
You're afraid of the unknown, okay.
I get it.
But we've got to be united, just like we
always have been. We've got to be strong.
No, you need to be strong, Matt.
We had a fling and it was charming.
We don't have the components
to build from that.
To create a relationship
out of mere physical heat.
It was inevitable. The natural order.
One day you'll see that.
Do you have any clothes
left in the house?
No.
Everything's in here.
Good.
Be a good boy.
Turn around and walk out the door.
Did you hear me? Leave, Matt. It's over!
This is completely unnecessary.
You don't have to show me this.
We would be comfortable knowing
you entered this procedure fully informed.
But I don't have time to keep
schlepping down here for visual aids.
There are several reconstructive
procedures we want you to know about.
Take a look.
We'd start by inserting
a balloon-like device, a tissue expander...
in the areas where the skin
has been tightened...
allowing it to stretch
and assume a more natural hang.
We'd also do a flap surgery...
where we take tissue and fat muscle from
your back and tunnel it to your front...
so your breasts could regain their
age-appropriate fullness and slope.
In other words, I'll have saggy bad girls.
I get it, okay? I get it.
We'd do several skin grafts,
which would also...
Oh, blah, blah.
Please, I'm going to be late for QVC.
Just cut to the chase.
Of course.
Who's that?
That's you, Ms. Rivers. What you would
look like now if you had nothing done.
Yeah. Very funny. Who is that?
These computer-generated images
are only an approximation...
of the natural aging process.
That hag looks like ET.
It is what you asked for.
No, it's not what I asked for.
I asked for someone who would look...
like a grandmother for Cooper,
not like some piece of shit.
Now, what is your problem here?
The kid loves me. I make him laugh.
He runs to me. If I looked like that,
he'd run the other way.
I thought you wanted to be natural.
You know what's natural? Evolution.
Cooper doesn't live in the Stone Age.
He lives in the year 2004.
And we have tweezers,
and we have alpha hydroxy acids...
and we have plastic surgery.
And thank God, because...
My God. If I looked like that now,
can you imagine what I'd look like at 90?
- I'm glad we caught this early.
- Oh, me, too.
Thank you both so very much
for giving me the heads up.
Oh, and put me down tomorrow
for another lift.
Oh, what the hell?
I'm in town anyhow.
It'll kill a couple hours.
So, what are you doing tonight?
Apparently, planning Ms. Rivers' tuck.
Julia's coming by with the kids.
Matt's staying with her.
He's not doing too well
since the Ava breakup.
Can you come by
and break bread with the family?
I didn't know Julia wanted me back in the
family after everything that's happened.
We told Matt
he'd have a safe place to land.
No matter what else is going on,
all of us need to follow through.
Hi, Mom.
Oh, my God. Adrian.
I was so worried.
Where have you been?
Squatting on empty houseboats.
You know, the whole Cunanan thing.
- What do you care?
- I do care, deeply.
Are you going somewhere?
Paris. But you're coming with me.
You, me, and Matt?
We'd make quite a sight, wouldn't we?
No, I ended it with Matt. It's over.
You know what I think, Mom?
I think he dumped you.
You couldn't take it because you
don't know how to handle losing anything.
So now you know what you're doing,
Mom? You're running away from us all.
'Cause that's the only thing
you know how to do.
I thought you were gone forever.
But now we can make
a fresh start together.
There are no more fresh starts!
Everything is rotten to the core.
Okay, look, just come with me.
We'll talk about it all on the plane.
Look, I've got two tickets.
It'd be just the two of us,
like you've always wanted.
You and me, Adrian.
Everything else goes away.
I don't believe you.
That's what kills me.
- I love you.
- No!
I needed to be sure
you'd never leave me again.
No!
I love you, you know.
I love you, too. Always.
I'll help you clean up.
So I'll see you tomorrow?
Make sure you lock this door.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Could you take off
your sunglasses, please?
Can I see your passport, please?
Thank you, Ms. Moore. Have a nice flight.
Thank you.
English - SDH