Hey, Paul, it's 7:08
and I'm downstairs.
So if you're sleeping, wake up.
Mia, sorry.
- I got detained.
- Where were you? I'm freezing.
My apologies. Come on up.
In Treatment - Mia -
Season 1 - Episode 11
swsub.com
You go back to Maryland
on the weekends?
Sorry about that.
What happened?
Amtrak broke down?
Are you upset
that I kept you waiting?
I'm stood up
even by the man that I pay.
If you took the train,
it must've left around
3:00 in the morning.
That's unusual.
None of my business.
I know.
But, you know,
this is our first real session.
And I'm already out
12 minutes.
We can add it on
at the end if you like.
No, I can't.
I have a meeting with a new client,
a plastic surgeon.
Lucky you don't need lipo.
You go to one of my guys,
you could end up dead
with nice thighs.
I'll remember that.
I worked all weekend,
which was fine
because this was the weekend
that Bennett and I
were supposed to go away together.
And, no, he didn't call
saying he wants me back.
Maybe this is a mistake.
I mean, if I'm gonna
be kept waiting at 7:00 a.m...
- Do you feel like I wasn't...
- On time?
I hope it was worth it.
Were you with your girlfriend?
Is that what you imagine?
Do you deflect
everything that's personal?
Never mind. I already know.
My being late seems to have
brought up quite a few feelings...
So this is more of a home really
than an office.
I think you said last week
that you found it homey.
Homey,
but cold. You must
turn the heat down when you go away.
Is this how
your Maryland office looked?
What happened
to all of those patients?
I mean,
I know what happened to Alex,
but all the others. You told them
their feelings were important,
and then you just left them?
Is it possible that you're worried
that I might leave again, Mia?
Winter equals hell for hair.
What's going on?
- I don't want to be here.
- Why not?
I don't like brownstones...
Too much brown.
And this has absolutely nothing to do
with the last week's session.
Because I had not even had a chance
to think about that.
Actually, I have,
and...
I was thinking about what you said
at the door just before you left.
When I said, "you owe me a child"?
That was a joke.
Maybe it was.
But I get the feeling that there might
have been a little more to it than that.
No, no, there wasn't.
It was just a comment.
Sometimes a comment
is just a comment, right?
How are you? Nice to see you.
You owe me a child.
Aren't you glad I'm back?
Who's Laura?
Laura?
Who is she?
I'm not sure
who you're referring to.
It's not a hard question.
I'm asking you about Laura Hill.
She's an ex-patient of yours.
If she's a patient of mine,
then you know I can't discuss her.
- But I can.
- Where is this coming from?
An envelope
was delivered to my office.
Henry must've made a mistake and
thought that I was still your lawyer.
And I opened it.
And it was her deposition
regarding Alex's state of mind.
And you read it?
Are you curious about what she said?
I hope that you gave
those papers to my lawyer.
It's obvious
she was in love with you,
or is.
How so?
It's in and between her words.
She might as well have
- sealed it with a kiss.
- And what does that mean?
You are curious.
Well...
She describes how she dumped her fiance
five minutes before the wedding...
That's a nice story...
And how she slept with Alex.
And that tells you
that she was in love with me.
She did it to make you jealous. It
doesn't take Freud to figure that out.
She wanted to walk into her session
and tell you that she was fucking
a fucking war hero.
And what else did she say?
She said that you two became friends
after the therapy ended,
that you called her on the phone.
You broke the rules for her.
How many other patients
have you done that with?
Mia, whatever happened-
Whatever you imagine happened...
I think you had an affair with her.
You're not gonna respond?
I must've hit a nerve.
So what, you broke her heart?
She broke yours.
Oh, she does
support your case, though.
She says
that you did not mistreat Alex,
she mistreated you
by sleeping with him.
- Come on.
- Let's look atyour actions here, Mia.
Oh, she says she wants you to know,
though, you're in her thoughts.
You opened a legal document
that was not meant for you.
Point taken.
I crossed a boundary.
More than that, you knowingly violated
a basic tenet of your profession.
- That makes two of us.
- And you brought it into session.
Paul, do you have any idea how many
therapists are successfully sued
for sleeping with their patients?
What are you trying to say, Mia?
How could you?
Was she that young and pretty?
Or did she make you feel
that big and important?
Take it. It's yours.
Do you want me to pick that up?
It's all yours.
I've just made an ass of myself,
haven't I?
I bet you're angry.
Maybe I am.
Mostly, I'm...
- I'm surprised.
- No, you're furious.
I can see it all over your face.
But...
you just can't express it
because you're not supposed to.
You want me to go?
Why would you think that?
You know what? You can stop.
Stop, 'cause I'm leaving.
It seems to me that you're pushing me
so that you can end this treatment.
No, I don't blame you.
And it's no big deal.
Actually, I think it's a very big deal.
You were the one who waited for me
in the cold, although I was late.
You waited for me.
Is it possible that you're goading me
because it's easier
to feel angry with me
than look at your own pain?
I saw this show on the TV
The other night... BBC.
About men and their...
specially-made sex dolls.
The men pick out the eyes,
and the mouth and the body.
And they buy them clothes.
And then they put lipstick on them
and take them out
for picnics and bike rides.
And they love their girls because
they don't talk
and they never get pregnant
and they don't get mad.
And they have three perfect holes
that can be repaired.
Young and pretty forever.
What were you thinking
while you were watching this?
I was thinking about
a receptionist in my office
named Stefanie
who likes to wear a lot of pink.
And she's so cute and friendly.
All she does is shop online, but nobody
wants to fire her because she's just
too adorable, you know?
And...
She recently announced
that she's quitting
because some idiot proposed.
So now I have to go to her engagement
party and her bridal shower
and her bachelorette party and
her wedding. And it's endless torture.
Sounds like
you've been there before.
Three younger sisters and
dozens of colleagues.
When men look at a woman like
Stefanie,
they just see the whole package.
And what would that be?
Easy and fun and, you know,
wild in bed at night
and muffins from scratch
in the morning.
And what do they see
when they look at you, do you think?
Blonde lawyer,
might be fun to fuck, but...
But what?
But that's it.
What I usually get...
What I usuallygot from men is sex.
What did you get from Laura?
Do you think
that I chose her over you?
Well, you had sex with her.
Would that make you jealous?
Well, I did
have feelings for you, Paul.
Even though it was 20 years ago,
you must have noticed.
And it sure felt
like you had feelings for me.
It's such a cliche, isn't it...
A young woman falls for her therapist?
But if you were
gonna get involved with a patient...
You wonder why I didn't pick you.
You didn't.
You picked her.
You and Laura
fucking your brains out.
What, on this couch?
That makes me sick.
I don't want to talk about it.
Don't make me talk about it.
What would happen
if we did keep talking about it?
I bet you wanted her from day one.
You were smitten.
How did you manage
to walk her to the door?
You assume
that I found her irresistible.
She knew how to get to you.
How?
Act helpless and girlish.
She probably had slim hips...
Smelled like candy apples,
wore pink or something.
Obviously, I have no idea.
Go on.
What do you imagine?
She'd stare at you all googoo-eyed,
impressed
by your brilliant interpretations,
made you feel
like the world's best shrink.
And then one day
her fiance got mad and she fell apart
and sobbed.
And you felt sorry for her,
so you sat next to her.
Go on.
And you touched her...
Her cheek, her tears.
And you realized how young
and beautiful and vulnerable she was.
And you thought,
"this is my moment."
And you kissed her
and there was no turning back.
Why not?
You had to have her,
unwrap her.
Take her.
And you had to feel
her perfect skin and her round ass
and her flat stomach.
It must've been amazing for you...
So forbidden.
And for her?
She probably didn't feel a thing.
She's made out of silicone.
Right, the sex doll.
It wasn't about the sex for her.
It was about winning.
What did she win?
You.
For those minutes you were hers.
Now do you want me to go?
I'd rather know
what you think happened next.
I don't know.
Maybe you held her
gently until she fell asleep.
And she would like that?
That's what
would make her feel good?
That's what she really wants?
Yes.
It's good to feel that closeness.
Maybe that's what you want from me.
You mean,
to fall asleep while you hold me?
To be comforted, contained.
- That would never happen.
- Why not?
Oh, come on, Paul,
just admit that I'm difficult.
I push men away.
Look at Bennett and Andre...
I mean, pick any letter in the alphabet.
I've sent them packing.
I'm like a knife in your neck.
It feels good when it's gone.
Right?
So you think
I'd be relieved if you left?
Sure.
I walk out that door...
You feel relief.
You want
to pretend it never happened.
Actually, I already told you,
I did think about our last session
and the ones from 20 years ago.
You know, it's okay, Paul.
You don't have to fake it with me.
You kicked me out of here 20 years ago
and you never thought about me again.
It's okay.
You know who that is?
That's you playing, isn't t it?
It's beautififul.
You kept that all these years?
Chopin's "raindrop prelude."
God, I love this piece,
how the eighth notes
sound like rain.
That's from m a recital.
My teacher, Mr. Campbell,
put that together.
He said that I was the best,
but not to tell the others.
So you two had a secret.
What age were you then?
I must've been 10.
That turned out
to be my farewell performance.
That's a shame.
You play really beautifully.
A few weeks after that recital I was
sent to live
at my aunt's in new jersey.
I don't remember you telling me
you were sent away when you were young.
It was only about six months.
But when I came back,
the piano was gone
and twin girls were there.
Do you rember anything else
about the separation?
My dad came to visit me
every sunday.
He'd bring my favorite candies.
I liked those colored dots
that were stuck to paper
and those bottles
filled with that sugary liquid.
And he would show me
pictures of the twins.
And I would tell him that
I missed them all
and wanted to come home.
But he didn't take you.
Where was your mother?
I don't know. I mean,
I'm sure she came,
maybe at christmas.
What about the rest of the time?
I went to school.
It sure was different
from Greenpoint, though.
Gosh, it was so clean...
And modern.
And all the textbooks were new.
I didn't really like the kids, though.
I thought they were boring.
Sounds lonely.
Maybe that's why you gave me
that casassette...
Because I'd know
how you felt when you were 10
and your parents made you leave.
Maybe you thought
if I listened to it back then,
I would change my mind,
let you stay.
- But I was difficult even then.
- You think you deserved it.
- I was impossible.
- How so?
I fought with my mother
all the time.
- Over what?
- Everything.
You were a difficult 10-year-old
who loved chopin.
I don't know why
we're talking about this.
They didn't do anything wrong
and I don't blame them.
Earlier in the session you said
that you didn't blame me.
I crossed the line.
I violated attorney-client privilege.
You thought I was kicking you out.
Well, I bet you wanted to, right?
I'm wondering, Mia,
if you were testing me today.
You reprimanded me for being late.
You violated my privacy.
You even wanted me to pick up
the deposition of the floor.
Well, I was pretty angry.
Maybe you were trying to see
if I could be pushed away.
So you're saying that...
my parents were right
and Bennett was right;
that I'm so fucked up
that nobody wants to be with me
because I push everyoyone away
and I'm demanding and I'm needy
and I'm angry and I'm weepy?
- I'm the seven fucking dwarves.
- That's not what I'm saying, Mia.
What I'm saying
is that maybe you are angry,
but you also want me
to be close to you;
and that no matter
how difficult you say you are,
that beneath the toughness
you still want to be connected to me.
But you're also afraid.
You're afraid
that I'm going to leave you.
I'd better leave.
They're early.
It's okay.
I have a meeting
and I don't want to be late.
And you don't want
to keep the next one waiting.
So then...
I'll see you next monday same time?
You owe me
the 12 minutes.
Okay, then I'll see you at...
- 6:48.
- Okay.
Did you have sex with Laura?
You know, this is
the second week in a row
we're having what's called
"a doorknob moment."
What a are you talking about?
That's when right at the end of
the session, a patient says something
important.
Is that your answer?
'cause that's a yes.
Is it?
I mean, did you?
No.
You might want
to water the plant outside.
I poureded my latte on it.