I came home from work a little late,
but I brought dinner, vegetarian,
and she wasn't there.
Once again, Anita,
what you're saying is
that you got so caught up
in your work life
that Elaine couldn't help
but feel excluded.
And, Elaine... the moment
that you felt shunted aside,
you ran back to your family.
Exactly.
It feels like you're kind of locked
in this cycle, that's very diff...
Walter, you're a little early,
and we're still in session.
Oh, jeez.
I'm sorry.
- I'll come back.
- Thank you.
So... I'm sorry, where were we?
Locked in a cycle.
I'm sorry about earlier.
It happens.
I didn't realize how many
fellow patients there were.
You're busy all the time,
aren't you?
So they...
finally released me
Monday afternoon.
Thank you for your help.
Connie and Natalie picked me up.
We headed straight out for the bay.
I have a few shacks there...
that Connie likes to call a compound...
on Shelter Island.
We drove up... a warm day,
first southerly wind
of the new year.
It was a beautiful day on Monday.
It's amazing when the cold finally
breaks.
Everything was so muddy, though.
They're a few weeks
behind the city Weatherwise.
The snow had just melted
and the ground was just soaked.
I imagine it felt good to be...
outside,
especially after the last few weeks.
You could say that.
But...
it didn't?
Well, no, the air felt great.
It's just that...
Connie and Natalie...
They were just so...
tentative with me.
There's a separate studio
near the main house
that I've used as an office sometimes,
or sometimes just to...
for a little peace and quiet
when the kids were younger.
I wanted to go there
but they kept asking me why.
Was there anything you needed
to do in your office?
Well, take care of some bills.
But mostly I just wanted
to be by myself.
I just wanted
to have a little peace.
That's unusual for you.
Well, Connie's a talker...
She's always been a talker...
and I guess over the years
I've learned how to tune it out.
But this time you didn't.
Something about her pitch...
It just bothered me.
So I went to the office,
and a few minutes later I looked up
and there's Natalie spying on me
from her bedroom window.
She's still...
She's still on duty.
Yeah, like I was a little boy
that someone had to babysit.
You told me once
that when you were
a little boy yourself,
you were the one on duty
with your parents.
I didn't do that much,
just kept an eye on things. Really
it's nothing even worth talking about.
So what did you do
when you saw Natalie
keeping an eye on you?
I glared.
Then about minutes later
she brought me some tea
which I hadn't asked for.
And she asked
if she could just sit with me.
- And how was that?
- Brief.
She's my daughter.
I don't go to her with my problems.
You have a good relationship
with her, though.
You wrote to her almost every day
when she was in Rwanda.
I imagine she'd worry less
if you talked to her a little bit more
about what's been going on with you.
Well, I just didn't feel
like talking.
So I went to the shed
and got this immense pair
of clippers and,
I started hacking away at the brush
down by the water,
limbing the trees
and paring down the bushes.
God, tore my hands up
something terrible.
All that brush-clearing...
it's kind of like
what we've been doing in here.
You lost me on that one.
In the sense that we've been working
on clearing paths,
opening up your view
of how you got to where you are.
So when you mentioned
this week's thaw,
it made me think of the way
our last session ended.
You know,
between the pills and the therapists
I saw at the hospital,
I'm not sure
I even remember that one.
You really don't remember?
I find that striking,
given how emotional
a moment that was.
Well, I know we talked about
getting me out of the cuckoo's nest.
And I showed you my pot holder.
Then I got angry
about you bringing up Connie's rehab.
I meant after that, when we talked
about the two Walters...
the one who you knew
and the one you didn't know.
That's right.
You seemed quite moved
when we talked about reconnecting
to the lost Walter.
Well, I might have teared up a bit,
but I was tired and there's been
a lot of stress.
I understand that,
but my memory is
that you didn't just tear up.
You were actually sobbing.
What is it, Walter?
Where did you go?
I just remembered
a dream I had this week.
Mr. Donaldson called me in
for a meeting.
Only it wasn't in an office.
It was...
It was in an old garage.
I went in,
we shook hands
and he told me they'd traced
the source of the contamination and that
it wasn't anything we'd done wrong.
Some nut job deliberately tampering
with the product
and then putting it back on shelf.
Go on.
I felt vindicated.
And then,
the old man did something
he never did...
he apologized.
He said that letting go of me
was the biggest mistake
he'd ever made,
that he wanted me to take
my old job back.
You'd be Walter Barnett,
C.E.O. again.
I tried to answer,
but I couldn't speak.
I opened my mouth,
but I couldn't get any words out.
I woke up in a sweat.
I kept trying to dive back into
the dream, but I couldn't get there.
You wanted to finish
the conversation?
What did you make of that dream?
Well, I guess I still want to think
the whole mess never happened.
I want my old life back.
Do you?
Because you said
you couldn't get any words out.
Is it possible
that you weren't sure if you
wanted to go back?
Probably just bargaining.
Could be.
Or perhaps now
with a little distance
you have a greater sense
of the enormous strain
you've been under for so long.
- It never used to feel like a strain.
- That's right.
I think you genuinely
didn't feel it.
You've become exceptionally adept
at overriding your feelings.
That's what we were beginning
to talk about last week.
Do you remember?
Right,
how the weak Walter
couldn't handle the stress.
Did you think about that
Walter this week?
The lost boy?
No, not really.
- You did make me think about my father.
- Your father?
How did I do that?
Just before, when I came early
and I walked in on you,
you just had a look on your face
that reminded me of him.
In what way?
After Tommy...
after the accident,
he couldn't sleep nights anymore.
Insomnia?
Yeah, and he started
to work the graveyard shift.
And
when he'd come home
from the factory,
he didn't want to wake up my mother,
so he'd go to sleep on the couch.
And I'd come downstairs and I'd want
to talk to him, you know, about...
I don't know...
the day before,
what happened at school.
And there was that look.
Can you describe it?
"How the hell do I get rid of you
"without making you feel bad?"
Come on, listen, it's okay.
Really, you were busy.
If it had been my session and somebody
walked in, I would have been pissed off.
Still, you felt rejected,
even abandoned.
I was early.
Right, the same way you were
too early for your dad.
Work comes first.
That's life.
My mother didn't see
much of him either.
She got used to it.
She'd come home from the hospital...
she was a nurse...
and I'd fix her an old-fashioned.
We'd eat.
I'd fix her another.
I had to get the cherry
and the orange wedge just right.
Then she'd go in her bedroom.
I was always nervous that
she'd fall asleep
while she was smoking in bed,
so I'd check in on her
and make sure
all the ashtrays were out.
That's a lot of responsibility
for a young boy.
Listen, they were...
you can't blame her...
either of them.
- Their lives were ruined.
- There's any need to blame them
in order to understand
your loneliness.
They were too grief-stricken
to take care of me.
I had to put away
my childish things.
Actually, I think the verse is,
"When I became a man,
"I put away childish things".
You were still a boy.
A lot of kids had it worse.
Do you remember any good times?
Did the three of you
spend time together?
Not so much.
On weekends
he was always tinkering with his car.
That thing was a real money pit.
- Did you have a garage?
- Yeah.
I used to peek in on him.
- And he didn't let you in?
- After a while I figured out
how to stand on a garbage can
and look through the window.
It turned out...
most of the time
he wasn't working on the car.
He was...
staring at a picture of Tommy
on the wall.
One time he saw me.
It was terrible.
You wanted to connect with him,
but you felt
he didn't want you there.
Is that it?
The boys used to spy on me
the same way...
when I worked on weekends.
They'd want to play or...
go swimming, and...
I always had work to do.
I probably gave them the same look.
Maybe that's why we don't have
anything to talk about now.
You know, it's not too late for you
to get to know them
and for them to get to know you.
I don't think they'd be interested.
Maybe they feel,
I don't know, intimidated by you.
Repairing those relationships is
something that we can work on in here.
I said I don't think
they're interested.
You were interested
in talking to your father...
about what you saw in that garage.
In fact,
you're still dreaming about it.
We never discussed it.
A few years later we moved...
to the next coal town over.
My mother didn't want to go, but...
my father thought it would be better
to start over again
in a new place without...
Tommy's presence
hovering over everything.
And how did you feel about it?
They didn't ask me.
It must be hard, as a child,
to know what your feelings are
when you're not asked about them.
For awhile there after we moved...
I'd run away...
back to the old home.
I'd get on my bike and...
I'd just go there, I don't know...
to check
if Tommy was waiting for us.
Go figure out a child.
What would you do when you visited?
Nothing.
I'd just sit there for hours,
waiting.
He never came back, of course.
I wonder if maybe...
Maybe you didn't go back...
just to look for Tommy. Maybe there was
someone else you were looking for.
Who?
The boy that you were
before Tommy was killed.
Maybe the old house was...
the only place
you could let yourself
feel your losses and...
find intimacy with something
that was gone, with your...
with your dead brother and...
your memories.
There was nothing there
for you, Walter.
And there was nothing
in the new home except...
duty, loneliness.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna cry.
I know how uncomfortable
that made you.
Is that how you thought I reacted,
Walter, to last week?
Come on.
You don't need to pretend.
I know I've been
a basket case in here.
I know how that disgusted you.
Why would I feel like that?
I'm a grown man.
I'm not a six-year-old.
And... men don't cry.
Maybe they do now.
But...
when I became a man, they didn't.
- Was that what your father taught you?
- He didn't have to.
Where I grew up,
a boy wouldn't be caught dead crying.
How about when Tommy died?
Did you cry then?
I was upset.
I knew it was my fault.
Maybe I started to tremble.
Maybe I started to cry.
Because the old man, I remember,
picked me up and...
shook me... hard.
"Don't you dare", he said",
"in front of your mother.
"Don't...
"you...
"ever."
Do you think
that's when you started to maybe...
shut down a little?
You mean...
that other Walter of yours?
Maybe it's not really fair
to call him "the other Walter".
The truth is, he's a part of you.
A part of you that was split off
and neglected...
for a very long time.
I was doing fine without him
all this time, wasn't I?
You did more than fine.
You accomplished great things
in your life, Walter.
So, why is this split a bad thing?
It can be hard to live your life,
to be genuinely fulfilled,
when a part of your...
your true self is locked away.
I think that what happened
was that the other part of you
the part that took responsibility,
that shouldered all these burdens...
that's the part that got rewarded...
early and often.
The more you took on,
the more praise you got.
Your dad must have been relieved
not to have to worry about his wife.
And your mom, I can imagine...
how important you felt just knowing
that you were her lifeline.
She was tricky.
We were always walking on eggshells.
My father and I didn't even tell her
I was going to Vietnam until...
two or three days before I left.
And you were...
a hero in Vietnam as well.
James Donaldson was the hero.
I just did my part.
But I'm sure
you were a natural leader.
And... in the chaos of the war
people must have looked to you.
And they were right to do so.
You'd been trained
from an early age to step up.
- It helped me survive.
- It's always helped you survive.
Even thrive.
It's how you rose
to the top of your field.
Except that...
it wasn't really your field, was it?
What do you mean?
It was James's.
Have you ever wondered
why you spent your working life
building
the Donaldsons' family business?
Was it just another rescue
that you took on, like...
the way you nursed your mother...
or...
or your wife?
See, that's the paradox...
You've been rewarded for so long
for your...
grace under fire that...
you just don't think
you're of any value to anybody
unless you're in that role.
Now that you've launched them,
your boys...
don't want to get to know you.
Natalie was done with you.
I don't want to see you at the door.
The only way to feel not rejected...
is to carry the weight...
and to keep carrying it,
even though your mind and your body
are screaming at you to stop.
I've stopped now, haven't I?
Walter Barnett, the C.E.O...
he's gone.
He came to you
with a sleeping problem...
and within weeks
his life was in shambles.
I think we both understand
that by the time you came to see me
there was no way to prevent the crash.
You knew I was headed for this?
The Walter you knew...
the hero...
he staved it off
as long as humanly possible.
If he could have
held it together this time...
he would have.
Well, it doesn't matter either way,
does it?
- We both know what you're telling me.
- What is that?
I missed it.
What did you miss?
My life.
Isn't that what you're saying?
I'm 68 years old...
and I haven't lived
one moment of my life
for myself.
What the hell
am I supposed to do with that?
Are you going to say anything?
Just that I think that now
is the time
to stop taking care
of everybody else, Walter,
and start reconnecting...
to yourself.
Was this your plan all along?
To break me down
so that I'd become dependent on you?
This would not have been
my conscious choice for you
any more than it was yours.
But the defenses that held you together
your whole life...
They just finally wore out.
You have two choices now.
We can try to wrap you back up.
Work on simple behavioral changes.
And you and I can both talk
to your psychopharmacologist...
get you back to managing things
the way you always have.
It's a valid approach.
Or?
There's a more challenging route.
If we can keep going,
doing the work that we do,
even at this stage of your life...
I know that you can achieve
a new way of being...
with Connie,
with Natalie and the boys,
but most importantly...
with yourself.
And we can keep exploring
those parts of yourself
that we've just begun to discover.
- I'm an old dog, Paul.
- 70 isn't old.
It will take work...
genuine...
introspection.
And you'll have to come more often.
You really want to spend
a couple more hours a week with...
- an old man?
- I wouldn't offer it
if I didn't think
it was worth your time...
and mine.
Why is it worth your time?
Because you've rescued
so many others...
I want to be there
when you go back and...
rescue yourself.
Fine.
When do we start?