Damn it, you're not listening to me.
Listen to me!
It doesn't matter.
We can't wait for the report.
We're gonna issue the recall.
All of it!
All right, Jace, fine.
Yeah, you think you need
to protect your ass, that's fine.
Just call the Donaldsons and tell them
it was my call, all right?
Jesus.
Synchro: So., mpm
Marie, is he off?
All right, get me Burt.
I'm sorry about this.
It's bad enough I'm late, but...
Burt?
Yeah, Walter.
I'm sorry but they wouldn't let me use
my phone until I cleared customs.
I can't reach the Donaldsons.
No, but we're gonna go ahead
with the recall anyway.
I don't trust Jace on this.
No, or on anything else really.
Well, okay.
Good good, all right.
Marie'll set up a meeting at...
10:00 p.m.
Marie, did you get that last part?
Good.
Okay, call Jace last.
Order food.
Any press, tell them
that we're working on a statement.
No, give me 40 minutes.
No calls, all right?
All right.
Thanks.
Oh, what?
Yeah, I'll text Connie.
Oh, Jesus.
Do you need a moment, Walter?
I'm not gone three days
and all hell breaks loose.
You know,
if it's an emergency, we can...
- We can reschedule.
- We've already rescheduled.
I was supposed to be here at 6:00.
It's 8:00.
No, it's after 8:00.
I'm really sorry.
And I appreciate
you're seeing me later.
I know you must have a life
outside of here.
No, it's fine.
I had an hour free.
If you understood... if you really
understood how loath I am to be late.
I'm really sorry.
This isn't me at all.
Really, it's fine.
- Here.
- What's this?
It's for your time.
- You're paying for the session in cash?
- No, it's not for the session.
I'll write a check for that. This is...
This is just something extra for you.
That's really not necessary, Walter.
Thank you.
Someone...
Unimpeachable, huh?
I like that.
- What do you mean?
- I wasn't trying to bribe you.
I mean, I'm...
That's not the way I operate.
Although, I tell you, sometimes
it might be easier for me if I did.
I understand.
You were just trying to make up
for lost hours.
- I understand.
- Exactly.
I know you value your time
and I've wasted some of it.
It was generous of you to offer.
Thank you, Walter.
- But I...
- Well, that's good.
You're a straight shooter.
That's a rare thing these days,
someone who's dependable.
I had to come to a walk-up
in Brooklyn to find it, but...
Marie, I said no calls,
for Christ's sake! Can't...
Are you sure?
That son of a bitch.
No, don't let him know
that you've reached me.
Just let him think
I'm walking into it.
I'll call you from the car.
Just give me a half hour of peace.
Can you do that?
Unbelievable.
This little pisser... Jace!
He's not even half my age
and somehow he thinks
he's gonna use this to bring me down.
He's so self-deluded he actually thinks
they're gonna give him my job.
- Walter, you seem...
- It's my own fault.
In a way.
I mean,
he was very bright, eager,
good schools.
I brought him into the company.
But he's green.
He's in over his head. It's...
Walter, can you listen to me
for a moment?
You seems like...
you seem like you're in the midst
of a breaking crisis here.
No, Paul, it's not breaking.
It's already broke.
We cull ingredients
from all over the world:
China,
Brazil, Indonesia.
Somehow something
got into the pipeline.
Walter, whatever is going on...
it could be contaminated milk powder
or bacteria
from one of the factories.
It could be a cheap lubricant leeching
into the machinery...
You don't seem like you're able
to get away from this right now.
I think that it would be
a very good idea for us to reschedule.
Reschedule?!
When?
It's not gonna get any better
tomorrow or the day after.
Paul, I'm going into combat
in an hour.
And if I...
if I don't talk to you now,
it might be another month
before I get a chance.
It's off, okay?
Both of them.
- Can I get a glass of water?
- Sure.
I hate this stuff.
Connie's always telling me
I should drink more of it.
So does my doctor,
but I don't have time for it.
You don't have time to drink water?
Sometimes no, I don't.
And this week, it's a good thing anyway,
where I was.
You've been traveling?
I spent the last 44 out of 72 hours
in an airplane.
And
the hours waiting for the six flights
were no barrel of laughs either.
So the trip was in response to the...
To the crisis.
What?
Well, you were just saying how you have
suppliers all over the world,
and I assumed that you were
trying to track down
the source of the problem.
I wasn't flying for the company.
- You weren't?
- No, I flew to Rwanda to get Natalie.
Did something happen to her?
No, she didn't say so.
But I knew that she was in trouble.
So
she didn't ask you to come?
She didn't have to.
Look, Paul, she's... she's my daughter.
And until she went to Rwanda,
I had spoken with her
every day of her life.
Wherever I was in the world,
I'd call her at bedtime
and tell her I loved her.
Before she could talk,
I made these little clicking noises.
Then after she went to Rwanda,
we emailed every day.
Suddenly,
Suddenly a week ago, she
writes her mother but not me.
Connie doesn't do email
so I had to print
the letters out for her.
And
she was asking Connie
if I was all right,
if
the company was really complicit
in this baby formula mess.
It was crazy talk.
Mightn't she have just been concerned
for your welfare?
Well, Paul, don't you think
I know my own daughter?
That's not what I'm saying, Walter.
I'm just trying to understand why,
with your company in crisis,
you would chose to visit
your daughter in Rwanda.
The emails,
her voice wasn't her voice.
She would never doubt her father.
Now I'm not saying
she's being brainwashed,
but I knew she was hiding something
and once I got there
I found out I was right.
- What was she hiding?
- To start with,
she cut all her hair off.
She'd always had
this long auburn hair,
like my mother's
when she was that age.
Well, that's gone now.
Don't you think that's disturbing?
I can see
why you might find it so, yes.
But cutting hair,
dyeing it weird colors,
lopping it off even, I mean,
that's what
what daughters do.
What else was different about her?
What was the same about her?
I didn't know who I was talking to.
She had no shoes.
She had given them away,
it turns out.
She was so thin.
She had this child in her arms...
a little girl hanging in her arms
like a sack of potatoes.
Are you okay, Walter?
This is where she's living, Paul.
This is where my daughter has chosen
to live... some hellhole near Goma.
When she saw you, how did she react?
I don't think I spoke right away.
I just stood there
looking at her.
Finally she got scared.
She said, "What is it?
Mom? Is mom all right?"
And I said, "Your mother's fine".
She said, "What are you doing here?"
And I said,
"I've come to take you home.
- "Get your stuff."
- And that didn't go down well?
No. At first she was...
distant.
"Dad, I can't leave right now.
I have to finish a procedure."
As if she'd got some medical degree
in the last month.
She said she'd meet me for dinner
in a few hours in the big tent.
Then she pointed
in the direction of some little shacks
in case I wanted to lie down.
She was living
in one of those shacks.
They looked like outhouses
and she was sleeping there.
I can see how upsetting that...
that might have been for you.
I mean, you spent your life...
providing a good home for her and...
this is how she chooses to live.
So what happened at the dinner?
Well, I didn't wait for dinner.
I went back into the shack
and I took all her stuff and...
I put it in the jeep.
I just...
I just wanted to take it back
with me to Kigali and at least
have her clothes cleaned.
I wanted to go back
to the hotel that night and...
take her to dinner
and maybe talk some sense into her.
The next thing I know, she's...
tearing across this field,
screaming at me
insane stuff...
How I'm trying to control her,
how I don't respect her,
how she's worked so hard to build up
trust with these people and now...
they're gonna think
that she's some neocolonialist
like me.
And there was something about Connie
I'm not even going to repeat.
I swear to god, Paul, it took
everything I had not to slap her.
Instead I just said, "Don't you
ever speak about your mother like that".
Then...
she broke down and started to cry.
What did you do then?
I put my arms around her.
I said, "Natalie, we're going home".
And then...
she told me to go fuck myself.
She'd never said
anything like that to you before?
She broke my heart, Paul.
She broke my heart.
Why do you think
she was so angry with you?
She made that pretty clear.
I got an email from her
when I got back to the hotel.
It turns out that I'm domineering,
obsessive,
that I'm the cause
of all her anxieties,
that it's impossible to thrive
or grow around me, and...
that's why she had to go away
and now I'm...
ruining her only chance
to free herself from me.
Now you see why I went over there?
I sensed this was coming
from earlier emails.
You know,
hearing that email makes me...
Can we talk about the way
you... came in here today?
Completely in charge on both phones,
handing me your bag...
Not quite like I was a bellhop,
but...
something like that.
- I'm sorry if I offended you.
- No, you didn't offend me. But...
it did catch my attention.
Walter, we both know that...
you are...
an excellent... manager.
World class.
Right?
But in other roles where...
you're not entirely in control,
like say being a patient here, or...
maybe when you went to see Natalie.
That's much less comfortable
for you.
But what are you saying?
I never try to control Natalie.
- I gave her whatever she wanted.
- Of course.
You've given her everything.
And that's...
That's something that's hard
for other parents to do but...
not for you.
Do you think it's possible that...
what's hard for you is...
just... letting her be?
Letting her go?
Did you think that...
you felt her pulling away from you
in those emails?
And then when you saw her
at the camp did you...
did you get frightened?
Scared... of losing her
so that you felt you had to tell her
to pack up her things and come home?
Can't a father worry
about his own daughter?
Of course he can.
But just look at...
how you responded for a moment.
In the midst of a major work crisis,
you read an email
that she wrote to Connie and without
stopping to think, you get on a plane
and you fly halfway
around the world.
It's all right.
These work pretty quick.
Xanax, it's...
Dr. Wells gave me the prescription.
Thank God he did.
Otherwise
I'd never have been able to...
get out of that place.
Did you take a pill...
after you saw Natalie?
Later.
I woke up in the middle of the night
in a cold sweat.
I had a nightmare...
that Natalie was gone.
Then I looked around me
and with the...
jetlag and the fatigue,
I had no idea
where I was for a minute.
I thought I was...
back in my parents' house,
in Tommy's room,
with all his sports trophies
and awards.
I just couldn't stay in that room
another second.
I had to get out of there.
I was having trouble breathing.
And then I remembered the pills.
Do you think it's strange
that you were...
that you were thinking about...
Tommy over there...
in Africa?
He's been on my mind lately.
Do you know when that started?
Has it been since Natalie left?
You said that you woke up
and you felt that you had to get out.
Hotels can be disorienting.
But losing Tommy was...
very painful for you, wasn't it?
My folks had the pain.
With all due respect,
when parents lose a child it kills them.
It's really admirable that you remained
so close to your parents
after that happened.
Like with the Donaldsons,
as you've said.
After their son James died,
you became like a son to them.
The good son,
the one everybody can depend on.
And then you had this dream.
And...
you feel
that you're suffocating in...
in Tommy's room.
What does this have to do
with Natalie?
Maybe Natalie
is trying to do something
that you've never
allowed yourself to do:
to separate from her parents.
For you to stay connected
means to never...
stray.
Now Natalie is trying to do something
in between, but you feel
that she's abandoning you
the way Tommy did.
He died, Paul.
Jesus.
- He didn't abandon me.
- I know.
But maybe that night in the hotel,
Natalie's separation
from you...
felt,
in some way,
- it felt like a death.
- God forbid.
There's no comparison.
There's a big difference.
When a child dies, he's gone.
Isn't that exactly the nightmare that
woke you up, that Natalie was gone?
It wasn't the same.
I was trying to find her.
I knew that no matter
how bad I felt,
I had to put myself aside
and think only of Natalie.
I took the pills.
And somehow it passed.
And...
I dragged myself
back to the hotel lobby
and I went online
in the business center.
That's when I read her emails
and I realized...
I realized...
You realized what, Walter?
It's okay to have the...
thought here.
You can say whatever you like.
I realized
that she didn't need me at all.
Or maybe that's just
what she needs to feel right now.
She's done with her old man.
I'm a booster rocket.
She's launched, like your boys, isn't
that what you said at our first session?
Did I? I'm sure I also said
that Natalie was different.
I'd have to agree with you.
You did raise her with the freedom
to think for herself,
to question authority figures,
to confront the world of adults.
You gave her an incredible gift.
Now she wants to use it.
- By telling me to go fuck myself?
- That's what you heard.
But before that, she wanted you
to talk things over with her.
- She invited you to dinner, no?
- She was just shining me on.
Possibly.
Or possibly she really
wanted to talk to you.
But you felt like she was disrespecting
you and you reacted to that.
You know, I think that...
for her whole life
she's been very aware of you
and how you feel and what you think
and what she can do to make you happy.
Maybe part of the reason
she's so angry is because
maybe for the first time in her life
she knows that...
what she wants...
is not what you want.
And she's having a very hard time
reconciling herself to that fact.
She's having a hard time?
What about me?
- So how did you leave things with her?
- I didn't.
I woke up the next morning to a barrage
of incoming faxes, phone calls,
emails, outbreaks of diarrhea,
children in hospitals
possibly from formula contaminated
at one of our plants.
I'd gotten out in front of this!
I leave for a few days and...
it's like they were just waiting for me
to turn my back.
I'm sorry, Walter.
With the late session,
I forgot to shut the...
Hello, this is Mr. Barnett's assistant,
Marie.
It's urgent
that he speaks with Burt.
If he calls me,
I can patch him through.
Back to battle stations.
I'd better be going.
Thank you.
26 messages.
Will you be all right?
I'll be fine.
They can't get rid of me, Paul.
Après moi, le déluge.
After you, the flood?
That's a lot of pressure.
The glue, Paul, the glue.
Just look what happened when I left.
I guess...
my daughter can survive
without me but...
the Donaldsons can't.
Will I see you next week?
Yeah, and thanks again.
You're welcome.
Call Burt and...
What do you mean you can't get him?
You just left me a message
he wants to speak with me.
What about the old man?