Previously on In Treatment...
If there's someone who does not know
the meaning of guilt, it's my father.
Mid-'50s, right?
Jim Crow, Oklahoma.
This mob with hoods
attacked his house.
So my father takes the family,
they run downstairs to the...
The boiler room, to the basement.
My grandfather, his father,
was very sick,
dying of lung cancer.
He had this hacking cough.
My father puts his hand over
his father's mouth and nose
and he kept it there
while they searched the basement.
Kept it clamped tight.
And then when
they finally cleared out...
my grandfather was dead.
I'd love to see him on this couch.
Doc, you'd have a field day with him.
I'm Paul Weston.
I was a friend of Alex's.
My deepest deepest condolences.
Thank you.
I... I don't remember...
You played racquetball with him.
Hello, excuse me.
I'm sorry. I didn't know which one
of these doors was the right one.
That's okay.
It's a terrible day.
Didn't want to knock on your residence.
No problem. This door is
usually for people who come in.
That's usually the exit door.
But it doesn't...
It doesn't really matter.
You have an entry door
and an exit door?
It's for people's privacy.
Some people don't like to...
They don't like to run into each other.
Are they ashamed?
No. It's just...
It's protocol really.
- Would you like some coffee?
- No, I'm a tea man.
But no, nothing, thank you.
- I'm fine.
- Please, sit down.
I got a lot of questions.
I'm sure you have. And I hope
that I can answer some of them.
One thing I do have
to stress from the outset
is that anything that is said
between myself and a patient
in this room...
is private.
- Even if the patient is dead?
- Yes, even then.
Well, I'm sure
we'll find something to talk about...
Something to help me understand
what happened to my son.
Transcript: FRM Team
Sync: Benj!
You weren't very forthcoming
about who you were
when we met at the services.
A friend, you said?
That's hardly the case.
Well, I didn't want
to betray Alex's confidence.
Daniel didn't hesitate in explaining
exactly what your relationship
to Alex was.
He's very direct... Daniel.
I like that about him.
Were you surprised to hear
that Alex was in therapy?
That he didn't tell me surprised me.
- I mean, what's the big deal?
- Why do you think he didn't?
We'll never know the answer
to that, will we?
Or I won't.
Maybe that's something
you discussed here.
You know, it always puzzled me,
the whole process here, you know?
I mean, that...
That a person is in therapy at all
often is never discussed...
Who the doctor is,
what he's there for,
how much it cost.
Funny thing is that it's secrecy
or misunderstandings,
things never spoken that...
usually land people
in therapy in the first place.
- Isn't at ironic?
- I don't think it's about secrecy.
I think it's about creating
an environment
where people
can come and feel safe
to talk about anything.
Safer than with their loved ones?
Sometimes
it's easier to talk to somebody
who's totally uninvolved
in your life...
Somebody objective.
Somebody who has no stake in it.
You mean like a prostitute, hmm?
Someone who's paid for their
intimacy and their discretion.
A man should have
someone to talk to
who cares about him,
Not someone
who charges by the hour.
I really did care for Alex.
And if I hadn't,
I'd actually be a pretty poor therapist.
Do you think Alex spoke about things
in this room that he never...
spoke to anyone else about?
That is usually
the case with patients.
So you probably know
as much about him as anyone did.
Do you feel
that you knew your son well?
I knew Alex when he was...
a little boy.
- And what was he like then?
- Well, he was...
quiet.
Introspective.
Daydreamer.
Inventor.
Did he ever mention that to you?
He never did, no.
He invented this thing
for his mother...
A pan that made flipping
an omelet over very easy.
He worked very hard on that thing.
It was really good.
So where did he get that from?
Were you an inventor?
Oh, no.
No, man. I was a knucklehead.
My father was an inventor.
He invented
this knife-sharpening machine.
It didn't make very much money.
He was proud of it.
Alex reminded me of him.
In what way?
You trying to shrink me, doctor?
I'm just curious.
Or perhaps you can't help yourself.
That's probably true too.
My father and Alex...
had the same mannerisms,
the same sense of humor.
It was unsettling.
When Alex was a little boy
and my father
had been dead almost 20 years...
There he was...
Sitting across the dinner
table looking at me...
Through me
with those eyes of his
on Alex's face.
Is your father still living, Mr. Weston?
Yes.
Yes, his body is in good health,
But his...
His mind is gone.
Were you close?
We had our differences, of course.
But we were close.
We are close, I mean.
How often do you see him?
About once a month.
Does he know you're there?
No. I don't think so.
But the visit is more for my sake.
What do you get out of it?
Connection,
a sense of...
belonging.
Do you ever have conversations
with him in your head?
Both sides of the conversation?
Yes.
When I was younger everything he said
went in one ear, out the other.
Now I hear his voice in my head
Loud and clear every day.
That's the sense of connection
that you mentioned. That's...
That's what I feel slipping away
with each passing day
since Alex's death.
That sense of...
I'm trying to find his voice,
you know, but...
He won't talk to me.
If you don't mind me saying so,
Mr. Prince, I think
that it's still too soon.
You're probably still
in a state of shock.
But his voice...
will come back to you.
I apologize
for comparing what you do
to, uh, prostitution.
I don't believe
they're the same at all.
Apology accepted.
How would you describe
my son Alex?
I'm not asking you
for a diagnosis.
You don't have to tell me
what he thought,
just what you thought
of him personally.
I thought that Alex was...
an extremely...
capable man.
Strong sense of mission.
A very strong sense of
what was expected of him.
Uh, mission or purpose?
- What do you mean?
- Well, Alex was a military man.
Military men have missions.
To have a purpose,
a sense of purpose,
that's something...
Something you do on your own,
something you want for yourself.
Did he have that?
I think that Alex
was struggling to find out
what he wanted for himself.
- Did he say that?
- No, sir, he didn't.
I'm just giving you
some of my impressions
without betraying
what he confided in me.
Frankly, it's more
than I'm allowed to do.
Were you in the service yourself,
Mr. Prince?
Eight months, you know,
after they drafted me.
Had an asthma attack
and they discharged me.
probably saved my life.
Funny, a breathing problem was...
my salvation,
and my father's death knell.
Alex told you about
what happened to my father?
These are facts about my life,
not Alex's treatment.
Do you happen to know
how my father died?
Yes or no? Simple question.
Yes. Yes, I do.
Anyway, I wasn't a war hero
like my son,
if that's what you were wondering.
How did you feel about Alex's...
service in the Navy?
I was proud of it, of course,
like any father would be.
- Was he, do you think?
- Do you suspect that he wasn't?
I want to understand my son...
mr. Weston.
And instead of helping me,
You answer questions with questions.
I think your son
found it increasingly difficult to
compartmentalize,
to keep his feelings
apart from his obligations
and to live up to
the expectations of others.
The expectations of the Navy?
Expectations to excel
like he had always excelled.
And at the expense
of his own needs
and his real desires.
Are you saying that Alex
was ill-equipped emotionally
To handle the pressure?
- Mr. Prince, you're asking me to...
- I'm asking your opinion.
Alex's emotional state
is not something...
You're playing a little fast and loose
here, aren't you, mr. Weston?
I can know my son was troubled,
just not how troubled?
I want to know
what his therapist believed
he was capable of,
how far he would go.
How far he'd go to what, Mr. Prince?
I've spoken to
a couple of Alex's fellow pilots.
It was a training flight.
They simulate a battle,
one plane against another.
The other pilot
made a snap decision,
Tried to get away,
apparently flying low.
They say Alex
didn't have time to straighten out.
There's also a rumor
going around
that Alex killed himself.
He was a superb pilot.
It wasn't combat,
it was a training exercise.
It was a training exercise.
There hasn't been any...
official...
finding,
Mr. Prince.
You said that yourself.
There's an ejection seat.
Why didn't he jump?
Maybe he...
didn't think
he needed to use it.
Well...
Michaela's been in church,
you know, on her knees,
praying, looking for answers.
My wife also.
And I told 'em, you know...
That's the wrong place to look.
God and me,
we've been over for a while.
My faith died...
when my father died.
A boy once beat Alex up.
He was about 10 or 11.
He took his shoes.
Little shit punk, you know?
Alex did nothing to fight back.
He didn't defend himself.
He wasn't a fighter. He was a...
He was a frail kid.
You know? Thin-skinned.
And that scared the hell out of me.
Where I come from,
thin black skin could get you killed.
And that was
the kind of world that...
That Alex was born into?
What are you implying?
- I'm simply asking if he...
- No. Let me tell you something.
I saw more injustices
As a child.
Horrors.
Did they...
Did they affect
my view of the world?
Of course.
Did they shape the manner
in which I raised my boy?
How could they not?
Strength.
Strength was essential to survival.
Vulnerability
was often a death sentence.
I wanted him to be safe.
I envy the time you spent
talking with him.
I admit...
Those kind of talks
embarrass the hell out of me.
This where he sat?
Yes.
Alex could talk.
He and his boy,
they'd talk for hours.
He even once told Roy
that he loved him.
Boy, I tell you...
Did I give him hell for that.
"You're trying to make
the kid a sissy or something?"
It was bad enough that
he didn't want to best Alex at anything.
He'd rather throw a chess game
just so's he wouldn't have
to beat his father.
Oh now, come on. That's no way
to raise a boy to be a man.
I mean, you have to challenge him,
make him compete,
Teach him how to fight,
take care of himself.
It's interesting
that you regret not being
more gentle yourself with Alex,
and yet at the same time,
You seem to justify being...
being harsh.
I hear you saying that you're a little
conflicted about the notion...
Mister,
I'm not in conflict about anything.
Is that how you tried to help Alex?
Second-guessing every word
that comes out of his mouth?
A stranger,
completely unfamiliar
with his background.
You go explaining
his world to him.
Actually,
our sessions were mostly
about me listening to what...
To what he had to say.
Yeah, well, there we go again
with the listening, huh?
He has his own personal
professional listener.
Listen,
when I smothered my father
do you think I paid someone
to listen to me, hmm?
You can't stop and dwell
on every ache and pain.
Maybe it's because
of what my dad did
or maybe it's because
of what my mother did.
Come on, you've got
to keep moving, man.
You know?
What good does all the talk do?
It's not gonna bring my father back.
You know what?
People like you...
You never stop to think
that we have a subconscious
for a reason.
Because there are things about
ourselves that we cannot face.
That we should not face.
Or else how in the world do
we get up out of bed in the morning?
I'll tell you,
World War III comes...
All those people who've been through
all of this psychoanalysis,
spend hundreds...
Thousands of dollars,
are gonna be the first ones
to lose their heads.
Darwin had a theory.
He called it survival of the fittest.
The fittest,
not the most self-reflective.
With all due respect,
I think that
Alex started coming here
because he felt that he needed to.
And you had to take him apart,
didn't you?
You had to pick at the scab.
Do you think
that Alex's therapy here
had something to do with his death?
You're the one who told him
he had to go look inside.
To reflect,
examine, feel.
Oh yeah, he felt.
And what did that get him?
Now he's a human pancake.
You're a hell
of a miracle worker, doctor.
Do you have a son, Mr. Weston?
Yes, I do.
And if another man,
someone from a different culture,
started giving him advice...
Every week...
Advice that you were pretty sure
would be harmful to your son...
What would you do?
Your son was a mature man
who decided to come here
of his own...
What would you do?
I would try to stop him,
If I could.
I can't get over the feeling...
That I was torn apart
in this room.
People have...
a misunderstanding
About what happens in...
In rooms like this.
It really isn't about...
blaming or looking
for scapegoats.
He was an outstanding person.
He was kind,
devoted,
loyal...
Too loyal.
Often, I wished that he...
would've just pleased himself, not me.
But we want to please,
don't we, Mr. Weston?
He did a lifetime
of trying to please me.
All that...
That tough...
That tough schooling...
And the training and...
the achievements...
That was for me.
I'm the one who needed it.
To feel...
that he was safe.
You know?
You son loved you.
And he had huge admiration for you.
He told me that.
Don't tell me that, man.
You think that comfort...
You think that comforts me?
No. I would have rathered...
that he hated me.
I would have rathered
That this was his "fuck you" to me.
Why do you say that?
For pushing him so hard...
To be tougher...
than the rest of the world.
I was so stupid.
Did I kill my son?
I killed my father
with my own two hands.
Did I kill my son too?
No, whatever happened
up there was not your fault.
You're not responsible.
We'll never know, will we?
Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
I'd appreciate it very much
if you'd call me a taxi, please.
Sure.