You don't get it, do you?
He's sick, Paul.
Look, he can't be missing school again.
What is the big deal?
He'she top of his class.
I don't care. He's not staying at home.
I swear to god, Paul,
If you take him
out of this house--
You swear what?
He's here.
Max ?
What are you doing ?
I thought you were watching tv.
103?!
You're not 103.
Your hands are cold.
So i suppose you wanna stay home
From school today.
We could rent a movie and watch it.
Oh, Max, i'd love to rent
A video and watch it with you,
But i can't.
I got no choice. I've gotta go to work.
You've gotta go to school.
You never believe me.
I couldn't open the door.
I'm sorry,
it gets, uh--
It gets stuck.
Hi, i'm Paul.
Sophie.
Nice to meet you. Come on in.
- Here?
- Yes.
- Uh, do you need
any help with the--
- No, it's okay. Okay.
Anna Colden recommended
that i talk to you.
Anna Colden?
She's my lawyer.
She heard about you
from a friend of yours.
I mean, a friend of hers,
Not a friend of yours.
From a patient of yours
Who is a friends of hers.
- Sorry.
So Anna Colden recommended you
Through a patient of mine.
Do you know, do you know his name?
- I don't know.
- So what-- What did
Anna recommend me for?
After my
accident--
I told you on the phone
about the accident.
Yes.
They told me that i need the opinion
Of a psychiatrist
Because the insurance company
Of the car that hit me
Has a problem with my injuries, or,
Something like that.
So that's why i'm here.
I'm here for your professional opinion,
- Not
for--
Not for therapy.
So let's see
if i'm, uh--
If i'm getting this right.
Are you
Suing the insurance company
Of the person who hit you? No,
Their insurance company
Had me talk to a social worker.
She started
Asking me all sorts
of annoying questions.
She was really annoying
So i refused to talk to her.
She started talking to me like
She knew me or something, so
I refused to talk.
And,
That didn't go over so well, so,
My mother said it would be better
If i came here to talk to you.
Okay.
So what happened at the accident
That
requires a--
A psychiatric opinion?
I really don't remember what happened.
I was on my bicycle
and a car ran into me
And i don't remember what happened next.
What did they tell you afterwards?
That i flew my bike
right into the street.
You're,
-
- You're laughing at that.
What that sounds like,
Flying straight into the street?
So,
You find that
Funny, yeah?
Because...
it reminds me of something
About two years ago.
A friend of mine, he,
Took me out on this motorbike
And he stopped to get something at
A convenience store.
Anyway, i was really bored, so,
I pretended that i knew how to drive it.
You know, you put your
hands on the handlebars
And you go like this. Well,
It was one of those
monster bikes--
Just by turning the handle
a little it just flies.
So suddenly i'm like
zoom, and it takes off.
My head whips back like this
And when i looked back down i realize
That i'm riding into the street.
Totally crashed into a car.
There was this old woman standing nearby
And she saw all this.
"I saw her, she did it on purpose.
She tried to kill herself.
She tried to kill herself."
That's what-- That's
what she was yelling?
- Yeah, she was like a crazy woman.
Of course, it couldn't
have been that funny
When it happened, i'm sure.
No, not really.
I wanted to kill her.
I was just lying there.
I couldn't move. I couldn't do anything.
I wanted to yell, "shut
up you-- You idiot.
Why are you screaming?"
You know, but i couldn't speak.
It's like
this feeling--
When somebody says something about you
And you can't defend yourself.
- Paul: mm-Hmm. -
It's totally unfair.
Like that social worker
You were talking about.
What does-- What does
she have to do with it?
Well, didn't you feel that she was
Speaking for you?
Yeah, but i could have said something.
I just didn't want to.
So tell me a little bit
more about this, uh--
This accident.
It's on that report.
Where did it happen?
In a gas station on madison
Near the gym where i train.
So you were on the way to the gym?
I don't know. I told you
I don't remember anything.
Do you feel comfortable
Talking about yourself, Sophie?
No.
My name is Sophie.
I'm 16 years old.
I've been a gymnast since the age
Of six and a half.
I was u.S. Junior
champion athe age of 12.
I'm an only child.
I don't know. What do you want to know?
In another few months
Are the
national trials--
Last chance to quality for the olympics.
I'm kind of like
An olympic hopeful.
Wow,
That's really impressive.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
So how is life in general?
What?
Oh, apart from the gymnastics,
How's life?
It's great.
I-- I st don't
have the energy
For "this is your life" right now.
"This is your life"?
What do-- At do you mean?
You know, like the tv show.
You're way too young
to know about that show.
It's on dvd.
My mom's friend watches it all the time.
- What do you think of it?
- It's okay.
Some of the people on it are so old.
Why do you think they
put old people on that?
I don't know.
Because they have nothing better to do.
They're retired and
they're dying off fast, so,
They put them on the
show before it's too late.
So do you think you can help me
With this professional opinion or not?
Well, it's not that simple, Sophie.
Why not?
Because it's not like
an x-Ray where you can
Take photographs, look at the results
And then you go on your way.
It doesn't quite work like that.
Okay.
Okay, so i guess i'll leave. ( Sighs )
Would you at least like to read
What it says in the report?
If you want me to.
- What, like you already
know what it says.
- No.
I have no idea what it says.
Listen,
I didn't come here to talk about myself.
I just need your opinion.
So you want me to give you my opinion
Based on what i read and
The conversation that we've had today.
Is that--
Is that it?
Is that a problem?
No.
I'll write up an opinion and, um,
When you come next week you can decide
Whether you want to use it or not.
Just like that without
Any more questions?
Well, what kind of questions
Do you want me to ask?
I don't know, shrink-Like questions.
Say about mom, dad,
That kind of thing?
Doesn't sound like you're interested.
Why would you say that, Sophie?
I am very interested in
Everything that you have to say.
I mean that.
You spoke to my mother
already, didn't you?
I didn't speak to your mother.
You already know what it says in there.
I've never spoken to your mom.
You did talk to her
And you're just letting me sit here
An you know exactly
What's in that envelope.
Was i-- Was i supposed
to talk to her?
What, did you, like, plan everything?
Like i'm some kind of idiot,
You planned this little charade.
What's the point? Whatever.
Of course she would send me
To someone like you.
I should have listened to my father.
He called them a cult
of crazies-- Shit.
Open the door for me, please.
- And if i did speak to your mom?
- I knew it.
- So what then?
- It means you're a liar,
Okay?
Because i know how
it's supposed to work.
You're supposed to read
What's written in that report
And ask the stupid
shrink questions you ask.
Doesn't it seem unprofessional
To so not do it that way?
Maybe i have something to say
About what it says in there.
I just wanted to read the report
By myself
Before our meeting
next week, that's all.
What meeting next week?
Well, i'd like us to
meet three or four times
For me to form an opinion of you.
To get to know you a little,
Don't you think?
Otherwise,
It wouldn't be professional.
I'll read it now,
Okay?
So are all these ships
Instead of sailing for real?
At least you won't get seasick.
Oh, i don't know about that.
- What do you mean?
- Sometimes i can get quite wobbly
Just sitting right here.
You have to make a round
window to the outside.
Then you'll feel like
you're in a real ship.
Did you really read all those books,
Or is just to make an impression?
Yes, you read them or yes,
You're trying to make an impression?
Yes,
I read them.
I feel sorry for the books up there.
Why do you feel sorry for them?
Where would you put them?
I don't know. They're
your fucking books,
Buster.
You suffer from asthma.
Yeah, how do you know that?
- There's an inhaler here.
- Oh, thanks. I,
I've been looking everywhere for that,
Thank you.
So what, you could have died without it?
According to what it says here...
it looks like you could have died too.
Yeah, that would have
solved a lot of problems.
What would it solve?
Nothing.
I didn't mean anything by it.
Can i talk to you like a normal person?
Do you drive your daughter crazy
With questions like this too?
Much more crazy, believe me.
How'd you know i had a daughter?
Because you do.
You know my mother.
You were on the pta committee
At arlington elementary.
I was there before
I went off to a private school.
I was in the same year as your daughter.
Well, why didn't you
tell me that before?
You said
that the--
That the social worker spoke to you
Like she knew you.
She was such a retard.
Did she ask
you if, um--
If you think about death a lot?
How did you know that?
According to what it says here,
She was trying to
prove that the accident
Was your fault.
It's a good thing you didn't answer
Any of her questions.
By the way,
Everybody thinks about death.
I bet she didn't say that, though.
Did she ask you if you had any
Specific thoughts about death?
- No.
- Do you?
Do i what?
Everyone--
Everyone thinks about death and, uh,
Imagines how it will come to them.
Do you have any more
Specific thoughts about it?
Maybe you have certain thoughts
That you'd like to talk about.
- Unless you're
worried about what i--
- I'm not worried.
Okay.
Is this how it's gonna be
For three appointments?
Is this a little diffult for you?
No.
Can i have some water?
Sure.
Hang on a minute.
Sorry about this.
It's for my little patients,
The elves.
It's a bendy one.
You need help with that?
Must be really
hard to be, uh--
To be handicapped like a,
What's the hardest thing about it?
Everyone treats me like a baby.
Did you come here by yourself today?
Yes, by bus.
Your mom didn't offer to drive you?
Yeah, right.
She knew there was
no chance i'd say yes.
Before when you
got angry when, uh--
When you thought that she'd called me,
I asked myself, "why didn't she call?"
It makes sense that
she would call me first.
I don't
-
- What do you mean?
Well, i'm just trying to figure out
Why you got so angry
- When you thought
She'd called me. - I don't
get it. - She did call?
- No no no.
Did she call or not? Tell me already.
She didn't call.
- So why are we back to this again?
Because i got the feeling that when
You got angry,
You wanted your mother to call
Just so that you could
get angry with her.
You have no idea what i'm looking for.
- You just don't get it.
- Okay.
So...
why don't you explain it to me then?
She thinks that what's
written there is true.
- What's true?
- Whatever
it says--
Suicidal tendencies, blah blah blah.
That's what your mother says,
Is true?
She thinks that this
accident is a wonderful
Opportunity to get rid
of the sports thing.
That's what she calls it.
But what does that have to do with
This report?
She's afraid.
She doesn't
believe that--
She thinks that because of all this
Competition and perfectionism
She thinks that i wanted to kill myself
And that's bullshit.
It's been like this for years.
I've been under pressure for years
And she has never supported me.
All the other mothers are right there
All over us visiting the gym,
The training camps, all of it.
And the only thing she has to say is,
"What do you need this for?"
It's obvious she doesn't
understand anything.
All this
pressure--
It doesn't make any difference.
It's so silly. Why
would i hurt myself now
Just before the nationals
When i have
all the--
And if i fail the lawsuit,
Then i really have no chance.
What do you mean fail?
Do you see this as a kind of test?
Tell me,
Why do
you--
Why are you making it sound like its...
what?
I didn't come here for therapy.
I just need you to write your opinion
And tell me that i'm perfectly all right
And tell them that i'm not some crazy
Who flies into cars every day.
Is that why you came here today, Sophie?
For me to tell you
that you're all right?
That you're not crazy?
Is that the test you're
afraid of failing?
I have to go.
It's 10:2 already.
You probably have to turn on
Your cell phone now.
Why are
you--
Are you worried that
i won't be available?
No.
Are you this much of a pain in the ass
With your daughter?
Much much worse, believe me.
And yes, i do try to
understand my daughter,
If that's what you're asking.
That's not what i'm asking.
Let's say she wants to talk to you now.
What'll she do?
I don't think she'll wait till 10 to
So she can talk to you.
Who do you call, Sophie?
Oh, suddenly you don't feel comfortable
Talking about your daughter.
Look, she calls me at 10 minutes
Before the hour, she leaves a message
And i get back to her.
But who do you call?
Who do i call for what?
When you need to talk to someone.
411.
411?
Yeah.  Because my father has moved
So many times in the past few years,
I can never remember
his latest phone number.
It's like a family joke.
We call 411.
How do you get on with your dad?
He's always there for me.
What do you mean he's
always there for you?
He's there.
He knows what's happening to me.
Like when i had the accident,
He called me when i w in the ambulance.
He knew something had happened.
- That's what they told me.
So is it like you guys have a kind of
Telepathy together?
He's the only person in this world
Who truly loves me
And the only one that
believes that the accident
Was not my fault.
The only one except Cy.
Who's Cy?
This is Cy.
Cy is a mermaid?
No, Cy drew it.
He's my coach.
Dana colored it. That's his daughter.
I used to be her babysitter.
Do i have to go now?
Yes.
So-- So you babysit
for your coach?
Yeah, since before i joined his gym.
So Cy is the only one,
Apart from your dad, who
Loves you ?
Or he's the only who
Thinks that you didn't crash your bike
On purpose?
I don't know.
Is that important
For your professional opinion?
Okay.
I'll tell you what i want us to do.
I would like, before our next meeting,
For us to do some homework.
We both write up our opinion
Of what's in that
report. What do you say?
How am i supposed to write like this?
You can get somebody to help you.
You can do it on tape, if you'd like.
What am i supposed to write?
Your own opinion,
Your own assessment
Of what's in there.
What do you say?
I don't think so.
I think you can do it.
This way.
So will you try?
We'll see.