[Beeping]
What are we doing, Sydney?
An experiment
about sexuality.
- Reproduction?
- That's one aspect of it.
I read the biology manuals.
Reading isn't quite
the same as feeling.
I'd like you to meet
someone, Jarod.
[Beeping Increases]
- You're a girl.
- [Woman On TV] Will you marry me?
- Never. No! Oh!
- [People Laughing]
[Woman]
Now will you marry me?
They seem to be able to withstand
an amazing amount of pain.
People find this type
of violence funny?
- Not people, men.
- [Men Laughing]
- [Man On TV] You moron.!
- Why is that?
Nobody knows.
The Stooges have been one of...
the great mysteries
between the sexes.
- [Man On TV] Ow.!
- [Laughing]
- I think I see it.
- [Jarod Laughing]
- [Man On TV] My piano.!
- No, not you too.
I'm sorry, but, really,
it is pretty funny.
[Laughing]
Oh. Oh.
I'm sorry.
I feel like such a...
Stooge?
[Men Laughing]
Hey, mattress brain,
the bill's 12.95.
Oh. Oh.
These guys have caused
enough distractions for one day.
[Men Laughing]
Park Service Rangers from all over
have joined in the search...
for Victor Simpkins,
an ornithology grad student...
who vanished
in our local mountains.
I spoke with Simpkins's mother
moments ago.
When I didn't hear
from Victor, well...
I just thought he was late,
but now it's been five days.
I'm just praying he's okay.
With a storm heading this way, rangers are
anxious to find Simpkins before it's too late.
Live from the Toluca National Forest,
this is David Milkson, Action 15.
- Okay, here's your...
- [Man #2 On TV] Thank you, David.
In other local news...
I need one more body to help sector out
Scovell Ridge, B-1 through B-7.
Steep approach, bad underbrush,
a lot of slippery shale.
- Who wants to hump that?
- I'm your man.
[Man Narrating]
- You got experience?
- I spent a few years...
in the Army Rangers.
- I specialized in high mountain work.
- Man, you were made to order.
- You could say that.
- What's your name?
Jarod... Forest.
All right, people, listen up.
Advance parties went up at dawn.
We move out in 30 minutes.
This kid's been missing for five days,
and his mother's very concerned.
He... We are running out of time,
so we leave no stones unturned.
We're looking for a needle, folks,
and we haven't even found the haystack.
- Forest. Derek Kobey.
- Nice to meet you.
So, had anyone seen Victor Simpkins
before he was reported missing?
No one was looking for him.
Of course, for the last few days...
the boss had me doing paperwork while he
got to do all the fun stuff.
- Fun stuff?
- Stan's been on the north side...
of the mountain clearing trails,
setting charges.
Lots of deep ravines,
caves, fallen old growth.
You take a tumble in that, I don't care if
you're Moby Dick, we might not find you.
It sounds like you know
the terrain pretty well.
Eight years. I came out here
on one of those...
"Let's expose the urban youth to
the great outdoors" programs.
- [Man] Hey, Derek.
- Funny thing is, it worked.
- Phone.
- I love the Bronx, but this is home now.
So, Forest, where did you do
your mountain training?
- In the mountains, mostly.
- Yeah.
No, seriously, where were
you stationed? Fort Lewis?
- You were in the army too?
- Fifteen years.
You ever come across a Sergeant Tripcheck,
a Ranger instructor at Benning?
- Sounds familiar.
- He's lying, Stan.
He's really one of the Stooges.
- You two know each other?
- We ran into each other once.
- Is she a ranger?
- No. She's a volunteer.
She runs a little outfitting
place a few miles down the road.
I wouldn't get any ideas.
She keeps mostly to herself.
Stan, just got word
from the advance team.
- They found Simpkins's base camp.
- [Radio Chatter]
We'll split into teams of two
and fan across the mountain.
I want everyone to report in
at 30-minute intervals.
- [Man On Radio] Standing by for an update.
- I need flares over here.
Where's Forest?
Disturbance in the Force?
- Uh, the Force?
- Obi-Wan Kenobi?
Star Wars?
- The satellite missile defense system?
- What are you doing?
I'm just trying to imagine
what kind of person Victor is...
and who would want to spend
months in isolation on purpose.
Somebody who's trying
to find himself?
In the middle of the wilderness?
Sometimes you have to get lost
before you can find yourself.
[Man]
One more man for the team.
Mrs. Simpkins?
Hi, I'm Jarod Forest.
I was wondering if I might
ask you some questions about your son.
Anything to help.
- Is Victor right-handed or left-handed?
- He's right-handed.
I noticed that he had
many books on predatory birds.
He's been out here for months documenting
the nesting patterns of eagles.
He's loved them since
he was a little boy.
He used to sit out in front of
his tent and watch them all day.
He's the only family I have.
Don't worry.
We'll find him.
- We won't leave the mountain until we do.
- This way, Mrs. Simpkins.
- So who am I paired with, Stan?
- Moe.
- You look confused.
- I am confused.
Victor had been out here
for months...
yet there was no sign of
a refuse pile or a latrine?
- Meaning?
- I don't know.
- Just another piece of the puzzle.
- You're a strange Stooge, Moe.
What about that left-hand,
right-hand stuff?
Victor's eyeglasses were on
the left-hand side ofhis sleeping bag.
Seems kind of awkward
for a right-handed man.
This way. Jarod?
Somebody's covered their tracks
by brushing over them.
They head up that way.
Aah! Aah!
- I didn't mean to startle you.
- That's okay. I'll live.
About two weeks less,
but I'll live.
Hi.
I'm Jarod, and this is Nia.
Bob. Sorry, Jarod.
You startled me.
Can't shake the hand
of a man who just startled me.
I have to wait till
the next time I see you.
- Are you hiding from someone, Bob?
- Hiding? I'm looking.
Oh. Oh, you're with
the search party.
Search party? They got
a search party to find Bob?
- I thought you were Bob.
- I am Bob, Big Bob.
Looking for Little Bob.
He's my partner.
Oh, uh...
- We're looking for a student.
- His camp was about three miles west.
- Brown hair, about 5'11".
- Don't know him.
Don't know his camp.
I ain't seen nothing.
Should we alert someone
about Little Bob?
No, you don't want
to get my partner mad.
I've seen him go into a bar
and tear it up from one end to the other.
- How will we know him if we find him?
- You don't want to find him.
He don't like strangers.
Truth be told, he don't like anybody.
[Sniffing]
Bad storm coming.
Bad one.
- [Chuckles]
- [Thunder Rumbling]
And before the Rangers?
Test pilot, thoracic surgeon,
lieutenant commander on a destroyer.
The usual. What did you do
before you became an outfitter?
Astronaut, Olympic skater,
Nobel Prize winner.
The usual.
[Nia]
What's that over there?
It's a carabineer.
I'm going to get it.
No climber would
leave that behind.
Be careful. You don't know these cliffs.
It's dangerous.
Relax. I was a Sherpa
on Mount Everest once.
Really.
Be careful.
These markings are fresh.
Looks like it's only
a few days old.
Jarod!
[Shouts]
Come on.
Ow!
That's Victor's mark.
Orange tape.
The Inuit sign for eagle.
He said anybody
could use their initials.
He's an experienced climber.
He wouldn't leave his equipment
behind unless...
Listen, the sun rises at 6:35.
We deploy here from K-4 to K-8,
just below the cliff.
I want everyone here
at quarter of 6:00.
There's a cold front moving
through in the next 48 hours.
Will my son
be able to survive?
Your son is
an experienced climber.
He may be cold and he may be hungry,
but people have survived worse.
I know he's out there somewhere,
worrying about you too.
Everybody, get some sleep.
We head out at
the crack of dawn.
- Hey, Kobey, where's the nearest motel?
- About 100 miles.
And when you get there,
you'll wish it was another 100.
I've got a spare room.
Grab your gear.
I'll wait for you outside.
Man, that must've been
some search up there today.
Hmm?
Senorita Iceberg invites you
over for a slumber party?
- You are in.
- In where?
Couch is old, and except for
a spring or two in your back...
it's comfortable.
I'm sure it will be fine.
The Casa Rosada.
You're Argentinean.
Is this you
with your parents?
Not too many gringos know about
the Argentinean White House.
I'm impressed.
- Is that everything?
- I travel light.
- On the run?
- Some days.
I do a lot of consulting work.
Take off your shirt.
Why didn't you say
it was so bad?
I guess I didn't realize it.
I'll try to leave some
hot water for you.
Okay?
[Beeping]
You're a girl.
My name is Jarod.
What's your name?
Miss Parker.
Shower's all yours.
Sleep well.
You too.
[Phone Ringing]
- This is Sydney.
- [Jarod] It's me.
I need to talk to you...
about women.
- Why is that?
- Because I met one.
[Nia] No.!
[Shouting In Spanish]
[Spanish]
[Shouting Continues]
It's okay. It's okay.
It's all right.
You're safe.
[Jarod]
It's me.
I need to talk to you...
about women.
[Sydney]
Why is that?
- Because I met one.
- Tell me more.
I've been around hundreds
of women since I left...
but I never experienced with them
what I feel with the one I'vejust met.
- Tell me about your feelings.
- I have a hard time focusing when I'm near her.
And if we happen to touch,
my heart rate...
my blood pressure,
even my breathing becomes erratic.
Frankenboy has a girlfriend.
- [Sydney] It's chemical, Jarod.
- Chemical?
The feelings you're having...
they're driven by your body's response
to an external stimulus.
- In this case, a woman.
- Tonight, when she came out of the shower...
- [Broots] There.
- What are you doing?
That's where the radio
in the background is clearest.
A little presto-chango, and maybe we
can filter it out and figure out the song.
I didn't hear any radio.
I would like to hear
the rest of the tape.
Maybe there's a clue
you might have missed.
[Clears Throat]
[Stan]
Now if Victor Simpkins went down here...
he had to go through an area
between this cliff face and the river.
Anybody find anything,
we're on channel nine.
All right.
Let's move out, quickly.
We found Simpkins's
carabineer here, right?
Yes. Why?
The Force still with you?
Why cross a cliff that dangerous
when you can hike around it?
Maybe he just got the urge.
People don't always plan things.
No, I guess they don't.
Thanks for
being there last night.
What did you mean when you said,
"I don't want to disappear"?
- I said that?
- Twice.
- In Spanish.
- You must've misunderstood me.
Hablo espanol muy bien.
[Clears Throat]
I said, "Here's the tape copy you wanted. '"
OfJarod's conversation.
Are you still here?
Uh, no.
[Young Miss Parker]
You're afraid of me, aren't you?
- No.
- You were yesterday.
- I could tell.
- I was nervous.
- You have soft skin.
- You didn't even touch me.
Yes, I did. In here.
Hold out your hand
like this.
Can you feel it?
What's your name?
Your first name?
[No Audible Dialogue]
[Jarod]
So let me get this straight.
They were called "The Three Stooges, '"
but there were actually four.
With Shemp.
Five if you countJoe Besser.
Though a lot
of people don't.
And six if you include
Curly-Joe DeRita.
But he wasn't even funny in Spanish.
[Laughs]
[Jarod Laughs]
- Was Larry one of the brothers?
- No.
- Moe, Curly and...
- [Twig Snaps]
- What?
- I thought I heard something.
[Shouting]
- Are you okay?
- [Groaning]
Sorry. I can't
shake your hand just yet.
This is the second time
you've seen me.
Except you just walked between two
pine trees. Ain't never gonna happen.
- Did you find your partner?
- No.
I gotta keep checking on my crop,
even without him.
- Checking on your crop?
- Yeah.
- Now I gotta do Little Bob's job too.
- Is he sick?
Nerves. Had the shakes ever since
that plane buzzed him last Friday.
And then the dynamite.
[Laughs]
That just about
put him over the top.
Someone was setting off
dynamite out here?
Yeah, Ranger Conrad was clearing
the trail of some old stumps.
- [Man] Sector 4, come in.
- Forest here.
I found Victor Simpkins's pack
about a quarter of a mile downstream...
from the cliff, lodged in some debris
along the riverbank.
Simpkins's tracks
led right to the water.
I'm guessing he got hurt
in the fall from the cliff...
made it to the water,
passed out or slipped and fell in.
If he didn't drown,
he's somewhere downriver...
- or in the Pacific.
- [Mrs. Simpkins] Oh, my God.!
- Are you calling off the search for my son?
- No, ma'am.
I'm shifting personnel and oversight to
the Anawalt County Sheriff's Department...
who's got direct supervision
of the river from here to the coast.
Now, listen,
I called Sheriff Hansen.
He's a good man. He'll do
whatever he can to help find Victor.
Come with me, Mrs. Simpkins.
He's got enough gear and food
to climb for days.
He was documenting
the nesting patterns of eagles.
There's nothing here
to write on.
It doesn't make sense.
His camp, his carabineer,
this... this backpack.
[Nia]
But what does it mean?
Someone wants the search
for Victor to go downstream.
You're not going,
are you?
No.
He's still on this mountain.
Can anybody hear me?
[Coughing]
[Shower Running]
[Young Sydney]
Jarod, Apollo 1 simulation.
The first warning is a flash as the spark
ignites the pure oxygen in the capsule.
I try to flee, but I can't.
I'm strapped in.
I know the escape procedure,
but the fire, it's too hot.
It comes into my air lines.
I try not to breathe, but it's too late.
I can't open the hatch.
I can't open the hatch!
It's too hot!
I can't think!
No one can get to us!
We can't be saved!
I'm burning! I'm burning!
Jarod! I'm here. It's all right.
No one could save them.
It was impossible.
I tried not to use
all the hot water.
[Closes Briefcase]
Is that boy you?
- I know it's crazy, but I can explain.
- Shh.
We all have scars.
- [Sydney] How much longer, Broots?
- Hard to say.
At first, I thought the song
from Jarod's phone call...
was "I Shot the Sheriff,"
but then I refiltered it...
- and realized it was "Bungle in theJungle."
- Mm-hmm.
How much longer, Broots?
Well, between BMI's and ASCAP's
computer base of playlists...
it could be some time.
But then as soon as we get a hit,
and we find the station...
I've programmed the computer
to call here.
Then... [Clears Throat]
we're in business.
- We're in business.
- Yeah.
How much longer?
Wake up.
I think I've got it.
We've been climbing
for nine hours.
- You want to tell me what we're looking for?
- That.
This was Victor's camp.
The Force is with you.
How did you know?
Something always bothered me
about Simpkins's base camp.
The camp was way too low
on the mountain to observe...
the nesting patterns of eagles, because
they always nest at the highest point.
- What the hell is that?
- The plane that scared Little Bob.
The pilot's dead.
There was a bullet in his head.
- Oh, my God.
- I found traces of narcotics in the back.
- And I found this.
- Deliver your drugs, pick up your money.
You don't file a flight plan with a run
like this, so if your plane crashes...
- No one looks for you.
- Somebody was up here.
There's two sets of footprints, but they
both come from different directions.
Then one chases the other... that way.
He heard the crash,
came down here.
He just wanted to help.
He saw the murder.
He's running.
He's running for his life.
Victor Simpkins.
And who was chasing him?
Who was blowing up stumps
when Bob heard the plane?
- Conrad.
- Conrad is leading the search.
- What were you... How did you...
- Trust in the Force, young Jedi.
I saw your laser disk
last night.
Those prints head down
to Box Canyon.
We'll start that way tomorrow.
I hope Victor Simpkins is under
some kind of cover tonight.
Because if he's not,
he's not going to make it.
Neither are we,
unless we find some shelter.
I know a place.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- What?
- Shut up!
- Let him alone.
- [Moe] You too. Come here.
- [Larry, Shemp Groaning]
- [Larry, Shemp] Mmmm.
- There.
- [Larry, Shemp Groaning]
- Morons.
[Jarod]
I need to talk to you... about women.
[Rewinding]
- About women.
- [Rewinding]
About women.
You know, girls mature
faster than boys.
[Thunderclap]
Nothing like
a home-cooked meal.
So I'm told.
When I was a child...
I was taken...
at least I think I was taken...
by these people who raised me.
They made me do things...
things that hurt other...
- You don't have to tell me anything.
- I know.
I never told anybody before,
but I want to tell you.
I don't know who I am.
You'reJarod,
and you're here with me.
[Chuckles]
- How old were you when you left Argentina?
- Thirteen.
Was it because of
the Guerra Sucia?
I saw the scars on your back.
I was eight.
They came and took us
for no reason at all.
My father
published a newspaper.
My mother met him
when she was a reporter.
But she hadn't worked
for years.
She was too busy raising me.
They woke us up
in the middle of the night.
I could hear my mother screaming,
cursing at them.
I never heard her
swear like that before.
They took us to this place...
this horrible place.
I never saw them again.
They beat me.
They... They...
[Whispering]
I'm sorry.
They wanted me to lie
about my parents...
that they hated the generals,
had plotted against them.
I wouldn't lie.
Finally, they let me go.
They put me with some family...
but no one will talk to me
about my parents.
They had disappeared.
Then the generals left,
and I came here.
I don't know if my parents
are dead or alive.
I don't know either.
I miss them very much.
- [Sobbing]
- I know, I know.
I know, I know, I know.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
Shh. Shh.
I know this is going
to sound crazy.
- I've never...
- Shh.
I just want to know who I am.
I can stand anything for that.
[Rustling]
[Rustling Continues]
[Snorting]
[Pats]
[Snorting Continues]
[Jarod]
Is that pig wearing a baseball cap?
There you are.
Look at him.
All the stress
made him lose weight.
Sooey, sooey, sooey, sooey.!
Come here you, boy.
- [Jarod] Is that your pig?
- Pig? He's no pig.
He's my partner in
a burgeoning mushroom empire.
- Little Bob.
- The one and only.
- And your crop would be truffles?
The finest damn nose
in these United States.
Found a mother lode too.
We could've been rich,
till someone went and blowed up...
the old mine shaft where he
discovered over a ton of them.
- Mine shaft?
- Yeah, the one down in Box Canyon.
Blowed it the same day
that plane flew over.
Come here, big boy.
Come on.
Footprints. Two sets.
[Jarod]
Two go in, but only one comes out.
Conrad chased Victor,
trying to silence him.
Victor ran in here to hide.
Conrad, running short of time, decided
to blow out the entrance, sealing him in.
The Force is with me.
[Chuckles]
Victor! Victor!
- [Nia] Victor.!
- Victor!
- [Gasping]
- Victor.
- [Nia] Victor.
[Coughing]
It's okay.
You're going to be okay.
[Keyboarding]
[Beeping]
[Imitating Three Stooges,
Gibberish]
- [Clang]
- [Horn Honks]
[Instrumental]
[Theme From The Three Stooges]
[Shuts Off]
- [Sydney] Miss Parker?
- What?
We've traced the song to a small radio
station in north-central Oregon.
- [Phone Ringing]
- [Radio Chatter]
Toluca National Forest,
Ranger Conrad speaking.
[Big Bob]
Uh, yeah, this is Bob Carsey.
Ranger Conrad, I think I found
the Simpkins kid.
Where is he? Is he alive?
I couldn't tell.
He was trapped behind a rockfall...
inside the old copper mine
in Box Canyon.
I could barely make a hole
big enough to look in and see.
I'm on my way.
Kobey, I need you here to coordinate
the men and the equipment coming up.
- Do you want me to call his mother?
- No.
Not till we're sure
we have good news.
[Clanking]
Hey, Simpkins.
Simpkins. Hey, Simpkins.
Well, it's about time.
My legs were starting to cramp up.
Kind oflike Lazarus,
huh, Conrad?
So, uh, is Simpkins okay?
You mean is he alive,
so he can testify against you?
- You betcha.
- So, why didn't you just call the police?
You're after
what's in the plane.
- Hey, there's a lot more where that came from.
- No deal.
[Booming]
[Jarod]
Kind of spooky in here, isn't it?
Do you think this is what
hell is like, Stan?
Imagine what it's like
to be trapped in here...
and no one
can hear you screaming.
There's only one way out!
Hey, Conrad,
I'd stand back if I were you.
No!
Jarod!
Don't leave me here,
Jarod! Please!
Oh, don't worry.
I'll lead the search for
you personally... in a few days.
Jarod! Jarod!
I know how to do many things...
but I don't know how to do this.
I know you have to go.
People are looking for me.
If I stay,
you'd be in danger.
You may already be.
I know how to
take care of myself.
I hope you find
what you're looking for.
You've already helped me
find a part of it.
Adiós, mi vida.
[Theme From The Three Stooges]
[Car Doors Opening, Closing]
- Have you seen this man?
- Yes.
He was tall, handsome,
a little mole on his right eye.
- Yes?
- He stayed for a few nights.
- He's gone now.
- Did he say where he was going?
No, but he did mention something
about loving Argentina.
Do you think he'll come back?
I hope so.
[Car Engine Starts]
[Mews]