[Child Humming]
Geese walk barefoot
Kri kra toad's foot
I finished my building.
I'm finished
This one's been with us
for only 36 hours...
and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
Hey! I'm finished!
Hi, Jarod. I'm Sydney.
- I'll be taking care of you for a while.
- Why?
Where's my mom and dad?
[Man Narrating]
Ma'am, the materials on board
are highly explosive.
So am I.
I never agreed with the company...
about flushing our tanks at sea.
I knew those chemicals
had to be doing something nasty.
Yeah, I'm glad
Captain Jarod turned us in.
You know,
I, uh, kinda miss the guy.
Although, uh, he was a little weird.
[Chuckles]
Everything with him was always
"20 Questions." And always the same subject.
- Which was?
- People.
This belong to Curious George
Yeah. Everything is just the way he left it.
Company made sure of that.
Say, are you pullin'my cork
aboutJarod not really being a captain?
Thank you for your help.
What is it?
Articles about that Aluet village...
where everyone was getting sick
from the contaminated fish.
He must have been in quite a hurry,
leaving all this behind.
It's got to be intentional.
A bread crumb.
He's trying to keep me close.
Your little monster
needs his teddy bear, huh, Sydney?
Jarod is not a monster.
[Giggles]
Call him what you want, Dr. Frankenstein.
Just tell me where he is.
I don't know where he is, Miss Parker.
But I'm afraid I know
what he's up to.
[Woman On P.A., Indistinct]
Sir, don't do this.
Lie down.
- [Chattering]
- [Phone Ringing]
- [Man] Excuse me. Excuse me.
- [Woman Speaking Greek]
- My mother's here for her exploratory.
- You're in the wrong place.
- You want Admitting.
- [Continues Speaking Greek]
- Speak English, honey.
- She won't speak English.
She says she doesn't
want to be cut open.
She doesn't trust doctors.
I don't blame her.
[Nurse]
End of the hall.
[Man Shouting]
She swallowed a marble.! B.P. 's 80 over 40.
Pulse is 110. Rapid and thready.
She's cyanotic.
- Get Dr. Shapiro!
- [Woman] He's in O.R. 3.!
Then page Dr. Trader!
Hold on, sweetie.
You'll be fine.
Nicole, get E.N.T., stat!
- All right, fellas. Let's go.
Move it.! One, two, three, go.!
- Dr. Trader to O.R. 3.!
- [Paramedic] Got it?
- [Nurse] Hyperextend her head.
- Where is Trader?
- I paged him. He's not answering.!
- Her pressure's falling.
- Get me a three-c.c. syringe
and a size eight E. T. tube.
Get Security to get this man out ofhere.
What do you think you're doing?
- She's going into respiratory arrest.
- She's not breathing.
- Would you like to do the trach?
- 02 set right down.
- Prepare to ventilate.
- No! Get Security!
- [Nurse] Get a doctor.!
- I am a doctor.
[Officer]
What's the problem?
- Gwen?
- Leave him be.
Give me the syringe.
Remove the plunger.
Give me the top
of the E. T. tube.
Bag.
[Air Expelling]
- What is going on here?
- Air entry on both sides of the chest.
She's pinking up.
- [Girl Inhaling, Wheezing]
- Now, that's a nice sound.
[Jarod] Well, I hope I didn't cause
too much confusion this morning.
Don't apologize.
You saved a life.
Oh, Dr. Hendricks.
I need your signature
on lines 10 and 14, please.
F.Y.I., Russell, if you need anything
done around here, ask Gwen.
I may run this place,
but she is the boss.
[Gwen]
Thank you. Doctors.
Miles.! Sorry. I'm late.
Dr. Jarod Russell,
Dr. Alan Trader, Chief of Surgery.
Nice to meet you.
I hear I missed you in action
this morning, Doctor.
Never seen a trach like that. Is that a new
procedure they're teaching at Hopkins?
- Well, actually, I read it in a book.
- [Laughing]
Well, wherever you learned it...
I appreciate you
standing in for me like that.
I don't know what happened
to my damn beeper, but...
it won't happen again.
Brand-new.
Even takes messages.
Please, sit down.
Well, your record at Hopkins
was impeccable.
We are honored
to have you on board.
Not many doctors with your credentials
come to a hospital as small as ours.
Why Queen of Angels?
Well, I could tell you it was
for the career opportunity...
but the truth is, you were
the only hospital offering stock options...
and rumor has it you might be
purchased by an H.M.O.
- [Chuckling]
- We've been talking to some people.
- [Laughing]
- Don't worry, Russell.
Stick with us, and you'll be
driving a new Lexus in no time.
[Both Laughing]
But on to more important business.
Do you play racquetball?
- I've heard of it.
- Good.
Good. We'll have a game.
Well, welcome to Queen of Angels.
We are thrilled to have you.
It's a pleasure to be here.
[Miss Parker] Imagine my excitement
at being recalled from corporate.
Only you...
could have created a mess
big enough to put me back in the field.
I am thrilled to be
working with you as well.
Hmm.
Not for long.
We've tagged Jarod's
account in Anchorage.
He uses an A.T.M. anywhere,
and he's ours.
Don't underestimate him. If we're to
catch him, we'll need to be patient.
Look, Syd, you may be satisfied
in your laboratory...
probing small minds
to solve big problems.
But I have career goals that don't
include schlepping across country...
chasing after Boy Wonder.
You were such a happy little girl.
What happened to you?
- [Beeping]
- I grew up, Sydney.
- [Buzz]
- So should you.
This is a waste of energy.
I've been through Jarod's room
a thousand times.
I haven't.
- What are you hoping to find?
- He left a bread crumb on the tanker.
And I'll bet he left one here.
Run the sim.
This is Jarod's last project.
When the black box on this flight
wasn't recovered...
he simulated the final moments
of the crash.
Using his innate Pretender skills...
Jarod effectively became
each member of the cockpit crew...
and pinpointed the cause of the crash
for our client.
Hmm.
Hell of an environment
you keep him in, Syd.
And with input like this,
maybe we'll find him...
masquerading as a postal worker.
He doesn't masquerade.
He's a Pretender.
- Hmm.
- He becomes anything he wants to be.
Well, the Centre should have stuck
to computers for their simulations.
- They don't run away.
- But they're not human.
They can't tell you how the crew
was feeling as the aircraft lost power...
how their emotions
contributed to their fate.
Jarod can.
Very, very clever.
- Do you know what this is?
- An origami angel.
But I haven't figured out
the emotional connection to him yet.
It's not an angel.
Its wings are bent. It's Onisius.
The Greek god of retribution.
He defends the weak and abused.
I'm impressed. How come you know
so much about Greek lore?
Oh, I did a lot of frat boys in college.
Here's your bread crumb, Sydney.
Your sociopath thinks
he is some kind of vigilante...
getting even for the little guy.
St. Andrew's Middle School, Queens.
[Ice Cream Truck]
- It tastes better before it melts.
- Oh. Right.
This is good!
This is really very good!
Do they whip air into it
to fluff it up?
I don't make it, pal.
I just serve it.
- [School Bell Rings]
- [Children Chattering]
[Boy] Come on.!
Shoot it.! Shoot it.!
- [Yells]
- [Shouting, Chattering]
[Car Alarm Blaring]
Now, this is fascinating.
They win money by guessing word puzzles?
You've never seen
Wheel of Fortune?
What rock you been living under?
Uh, I've been busy.
"The courtship of Miles Standish. '"
[Loud Whistle]
Hey!
Uh, we got us
a little situation here.
Uh, the A.T.M. says that your bank account
in Alaska has been frozen.
- No pun.
- [Chuckling]
Now, maybe you're happy,
but I'm out a Benjy for my efforts.
Did you do what I asked?
My friend,
it was an Oscar-winning performance.
Thank you.
You're giving me a C-note
for finding out you're broke?
We had an agreement.
Hey, whatever sends you.
Say, you know where to find me
if you need me, huh?
[Knock On Door]
Just a second.
Come in.
Good morning, Dr. Russell.
Sorry to bother you,
but could you go talk to the Greek lady?
She yells at everyone that goes to her room.
No one understands what she's saying.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
Nicole, do me a favor.
Have the lab run a complete
diagnostic testing on this.
And put a rush on it?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
[Door Closes]
[Speaking Greek]
You a doctor?
I am today.
You speak English.
When I feel like it.
And I don't need no operation.
- Hey!
- This hurts, doesn't it?
Hell yes!
I haven't gone for weeks.
Well, you need to relax.
How can I relax
with all these tests?
And now they want to cut me open.
Okay. If you don't want surgery,
I'll cancel it.
- No surgery?
- No.
I'm gonna try something else.
You're no doctor.
You are human being.
Mm-hmm.
Sandy, make my day.
Well, we have an A.T.M. hit
on Jarod's Anchorage account.
Some genius.
Satellite feed should be up in...
two seconds.
He's in Santa Fe, New Mexico.
Call the hangar
and get the jet ready.
- Hold it. He's not in Santa Fe.
He's in Rome. No, Luxembourg.
- Chicago, New York.
The little S.O.B.
scrambled the A.T.M. system.
Miami, Philadelphia, Barcelona.
Hello, Jarod.
- [Gwen] You canceled Mrs. Nikkos's surgery?
- [Jarod] Yes, I did.
Fine. You're the doctor. As long
as I don't get blamed for anything.
And I would like to try her on an herb tea
called Cassia Senna.
Doctor, this is Queens.
We don't do tea.
We do now. And I'd like
the key to Radiology, please.
Well, Andy's out to lunch, but...
- I know.
- There you are.
Thank you.
- Hi!
- Hi, Mama!
How you doin', little sugar baby?
Ooh.! There he is.! There he is.!
Bring Mommy lunch today?
Guess what it is.
[Gwen]
I'm hoping for tuna fish or peanut butter.
I could use a hand with these.
That is, if you have one free.
- Oh, God. It's Dr. Russell.
- [Andy] Dr. Russell?
I'm new.
I'm, uh, embarrassed.
But, um, always, uh...
always happy to help, Doc.
[Clears Throat]
Uh, now...
Uh, I don't understand.
Kevin Bailey is Dr. Trader's patient.
Any special reason
you're looking at these?
that you're in here half naked?
I can be forgetful if you can.
All right.
Your problem is right here...
at the T-eighth.
The eighth thoracic vertebrae was crushed,
severing his spinal cord.
- Kid never had a chance.
- That I understand. But look here.
This is the pre-op,
and this is the post-op X-ray.
- Yeah.
- But both of them are identical.
- How is that possible?
- It's not.
Someone must have made
a duplicate of the post-op X-ray.
You see that fogging
in the corner there?
The old processor
we keep in the basement does that.
I spilled some soda on it
when I first started working here.
The new processor's fog-free.
Why would someone make a copy of
a post-op X-ray and label it pre-op?
Makes you wonder.
[Young Jarod]
I'm on the last flight of stairs...
terrified of what I'm about to do.
My heart's pounding.
My hands are sweating.
I can hardly hold on to the package
I told everyone was curtain rods.
Sydney, is it possible for kids
to forget their parents?
[Sydney]
Keep your mind focused, Jarod.
Concentrate on the simulation.
As I near the window...
I can hear the sounds
of the crowd rising from below.
[Young Jarod]
I can see them coming.
- How fast are they going?
- Forty miles per hour. You know that.
My mouth's dry.
My hands are shaking.
I raise the Mannlicher carbine.
I can't fire enough shots
before the car goes under the overpass.
I can't.
I can't do this alone.
He wasn't alone.
[Jarod]
He had to have had help.
Trader wasn't alone either, Sydney.
[Exhales]
[Grunts, Laughs]
[Gasps]
Good one.
[Exhales]
Good game.
[Panting]
Don't let it bother you.
He never lets anyone win.
- [Jarod Laughs]
- At leastJarod's competitive.
- He's young.
- And you're lazy.
- Yeah, well, there is that.
- [Both Laughing]
Calsix.
You have a heart problem?
Miles is a type-A time bomb.
Two heart attacks.
One more, and it's bypass time.
Which is why I play racquetball.
And I need a refill.
So do I. Um...
It's my day off.
You exercise your way,
I'll exercise mine. [Chuckles]
- So, Jarod, does Queen of Angels
get a passing grade?
- Absolutely.
Frankly, I expected there to be
more fallout from the malpractice problems.
Well, unfortunately,
that's the cost of doing business.
We've had our difficulties, but I would put Queen
of Angels' record up against any hospital.
Are you sure there's no hidden land mines,
even with the Kevin Bailey case?
Well, that was a tragedy,
but let's face it...
an orphaned boy in a wheelchair
make for sensational headlines.
It was a damned witch hunt.
Yes. Once the frenzy died down,
the truth took over, and we were exonerated.
That is all behind us now.
[School Bell Rings]
[Shouting, Chattering]
- Get serious.
- It's good.
Hasn't anyone ever told you? You talk
to strangers, you end up on milk cartons.
My name's Jarod.
It tastes better before it melts.
Your hands still cramp up
when you wheel?
What would you know about it?
I have a good imagination.
[Kids Screaming,
Shouting, Chattering]
[Sighs]
It's gonna get better.
[Car Horn Honks]
I promise.
[Woman] Sir, there's a Shreve Harmon
calling on line seven.
Shreve and Harmon built
the Empire State Building.
Put him through
and trace the call.
[Buzz]
[Chuckling]
Very clever, Jarod.
Are you all right?
I'm broke.
You froze my bank account.
I must have just missed you
in Cincinnati.
The flowers were still fresh.
Well, my parents have been dead for 30 years.
I figured it was time I said good-bye.
- I want you to come home.
- [Chuckles]
There's an interesting way
to put it..."home."
- Why did you leave?
- You're the shrink, Sydney.
You want the truth?
It's because of the lies.
Your lies.
What lies?
I found out the real application
of my simulations, Sydney.
South Pacific
fleet simulation 118.
You took my results
and blew a ship out of the water.
A hundred and 33 people
were on board.
My outbreak simulation?
You used it in the field.
Forty-six people died
of the Ebola virus, Sydney.
Simulation 27.
Simulation 16. Simulation 42.
Jarod, these were
military contracts.
I had no way of finding out
about their ultimate application.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
You need to come home.
I'm worried about you.
I've been walking around your room,
and it feels... empty.
Well, I can't say I miss it.
And by the way...
ice cream is good.
Jarod, this is getting serious.
- They brought in Miss Parker.
- Uh-oh.
Well, you better
watch your back too, Sydney.
- What are you doing, Jarod?
- Using the skills you taught me.
[Man] I'm completely locked out here.
I got nothin'.
- Are you getting anything?
- No. Let me try a new access code.
- Talk to me.
- We've been locked out.
Our client hired us to see if the stock exchange
was vulnerable to manipulation.
- Jarod spent four months on this simulation.
- What's the problem?
The client gave us five million
to testJarod's results.
Jarod knew today
was the day of the test.
Everything was going to plan until someone
on the floor started to manipulate markets.
- They've stolen our five million.
- Gee.
I wonder who that could be.
Well, at least we know where he is.
[Laughing]
That's some kind medicine
you got there.
I might laugh myself dead
before I poop!
[Chuckling]
Laughter is very good medicine.
And so is reflexology.
Nicole, massage these marks,
would you, please?
Thanks.
You gonna tell me the truth?
What truth?
A man who gives me the sun...
who massages my feet...
who gives me stinky tea...
Who are you?
Oh, so much sadness.
And so much joy.
[Miss Parker] Comforting to know
there are only 137 hospitals...
in the metropolitan New York area.
Your rooms have been prepaid,
Miss Parker.
- Prepaid?
- In cash.
And the gentleman left this.
Not a word.
- Alan. Hey.
- Jarod, hi. Hi.
Denise, I'll have
another ginger ale, please.
- Make that two ginger ales.
- Okay.
Either you've
just been mugged...
or it's been one hell of a shift.
Four gunshot wounds,
a lobectomy and a ruptured spleen...
and I'm only halfway through.
Alan, I think I might have
screwed up today.
Really screwed up.
Hey, how you doin'?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Hey, look, is this Trader's exchange?
Good. Look, I gotta
get a message to him. Yeah.
So...
what's the trouble?
The lobectomy? I think I left
a hemo inside when I sewed her up.
- No problem.
- No problem?
- You think that's gonna make the H.M.O. happy?
- Check her chart.
If the white count is spiked,
you've found your hemo.
Well, then what?
Take it out.
Tell her you found
some internal bleeding.
- Hey, you're the doctor.
- Oh.
- [Pager Beeping]
- Ah.
Always count on it happening
on your lunch break, huh?
Um, I gotta get back.
- Well, thank you for the advice, Alan.
- Yeah.
[Typing On Keyboard]
[Knock On Door]
- [Beeps]
- Come in.
Oh, good.
You're still here.
The lab report
on that blood workup you asked for.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
[Door Closes]
This one's been with us
for only 36 hours...
and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
Hey! I'm finished!
Hi, Jarod. I'm Sydney.
- I'll be taking care of you for a while.
- Why?
Where's my mom and dad?
- Where's my mom and da...
- [Clicks Off]
[Horn Blasting]
[Man]
Please evacuate the building.
- [Alarm Blaring]
- Keep moving. Please remain calm.
Thank you.
- Sydney. Downstairs.
- Please make your way to the emergency exits.
- This way.
- [Woman] Wait up for me.
- [Alarm Continues Blaring]
- Just one minute, sir.
[Female Voice] Please exit your room
and proceed to the nearest stairway exit.
My God.
Sorry to wake you, Sydney...
but I needed
to speak to you face-to-face.
You look well.
What's this?
Instructions for retrieving
the Centre's five million.
- Less my commission.
- [Chuckles]
Don't look so surprised.
I don't want money. I want the truth.
What are you talking about?
Who am I?
Did the Centre adopt me?
Was I bought, or was I stolen?
And where are my mom and dad?
Jarod, we've been over this
a thousand times.
Your parents died
in a plane crash.
Yes, I know the story, Sydney.
It's been burned into my brain for 30 years.
But, you see,
I did a little checking.
There's this genetic anomaly
that's in my blood...
that should be in my supposed parents.
But it's not.
Therefore, it's impossible
that I'm their son.
So, the truth, for once.
- [Man] I thought you quit.
- [Miss Parker] Shut up.
Where were you going, Sydney?
- Damn it!
- What?
No smoke!
Out of my way!
I'm sorry, Jarod.
I didn't know.
You have to believe me.
But it doesn't matter.
It matters to me.
I am not gonna be your little
science experiment anymore, Sydney.
I can be anything I want to be.
You trained me well.
I can be a doctor. I can be an engineer.
I can be an astronaut!
And so much more!
But I don't know who I am!
- Tell me who I am.
- I don't know either.
At the time, I had no reason
to question what the Centre told me.
- I swear.
- Then prove it.
Give me tomorrow's code
to the Centre's mainframe.
The truth about who I am
has to be in there.
- You know I can't do that.
- Sydney, you stole my life!
Please give it back to me.
Sydney.! Shoot him.!
7-5-1-2. Go.
- [Gunshot]
- [Sydney] No.! No guns.!
- Let me go!
- [Elevator Bell Dings]
[Grunting]
Make up your mind, Sydney!
Be a scientist or a mommy!
You can't be both!
- [Man On P.A.] Your attention, please.
- [Train Horns Blowing]
Final call for all passengers
departing on the Atlantic Special...
to Washington, D. C...
with stops in Trenton,
Philadelphia and Baltimore.
Now boarding on Platform 12.
All aboard, please.
Excuse me.
Gwen.
Gwen!
- Dr. Russell.
- Can I speak to you for a minute?
Is there a problem?
You're not supposed to have that.
I knew that Trader was involved.
What I couldn't figure out was
why would anybody help him cover it up?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I didn't either, until I found this.
It's a printout of your record.
Who else knew you were in prison
besides Trader?
Who the hell are you?
Someone that doesn't think
what happened to Kevin Bailey's fair.
A-And you think I do?
You don't know what it took
for me to get back on my feet.
I've got a job.
I've got a good man.
I've got a beautiful baby boy.
I don't want to lose them.
I don't want you
to lose anything.
Just tell the truth.
What would you do
if your wife came home and told you...
that she'd been a crackhead
and a convict?
I'd say she paid her debt.
And I'd ask her why she didn't
trust me enough to tell me the truth.
At least that's what
I think I would do.
You don't know how scared I am.
I think I do.
I had to page Dr. Trader
that night at the Silver Rail.
We all knew he drank...
but nobody wanted to admit it.
I showed him the X-rays.
Even I knew that the boy
should have been stabilized...
but he insisted I was wrong and...
He was the doctor.
He severed the little boy's spinal cord
when he moved him.
But it was Dr. Hendricks
who covered it all up...
and threatened to expose my past
if I didn't go along.
See, uh...
when Trader realized
what he'd done...
he gave me the pre-op X-rays
and told me to burn them.
But I couldn't.
I went to Dr. Hendricks instead.
I don't know why I thought
it would do any good.
He's been covering for Trader for years.
He took the X-rays...
and he made me swear that I wouldn't
tell anybody that he had 'em.
He said that he might be able
to use them for insurance.
[Sighs]
Thank you.
Dr. Hendricks
isn't gonna give you that film.
He'd rather die
than risk that hospital sale.
- Dr. Trader.
- Alan? It's Jarod.
- We need to talk.
- About what?
Uh, not on the phone.
Can you meet me today
at the Silver Rail at noon?
- I'll be there.
- Thanks, Alan.
[Punching Keypad]
Miles.
Jarod Russell.
Jarod.
What can I do for you?
How about another game
of racquetball?
Why would you want another game
so soon after I crushed you?
[Chuckles] To return the favor.
How about today at noon?
Well, it's your funeral.
Well, we all have to go sometime.
- [Groans]
- Point, game, match.
Toss me my water, will ya?
Sure, Miles.
[Hendricks Grunting]
Geez.
[Sighs]
So, Jarod, why the self-torture?
Well, I figure I let you
win a few games...
I earn your pity,
you cut me a better stock option.
Well, my pity doesn't come cheap.
I'll tell you something... you ran me
all over that court. You are getting better.
- I've been practicing.
- Ah.
But I won.
[Gasping, Panting]
You okay, Miles?
Jarod...
[Gasping]
Miles?
Can somebody
call an ambulance?
Dr. Russell says
he's running a bit late.
Show me a doctor
who isn't, huh?
I'll have another quick one.
Sure.
Get O.R. 3 set.
Dr. Hendricks is having a heart attack.
[Woman]
Watch your back.!
Pulse is 112 and thready.
B.P. has dropped from 75 to 60.
I want you to start him on a nitro drip
and get him prepped for surgery, stat!
You lied to me.
Last night, you told meJarod came here
to return the five million.
- All he really wanted was the mainframe code.
- It was the least I could do.
He was lied to about his parents.
So was I.
Stop pouting.
It was need-to-know.
You didn't.
Anyway, you've done us all a great favor.
You see, I tagged Jarod's file.
- He logged on this morning.
- Where is he?
Queen of Angels Hospital.
They're bringing the car around now. Let's go.
The Centre wants him alive.
Preferably.
[Monitor Beeping]
Miles, we were unable
to bring in a cardiologist fast enough.
But don't worry.
I paged Dr. Trader.
No...
He'll take care of you, Miles.
- He took care of Kevin Bailey.
- No.
[Gasping]
Please.
You do the operating.
Okay, okay...
O-Okay, Miles. No problem.
But first...
you tell me where
Kevin Bailey's pre-op X-rays are.
[Continues Gasping]
Behind the Punjab painting in my office.
Now, you do the operation, Jarod.
l-l-I'd like to, Miles.
I really would.
But that wouldn't be ethical.
You see...
I'm not really a doctor.
And you're not really
having a heart attack.
Trader, he's all yours.
Okay.
Let's do this.
[Wheezing]
Jarod. Jarod...
[Miss Parker]
We'll start on the first floor and work our way up.
Jarod does not leave.
Nicole?
Would you page Security and have them
stop Dr. Trader from operating?
- He's drunk.
- Oh, my God!
Yeah.
You take that side.
Jarod!
Guess what.
Guess what I did today.!
Oh!
Well, that's great!
Sorry.
He's got to be
in one of these rooms.
[Mrs. Nikkos Screams]
Let's go!
Hey.! A man.!
He ran out the fire escape.!
He's heading to the roof!
- [Speaks Greek]
- [Mrs. Nikkos Laughs]
[Speaks Greek]
Jarod!
[Woman On P.A.]
Your attention, please.
Flight 1428 to San Diego
will be departing from Gate 12.
Please have your
boarding passes ready.
You'd better board, sir.
You don't wanna miss the flight.
Don't worry.
They're not going anywhere
without me.
[Mews]