[Clock Ticking]
Hi, Jarod.
Mom?
What are you saying?
I can't hear you.
[Ringing]
Mom?
- [Ticking, Ringing]
- Mom?
[Shrill Ringing]
[Broots] He's been calling every two minutes
like clockwork but only wants to talk to you.
Here's your extension, okay?
I'll be right over here.
- What line?
- Well, don't you think
we should wait for Miss Parker?
- We'll do it without her.
- Sydney, she's gonna kill me.
- What line?
- Okay, two.
But keep him on as long as you can.
I've already initiated a trace.
[Beeping]
[Sydney]
Hello, Jarod?
- I had the dream again.
- Are you all right?
Keep talking to him.
We almost got him.
- [Loud Whistling Over Phone]
- Tell Broots I discovered Radio Shack.
Strange.
Feeling homesick.
Only I don't know
where home is.
Your home's here, Jarod.
You were never meant
for the outside world.
Spare me the white-leopard
speech, Sydney.
Somebody at the Centre
knows who I am.
- I want the truth.
- I'm sure we can explore...
these questions if you come back
and resume our work.
I wish I could believe you.
What you believe or don't believe
is not the issue.
- What is?
- Those digital simulations you stole.
They contain the only
existing record...
of over 25 years of research.
The Centre...
I want them back.
Well, then perhaps they...
you... would consider a trade.
A piece of my past
for a piece of yours.
[Ringing]
Get back to me, Sydney.
I'm running late.
- Late for what?
- Justice.
[Buzzing]
Mr. Holmes?
Isaac.
Mr. Dexter?
- Is something wrong?
- You're a man.
- Last time I checked.
- But you dress like a woman.
- Didn't anybody tell you?
- No.
Listen. I know you don't know me,
and I'll admit I'm a little different.
But if you don't help me, they're gonna put me
away faster than you can say Chanel No. 5.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Those men were trying to kill me.
I just defended myself.
You walk out on me,
I'm a dead man.
- Don't worry, Mr. Dexter.
- [Patting Shoulder]
I'll stand up with you.
Thank you.
I knew you were a good man.
- I could see it in your eyes.
- Here.
Your mascara's running.
Oh.
- So how long you been a lawyer?
- About seven minutes.
Oh.
[Man Narrating]
[Indistinct]
Jarod, please, join us.
We wanted to be the first to congratulate you
on your victory in court this morning.
- It was beginner's luck.
- We heard your client was quite a looker.
Just how lucky did you get?
Don't let Bradley
get under your skin.
All junior associates get thrown
a ringer their first time out.
There's honor in keeping
poor, innocent men out of jail.
- Even if they do wear chiffon.
- Excuse me.
- Mr. Dumont, Michael Metzger's
waiting in reception.
- Thanks, Annie.
Thankfully, a client
who's neither poor nor innocent.
Speaking of poor, innocent men...
have you finished your brief
on the Whittaker appeal?
Ben, I'm spending 70 hours
a week on the Metzger merger.
My plate is full.
Dumont is a pit bull in the court,
but sometimes forgets...
who signs his paychecks.
[Chuckles]
All right, I'll take care of it.
Oh, Jarod, in case
you're interested...
Collins department store is having
a two-for-one sale on the lingerie section.
- See ya, tiger.
- Jarod, keep up the good work.
- I'll do my best, sir.
- Annie...
there's something
I want you to do.
- Brad, may I speak to you for a moment?
- It was a joke.
I understand that.
I wanted to ask you some questions...
about the Whittaker trial.
Old Man Sloane lost a murder defense
a few years ago...
and I got stuck holding the bag.
Why would Sloane tie up
his best trial attorney...
writing an appeal that could be handled
by a first-year law student?
The Whittaker case is
a raw nerve with Sloane.
- He hates to lose.
- Let me write the appeal.
You said your plate is full.
And I could use the practice.
The old man will have my head if he finds out
I dumped this on a junior associate.
I can keep a secret
if you can.
Let's talk.
You find Dumont for me now,
or I'm gonna find him myself.
Base it on my previous appeals
and keep me in the loop.
- You're the boss.
- Not yet, but I'm working on it.
Mr. Metzger. I just got
off the phone with the judge.
I think everything's gonna work out
just the way you want it.
- Good.
- Have you lost weight?
[Sydney]
Madam Director...
allJarod wants is some
small piece of himself, of his past.
I believe if we can
accept his trade offer...
it would go a long way
towards reestablishing...
the kind of trust I need
to bring him back.
What about S.I.S.?
Well, Miss Parker believes she can pistol-whip
her way into any resolution.
But I know Jarod.
The harder we chase...
the harder he'll run.
I'll discuss your proposal
with the Tower.
But I make no promises.
Oh, damn.
The idea is to get all the same colors
on the same side?
[Scoffs]
Where were you during the '80s?
I led a very isolated life.
When did you quit smoking?
How did you know that?
Oh, your trembling hands...
nicotine stains on your fingertips,
irritability.
You know, you can try
a simple Epsom salt bath.
The salt, it draws the tar and nicotine
out of the bloodstream through the skin.
So, you're a doctor and a lawyer?
- And I'm working on Indian chief.
- Annie.
Would you please transcribe, proof and
hand-deliver these to my boat tonight?
Tonight? Oh, no, no, no.
Mr. Sloane, I can't, because my daughter...
Is a very lovely girl who knows
how valuable her mother is to this firm.
Annie's the best, Jarod.
Annie do this.
Annie do that.
I'll tell you... it's like being Sloane's wife
without the fringe benefits.
Too bad paychecks are harder
to quit than cigarettes.
So, did you need something too?
Actually, Bradley Dumont
asked me to go over an old case file.
Marcus Whittaker?
Oh, yeah. Mr. Sloane had those files
moved down to the basement.
But I'm gonna warn you. It is impossible
to find anything down there.
Nothing's impossible.
Jarod.
Isaac, what are you doing here?
I got to thinking how nice you were,
how decent.
- And I wanted to repay your kindness.
- Repay?
- My chariot.
- Isaac.!
- It's beautiful.
- [Chuckles]
It'll be more beautiful
after 37 payments.
That's when I plan to trade it in
for a limousine.
Actually, I offer
a very valuable service.
You'd be surprised how many cabdrivers
won't pick up a man in a dress.
Really? Why?
The truth is,
I'd like to offer my services...
as your personal chauffeur.
No kidding!
Well, that's great.
- Now, you sure you have a driver's license?
- Don't worry, boss.
You're in good hands.
And I promise to be
the perfect lady.
- [Horn Honking]
- [Man Laughing] Hey, baby.!
- Up yours, pal!
- [Tires Screeching]
[Computer Rings]
Very good.
Sydney, a word?
- Do you wanna tell me what's going on?
- Nothing, really.
An alpha brain wave experiment.
- Quite promising, actually.
- That's not what I mean, and you know it.
You spoke to the director?
Answer the question!
- Jarod wants to make a deal.
- A deal.
He wants to find out the truth
or part of it.
It is the humane thing to do.
You are out of line lecturing anybody
about humanity.
I'm not the one who kept
Jarod locked up for 30 years.
I'm killing your deal, Sydney.
And then I'm gonna find Jarod.
And I'm gonna end this thing
once and for all.
Everybody's a critic.
[Blues]
Doesn't this music just give you chills
up and down your spine?
It's very... sad.
It's the blues, baby.
The blues.
- I like it.
- It's about life...
about pain...
it's about truth.
- Truth is good.
- Yeah. Look at me, for example.
I come out here every day
like a target.
And I say to the world,
"Ha!
This is me.
Take it or leave it."
- Can I ask you a question?
- Why do I dress like this?
Well, it does seem
to draw attention.
I don't know why I do it.
I just know it's right for me.
I mean, I grew up like
everybody else.
I played football,
dated a cheerleader.
But I never felt complete
until I found this.
It hasn't been easy, though.
- Why do it then?
- It's who I am.
People can't go around acting like
they're something they aren't.
You do that long enough, and pretty soon
you can't find yourself anymore.
Know what I mean?
Yeah.
So, who we lookin' for?
[Buzzer Sounding]
[Jarod]
His name is Marcus Whittaker.
- Friend of yours?
- Not exactly.
[Isaac]
What'd he do?
[Jarod]
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
The Tower has considered all the variables and
has decided to move forward with the deal.
- You can't be serious.
- I think you know that I am.
The chairman is going
to hear about this.
Your father cast
the deciding vote.
The information Jarod requested
will be on your desk within the hour.
- Use it wisely.
- [Elevator Bell Dings]
- [Sydney] You'll only have one
shot at the terrorist, Jarod.
- I had the dream again.
It's just a dream, Jarod.
Forget about it and concentrate.
Is it possible...
to forget who you are
and where you came from?
Jarod, please.
It's just that in this dream,
I can't see my mother's face.
She's in the yard hanging wash.
One shot, Jarod.
Time's running out.
The hostages are counting on you.
But I wanna see her, Sydney.
I wanna see my mother's face!
Finish the simulation
and I'll see to it that you do.
- Promise?
- Promise.
Wait. I can't
complete the mission.
I might hit a hostage.
- I might kill an innocent person.
- Sometimes, Jarod...
one life must be sacrificed
in order to save others.
- [Machine Beeps]
- [Video Stops]
[Woman Reporter]
Murder suspect Marcus Whittaker...
accused of beating Audrey Price
to death in her apartment...
was arrested in the early morning hours
in his janitor quarters...
of this West L.A.
apartment building.
Marcus Whittaker has
an unusual benefactor in this case...
his employer, real estate magnate
Michael Metzger...
whose company owns the building
in which the murder took place.
How long we gonna stay here?
Hello?
Audrey Price's death
is a tragedy.
But Marcus Whittaker shouldn't
be forced to take the rap...
for the sloppy handling
of this investigation.
I'm just grateful that Ben Sloane
has agreed to represent Marcus.
Mr. Metzger was with me on my boat
when word reached him...
that a murder had taken place
on one of his properties.
Naturally, I offered my services.
Isaac, let's go shopping.
Whoo! Now you're talking
my language.
[Man]
It's creepy.
He's been doing that
for almost an hour.
Check out his girlfriend.
- Are these all the boat shoes you have?
- Yes, sir.
I'll take them all.
You want seven pairs
of boat shoes?
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you carry these in a 13?
[Knocking]
Well?
I did it. Just like you said.
And?
I dragged it around
behind my bike.
- Excellent.
- [Scoffs]
Oh, yes, right.
Five dollars.
That's right.
I have friends. We could really mess up
your car if you're interested.
I'll let you know.
Cool.
Mr. Whittaker is the only
possible perpetrator.
The defense has no relevant evidence
to the contrary.
You're wrong, Mr. Edwards.
[Edwards]
Thank you. Enjoy the book.
My God. What did you do,
drag this behind a car?
Well, actually, I paid a kid
to drag it behind his bike.
- Truthfully, it's been like a bible to me.
- Well, I'm flattered.
- Whom should I make this out to?
- John Corey, Jr.
I knew a John Corey
at Dartmouth. You're not...
Guilty. Dad's been after me
to look you up for years.
So there's your father wearing nothing but
a drunken grin running up the dorm hallway...
shouting, "Banzai!"
- Dear old Dad.
- Yeah.
I never saw a better litigator
in my life.
He said the same thing
about you.
I especially admired the way you brought
down Ben Sloane a few years ago.
- The Whittaker trial?
- Oh. Sloane had no case.
Really? What about
the shoe print?
- How'd you know about that?
- I did a paper...
the People vs. Whittaker, at UCLA.
I read the case files.
- 5,000 pages?
- 5,612 to be exact.
Michael Metzger buys Whittaker
the most expensive lawyer in the city...
and the guy drops the ball.
- We couldn't believe he missed it.
- The D.A. knew about the print?
We provided it in discovery.
We kept waiting for Sloane
to play the card, to create doubt.
But it never came.
And you never said anything?
[Sighs]
We had witnesses...
who said that Marcus Whittaker
was obsessed with Audrey Price.
His prints were
all over the apartment.
He was caught in his janitor's quarters
cleaning her blood offhis clothes.
Now, you don't have to read Proust
to connect those dots.
Yet you never found
a murder weapon.
Marcus Whittaker
was guilty of murder.
Ben Sloane was just guilty
ofbeing a bad lawyer.
[Man]
Mr. Sloane came to the police station.
He was nice to me.
He brought me a ham sandwich.
What are you making?
Paper clocks.
A pen pal taught me.
They really work.
They'd be better with note cards.
The-The paper the guards give me
gets all soft.
- Would these do?
- Can I have those?
Sure.
Marcus, I wanna ask you
some questions about your case.
Mr. Sloane is my lawyer.
I know, but I'm here
to help him, and you.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Can you tell me...
why you ran away the night
that Audrey Price was killed?
I didn't wanna go to jail again.
You had gotten into some trouble when you
lived with your mother, is that correct?
Some boys were making fun of her.
I had to fight 'em.
I didn't wanna hurt anyone.
I had to go live at Milltown.
The detention facility.
Now I wanna ask you
about the night of the murder.
[Exhales]
I was bringing flowers
to Miss Price...
like I did every day.
I was finishing up late.
She would always pay me
an extra two dollars for them.
[Clears Throat]
But this time, when I walked in...
I saw her body on the floor.
Marcus? Marcus?
It's okay.
You don't have to be afraid.
She was all twisted up.
Her face was covered with blood.
The... The owl
was sitting beside her.
The owl?
Made of rock.
It was green.
Miss Price had
a whole family of them.
She kept them on top
of her coffee table.
She looked so quiet.
Like she was sleeping,
except for the blood.
- You liked her.
- She was nice to me.
The other lawyer said
I wanted to touch her...
but I just thought she was nice.
Did you ever notice her
having visitors?
Boyfriends?
Mr. Metzger would come visit her
at lunchtime almost every day.
- Mr. Metzger?
- Yeah.
He had a cool black car.
- It had real shiny wheels on it
and the top was gone.
- Marcus.
Did you ever tell Mr. Sloane or the police
about Mr. Metzger's visits?
Oh, Mr. Sloane said
that I shouldn't say nothing.
It might not look good.
Mr. Sloane always
looks out for me.
They really work.
- [Line Ringing]
- It's 9:20, and Michael Metzger
has just killed a woman.
- Who does he call?
- You've reached Benjamin Sloane at the marina.
I wish I was on my boat right now, but I'm
probably in my office working to pay for it.
Leave your name and number
and I'll get back to you.
[Machine Beeps]
I don't understand. Why would
a defense lawyer like Mr. Sloane...
put a poor, innocent man in jail?
To keep a rich, guilty one out.
[Clock Ticking]
Hi, Jarod.
[Ringing]
Mom?
- [Ringing Continues]
- Mom?
Time's up, Sydney.
I need an answer.
[Sydney]
Miss Parker's not happy.
In fact, she's removed herself
from this case...
because the Centre has agreed
to your request, Jarod.
Your information in return
for the stolen disks.
They said that?
We... you and l...
have guarantees from the council chairman
and the director.
I'm sending it through now.
Hope this is what
you need, Jarod.
[Computer Rings]
Is this her, Sydney?
Is this my mother?
Yes, it is.
I'll-I'll meet you at the place
and time we agreed on earlier.
Mr. Sloane, is it true that your client
will not be testifying in his own defense?
Mr. Whittaker suffers
from a severe learning disability.
It was his feeling and mine that it was not
in his best interest to take the stand.
[Reporter] Well, what is your assessment
of the prosecution's case so far?
I think this deliberation doesn't
bode well for the prosecution...
especially in light of the fact that they still
haven't produced the murder weapon.
The murder weapon. The murder weapon.
Produced the murder weapon.
Yeah. I wonder why.
[Knocking]
Bradley, will you check my brief
for the Whittaker hearing?
I worked from your old appeal,
and I made a few notes.
- You what?
- I went over the old case file.
- There's some areas we should explore.
- No, there aren't!
Copy my draft! Change the date.
Stamp my signature on it.
Get it to the court by 5:00.
If you can't handle that,
I'll hire a monkey who can.
- Sure thing, Brad.
- [Whirring]
[Engine Not Turning Over]
Shoot. Damn it!
[Car Door Closes]
Don't fight it, brother.
At times like this,
a man's gotta believe in fate.
Bad luck...
meet good fortune.
My chariot.
[Whittaker] I got a letter from my mom.
She's really sick. She shouldn't be alone.
Don't worry, Marcus.
You're going to see your mother again soon.
I promise. But first,
we have to go to court...
one more time.
- Mr. Sloane will be there too.
- What do I have to do?
Trust me.
- [Isaac] So, how was your lunch meeting?
- [Dumont Chuckles]
Extremely profitable.
Arriving in this limo
didn't hurt negotiations either.
Excuse me. Um, sir, this isn't the way
back to the office.
It's such a fabulous day,
I thought we'd take a little ride.
- [Chuckling]
- A ride?
To... To where?
- [Laughing]
- Hey.!
[Doors Locking]
What the...
In the matter of
Beaumont vs. Markswatch...
Jarod.
I wanted to congratulate you
on the Whittaker appeal.
- Dumont says that the new trial is a slam dunk.
- New trial?
The court has accepted Dumont's motion
to present new evidence.
Evidence?
Yes, he's confident that he's gonna have
a warrant for the murder weapon by tomorrow.
He didn't tell you?
- [Intercom Beeps]
- Annie, where's Dumont?
[Annie]
He's been out all afternoon.
The last I heard, he was having lunch
with Ira Klein, the criminal attorney...
I know who he is!
Annie!
[Muttering, Shouting]
I wanna know
where the hell Dumont is!
[Dumont]
Hey, pal, this is kidnapping.
- [Blues]
- I'm a very successful attorney, you know.
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
That's gonna cost you another
hundred miles, Esquire. [Laughing]
Whoo.!
[Sloane] Mr. Metzger was with me
on my boat when word reached...
Mr. Metzger was with me
[Voice Distorted]
With me on my boat.
Hello. I would like to book
a nonstop flight to Los Angeles.
[Sloane]
Tell the associates this is top priority.
[Keyboarding]
Yes, I'd like the number
for the Los Angeles Chronicle.
The city desk, please.
[Sloane] Annie, there's something
I want you to do for me.
[Phone Ringing]
Hello?
Mr. Sloane.
Well, no, sir.
I was just listening to some
very interesting old recordings.
The hearing is tomorrow
at 9:00 a.m.?
Yes, sir, but shouldn't
we wait for Mr. Dumont?
Yes, sir. I understand.
I'll see you first thing
tomorrow morning.
Like clockwork.
[Sloane] Annie, there's something
I want you to do for me.
Annie, top priority. There's something
I want you to do for me on my boat.
[Tape Rewinding]
Annie, top priority. There's something
I want you to do for me on my boat.
[Sloane]
Just watch, listen and learn, Jarod.
You won't see this kind
of dismantling again soon.
I'm looking forward to it, sir.
What are the press doing here?
- [Reporters Clamoring]
- There's nothing I can say at this point in time.
But I will say that there's
going to be some surprises.
- The district courthouse.
- What the hell?
You didn't seriously think the Centre
would cut a deal with Jarod?
Double double cross, Syd.
It's just business.
Have a seat over there.
What the hell is he doing here?
I invited him.
[Judge]
On the record in People vs. Whittaker...
the court hearing a defense motion
to present new evidence.
Mr. Holmes.
Your Honor, Mr. Holmes
is a junior associate in our firm.
He doesn't represent
this particular client.
With all due respect, Your Honor,
I wrote the motion...
and I did the research
for this hearing.
To assign it to another attorney is to deny
Marcus Whittaker a chance at fair representation.
- What the hell do you think you're doing?
- Trying to get an innocent man...
- a fair shot atjustice.
- That's enough.
Mr. Whittaker, is there an attorney
you'd like to represent you?
Jarod.
- Your Honor...
- It's over, Mr. Sloane.
Call your first witness, Mr. Holmes.
Your Honor...
the defense calls Benjamin Sloane.
- [People Chattering]
- [Gavel Rapping]
Mr. Sloane, you represented Marcus Whittaker
to the very best of your ability.
- Is that correct?
- Absolutely.
And to the best of your knowledge,
nothing slipped through the cracks?
- There are no cracks at Sloane and Associates.
- Hmm.
Would you explain your relationship
with Michael Metzger?
He's a client.
Were you aware that your client
was carrying on an affair...
with Audrey Price
at the time of the murder?
- Do you have any proof of that?
- Marcus Whittaker would gladly
testify to it under oath.
What's your point, Mr. Holmes?
Now you went through great pains
to establish the fact...
that Michael Metzger was a guest on your
boat at the time of the murder... is that correct?
I wouldn't call it "great pains."
He was there.
Do you remember what time
Audrey Price was killed?
- Between 9:00 and 9:15, if memory serves me.
- Interesting.
Then maybe you could tell me...
why Mr. Metzger made
a cell phone call to your boat...
at 9:20 the very same night
if he was with you.
May I see that, Mr. Holmes?
Proceed.
For the record, the D.A. has cataloged
this photo...
as a partial shoe print
from the murder scene.
Mr. Sloane, would you explain to the court
why the jury never saw this photograph?
The police never made
a positive match.
It proved nothing.
Well, perhaps I could help
the police out.
It's a size 11, deck shoe.
You were on your boat that night,
weren't you, Mr. Sloane?
- [Chuckles] So, now I'm the killer?
- No.
You were the janitor.
- We'll get to the killer.
- Your Honor, this is pointless harassment.
- [Judge] Mr. Holmes.
- [Door Closes]
One moment, please.
- [Annie] Mr. Sloane's on trial?
- Not officially.
Not yet, anyway.
[Banging Desk]
I love this part.
A size 11 deck shoe...
from Mr. Sloane's closet.
- Proves nothing.
- No.
But this certainly does.
The murder weapon.
Stained with the victim's blood.
Mr. Sloane, would you care
to explain to the court...
what the long-lost murder weapon
was doing on your boat?
[Scoffs]
This is ridiculous.
I don't think that
Michael Metzger thinks so.
You've been blackmailing him
with this since the murder trial.
Michael Metzger beat
Audrey Price to death.
And then he called upon
Mr. Sloane to clean up the mess.
Only before you got there,
Mr. Whittaker arrived.
He found the victim.
He panicked.
He ran away.
You allowed an innocent man
to go to jail.
If I've missed something,
feel free tojump in.
Your Honor, there hasn't been
a piece of evidence...
presented here that a good
defense attorney couldn't shoot down.
Then I suggest
you find a very good one.
I'm ordering you into custody
as an accessory to murder...
and issuing a bench warrant
for the arrest of Michael Metzger.
- Court adjourned.
- [Gavel Raps]
I don't know what kind of law
you're practicing here.
The kind of law that applies
to millionaires too.
Congratulations, Marcus.
You're a free man.
Go, Sam.
We'll head him off downstairs.
- [Monitor Beeping]
- Hey, hold it right there!
You don't understand.
I have a permit to carry that.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Out of my way!
That way.
Jarod!
Damn it!
Next time I'm just gonna
shoot the little pain in the ass.
[Horn Honking]
Get in the car.
[Engine Not Turning Over]
Right this way, Mr. Metzger.
Look, I wanna see my attorney,
all right?
I said, I wanna see my attorney!
[Policeman]
You're in luck.
[Gate Alarm Buzzing]
[Woman]
Excuse me.
[Whistling]
Mom!
[Laughing]
How'd you get here?
A man sent me a ticket.
[Mom]
What is it?
It's a paper clock.
"Now you have all the time
in the world.
"Cherish your freedom, Marcus.
Your pen pal, Jarod."
Hold on to it now.
Right there.
- You all right?
- [Jarod] Eight seconds?
- That's it?
- Uh-huh.
- Eight seconds? Eight seconds?
- [Lowing]
- Let her rip.
- [Alarm Sounding]
[Announcer] Ho.! Watch that bull fly
right out of there, ladies and gentlemen.!
What a ride.!
[Mews]