[Miss Parker] People don't just sit around
a junkyard for a month.
Mr. Woods said he was tired of being on
the road and wanted some peace and quiet.
He wanted to catch up
on his reading.
Like there was money in it.
That man read night and day.
Read?
Read what, exactly?
Books.
Hundreds of'em.
Look at all these.
Mr. Woods brought
all of these with him?
Most were delivered when he bought out
stock from the old library.
All of these are about
mathematics and science.
- Same here.
- Mr. Woods was a big science nut.
Once, he spent 14 hours sitting
in this rocking chair, flippin'a half-dollar.
Fourteen hours?
Weird, huh?
Said heads were better odds.
Somethin'about the suryace
and the, uh, aerodynamics.
Except for dimes. He said never
bet with a dime. Didn't say why.
"Factoring Statistics."
"Physics and Random Probabilities. '"
Oh, I think I'll wait
for the movie on that epic.
"Making Odds Even. '"
May I?
Jarod's left a message.
We're close.
We're nowhere except
whereJarod wants us.
Why would a man
want to learn so much?
Damn good question.
- [Bell Ringing]
- [Dealer] Blackjack.
- The guy on table nine is killing us.
- On my way.
This guy's gotta be a cheat.
No, no. There's no way
he's counting eight decks.
- [Dealer] Another winner!
- [Cheering, Applauding]
- How much is he up?
- Over a hundred grand, it's gotta be.
What?
The chief, Mr. Morgan,
approved the increased credit limit.
Who the hell is this guy?
[Cheering, Applauding Continue]
Ivy, come here.
- What's he drinking?
- Dr. Pepper.
Offer Cristal or Stoli.
I tried that. He wants Dr. Pepper.
[Cheering, Applauding Continue]
Excuse me, please.
Dr. Pepper.
Heads.
- Ten in a row.
- [Dealer] All bets are down.
Be my luck.
Mister, I couldn't even win
the big half of a wishbone.
Hi. I'm Ivy.
Mr. Felson.
Hit me.
House stands on 17.
Twenty-two.
House wins.
See? I'm a total jinx.
You can only be a jinx
if you believe in luck.
- Do you believe in luck?
- No.
- [Dealer] Blackjack.
- All right!
Neither do I.
- And another blackjack.
- [Cheering, Applauding Continue]
That's it. I'll deal with Mr. Morgan.
Shut him down.
So much for jinx.
- Let it ride.
- [Cheering, Applauding]
[Man Narrating]
[Man]
lfhe's counting cards, I can't catch it.
- You think this is a game?
- Well, this is Las Vegas.
- Isn't everything?
- [Door Opens]
This is the guy,
Mr. Morgan.
Like to count cards, do you?
- Davis?
- His name is Jarod Felson.
I ran his I. D...
cruise ships to Monte Carlo.
Didn't find a file
on him anywhere.
I'm honored Mr. Felson has
selected the Marquis Casino...
for his first scam.
Who here thinks that makes
Mr. Felson a complete idiot?
[Jarod] Maybe your security chief
didn't dig deep enough.
Why don't you try
the F.B.I. file under RICO?
You run rackets?
[Typing On Keyboard]
Hello, Mr. Morgan!
You set this up.
You knew we'd have this conversation.
Not bad for a complete idiot.
[Davis]
Where are your blackjack winnings?
I had them delivered to Mr. Morgan's office
by a nice young lady named Ivy.
- You're giving me the money back?
- Money doesn't interest me.
If not money, what does interest you?
I'm not here to make a fool of you,
Mr. Morgan, or to rip you off.
So, what do you want?
Excuse me?
You have an incredible
security system, Mr. Morgan.
It's a shame no one here
knows how to use it.
[Jarod] The bet was $ 1,000.
What did the dealer pay out?
Purple chip.
A grand.
[Jarod]
Meet Martin Rawlings.
He's been dealing blackjack here
for 10 years.
He's the best we have.
That's too bad, because
he's about to lose his job.
He used to work
at a magic club in Kentucky.
His specialty?
Sleight-of-hand.
An extra thousand for the plant.
He passes it to the courier.
Gave the chip to the waitress.
Where's she going?
Forget the courier.
Focus on the chip.
Because it and dozens like it...
are on their way
to your security chief's mace holster.
- Mr. Morgan...
- [Morgan] Remove it.
I've worked here for ten years.
- All of a sudden some jerk in a shiny suit...
- Help him.
That's over $10,000.
Get him outta here.
It's not gonna stop here.
- A casino... it's always a target.
- [Door Closes]
So, Mr. Felson...
what do you want?
Five percent of what you don't lose
while I'm in charge.
Don't you little ladies forget...
come see my show tonight.
There's no cover, no minimum,
and there's free hot hors d'oeuvres.
- [Ladies Giggling]
- I'll see y'all later. Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Hey there, teddy bear.
You come to rub elbows
with the king of rock and roll?
No. I'm trying to understand this.
You dress up in a rented costume
and pretend to be a dead singer?
"Singer"? Son, do you have
any idea who I am?
- Well, actually, I would assu...
- You are looking at a national monument.
Mount Rushmore
in blue suede shoes.
There's not a human being
on God's green Earth...
that has ever demanded
the attention and respect...
of the man you are lookin' at
this very moment.
Hey, Bernie, some guy at the craps table says
he'll give you five bucks to goose his wife.
I'll be right there.
Well, my fans beckon.
I must go.
Thank you very much.
That is the last of them.
I've run every one of these
through the mainframe...
and I can still find
no correlation.
Although there is something
to be said forJarod's theory...
on the aerodynamics
of a 50-cent piece.
Heads.
Okay.
Jarod is trying
to tell me something...
and this book is the clue.
That's a hell of a clue, Syd.
Jarod highlighted the entire book.
But look at this page of statistics.
He traced over
all the number eights.
Now, eight is Jarod's favorite number.
His favorite figure.
He calls it upright infinity...
because of the way one loop
coils into the next, never ending.
Maybe your Boy Wonder
has turned into Brian Boitano.
Mm-mmm.
Jarod is looking
for a purpose.
He's playing games.
Games?
Games with numbers?
High-stakes games?
High-stakes poker.
Baccarat.
Well, that narrows it down...
to any of the thousands
of gaming establishments on the planet.
Any ideas where to start?
I know just the man to see.
Hello.
Have you read this?
It's... It's very good.
It's about this inquisitive
little monkey named George.
He was curious.
I've only read it
about a thousand times.
Oh, well, good.
Then maybe you can help me.
Who is the man
in the yellow hat?
I don't know.
- Oh, well. Thank you anyway.
- Okay!
Can I help you?
Jarod.
It's about time.
- Hanlon's been asking for you.
- Asking for me?
Exposing Davis's scam saved him more money
than his creative accountant ever did.
Steve Hanlon, Jarod Felson.
It's a pleasure to meet you, sir.
I want to thank you
for helping us out.
Here at the Marquis,
we think of ourselves as family.
Nothing worse than being
betrayed by those close to you.
Truly impressive, the way
you came in and cleaned house.
I guess the only question
I have... is why?
Why would a man I never heard of,
never laid eyes on...
step in to help my business
out of the blue like that?
I'm a fan, Mr. Hanlon.
You took a no-name video store.
You turned it into an empire.
You listen to people.
You give them what they want. I like that.
You study people too.
Master your space.
My lecture at Brownstone.
- That must have been 12 years ago.
- It was 11.
And it was the first time you used
"Family First" as the company motto.
- You were there?
- No, sir.
But I bought the cassette.
I wore out my tape player.
Peter, watch out.
I might steal this man for corporate.
[Laughs]
Well, thank you, sir.
We finally got corruption
out of the Marquis.
I would like to help
keep it that way.
Jarod, you have my permission
to do whatever it takes.
I thank you, sir.
Jarod, this is my wife, Kitty.
Kitty, Jarod Felson,
our new security chief.
- Nice to meet you.
- A pleasure, Mr. Felson.
I saw your picture in the lobby.
Kitty used to
headline the show here.
Uh, I need to steal
Mr. Hanlon for a moment.
- Nice to meet you, Mr. Felson.
- Nice to meet you.
So, you're a company man, huh?
I agree with Mr. Hanlon's theories on family,
if that's what you mean.
The only thing Hanlon likes about family
is the procreating part.
He spends millions
building this playground...
and proclaims families now have
a reason to vacation together.
And you don't think they do?
At a casino?
Jarod, people who never even dreamed of
gambling now think it's sanctioned by God.
Add a few flashy arcades,
even the damn kids go home broke.
Don't let Hanlon fool you.
He may talk the new corporate attitude
in this town...
deep down, he's still old Vegas.
[Monitor Beeping]
I'm sorry it took me
so long to get here, Maggie.
[Beeping Continues]
[Door Opens]
Visiting hours
are over at 8:00.
[Woman On P.A.]
Dr. Ryan to O.R.
I thought she was all alone.
Well...
she's not alone anymore.
No offense, uh...
She isn't going to wake up.
I know.
But it doesn't mean she can't hear me.
My name's Jarod.
Oh.
Name's Buddy.
Nice to meet you.
- Buddy.
- Hmm?
If-lf anything happens to her,
will you page me?
I didn't mean to...
sound cold before, but...
I've learned not to
get too attached.
But it is nice to know...
someone gives a damn.
[Door Closes]
[Tires Screeching]
Miss Parker,
what are we doing here?
Saying hello to an old friend.
Hey, I know you're excited to see me.
Just keep it in your pants, Vito.
Sydney, say hello toJohnny.
Johnny's brother hacked
into the computer profiles...
at one of our satellite companies
in Chicago.
- Now he's serving 10 hard in Joliet.
- What do you want?
He's working a con in a casino.
This face? He's not a con.
He's not the type.
He is every type.
Find him for me.
- Pass.
- Mmm. Not an option.
Because, you know,
I heard that at 3:00 tomorrow...
you're shipping out a boatload of...
[Whispering] stolen cars to Venezuela.
Now if you don't want the Port Authority
all over your little boat, well...
- You wouldn't.
- Wanna bet?
Fifty thousand for information.
No questions asked.
- [Applause]
- [Sighs]
[Emcee]
Thanks, ladies and gentlemen.
You've been
a terrific audience tonight.
Hey.
If you're not staying at our fabulous hotel,
please drive safely.
Well, welcome
to the Heartbreak Hotel.
What are you doing here?
You should be on stage.
Oh, no.
There's no more stage for the King.
The casino fired me.
I'm sorry.
Did it have something to do
with that bird thing?
- Bird thing?
- The... goose.
[Snickers]
No. No, they said they had had
complaints about the show.
So I put on 20, 30 pounds.
You think it's easy
being the idol of millions?
- I would guess no.
- You're damn right it isn't.
I sacrificed everything.
I did it 'cause I loved it.
It's what the people wanted.
I just wish some of those casino bigwigs
could spend one hour...
wearing the cape...
just one hour.
They'd walk away singing a different tune,
I guaran-damn-tee you.
Well, couldn't you get a job
at another casino?
No. No, buddy boy.
After 24 years
of making people smile...
singing the songs and...
spreading the good vibrations...
I'm afraid it's the end of the line
for the King.
No, we... we had one hell
of a ride though. Didn't we?
I bet you did.
Look, l... I'm sorry.
I'm spilling my guts,
and I don't even know your name.
Jarod.
Felson.
Bernie Baxley.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
Thanks.
Jarod?
I'm scared.
Of what?
Him.
[Phone Rings]
- Sydney.
- Hello, Sydney.
Jarod.
Good to hear from you.
It's been a while.
Where are you calling from?
You'll figure that out
sooner or later.
- I'm counting on later.
- Counting on or betting on?
You are so well read.
You know, it's such a pleasure to have
the freedom to read whatever I want these days.
Why the games, Jarod?
It's in the mail.
Jarod?
[Dial Tone]
[Imitating Monkey Hooting]
[Jarod] I'm having trouble
understanding the account totals from July.
Guy even works on his day off.
You pay me
to locate discrepancies...
and I can't reconcile
the figures against last year...
specificallyJuly.
- Just set it aside.
- Set it aside?
Jarod, there's a reason
those numbers don't match.
One of our showgirls
was attacked in the parking garage.
Our revenue dropped 30% for three days.
It was an anomaly.
[Morgan]
Not to mention a publicity nightmare.
Fortunately, the megabuster jackpot
hit two days later...
and everybody came back.
Sometimes Lady Luck
even smiles on the house.
[Hanlon Chuckling]
[Ivy]
Thanks for the escort, Mr. Felson.
None of us walk alone anymore.
Not since Maggie.
Maggie.
She was the woman that was attacked.
- Right.
- You knew her?
Well, I'd seen her in the show and around...
backstage, you know.
I read in the paper
there was no evidence of a robbery.
No.
The night it happened,
the showroom was completely packed.
It was the Fourth ofJuly.
Maggie was so happy.
She'd just landed the lead
in a big show in Atlantic City.
Maggie was leaving town?
Yeah, I guess so.
I know I would.
God, it happened right here.
- Gardenias.
- Excuse me?
Uh, Maggie always wore
a gardenia in her hair.
I know it sounds strange, but...
every time I pass this spot,
I swear I can smell gardenias.
- Listen, thanks.
- Sure.
- Drive safe.
- Thank you.
[Engine Starts]
[Young Jarod]
This is weird, Sydney.
This doesn't make sense.
I made it inside.
She doesn't hear me.
The hallway's dark.
It smells like...
flowers.
I round a corner.
To where?
The kitchen.
I'm getting closer.
I know they made her do things
that she didn't want to do.
Did she do something wrong?
Keep going, Jarod. Now focus
on the killer and not the victim.
Is the woman on the bed
her old self or her new self?
They are the same person.
She doesn't think so.
[Sydney] You have what you need
to complete the simulation.
[Young Jarod]
But I don't know why he's there.
Is he trying to kill Norma Jean
or Marilyn?
I'm confused.
[Sydney]
Finish the simulation.
[Young Jarod]
Itjust seems so unfair.
No one should have to die alone.
Something's wrong
with this picture.
with this picture too, Sydney.
Somebody's luck just ran out.
[Bell Dings]
- Thanks for the escort, Mr. Felson.
- It was my pleasure.
Now, you're absolutely sure that you don't
know who this man in the yellow hat was?
Sorry.
- My car's right here.
- Well, have a good night.
Thanks.
This was just delivered.
Come on, Sydney.
We have a plane to catch.
Packin' up, huh?
Gotta stay mobile, son.
You know, I was thinkin'
about headin' back east.
You know, try Branson.
Vegas has changed, you know.
Not much in a city like this
for an old dog like me.
Thanks.
Oh, that...
is an official piece...
of Graceland memorabilia.
- Well, it's very nice.
- [Sighs]
Oh, kid, you know...
you should see the house
in person.
It's, uh... The King
named it for his mama.
People talk about how Elvis let himself go
there near the end...
how he stopped caring
about the people, about the music.
To me, it was just the opposite.
- The opposite?
- Yeah.
He cared too much.
He ran so fast...
so quick...
he didn't have anything left
to finish the race.
Too bad I won't be able
to finish it for him.
You never know, Bernie.
Sometimes a change of scenery
can do you good.
Maybe.
[Pager Beeping]
[Monitor Beeping]
It's okay, Maggie.
You're not alone.
[Monitor: Sustained Tone]
[Monitor Clicks Off]
So, where is he?
It's a hundred grand.
- That was not the arrangement.
- Actually, Sydney, it was.
Your boy is in
the Marquis Casino in Vegas.
It's always a pleasure
taking white collar to the cleaners.
[Miss Parker Chuckles]
I know what you mean.
I brought 200,000 with me.
Who knew you'd be such a cheap date?
Come on, Syd.
We're going to Las Vegas...
a place where
maybe even you could get lucky.
[Line Rings]
[Woman] Hospital Administration.
Can you hold, please?
[Jarod]
Uh, yes, I'll hold.
Yes, I would like to arrange
to pay Maggie Blaire's hospital bills.
They have?
Could you tell me by whom?
- Thank you.
- [Line Disconnects]
I thought you'd come.
I wanted to pay my respects.
Just like you paid
for Maggie's hospital bills...
and for this funeral?
You found the videotape, didn't you?
What?
The real security tape
from the night of the attack.
The one that Peter made sure
the police never saw.
It shows Maggie leaving the Marquis
with your husband.
- They were having an affair, weren't they?
- Who are you?
Somebody who doesn't believe
that Maggie deserved her fate.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You don't have to pretend
like it's not happening anymore.
You don't understand.
He doesn't mean to hurt me.
Yes, he does.
This is your husband's rap sheet.
You're not the first person
that he's hurt.
And unless he's stopped, Maggie's
not gonna be the last person he kills.
My God.
Kitty... I'm here
because I want to help you.
I can stop him...
if you help me.
No. No, l... I can't do that.
When I told him that Maggie was dead
and that I knew what had happened...
h-he lost it.
He said he'd kill me
if I told anyone.
And then he just hit me
again... and again...
[Sobbing]
and again.
Why did he stop?
The phone rang.
Kitty, one day
the phone's not gonna ring.
Mr. Hanlon.
Jarod Felson.
I've discovered a serious problem...
and I'd like to discuss it with you
one-on-one.
Say tomorrow morning,
around 10:00?
Ivy, it's Mr. Felson.
I was wondering if you
could do me a favor.
[Speaking German]
- Hello?
- Peter.
Jarod Felson.
Jarod. What's up?
I've discovered
an even larger problem than before.
- Is it Davis again?
- No.
But it's big,
something you need to handle...
personally.
Can you meet me tomorrow morning,
around 10:00?
Absolutely.
I'll see you there.
So, what are you,
about a 38?
- What?
- Waist.
Uh, 30... 36.
SeñorJarod,
five nights and you don't sleep.
- [Chuckles]
- Hmm?
Too much to do, Blanca.
Not enough hours in the day.
Jorge!
- ¿Has leído este libro?
- Si.
Mucho.
Tengo cinco niños.
¡Blanca, peryecto.!
¿Quién es el hombre
en el sombrero amarillo?
Mmm.
No sé, señor.
- No sé.
- [Sighs] Gracias.
¿Blanca?
¿Sí?
Would you do me a favor?
- Peter, come on. We don't have much time.
- What's this about?
It's about a hundred grand walking out
of this casino right under your very nose.
Mr. Hanlon.!
From Jarod Felson.
He said he'd meet you in the security bay
as soon as he can.
[Jarod] Somebody has been
double-counting the cash outlays.
Based on my findings, over a hundred grand
is being skimmed off the top...
every Tuesday cash pickup.
- You think Davis was behind this?
- I'm not sure.
But it's bigger than one guy.
An accounting scam
tied into the armored car courier.
For every $300,000
that's deposited on paper...
another hundred grand
is being dropped off at a second locale.
But if we keep this scam going...
we find out where the locale is...
we can bring down everybody
that's been ripping off the Marquis.
Why don't we just
bring in the cops?
Peter, think about this.
If you pull this off...
you are gonna be Steve Hanlon's
$20 million hero.
- The Marquis. Now.
- Yes, ma'am.
Why me?
I'm the new face around here.
Nobody's gonna trust me.
But if their courier is greeted
by the president of the casino...
he's gonna play
right into your hands.
It's showtime.
Where's Mr. Davis?
[Clears Throat] Mr. Davis worked for me
in more ways than one.
I'm Peter Morgan.
I run the Marquis.
It's business as usual.
You understand?
Sure.
Business as usual.
Take the skim to the drop.
Deposit the rest in the bank.
- We'll see you next Tuesday.
- Okay.
[Imitates Elvis Presley]
Well, thank you very much.
That was exciting!
Guy fell for everything I said.
He must be a complete idiot.
[Sighs]
Find him.
[Chuckling]
[Morgan]
Steve.!
- I didn't think you'd be here.
- Surprise.
- You won't believe what I've been doing.
- Bet me.
Business as usual.
Take the skim to the drop. Deposit the rest
in the bank. We'll see you next Tuesday.
[Bernie]
Okay.
Steve, I wasn't really
taking the money. We were...
There's a great deal of unreported cash
leaving this casino.
I know!
And, uh, we were...
And a great deal of cash
is going in your Swiss bank account.
- I don't have a Swiss account.
- Oh.
Electronic transfers...
for $4.6 million.
That is your signature, isn't it?
I didn't do this.
Tell him.
Tell him the truth.
I am sorry, Mr. Hanlon.
I'm sorry
I didn't catch this sooner.
And the figure is closer to 4.8.
Every instinct in my gut
told me you were bad news.
Steve, I didn't do anything wrong...
[Groans, Panting]
Felson, damn it!
I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Neither did Maggie Blaire.
Detective Benson,
Homicide.
- I'm looking for a Peter Morgan.
- He's in a meeting right now.
[Thud, Crash]
I think he's asking for a raise.
[Blow Lands]
- [Whistling]
- [Snapping Fingers]
[Bell Rings]
[Coins Falling Into Tray]
[Continues Whistling]
[Slows, Stops]
Jarod!
Take the rear!
Jarod! Don't run! Please!
There's nowhere to go.
[Man On Radio]
Security alert. Pool area.
My lucky day!
[Approaching Footsteps Running]
We got your radio call, Mr. Felson.
Is there a problem?
Yes, there is.
A couple of grifters
trying a roulette scam.
Call the L. V.P.D.
and have them picked up.
Let go of me.
You might want to strip-search this one.
She could be palming chips.
Oh, you bastard!
I'm just doing my job, ma'am.
Head of security, you know.
- I will get you.
- You wanna bet?
Tails.
Come on, lady.
Not a paper clip.
No trash, no lint.
Nothing but this.
And the usual.
Senor Sydney?
- Dígame.
- Para usted.
"To the man in the yellow hat.
From the monkey who got away."
All right.
[Chuckles]
You're really gonna release
him back into the wild?
That's the plan.
Living creatures,
they don't belong in captivity.
[Hooting Quietly]
[Chuckles]
[Mews]