[Man Narrating]
Previously on The Pretender.
[Sydney] His name is Angelo.
Think ofhim like a sponge...
someone who can absorb
the intellectual, emotional...
even the physical
traits of others.
He will find Jarod for us.
[Miss Parker]
He better, Sydney. Hejust better.
[Keyboard Clacking]
Yes, Mr. Parker.
He's searching the Internet
for any signs of him now.
We'll find Jarod...
and whoever inside the Centre
is helping him.
[Phone Hangs Up]
Keep working, Angelo.
Keep working.
- [Explosion]
- [Man] Whoo-whee.!
You see?
Get too close to that bad boy...
and you'll be a-picking
your nose with your wrist.
[Chuckling]
Now, you boys are 21, aren't ya?
That's what I thought.
Fill up
their trunk, Eugene.
- Now, where were we?
- You were telling us about Mr. Nobel.
Yeah, old Nobel was like
a Picasso of gunpowder.
- He invented the Big Bertha, you know.
- The Big Bertha?
The mother of all Roman candles.
Three time-delayed sparkle explosions...
wrapped in a color-spray
smoke banger...
lined with quarter strands
ofT.N.T.
- Sounds impressive.
- Put on a New Year's Eve show...
that put old Dickie Clark
to shame.
[Chuckling] I don't know
where he went. Just disappeared.
- Yes.
- Hmm.
He has a habit of doing that.
Thank you.
There is no way thatJarod could have
known we were coming.
Zero.
Have you noticed that it never seems
to work the other way, Syd?
Maybe there is a reason.
Stay frosty, Nobel.
It's all being recorded for posterity.
This way.
The note that was faxed said
we'd find the bomb over here.
- Carlson.
- [Beeping]
Hello.
Oh, yeah.
Bad Betty.
Fax Bomber's usual.
Whoa, cowboy.
Betty needs her beauty rest,
or she's a real witch to wake up next to.
Tools.
Whoa. I found something.
- Looks like a note.
- He always leaves one.
What's it say?
"Catch me if you can,
you miscreants."
"Miscreants"?
What does that mean?
[Rapid Beeping]
It means "Get the hell
outta here"! Move! Move!
[Coughing]
Is it always like this?
Welcome to
the Bomb Squad, Jarod.
[Man Narrating]
[Chatter On Police Radio]
So, Nobel,
now you know...
what a close encounter with
the Fax Bomber feels like, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Man, I wish
I could have been here.
Can't imagine why, sir.
- My ears are still ringing.
- Used to be some scumball
went to make a bomb threat...
they'd pick up the phone
like a decent human being.
Now what?
They fax 'em in.
- Scumball?
- Sort of like a miscreant, only different.
[Forced Laughing] Someone mark
the calendar. Lamont made a funny.
Now, this bomber
faxes his threats in.
That's a unique M.O.
Must help him cover his tracks.
Well, this guy doesn't need any help.
We have run...
every piece of evidence he's left behind
through the best technology we have:
D.N.A., hair samples,
fiber, impressionology...
Guy leaves us nothing
to follow. Nothing.
We gotta catch
a break sometime.
So you, uh... You people, you
stay here and keep after this.
I'm gonna go
lie to the press.
[Groans]
What's the matter, Carlson?
You catch a little more steel last night?
Hey, Lamont, why don't you be a good civil
servant? Get the two heroes some coffee.
He loves me.
Did you have another bomb
go off on you before?
I got a little shrapnel
in my shoulder during the war.
Hero here's the only guy
refers to Grenada as a war.
- I got the medals to prove it.
- Come on. You know the only medals...
that count in your family
are the ones your big brother won in 'Nam.
I heard that you brought the last two
of the Fax Bomber's devices in intact.
I got lucky. Hey.
Don't you worry about it,J.
One day this Fax Bomber's
gonna slip up.
When he does, we're gonna
be there to catch him.
I just hope the S.O.B.
blows himself up.
[Man] The detonator was
connected to an accelerator.
This is a dangerous new escalation
for the Fax Bomber.
Hand those out,
will you, John?
This is my sight profile
of the bomber.
It includes a, uh, computer-generated
composite sketch...
based on some
incomplete information.
- He looks like my Uncle Fred.
- Looks like everyone's Uncle Fred.
Based on his, uh, faxed threats
and other data...
the bomber is a left-handed,
disgruntled ex-city worker.
The chances are he's already
expressed his discontent.
- We all know what that means.
- Back to the crank files.
Excellent, Lamont.
Now, I expect...
that all of you people will put in
whatever overtime is necessary...
to screen those files and to interview
every possible perp.
Questions? No? Good.
Go to work.
- Excuse me. Lieutenant Chomsky,
do you have a moment?
- Sure.
I've been going over your file on the fax
bomber, and with all due respect, sir...
You know, when people say, "all due respect,"
they generally don't have it.
Sir, it-it's just that I think that
your profile of the perp...
is exactly who
he wants us to think he is.
I think that his grudge against the city
and everything else about him is a mislead.
Guy's here a week,
he's already bucking for my bars.
No, sir. I just happen
to have a different opinion.
- Based on what?
- I know people.
I'm listening.
The D.N.A.
and the impressionology...
all came up empty.
He's trying to lead us
down a high-tech path...
but I believe that we can snag him
with a low-tech solution.
He's right-handed...
but he wants us
to believe he's a lefty.
The verticals and the horizontals
are all jagged...
which would indicate that he's been
writing with his subdominant hand.
- You're a graphologist?
- Uh, no, sir, but I was a palm reader once.
Shall I tell you
about your future here?
Sir, I believe
that our bomber...
is a city employee who is not
necessarily disgruntled.
He's enjoying
watching us run around...
almost as much as he enjoys
setting off explosions.
If you want to suggest that, uh, this clown
is some kind of a Merry Prankster...
I recommend that you
talk with Rachel Newton.
Rachel is gonna spend
the next year of her life...
learning how to read Braille
because of the Fax Bomber.
- I wasn't trying to trivialize that, sir.
- No, no. I know you weren't.
You were just trying to
make, uh, an impression...
show off your erudite
European upbringing.
- My what?
- The cadence in your voice...
You were raised by a French nanny.
Well, could be Belgian, I suppose.
- How did you know that?
- Oh, I know about people too.
[Sydney Speaking Foreign Language]
[Continues]
[Miss Parker] Damn it, Broots.
You said we had him cornered.
But we did.
I don't know what happened.
- Jarod happened.
- Oh, spare me, Sydney.
All I know is
that I'm fed up...
with always being
a step behind him.
[Raines]
So am I.
- Uh, l-I gotta go.
- Stay here, Mr. Broots.
- What brings you down from the Tower, sir?
- Plumbing.
Plumbing?
I've come to plug a leak.
- Hey.
- Hey. What's up, Nobel?
The Fax Bomber,
a.k.a. Uncle Fred.
Okay.
Not my finest hour, but, hey...
nobody got a great look at this guy,
so the sketch is, you know, sketchy.
This is
a fascinating machine.
Yeah. This here is a Decatronics
Turbo Graphics II workstation.
This little bad boy makes composites,
puts disguises on portraits...
ages missing kids,
which is what I'm doing now.
- That's incredible.
- Some of my best work's been
on the backs of milk cartons.
[Chuckling]
Think of the D. T.G. II...
as sort of a high-tech
Mr. Potato Head.
- Mister who?
- Potato Head.
Oh. Now,
this is interesting.
You call him Mr. Potato Head,
yet his head is his whole body?
Yeah.
Cool, huh?
He comes with little
interchangeable ears...
eyes and little hats.
Old Spud Man is the original
master of disguise.
You know, this would make
a wonderful toy for children.
Hey, Nobel, crank file
just turned up a hot one. Let's run.
- Hmm.
- [Doorbell Ringing]
Oh, God.
What'd he do?
Curtis! They finally
came to arrest you!
- Curtis!
- Busy, Ma.!
Mrs. Haring,
we're not here to arrest your son.
I knew someday the cops would
show up and take him away.
- Curtis.!
- I said, get off my back.!
- Ma'am, we just wanted to...
- Thirty years old, and he still lives in my basement.
Day in and day out,
writing his little letters.
I should've bought
stock in Bic.
Don't say nothing, Ma. This is all
going on tape somewhere. I know it.
Listen to that. Do you know
what it's done to my social life...
having him
down there?
- You're not gettin' nothin' out of me.
- I'm in the prime of my life.
I should go out, get myself some
nice shoes and find myself a man.
- Ma!
- Sir...
did you write these letters
to the utilities commission?
And I'll write a hundred more
till they give me back my workman's comp.
I got an inoperable hernia
working for this city...
and they threw me
to the wolves.
How'd you get that letter?
What's your name?
I'm Carlson.
This is, uh, Nobel.
Hold still, man.
I can't see your badge number.
He don't have no hernia. Hejust don't
wanna move out of the basement.
Shut up, Ma! You know how my legs
tingle every time I sit for too long.
Yeah, and I know
where you're sittin'!
Sir, we're not here to talk
about your workman's comp.
We want to ask you some questions
about your whereabouts.
Hey, if you think you got something on me,
you come back with a warrant.
Till then, me and my mother's got nothing
to say to you miscreants.
I should've married
a dentist.
- At least then his teeth'd be better.
- Ma!
This guy's classic
bomber material.
Former city worker,
domineering mother...
basement workshop,
a little antisocial behavior.
- I'm not convinced.
- Huh?
He's written 253 letters
to the city and counting.
If he's crossed the threshold
into planting bombs...
don't you think he would have given up
the correspondence?
- Did you notice what he called us in there?
- Miscreants.
- Right. Nobody uses that word
except for that guy and...
- The Fax Bomber.
I'm gonna get under this guy's skin
before he hurts someone else.
[Electronic Squawking]
Wake up! Wake up!
Good morning!
... five, six...
seven, eight...
nine, ten...
- You can stop counting. You're here.
- Oh. [Chuckles]
You must have stepped into the room.
It's 11 steps to the door.
I did.
That's very good.
It's funny, Dr. Jarod.
I used to hate math in school.
Now my entire life
is basic arithmetic.
Nine steps from my bed
to the bathroom...
14 steps to the hallway,
seven steps to the chair.
Just be happy
it's not long division.
It's a beautiful day.
Why don't we go outside?
Oh, no. l... l-I think
I'd rather stay here.
Rachel...
you have to go outside
sometime.
I was supposed to work
in my studio...
but it was such a nice day,
I decided to go on the rooftop at city hall.
That's what happened
the last time I went outside.
You were in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
But that is not your fault.
You can't stop living your life
because of it.
I hear he set off
another bomb.
Yes, he did.
Thankfully, nobody else was hurt.
You know, when I had
my eyes behind a camera...
I could see things
no one else could see.
I could take
a thousand shots...
and tell you which one was peryect
before it was even developed.
I can remember details of nearly
every picture I ever took.
That's ironic.
They tell me
he was there that day.
That I must have seen the man who did this
to me as he was setting his bomb.
But as hard I try,
I can't remember.
I can't believe
they think one of us...
is leaking
information toJarod.
[Sighs] Oh, I wish I hadn't eaten
that poppy seed muffin.
They're giving us
a polygraph, you idiot...
not a urine test.
I thought it was both.
It should be,
for you.
What-What is that
supposed to mean?
You're the one who handles
the information around here.
I'm sorry. I'm in a filthy mood.
Let's not accuse each other.
Oh, that means a lot
coming from Jarod's teddy bear.
Miss Parker.
To calibrate the machine...
please answer the following
question untruthfully.
- Are you Eleanor Roosevelt?
- Yes.
Have you pursued Jarod
to the best of your ability?
- Yes.
- [Raines] Become her, Angelo.
Tell me if she is lying.
[Man]
Did you willfully misfire your weapon...
when attempting to apprehend
Jarod in Miami, Florida?
- What?
- Yes or no, please.
No.
Smoking is not permitted
during a polygraph.
Have you received...
a personal message
from Jarod?
It was a bunny.
Yes.
Did you secretly contactJarod
via a secure Internet connection?
Yes.
Did you attempt to provide him
with classified information?
Yes, but with a view
to bringing him home.
- Have you ever secretly met with Jarod?
- Mm-mmm.
No.
Is he lying?
Is he the one?
Have you ever used
a controlled substance?
[Clears Throat]
No.
Were you in the lab when information
regarding Jarod's origins was leaked?
Yes.
Did you leak the information
Jarod received...
- via special courier in Miami, Florida?
- No.
- Have you ever lied to the Centre?
[Gasping]
He's the leak,
isn't he, Angelo?
So, you've decided to put in
a transfer to Forensics, hmm?
I've just been sifting though
all the Fax Bomber debris.
You went over three thousand
pieces of evidence here?
Three thousand
and twenty-five.
- I've specifically been studying the wires.
- No, no, no.
The feds, they covered every
centimeter of that copper.
I know. I've been studying
the encasements.
There's no pattern.
This guy is random...
except for
the detonator connectors.
He's very sensitive
about them.
He wants to be sure.
That's why they all have exactly
the same parallel cut pattern.
Come on.
Exactly the same?
Exactly.
Notice the angle of the grooves
on the parallels.
Gives us something to run down
with the knife manufacturers.
- And the cut contours confirm that he's...
- Right-handed.
Yes, sir.
Low-tech.
- Very.
- Mmm.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hey. How's the spud
of a thousand faces?
Well, I only have
the 13-piece set so...
technically,
this one's only got, uh...
One hundred and seventy-nine.
I have a project for you.
I'm up to my ears
in milk cartons here.
Well, this one's
very special to me.
It's my mother.
I was wondering...
if you could age her
30 years.
- I want to see what she would look like.
- [Pager Beeping]
- I'll make it worth your while.
- Hey, I'll see what I can do.
- Thanks.
- All right.
[Siren Wailing]
It's right over there under the bus.
- Did the threat come in by fax?
- It was more of a phone call.
One of my drivers found the unclaimed
suitcase on the 3:15 from Traverse City.
- All right. We'll take it from here.
- Thanks.
Hey, can you guys
kinda hurry up?
'Cause I got buses backing
up on me here, man, and l...
Take as much time as you need then.
Thanks.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Come on.
[Buzzing]
[Horn Honks]
Got a backache?
[Switches Off]
They told me we would have a lot
ofhoax calls in training...
but I never thought
it would feel like this.
- Let go,J.
- That's easy for you to say.
- It was pretty tense back there.
- Don't worry about it.
- That's nice work.
- Oh. Yeah.
- From my army days.
- Let me guess.
- You got drunk one night.
- Blitzed. [Chuckles] My whole unit.
After Grenada, they stationed us down
at Fort Buchanan, Puerto Rico.
I do not remember one thing
that happened that entire month...
except for this
needle artist.
He was a shriveled-up little
Puerto Rican guy...
who had a hole-in-the-wall
shop in old San Juan.
- He inked every single guy in the whole platoon...
- The whole platoon.
You know how many eagles
this guy had to do in one night?
Give us a break,
will you, Carlson?
You partner with this guy too long, you know
his old unit like it was your own family.
[Rachel]
What are you doing?
I'm going to turn this space
into a darkroom.
- I live in a darkroom.
- Good.
Because I need you...
to develop a roll
of film for me.
Oh, that smells
familiar.
- I thought you'd remember it.
- Is this some kind of new therapy?
Call it a simulation.
- Simulation?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm going to create
an environment...
with all the stimuli
you need to recreate an event...
and for you
to become someone.
Who do you want me
to become?
- Yourself.
- Oh!
Oh, my camera.
Oh, I haven't
touched this since the...
well, since the day
at city hall.
Now I want you to develop
that roll of film...
the pictures
you took that day.
- Oh, but there's no film in it.
- I know.
I want you to develop
the pictures in your mind.
I'm on the rooftop
at city hall.
Natural light is at its-
its peryect angle.
The building is... is closed.
It's Sunday.
And I'm, uh, getting last-minute shots
for my gallery opening.
[Jarod]
Are you alone?
I think.
l-I don't see anyone.
I don't...
I don't see anyone...
but I feel a...
a tingle
on the back of my neck.
- [Footsteps]
- I don't see anyone, but I hear something.
- What do you hear?
- Footsteps, walking quickly away.
But, uh, you don't think
anything about it...
because you have
other pictures to take.
It's right
before it happens.
We can stop this
if you want.
No.
I walk over to where the footsteps
are coming from...
but he's gone.
Rachel,
do you see the bomb?
It's only an instant
before the flash.
- Do you see him?
- No.
But...
I smell something.
- I smell...
- You smell him.
It must be, um...
I don't... I don't know
what it is.
It-It's cologne.
No, it-it's, um,
medicine, menthol.
- What athletes put on sore muscles.
- Liquid heat.
Thank you.
- Are you Steven Johnson?
- Yeah.
Special Agent
Jarod Webster.
F.B.I.?
What did I do?
Nothing, Mr. Johnson.
I'm just doing a security check...
on one of your old army buddies,
Daniel Carlson.
He put you down
as a reference.
If you want to clear Carlson,
you're talking to the wrong guy.
- Why's that?
- Carlson talks a good game...
but the rest of the squad
had to carry him every step of the way.
Well, the way he puts it,
you were a very tight unit.
We'd probably have shot him ourselves
if he hadn't caught the shrapnel in the shoulder.
He has the company tattoo
on his forearm.
You don't see any moronic little birds
on me, do you?
Hell, Carlson come in
one day all drunk...
queer little bird on his arm, talking about
how he wanted the rest of us to get 'em.
Guy's a dangerous little
wannabe.
Well, thank you very much
for your time.
Hey, what's the little weasel
applying for, anyway?
- Bomb Squad.
- God help us all.
- [Siren Wailing]
- [Jarod] You paged me?
[Man] Oh, yeah, dude.
Sorry Santa was a little late...
but, uh,
"Ho, ho, ho."
She's still beautiful.
Now, um, you said
you'd make it worth my while.
Patience, Mr. Potato Head.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Jarod, the Fax Bomber
just blew himself up.
- Where's Carlson?
- He phoned it in.
[Sirens Wailing]
Let me through.!
Let her through. This is her house.
This is her son. Let her through.
Are you hurt?
I wasn't home last night.
I had a date.
Curtis? Curtis, Mama's here.
Ma's here, honey.
I had a feeling about this guy.
I came over here to see if I could get him to talk.
He must have seem me coming
because the whole place went up.
- It knocked me all the way back
to the end of the driveway.
- It was a nice play, Carlson.
- Get yourself cleaned up. You look like hell.
- Thank you, sir.
I should have known
it was him.
Another croissant,
Miss Parker?
Cold coffee's plenty.
He always seemed to be...
a step ahead...
and then suddenly,
we were a step behind.
Broots has the classic
nonconfrontational personality.
I doubt he would put
himself in harm's way.
[Car Engine Starts]
[Miss Parker]
Where the hell is he going now?
Private investigator?
Could he have found Jarod?
I don't know.
But somebody
just put themselves in harm's way.
It doesn't make sense.
The same bomber, who was so
intelligent he didn't leave...
as much as a speck of D.N.A. behind,
accidentally blows up his own mother's house?
- Don't start with me, Nobel.
- And why would he keep all of
his bomb-making equipment...
in a box in the garage when he had
his own basement workshop?
- Maybe he was feeling the heat
and was planning to make a move.
- I don't think he's our man.
Why?
Is he left-handed?
As a matter of fact, he is.
The issue of guilt
is up to a jury.
Our job... collect evidence.
[Alarm Chirps]
[Man] Now we have an exclusive with
Officer Dan Carlson of the city Bomb Squad.
So, you defused his devices
and brought him to justice.
How does it feel to be the man
who uncovered the Fax Bomber?
I'm just glad this nightmare for the city
is finally coming to an end.
Not quite.
- Here.
- [Gun Cocks]
What do you... What is this?
What are you doing?
Sweepers? In my house?
- [Crying]
- That's all right. That's okay. It's all right.
He's in the middle
of the custody battle.
The P.I. was trying to dig up something
on the ex he could use in court.
- The plane ticket?
- Time for little Susie to fly home to Mommy.
At least
we've cleared him.
Cleared him?
He lied to the Centre.
- He never said anything about being married.
- He wanted his privacy.
- None of that justifies what we did.
- You're damn right.
You're late.
Well, I spent all morning on the phone
with a lawyer. He dropped my case.
Hmm.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Mmm.
Are you, Miss Parker?
Thanks to you, my daughter
hasn't stopped crying since last night.
Tomorrow, I have to send her back to her
mother, which is a place she doesn't want to go.
None of that has anything
to do with the Centre.
I work here.
I sold my soul to be in this place.
I'm not selling her.
So don't mess with her.
And don't mess with me.
Hey, Lamont,
what are you doing tonight?
- Hey, Carlson.
- What?
You'd better take
a look at this.
What?
Ugh. This is
some kind of hoax.
Now, we know the-the Fax Bomber
is in a hospital bed.
Well, I guess he
checked himself out.
Let's go.
- Main elevator banks.
- Right over there.
- Come on!
- Maybe we should wait for backup.
And miss our chance
to be heroes?
Come on.
Whoa.
Another Bad Betty.
Oh, God.
Let's not rush
into anything here.
Oh, look.
He left a note.
Careful. Slow.
"This time it's real."
Hmm. See?
- No!
- [Bell Dings]
Forget it, Carlson.
This is the express.
It won't stop for 60 floors.
Oh-oh.
Sixty floors if we're lucky.
- What are you talking about?
- Barometric detonator.
Designed to detonate
at altitudes 600 or 700 feet.
My guess is we're good
for 45, 50 floors, tops.
- We gotta get out of here!
- No, we've gotta defuse this bomb.
- No, there's no time!
- Oh, there's plenty of time.
It should be easy for you.
It's just like all the other bombs
you used to make.
- Huh?
- You know...
the bombs you defused...
- so you could be a hero
just like your big brother was?
- Who the hell are you?
Just your average,
everyday miscreant.
And someone who doesn't think that
Rachel Newton should have lost her eyesight...
so that you could be
put in the limelight.
Now, listen to meJarod.
I did not expect anybody to get hurt.
Tell that to Curtis Haring.
He was the guy you tried to blow up...
so you could
cover your tracks.
All right! That's enough!
Now, come on! Defuse this thing!
Not so cool under pressure
when it's not your own bomb.
But you see, people that plant bombs,
they're cowards at heart.
And since I planted this one, I don't
want to stick around to watch it blow.
- [Bell Dings]
- Uh-oh.
Twentieth floor.
Better get to work.
Hope you can figure out
which wire to snip.
Bye-bye, hero.
No! Jarod!
Jarod!
[Beeping]
[Thudding]
I guess that's why
they call it the express.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Electronic Male Voice]
Ten, nine, eight...
seven, six...
five, four...
three, two...
one.
Kaboom.
You're under arrest,
Carlson.
[Curtis]
... that all of you at city hall...
will pay egregiously
for what has happened to me.
- Are you sure you want to say that?
- Say what?
- "Egregiously"?
- Who's writing this letter?
- I was only making a suggestion.
- It's my letter!
- All right, already. What do you want from me?
- Ma!
- You don't even know what it means.
- Do too!
- Well, I can spell it.
- Just write it!
- E, G, R...
- Get my dictionary.!
- I'm not going in that smelly basement.
- Ohh! There's a fly on me.
- "Egregiously."
- A fly on me! Aah!
- [Knocking]
- [Jarod] Morning, May.
- Where's Rachel?
- There's something you should see.
Took her about a halfhour
to get down there.
But she got there
all by herself.
He's still searching,
Mr. Parker.
But we will
find the leak.
I promise you that.
Did you find
something, Angelo?
Keep working.
[Keyboard Clacking]
[Mews]