It's got no electricity
And no running water.
A hundred bucks a month.
Deal.
Ready?
I hope this works, popi.
That book of yours-- it's just a bunch of coordinates
In there, right?
Among other things.
Does your father still have
That phone number I gave you?
I think so.
Well, tell him to call my brother.
Papa, make that call for my friend.
The american?
If time runs out,
And I don't have the second half of those coordinates,
Lj and the senorita stop breathing.
Just wish there was another way to do is.
To save lj without handing Whistler over.
Look, man, that's it-- there isn't.
What is that?
Kesslivol.
When heated to a certain degree,
It eats through steel.
As soon as linc cuts the power we go.
What about the backup generator?
There's a lag from when the power cuts out
To when the generator kicks back in.
How long a lag we talking about?
30 seconds.
We only have 30 seconds. go.
Move it, move it.
Come on.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go. not yet.
We have to go now. we're running out of time.
Trust me.
Come on, mate.
What's the holdup, Michael?
Just a little bit longer.
What happened?
They got caught.
What's going on? shut up.laring)
What, what...?
Don't try anything.
Bring 'em over here! bring 'em over here!
You-- on your knees, get down!
Don't move,
Or you're like your friend over here.
What's going on, Michael?
This sure as hell better work out.
For everyone's sake.
You two,
On your feet.
Where the hell's Scofield? shut it.
If Scofield doesn't get caught,
He could still fix this mess.
What do we do now?
The lights are on, they know about the escape... what's your plan,
Michael?
This is the plan.
Michael, how the hell
Is getting caught your plan?
You told them they had 30 seconds to get across
When you knew the generator was going to kick in sooner.
I must have miscalculated.
We've got about ten minutes till the sun rises.
And there are soldiers out there, okay.
They'll take count. we got to get back to the yard.
We're not going anywhere.
It's almostime.
What do you tnothing. it's just probably my wife.
You know, we live a couple miles away
And she must have heard the sirens, so...
You can make your calls when I'm done with you.
What else you got?
Sucre? I'm not here. say what you got to say.
Sucre, where the hell are you?!
We're counting on you to be here!
If you're not there, we're dead, man.
Now call me back, please.
Put these with his personal effects.
What's going on out there?
Some prisoners tried to escape.
Did they get out?
They got caught.
One of them got shot pretty bad.
Sucre?
No, it is Alphonso Gallego.
You where you need to be?
Yes.
I left the suburban on the side of the road.
The keys are in the wheel well.
Are they still t hecheck 'em out.
They're here.
Good, good.
You will be here too,
On the 312?
Yeah, yeah, the 312.
See you there.
These all the men? si, senor.
Tell me, how did you get out there?
How did you get out there?
Hmm? don't want to tell me?
A tunnel.
Where?
Under Lechero's room.
Show me.
How much longer?
It's just a matter of seconds now.
Michael?
The door.
I don't know the combination.
Then improvise.
This is insane.
Let's go.
Vamanos.
Hurry!
It wasn't me!
It was Scofield! he did this!
Just check the yard-- him,
Whistler, Mahone and that basketball kid--
None of 'em will be there!
This is captain solo. other inmates are missing.
I want a post-and-protect
Around the entire perimeter of the prison.
General, we see no one.
Are you sure there's prisoners out here?
You won't find the prisoners here in no-man's-land
Because they're already gone.
Off the bus now!
Get off the
Bunow!
What's wrong?
My ankle! I've torn it apart!
Come on.
It's not that far. help me up!
Mr. Whistler, we'll drag you by your hair
Because we got to go!
I'll slow you down. just go! just leave me!
We both know that's not an option.
It's only a quarter
Of a mile to the beach.
If we stick to the bush, we can make it.
Alex, a little help?
Go. come on!
Hey. we only have a few minutes.
We got soldiers right behind us.
Cops as well.
We got what we nd?
Yeah, we got what we need.
What do we need?
Always picking up the strays, huh?
This way.
Listen, Michael, if you think the company's just going
To let you swap me for your nephew, you're mistaken.
Shut up.
Once they get hold of me,
They're gonna kill all of you,
And I don't want Sofia caught in the crossfire.
Listen, just let me go.
I'll contact them, I promise.
I'll say I'll turn myself in once I know lj's safe.
Hey, you got no say in wha happens to my son! you got it?
We don't need a suntan.
We need to get lost.
The military patrols all the roads around the prison.
You didn't consider a boat?
They show up here and we're ten yards off the shore,
We're target practice.
We need to be invisible.
Five guys, four tanks.
Sucks for you, Mahone.
Lincoln and I will share.
Toss your boots in the box.
Yeah?
Tell me you have him.
Yeah, I got him.
Where's my son?
With me. put him on the phone now.
Say something.
I'll be there soon. just don't hurt anyone.
You happy?
You have 20 minutes to meet me in panama city
Where we agreed.
We'll be there.
Hey, I need to put my book in there.
The book? my book!
It must have fell out of my pocket.
I thought you already figured out the coordinates.
Well, I didn't memorize them! I wrote them in the book!
I'm pretty sure they're still looking for us, guys.
It's gone. now get in the damn water.
Would you please? it's a picture of my son.
Can you, uh...
Put it in the bag?
Screw you, Mahone.
Let's go.
McGrady. mcGrady?
I don't swim so good.
What?
Too bad, kid, you're getting wet. get in.
Look it's all right.
We'll share tanks. just hold onto me
And we'll switch off back and forth, ten seconds apiece.
Come on. let's go.
Where is Scofield?!
I don't know! he didn't tell me nothing!
Where is he running?
I told you, I don't know nothing!
Well, there's only one way to make certain of that.
This is general Mestas. the men will be sent.
And, Sojo, I expect every prisoner
To be returned to Sona today.
Dispatch fourth platoon.
Hey, hey, look, man, this is getting crazy here.
Look, I'll plead guilty for ignoring the warrant.
I'll show up for the court hearings.
Let me get out of here.
You know, with this alarms and the guns,
They're making me a little nervous.
Until things settle in, you go nowhere.
So just sit tight.
Urfo platoon goes to Cabrillo beach ahora.
There!
Where is he?
Where's who?
Sucre with the boat.
Ju hold on.
You all right? you all right?
Yeah.
I'm all right, I'm all right.
We're not gonna make it
Out here too much longer, Michael.
Sucre is coming. be patient.
Excuse me?
Boat 312, why is it still here?
Wasn't someone supposed to take that out today?
Someone reserved it, but they never picked it up.
Yes, general.
I want an update.
Still no sign of them. nothing on the coast.
I think they may have gone back into the jungle.
The jungle? you asked me to send men to the beach!
Capitan...
Just a moment, general.
General, I think we have to call the coast guard.
Come on!
You all right?
My legs are starting to cramp.
You gotta hold on, buddy.
We're not gonna last out here too long, Michael.
Where's your friend, Michael?
Sucre's not just gonna abandon us out here, all right?
He'll show, he'll show.
The coast guard is launching four vessels...
They've been in the water this whole time.
They're probably at the bottom of the ocean by now.
Well, look it here!
A drunk and disorderlyke we warrant for jorge rivera.han
Failure to pay child support.
You're not going anywhere.
Once we're done processing you, then you can go.
Until then, sit tight.
I should have heard something by now.
I've lost all damn track of them.
Burrows will eventually reach out if he wants his son ck.
Yeah, well, that might no longer be an option.
Look! look!
Sucre!
He's supposed to be flashing a light.
He's not responding, Linc.
The coast guard. they found us.
Papa!
Michael... Michael?
If I don't get another chance, I want
You to know that I appreciate everything you've done.
You're welcome.
Come on, son.
How'd you find us?
You never showed, and you said you'd be coming
From the southwest, so I took a chance.
What do you think happened to Sucre?
Don't know, but we gotta move.
Guess that just leaves one.
Get up.
Let's go.
I saw the boxes in the back, so I took your car--
Figured you'd need to change
How's the ankle?
I need to get off my feet.
All right, guys, get changed and make sure
You don't leave any wet clothes behind.
Listen, uh...
Thanks for everything.
Thank you for my boy.
I hope you get your son back, too.
Yeah, me, too.
Come. we need to get back to the truck.
Michael?
Thank you.
Go be with your family, Luis.
Yeah?
Where the hell are you?
We ran into some trouble. we're-we're downtown panama.
No, Lincoln, you're not.
We got company.
How'd they find us?
You have them?
We're right on top of them.
Hold on!
They must've gotten to Grady's dad and bugged this car.
Or one of us.
Then why didn't they find us when we were in the water?
It's because the water was blocking the signal.
What you do with that stopwatch that Gretchen gave you?
Oh, my god. I didn't know.
I didn't know.
Okay, hold on, guys.
All right, it's time to use this rig to our advantage.
Go! here we go!
Uh... this is, like, a dead end right here.
Stay in the car, then.
This way!
Why don't you just tell us what you know?
Then you won't wind up being beaten half to death
Like your friend. I know less than you do.
Which is hard, considering how dumb you are.
I want everything you can find on the men who escaped
And I want it immediately.
Go see the clerk about your stuff.
They're barricaded.
What are you doing?
Get back!
All that gunfire and they only
Hit your car three times?
Son of a bi...
Listen, Linc, you've done a great job getting us
Out of the frying pan, but it'll be for nothing
If we end up back in the fire.
There's no fire, just an exchange,
Then I'm done with you.
You think it's that simple?
Yeah, they want you, they get you. it's that simple.
This is not about me. it's about Sofia and ur son. Michael--
Tell him-- tell him these people
Won't just let us walk away.
We already had this discussion back at the beach, James,
And you were outvoted.
You're making a terrible mistake.
People might die because of this.
Take off your pants.
Excuse me, ser?
I said take off your pants.
If I knew you boys partied in Sona like this,
I never would have tried to escape.
One cell phone.
One wallet.
And some change.
There were some papers.
A boat-rental agreement. I need them.
I'll check the drawer.
Take them down.
Come on, now, hombre.
There's no need to refry my beans.
Always with the wise talk.
Never saying anything we want to hear.
Now, all I want to hear are your screams.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no. listen.
I told you, I don't know nothing.
No, actually, I don't know nothing.
I swear. I swear I don't.
But he does!!
He knows everything!
Hey! not so fast, amigo.
Hey. a little help.
What is this place?
Where we're gonna make the exchange-- on our terms.
There's a service road out back, just in case
We want to get lost. yeah, assuming you're still alive.
You still talking?
Linc?
Yeah.
Gotta commend you on that boom box trick.
Very sophisticated.
You steal that one from home alone?
You fell for it, bitch.
All right, listen. if you wanna see your son...
You're not calling the shots anymore.
As long as I have lj....
As long as I got Whistler, u'yo gonna do exactly what
I say. you got it?
Now, listen up.
We're at an abandoned
Warehouse five miles down the road
From the barrios interchange. be there in 20 minutes
With my son.
And once I get there?
So now we wait.
Yeah.
Think this'll work?
Yeah, it'll work.
You, me and lj.
Yeah.
I just hope it works out for mcGrady, too.
Oh, no.
They must have closed all the roads out of panama.
Papa, what do we do?
You gotta turn around, papa.
I can't go back to sona. I can't.
I don't care what he says.
He's a convict! he's a piece of garbage.
I don't know anything about this Michael Scofield guy.
General.
Here is everything we have on the escaped prisoners.
You don't know Michael Scofield, is that right, jorge?
Yes.
You sure you don't want to ange your story, Fernando?
This should help make you a decent brace.
Thank you.
Should be able to see them coming from up here.
You know, Linc...
You did great.
Thanks.
I just want lj back, you know?
It's just a matter of time.
Yeah.
Considering I don't have
A pony in this race...
After what you did to us?
What you did to my dad?
No.
I was gonna kill you at the beach,
But I didn't want to do anything that was gonna get us caught.
You shot my dad in the back. I'm gonna give you
The courtesy you never gave him.
Turn around.
I was told to choose between your family and mine.
That was my option.
I chose mine.
Go to hell.
Linc, you don't have to do this.
Mahone!
Hey! my truck!
Stop!
What are we gonna do now?
Previous on Prison Break
we leave tonight
you have a warrant out for your arrest
you are not going anywhere
everything's dark
stop, or we'll shoot
stop
we have an escape in progress
we have an escape
staus?
no other prisoners have been found
bring them inside
move
have someone drag in
the bleeding pig
hurry it up
nothing
you're sure?
absolutely
it's son of bitch  so is out
are you certain?
absolutely
it's empty
did you finish the count?
just finishing now, sir
sir... we are four short
faster. we're losing them
he just started shouting
to get off the bus
how would you describe the suspect?
well, he was tall...
more than six feet
what nationality?
american
he spoke English
if you saw him, would you recognize him?
yes, of course
come on. let's go
over here
towards the beach
i could've sworn
they were headed in this direction
give me the binoculars
do you see any boats?
not a one
...where the hell are they?
i want men covering five kilometers
both east and west and check-points
on all coastal roads--
every vehicle is to be searched
contact the general...
i need more men sent to me at once
What kind of man doesn't
take care of his family?
Not a good one.
Please let me go...
they are waiting on me.
He's done
What about him?
He's even worse off.
What the hell is he still doing here?
Unless it's for murder
get him out of here!
What is this?
I guess this is where we say goodbay
Think I am going to let you just walk out of here?
Linc, think about what you are doing