Previously on Prison Break...
They refer to it as "Scylla.
" It's like the company's black book.
What's that?
Wireless hard drive that swallows up
any electronic data within ten feet of it.
And the information embedded in Scylla?
If we can get close enough...
it's ours.
If Scylla was like a pizza, all we got's a slice.
So Scylla isn't one card, it's six.
They killed myoy.
I need to find out who did it.
?????????????
Hello?
Cole Pfeiffer, Gregory White here.
I'll see you at GATE first thing tomorrow.
And I will personally hand you your bonus check.
Sara Tancredi's somewhere safe, ist she, Bruce?
So tell me, where is Sara?
Los Angeles?
Good job.
It wasn't a meeting between two Scylla cardholders, Agent Self.
It was a meeting between all six cardholders.
So now we know who has the other five cards.
Hey.
You got anything off the video?
It's a camera phone 50 feet away.
So, it's pretty grainy.
Still printing.
You ever been on one of those?
Yeah.
I was still drinking at the time,
so I don't remember much.
Um, told I was a lot of fun.
You?
No.
Not a lot of yachts where I'm from.
I always kind of wanted to live on one.
I thought it'd be nice to have
the ocean as my front yard.
The ocean is your front yard.
What's wrong with the SS Minnow back there?
Nothing.
You really want to drop that thing in the water
someday and sail off to parts unknown?
Yeah, why not?
As long as it's you and me.
I like the sound of that.
SUCRE: Yo, papi.
We got something.
One day.
What've we got?
Uh, we got a, we got a license plate.
It's a printout from the camera phone.
BELLICK: The numbers are fuzzy, though.
The whole damn thing's fuzzy.
Forget the numbers.
What's that next to the plate?
Looks like a sticker.
SUCRE: DMV?
That's a flag.
SARA: It's a diplomatic plate.
The Six Ps, guys.
When I supervised 32 COs back at Fox River
it was the Six Ps made it happen.
Can you blow it up?
I need to see more detail.
I'm already on it.
Prior, Planning, Prevents, Piss-Poor, Pformance.
How about you quit shaking your ass
and say what's on your mind?
The second step.
Deciphering the cards.
The break-in.
We need to plan.
Agent Self will provide that information.
You worked with Whistler.
Didn't he say anything about a location?
Wasn't that in his bird book?
Which T-Bag has.
If he made it out of Sona alive.
Finding where the break-in is doesn't mean anything if we don't have the cards.
ROLAND: Here's your flag.
MAHONE: Algeria?
Turkey.
Find out where the Turkish Consul is in town.
You know what?
Get with the program.
You're up.
Uh, his name's Erol Tabak.
Consulate is downtown.
Yeah, but we can't get into the consulate.
We can follow him from there.
SARA: Michael.
I'm gonna stay back and work on the video.
Okay.
One day.
Cole Pfeiffer.
How are ya?
Cole.
Pfeiffer.
P-f-e-i-f-e...
Damn it!
Cole Pfeiffer.
How are ya?
No.
Call me Cole, please.
P-f-e-i-f...
e...
Damn!
Breaking down the captivity of negativity.
That's what we're doing here.
That's what we're doing here at GATE.
And I would encourage all of you to...
P-f-e-i-f-f-e-r.
f-e-r.
P-f-e-i-f...
P-f-e-i-f-f-e-r.
SUCRE: What do diplomats usually do?
Not a whole lot, but they park anywhere they want.
Put this on the dash.
Can we get any closer?
LINCOLN: That's our car.
Yeah?
We're copying.
He's got the card on him.
SUCRE: Hell yes.
LINCOLN: That's the wife?
Sign me up.
You lost it.
How?
Dude, I don't know what to tell you other than you lost it.
It's gone, man.
MICHAEL: We lost it.
SUCRE: Wha!
How did we lose him?
We're right next to him.
He's not the cardholder.
She is.
We gotta get out ohere now before we get made.
Come on, go! Go!
【XTM 字幕组】
http://cnX264.com 荣誉出品
sync: baozi  虾米
《Prison Break》S04 E04
You know what we've got in common, right?
What?
We both live in the real world as opposed to these other knuckleheads.
So that whole prior planning thing you were talking about,
if you got something on your mind and no one else is interested,
you just run it by me, okay?
And we'll just leave it at that.
All right.
Hello?
Sara?
Hey, it's Don Self.
Listen, um, I have sbad news.
Bruce Bennett was found dead in his apartment this morning.
I'm sorry.
Lisa, come in.
This will be quick.
I know you're on a schedule.
The value of the kip is at ten right now.
I'll let you know as soon as it reaches 15.
At that point, you'll have to leave immediately.
I have my bags with me.
I could go now.
Don't you have that event tonight?
Yes.
But I...
It's important to keep up appearances.
Not arouse suspicion.
Fine.
I have no doubt in your leadership abilities, Lisa, but...
Good.
Nor do I.
So I won't keep you any longer.
Please...
be safe.
There she is.
All right, do what you gotta do.
Be next to her for two minutes so the device can copy the card.
I'll get it.
Take a seat.
See the three suits?
Forming a triangle around her?
Those are private contractors.
The Company would only do that for the inner circle.
We're not getting anywhere near that lady.
Not today.
LINCOLN: Great.
What's wrong?
Hey, Teddy.
Well, if it ain't the Brothers Grim.
Easy, Linc. Remember, we need him.
What are you doing in Los Angeles?
I was thinking about maybe getting me a career in pictures.
???????????/
Hey! If anyone'sgot a right to be pissed-- it's me.
You put me out to pasture back in Panama.
Left me for dead.
Which makes it the third time, I believe. So, congratulations,
you got yourself a turkey
. Where's the bird book?
Bird book?
Where's the book?!
Ooh, look who's looking, pretty.
Look who's looking.
I don't thinkthe two of you are supposed to be carousing
around the Angel City any more than I am.
You don't know what you've gotten yourself into,
Teddy. But if you don't want to find out,
you're gonna tell us where that bird book is.
You're gonna let me go right now
or all of us are going down together.
Your choice.
Linc, come on.
WYATT: Tancredi. T-A-N...
C-R-E-D-I.
Make it a buckshot across the grid.
35-mile radius.
If she or any of those other names come up, call me.
FEMALE VOICE: Confirmed.
Where are you?
Los Angeles.
Trailing Dr. Sara Tancredi.
I ask for the knights, you're chasing a pawn.
She's irrelevant.
Not to Scofield.
If anyone knows what rock he's hiding under, it's her.
What about Gretchen?
I'm having her softened up,
but I question the merit of keeping her alive.
I don't think you should allow...
She must know something.
She lives until she talks.
Now, I have something else I need you to do for me.
It seems a former employee is looking into Scylla.
T-Bag's in town?
Yeah, but we lost him.
He could be anywhere by now.
It's not where he is. It's what he's doing.
He blew this whole thing for all of us.Where's Sara?
The boat.
SARA: Of course
it's my fault that he's dead.
- It's not true.
-  We both know it is.
I shouldn't have called him.
I knew that. I should never have reached out to him.
I shouldn't have involved him in any...
Bennett chose to help you.
The Company killed him, not you.
Listen to me, Sara. This is...
This is not your fault.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Hi. Can I help you?
With that smile, you already have.
I'm Cole Pfeiffer.
Mr. Pfeiffer, uh, welcome to Los Angeles.
No, please.
Call me Cole.
Mr. White is looking forward to meeting with you,
uh, Cole, but he's just running a few minutes late.
Precisely how few minutes are we talking about?
Oh, it shouldn't take long.
You can have a seat right over there.
Oh. Ooh, I almost forgot.
You already have a message.
I do?
Mm-hmm. Mr. Xing called.Twice.
I guess your reputation precedes you.
I guess so.
Don Self.
When did they find the body?
This morning.
They're saying it was a suicide,
but you and I know better.
So I need to ask you something very important, okay?
Did Bruce Bennett know where you are now?
I don't know.
Because if he did,
there's a damn good chance
that the Company does now, too.
Okay? So you need to work double time.
Get some eyes in the back of your head, you understand?
Look, I appreciate the motivational speech,
but how about you figure out where we have to break in
so we can
decode those cards?
I've, I've got
some guys doing some digging, okay?
Actually, you might have two.
Well, what are you... what are you talking about?
His name is Theodore Bagwell.
He was with us in Panama,
and now he's here in Los Angeles,
and he has a book that used to belong to Whistler, and Mahone thinks...
Mahone thinks this book has a plan for the break-in.
You've got to be kidding me.
I wish I were.
You've reached Jasper Potts.
Leave a message.
Hey, it's me. Listen, I need that information we talked about, like,
yesterday, you understand?
Call me back. Call... me... back
as soon as possible.
MAHONE: Lisa Tabak. Wife of the Turkish Consul.
Married four years, children-- none.
Listed as the logistician in the executive profile for SENSA,
a privately funded think tank with offices in D.C,
New York, Chicago and Los Angeles.
Yeah, and the only thing
I want to know about this chick is her schedule.
What she's doing, where she's going.
We might not have that kind of time.
This morning, when she first got out of the car,
she had a suitcase.
Well, let's check the airlines, match her name against
any departing flights.
Maybe she's already gone.
I don't think so.
If she's going anywhere today,
it's gonna be on the red eye.
According to this press release, Lisa Tabak is being honored
at some charity shindig downtown.
Well, that's great. That's where we'll get her.
What's the benefit for?
She's the top donor of an organization
called Eagles and Angels.
Eagles and Angels?
You've heard of it?
When a police officer dies in the line of duty,
he's an Eagle.
The ones he leaves behind are Angels.
That's a benefit for the Association of Law Enforcement.
If you're gonna get near her,
it's gonna be with about half the cops in L.A.
Jasper, where the hell you been?
Thinking. SELF: Thinking?
Come on, the only thing you should be thinking about
is what I asked you to get for me.
Did you find the location?
Yes, yes, and don't say anything else, okay?
I heard clicks yesterday on my phone.
All right, settle down, all right? I'm coming to you.
It doesn't matter, you know, 'cause you're never gonna be able to get in,
not where they're keeping it.
I should have never helped you out. I...
Just relax, okay? I'm coming to you right now.
Think they're strong enough?
Together they should be.
That's everything on the list.
You sure we have to steal them?
It's the one thing we need that we can't get at a store,
buddy, so yes, we got to steal them.
We'll get everything else and meet you there.
All right.
Look, um,
you gonna be okay?
Yeah. I just need time.
Right.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
WHITE: I am so sorry
I'm not going to be around next week
to see you in action, Cole,
but you'll be in good hands with Andy here.
I have got to catch a flight to San Francisco,
but I just wanted to say how thrilled we are to have you here,
and hopefully, some of the rest of the sales force can learn a thing or two.
Uh, we'll settle up that check when I get back, all right?
Uh, remember, don't call it Frisco.
They hate that up there.
True.
Well, why don't I show you to your office, Cole?
- Okeydoke.
-  I'm sorry.
I didn't see anywhere in your paperwork
that you were... handicapped.
Otherwise, I would have made the necessary adjustments
to your work space.
Andy, I like to think of myself as...
handicapable.
Right. Yeah.
Well, here you are.
Right, right.
So this is where I'm gonna be doing my, uh...
my work, right here in this, uh...
...office.
That's right.
So, I'd better be rolling up my sleeves, then.
You know, Cole, I-I got to tell you.
I'm still a little amazed at somebody
I've never even seen at a convention
or seminar just falls from the sky
and shatters all of our sales records.
When you believe in GATE like I do,
it ain't that hard to sell.
There you go.
Well.
And here's your corner office as requested.
Welcome to the team.
All righty, then. Thank you.
One...
22...
...B.
Oh.
Hello, Sara.
ROLAND: Hey, Sara, where you going?
BARTENDER: What can I get you?
Club soda, please.
BARTENDER: How many years?
Sorry?
In the program. How many years
have you been sober?
About three years and three months.
Good for you.
Yeah, it doesn't feel good today.
But I'll take the high five for cracking the big question.
Which is?
Is life a tragedy,
or is there...
...hope?
You tell me.
Double bourbon, neat.
Just pour it.
Cheers, honey.
Over here.
Eagles and Angels, with contributions from the Company.
This thing's supposed to start in five minutes.
- Excuse me, sorry.
- No problem.
Where do you work out of?
That's one of my guys up there.
MICHAEL: I'm sorry, I just...
Oh, sure, sure.
Of course.
SARA: I've known him my whole life.
He was a very close person to my family.
It's always the good ones.
MAN: You ain't gonna drink that?
Honey,
the Good Shepard is here to ease your pain.
Ronald Winston Shepard-- you can call me Shep.
Shep, I really don't feel like talking right now.
You've been talking to her.
Leave her alone, okay?
Pardon me.
BARTENDER: Go on.
When I was 13, I had to go see Annie, the musical,
but my mom had passed away earlier that year
and my dad had agreed to take me and...
I was all ready in my new dress,
and, uh, and I knew every word of this thing.
And my dad called from work,
and he said he wasn't going to make it.
That wasn't the first time.
And I remember feeling like I was floating...
like I was the only person in the whole world.
And Bruce came.
He showed up to take me and...
And after, he took me home, and he said
that if I ever needed him, he'd be there for me.
And a month ago, I needed him, and I called him.
And he died for it.
Just a sec.
What would he want you to do?
Let me do you a favor.
????????
LIEUTENANT BERNITZ: Uh, before we sit down to eat,
I'd like to welcome everyone
to the 15th Annual Eagles and Angels Benefit.
We all know why we're here tonight,
so I'd like to begin with a moment of silence
to renew our dedication to the law
and to honor those whose lives were cut short
by their fearless pursuit of justice.
They will truly be missed.
BERNITZ: Thank you.
Enjoy your dinner.
I've been made, guys.
Just get the hard copy.
Here we go.
We copped him.
Hi, my condolences.
Yes?
The kip's at 15.
I understand.
I'm very sorry, but I'm going to have to leave.
Yeah. I'm so sorry. Yes.
What's she doing?
She's leaving.
I'm... so sorry.
???????
Yeah?
I've been made. Meet me out back.
Hey.
?????????
I don't know who you think I am, but...
I know who you are. Now put the gun down.
Slowly.
Three. Copy?
Move.
Move it.
MICHAEL: Time to get the device.
That's far enough.
Why don't you just call one of the cops?
I work for the Company, Burrows. We don't need cops.
Got any last words?
Yeah?
We got a problem. I just killed one of the guards.
Let's go now!
No. We don't have it yet.
Do what you got to do.
We got to get rid of the body.
Let them find him.
What?
Wait for Mahone.
Gretchen.
How's my girl?
It seems your friend Whistler wasn't the only one looking into Scylla.
You know anything about that?
No.
You never know anything, do you?
You have nothing to do with any of this.
Scofield, Burrows...
- You don't know who...
- No.
You can't keep lying to me.
No!
I don't know!
You look so...
...damn easy.
I can make this a lot harder.
Yes.
WOMAN: A credit card belonging to Bruce Bennett
was just used at a bar in San Pedro.
MAHONE: Excuse me.
Excuse me.
we have a DOA outside,
I believe it's one of your men.
You need to come with me.
Excuse me?
No one's leaving here until you make an ID.
Please.
Mathers.
Stay with Mrs. Tabak.
Uh, what happened? I have a plane to catch.
I understand. We'll make this fast.
Officer Mathers, he'll wait with you.
Please. Stay with her.
If you could just wait with me, ma'am.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Should only take a few minutes.
???????
This is a nice memorial.
I very much respect the sacrifices you men make.
There's a lot of bad people out there.
Officer Mathers, you, um...
you have something.
Your, your nose is bleeding.
One day...
Excuse me.
I'm looking for this woman.
Sara Tancredi.
You okay?
???????
Hell, yes.
It's nothing. Travel safely.
Mrs. Tabak, we've got to leave.
Ma'am, now.
I'm telling you, I haven't seen her.
You're sure?
Oh, look out, fellas!
It's the pigs! Run!
Shut up, wiseass.
You're sure you got the whole thing?
A hundred percent.
Where's Sara?
It's not my turn to watch her.
What the hell are we gonna do? Someone must've seen us.
SELF: Don't worry, it's handled.
PAD MAN: Politically motivated?
???????????
Tip came in to LAPD.
The assailant thought the consul was at the event.
Lisa's bodyguard got in the way.
Did Lisa make her flight?
Yes, General.
What do you got?
I had a guy.
I did. I had a guy.
He, uh, was an informant.
Actually, he used to work for the Company
for about 11 years until he
turned against them and decided to help me.
He said he had the location we needed.
But I, uh...
found him dead in his apartment today.
I'm sorry.
First Bennett, now your guy, huh?
Yeah.
They're closing in on us.
There's no doubt about it,
and now, I'm, uh...
empty-handed.
And now I have no idea where we need
to break into.
We keep moving forward, Agent Self.
Nothing changes.
- No matter what.
- Right.
Okay.
Regardless of what happens, I, uh,
I like your style, Scofield.
You need anything else, Mr. Cole?
I'm all right, little lady.
What was your plan, Mr. Whistler?
What was your plan?
FENG HUAN: Shan Xing...
Cole Pfeiffer did not arrive for our meeting.
So you don't have Scylla?
Next time, Shan Xing.
I'll be in Los Angeles if anyone needs me.
Number two down, on to number three.
We manage to get anything off Lisa Tabak's phone?
I don't know.
I didn't pick up anything but the card.
I want to thank you
for what you did back there.
I need you to do something for me.
Yeah, doesn't everybody.
I'm looking for the man who killed my son.
What do you need?
Here's the police report.
I need you to get into the FBI database
and find a profile.
This man is a professional assassin.
He's African-American, six foot, four.
About 220 pounds.
That's for your eyes only.
Hi.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Well, I was worried. Where are you?
Let me come get you.
No, it's okay. I'm almost home.
Um, listen...
You're what's keeping me going right now.
And you're all I have left, and that scares me.
I just want to be together.
I know the circumstances are a little less than ideal,
but we are together.
You're here, I'm here.
It's not "one day" anymore, it's, um...
it's today.
Well, why don't you come back
and, uh, we'll make some dinner
and maybe find a little time for ourselves.
Okay, I'll be right there.