Previously on Weeds...
- What are these?
- Snacks.
- Heavy snacks.
- This is my cousin Amparo.
- What's wrong?
- Migraine.
You got too much stress now.
This will unwind it.
Ayahuasca's like 30 years
of psychotherapy in one night.
The plant teaches you
what you need to learn.
You know.
No more hiding.
She's losing her shit.
The clock strikes 18, and I'm done.
- Do you party?
- They really want to have sex.
Then go do it.
This is the woman
your depressed amigo searches for?
- That's the one.
- We will help the sad, tall,
angry, baby man find her.
You're as beautiful as I remember.
- You take too many drugs.
- Mostly Xanax and coke.
You need to keep
better care of yourself.
Cocaine?
Coca.
If you don't deal with this,
I will call your mother.
I lie to myself all the time.
I make compromises. I tell myself
I'm not doing harm when I am.
I so am.
- Do you see her?
- There's no one there.
Of course not.
Weeds - 4x11
Head Cheese
Transcript : SadGeezer
Synchro : Macanto, mpm, golgi
These pop-tarts are good.
Are these pop-tarts sugar-free?
The regular pop-tarts aren't.
I don't think they make
sugar-free pop-tarts.
I'm not allowed to have these, then.
My mom doesn't let me have these.
Then this is a really big day for you.
Neither of your parents has a problem
with your sleeping at some...
boy's house they've never met?
They're totally cool with it.
- How bohemian.
- No, they're American.
I'd like to hear more
about this science project.
It's sort of like an experiment.
Biology.
You could say that.
Fascinating. Reproduction...
Disease.
I assume the presentation
you three are working on
will deal with those things,
in addition to volcanoes
and wind.
Where were you last night?
I'm an adult, Shane.
You're a child.
What happened here last night?
- Got to go.
- Bye, Shane.
What was that?
Did you have sex?
I'm 13 years old.
Exactly. You're 13 years old.
They're 13 years old.
- They're in my grade.
- That's too early, Shane.
You're too...
- Fuck you, Judah!
- I can handle it.
Well, I can't.
I don't want you seeing
either of those scary,
little sluts again.
Quit pretending to be a mom.
Good morning.
- You okay?
- No! I'm not okay! Do I look okay?!
How did this happen?
You had boys.
Morning, señorita.
Señor Doug?
Dónde?
- Is this your house?
- This is my place, babe.
You passed out in the van,
and I carried you up, like a bride.
I tried waking you for a little nooky,
but you sleep like a corpse.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. I just...
I can't believe you're really here.
You are so totally beautiful.
You are very kind.
I'm kind, and you're pretty.
Together, we're kind and pretty
and nice and beautiful.
Señor Doug?
- What are you doing?
- I want to make the sexo with you.
- But we do not know each other.
- Let's get down to it.
I am not some piruja.
We must take time.
You must win my affection.
Okay, I hear you.
Get to know each other, win your heart.
Sí. Thank you.
Can I just see one boob?
The next two weeks of your life
are going to be
some of the most difficult
you have ever faced.
All the pain that you've been numbing
for years with your substance addiction
will hit you at once,
and it will be excruciating.
But know this... you're not alone.
The people next to you
will become your best friends.
So get ready everyone...
because you are all about
to go through hell together.
Give it up!
Let's go to hell!
- Why is this locked?
- We're closed.
Who told you we were closed?
The sexy, scary, beardy one.
Don't you think it's conspicuous
if the whole mall is having a sale
but we're closed?
I do what I'm told by men
with semiautomatic weapons.
I'm a total bottom that way.
You look tired.
Love tired?
- Sex tired?
- Tired tired. I'm just tired.
So, what's the haps in here?
Look. The crates again.
Yes.
The crates from America
going into Mexico.
You look tired.
What's in the crates?
Maybe you should go and lay down.
I'm just gonna take a little peek.
No.
- 'Cause if I peek...
- I'll shoot you.
- You're not gonna shoot me.
- It's my job.
It's your job to threaten to shoot me,
not to actually shoot me.
That's not pot.
Everything's fine, Sanjay.
Go back to your book.
- What the fuck?
- Exactly. What the fuck?
It's supposed to be a pot tunnel.
I know you ain't as slow you're acting.
It's a tunnel.
There's no magical "weed only" sign
at the entrance.
Cut the shit.
- When did the floodgates open?
- When the water got here.
- Head cheese sandwich.
- 6 inch or foot long?
Foot long all the way.
- Enjoy.
- You know it.
- Head cheese sandwich, please.
- Six inch or foot long?
Six inch.
There's no meat
anywhere in there, right?
'Cause if meat even touches the weed,
I can't smoke it.
- I'm vegan.
- No worries.
- That's $240.
- Bargain.
- $240.
- I gave you $5.
You ordered the head cheese sandwich?
I did. Everybody seems to like them.
You may actually have gotten
the wrong sandwich.
- Let me check.
- Yeah. I gave you the wrong sandwich.
- My bad.
- And we just ran out of bread.
You got a stack of sandwiches there.
Those were preordered.
What's going on here?
Sir, you're too fat.
You fattist.
I'm gonna write you up on Chowhound.
Your mom's a rude bitch.
Nice save, Mom.
Celia, we're waiting
for your promise partner, Barry.
Any idea where he is?
I saw him at breakfast.
What?
Oh, right.
"I'm responsible for him,
and he's responsible for me
"'cause I can't do this...
"alone.
I do this as a we."
So that means...
I'll be right back.
Promise partner.
What are you... doing?
Where did you get that?
17 years as a commercial pilot.
I think I know
how to sneak shit past security.
And I can't take these places sober,
you know?
Therapy, bonding,
all the fucking yapping.
Hey, this ain't my first time
at the fair, okay?
I've been to Betty Ford,
Cottonwood, New Days,
Fresh Start in Albuquerque.
That place is like a whorehouse.
18-hour layovers in Bangkok
are nothing compared
to the saunas at Fresh Start.
You're a pilot?
Do you... fly like this?
Coked to the gills. You don't want
to fly with me when I'm sober.
I crash, we all crash.
Remember the Trump shuttle?
That was my first gig, right?
I couldn't afford blow.
Fucking Nodoz and Dexatrim.
That is no way to live.
I love the moment right before,
you know,
when you're still looking at it.
I love when it goes up your nose
and you feel fucking awesome.
Here.
I'm gonna help you.
Barry, I am your partner.
We can do this.
Clean and sober.
Come on.
Fuck off!
I was gonna share this with you.
- Now you're bumming me out.
- Give me the straw.
- Give it to me!
- That's my...
I snuck this in up my ass, okay?
Give it to me!
You can't!
She was fucking forcing me
to snort coke!
You got to help me.
It's bullshit.
I spent 25 years with a woman
who didn't put out.
I deserve some.
- It's been one day.
- And a half.
- Right.
- I don't know what to do.
I mean, it's been forever
since I had to court a chick.
And let's face it...
getting laid in the'70s was easy.
I drove a Camaro.
Oh, man, I wish I grew up then.
I got totally shafted...
Fucking AIDS.
Ruined everyone's fun.
- I thought you got laid all the time.
- Yeah, but I had to use condoms.
Andy, I smuggled her here.
I think that merits some cockamole
on her faceadilla.
Possibly.
But...
- What do you really know about her?
- Not much.
Maybe I should buy her
some scented body wash.
Look, she's probably scared.
I mean,
she's totally out of her element.
Make her feel comfortable.
- How do I do that?
- Talk to her.
- OK. Talk to her. About what?
- About anything.
On the way over here,
we had great talks.
She grew up in an orphanage.
Start there.
- She's an orphan?
- Yeah.
Sweet. Daddy issues.
Age difference should work in my favor.
- Hasta luego.
- Thanks.
Finding God?
God finds me.
- You don't look well.
- No.
No. I'm not well.
That ayahuasca really fucked me up.
You, however, look fantastic.
I have a charity function.
But my love says we need to talk...
So...
charity waits.
What's coming through the tunnel?
What comes through the tunnel?
I am told by the people I work with,
the people you work with,
that boxes come through that tunnel.
Right.
Weed, heroin,
cocaine,
guns. Stop me if I make a mistake.
- Boxes.
- Girls.
- No. No girls.
- There was a girl.
Guillermo brought her in.
He said she was his cousin.
I don't get into details.
I really don't.
There are guns coming
through the tunnel into your city.
Where are they going?
They go to the people who want them.
And you're okay with that?
It's how I build schools,
hospitals.
It's how you provide for your family.
Yeah.
She wasn't Guillermo's cousin.
Charity calls.
It's not enough...
your charity.
Go home.
Get some sleep.
Eat with your children,
take a walk by the water.
Nothing is ever enough.
But we live...
and we try.
- Got a proposition for you.
- Can it wait till after my bath?
Guess not.
The cheese shop is really taking off.
Well, people love cheese.
People love my weed.
- The proposition?
- I'm getting to it.
Okay, get to it faster.
Okay.
The problem is space.
I need more space.
- You and me both.
- Secure space,
where people can't wander in.
Larger,
safer, away from where I sell, right?
- Right.
- Okay.
So, here it is.
We're partners.
You stake me.
I find a place to grow.
Been there.
Done that.
Fucked it up. Twice.
We don't have to make
the same mistakes this time.
We've learned.
We've learned to not do it anymore.
Lisa told me you would say no.
Let me think about it.
- That's all I'm asking.
- Good.
That's all I'm doing.
What was it like?
Confusing. Brisk.
Messy.
I don't know.
- My mom hit me.
- You told your mom?
Have I taught you nothing?
Tell her what she wants to hear,
and then you do what you want.
How's your mom doing in rehab?
Fine, I guess.
I can't visit till she's detoxed.
Where did she get the coke?
Probably the maternity front.
What?
- You're kidding, right?
- No.
My mom was in jail,
and then suddenly she's free
and working for your mom.
- Retail?
- You think my mom's dealing cocaine?
I think they're both dealing.
But your mom's a control freak,
and mine's weak and addiction-prone.
Good times, huh?
How great would it be
if we were both 18?
- So, you gonna dump them?
- Why?
'Cause the slap-happy drug dealer
told me to?
Screw that.
Simone, Harmony, this is Izzy.
Does she party?
Depends on the party.
Are you sure
there is no border patrol here?
As long as you don't walk outta the surf
with 10 other wet Mexicans,
you'll be fine.
So, Andy tells me
you grew up in an orphanage.
I prefer not to talk about it.
Then what should we talk about?
We should talk about you.
I grew up in the Valley,
married my high-school sweetheart,
it didn't work out.
- Divorced?
- No. Not yet.
- You're married?
- Technically. Gotta sign the papers.
Well, why do you not sign them?
I'm on the run.
But it's nothing.
Just a little embezzlement.
- You steal?!
- Borrow.
I was gonna pay it back.
- When?
- Someday.
Hey, what the heck?
You wrecked our castle.
It wasn't a castle.
It was a... lump of sand.
You're a bad man.
You're a... bad castle builder.
Little shit.
You do not like children?
I like my four.
Well, three of them.
You have four children?
When do you see them?
When I can trust they won't tell
my cunt ex-wife where I am.
- What's the matter?
- I am...
I am not feeling so well.
Perhaps we should stop talking.
Okay. I'm cool with that.
Let the silence bring us closer.
Yeah, I can dig it.
I was weak. I was dishonest.
I let the plane fly me.
If it wasn't for Celia Hodes,
I'd be back in the air in 30 days
snorting lines off the dashboard
and jamming blow up my urethra
so I could fuck Paula,
the 57-year-old flight attendant.
I wanna apologize to you, Celia.
Thank you, Barry, for your share.
We're all like one big...
wonderful, dysfunctional family,
and I love you guys.
We're all working through it together.
I mean, I never really had a family.
I mean, I have a family,
but they're not like you guys.
Celia, can we borrow you
for just a minute?
Yeah. Sure.
Hurry back, okay? 'Cause I need you.
And everybody needs you.
We ran your insurance info a few times,
and it's not exactly accurate.
- What seems to be the problem?
- You don't have any.
The policy number you gave us
belongs to an individual
who is deceased...
and Korean.
Listen,
this is going really well.
And I'm only on my second step.
I am so proud of me.
We're proud, too.
We have no intention of abandoning you.
Our sister facility across town
has a bed available,
and they're holding it just for you.
No, I belong here.
Barry needs me.
Don't you have a work program?
I could do...
dishes, landscaping.
I'm sorry, Celia.
What we pay our help in a year
won't cover a week here.
Discharge paperwork is in the folder.
I'll need your signature on all pages,
and you can drop it
at the front desk on your way out.
Best of luck with your recovery.
We're going to need your room vacant
within the hour.
Doug around?
He go to buy some mouthwash,
some toilet paper, and some tweezers.
Oh, cool.
Right.
So, how's it going... things with Doug?
Just okay?
He is a terrible man.
What?
Come on.
- He's a great guy.
- He is a criminal.
- He's an accountant.
- A thief
who has abandoned his wife and family
and wants to make me his whore.
A CPA with legal problems
who's going through a divorce
and is wildly in love with you.
He has warts on his genitals.
Yeah, I got nothing for that.
Please, Andy,
help me.
These are for you, my love.
Look how thoughtful he is.
This is a good man.
Yeah, over there.
Bust it open.
I could use the hand lotion.
Here you go.
Something to put in the piñata.
You say $20 each.
I say $20 total.
Don't pull that Mexican shit with me.
Look, honey.
I got us a bed.
That's when I took that crack pipe,
broke it off, stuck it in his neck.
Said, "I'm not using this
except to kill you, motherfucker."
Like half a rock is worth getting fucked
with a mannequin leg, shoe still on it?
Fuck that.
Anyway, that's all I got for now.
Thanks for listening.
Ain't we fancy.
You're gonna have to take
that fucking attitude out the door.
We don't play that shit in here.
I'm gonna have
that fucking combination changed.
- I'm just putting money in the safe.
- Yeah, then do it.
More cousins?
Yeah, that's right.
Are you girls okay?
- I'm not seeing this.
- You're catching on.
About fucking time.
Day's over.
Go home.
Thank you for coming.
I know you're busy.