Previously on "weeds"...
what was it like?
Confusing, brisk, messy.
How's your mom doing in rehab?
I can't visit till she's detoxed.
- Chilea?
- Celia.
Oh, ain't we fancy.
You're gonna have to take that fucking
attitude out the door right now, you hear me?
Head cheese sandwich.
Six inch or foot long?
Foot long all the way, bro.
Enjoy.
It's her, man.
She didn't get fat, did she?
No. She's beautiful.
Se—or doug? W-what are you doing?
I want to make the sexo with you, baby.
But we do not know each other.
Okay, I hear you. Can
I just see one boob?
Go get miss hodes a glass of water.
Now, agent shlatter.
Deliver me guillermo garcia gomez.
I don't know of any gomez.
If I did once, I don't anymore.
Not what I hear.
What the fuck?
Exactly. What the fuck? This
is supposed to be a pot tunnel.
It's a tunnel.
There's no magical "weed
only" sign at the entrance.
Cut the shit.
Guillermo.
Garcia...
gomez.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Weeds
Season04 Episode12
I asked you toonome alE.
Agent shlatter's my partner.
And so your word is shit.
My word is shit?
You called. I'm here.
Gomez.
I need assurances.
What kind of assurances?
Everything I ask for, I get.
I'm not your daddy.
Hey, I'm not fucking around here.
This information I have,
very few people have it.
I'm listening.
It's gonna look like it came from me.
It cannot look like it came from me.
More important than anything
you do with this information,
it must not look like it came from me.
Okay.
You make a bust, I do
not go down with it.
My people do not go down with it.
- Still, it never comes back to me.
- Fine.
My name never appears
on any piece of paper.
No one ever speaks my name.
- This meeting never happened.
- Done.
I will not be fleeing.
My family will not be going
into witness protection
because there will be no reason for
us to go into witness protection.
You're getting repetitive.
There's a tunnel.
So, I go to see one of my kids in the foster
home, and I'm beggin' him to forgive me.
******
"Who are you, lady?I ain't your kid."
I'm thinkin', "my own boy
doesn't even recognize me."
That's the saddest thing ever.
But it ain'T.
The saddest thing is, I was so
fucked up, I went in the wrong house.
It was so devastating,
I miscarried right there.
Thanks for sharing. Celia?
I thought i had hit bottom.
But after hearing your stories, I
realize it could be so much worse.
The truth is,
none of you have any chance in hell of
ever pulling your lives back together,
if you even had lives to begin with.
As I have listened to your tales of
burning wreckage and shattered existence,
I realize that i am the only one
here that has any chance at all --
a chance to make amends
and to start over...
fresh.
Stupid-ass bitch.
- Andy?
- Yeah?
Hi, maria.
I'm so sorry.
No, don't be sorry. Don't be sorry.
okay, no towel. One sec.
What you doing here?
You have beein my eams.
Oh, yeah? H, yea well,dreams are weird.
Uh, I have this recurring one where
I'm playing pool with lou dobbs.
And suddenly, his big,
fat stomach opens up
and these nasty teeth grow out
of his torn, fat, marbled flesh.
Please make love to me.
Oh, n ino, can't do that.
Do you not t nktti am aractive?
Yeoh, Who locked the fuckin'
do-- you're very attractive, yeah.
I think you are attractive.
M, u but doug.
He is not the man for me. U are.
Okay.
You are excited.
Nono. It's jndt wiy out.
I do not think it is the wind.
Lou dobbs. Lou dobbs.
Lou dobbs. Ou dobbs.
Lou dobbs. Lou dobbs. Lou dobbs!
No. We're going to a wedding.
It's casual, but
evening casual, you know?
I was thinking something
with a drop waist.
Kind of tory burch?
Exactly.
- I'll help them, sanjay.
- Well, I got it.
No, I need you to
redress the mannequins.
Well, it's about time. Can I do a theme?
Yeah. Go for it.
Um, the dressing rooms
are back this way.
Just let me know if you
need help with anything.
I'm thinking shades
of blue for the window.
And I'm thinking that that man
you just helped is gay, gay, gay!
The guy in the couple?
Not a couple. There's weirdness.
I'd say maybe she's his surrogate,
but he called her "wife."
It's a puzzler.
They're a nice, married
couple having a baby.
They're not a couple.
You need to get your gaydar checked.
Uh, listen, breeder, my
gaydar is never wrong.
That man hearts cock.
Clearly, he hearted her
vagina at some point.
You ever hear of in vitro?
So what? Religious and societal pressures
have forced him to live the lie of domesticity?
Or maybe... he's a cop.
- What?
- Oh, that's it.
He's an undercover cop here
to scope us out and bust us...
and then ask me out.
All right.
Of course. That's got to be it.
Oh, I'm telling you.
Get back to your vision in blue.
Leave the nice couple alone.
I'm going, but know this -- no straight
man knows what a drop-waist dress is.
And if he does, he denies it.
I really do not feel
like going back to class.
Fuck class.
Shit! I think something just bit me.
Could you not blow smoke in my hair?
You should dye it black.
It would look totally cool black.
Let's break into the science
lab and get high on nitrous.
They keep it in a locked cabinet.
We could break the glass
with a fire extinguisher.
Yeah, 'cause no one would hear the sound of breaking
glass in the science lab in the middle of the afternoon.
- But I want to get high.
- Me too.
- I could get some pot.
- Shane!
Mind your own business.
- Can you get it like now?
- Sure.
I'm going to class. Are you coming?
No. He's gonna hang with us.
I'm gonna hang with them.
You two are totally making
me reconsider fucking boys.
You do them once, and
they become your puppet.
She's a dyke.
In that case, she should go purple.
Her hair would look totally cool purple.
Head cheese sandwich, please.
What are you doing here?
You heard me. I want a sandwich.
Then go to subway.
They don't have the kind I want.
Neither do we.
Oh, I think you do.
Fuck off.
Come on. Just one?
I'm not giving weed
to my little brother!
You gave me a condom.
That was sex, shane. This is
drugs. Why aren't you in school?
I knew you smoked when
you were 13. I saw you.
Well, you're already stupid enough.
With that asshole danny melcher.
You were both giggling, and then he stood up
on our water slide and took a piss in our pool.
You saw that?
Why do you think I didn't
go in the pool for a year?
Look, I'm not gonna sit here
and say "don't do drugs."
'Cause that would make
you a total hypocrite.
But... I'm not gonna
be your fuckin' dealer.
Hey, does anybody work here?
Be right out.
I'll give you 300 bucks.
Go back to school, shane.
Sorry about that.
Do you know what a barcarole is?
I do not.
It's a boat song.
From the days when men
serenaded women in boats.
You got a thing for boats.
The finest barcarole ever written
-- and this is not my opinion.
It is generally agreed
upon by men of substance --
is the one you're hearing right now.
Who are the girls?
Melia, cybelle,
adelita -- my daughters.
No pictures of mommy?
She's remarried now.
Lives in france.
They're all there.
You don't get to see them much?
Over christmas, we're
going skiing in whistler.
This picture wasn't here before.
I hid it.
It was a strange thing for me to do.
You make me do things
I wouldn't usually do.
Where are you?
What?
You're in your head and not here.
No.
I'm -- I'm here.
No, I'm here.I --
I want to tell you something.
There were more girls in
the tunnel. I know that.
You do?
It is the business of
dark-hearted people.
And you and i are not dark-hearted.
S girlwier nev hrcome
theough t tagnel ai oh.
Do you dance?
I do.
Would you care to dance
with me, nancy botwin?
You should say, "yes"
yes.
I threw up on my prom date.
charming.
Do you love me?
Are you in love with me?
"Are you in love with me"?
That's not an answer.
You don't ask the mayor
of tijuana if he's in love.
That is just not done.
You should have said "yes."
Would you like to take a trip with me?
Christmas in whistler with the kids?
No. Sooner. And only us.
I have a job.
I manage maternity world.
I'll have to ask.
May I have a week off?
You didn't say "please!"
Please, kind employer?
You may.
Patron.
What are...
Out!
It's ....
Tell....
He says....
red licorice.
S?
Call ....
What does that mean
-- regaliz rojo?
Very bad.
Place is really coming along, yeah.
Not bad, huh?
But as soon as we figure out our next
venture, I want to get a bigger place.
I'm thinking generic
mexican pharmaceuticals.
Sell them to old people with
no insurance. What do you think?
Yeah. That's a great idea.
So, where are we eating?
Maria, any ideas?
Just, please, no more mexican food.
- cuban?
- Nothing with beans.
Andy, any ideas?
Maria and I had sex!
What?
We had sex. I'm sorry. We did.
Just once. Okay, twice.
But not two separate times.
One time.
And then again after.
You guys had sex?
It wasn't planned or
anything. It just happened.
I seduced him.
I feel like shit.
You're my friend.
I love you, man, and I'm --
it's tearing me up inside.
I had to come clean.
It's never gonna happen again, I swear.
It was a one-slash-two-time
thing -- meant nothing.
I love him.
No, no. You don't
love me. You love doug.
No. I love you, andy.
You are the best lover I have ever had.
Yeah, but doug's gonna
be even better, right?
I mean, he's so tall, and
he's so good with numbers.
She got scared, doug.
I was a fear fuck, 'cause she's so
totally into you it freaked her out.
Tell him, maria.
I'm so sorry, doug.
But sometimes, we
cannot help who we love.
Well... okay.
All right. I hear you.
I guess I'm glad you
were honest with me.
It'll never happen again.
It will. It will happen many times.
Stop saying that!
It's fine.
you're my best friend, and I love you.
And maria's right -- we
can't choose who we love.
But, maria, as much as
I've enjoyed having you,
it's a little awkward
for you to stay here now.
I understand.
You guys mind if I have a few minutes?
Of course, man. Take
all the time you need.
San diego county.
Department of immigration
and naturalization.
You did very good work, captain.
Clini--
clinique.
Tell your men I said that myself.
He'll be taken care of.
You'll be taken care of.
There's a press conference. I
should be there within the hour.
Jimmy jam, too.
- Now -- -
stay calm.
- I'll see you there.
- Bye.
You?
Many arrests.
And one of guillermo's men was killed.
- Someone talked.
- Really?
The one with the drug
problem -- your lesbian lover.
Celia? Oh, no. No way.
She's terrified of me.
You know we're not lesbians, right?
I take your word.
What about the asian homosexual?
Why are we focusing on my crew?
My people don't talk.
Oh, really?
Well, someone ratted out guillermo
when he said he wanted to kill me.
What about that guy?
We'll be looking at everyone.
Will you be looking into me?
Should I be looking into you?
Only if you don't trust me.
Reckless, impulsive, but not suicidal.
You're gonna have your own
problems because of this.
Adelante.
Patron, the car is downstairs.
It's gonna be hard for me to see you
in the short term. You understand?
Of course.
It's an inconvenience, but we'll get by.
Dig another tunnel, right, cesar?
Already digging.
Call cesar if you run into problems.
I will.
Oh, I almost forgot.
- Yes.
- "Yes"?
The answer to last night's question.
And I'm sorry for the massive
body issues I have given you.
And I'm sorry for judging
your lifestyle choice.
If you want to love the
ladies, love those ladies.
Vagina power!
I'll buy you a big
strap-on for hanukkah.
Jesus, celia.
Okay, fine. I'm sorry about that, too.
Do you forgive me?
That's it? That's all you're sorry for?
What else is there?
Apology accepted.
Okay. Dean, you're next.
Isabel, would you mind
leaving us alone for this one?
Fine. I'll be at the pool.
Okay. Here goes.
I'm sorry for being married
to you without ever once,
I mean, not even for a moment,
being sexually attracted to you.
I'm sorry every time we had sex
I fantasized about other men.
I'm sorry the sight of your naked body repulsed
me to the point that I was forced to stray.
I'm so glad this is
making you feel better.
I'm sorry I had children with you.
I'm sorry I made a life with you.
That my hatred
of you --
- all right, enough.
- No, no, no. I'm just getting started.
No, you are finished!
I could care less about
your fucking apologies.
But we happen to have a daughter out there
who hasn't seen you in over two years,
who bore the brunt of your insensitivity
and anger and who could use an apology --
a real apology, celia, a hell
of a lot more than I could.
I don't know where quinn is.
She's living in oaxaca
with a guy named rudolfo.
Rudolfo?
Go. Find quinn. Make things right.
Vaya con dios.
The....
would....
without....
of....
the ....
and....
Let....
as....
We....
To....
From....
who ....
You...
...very carefully.
Then...
...do...
Let's...
- You totally rock.
- Totally.
I see you're still alive.
You're late.
Got stuck doing interviews. Big story.
Big spotlight shining
on that maternity store.
What am I supposed to
do now? Can I go home?
Sure.
We'll arrest you tomorrow
and make it look right.
Store manager. Got to question your ass.
We'll pretend to ask, and
you'll pretend to know nothing.
And we'll pretend to
fuck up on a technicality.
Sounds like a plan.
What about sanjay?
We took him to long beach
and put him on a plane.
And guillermo?
Guillermo's going away for a
long time, and so is his crew.
There was some international confusion.
Who is guillermo's boss?
I have no idea.
Well, I hope that's the truth 'cause
we got you covered on this side.
But they play a harder game down south.
You should know that.
You make it look right, I'll be fine.
Agent shlatter, I think
it is your partner.
Maybe we let it go to voicemail.
"Informant details
location of said tunnel.
Informant confirms hour of delivery."
I'm going to ask you
again the same question.
Who is "informant"?
I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know.
He's...
Get...
Then...
I did not hear you.
One more time, amigo.
Nancy botwin.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Weeds
Season04 Episode12