Previously...
All I know is some stiletto-heeled
Mexicunt screeches at you,
and suddenly the marriage is off.
They want me to have this baby totally
off the grid, no birth certificate.
If I disappear, if the baby disappears,
nobody knows, it's Rosemary's Baby.
We gotta go to Dr. Lehman's.
I have to have this baby right now.
- My boob.
- Deal with it.
I need to ask you a question.
Are you a closer or a loser?
You're Pretty! will front you
all the products that you need
to put yourself on the road
to financial freedom.
Very impressive.
Thanks for involving me, dickhead.
- You're fucking jinx.
- You're a douchebag.
- Everybody down!
- Shit.
- Is this a joke?
- No, it's no joke, fat-ass.
You have the right to remain silent.
I need you to get the baby out of me
as soon as possible.
You're two days away
from your due date.
The father is a drug kingpin,
which could pose a problem
if he decided
to kill its mother
the minute she gives birth.
He has your eyes.
Weeds 508
A Distinctive Horn
By the Fumistes team.
lesfumistes[at]gmail.com
This is a very handsome boy.
You must have a very beautiful life.
- Do you want...
- What the fuck are doing?
Don't interrupt me, Nancy.
It's impolite.
And breaches in etiquette
make me want to
throw things.
Right, mi rey pequeño?
Do you want to know
why I've never had children?
Because you'd eat them
and children are super fattening?
Children are inconvenient.
They complicate
even the simplest things.
And they want, and they want,
and if you let them,
they'll take everything you have.
This little milk ball was a mistake.
A mistake that would end the career
of a very promising politician.
I am here to correct that mistake.
You can help me,
or you can try to stop me.
Which do you think would be better
for the handsome man
in your beautiful life?
Raylene, I need to talk to you.
There is a Q&A after the seminar,
I'm sure it'll answer
all your questions.
No one is buying this shit.
I'll be just a minute.
It's like the depression out there,
all right?
Women are pinching
their cheeks for blush.
Trannies,
they're staining their lips
with plum juice.
I cannot sell makeup
when civilization is collapsing.
Cee-Cee!
Economic downturns
are great for beauty.
Poor people wear the most makeup.
Then they're stealing it,
because I can't move anything.
And it's Celia.
Well, I'm not interested in Celia.
I'm interested in Cee-Cee.
See, Celia
is a quitter.
But Cee-Cee, she sells a life style.
Cee-Cee sells self-esteem
in small doses,
a positive reflexion
in a floor-length mirror,
confidence, happiness, sex.
Well, bully for Cee-Cee.
I am returning your shit product.
I will pay for what I used.
Doesn't work that way.
You signed a contract.
Meaning you owe for what you have
and you owe for the deliveries
you'll be receiving
for the next 12 months.
If you break the contract,
if you do not pay what you owe,
then you will go to jail
for defrauding our company.
- Is that you want?
- I will not go back there.
I will die first.
No, you will sell cosmetics first.
Come on! You just need
to remind Cee-Cee
that she is selling
the You're Pretty! dream,
so that Celia doesn't have to live
the "You're ugly and behind bars"
nightmare.
Who's pretty?
You're Pretty!
I am
the father of this child.
Not according
to your dear friend Pilar.
And the birth certificate.
She's jut protecting
my public image.
And she has a point.
Did you break an ankle
backpedaling that fast?
She threatened our son, your son.
We can leave the father's name blank
until after the election.
- Then...
- Another election and another election.
- I will speak to her.
- She was very clear.
Your name will not appear
on that birth certificate.
There'll be no public record
linking you to me,
to your son.
I will not allow
another man to sign this.
Then you sign it.
Tell that cunt to eat shit and die.
We'll live happily ever after,
the end.
It's not that easy.
Because she owns you.
But you love me.
And I love you.
- I'll have Cesar...
- That's okay.
My family's coming.
I'll go with them.
- I...
- Okay then, Mrs. Botwin.
I've got your discharge paperwork
all set up for you.
Just need a few scribbles
on a few dotted lines.
Hi, there.
I'll get you a wheelchair up here.
No, I don't...
I don't need
a wheel... thing... chair.
Now... Hospital policy, you know.
Did you get that birth certificate form
all filled out for me?
Fuck it.
Great, thank you, baby.
Why the hell should I help you?
As opposed to the many multinational
corporations you represent?
Business has been just fine.
Customers from the tea place next door
been wandering in here by accident?
- Suck it.
- Mr. Hodes, please help us.
We can't get our weed back
without a court order.
My rate is $500 an hour.
That better include a rim job.
Look, when we're back in business,
we'll lay a couple ounces on you.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you,
and fuck you.
I know what this is about.
You're pissed off
because I did not cut you in
on the pot club.
But that's just
'cause you're cursed with schmuckness.
- You're an asshole.
- Okay, look...
The truth of the matter is,
you're cursed with schmuckness.
You want my help?
Is that what you want?
Fine, I will help you.
My gosh! Thank you.
After I slam his dick
in this drawer.
- Let's go, he's not gonna help.
- No, I will.
Seriously.
But first, his dick, this drawer...
slam.
- And then we get the pot back?
- Guaranteed.
- This is bullshit.
- No, it's cool. I can do this.
- Are you out of your fucking mind?
- If I'm hard, it won't be so bad.
- Give me a second.
- Take your time.
In the meantime, Silas, I need you
to sign this power-of-attorney form.
Great, I will go
see the judge tomorrow.
Now...
Ready.
Right up in there.
You're good?
Okay, here we go, one...
two...
Nice job baby-proofing, Shane.
I got the diapers
just like you asked.
They're eco-friendly.
It got a name yet?
It's a he and for right now,
he's still baby boy Botwin.
- Do you want to hold him?
- No.
- He's your brother, get used to it.
- I thought you said it wasn't an it.
Fine, get used to him. I gotta...
take a fucking shower.
- He's kind of cute.
- Who cares?
He's probably gonna
want to play soccer.
I've to reclaim
my territory, Superfly.
You mean the piece of land
that my grandmother
left to my thieving father
to whom I am now
the closest living relative?
You in my house, lady.
I have a baby.
There's a lovely empty bedroom
just across the hall.
With your name on it.
Funny you should say that.
- What do you mean?
- It means...
I just got an interesting call
a little while ago,
from a lady at the hospital.
Phoned me to tell me
about their new daddy classes,
perhaps I should check them out.
I was of course confused.
Asked her if she had the right person.
"Is this Andrew Botwin," says she.
"Why, yes!" I reply,
as I usually do
to that particular question.
So, riddle me this.
Why would some lady from the hospital
you were just discharged from
be under the impression
that I'm a new daddy?
I couldn't put Esteban's name
on the birth certificate.
So you put my name on it.
Congratulations.
A little presumptuous,
don't you think?
No, you're always talking
about how you want to...
carry on the Botwin name.
Mazel tov, you're a father.
No, I'm not.
And I'm not signing a fucking thing.
What is the big deal?
It's a piece of paper.
It's not a piece of paper.
It's a fucking birth certificate.
The kid's first I.D.
You want to make it a fake one.
Way to start him off on a life of crime.
Come on.
I'm through playing
baby-daddy to your kids.
Andy, I don't have anybody else.
Whose fault is that?
You gotta get me
out of this contract.
- Is this thing scented?
- Jesus, Dean!
Isabel would like to go to college.
You can't be spending
the last dime you have on weed.
No, that belongs to a client.
This contract is signed,
countersigned and notarized.
- Looks like you're fucked.
- Isn't there something you can do?
I can get you high.
No, I'm clean.
Do you have any booze?
I got some scotch.
Don't... Come on. God.
So tell me, who is this client?
I can't divulge
privileged information.
But it rhymes
with "drug" and "hilas."
Their "pop" club got "rusted."
They need me to get their "schmarijuana"
back from the "grolice."
Of course, they have
a roomful of "shmarijuana"
and I have a roomful
of You're Pretty!.
I'm so fucked. I sell a product
that nobody wants.
And you,
you have all of this pot
that belongs to fucking...
assholes.
Hilas is not an asshole.
He's a nice kid.
Really, he is?
What did Silas pay you
for all of your valuable
legal advice, Dean?
- I'm smoking it.
- Tell me something.
Are you a closer or are you a loser?
I like to close drawers.
Well, close the drawer then
and open your mind.
I could sell
a lot more makeup
if I give a free gift with purchase.
I... I can't steal their weed.
Just tell them that you got
ripped off by black people.
- They won't buy that.
- They will when they see the bruises.
What bruises?
Putz.
You know, I admire you.
Go away.
This is my spot.
Despite the backwards nature
of your convictions,
you're tenacious and that bespeaks
a certain something of something,
so bravo.
- Which side are you on?
- On the side of sticking to one's guns.
I finally said no to her.
Oh, God!
The wave of relief that washed over me,
weird protestor guy.
I'm buoyant.
I'm a buoy.
Bluebirds on my shoulders.
- How's Nancy? Is the baby okay?
- Baby murderer.
25 feet, Gayle.
The baby's fine.
A thousand suns in those chubby cheeks.
You're wearing armor.
- You can never be too careful.
- And you're smoking.
Sometimes you can be too careful.
Can I help you with something?
You want to go out?
I'll buy you dinner. I shaved.
- When?
- Just now, right before I came.
When do you want to go out?
Tonight.
Pick me up here at 7:00.
- How will I know your car?
- It has a distinctive horn.
You're in the cross hairs
of the righteous.
Ignore the dark warnings
at your own peril!
Take a Claritin, Gayle.
Today's pollen count is off the charts.
- I'll see you at 7:00.
- Yes.
She likes me.
She's gonna burn in hell
for all of eternity.
I'd rather laugh
with the sinners, Gayle.
For now.
Lupita, thank you.
Good timing!
William Moris just merged with Endeavor
and Mr. Kaplan, out on his ass.
Look like a dyke bar.
- I haven't had time to redecorate yet.
- So where is my bedroom?
We're a little short on bedrooms.
Upstairs, your bedroom's upstairs.
I'm sleeping on the couch.
I had my last baby when I was 52.
The women in my family
bleed forever.
- How old are you?
- 37.
So, the baby?
- One-night stand?
- A little more complicated than that.
- Maybe he leave his wife.
- Even more complicated.
Good to see you, Nancy.
You pay me cash, you feed me,
I no work on Sundays
or when Secretos Houston is on TV.
- Done.
- No cleaning,
no laundry, just baby.
- Done.
- I like it, this is nice.
Ocean...
Maybe I start surfing again.
Dios mío! Shane!
- So tall!
- Hi, Lupita.
- You surf too?
- No.
- I teach you.
- Okay.
- Surfing lessons extra.
- Of course they are.
- Oregon.
- Yeah.
And then West Germany.
And then Uruguay.
You?
Tarzana.
And then, the other side of Tarzana.
What did you want to be
when you were a kid?
Jane Goodall. You?
A dog.
This is fun. I'm having fun.
It's getting kind of late.
I think I should go soon.
What?
Haven't even gotten
our Combo Platos yet.
- Are you feeling okay?
- Yeah, I'm great.
I... Just considering my options
for the rest of the evening.
And my PJ's and the Friday Night Lights
box set is winning hands down.
We're having a great date.
What's wrong?
Nutshell? I'm past you.
- Past me in what?
- In life.
Look, Andy.
I know there are plenty of girls
that would be dazzled
by $2 taco night at Borracho's
and the fact that you can balance
a salt shaker on the bridge of your nose
but honestly you lost me
about 15 minutes in.
This is stunning. I'm stunned.
Stunned? Really?
You're unemployed,
you're closer to 40 than 30,
you drive a car from a TV show
and your greatest recent
accomplishment
was beating the upside-down
kill screen in Ms. Pac-Man.
I didn't beat it, I just got to it.
Died almost immediately.
The thing's upside down.
You're a frozen margarita, Andy.
I happen to like slushy beverages.
And I'm a doctor.
Fine, you're a doctor.
I play doctor.
Why did you even agree
to go out with me?
'Cause my mother always said
that "if they feed you, go."
I'm starting to realize
my mother gave me lots of bad advice.
Thank you for the drink.
- I'll drive you home.
- No, it's all right.
I'll find my own way.
Preferably in a car
with the doors open.
Good night, Andy.
This baby sleep too much.
It probably just wants
to wake up when it's all over.
Shit, now I'm calling it an it.
Him an it.
Him a him.
I need to name this baby.
I go surf now.
I like Bernardo,
like in West Side Story.
Bernardo Botwin.
I'll think about it.
Bernardo?
He gets killed by Tony.
On the birth certificate,
he'd be Andy Jr.
That's what I call my penis.
Wait, no, God!
I need to stop playing doctor
and be a doctor.
- What?
- I wanna be the father.
- Really?
- Really.
But I mean really, really.
If my name is
on this child's birth certificate,
then I will be its father.
And we will raise it together.
- Him.
50% ownership.
Half the voting shares.
And I'm on the bimah
at the bar mitzvah.
He's Jewish now?
Reform, but yeah.
And just so you know,
I'm not doing this for you.
This is for me.
I want something that matters.
I want to be a substantial human being.
You know what I mean?
Substantial.
He's substantially wet.
I think you should change him, papa.
All right.
What's up?
All right, come on, little buddy.
Let's see what you're packing
downstairs.
Let's see what's going on down here.
I know it.
Bun's still on the hot dog.
Right, that.
I got to take care of that.
- Next checkup.
- Checkup?
A briss with a mohel and a Rabbi.
Yeah, bagels and whitefish.
Those are my demands.
- Demands?
- That's right. 'cause I'm the papa.
I'm the papa.
- Tradition.
- Oy.
Who are all these people?
The Rabbi brought them.
You need 10 Jews to watch him
lose his dick head or it's not official.
That's it.
Mazel tov.
Let's name this baby and eat.
Nice work, Rabbi.
Well, thank you.
I've been at it a while.
- What do you practice on?
- Goyim.
I think it's a barbaric ritual.
Well, it represents a covenant
between our people and God.
- It decreases pleasure.
- Paid for my summer house.
Oh, excuse me.
Will you look at this.
A professional woman,
a doctor no less,
playing a juvenile video game.
It's just so immature...
For a doctor.
I had no idea
this game was so awesome.
So, clearly,
you're open to looking
beyond first impressions.
I didn't say that.
Damn, I just died.
You are here
'cause you like me, aren't you?
I'm here because Nancy invited me.
And I am fascinated by how
this is gonna play out
with the gangster baby-daddy.
I'm obsessed with the drama.
- You were mean.
- I was honest. That's not mean.
It was harsh.
It was a snap judgment.
I'm almost inclined
to not ask you out again
just to show you how wrong
you are about me.
- Almost?
- Almost.
Almost.
All right. Whitefish?
Dimes go in the lipsticks.
Eighths go in the compacts.
Half ounces in the eye-shadow kit.
This is exciting.
When are you gonna break
the news to Doug and Silas?
I'm working up to that.
Well, you better do it soon
before that swelling goes down.
You fractured my cheekbone.
There's some old gym equipment
in the garage.
I've been lifting.
You look good.
Thank you.
- From a drawer?
- That's right.
- Can you fix it or not?
- Go see a doctor.
I don't have any insurance.
I've been taping it to a popsicle stick,
and it's turning blue.
Try cherry.
What are you looking at?
I did not approve this.
Now he looks like his daddy.
And you, too, from what I hear.
But slightly smaller.
My son is not Jewish.
Oh, yeah, he is now.
It's an ancient
and scholarly religion.
Disproportionate numbers
of nobel prize winners.
- Meet my son... Avi Melech.
- That's his Hebrew name.
"Avi" means "my father."
"Melech", the king.
That's my boy.
In english, it's Steven Ray Botwin.
Stevie Ray.
Would you like a bagel
with whitefish?
I'm gonna have to speak
with you privately.
This is unacceptable.
My son, our son,
will be baptized
by a priest in a church.
Sorry, he's Jewish.
Snip, snip.
Eat fish.
Start saving for law school.
I am his father.
I choose his life.
You had your chance to choose.
You walked out.
I have to think about the baby now.
You think about yourself.
Don't pretend that's a mother's love.
From the man who refused to put his name
on his own son's birth certificate!
My son's not gonna be raised
by that pendejo!
That pendejo sticks around.
He fights for what he loves.
And he's not a coward.
Get out.
My son won't grow up to be like you.
He won't see you.
He won't know you.
He is mine.
No, you lost him.