Previously on Weeds
I got busted.
Head of campus security at Valley State.
- We just got jammed.
- Here... This is yours.
If you need protection on campus,
just ask for me.
You still owe me 150 G's, lady.
How am I supposed to put...
food on my table?
You keep upping my debt.
Get a fucking job.
Chop that shit up, move it.
- Can you grow here?
- Hell, yeah. It's perfect.
Shame it's all gonna be for U-Turn.
Silas Botwin, you're sentenced
to 6 months of community service.
Injury such as yours may have
rendered you unfit for duty in the past,
I'm afraid times have changed.
Welcome to the army.
Your Battle Buddy
is like your Siamese twin.
You gonna shit when I shit.
Why are you doing this?
Because I let everything
at line for you,
and you fucked me.
Kachichian says goodbye.
- Peter is dead?
- Yes!
Make the fucking bags lighter.
Agent Fundis, DEA.
I'm here to talk about Peter Scottson.
~ SeriesSub.com ~
present
Sous-titres VO :
San-A / Loky
Season 3 Episode 4
We broke up...
me and Peter... Scottson.
He hasn't come in to work for a few days
and we haven't heard from him.
It's unusual.
I don't know...
- We broke up.
- Look, Mrs. Botwin,
- I'm his partner.
- The one who burps?
It's reflux.
When did you last speak with him?
Few days ago, he brought oranges.
Do you want them?
- Why would I want them?
- I have no idea.
Listen, we broke up.
I think we established that.
When he brought this citrus over,
did he say anything to you?
Where he was going?
What he might be up to?
- Work stuff?
- No.
He didn't talk about work much.
I didn't even know what he did 'til...
I tried on his jacket once by mistake.
I was cold and... I had to pee.
About the break up, we were just...
you know, different places,
I think we just wanted...
different things.
I think he was working at some...
undercover investigation on his own,
which is stupid but,
even when he goes indie
he calls,
to let me know everything's fine.
He knows I worry.
- I hope nothing is wrong.
- Well, if you hear from Peter,
I'd like you to give me a call.
He really liked you.
Thanks for your time, Mrs. Botwin.
Where is Peter?
We broke up.
Is that gonna be a problem?
What makes you so sure?
Mummy just knows.
Behold.
The incorporated city of Majestic.
A city... experiencing a rate of growth
few people could have anticipated.
Now, we've been a noisy neighbour
and for that...
I want to apologize.
That sound
you heard coming from the East,
the West,
the North... houses
popping up like...
so many Californian
wild flowers, well...
that...
is the sound of an economic miracle.
A month ago,
our own city council had a session
trying to come up with a new town logo.
Something we could put
on our signs, our brochures.
Italy is shaped like a boot,
Sicily, the ball
that's about to be kicked,
Majestic is shaped like a... well...
some people say, a horseshoe.
Others, a smile.
But, for some of us
who are aware of
a particular infrastructure
problems facing Majestic,
well, we saw a different image.
In the midst of all our backslapping,
we forgot a fundamental principle of...
smart growth.
If you gonna poop,
make sure you can flush.
What we need, is a ball.
Agrestic is that ball.
Now,
in exchange for
the right to redirect
a small portion of our sewage
through your town,
we'll retrofit
your existing sewage system with
the most advanced technology available,
at no cost to you.
We also grant you unrestricted access
to all our recreational facilities,
including...
our non-denominational
modern house of worship,
The Absolute Truth Ministry
of Majestic.
Now I know these are
tough times for Agrestic,
your tax basis is shrinking
while the cost of maintaining
basic services is rising.
It doesn't have to be that way.
We're neighbours.
And this...
is a hand
extended over the fence.
- Thank you Mr. Groff.
- Sullivan, please.
Sullivan.
Dumb name.
Education.
Two and a half semesters at Berkeley.
Graduated Berkeley.
with...
- honors.
- No lying.
- Thay can check these things.
- This is Agrestic.
No one's gonna check,
and you're gonna look totally lame
and stay unemployed if you don't lie,
'cause everybody else does.
Remember that guy
who came to the door, last night?
- Peter's friend?
- Yeah.
Even seen him like
looking around or anything obvious,
seen his Impala parked around?
- Working?
- Looking.
No, I haven't.
Why would he be looking?
Does he know you're a drug dealer?
No, I don't think so.
I just thought he is...
- a lurker.
- Mum.
Can you type?
With two fingers.
Proficient...
typing skills.
- Now, what kind of job do you want?
- Anything.
So long as there's no folding,
lifting or scooping involved.
Then I'll give you
a graduate degree in English,
and we'll take it from there.
Let's not overdo it.
I'm just...
proud of you.
What for?
Getting a real job.
Well, thank you, Shane.
Go!
- Come on guys
- Get up!
Move it on!
Go Botwin, Rodriguez!
Get that cock violated asshole
up that rope Botwin!
So help me! If you don't,
I will rip up by
your goddamn large intestin
and string it up by
your tiny little pecker with it!
- How fucking cool is this!
- We both gonna die.
Let's go! Move it!
Actually, you're gonna die.
I'm gonna hide under your corpse
and pretend I'm dead
'til everybody's gone away.
I ain't gonna be
nobody's dead body blanket.
We're gonna get them first.
We won't speak the language,
we know nothing about the culture.
But we have the news
fuck you up good technology.
That sergeant is dead meat.
We're the fucking insurgents.
We're the goddamn USA,
we're the best,
we're the coolest,
richest, most righteous nation on Earth.
We're a death-laden nation
of religious hypocrits.
All we do well is...
shop and drive gas guzzling SUVs.
You're fucking Un-American!
Get your corn holly shit
shit-stained asses over here*
What's with all the...
recurring homophobic imagery?
I'm starting to worry about this guy.
I think they're onto you man.
I think you gonna get court martialled
for that muslim loving shit
you've been spotting.
Yeah? They're calling you over too!
I want you two, soldiers,
to return to your barracks
changing to fresh greens and
report to my office in 9 minutes
Not 8, not 10.
- Is that clear?
- What's up?
You do not ever...
ask a commanding officer "what's up"!
He's not your fucking friend!
He's your goddamn master,
your motherfucking God!
- You hear me, sperm breath?
- Yeah!
- It's "yes sergeant"!
- Yes, sergeant!
Fall out!
Lights in the church roof.
- What shame is this
- Come on, Doug.
It's my turn.
So... are we prepared to commit
our city to being Majestic's ball
because a guy next door
bought up a cool model?
I'm not 100% sold.
Do you understand the numbers?
- I do.
- And?
And we have to be able to renegociate
on our terms and not theirs,
otherwise we...
What's going on?
I thought that we dealt
with this last night.
We did.
Why are you here?
Why am I here?
Why is he here?
- Slumming!
-Yeah!
And that's a good thing too,
'cause no one here knows his ass
from a spreadsheet on the ground.
Or her ass, as the case may be.
Thanks for coming by.
But we don't need you.
We agreed to hire
an independant accountant
who was gonna walk us
through the entire proposal.
It's in the minutes.
- Right, Sarah?
- The city coffers are empty, Celia.
Doug, what's your take
on this Majestic proposal?
Basically,
Majestic's overflowing a river of crap.
It's got no place to go,
but through us.
Like a physical colonic.
We got them by the sphincter.
Shit highway could be
our road to riches.
Our road to riches?
You know, the last time I checked,
you weren't even on the council.
Graduated at Berkeley with honors.
Associate editor,
Oxford University Press.
What division were you in?
- Sorry?
- What division?
Academic books, reference, trade?
Academic textbooks, mostly.
History,
lots of civil war stuff,
reconstruction.
And how did you like New York?
Oh, it was...
big, dirty, lots of people.
Coconut... Nice!
You're a very beautiful woman.
I bet you look good, rolling
right out of bed in the morning.
Or in it, the night before!
I have... my moments.
You know, if I hire you,
I'll be paying for the right
to make comments like that.
You okay with that?
As long as you're okay
with being shut down every time.
I like you, Nancy Botwin.
You're an operator.
The resume's bullshit of course, but...
the mind is there...
Here is what I do,
I sell values based communities,
which means that I, and you,
need to act the part
crucifix pin under the lapel,
smile on the face,
and a pleasant word for everyone.
No fucking the construction cruise
like my former assistant,
then broadcast it on the internet.
I don't do porn so much any more.
I found it very tiring.
Now, Majestic is my night community
and by far, the most ambitious.
There's a lot that comes
through that door every day
that needs to be delt with.
For instance, today,
I need to find
personalized gifts
for every member
of the Agrestic city council
and I have no idea what they'd like.
I can do that,
I know the people on the council.
I figured as much since Celia Hodes
who recommended that I speak to you.
I think this is
what's referring to as kismet.
Psst! Hey, space shuttle!
You've just gotten yourself a job!
You start on Monday.
Can't believe they expect us
to do this job straight!
Que?
Si, Mota! Muy bien!
- Mrs. Gruber?
- Silas!
Did you know that if you drink
and take Ambien,
you can randomly blackout
and run your car onto a boulder?
*
Who's that cute latino guy?
It's so hot!
Why don't you take your shirt off?
I'm fine.
You have nothing
to be ashamed of, you're...
you're young and lean
like ostrich meat.
Have you been drinking Mrs Gruber?
Don't tell!
Anyway, it isn't illegal unless
you're behind the wheel of a car, is it?
I guess not!
I'm wet!
How you know
how high to hang a light?
30 inches above the plant,
makes the upper root on my hemp
enough space to size.
And you gonna control
the temperature too?
Not just controlling temperature.
It also controls humidity, so the plant
don't grow bacteria nor fongus.
Anything else you wanna know?
I'm a wealthy information.
Kinda impressed, aren't you ?
You're like "Wow", that Conrad,
he knows what he's talking about!
If your dick was half
as small as your brain...
you would have stayed far away
from that girl like I told you.
If we're gonna work together,
you gotta get off my dick,
dumb as it might be.
Ain't gonna happen otherwise.
Fair enough.
They need us, and we need them.
Let's be their ball!
No! This is closed session, Mr. Wilson.
Hold that thought!
I have an annoucement to make.
For personal reasons, I've decided to
give up my position on the city coucil,
so in accordance with
our by-law section 3-24,
paragraph C,
we're hereby compelled to elect
an interim council member to replace me
until the next election.
I'm now opening up
the floor to nominations.
I nominate Doug Wilson.
I second the Doug Wilson nomination.
All those in favor of the resolution
to elect Doug Wilson
as an interim coucil member, say aye!
- Oh, you guys!
- All those against?
The resolution passes, Doug Wilson
will take my seat on the council.
Effective immediatly!
- No this can't possibly be legal.
- It is!
- And what makes you so sure?
- I wrote the by-laws.
So, now that that's that,
I would like to open up
a new order of business.
Since is no longer conflict of interest,
I would like to nominate
Mitch Kamin, to contract
all requisite landscapping
that will accompany shit highway.
This is bullshit.
No Celia, it's human shit.
You got to get
on the same page with us.
I'm not gonna allow this to happen.
You are not going turn this into
your little corrupt kingdom, again.
This time, there is going to be
checks and balances,
there is going to be oversight.
Are you hearing me?
I'm shaking.
Dastrovia.
Mummy got a job.
- Icecream for everybody.
- I'm the only one home.
Well then... more for us!
What's your job?
I'm the new...
Westcoast Head of Random House.
Mom, that's great!
I told you! Yes!
Actually,
I'm the executive assistant
to the Head of the Majestic project.
By the way, darling,
they do check resumes, so...
let's thank God
mummy smells like coconut.
- Hello?
- Where the fuck is my money?
Hold on.
I'll be right back, sweetie.
Hey, guess what, I got a job.
Your job is being my bitch.
Where the fuck is my money?
Okay, I'm having a little difficulty
moving your brick at the moment.
It's mothercking weed.
Everybody like that shit.
Sell it, and bring me the money.
The DEA came to my house.
I can't make a move right now.
The fuck you can't!
DEA's been up my ass since I popped out
of my mama's secret place.
That didn't stop me one bit,
fuck them!
I'm afraid I don't have
your confidence.
Then, find it, bitch!
Fuck you, guinea, not so hard!
Look, I want my money,
you hear me?
Sell the weed
to the fucking DEA all I care.
No more excuses.
Santa * California.
Valley State campus security.
I don't mean to quibble,
Mrs. Botwin, I don't want to invite
another visit from your friends, but...
Some of these bags look
a little light to me.
I assure you, they're not light,
it's just an airy plant.
- Look, you want it or not?
- Yeah, I'll take it.
I don't have the money on me.
So, uh... I'll be right back.
Why would you not bring the money?
I don't know, you...
you make me nervous.
I make you nervous?
You're scary.
You're the scary lady
drug dealer with thugs.
That's me.
Go get the money.
Leave the bag,
go get the money, now!
- Okay, I'll be right back.
- That's right. You will.
I have to drive to
where the money is, so...
You wanna...
come with me or
wait here or what?
I'll wait here.
I'll be right over there...
on that bench.
Okay? Make it snappy.
This is boring.
Get us out of
that fucking obstacle course.
Alright, give me that phone.
They said not to fuck with it.
I'm not gonna fuck with it,
I just wanna look at it.
Come on.
What do you think could happen
if we make a call?
We're not supposed to make calls.
We're just supposed to turn it on,
stand here,
let some drone take pictures of us.
- What are you doing?
- Making a postcard.
Hey, that's funny!
- Give me a lighter!
- What for?
I want you to take a picture of me
ligthing my fart.
Okay, that's the spirit.
Jesus, lady!
I thought you were someone else!
Come on!
This phone has video,
we can make a movie.
- Fuck!
- What's the matter?
- I've got nothing, I'm tensing up.
- Give me that.
Lemme show you how it's done, alright?
Okay, hold on.
Point the camera on my ass, hurry.
I don't want to see your balls man,
tuck'em in!
Alright, there, there, fine.
Ready? Okay, it's coming.
It's a good one,
here it comes!
- Man, what is it?
- It's showtime!
Holly shit.
Something.
Something, something.
Evidence.
Sorry Battle Buddy.
Merci, merci, madame.
Please.
Just like Paris, huh?
Sullivan!
I owe you a thank you.
Your friend Nancy,
she's gonna work out.
-Thanks.
- Honestly, the poor thing...
Really is help.
Entering the job market,
you know, at her age...
That "crouton" thing
they do on top of the soup,
not good.
Try the "croque-monsieur" next time,
or the "quiche".
You seem to know
your way around here!
I travel a lot.
There's a "café Du Merci"
in just about every city.
Same menu, same framed posters,
same smell.
There's a certain
conforting predictability to it.
You live around here?
I sort of, yeah.
Yeah, I sort of. I'm in a hotel.
- temporarily...
- Are you in the All Suites ?
That's where I am.
I'm staying in
one of the other ones.
Listen,
what would you say
if we dump this crap
and go some place where the lighting
is better and there's a full bar?
I'm buying.
Thank you.
I think maybe another time though.
I insist.
Why are you alone?
I actually have some place
I need to be.
I totally forgot.
I'm sorry,
I have to go.
You know, thank you...
though.
A rain check.
Should you reconsider.
À bientôt, mademoiselle.
First new message.
I know you been
dodging my calls, bitch!
Did you move my brick?
I want my money.
If I don't from you soon,
I'm gonna pay
you and yours a little visit.
I got a guy on payroll that just thinks
some fucked-up shit they do to people.
You're gonna be late.
It's okay.
You know, this community servicing
is totally unsupervised.
Every morning,
they tell me where to go
and what to do,
but no one even bothers
to check and see if I show up or not.
I still wait you showing up.
The thing is...
I can pretty much do anything I want.
No one is watching me.
No one.
I'm watching.
Plus, I meet
lots of really cool people,
people who like to have fun,
people who would pay to have fun.
This is a non starter.
I will never let you deal.
You don't have the choice.
I know you don't.
It's too dangerous.
I don't want this for you.
Come back here.
We'll discuss this later.
[ www.seriessub.com ]
Special Thanks to
Kasius
Benj!
Special Thanks to
gilles.silberzahn
niteowl
Special Thanks to
gwene
mlecuni