Jake Foley was an ordinary guy
until a freak accident transformed him
into the world's first
computer-enhanced man.
Millions of microscopic
computers interface
with his biochemistry and
make him stronger and faster,
able to see and hear
farther than normal men.
They give him the power to
control technology with his brain.
Jake Foley - America's
secret weapon.
He takes on missions
no ordinary agent can perform.
He is the ultimate
human upgrade.
Stay sharp, Jake, could be anyone.
Sector one all clear.
This is two. Nothing here
displacing a ticket counter.
Copy that, two.
Possible multiple targets
in three's location.
Moving west to the food court.
Give us the word. Check that.
It's nothing.
Got a guy with a suitcase.
Fits the profile.
Mid to late 30s. Possible ex-military.
Give us the word. Possible
confirmation at Foley's 20.
He's opening his bag...
False alarm.
That's a negative. Standing by.
Kyle, Kyle! Trash can, north exit.
I'm on the suspect. Guy is white,
baseball cap, khakis.
He's heading for the escalators.
Roger that, two is moving.
Three's rolling.
He's down! Do not move!
Do not move!
What do we have?
That canister was full of ricin gas.
Coagulant fuse.
It would have liquefied
and released in five minutes.
Hundreds could have died.
Tokyo all over again.
He doesn't fit the profile. He's
just a kid. Why would he do that?
It's because it's all he knows.
Both our intel
and the viciousness of the attack
point to one conclusion:
Today's incident was the work
of Ethan Fulton's militia.
Fulton is an extremely
dangerous and driven man.
His wife Ann
was FBI.
She was gunned down in a botched raid
on Henry Travis' compound
near Bozeman in 1994.
Fulton blames the government
for her death,
not without some merit.
Who is this guy?
Chief Director Skerritt. Lou's boss.
- Lou has a boss?
- Shhh.
We've been targeting
Fulton's militia for years.
They are responsible for six
domestic terrorist attacks
including the near miss on
the Supreme Court in April.
Now, as you can see,
we haven't been able
to I.D. many of them.
So today's capture
is a very important step
forward in our investigation.
Now I would like to acknowledge
Agent Foley's part in that capture.
- Lou's boss just complimented me.
- I heard.
We have an I.D. on the assailant?
No, sir. He's being
interrogated right now.
You keep me posted.
Excellent work, all of you.
Good-bye, sir. It was
very nice to meet...
Okay, you heard him.
Fulton is aware
the noose is tightening
so watch your backs.
Hey!
Yo, chill!
Is that any way to treat
your kid brother?!
Oh Jerry? Oh...
I could have killed you.
Yeah, yeah, right, dude, right.
What are you doing here?
Came to see you, of course...
also, our nation's great capitol.
I hear downtown's strip club-alicious.
That's me. Jake Foley,
I'm in Tech Support.
Security Clearance: Low.
Very low.
Then one day, it all changed.
Life just got real interesting.
- Okay, Ensenada.
- How could I forget?
Booze cruise, bikini twins, discotheque.
No. Federales, a pumped stomach
and a switchblade fight.
No, it was a butterfly knife.
You dug it. Admit it.
All right, I will admit that you talked
us out of it. I'll give you that.
Um, hello. Can we get some
Servicio, Por Fa-please?
Oh, god.
So, why aren't you in school?
I needed a break. You know,
I've been working pretty hard.
I got classes every
Tuesday and Thursday.
Uh-huh.
Plus I wanted to hang with my big bro.
Mom and dad know you're here?
Jake, I keep mom and dad on a strictly
need-to-know basis.
What happened there?
Um, it's a
work-related accident.
Oh, what your motherboard cut?
- What up?
- You guys ready to order?
Uh, beer. Start with a pitcher of draft.
Can I see your I.D.?
Oh, he's 26. He just looks young.
Your I.D.
Oh, me. Oh, um,
because when we left,
you were going to drive, so I...
I left my wallet at the house.
I'm sorry. I can't serve you then.
This is my brother. He'll vouch for me.
Oh, right. Yeah, he'll have a red bull.
Make that two, please. Thank you.
You call yourself a big brother?
That's right.
I'll let you make it up to me.
What do you say we shock on our
red bulls and hit the strip clubs?
Jerry, I can't. I have to be
at work tomorrow.
Hey, if I can make it through
a rigorous day of study
with a massive hangover,
I think you could, too.
I'll do you a favor; if I can get
off work tomorrow night,
we'll go out and do
something fun, okay?
Yeah, I can't wait.
Anyway, don't worry about me.
You won't even know
I'm here. I promise.
Hmm.
Sorry.
Whoa!
Yo, Jake, wake up.
Jerry,
I'm trying to sleep.
It's kinda important.
Oh, what is it?
- Promise you won't get all pissed?
- Oh, just say it.
I need a fire extinguisher...
like pronto.
What?
Okay, you're done.
Your vitals look good.
Have you had any
lightheadedness or nausea since
we had to, you know,
reboot the nanites?
Since you saved my life?
Yeah.
No, I'm fine.
Okay. Any recent glitches,
complications, any abnormalities?
My little brother's in town.
He's a bit of all three.
- I didn't even know you had a brother.
- Mm-hmm. Hmm.
He's checking out Georgetown
or burning down my apartment,
whichever comes first.
How old is he?
Nineteen... going on six.
Hmm. A little immature.
No, no, he's a lot immature.
When I was his age, I was
working two part-time jobs
while was taking eighteen
credits at Georgetown.
Did you have to walk six miles in
the snow every day to get there, too?
Funny. I'm serious. I don't get it.
He's a smart kid. He could go far.
He always screws it up.
He has no focus, you know?
Who does at 19?
Oh, well, except for you
and Bill Gates.
- Huh, duty calls.
- Yeah.
Stop by any time.
I have good news and bad news.
The young man who put
ricin gas in the subway
is Caleb Fulton,
Ethan Fulton's only son.
Now, Ethan blames the government
for the loss of his wife
and our capturing his son
will not sit well.
On the other hand, Caleb
grew up inside of the militia.
He knows it inside and out.
And next to capturing his father,
he's our best hope
in shutting them down.
- What's he saying?
- Nothing.
Our best interrogators
are working on him.
So let's get back to work.
Follow every lead,
every scrap of intel.
Um, do you think maybe
I could talk to him?
It's just we might have a connection
'cause I was the one that captured him,
and we're closer in age than you guys.
Not that you're old or anything.
You look great. It's just, uh...
I think he might relate to me better,
possibly.
Quit while you're ahead, Jake.
See what you can do.
Well, your pistons are shot,
your gas filter's rusted
and it looks like you might have
a crack in your engine block.
But I could have it ready Monday.
Say hello to the wife for me.
Thanks, Jimmy. I owe you.
They knew what we were doing
before half our men did.
Now, can you explain
to me how I let my son
walk right into an NSA sting?
You didn't crypt the final transmission
to our people in Virginia.
Ethan...
There is no excuse that
is going to free my son.
Sir.
There's been some concern
among the men about Caleb.
That they might possibly
force him into talking.
Caleb won't talk.
And neither will he.
Caleb.
I'm Jake.
You're pretty quick.
Thought I was chasing Emmitt Smith
down there in that subway yesterday.
I guess that's appropriate
since you were
all-league running back in high school.
Was it 24 touchdowns you
scored your senior year?
That's impressive.
I can barely score five when I'm
playing Madden on my PlayStation.
You should try the rookie
setting, it's easier.
Yeah, I will. I'll try that.
Thank you.
So you read my file?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
But this isn't your file.
Have you ever seen what ricin
gas does to the human body?
That little boy right there
is three years old.
That's his sister.
That's her mom.
The gas fills your lungs.
It feels like fire, but really
it's more like drowning
because your lungs literally burst.
That's why there's so much blood.
You almost did that to a lot of
innocent people yesterday.
But you didn't.
It's not too late,
you can change your life.
I can help.
How?
Tell us where your father is.
I'd rather die than betray my father.
He did not say that.
What do you look like?
So, what are you going to do tonight?
You should totally come over.
Jerry...
Hey, you got to try everything once.
And I'm telling you,
you haven't lived life
until you've tasted
my pasta a la Jerry.
Now get your buns over
here and I'll prove it.
She so wants me.
You met a girl already?
No. You did. Sarah.
She as hot as she sounds?
My Sarah? Were you talking to her?
No, relax, bro, it's fine.
I know we talked forever.
She's coming over to see you.
- Whoa, whoa, tonight?
- Yeah, man.
I'm hooking you up.
What's the deal with you two?
Nothing. We're friends.
Oh, I get it. She's a bowser.
No.
Fat?
She is beautiful and
she's intelligent, okay?
- So...?
- So...
it's complicated.
And it's none of your business.
Hey, whatever you say, man.
Do you mind keeping
it down for a while?
I'm gonna squeeze in a nap
before smackdown. Thanks.
Any progress?
- We know he's NSA.
- We knew that yesterday.
We know he's local. We believe
he works out of Fort Mead.
I want the name and
location of the man
who captured my son.
And then I want him standing right here
in front of me
so I can kill him myself.
Yes, sir.
Pasta a la Jerry coming your way!
Sarah. Sarah.
- No worries.
- Don't eat the food.
- I'm serious.
- I'll mop that up later.
Dinner... is served.
So, uh, what's in this?
Uh, pasta, vietnamese hot sauce
and selected seasonings.
It's a dorm room classic.
Dig in, Wedgie.
Wedgie?
One of Jake's many nicknames.
So what do you call him?
Oh, no, I'm far too mature
to embarrass Jerry like that.
Right, Humper?
I don't even want to know.
We've just begun picking up some
encrypted chatter from Fulton's militia.
First time since the ricin incident.
That's right. We believe there's
something going down tonight.
How long before we can decode it?
It's an algorithmic encryption.
It's gonna take a while.
Get every one of your code
breakers on this thing immediately.
You've got to hear this one.
Jake shows up to
Cheryl Rhodes' sweet 16
dressed like Gene Simmons.
I mean, full KISS makeup,
leather codpiece...
They told me it was a costume party.
Look at the time.
No, no, no. Hey, hey
I've got one more.
No, no, Jerry, you really don't.
Hey, this may be Sarah's only
opportunity to know the real you.
Right?
It's Christmas, and I was, like, seven.
And all I'd asked for that year
was this kick-ass red huffy bike.
Apparently, "Santa" got the message
because Christmas morning, there it was
along with a list of rules from my dad.
Number one being you
always lock the bike.
- Wha...?
- So Christmas Day,
I'm riding that sucker all
over town like it's a Ferrari.
I pop into the store for a soda
and when I come out, it's gone.
Jake finds me two hours
later crying my eyes out.
We go home and Jake tells my dad
he borrowed my bike
and forgot to lock it up.
Yeah, he got grounded for three weeks
just to keep his little
brother out of trouble.
That is so sweet.
I'll be right back.
Cool story, huh?
None of that ever happened.
It's no biggie, she'll never know.
That's not the point, Jerry.
Hey, I'm helping you seal the deal.
You can thank me later.
Where are you going?
I'm clearing the runway, man.
You can't land a plane when your little
brother's sleeping on the airstrip.
I'm not to trying to land a plane.
Hey, that's your own issue.
Can I borrow some cash?
I'm a little light.
You know, from dinner.
Yeah, sure. Take whatever
you need from my wallet.
Where's Jerry?
Uh, he had to go.
You, uh...
pizza?
- Yeah.
I thought you might be cold.
Your father never told you
about this part, did he?
I'm prepared to die for my cause.
Did your daddy teach you that?
Caleb, how many people have to die
before you realize your
mother's never coming back?
I take it you're not married.
Got any kids?
That's none of your business.
No matter, I can tell.
In your world, your job comes first.
In ours, it's family,
it's loyalty to your blood.
I feel sorry for you.
The feeling is mutual, Caleb.
Hey, can I help you?
Uh, scotch, neat, two napkins.
You got your I.D., kid?
I never leave home without it.
What kind of scotch?
Uh, the brown kinds.
Right.
Hey.
You a secret agent or something?
Huh?
I snuck a peek at your NSA badge.
You naughty little girl, you.
- There you go.
- So, are you? An agent?
I could tell you,
but then I'd have to...
Kill me?
I was going to say "sleep with you,"
but, uh, if that's your thing...
- start a tab.
- You got it.
You got to understand,
we were best friends.
We went through the Academy
together. We had nicknames.
So what happened?
I looked into his scared dark eyes...
and I asked him one more time.
I said, "Are you a double agent?"
He took a deep breath...
his hand slowly slipping from mine,
and he muttered,
"Si, Senor... Si."
Then I let go...
and watched him plummet to his death.
Wow.
Right. So where'd this all happen?
Where did this happen?
Can't tell you that, sir.
It's classified.
Yeah, stupid, it's classified.
All right, the drinks
are on Agent Foley.
Yeah!
Fo-ley! Fo-ley!
Anything on Foley?
NSA has him listed as a tech support,
but our people in payroll
can't confirm this.
There's no record of him on file.
I don't give a damn where he's listed.
I want to know where he is.
We're working on it, sir.
- You check DMV records?
- Came up clear.
You can't take a piss in this country
without someone knowing.
You're trying to tell me we can't find
this government piece of trash?
Wait a minute, we got something.
Foley just used his credit card
in the last ten minutes.
- Where?
- Georgetowne Station.
It's a bar on 4th and K street.
You get on him, now.
But having no idea where
little kids come from,
I just put it on my Christmas list:
One little sister -
and I was so pissed
when I didn't get one.
I just wanted someone to take care of,
you know, like you and Jerry.
Oh, Jerry never needed
anybody to take care of him.
Oh, come on, I heard the bike story.
Sarah, uh... that never happened.
What?
He made it up, but that's Jerry -
he's just trying to help.
To help what?
Uh, well
I-I guess he thought
that-that you and...
and-and me m-
uh, I guess he just thought that
maybe you'd like me better if...
Well, he was wrong.
Yeah.
I don't need any more reasons
to like you, Jake.
You got your standard military grip
that's been around since the 1800s.
I prefer a more modern approach
made popular by rappers
and drug dealers.
It's, uh, "let's kick back" and...
just plain cooler looking.
Come on, people, you with me?
We found him.
Oh, Jake, you have a little, um...
What? Here?
Uh, I-I'll get it.
I should...
Answer the phone?
Yeah.
Hello? Uh. Hello?
- Uh, Jake?
- Jerry?
Yeah. I'm in big trouble.
Okay. This one's for you,
and this one's for you.
Let's just say I understand the part
where you take my car without asking
and accidentally bump
into a police car.
Let's just say that
I understand the part
where you threaten to call
your friend, Mayor Williams,
if they don't let you go. But why
would you give them my I.D.
and pretend to be me?
First of all, you have a
much better driving record,
and second, you're NSA -
they should've let you walk out
of professional courtesy.
What is wrong with you?
Don't go all parental on me. We got
a couple of tickets - it's no big.
Yes, yes, it is big, Jerry,
and the amazing thing is,
you don't see it.
You know what?
This has been fun,
really, a lot of fun,
but I think it's time
you go back to school.
I can't.
Why?
Because I dropped out.
What?
I don't need school.
Oh, my god.
I know this guy, Randy Marshank,
he's making 10k a month with a web cam
and a girls' volleyball team.
Jerry, even for you,
that is the dumbest thing
I have ever heard in my life.
Why, because I want to do
something with my life?
No, you don't want to do
something with your life.
You want to avoid doing
anything with your life.
- I have a plan.
- No, you don't. No, you don't.
You have a scam.
That's all you ever have.
You know what? I don't need this.
I don't need some nerd
who sits at a computer all day
telling me how to live my life -
I don't need you.
Good. Good.
'Cause I don't need
some irresponsible child
hanging around wrecking my apartment
and stealing my stuff!
- Lou?
- Yes?
What's wrong?
We've decrypted the chatter
from Fulton's militia.
It's about his next target.
What is it?
Jake Foley.
Foley.
Oh, whoa, oh, hey, man,
you were in the bar, right?
And you brought your friend.
Oh, is-is this about that girl?
I didn't touch her, man.
She said she was single.
Respect, bro - I'm all about respect.
Whoa! Whoa, take it easy.
It's... we should all
go back to the bar,
and I'm buying. Sorry about...
Let's go.
What?
Jake, it's Lou. You need
to come in right away.
They took my son away from me, Foley.
And you need to know...
That that was a mistake.
What? I don't know what
you're talking about.
I don't know you.
Why are you doing this to me?
This is the NSA nowadays?
We're going to win this war.
I'm talking about my family, Jake,
and how you're going
to pay for what you did.
I'm... not Jake.
I thought he was a little young.
He was at the bar spouting off.
- He said he was Jake Foley?
- Yeah, he had Jake Foley's I.D.
And credit card.
Jerry Foley. Jake's brother.
Oh, god. But at the bar...
Yes, at the bar he was 'spouting off'.
I remember.
I'm sorry, sir.
I failed you and your son.
You didn't fail.
In fact,
you might have saved my son's life.
What's going on?
We've had a communication
from a man claiming to be...
Ethan Fulton.
All right.
- Was it about me, or something?
- Yes.
- Where is he?
- We don't know.
What do the communications say?
That they've got your brother.
They want an exchange.
Him for Fulton's son.
And if we refuse?
What did it say?
If we don't release
Caleb in one hour...
they're going to kill Jerry.
Okay. Okay.
So, so, we have his son.
So, we figure out a way to do this.
Where do they want to do it?
- Jake...
- I get it.
- We have to get them to come to us.
- Jake,
the National Security Agency
doesn't negotiate with terrorists.
What?
No, we have to...
This isn't a negotiation.
- We're just figuring out a way to...
- I realize this is difficult.
They have my brother!
And we are doing everything we can.
But we do not negotiate.
It only makes it more likely
that someone else's brother
or sister or father
will be taken in the future.
We have to help him.
I'm very sorry.
- Lou, we got to figure this out.
- Jake, I need a little time.
No, ee don't have a little time -
we don't have any time.
This is insane.
I'm not going to let them...
He needed me and
I wasn't there for him.
And now they're going... Please, please.
Jake, did you hear Skerritt said?
We don't negotiate with terrorists.
There's nothing I can do. I...
I can't go down to Caleb's
cell and let him out.
Do you understand?
I can't do that.
Jake, you have ten minutes,
and they're right behind you.
Does your brother love you?
We're about to find out how much.
He's got...
25 minutes.
Put this on.
- Why? What's going on?
- Don't ask me any questions.
I'm getting you out of here.
Good. Let's go.
Aw, come on.
This way. Go.
Go. Up the stairs.
Okay, try it now.
Isn't technology grand? Thanks.
What the...?
Call your father.
- I told you...
- Caleb, he has my brother.
He wants you in exchange. Now
I figure we've got about two minutes
before the NSA figures out that
you're gone and I took you.
So if you ever want to see your
dad again, you call him. Now!
Louise,
what you know about
Caleb Fulton escaping
from a supposedly secure lockdown?
I'm aware of the situation,
and I'm on it.
Well, you better be.
You made it.
I was pretty scared.
You're my son.
You never, ever be afraid of anyone.
Not them, understand me?
Yes, sir.
He came alone and unarmed.
You're a man of your word.
Where's my brother?
I'm a man of my word, too.
Oh, Jerry.
It's okay.
Come on, it's gonna be okay.
You moving on?
It's how we survive.
- What about Caleb?
- What about him?
He's just a kid.
Why don't you let him have a life?
Because his life is here
with his family - with me.
And I wouldn't overstay
my welcome if I were you.
Come on.
Watch your back. There are friendlies
in the building! Standing by.
This is the NSA.
Throw down your weapons
and come out with your hands up!
You are surrounded.
Hold your ground.
Weapons down! Let me see your hands!
Hands!
Clear!
Okay, we're clear.
You okay?
Yeah.
No. Caleb...
You okay, sir?
Well, we had a terrific
success last night.
We shut down the militia,
arrested Fulton and his men.
However...
I have people very high up
I have to answer to.
I realize that.
Do you?
And what am I supposed to tell them
about our policy
of never negotiating with terrorists?
Tell them we didn't.
God almighty, Beckett,
you got bigger ones than I do.
Thank you, sir.
You ready?
I think so.
You going to have any
trouble re-enrolling?
You mean the work studies
chick in admissions?
- Tight.
- Nice.
So now, uh, about the parental units?
Yeah, you came to check
out Georgetown...
because you insisted
on me having a plan...
once you get out of junior college.
Sweet. Thanks for everything.
Yeah.
Okay, enough of the Gilmore
Girls. Let's roll.
- So, can I ask you one question?
- Sure.
What exactly do you do at the NSA?
I could tell you, but then
I'd have to kill you.
www.tvsubtitles.net