Jake Foley was an ordinary guy
until a freak accident transformed him
into the world's first
computer-enhanced man.
Millions of microscopic computers
interface with his biochemistry
to make him stronger and faster,
able to see and hear
farther than normal men.
They give him the power to control
technology with his brain.
Jake Foley - America's secret weapon.
He takes on missions no
ordinary agent can perform.
He is the ultimate human upgrade.
I thought this war was with our enemies
out there, not our superiors in here.
Either the board is satisfied
with your explanations
or we terminate the program.
They're threatened by things
they can't control,
and they can't control you.
I don't know if I can do
this anymore, Diane.
I have a contact.
He creates new lives for people
and erases the old ones.
I thought that I would find Jake here.
You won't.
Jake... you're back.
This is four-one-Baltimore,
who has visual on the subject...?
- I did, but I lost contact.
- Where?
Northeast quadrant.
Damn it, who has the subject in sight?
I got her. She's heading south,
toward the river.
Who's got her?
Who said that?
Me. Uh, Jake... Six-Two-Denver.
Say your number first.
Jake, stay put, we're on our way.
Okay, she's... she's heading
toward a car. She's going to bolt.
- Jake, stay put.
- This is Beckett.
Dankova must not get away.
Use all necessary force.
- Is that a shoot to kill?
- That is affirmative...
Lou, we need Dankova alive.
Hold the shoot to kill
unless it's the only resort.
Wait until we get there!
Don't let her get away, Jake.
- Don't do anything until...
- Oh, would you just shut up!
Ow.
Now, how could this happen?
How did he let Dankova get away?
"He" practically got tire marks
on his face from trying to prevent it.
Is it so hard for you
to do what we tell you?
Yeah, when you're telling me
fifteen different things, yeah.
Put it up.
Yeah... no, the leg's fine.
Thanks for asking.
- Why don't you try and be useful.
- All right, all right.
We had Elena Dankova in
our sights and we lost her.
This woman is a former KGB
operative who tried to sabotage
our Wilmington nuclear
facility in 1986.
We narrowly avoided
our very own Chernobyl.
Now, Dankova is a true believer.
She went rogue the day
the Berlin wall came down.
As far as she's concerned,
the cold war never ended.
Let's see if we can track her down
and see if we can
hold on to her this time.
And don't be afraid to think
outside the box.
Hey, Lou... what do you think
about bringing in the agent
who was point man on
Dankova in the eighties?
Are you talking about Richard Fox?
Uh, yeah. He has a lot of
commendations.
Fox.
Big deal back in the day?
The biggest.
He single-handedly captured
Mikail "The Shark" Petrovitch.
That was the beginning
of the end of the KGB.
Retired in eighty-eight.
- Where's he living?
- Here in D.C.
File says he has two addresses.
Bring him in.
You're about to meet a legend.
Call me. I mean it.
If you don't, I will hunt
you down like a dog.
Bye, baby.
You got company.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Y'all lawyers or bill collectors?
NSA.
I'm Agent Duarte,
this is Agent Foley.
Sir, would you please put that away?
We were hoping we could talk
to you about Elena Dankova.
You are Richard Fox?
Call me Dick.
Anybody want a Fresca?
No, thanks.
Well...
Smoke bother you?
Uh... no.
Maybe...
You know, she always
was a real bastard.
You boys have got a problem, all right.
Well, that's why we came to see you.
What do you think
we should do, Mr. Fox?
Dick.
Well, first I think you should find her
and then kill her.
Good luck.
At the risk of sounding corny,
your country needs you.
Oh, shucks, really?
I gave 'em thirty years of my life
and they gave me this nifty watch
and they need me now?
Tell you what I'll do -
$80,000 retainer, and I'm all yours.
I don't think we can do that.
I was just kidding. Make it fifty.
Actually Mr... Dick,
your NSA contract is pretty
specific on the matter:
You can be recalled to
active duty at any time.
Failure to comply
can result in arrest,
confinement and/or
cessation of pension.
I thought you were the smart one.
Me, too.
Well, I guess I better get
gussied up and get some clothes on.
But we do this, we do it my way.
Is that clear, boys?
You can take that up with the boss.
Oh, I will.
What's his name?
Deputy Director Louise Beckett.
Well, hot damn. Fill me in.
All right.
We suspect that Elena Dankova
slipped into the country four days ago.
Since that time, we've had sightings
of her in Cincinnati and Chicago.
We know for a fact that she
was here in D.C. Yesterday.
How so?
We had her in our sights
and we lost her.
Who was the pinhead
that let that happen?
Uh...
I would be that pinhead.
Oh, The Smart One.
Were you sober?
Yeah. Of course.
Well, that was your first mistake.
And were you doing everything
they were telling you to do?
I was trying.
Kid, you got a lot to learn.
Can we could move forward, please?
Copy that, sir.
Listen up -
Chicago, Cincinnati, D.C.-
Run these names: Nicolai Iskanov,
alias Nolotov;
Liam Petrov, A.K.A. Kovalev;
and Max Romanov,
alias Petrenko and/or Bulgakov.
My guess is Dankova's
has contacted sleepers
left behind after the collapse
of the soviet empire.
- Why?
- Well, to finish the job
that we stopped her from doing in '86.
Are you saying she's planning another
attack on a U.S. Nuclear Facility?
I'm saying that if it looks,
sounds, feels radioactive,
I'd park my ass in front
of it with an M-16.
You never gave up, did you?
Cold war ends and
you're a relic overnight.
Betrayed by your own country.
I know how you feel, Lenochka,
but you shouldn't have set
foot on American soil.
Going to have to bring you down.
Bring you down hard, baby.
I think I have something.
There's a Max Petrenko,
living in Atlantic City...
well, he was living there. I don't see any
hits on him in the last couple of years,
but he has a line of credit
at something called "Rudolph's Red."
- Is that a casino? I never heard of it.
- Russian mob joint.
It's off the boardwalk,
low-rent, high-rollers.
- You got a facial?
- I've got a passport picture.
That's our man - Romanov.
One of the soviet union's
top nuclear engineers.
I'll bet bucks to beans he's the key
to whatever Dankova's got up
her sleeve. Good work, son.
I've got a Nicolai
Nolotov in Cincinnati.
Okay, I want teams in the field.
One to Cincinnati to pick up
Nolotov, one to Chicago.
Smart boy and me here
will take Atlantic City,
if that's all right with you, boss.
- You want to partner with Jake?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- Best man for the job.
He let Dankova get away once.
I don't think he'll let
that happen again.
I want you checked out
by medical staff.
Whatever you say, boss.
Get me Homeland Security.
Was there something else?
Sure got real pretty eyes.
Okay.
No, no, no. Not on my watch.
Oh, pretty and tough.
I'll be right back.
Just take your shirt off.
Okay, but I expect you to do likewise.
So, you and the doc there -
you got a little thing?
No, no, no. We're just colleagues.
What's that, a fancy
word for "friends"?
Yeah, I guess.
You kids nowadays.
You know a man and a woman
can't be just friends.
They got to be lovers or enemies.
Like you and Elena Dankova?
Well, sometimes,
it's a little of both.
And why is your shirt still on?
- Uh...
- And if you say, "why is yours?"
You'll stick a scalpel in me.
Yes, something like that. All right.
Look, I'm as fit as I'm going to be.
- Me and the kid here, we got work to do.
- Yeah.
Not until you get a full medical
work-up. See, I have orders.
Let me see that.
Yeah, well, you do everything
they tell you in this joint,
you'll go nuts.
No, no, no. But, you can't...
- Uh...
- Hey, Lou.
Is he ready yet?
- Uh...
- A hundred percent.
Let's get this show on the road.
Jake, this one's by the book.
All right.
Just wait till you see this.
You're not going to believe it.
That salesman never saw me coming.
Vintage Mach I. Only three thousand
of these babies left in the states.
Oh, sweet. They don't
make 'em like this anymore.
You just spent almost every penny
in our expense account on a car?!
What are we gonna
live on in Atlantic City?
What am I gonna tell Lou?!
You always wound this tight?
Kid, this car is the mission.
It's your ass on the line out there.
How you look, how you
feel, what you drive
can be the difference in coming
back alive or in a body bag.
The number-crunchers
back at headquarters,
they'll never understand
a thing like that.
You want to know
the secret to this job?
- Okay.
- Get in.
"Go with your gut."
At the end of the day, the only thing
that matters is that you
get the job done right.
Okay, kid, you ready
to have a little fun?
Yeah! Ha-ha!
Now, this is what going
undercover's all about.
Romanov has a big line of credit,
so I'm guessing he's a high roller.
Maybe we should...
What are you doing?
I'm ordering a pizza.
What does it look like I'm doing?
That's all the money we have left.
I'll play these three hands.
Four hundred on each and
an extra hundred for the dealer.
- Thank you, sir. Good luck.
- Dick!
If you want to look like a high
roller, you got to act like one.
Twenty-one.
- You won?
- All right. Double down here.
Yes, sir.
Are you just going
to stay here and gamble?
No, I'm going to stay here
and gamble and... drink.
Winner.
Cocktails.
Why don't you go look for some
big guys in expensive suits?
They would be the Russians.
Hey, honey, let me have a double scotch
and drinks all around, huh?
Hit me here.
All right. I'll stand.
Twenty-one.
Thanks, sweetheart.
I was getting thirsty.
There you go, darling.
- Thank you.
- Cutie.
Hey, see that poker table
on the other side of the room?
The guy at the end - Is he one of them?
Only one way to be sure.
This will be phonetic Russian, okay?
I want you to join the game.
Wait for him to make a bet,
and when he does,
say this to him. If he says "da,"
finish the hand.
We'll wait for him outside.
- Uh, maybe I should hold onto...
- I'm in.
Or not.
What do we have?
Liam Petrov. One of
the names Fox gave us.
A team in Chicago
just found him... dead.
Murdered in his own home.
Two bullets right through the eyes.
- Dankova's trademark.
- Nice lady.
My guess is whatever
Dankova has planned,
- Liam wasn't going along.
- Why would he?
A hundred and fifty K a year
making plumbing equipment,
four-bedroom house in the suburbs.
Capitalistic imperialism's
been very good to him.
It gets worse.
Nicolai Iskanov was working
at the hope creek nuclear
reactor under an alias.
He hasn't reported to work in a week.
Around the same time,
one hundred curies of cesium 137
disappeared from their waste depository.
- They're making a dirty bomb.
- Yeah, that'd be my guess.
I've notified FBI, CIA,
Homeland Security.
All right, make sure we're
sharing intel as it comes in.
Last thing we need is another
communication breakdown.
Set up around-the-clock feeds.
New York City and D.C.
Radiation sensors.
We're on it.
T'voya mahts vonyayet kak abyeziana.
(Your mother smells like a monkey.)
"Moya mahts vonyayet kak abyeziana."
(My mother smells like a monkey.)
Ya yevo oobyu. (I will kill him.)
You wouldn't think that skinny
kid could fight that good.
What do you say we get out
of here? Grab your money.
What?
Oh...
Director Beckett, I've got Jake.
- Beckett.
- I need a shoot to kill order.
What?
Dick - your legend - spent all our money,
tried to have me beaten
to death by strangers,
and then ditched out on the
mission with a cocktail waitress.
- Why didn't you notify me earlier?
- That's a very good question.
Look, the Atlantic City field
office is tenth and park.
- Can you get there?
- Yes. What about Dick?
Sounds like he's got some issues.
At any rate, you're
both off the mission.
And Jake, I look forward to your report.
Yeah.
I've been looking all over
for you, son. Come on. Get in.
No.
Okay, so you're pissed. I get it.
Why don't we go somewhere, grab
a couple of beers and talk about it?
There's nothing to talk about.
We're off the mission.
It's over. Finito.
Sounds like you've been talking
to the suits back home.
Yeah, I was. And if I were you,
I'd turn around and leave me alone.
I can't do that, kid.
Get in.
I'm not too proud to beg.
All right, hand it over.
Come on. Give it to me.
Back in my days, these things
were the size of a thermos.
So damn heavy, they
practically gave you a hernia.
Roll down your window.
You're making a big mistake.
Yeah, I've been hearing
that all my life.
Still doesn't phase me.
Apologies for the note.
These Russians, they
got no sense of humor.
You tried to get me killed!
If I wanted you dead, I would have
been a little more creative than that.
I was just testing you
to see what you're made of.
You know, your life's in your
partner's hands in this game.
You handled yourself well.
Gee, thanks.
Maybe a little too well.
What do you want?
I want to know what you are.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Yes, you do.
What did those bastards
at the NSA do to you, kid?
You know, you and I may have
more in common than you think.
Way back when you were just a tickle
in your daddy's pouch,
the NSA had these programs.
Enhancement programs: Steroids,
G-H-B, H-G-H.
Those were just the training wheels.
They moved up from there.
And you were...
Quid pro quo. And I asked you first.
Look, I know it's hard.
They can really screw you up.
You don't know what
you can or can't say,
who to listen to, who to trust.
Sorry about the gun.
It was a little heavy handed,
but you wouldn't have gotten
back in the car otherwise.
They, uh,
they did do something.
I can't really get into specifics.
There was an accident...
Yeah, there's always an accident.
What was that?
What was what?
Is there someone in the trunk?
No. You kidding?
Dick, open it up.
Okay, Mr. Paranoid.
Here have a look.
Vsyo gatovah. Davai.
(Everything is ready. Come on.)
Throw your weapon out of the car,
then step out.
Arms in the air.
Lenochka, don't you trust me anymore?
I slept with you many times,
but I never trusted you.
That's no way to build
a lasting relationship.
Do you have it?
But of course.
Open it.
You know, I don't take rubles.
Who does anymore?
Who did ever?
It's been a pleasure.
Call me.
You are so lucky you
don't have a concussion.
You just have some lacerations and
some bruises that should heal in, like...
well, very soon.
I hear they got every
available agent out there
looking for Dick and that car.
Between you and me, I thought
that guy was kind of a nutcake.
Jake?
Diane,
before the nanite project,
were there any other
enhancement programs?
Um...
um, I mean, I'm not familiar with any,
but I would have to say
that there were, yeah.
I mean, the NSA has more research money
than any other intelligence agency
and they have a mandate
to stay ahead of the curve, so...
why?
Do you think they did
something to Dick?
Uh, it's just...
I'm not sure that guy really is crazy.
I have a feeling he knew exactly what
he was doing every step of the way.
Excuse me.
Lab.
Okay, yes, ma'am, right away.
Lou says there's something in SAT OPs
that we have to see right this instant.
Okay.
Dick?
My name is Richard.
And having armed guards
hovering over me like this
is not the way to treat someone who
bled for this agency for thirty years.
I've been in Finland for the past
month doing some consulting work.
I came as soon as I got your message.
Now how can I help you?
Uh...
Look, I don't know what kind
of mind game you're running,
but you've got some explaining to do.
Look, you called me.
I'm reporting to duty per the
activation clause in my contract.
And with all due respect,
I don't understand
how the NSA shared
critical mission information
without first verifying the
identity of an operative.
Wait. Hold on.
So I just spent thirty-six
hours with what?
A double? Decoy? Clone?
There's no such thing, Jake.
- You've been watching too many spy movies.
- Don't be too sure.
Does this mission have anything
to do with Ex-KGB Agents
from the former Soviet Union?
We don't share any information with
you until we find out who you are.
Well, then let me do the sharing then.
Classified archive
Delta-X-ray-Oscar Niner.
The Crimean Project.
A joint operation by the KGB/GRU set up
to collect biometric data
on American Intelligence assets.
The goal was to destabilize
our intelligence-gathering ability
by creating doubles of American agents
using plastic surgery, drugs,
advanced language
and cultural conditioning.
I was to be one of the targets.
So whoever's doing
this must have known
I'd be out of the country
before activating their plan.
Can't find the archive
in the computer, Dick.
You're not going to find the
Crimean Project on a computer.
It's on microfiche in the basement.
Code named "Double,"
classified and secured under
the 1982 National Security Act.
It's only accessible to
Deputy Directors and above.
And you may refer to me
as "Richard" or "Agent Fox."
Okay, Agent Fox.
Let's hope, for your sake, that I come
back from the basement with a file.
Keep your eyes on this man.
While I'm waiting,
I hope someone's here
to take my blood and fingerprints.
That'd be you, little lady?
I didn't know they let agents wear
their hair that long nowadays.
Yeah. I'm a regular old beatnik.
From the looks you're giving me,
that impostor must have
done quite a job on you.
You know, if you'd gone by the book,
none of this would've happened.
You know, I'm not ready to take
lessons from you just yet.
Well, I'm not ready to give them.
It's all here. The Crimean Project.
Looks like the soviets
really were trying
to copy our agents
using plastic surgery.
- So he's legit?
- Apparently.
Now if his fingerprints
and blood match our files,
we're going to have to give
him the benefit of the doubt
- and debrief him on the mission.
- What about trusting him?
Absolutely not.
Good. Any word on the mustang?
Sat-ops is working with local law
enforcement up and down the seaboard.
We'll find him. In the meantime,
I want your eyes on Richard 24-7.
Yeah.
This is odd.
Yeah, but DNA does not lie.
This is Richard Fox.
And I looked at those
Crimean Project files.
Everything they were doing to duplicate
our agents is medically feasible.
I mean, it's dangerous
and nuts but it's doable.
Hey, you remember that cigar
that Dick left in your lab?
- Yeah, you want me to run DNA on it?
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
All right. Agent Fox has
been brought up to speed.
I want you to give him
your full cooperation.
And we don't have much time.
Look, I'm sorry you were duped, son.
But the soviet agent
that was impersonating me
was using you to find out
everything the NSA
knows about Dankova's plan.
And we're three steps behind them.
- We've got to level the playing field.
- Seems to me the best way of doing that
is by finding the impostor.
Why don't we take a look at the
security tapes from that casino.
Okay.
And you thought that was me?
Look at the way he carries himself.
Did you look at any of
the pictures in my file?
All right, stop frame right there.
- What do you see?
- Dick's flirting with the waitress.
Look closer.
I don't know, he's playing her.
He's making like a high roller.
He distracted you once;
don't let him distract you again.
Okay. Uh...
The girl?
Cute. Fair skin.
High cheekbones.
Strong chin, possibly...
slavic.
Hey, can you pull up
that photo of Romanov?
Okay.
Okay, now freeze on the
waitress and enhance.
Romanov's daughter?
Romanov took his own
life two years ago.
Couldn't hack it in
the new world order.
She was a student at
The Central Academy
for Advanced Physics in Voronezh.
When the wall fell she came
to Atlantic City with her father.
Why is she serving drinks at a casino?
Our country's full of highly-educated
immigrants doing menial jobs.
The point is, she has the know-how
to put that bomb together.
He walked out of there with her,
- put her in the trunk of his car...
- and delivered her to Dankova.
- Right under my nose.
- Clear the board!
All stations on alert,
we have a red ball.
This was on its way to a Moscow
TV station for broadcast tomorrow.
We intercepted it from
a private courier company.
At midnight last night,
we cut out the heart of our enemy.
After years of humiliation,
we stand proud,
defiant and soviet to the end.
This is a code six:
We believe these people plan
to detonate a dirty bomb in D.C.
tonight at midnight.
Exactly one hour from now.
Rewind. Kill the audio.
- You see something?
- Yeah. That.
Magnify frame 1,000 percent.
Shift focus to the window.
Can you enhance it further
and ID the plane?
Not without pixelation.
It's all we've got.
They may have shot this
in sight of the glide path
for Reagan, Dulles or BWI.
Get me Homeland Security.
I want choppers in the air
with radiac detectors now.
The rest of you, you have
exactly five minutes
to find the most likely
locations for this device.
Kyle, assemble the strike teams.
Lou, Agent Fox and I
made some progress.
I think finding his double's
the best way to stop this.
I don't. I want every available agent
trailing this device.
Is that understood?
What do you think?
I think we have our orders, son.
Backup clip,
check, body armor plate, secure.
Strike team, this is Thunderbird.
We're less than ten from the target.
- Diane, hey.
- Jake,
I just got the preliminary
result on that DNA.
Okay. Thanks.
What was that?
Hang on to something.
Who broke formation?
What the hell are you doing?
You are jeopardizing this mission.
You turn that car back around.
That's an order.
Kyle, bring him into compliance
by any means necessary, now.
Damn it, Jake, what are you doing?
I'll tell you what I'm not doing.
I'm not stopping this car.
This is a flagrant breach of protocol.
Kyle, you gonna have
to trust me or shoot me.
What are we doing here?
Mustang Mach I. That's him.
Lou, this is Kyle.
I think we found Agent Fox's impostor.
He's here. Son of a bitch.
- I'm going in.
- No, wait!
Jake.
Down! Hit the floor now.
Screw you and get out of my house.
You want me to shoot, I'll shoot.
Good call, kid.
Now I'm going to put an end to you
and everything you stand for.
No, you won't.
You know you can't execute
someone without an Order.
In your case, I think
I can make an exception.
Lima one, do we have a visual?
Negative on that, Thunderbird.
Proceed to southeast
and northwest corners.
Copy that.
SAT Ops, do you have
anything on the location?
No unusual activity
on the radiac sensors.
And thermal imaging shows
nothing moving inside the building.
Thunderbird, again. It's a negative.
We have the wrong location.
Reports are coming in
from the other teams.
Negative on Delta.
Negative on Sierra.
Negative on Bravo.
Kyle, did you find him?
Sort of.
- He may be our only chance.
- We're working on it.
What happened to him?
The NSA.
Thirty years of being pulled
every which direction.
God knows what else they did to him.
Split him in half.
Richard...
- I don't think you wanna do that.
- This man's an enemy agent.
Who can lead us to
Dankova and the bomb.
Kid makes a good point.
Shut up.
He screwed you once.
He'll screw you again.
That's why I need you, Richard.
To make sure that he doesn't.
I need you, Richard. And Dick.
I need you both.
All right, kid.
Now, let me tell you the plan.
What?
We have a location! Let's move out.
All right. Let's go!
It's ready.
Once we're clear the
blast area, we detonate.
SAT Ops just confirmed heat signatures
for five people inside the location.
Stealth is crucial.
I want snipers first at the scene
and fully deployed before
the ground assault.
Repeat, stealth is crucial.
Open the door.
Pack up the van.
Weapons down! Now!
Now!
Stand back!
We're getting too
old for this, Lenochka.
Did they offer you more money?
Don't I wish.
Go ahead, knock yourself out.
Boom.
Anytime, Agent Foley.
Were you waiting till
the last possible moment?
She was working with you?
Well, I did promise Miss Romanov
a little something
if she helped us out.
It's all yours.
Very nice.
So's the hundred grand in the trunk.
Also, my phone number's
in the glove box.
It comes standard.
The whole time, he was
two steps ahead of us.
He tracked Romanov at the casino,
told her we needed
somebody on the inside.
Then he paid her to rig the
bomb so it wouldn't go off.
My office 0700 tomorrow morning.
Special commendation from
The Secretary of Defense.
It's not every day
you stop a dirty bomb.
We have a problem, Jake,
and something's going to have to give.
There are people upstairs who
don't like the way you do things,
and they would love nothing
morethan to shut us down.
Now I do everything in
my power to protect you,
but there's a limit to what I can do.
So at the very least, when I give
you an order, you follow it.
You don't question it.
Just like all my other agents
who work for me.
Are we clear?
Lou,
I respect you.
And believe me,
I appreciate everything
that you have done for me.
But I'm not like all your other agents.
I wake up every morning with
millions of nanites inside of me.
Now, if you want me
to follow every rule
and regulation to the letter,
then that's what I will try to do,
but if you ask me to do that,
then one day something
is going to give.
It'll be me.
Aston Martin V-12?
No, no, no. Way too small.
What did I tell you?
If you get a hundred thousand
dollar car for a mission,
it needs to be fast and comfortable.
That's my boy.
All right. Bentley Continental GT?
Please. That thing looks like a hearse.
Speaking of hearse.
By the way... thank you, son.
What else you got?
Oh, uh...
Mercedes Benz SLR Coupe.
Oh, give me a break.
I can run faster than that heap.
Really?
How about another Fresca?
www.tvsubtitles.net