Previously on Charmed:
For our plan to work,
we need to get the sisters...
And Leo and Chris out of the way.
It opened up a portal
to another world.
- Like evil?
- Precisely.
And if you encounter
your counterparts, be careful.
They will kill you.
I'll take mine, you take yours.
- It was Gideon all along.
- And he's still out there.
He wasn't vanquished here,
he wasn't in our world.
The imbalance has caused
a shift in both worlds.
Put him in the playpen.
Don't want him to see.
- But Phoebe...
- Just do it.
Okay, there we go. There you go.
Don't let him out of your sight.
- What's wrong, what's taking so long?
- I don't know.
Damn it, Leo, you should have
just healed her outside.
Right, and risk you getting shot too?
I don't think so.
Okay, so I just sent our evil twins
through the portal, although...
What happened?
- Thank God.
- Stay with Wyatt.
I got him.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Just remind me to never park in
Mrs. Noble's driveway again.
Will someone please tell me
what is going on here?
The neighbourhood patrol
shot her point-blank
and nobody so much
as blinked an eye.
What? Why?
Because by getting us all
to the evil world,
Gideon screwed up the balance,
the grand design.
If you ask me, the grand design was
messed up in the first place.
Wait, so are you saying because of
what he did, our world is bad now too?
No, on the contrary, it's good.
Too good.
Where every little infraction
is a capital offence.
And everyone just accepts it.
Oh, so we're starring in a little movie
called Pleasantville?
Okay, how come
we weren't affected?
Because we must have been
crossing over when the shift occurred.
Well, that must mean Gideon's
not affected either.
No, he wouldn't be,
because he's an Elder.
How do we know he's not using
this situation to his advantage?
- To come after Wyatt?
- Because I'm gonna find him first.
No, you can't hurt him, Leo.
Not until he shifts the balance back.
And you know he knows
how to do that.
Oh, my God, we totally forgot about
Piper. We have to get to the hospital.
- Who's gonna watch Wyatt?
- I will.
Look, I didn't come all the way from the
future just to lose him now, all right?
I think we should drive.
I don't wanna risk orbing.
All right,
just watch your speed, okay?
Oh, give me a break.
You're lucky.
It could have been worse.
Well, well, well,
the new peeping Elder.
How the mighty have fallen,
so to speak.
Show yourself.
Only if you agree to a truce.
I promise, it is in your best interests.
Why not.
This particular day
couldn't get much worse.
Actually, it could.
You could die.
The world has changed, my friend,
as you've obviously just witnessed.
You're referring to the witches
constantly hunting me.
That wouldn't happen to be some of
your doing, now, would it, friend?
Not by intent, but it's why I'm here.
If I'm to shift things back
to the way things were,
to give evil a fighting chance again,
then you and I must work together.
Now, why would you wanna
give me a fighting chance?
To restore the balance,
the grand design,
as I am honour-bound to do.
Just out of curiosity,
how is it this imbalance
happened to occur?
Come on. You can say it.
I know you can.
"I made my move on the boy
and I screwed up."
I took a calculated risk.
You screwed up.
And now you wanna hide out
down here with me,
and just hope that the boy's aunties
don't know how to find you.
Isn't that about right, friend?
Believe me, you don't want this child
growing up any more than I do, Barbas.
His power is too great.
He is an enormous threat
to both of us.
I see.
Any shift between good and evil
is supposed to happen
naturally over time.
By intervening,
I've allowed too much good
to corrupt the other world.
And the only way to get it back
is for a great evil to corrupt ours.
Oh, and you just naturally
thought of me.
I'm very flattered.
I have to complete what I started,
for everyone's sake.
Help me.
Distract the sisters.
And I will help you
get your world back.
You won't find Gideon that way.
We've already tried.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to remind you
of your responsibilities.
My responsibilities now
are to protect my son.
How? By taking revenge
on one of our own?
Gideon stopped being one of us
when he went after Wyatt.
Oh, that's not for you to decide.
You're but one voice
in a chorus, Leo.
We can't allow you to take matters
into your own hands.
- Gideon did.
- Yes, and look what's he's wrought.
The world is spiralling out of control.
Innocents are being hurt, killed.
- All because one Elder acted alone.
- I know what I'm doing.
Gideon thought he knew
what he was doing too.
Truth be known, he was not alone
in his thinking.
There are others who share
his fears of Wyatt.
That your union with a Charmed One
might have created too great
a concentration of power.
- Wait, so you're on his side?
- No, of course not.
- What Gideon's done is inexcusable.
- Then let me handle him.
Please, Leo, your emotions
are clouding your better judgment.
The fate of the world is more important
than any one child.
Not more important than my son.
They're all your sons,
your daughters.
They're who you should be protecting.
That's the greater good.
Come, help us find a way to restore
what was while we still can.
I can't.
Not until I stop Gideon.
Anti-immunologist to the quarantine.
You're all done, sir.
All you have to do is pay your fine.
Okay.
- You know, I'd really like to, but I can't.
- Over here?
Wow, it's just as creepy in here
as it is out there.
Actually, creepier.
Welcome to
San Francisco Memorial,
how can I help, help, help you?
Well, you could take it
down a notch.
She's kidding. She's a kidder.
Just out of curiosity,
what happened here?
- Was it a freeway accident?
- Oh, heavens, no.
It's always like this around here.
- Lawbreakers, you know.
- Right.
- You visiting?
- Yes. Piper Halliwell.
Halliwell, Halliwell.
What was her offence?
Oh, no, no offence.
She's having a baby.
Oh, a baby!
Oh, why didn't you say so?
- Because we were just too excited.
- Oh, of course you are.
There's nothing more exciting
than a baby.
Room 1402. But don't dawdle.
Visiting hours are almost over.
You have a wonderful day,
now, okay?
Day?
It's almost 8:00.
It should be dark now.
Dark? Why on earth would anyone
say such a depressing thing?
Lmagine the sun going away,
not having sunshine all the time.
Anyone who'd want
that should be, well, well, shot.
She's joking.
It's my sister, the jokester.
We're gonna go see
our other sister now.
She's having a baby. Yeah.
Okay, have a good day, everyone.
Oh, there you guys are.
Where have you been?
- Seems normal.
- Come on, come in.
- Piper, you okay?
- Of course I'm okay.
I'm having a baby,
for crying out loud.
Jell-O? It's really yummy.
No, thanks.
Excuse me.
How'd you like your dinner?
Are you kidding? The frozen peas
and processed turkey?
It was to die for.
Oh, here, let me give you a hand.
- Piper, that's not funny.
- Oh, that's okay.
- It's my fault it even happened.
- Why is it your fault?
I used my cell phone in the hospital.
Talk about your big no-nos.
- Hey, good luck with the little one.
- Thanks.
He really should have known better.
Piper, snap out of it.
This is crazy-making.
- What is?
- This. Everything.
You, the hand,
the whole damn world.
It's driving me insane.
Phoebe, you really should not swear.
They will cut your tongue out.
This is ridiculous.
Okay, Piper, you have to listen to me.
Wyatt is in danger.
What do you mean?
What kind of danger?
It's Gideon.
He's trying to kill him.
- It's not funny, I'm being serious.
- That's ridiculous.
He's an Elder. He couldn't hurt a fly.
- What's so funny?
- Oh, don't ask.
- Whoopsie, that's not good.
- What's not good? What's going on?
Those darn contractions are a lot
more painful than they should be.
- What does that mean?
- Visiting hours are over. Bye-bye, now.
- No, we're not leaving her.
- Well, I'm sorry, but rules are rules.
Did you wanna keep your legs?
- We'll call you.
- Okey-dokey.
Are you sure we should leave?
I'm worried about her.
We have to. We can't wait for Leo.
We have to fix this.
This isn't the world we want
Chris to be born into.
Okay, but how?
Okay? Especially now
that we're down a sister?
Maybe we should have
another little talk with ourselves.
You were right.
Piper's the only one
of the sisters affected.
And therefore the only one
that can affect her sisters.
She can cast a spell on them,
make them think as she does,
so that they won't be
concerned about me either.
And your theory is that I'm
going to make her do this.
How, exactly?
By doing what you do best:
Tapping into her fear
of losing her sisters.
I don't know.
She's out in cloud-cuckooland
someplace.
She's in a place where she doesn't
even fear her own affliction.
What makes you think
she's gonna fear losing a sister?
Family means everything to Piper.
In any world.
The sooner you hit that nerve,
the sooner we both
get what we want.
Anything?
I thought I had him for a second,
but I lost him.
Well, keep looking.
Gideon's bound to surface again.
Well, maybe you should ask
the other Elders for some help.
No.
Trouble in paradise?
Let's just say we're not
seeing eye to eye.
Well, then, maybe you should,
I don't know, quit.
The girls are gonna need another
whitelighter the moment I'm gone.
That's not why you
want me to quit, Chris.
Okay. Fine, I admit.
I'd like to go back to a future where
my parents are still together, all right?
It's just like I said
when I was making the potion...
Potion.
- What about the potion?
- Gideon didn't want it to work, right?
But he did want us in this other world,
which means it probably does work,
which means we can get you home.
- No. I'm not going back.
- Chris, you have to.
Not until I finish what I came here
to do, and that's to save Wyatt from...
Turning evil.
What?
Well, what I don't understand is,
if Gideon always viewed
Wyatt as a threat,
why did he turn him evil in my future?
I don't think he did, intentionally.
I think Gideon tried to kill
Wyatt in your future.
Only, just like in this time, he found out
that Wyatt can protect himself.
So he probably had to get him away
so he could figure out how to do it.
- You mean kidnap him.
- Imagine being taken away from us
for weeks, maybe even months,
constantly fending off
Gideon's attack.
I had no idea.
We're gonna change
that future, Chris.
For both of your sakes.
The power of four has worked before.
Yeah, but that was when
we were in the same world.
We can't even contact them now.
There must have been a way that
Gideon contacted his evil counterpart.
Hey, do you hear an echo?
- I knew it.
Nice to see you.
So is your world as
messed up as ours?
I've never seen everybody
so miserable.
- Every little good thing that happens...
- Gets punished.
Limbs get cut off
for saying "gesundheit."
I never thought I'd say this,
but I would kill for
some daylight right now.
We got plenty of it in our world.
- It sucks.
So, what do you think happened?
I think we did too much
good together
when we were trying to
get Gideon in your world.
My thoughts exactly.
Maybe we need to do some
serious evil on your side
to shift the balance back.
- Right.
- The problem is,
I don't know if our collective powers
will work with us in different worlds.
Well, we better think of
something fast,
because Gideon's still
after Wyatt in both of them.
- The power of three.
- What?
If we can cast a spell on
our respective Pipers...
We're back to full power again.
Then bring us to your side
so we could shift the balance back.
And then kick some ass.
I like it.
Security to the prison floor.
Does it hurt when I touch here?
Boy, that smarts.
Well, we might be looking
at a C-section here, Piper.
Might be the only way
to get the baby out safely.
Safely?
Oh, let's get another ultrasound,
shall we? I'll be right back.
It would be so sad if your sisters
weren't here to help you
through all this.
You heard what they said
about Gideon.
Imagine, saying such ugly lies
about such a nice person.
Gideon is trying to kill Wyatt,
we have to stop him.
No, no, no, no.
- Stop it. He's an Elder.
- No, Piper, he's evil.
No, he's not. Now, shush
before someone hears you.
No, no, no, don't hurt them.
They didn't mean it.
You have to help them conform.
Save them from themselves
before it's too late
and you lose them forever.
Call now the powers blessed be
To make my sisters happ... Happy
What are you doing here?
Is Piper okay?
No, but she will be, thanks to us
and our evil twins.
Wait, you saw them? Where?
In Gideon's office.
Talk about your vanity mirrors.
We have a plan.
We're gonna shift the world
back from Gideon
so he can't use it to his advantage.
- How?
- We're gonna use a spell to...
- What just happened?
- I don't know.
- Are you guys all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I've never felt better.
Okay, so back to the plan.
You were saying?
Yeah, the plan is just to go
see Piper in the hospital.
- That's a really good plan.
- I know.
No time to dawdle.
There's a baby on the way.
Guys, this is crazy.
You can't leave like this.
Well, we can't very well ignore
Chris' birth. We have to celebrate.
I'm the baby.
I give you permission not to.
What, and miss all the excitement?
Seeing you for the first time.
Burping you.
Picking out a name.
I already have a name.
Oh, gosh, you do, don't you?
Well, now would be
the perfect time to change.
How did you get your name?
It doesn't start with a P.
It was Leo's father's name.
That is so sweet.
I can't wait to tell Piper.
I'm gonna get her bag.
It's in the kitchen, all ready to go.
Oh, you are gonna be so cute.
Yes, you are. Yes, you are.
Okay.
We need to snap them
out of this, fast.
Piper must have cast a spell.
She's the only one who could do this.
- Why would she do that?
- She wouldn't.
Unless Gideon wanted her to,
to distract them like before
so he can go after Wyatt.
- All set.
- Let's go.
You guys can't leave yet. Gideon
might be coming for Wyatt any minute.
Oh, is he babysitting?
No, he's trying to kill Wyatt.
Don't tell me you don't remember.
You're laughing. That's great.
Your nephew's almost killed,
and you're laughing.
You're silly. Yes, you are.
Oh, yes, you are.
Like an Elder would ever,
ever do that.
Must be the spell. They don't remember
because Gideon doesn't want them to.
A spell? What spell?
Visitors.
Hey, stay with Wyatt.
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, you cannot open that door.
- What if it's the patrolman?
- That's a good point.
I forgot to move my car.
Finally.
Well, I'll just have to take
whatever's coming to me.
What?
- Hi, ladies. Chris.
- Hi.
We thought you were the patrol guy,
come to shoot Phoebe.
Sorry. Actually, I'm here to get Chris.
I'm afraid I have to take him
into custody for assaulting me.
Dude, I didn't assault you.
- No, but evil Chris did.
- That wasn't me.
- You're still a fugitive anyways.
- Okay, you're not helping, thanks.
You know, I'm only giving you this
chance because we used to be friends.
That is so sweet, Darryl.
And evil double or no,
someone has to do the time.
Take him away, Darryl.
- So, what, you're just gonna leave?
- Listen, young man,
we can do this the easy way
or the hard way. Your choice.
I don't have time for this.
Have a nice day.
I was thinking if Gideon did get to
Piper, maybe he left a trail I can follow.
Hurry.
If I know Leo, then right around now
he'll be figuring out
that I made Piper cast the spell.
No, no, no, correction,
I made her cast the spell, remember?
The point being
he'll go to Piper next
to see if he can't find
any magical clues to find me.
- Find me, you mean.
- Actually, yes.
- But then again, that's what we want.
- Oh, really?
With the sisters
sufficiently distracted,
Leo is the last powerful being
in my way.
One who you should
easily be able to distract
whilst I make my move on Wyatt.
I don't know, this all is starting
to sound very interesting,
but, you know, it seems to me like I'm
the one doing all the heavy lifting here.
- Have you noticed that?
- Barbas!
While you, you're hiding out
down here,
relaxing in my lair,
all safe and sound.
What could possibly be wrong
with that picture?
Leo is the last impediment,
I promise.
Paralyse him with his greatest fear,
keep him occupied,
and we'll be one step closer
to returning the world to a place
where evil at least
has a chance again.
You're such a tease.
Excuse me, do you know
where the maternity ward is?
Are you kidding?
That's everyone's favourite hang-out.
- Just go in that elevator and...
- Thanks.
You're welcome.
- Paige.
- Leo.
Well, it's about time the nervous
father made an appearance.
Where's Phoebe? Is she with Piper?
Of course. We would never leave
Piper alone at a time like this.
Good. I wanna ask her
if she's seen Gideon.
Gideon? No, silly,
not with the complication.
Complication?
- Oh, dear, you don't know?
- Know what? Is something wrong?
Well, I'm sure the doctors
are gonna find out any minute
and everything is gonna be
just peachy.
- I gotta go see her.
- No. That's against the hospital rules.
- Screw the rules.
- Okay.
But you're going to get in trouble.
Wyatt?
Watch as the thing you fear most
comes to life and the future is lost.
- What?
- What's the matter, Dad?
Don't you recognize me?
I'm the Wyatt you're trying to save.
The one from Chris' future.
It'd appear that there is
no way to save him,
that he is lost to evil.
Excalibur.
And that you are a failure
as a father.
This isn't right. You're good.
I'm here to save you.
I don't think so.
Hello?
Okay. It's time to get you out of here.
Don't make me sacrifice you both.
Dad.
Chris.
In trying to save one son,
you have lost both sons.
- Very, very sad.
- No!
Wyatt. Wyatt.
It's for the best, Leo.
Chris. Chris.
Finally.
Now what are you doing?
Would you come on?
Let's get this thing over with.
Not so fast.
This will take some thinking.
And I'd prefer not to get
stabbed again if I can avoid it.
How cute.
The great big Elder is afraid
of the teeny-weeny, itsy-bitsy baby.
Oh, he's much more than that.
Trust me. Cocky, too.
Notice his shield's not even up.
His shield is not up
because you pierced it already.
Fools and idiots.
Why is it that every time
you want something done right,
you gotta do it yourself?
No!
Slippery little devil, isn't he?
Now look what you've done.
Well, you didn't tell me
that he could orb.
I didn't know he could.
That's why I wanted to be careful.
Although I doubt he's able
to orb out of the underworld.
Even he's not that powerful yet.
Now, I suppose all of this means
that you've lost your interest
in fixing the world at this moment.
And allow the Charmed Ones
the chance to rescue him? No.
The world stays exactly as it is
until Wyatt is eliminated.
You and I will have to work
together to find him.
Quickly.
Or perhaps we could work together
in order to eliminate him,
seeing as how much trouble
you're having by yourself.
Interesting.
It could work, especially if you
bless the athame too.
But to try,
we need to get him back.
Well, then, you track him
with his orbs.
I'm going to track him
with his fears.
- You have to find Wyatt.
- We're gonna find him together.
It won't work, you've already tried.
Gideon's magic did this to me.
He's the only one who can stop it.
Just go.
Saving Wyatt saves the future.
You know that.
Gideon doesn't know how
to kill Wyatt, remember?
- We still have time.
- Only till the trauma turns him.
I'm not gonna choose between
you and Wyatt, Chris. I can't.
You don't have to, Dad.
Find Gideon...
...and you save us both.
All right. All right, but I'm not
leaving you alone. I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
To get your one of your aunts
to watch over you.
Look, you're gonna be fine, okay?
I promise.
Okay, Auntie Paige, big smile.
Leo, don't you think you
should be more careful?
I mean, you don't wanna
bring back the witch trials.
Gideon got to Chris.
He's hurt bad.
What? Now, why would Gideon
want to hurt Chris?
- To get to Wyatt, which he's done.
- Gideon is the paragon of all good.
I told you that, remember?
- Smile.
- But he's not good.
He's trying to kill my sons.
Your nephews. How can that be
good under any circumstances?
- Oh, I don't know, but...
- You don't understand. Chris is dying.
- What?
- I have to find Gideon,
but I can't leave Chris alone.
Somebody has to be with him.
Come on. I know, deep down inside,
family matters to you
more than this twisted sense
of right and wrong.
You love him, I know you do.
And that's gotta trump everything,
even this stupid spell that you're under.
You have to help me save him.
You have to help me
save them both. Please.
- What just happened?
- I think we were under a spell.
And he took us out of it.
- Okay, come on. Let's go.
- No, we can't all go.
Piper's being prepped for surgery.
- Surgery? What's the matter?
- They're not saying.
Don't worry, we're not
gonna lose either Chris.
I'll go home, you stay here,
and you, you go find Gideon.
Chris?
Easy, easy.
We got one of them. Stand by.
- Darryl, what's going on?
- Good day, Miss Matthews.
- Where's Chris?
- Chris?
Chris who?
Paige, please.
We've been waiting here to give you
one last chance to turn him in,
for your sake.
Go to hell.
Watch your tongue.
He's gotta be hiding
in the underworld.
I agree. It's the only place
he can go to avoid being sensed.
Which means he must have
both of our Wyatts there too.
Still, it's too vast.
We have to narrow it down.
Wait, it is too vast.
For Gideon too, right?
- Somebody's gotta be helping him.
- But who?
Whoever helped him
get to Piper in the hospital.
- I went and tried to pick up a trail.
- But I was overwhelmed with...
...hope.
- Fear.
- Barbas.
- So if we find Barbas...
- We'll find Gideon.
For both of our sons.
Damn.
Leo. Leo.
Sorry. I was in the underworld,
looking for...
What's wrong?
What's going on?
The hell are you doing here?
Nothing. We didn't have to.
I'm sorry, Leo.
- Chris.
- Hey.
Hey, I'm here right now.
You can hold on, okay?
Hold on, hold on.
I'm here. You can hold on, okay?
Don't give up, okay?
You either.
No, no, no, please.
No.
No, please. No.
No! No!
Leo, stop it.
What are you trying to do, kill us?
This isn't gonna bring him back.
I promised him
I'd get him home safely.
I know, but you can still
save his future.
And you can still save Wyatt,
we just have to hurry.
And you have to focus, okay?
Look, you were saying something
about the underworld,
about looking for
something there. What?
Barbas.
Barbas? What's he got
to do with this?
He's working with Gideon.
That's how I think he got to Piper,
that's how I think he got to me.
Gideon teamed up
with a demon for that?
No.
An act of great evil in our world
restores the balance.
That's what I think
he was using Barbas for.
So they're working together.
That means they must be
in contact with each other, right?
So?
So that means maybe that's
a way to find Gideon.
The next time they try to contact
each other, you can just intercept it.
Wyatt?
Wyatt, can you hear me? It's Daddy.
Hello, son.
So sorry to lure you like this.
Barbas, where are you?
Barbas.
It's time.
Well, it took you long enough.
Your impatience is growing tiresome.
I blessed it already.
Now it's your turn.
Is something wrong?
As a matter of fact...
...there is.
Why?
Because you murdered my son.
I'll be right back.
Leo, please.
You have to understand.
I am only doing this
for the greater good, I swear.
How is killing a child
ever for the greater good, huh?
And who the hell are you
to decide that?
I'm an Elder, so are you.
It's what we do.
I'm not one of you anymore.
Leo, listen to me.
You know what happens.
You know what
Chris came here to stop.
Let me finish what I started.
Let me save the future
the only way it can be saved.
You're the reason the future's
threatened, Gideon. Not Wyatt,
- No.
- But because of what you do to him.
I'm about to make sure neither one
of you get the chance again. Mirror.
- You ready?
- Yeah, but remember,
you can't do anything.
I have to do this alone.
I know.
- Do what?
- A great evil.
Fade away? What do you mean,
he just faded away?
In Leo's arms, after he died.
Yeah, maybe he didn't die, I mean,
maybe he was just going back...
Oh, God.
Poor Leo.
Dr. Roberts, how's Piper?
Well, it depends on how
you look at it, I suppose.
Me, I like to think she's
moving off to a better place.
- What?
- What is that supposed to mean?
Well, I think you know what I mean.
She's haemorrhaging.
We can't stop it. It's everywhere.
But let's all try
to think positively, shall we?
No, you listen to me.
You get your ass back in that room
and you save my sister and her baby,
you understand me?
Security.
- Let's take care of this.
- Locked and loaded.
Okay, they shoot people here,
remember?
We gotta get Piper out of here.
We gotta get her to Leo.
We can't.
We don't know where Leo is.
We can't just do nothing.
What's going on?
Phoebe, it's night.
Everything's back to normal?
I'll do everything I can, I promise.
Excuse me.
Leo must have done something.
You have no idea what you've done.
Didn't know you had it in you.
Our worlds can never
cross over again.
Take care of your family.
You too.
Hi.
I got you. You're safe now.
I have you.
- To Triage.
Please report to Triage, stat.
He found him.
Hey.
- Is he okay?
- Yeah.
He wasn't with Gideon long enough
to do any damage.
What happened to Gideon?
How's Piper?
She's resting comfortably.
Is she okay?
We stopped the bleeding.
Obviously, we had
to perform a C-section,
but I think she's gonna be okay.
And the baby, is he all right?
You tell me.
Congratulations.
He's perfectly healthy.
Really?
Oh, look, he's beautiful.
Baby Christopher.
That's your brother.
Looks like we didn't lose him
after all.
Can we see Piper?
Well, maybe just one of you for now.
Go tell her we love her.
Where'd that baby go?
That's your brother.