Previously on Charmed:
Leo's missing.
The Elders think he's been kidnapped.
- Leo, I didn't know you had it in you.
- I've changed.
- That was awesome.
- Piper doesn't complain anymore.
- You took my feelings away?
- Pain almost destroyed you.
- I wanted to help you.
- I am an empath.
I'm a dog walker.
We just need to borrow
your soul for a couple of hours.
This is definitely over the limit.
Don't freak out, because magic got us
into this and magic will get us out.
- I don't belong here.
- You have much to teach my warriors.
Attack!
He needs our help.
The only way to get close to Leo
is by proving to the Valkyries
you're one of them.
They tried to kill us
when we tried to save him.
You left us.
I promise I will explain everything
when we get home.
- We don't have a home.
- Her heart is breaking.
Come on, Piper, we gotta go.
Go? Go where?
We gotta leave her. Come on!
- Be careful of Darryl's body.
- Thank you.
Is he...? I mean, am I still alive?
- Barely.
- Barely?
- We gotta go back and get Piper.
- How, by force?
She won't come. She's withdrawn.
Besides, we can't go back now.
- But we can't just leave her there.
- They're not gonna hurt her.
They need her to get to us.
Listen, about my body...
Oh, I'm sorry.
You can just step right back in.
That's it?
I mean, even though I'm solid?
You're still a spirit, trust me.
Okay, we gotta go
and figure out what to do.
Thanks again.
Don't mention it.
Great. That's just great.
Jeez, it's about time.
I was starting to get worr...
- Where's Piper?
- You son of a bitch.
- Why'd you do it?
- Do what?
Leo, stop it!
Leo, enough!
This hostility is killing me.
What is wrong with you?
You've been playing gladiator too long?
You didn't tell them, did you?
- Tell us what?
- That he was the last one to see me.
Right afterwards, I was
mysteriously trapped in Valhalla.
Oh, so, what,
that makes me responsible?
- Is that what you're saying?
- Why would Chris do that?
- Why else? To get rid of me.
- That doesn't make sense.
Doesn't it? He manipulated things
so I'd become an Elder.
- Forced me out of the house.
- So you could save the world.
All right, Leo,
I know how upset you are.
And by "know,"
I mean I literally know.
But you're way off base here.
Chris has been the model whitelighter
since you've been gone.
He's done nothing but good.
He sent us after so many demons,
if anything, he's been too good.
He's the reason we were
able to save you.
You're welcome.
- Where'd you get the pendants?
- Leo.
All right.
All right, I'll let it go for now.
- So where's Wyatt? Can I see him?
- No, you can't.
He's staying with Sheila until
we figure out how to rescue Piper.
Which is gonna be hard,
because she doesn't wanna be saved.
If we're gonna save her, it'll have
to be as witches, not as Valkyries.
- Book of Shadows?
- Got it.
- Well?
- She's Valkyrie.
But it's not pure.
- Deep inside, I sense...
- Witch?
- Yes.
- I told you.
She came with the other witches.
She has to be one too.
But it's very faint.
I could barely read it.
Still, she helped them escape
with the warrior, didn't she?
Yes, but she didn't escape with them.
- Maybe they left her.
- Why would they do that?
Because they would have
been caught if they hadn't.
Either way, she can be
of value to us.
She wouldn't be the first witch
to convert.
And if she has, then we've
gained a powerful sister.
But if it is just a spell
and she's not truly one of us,
then we'll use her to lead us
to the other two.
After all, we can't have anybody
knowing where to find us
and risking what we do,
now, can we?
The warriors who pursued, aren't you
concerned about them being exposed?
They're well-trained.
They'll know how to avoid it.
Besides, hopefully
they'll find the witches
and take care of the problem for us.
What do you think about that?
I think that if they don't, we will.
I don't understand. Why don't we
just storm the place and find her.
- Not like we don't know where she is.
- They'd be expecting it, that's why.
- It would be suicide.
- We got you out, didn't we?
- But it cost us Piper.
- Okay, guys, would you knock it off?
I'm still reeling from Piper's emotions.
I don't need this.
Sorry.
So how's it going?
I am almost done.
I don't mean to burden you with
my emotions,
but I don't quite see how reversing
the memory spell is gonna help.
Piper needs to believe
she's a Valkyrie
because it's too painful
for her to be herself.
Way too painful, believe me.
I almost passed out back there.
Then believing she's a Valkyrie
is the perfect option.
To serve the greater good,
they're always in control.
They don't deal with pain or loss.
Well, that's why we have to make
Piper believe she's Piper again.
If we don't get her back mentally,
it won't matter if we get her physically.
Okay, but Piper wasn't exactly
back before the spell either.
- What do you mean?
- Well, that magical whammy
you performed on her
kind of backfired.
Yeah, you see, after you left,
Piper was really...
Chipper.
Yeah, incessantly, increasingly,
annoyingly chipper.
What she said.
It was supposed
to make her feel less pain.
I guess with me not around
to pull it back a little bit,
she got happier and happier?
No, psychotically chipper.
Way to go.
- Chris.
- What?
Oh, I swear my new power
is gonna drive me crazy.
You'll get the handle of it.
Just be patient.
Are you sure? Because I remember
Prue almost being destroyed
that time that she was an empath.
Well, she wasn't supposed
to become one. You are.
Maybe all this with Piper has
made it happen a little sooner,
but you can handle it,
I know you can.
I just wish I knew how
to turn it on and off.
I feel like I'm at the mercy of
everyone else's feelings, and it sucks.
Bright side, maybe you can actually
find out how Jason feels about you.
Yeah, but what if it's not good news?
Then you dump him
before he dumps you.
I think the spell's finished.
Oh, great.
- You got a dog?
- No, I got a career.
Sore subject. Don't ask.
All right, I'm coming.
Oh, my God.
Darryl, what happened?
I think I just got attacked
by Attila the Hun.
Freyja, I need to speak with you.
In private.
You can speak freely.
The warriors who
followed the witches,
they've killed civilians.
- What?
- Innocents?
I don't know,
but they turned off their locators.
What does that mean?
They're trained to do that
when the final battle between
good and evil begins.
- We have to stop them.
- But how can we?
We have no way
of finding them in the city.
I'm from the city.
I can help you find them.
- Feeling better?
- Yeah.
Thanks, man.
It's good to have you back.
- Thanks for helping me get back.
- Don't mention it.
Would you...?
How long after we left
did the warriors show up?
Not long, maybe a couple seconds.
They must have followed us
from Valhalla.
Right. That means they're
after us now.
Except they didn't hang out long
enough to ask me where to find you.
I was looking through swollen eyes, but
they just seemed lost and confused.
- So, what, they just took off?
- Thank goodness they did...
We should've never put you
in that situation.
We should've come up with
another way.
- Forget it. You know, it worked.
- Yeah, for you, maybe.
What about the next poor guy
that runs into those warriors?
They're trained killers.
- Yeah, but they only kill evil.
- He's not evil.
Chris is right.
Not everything is black and white.
Warriors can't always tell
the difference between good and evil.
- What do we do?
- Well, we need to find them, fast.
That shouldn't be too hard.
They'll stand out.
Even in San Francisco.
Which is why we need to move fast.
If they're exposed, so are the Valkyries.
Awfully forgiving, considering
everything they put you through.
They still have a noble purpose
to perform.
Keeping their secret is key
to them fulfilling it.
Besides, it's not the Valkyries'
fault that I ended up there.
Which brings us back to the warriors.
And let's not forget about Piper.
Maybe we should split up.
You should go to the police station.
They're gonna show up
on the radar screen.
You know what?
My office is paging me anyway.
Make sure you're first on the scene.
We might need to buy some time.
Okay, you got it.
Maybe I should go to the newspaper
and do the same.
Good idea. Paige.
I should take Oscar home
before I get fired.
You're kidding, right?
No. I promised the temp agency
I'd have him back in the morning,
and it's the morning.
Listen, before you say anything,
you've been gone,
some things have changed.
One of those things is that
I'm determined, now more than ever,
to have a life separate
from being a witch.
Fine, but now?
Yeah. I've already done
the reversal spell.
Can't do it without Piper,
and we don't know how to get her, so...
I'm just an orb away
if you need help.
- Paige...
- Let her go.
It might seem silly to you,
but it's important to her, I know.
See? It helps to be an empath.
No, it helps to be a sister.
And while we're on that subject,
we have to come up with another plan
to get Piper out of Valhalla.
She's right.
- Let's go.
- But...
- Come on, in here.
- Easy!
Who goes there?
What's the matter,
don't you recognize me?
Leo. But we'd heard that
the witches had broken you out.
Disinformation. Enemy's favourite
tactic. Don't fall for it again.
Right. Sorry.
It's just that everyone's a little on edge
since the alert's been sounded again.
I know. I caught the intruder.
Where's Freyja?
She'll want to question him.
She's not here.
She went after the warriors.
And the new Valkyrie, where is she?
- They took her with them.
- All right.
Then I'll have to question him myself.
Alone.
What are you doing?
Leo, what's going on?
I'm gonna get the truth out of you
one way or another.
No sisters around here
to help you this time.
No orbing, no way out.
Just you and me.
You're joking, right?
I mean, shouldn't we be getting back
to fill in Phoebe and Paige
- and find Piper?
- I already lost Piper. Pick it up.
You know, this isn't funny anymore.
And this isn't very Elder-like either.
Being trapped here for five weeks
and fighting for my life
has changed me a lot.
Pick it up.
Forget it.
I didn't do it.
You can't kill me, I'm a whitelighter.
No? Then why are you sweating?
I'm gonna find out the truth.
I'm gonna find out who
did this to me, I promise.
Right now, we're gonna catch up
with Phoebe and Paige
and have a little chat with the Elders.
This is the last place they were
before they turned off their locators.
Why did they do this?
This is not what we're
training them for.
Maybe they were confused
by all the evil in the city.
It's everywhere.
Then how will we find them
before they hurt anybody else?
- I could scry for them.
- You mean like a witch can?
What do you need?
Something of the warriors.
The knife.
Anything else?
Well.
Hell's bells,
what have we got here?
What, is there a X ena convention
in town or something?
On your knees.
Excuse me?
I got a better idea.
How about you get
on your knees instead.
- Who are you to speak to us that way?
- Kara.
You don't command us,
we command you.
- How dare you?
- This isn't Valhalla.
You don't have dominion
over men here.
Then how do you train them?
How do they take orders?
They don't.
They do what they want.
You know, I have an idea of
how we could blend in better.
A motorcycle, Darryl?
Are you sure?
That is just so not Piper.
Leo did say that she might be back.
All right, well, I'll call Paige,
and you keep an eye...
Oh, my God.
Let me call you back,
let me call you back. Jason!
- Hi! What are you doing here?
- Who, me?
- I own the place.
- Right.
And I work here, that's why I'm...
What was I saying?
Did you forget I was flying in today?
No. Of course I didn't forget that
you were flying back today.
I'm just a little scattered, that's all.
Is the air conditioning
not working in here or what?
It feels fine to me.
Phoebe, you look great.
Really.
I like your hair.
Thanks.
I like yours too.
Listen, I was gonna go home,
unpack, take a shower.
But I was hoping that maybe later
we could get together
and have some dinner.
You know? I know we don't have
anything planned officially,
but, you know,
I was thinking that we could...
- I'm gonna take that as a yes, then?
- Oh, no, no.
No, no, no. No. No, no.
No? All right.
I just really missed you, Phoebe. L...
Oh, I know. I can tell.
It's just... It's very hard.
I mean... I mean, hard to explain.
That kind of hard, you know.
Not the other kind of hard.
You know? Am I making any sense?
- Phoebe...
- No, no, no. Don't come any closer.
It'll just get harder.
Oh, God.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
Stop, stop. Piper.
No! No!
No, wait. It's me.
You're making a mistake.
This is not the final battle. We've come
to take you back to Valhalla.
What do you think?
I think the enemy
wears many masks.
Well, you're the agency, how could
you not know they were leaving town?
They abandoned their dog.
That is animal cruelty, okay?
No, I can't take care of the dog.
I've got... I've got responsibilities.
Pressing ones, too.
And besides, I need to make
a statement to my family.
This is not helping here.
Hello?
What am I doing?
Okay, I've just gotta trust
the universe.
Things happen for a reason.
What is going on here?
Badass fight, that's what.
Who said that?
Oh, wait, you mean
you can hear me?
Well, hallelujah. It's about time.
Please don't tell me
you're talking to me.
Are you kidding? I've been trying to
get your attention for two days now.
- I'm in serious trouble here.
- Okay. It's okay, Paige.
You've dealt with
weirder things than this.
Maybe my powers
are just advancing.
Maybe I can understand animals now.
Oh, please, give me a break.
Until you accepted that there
might be a reason you got this job,
you weren't gonna be
open to helping me.
Help you do what?
Reverse an evil witch's curse.
Make me human again.
Come on, if I'm evil too, it won't work.
You know that.
What have you got to lose?
Well, that's a good point.
This day couldn't get much suckier.
Okay, here goes.
I call upon the Halliwells
I call our powers to undo this spell
Make right again, that we must
Reverse the curse that made this mutt
That's better. Thanks.
All right. Don't mention it.
As long as you don't hump my leg
anymore, we'll be cool.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
That's just what dogs do
when they like someone.
Oh, that's very sweet.
So why did an evil witch turn you
into man's best friend, anyway?
Well, it's kind of complicated.
Let's just say there
are a million reasons.
But let me help you.
All those dogs out there,
they're barking because there's
some serious magic in the air,
the kind of magic that you
might be looking for.
I am so sorry.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
Why not? Why are you apologizing?
- You were unbelievable.
- Oh, please don't say it.
Just don't.
- Well, it wasn't just you, you know.
- Oh, yeah.
I know. I just...
I wasn't myself, that's all.
I don't understand.
Yeah, I know you don't,
and that's okay.
As long as you stay
on that side of the room,
everything should be fine.
It's the only way that I really know
what I'm feeling.
- Phoebe.
- Please, please.
- Please, please. Don't, don't.
- Hey.
What's the matter?
You can talk to me.
We like each other, Phoebe.
You don't have to be afraid of that.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- Really?
- Really.
Come here.
Oh, no. Not again.
- What?
- What do you mean, "what"?
Don't think I don't know.
- Hi.
- Excuse us. You got a minute?
- Yeah.
What is the matter?
Weren't you supposed to be?
But you don't have to yell at me.
I can sense how mad you are.
Okay, just because you can sense
doesn't mean I can't vent.
- Where are we going right now?
- To find Piper.
- You know where she is?
- Yeah, a little doggie told me.
No!
Come on. Get up.
Way to go, Piper.
What? She's good.
I'll take care of them.
Reverse the spell.
Spell was cast, now make it pass
Remove it now, don't ask me how
Well, it serves you right.
What kind of spell was that?
Okay, Piper, I know why you
would rather be one of them.
It's because you don't
wanna feel pain.
But you have to feel the pain,
because if you can't feel the pain,
then you can't feel
the good stuff either, you know?
Right?
Oh, and that was so much better.
Police, drop your weapons.
Piper.
Now do you believe me?
Go, get in.
Piper, let's go.
Piper, don't go.
Hurry.
Please.
There's gotta be a way
to get Piper out of there.
I know it.
Well, unfortunately, the reversal spell,
as you so kindly pointed out,
didn't exactly help Piper
remember who she was.
What do the Elders think?
They think it had to be a demon
who stuck Leo in Valhalla.
- But they're not sure.
- Still, it's their leading theory.
Guys, this is about Piper.
Actually, the Elders believe your new
power is key to helping save Piper.
My new power? How do they figure?
All it's done is make things worse.
There's a reason you received it,
and they...
We believe it's to help save Piper.
So, what exactly did you feel
the last time from her?
Not much.
But you said you felt
something familiar, little things?
Well, I mean, obviously I felt pain.
And desire to help.
Okay, well, she helped Darryl.
That wasn't with her Valkyrie powers,
that was with her Charmed powers.
- The witch within must still be alive.
- That's how you'll reach her.
Yeah, but how?
I mean, just because I could feel
some glimmer of Piper's feelings
doesn't mean she can.
- She's completely cut off from them.
- Wait, wait, wait, hold it.
Isn't there a spell that allows
somebody to feel what you feel?
Which in this case would be
Piper feeling
what you're feeling
Piper should be feeling.
Did that make sense?
Frighteningly, it did.
What about the spell
I used on Cole last year?
The one to make him sense
whether or not you loved him?
I could reword it for Piper.
Actually, that's worth a shot.
You still have to get close to her
to try it, and that's not gonna be easy.
- Especially with Piper's powers.
- Maybe I can orb you.
No, Leo. You're the reason she's
in this emotional cocoon.
You need to stay far away from her.
No offence.
Well, then the question is
how do we get close enough to her
without her kicking our butts?
I could use my new power
to counteract hers.
- How do you figure?
- Our powers are emotion-based, right?
If I can channel Piper's feelings,
why can't I channel her powers?
And then use them against her.
What are you doing here?
We're here to take you home.
Why does she always
pick on me first?
Paige, now!
Open Piper's heart to reveal
That part which only Phoebe feels
Send it back from whence it came
But don't protect her from the pain
- No, wait.
- Did they harm you?
No, they helped me.
I know what you do here.
I understand its purpose.
So you can trust
that your secret is safe.
But I think it's time
for me to go home.
- Jason Dean.
- Hi.
Hi, Phoebe.
I was starting to get a little worried.
Did you get all my messages?
Yeah, I did. And I'm sorry
I didn't call you back, but...
Let me guess, something came up.
- You're a mysterious woman, Phoebe.
- Is that a bad thing?
No, it's a good thing.
Except for when I'm trying
to figure you out.
Well, if it makes you feel
any better,
I'm having a hard time
figuring myself out these days.
I'm glad.
I mean, I'm, you know...
Not that you're having trouble.
It's just that it's not about me.
It's not about me, is it?
No, it's not about you.
It's just that my feelings have been
a little mixed up lately.
Well, long-distance relationships
are not easy.
No, they're not.
So am I gonna see you again
before I leave?
I want to, I really do.
But I'm not so sure
that's a good idea.
I understand.
That's a lie. I don't.
It's just that my favourite
advice columnist once wrote
that it's important for guys
to be more understanding.
So how am I doing?
You're doing great. Really great.
So should I call you?
Yeah, you better call me.
Have a safe flight.
Thanks.
- Bye.
Hi, Chris.
- What are you doing?
- You look amazing.
Thank you. Leave it.
I'll help you clean it up tomorrow.
It's okay, I don't mind.
It's the least I can do.
What do you mean?
Well, you know,
for fighting with Leo and...
- He attacked you. Don't worry about it.
- Yeah, I know.
Like I said, it's cool.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Guess it didn't go that well
with Jason?
Well, I went all the way down
there to talk to him,
and then I figured maybe it wasn't
such a good idea that I even see him,
at least not until I can
control my new power.
Well, judging by how it's been going,
it might be just a little bit.
I know, but what
am I supposed to do?
I'm gonna have to figure out
how to use it sooner or later.
And until then, I'm just gonna
stay away from horny men.
Good luck.
At least your new power
helped save Piper.
That's gotta be a good thing.
It won't help her with what
she's going through, though.
But at least
she's going through it now.
- And that is a good thing.
- Yeah, well, let's hope.
Well, I'm off to see Oscar.
Wait. Oscar the dog?
Yeah, he's having a bit
of a tough time adjusting.
I don't really want him
roaming the streets by himself,
especially since I'm the one
who rescued him.
I was having trouble with the
whole idea of that temp-agency thing.
But I'm kind of digging it now.
It's all right.
- Wait, wait, about Oscar...
- Bye.
Who is it?
It's me.
Come in.
Hi.
Wanna hold him?
Are you kidding?
He's gotten so big.
Yeah.
Look out. Yeah.
Look, Piper...
...I wanna say I'm sorry
for taking away your feelings.
Leo, you don't have to apologize.
I know that you were
just trying to help me. I do.
And it wasn't your fault you weren't
around to take the spell away.
Well, it's somebody's fault.
And I'm gonna find out whose.
The other Elders want me
to stick around until I do.
To make sure nobody
is targeting us again.
So you're still an Elder, then.
Yeah.
I need to ask you a favour.
Anything.
I need some space from you.
I mean, who knows, this might actually
turn out to be a good thing for me
in the long run.
I might be able to live
some semblance of a normal life,
not being married to an angel.
I get why you have to leave, Leo.
And I understand that
you can't ignore your calling.
But I do have to deal
with it somehow.
With being alone,
with being a single mother.
And I can't really do that with
you hanging around the house.
I'm sorry.
Leo, please, I need this.
I won't be far.
You deserve a normal life, Piper.
I really hope you find it.