- Okay, sign there.
- All right.
And there.
And give me your John Hancock
right there.
And you are done.
- All right. What about the Smith case?
- Settled.
- The amendments to my living trust?
- Filed.
Did you take care
of my donation to the...?
Children's Foundation. Got it.
It's going through in the morning,
and, may I say,
that is a very generous donation.
Yeah, well, it was the least I could do.
Believe me.
I couldn't have gotten through
all this without you, Paige.
You have been a miracle worker.
Thank you. You should have seen me
at my other temp jobs
if you wanna see miracles.
This is for you.
It's just my way of saying thank you.
- I really can't...
- Just take it.
I know a good soul
when I see one.
Thank you.
So you better go. I'm sure
your family would never forgive me
- if I kept you here past midnight.
- Okay.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
I wouldn't count on it.
No, no, no!
Behind you, Paige!
No, Paige!
- Larry?
- Forget it, witch! You lost him.
- Let's try just a little bit. It's good stuff.
- Good morning!
So how was your date?
Don't ask.
You need a hand?
Sure, if you want to go
get my car washed,
go to the dry cleaners for me
and go to work for me too.
- That would be great!
- Sure, if you run the club for me,
go to the dentist
and raise Wyatt for me.
Today, I would trade with you
in a second.
Do you remember Spencer Ricks,
that slimy advice columnist?
- The one you turned into a turkey?
- Yeah, well,
I should have kept him that way.
Elise just hired him away
from the competition to work with me.
- Look how handsome he looks.
- Why would she do that?
I don't know. I guess to promote
his hiring, she wants us to pick a letter
and each give advice on it. So,
you know, one, sensitive and caring
- and the other one, chauvinistic and...
- Slimy?
Thank you. I have half a mind
to call Jason and complain about it,
but I don't wanna use
our relationship for leverage.
What's the use of sleeping
with your boss, then?
Because I actually enjoy
sleeping with my boss.
Yeah, don't brag.
- Not getting any is making you bitter.
- Hello. Hi. Excuse me.
Oh, he doesn't know
what we're talking about.
He's 10 months old. He thinks we're
talking about milk, for God's sakes.
Phoebe, he conjured a dragon.
- I wouldn't put anything past him.
- Good point.
Now, if he could only find a way
to keep guys from bolting
every time they lay eyes on him...
It's not easy dating
as a single mom.
There's gotta be lots of guys
out there that like kids.
Yeah, I haven't met any so far.
So I'm just gonna cut to the chase.
I've got three dates lined up. They're all
gonna meet Wyatt on the first date,
and if they don't like it, tough.
You could always turn them
into a turkey.
Where you been?
Paige?
Paige, what happened?
What's the matter?
What time is it?
Eight. Were you out all night?
- Yeah, I guess I was.
- Come here, mister.
- You hang on right there.
- Okay. Sit down here for a second.
Talk to us.
I lost an innocent last night.
A demon killed him right in front of me.
- Oh, God.
- At your temp job?
Yeah. I should have seen it coming.
Every other job,
someone's wound up needing my help.
- I just don't know why I didn't see it.
- Well, maybe you weren't meant to.
No, I was. I just... I didn't.
Even worse, when I tried to save him,
he wound up saving me.
I just wish I knew
what was going on.
Why they were after Larry
in the first place
and how he knew
they were coming for him.
- What do you mean, he knew?
- He just did.
He was finalising his will,
making donations,
tried to get me out of there.
- He knew.
- How could he have known?
I don't know,
unless maybe he wasn't so innocent.
Which is probably why
you weren't meant to save him.
No, I don't believe that.
Look, Paige,
even if he was an innocent,
you can't save everybody.
I mean, that's just the lesson
we've all had to learn, unfortunately.
I know.
Paige, you can't blame yourself
for what happened.
If you were meant to save him,
you would've. You have to believe that.
I can't.
Leo. What are you doing here?
- Get off of me!
- Are you following me again?
I thought we were past
these issues.
- What is that?
- That? Nothing.
No?
What the hell?
Long story.
What is that, a time portal? Is that it?
What are you using it for?
- I don't have to answer that.
- Thought you said
- you had nothing to hide?
- I don't have to answer that.
- Wanna bet?
- No.
- Where are we?
- How the hell should I know?
That's what I was trying to tell you.
I can't control it.
Yeah.
- So if there's anything that I can do...
- Thank you.
I just can't believe that he's gone.
I know.
I'm grateful that he was not alone
when it happened.
I know that he didn't know you long,
but I'm glad you were with him.
I just wish I'd gotten there sooner.
Well, there's nothing
you could have done.
He had a heart attack.
It was his time, I guess.
Yeah, I'm not so sure about that.
I just...
I mean that he was so young.
And from everything
that people have said,
he was just this great guy,
you know?
- It just doesn't seem fair.
- No, it doesn't, does it?
Listen, Mrs. Henderson,
I feel weird asking you this,
but was he acting
any differently before?
I'm sorry, I have to go now.
But if there is anything you need,
just call me.
Yeah, okay. Thank you.
I don't mean to be taking up
all of your time.
No, wait, please.
What made you ask that?
It's just some of the things that
he asked me to do for him before...
It's just almost as if he knew
something was gonna happen.
Actually, he knew about a lot of things
before they would happen.
In fact, sometimes I almost thought
that he was clairvoyant.
- Really?
- I mean, at least in business anyway.
Up until a couple of years ago,
we had nothing.
Flat broke, going nowhere.
- And then, just all of a sudden...
- All of a sudden?
I don't know, it was like
he won the lottery or something.
Suddenly he couldn't lose.
Every deal he made was golden.
And at first he was happy,
of course,
but then he wasn't.
And whenever I would ask him
how he did it or how he knew,
he would just say that he could sense,
you know, what was about to happen.
What could that possibly mean?
Excuse me.
His brother's on the phone.
Hi, Paige.
Richard.
Last time I saw you,
you were kind of saving my life.
How are you?
As I live and breathe. Feeble.
Where you been?
What, are you keeping bankers' hours?
Turkey. Okay, first of all,
get your feet off my desk.
And secondly, get out of my chair.
And here I thought
we were gonna be friends.
Now!
All right, all right.
Jeez, keep your panties on.
Nice.
Okay, let's get a couple
of things straight here.
I didn't ask for this
and I don't like it.
- So don't push it, or else...
- Or else what?
You know what?
Let's just pick a letter.
Well, let's start with there is nothing
good in this pile of drivel.
I mean, there's some lady
who wants to break up with a loser,
another who wants
to be closer to Mommy.
And this one,
she's worried about losing her virginity.
It's like a freaking PMS convention.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you ever get letters from anybody
other than a bunch of whiny chicks?
As you were saying?
Piper.
Ryan, hi.
Good, you got my message.
Yeah, my secretary caught me
before I left.
I thought we were gonna meet
at the restaurant.
- Yeah, sorry. Something came up.
- Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
It's just that my babysitter cancelled
at the last minute.
Babysitter?
You have a baby?
What do you think?
I think...
...he's adorable.
- You do?
- Absolutely.
- What's his name?
- Wyatt.
So you're okay with this?
You still wanna go out?
What, are you kidding?
I love babies.
Although, I think we should go
to Chuck E. Cheese now.
- You mind?
- No. I'll just grab my purse.
Sure. Hey.
Hey there, big fella!
You wanna go with Mommy and me
to lunch, huh?
Oh, my...
We should probably take separate cars
because of the baby seat.
Hi. What are you doing?
Well, fine.
Actually, I'm all by myself
in the house now.
My mom moved out,
Eve's family followed.
It's weird to think the only thing
holding us together was a feud.
- Makes me sorry I helped end it.
- Don't be. It's an amazing freedom.
You're really beating
yourself up, huh?
Yeah, I guess I am.
You know, I think I was put
in Larry's life for a reason
and it probably wasn't
just to watch him die.
You really believe in that stuff,
don't you?
- What?
- Fate. Destiny.
Yeah, don't you?
I didn't. Not until I met you.
With all the magical wars in my family,
if there's some kind of grand plan,
it sucks.
What are you smiling at?
Nothing, it's just kind of nice to talk to
someone about all this magic-y stuff.
I mean, other than my sisters,
of course.
What do they think
you should do about Larry?
Basically, just let it go.
Well, if you'd have let it go with me,
I probably wouldn't be alive right now.
Still, I wouldn't even know
where to start.
Start with Larry.
Wouldn't be the first ghost
you've summoned.
The cream of the crop,
ladies and demons.
The best souls you'll find up for auction
anywhere in the underworld.
Guaranteed, or your powers back.
Straighten up!
Take for example,
Larry Henderson here.
Now, I'll spare you the pitiful details
of his life and only say,
that thanks to me, he became
one of the most prominent lawyers
in San Francisco.
Friends, don't let this one get away.
He's a true prize for any soul collector,
eater or trader.
So, what say we start the bidding
at two powers?
- Find him!
- Yes, sir.
- Welcome back, Larry.
- What?
Okay, you've gotta send me back
before Zahn gets pissed.
Zahn. Is that the demon that?
Killed me? Yeah.
For all intents and purposes, yes.
- Reverse the spell, come on.
- I can't. Not till we figure out
- what's going on.
- Paige, I'm begging you.
Larry, give it up.
She's stubborn when she wants to be.
Trust me.
- Do I know you?
- No.
You know my family.
You did some accounting for us.
And exactly how are you
involved with this?
Just fate.
Great, fate.
Well, you wanna talk about fate?
If I don't live up to my end of the deal,
my wife's fate is screwed too.
And I'm not gonna let that happen.
Now, come on!
What, did you make
some sort of Faustian deal?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
Look, I'm not proud of it. All right?
But Zahn came to me five years ago,
when I was down and hurting.
And he promised to pull me out of it
in exchange for my...
For my soul.
And last night,
payment became due in full.
So that's how
you built up your firm?
Among other things.
But then, when I realised
how Zahn was making me rich
off of other people's pain
and freak accidents,
I tried to stop it.
I tried to break the deal,
but when I realised I couldn't,
I tried to make amends
and I tried to give away everything
before it was too late.
Paige?
Oh, hey, you remember Richard.
- Hi.
- What's going on?
- Oh, you know,
just summoning a ghost.
- Okay, okay.
- What was I supposed to do?
Just let him rot in hell
or wherever he was?
That's the thing. You don't know
where you summoned him from.
How do you know that demons in the
underworld aren't out looking for him?
- All the more reason to save him.
- Save him? He's dead.
No, he hasn't moved on yet,
which means I have a chance
to save his soul before Zahn gets it.
- And who is Zahn?
- The demon he made a deal with.
No, that's not what I mean.
What is his level, what are his powers?
I don't know,
I haven't checked the Book yet.
So you have no idea
what you're up against?
No. But does it really matter?
Paige, look,
I know this search is important to you
and you need to maintain
a separate identity,
but you can't keep
going off on your own.
It's not how we work.
Well, if I hadn't,
Larry's soul could've been lost by now.
- He sold his soul. It was his choice.
- Well, so he makes a mistake in life.
Does that mean he has to pay for it
in his afterlife too?
Yeah, maybe,
because actions have consequences.
We can't go around cleaning up
after everybody's mistakes.
Especially mistakes like this.
So, what, do you want me
to just send him back?
I think that if you bring danger
into this house,
you need to talk to us
about it beforehand.
I did, but you weren't supportive.
Unlike Richard, who actually was.
What does Richard
have to do with this?
- You barely even know him.
- Maybe.
But he seems to get me
more than you.
Hey, listen,
thanks so much for your help,
but I think maybe you better go.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, but I'll call you later.
Okay.
And you. Come with me.
- What...? Where are we going?
- We are going to save your soul.
Come on!
I don't understand.
Why can't we orb?
Prehistoric. Magic won't be around
till there's people around to use it.
Perfect. We'll just hang out for the next
million years or so? No problem.
More like 65 million.
Looks like the Cretaceous Period.
Man, you are old.
I think he's gone. He looks gone.
Do you think he's gone?
- No.
- Neither do I.
The sooner we get back to our time,
the less we'll have to worry about it.
- Yeah, that's gonna be a problem.
- What do you mean?
I mean, you just don't create
time portals out of thin air.
It's not like that.
Well, you coming back from the future
originally seemed like exact science.
That was a spell, all right?
A one-way door.
It only goes backward in time,
not forward.
So, what, you're creating portals
to get back to the future, is that it?
Why?
To see if it changed, okay?
To see if I stopped the demon
who was after Wyatt.
What, you still don't believe me?
All I care about right now
is getting back home.
Well, all you gotta do is find the portal
that dumped us here. Good luck.
- Watch out for the dinosaurs.
- You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Get rid of me once and for all?
You were the one who sent us back
to Jurassic Park, all right? Not me.
Wouldn't be the first time
you tried to get rid of me.
Think what you want,
but know this, if we don't get back,
Wyatt's screwed.
If you don't believe me, believe that.
- Have you tried calling for Leo?
- Yeah, he's not answering either.
He's probably out chasing after Chris,
and God only knows where that is.
We'll have to talk to them. They're
never around when we need them.
Yeah, I think we need to talk
to Paige first.
Because this little power-of-one kick
of hers is getting out of control.
Yeah, but didn't we promise her
we wouldn't butt in it anymore?
Yeah, but that was when
she was just helping Richard.
She wasn't yanking souls away
from angry demons.
Look, I'm not saying
that we need to gang up on her,
but this is clearly becoming a pattern
and we need to remind her
that we have a shared destiny
to worry about too.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Okay, bye.
All right, let's get this over with.
What do you think?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
where are you going, toots?
- Home, if you must know.
- Home? Are you nuts?
We got a column we gotta write.
And I have just found
the perfect letter for us to respond to.
"Dear Pheeb, I am a breast man at
heart, but the problem is, this girl I like
is flat as a board.
Should I even bother asking her out?"
Now, this is a letter I can respond to.
Must have been the wrong potion.
Excuse me. This way, please,
this way. Inside, inside.
- Brett, hi.
- Piper.
I didn't think you were...
...home.
- Oh, sorry it took me so long.
- I had to go get my baby.
- Your baby?
I actually didn't realise you were a...
- A mom?
- Right, that.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Well, you know,
some guys
just don't hear that very well.
Go figure, right?
Well, I don't mean to be rude,
but something's come up
and I can't go out right now.
So if you don't wanna reschedule,
it's perfectly understandable.
Why wouldn't I?
Unless you got ten more
of those somewhere.
- No, just the one.
- Not a problem.
Did I pass the test?
With flying colours.
Paige?
I better...
...go.
You know, ordinarily I'd be upset
if you summoned me, but seeing as
how you just helped me find Larry,
- I'll be merciful.
- No, don't hurt her, Zahn, please.
She didn't know.
She was trying to help me.
Help? Really?
What, you thought vanquishing me
would set him free?
- Is that it?
- As a matter of fact...
- You were saying?
- You're a low-level demon.
- You're not supposed to have power.
- Lady,
I haven't been low-level in years.
Not since I started trading
souls for powers. Wanna see?
Paige?
Piper!
And just for future reference,
even if you could vanquish me,
it would only make it worse for Larry.
Paragraph five,
subsection six, line three:
All souls in my possession
will burn in eternal flames
upon my untimely demise.
Believe me.
It's a fate worse than anything
that could possibly happen at auction.
A little protection clause
I put in all my contracts.
Consider yourself repossessed.
This would all be so much easier
if someone that could heal you
was actually listening!
It's no big deal, I've had worse.
Still, those two need a talking-to,
I'll tell you.
I don't understand this. Faustian deals
have been around for over a century,
but there is nothing in here on how
to break them. How is that possible?
Maybe because
they can't be broken.
It can't be. There's gotta be a way.
I am not giving up on Larry now.
Listen, sweetie, maybe you should.
- I know you feel guilty about it...
- That's not it.
It's affecting all of us now,
not just you.
- I said I was sorry.
- That's not the point.
Listen, I just want to save his soul.
But you can't!
Larry said that Zahn keeps
his contracts locked up somewhere.
So if we can find and destroy them,
then we can set all those souls free.
I don't think so.
- Why not?
- We think we should go after Zahn.
Stop him before he gets
any more powers.
What, and just
let all those souls burn?
They're already lost, Paige.
He's already got them.
I think it's important that you stop him
before he becomes unstoppable.
No!
Paige, we don't like this
any more than you do,
but this is where we're at.
He's my innocent.
Yeah, but this is our problem
and one we did not ask for, by the way.
No, I'm not sacrificing him.
You don't have a choice.
This is beyond your control.
I'm sorry.
- Hey, Paige.
- Hey, your housekeeper let me in.
- I hope you don't mind.
- No, it's fine.
You okay? Everything all right?
No.
- This looks familiar, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
Maybe we should split up,
find the portal faster.
Wait.
If one of us gets caught, the other one
needs to keep going. For Wyatt's sake.
Oh, you believe me
about him now?
No, I just wanna let you know what's
gonna happen if you get caught.
Found it!
Leo!
Come on, come on. Go. Go. Go!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Thanks for not listening to me.
Anytime.
You boys Yankees?
Get up.
- Here.
- Thank you.
So, what are you gonna do?
Well, I got a plan on how to save Larry,
but it's kind of risky.
Maybe you shouldn't
go through with it.
I mean,
maybe your sisters are right.
You're the one who told me
to follow my instincts.
I know, I just...
I don't want you to get hurt.
Listen, I'm gonna need your help
to pull this off.
- Paige, if I do magic...
- No.
No. I am not asking you to do that.
I'm just gonna need you
to get my sisters when it's time.
I need their help, but they can't know
about it until it's too late to stop me.
Won't they get pissed?
Yeah, probably.
Guess I'm pretty stubborn, huh?
Yeah. In a good way.
Paige...
...you have a gift.
Don't fight it.
Thank you.
Got any candles?
How do we know she's not gonna
just summon him herself again?
Who, Zahn?
She won't try that again,
not without a potion.
What about Richard?
He can make potions.
Isn't he on the witch wagon, though?
I'm just saying,
I wouldn't put it past her.
I can't believe
it's even gotten to this point.
- It'll work itself out. It always does.
- I don't know about that.
I mean, we've all disagreed
with each other
at one point or another
over the years, obviously,
- but this is different.
- So maybe we should call her again
and talk to her about it.
Or we can just summon Zahn
and vanquish him quickly
before she gets
her pigheaded self killed.
Oh, no, pig.
I'll take care of it. Don't even ask.
Okay, we give him one chance
at giving up Larry's soul and that's it.
Okay.
We call upon the ancient powers
To summon one to save his soul
You will be first up for auction.
Again.
All right, my fellow demons,
let's start the bidding, shall we?
Oh, great. Not again.
- What happened?
- Where did he go?
You again.
- This time, it's gonna cost you.
- Wait.
I'm gonna make you an offer
you can't refuse.
I think you'll find
that everything's in order.
You don't mind if I look it over first?
Suit yourself,
but it's exactly as we discussed.
You'll notice the same clause
I mentioned earlier.
To protect me from your sisters,
of course.
- You won't have to worry about them.
- Good.
- Just sign on the dotted line.
- First Larry.
- Paige, what are you doing?
- Exactly what I said I'd do.
Saving you.
No, Paige, don't!
Have a nice afterlife.
You must really be a good soul
to do what you've just done.
It's been a pleasure
doing business with you.
- Did she answer?
- It's just her voice mail. Scrying?
Nothing. I can't find her anywhere.
You don't think Zahn?
I don't know, but if he didn't, I will.
What was she thinking?
Chris! Leo!
- Where are those guys?
- Forget it, they're not answering.
What are we gonna do?
- Richard. Hi.
- Hi.
- You seen Paige?
- That's why I'm here.
Okay, inside, inside.
- Where is she? She all right?
- I don't know.
What do you mean?
What does that mean?
It means...
Does he do that a lot?
- Wyatt.
- What is he doing?
- Why is he doing that?
- Apparently, he's trying to scare away
all of my dates. You little rot...
Did your father teach you that?
- So not the time.
- Right. You're grounded.
Okay, back to Paige.
She's with Zahn,
or rather her soul is, right about now.
- What?
- Yeah, it's all part of her plan.
It's why I'm here.
You don't have much time.
She told me to tell you to reverse
a to-call-a-lost-sister spell?
- It'll take you right to her.
- To do what?
To save her.
Please, everyone!
May I have your attention, please?
Tonight,
I have a special treat for you.
A once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
to purchase one of the most
unique souls there is or ever was.
A Charmed One,
ladies and demons.
One of only three in existence.
And I have her here tonight.
Both soul...
...and body.
To be auctioned off separately,
of course.
Hurry up.
Shall we start the bidding at say,
ten powers?
- I'll give you 15.
- Fifteen...
- Twenty!
- I have 20!
And another 20 for the body.
- Do I have 30?
- Thirty, just for the soul!
- Any more? Thirty-two.
- Thirty-two.
- Thirty-six.
- I have 36!
Forty! And I'll throw in my minions.
And minions!
More Charmed Ones.
- One hundred for all three.
- Sold. To the dead grimlock.
Way to channel.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Piper, hurry. Blow up the vault!
My contracts!
Cut it a little close.
- What the hell is going on?
- Bitch later, vanquish now!
No!
I love watching lawyers explode.
- Now can I bitch?
- No, let me explain.
I had to lure you down here. It was
the only way to destroy the contracts.
- All I had to do was find them first.
- But by dying?
No, I'm not dead.
See, your brain has to be dead
before you can die, so I'm still alive.
Okay, so where's Larry's soul?
Larry's saved. He's moved on.
And that was worth
risking your life for?
No, I wasn't risking my life.
See, I knew no matter how pissed off
you got, you'd still come and save me.
We are sisters.
Thanks.
We're just taking a short break.
Back in 20 minutes, thank you.
Piper, how did you have time
to book Steadman in your club?
Between raising my nephew
- and trying to date and vanquishing...
- A sister?
Does that mean
you're still mad at Paige?
Well, yeah, aren't you?
Well...
I mean, come on,
she didn't just risk her own life,
she risked ours as well.
Not to mention the power of three.
Yeah, I know, but don't we kind of
do that every week anyway?
No, not unilaterally we don't. Ever.
I'm not saying she has to answer
to us all the time
or that she can't go find her bliss,
whatever that may be,
but not at the risk of what we do.
I totally agree, but still,
we have to figure out a way
to work it out.
You know, let her feel like she has a
voice in this whole thing. Compromise.
Since when did you become
Solomon all of a sudden?
I have surrendered
to being the middle sister.
Or does it have more
to do with this?
Look at that pig.
And I don't mean literally.
At least, not anymore.
Hey, look who it is.
Where you two been?
Long story.
We got a little lost, that's all, and it
took some time to find our way back.
So, what did we miss?
- You lay into them. I have a date.
- Hey, a date? Really?
- Does he know about Wyatt?
- No. He's not gonna any time soon.
- At least not till after the honeymoon.
- Hey, what did we really miss?
You know what?
It's a long story.
Come on, I'll buy you a drink.
Whitelighters don't have any money.
It was a gesture.
- Two cold ones, Billy.
- You got it, Leo.
It's on me.
For Larry. May your soul
find freedom and peace.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
What about you and your sisters?
Oh, we're gonna be fine.
Just a few growing pains.
I wanted to thank you, though,
for everything you've done.
Hey, I just delivered a message.
No, I couldn't have done it
without you.
Anytime.
Lucky I ran into you.
Luck.
It was fate.