Previously on house.
I don't know how I got here.
I saw a symptom
before the crash.
???
Medical hypnosis
can bring the brain
to a class two theta state.
Taxing an already injured
brain.
Someone is dying
because I can't remember.
It was amber.
She was on the bus with me.
She's the one who's dying.
Her heart won't stop racing.
No idea
what's causing it.
Sure it wasn't the bus
that landed on her?
It's not trauma.
She was stable post-op.
This didn't start
until an hour ago.
Oh, my god.
Delayed reaction
to the trauma.
She lost both her kidneys
in the bus crash.
She ripped up
her femoral artery.
We fixed the artery,
got her on dialysis
for the kidneys.
Whatever's doing this
to her heart,
it isn't from the crash.
- Check her potassium?
- Of course.
Why didn't you call me?
She's been under
the whole time.
- she had no i.d.
- Pushed adenosine?
and verapamil, and floated
the swan an hour ago.
Coronary angiography?
Three critical patients
ahead of her.
We'll have her in
within the hour.
We're 15 minutes away
from princeton plainsboro
by ambulance.
You want to move her?
Her heart rate is 130.
She's hemodynamically stable.
We're moving her.
You're not her doctor.
You can't make that decision.
Her husband can.
Right?
Move her.
If the trauma
didn't damage her heart-
Why was she on the bus?
I don't know.
If she had
any underlying condition,
the accident could have
exacerbated it.
Why were you
with her?
I don't know!
I'm not hiding anything.
I just don't remember.
What else could damage
her heart?
Wilson, don't get lost.
I'm barely coherent.
I need your help right now.
V- fib.
Charging.
Okay. Okay.
- Clear.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Protective hypothermia.
You want to freeze her?
Her heart's not beating.
Her heart's already damaged.
If you restart it, it'll keep
racing, shoot off free radicals,
and kill her brain.
We ice her down,
put her on bypass
until you've diagnosed her.
This is not a solution.
All you're doing
is pressing pause.
It gives you more time
to find a diagnosis.
House, this is amber.
Please.
Cold saline solution.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
House 416
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译: 校对:
时间轴:我爱狮心小s 白二
cool temperature down
to 90.
Bypass circulating.
She's stable.
Why are we doing this?
Bought us time
to think.
The trauma must have stimulated
a pre-existing heart condition.
Autoimmune congenital anomaly,
blood clotting disorder,
lead poisoning...
It could be anything.
Great,
let's explore that.
Quick, get her
on panacea.
We can narrow it down
by looking
for arterial blockages.
how?
On an echo?
Can't see wall motion
when there's no motion.
Ekg, nope.
Heart's in the off position.
Thallium uptake scan?
Useless on a cold heart.
Yeah,
we get it.
Her heart's not beating.
It's gonna make it harder
to diagnose.
On the other hand,
she's not gonna die
while you're whining
about it.
What else?
there is another way
to narrow it down.
If you really did see
a symptom in amber
before the crash,
physostigmine helped
your memory last time.
Why not cyanide?
He's a mess.
He needs to sleep.
I had a heart attack
this morning.
I can't do any more drugs
till lunch.
Get her an angiogram.
It could show damage
even in a stopped heart.
The rest of you
search her apartment.
Toxins, heavy metals,
drugs,
anything that might make
her heart race.
I need to know if there's
anything medically relevant
that you couldn't share
publicly.
Is this a philanderers anonymous
intervention?
You were obviously drinking
last night.
Maybe you took amber
to a bar.
I left here
on my motorcycle alone.
You ended up
drunk on a bus
together.
Maybe you met amber
in the bar.
I was not having
an affair with her.
You can't
really say that
if you don't remember.
I lost four hours,
not four months.
Maybe it was
the first time.
If you drank together,
any chance you did any drugs?
I'll run a tox screen.
You coming?
Correspondence,
letters to patients,
she could have caught something
from one of them.
Copy it
to a thumb drive.
Let's get out of here.
Travel.
Do you know if she's been
out of the country recently?
It's just video clips.
Maybe she narrates
where they are.
And... Action.
Looks like she didn't travel
very far.
You look beautiful.
You look nervous.
I've never done this before.
I have.
Trust me.
You'll love it.
- Hey.
- not even close to relevant.
As long as we don't know
what's wrong,
we don't know
what's relevant.
Yeah, maybe they're having sex
on a pile of asbestos.
Go watch it.
If we were
in a stranger's house,
you'd be watching the video.
You altered your behavior
because you're friends with her.
Are you okay?
We shouldn't be treating her
at all.
I'm gonna search
her bathroom.
Are you okay?
can't really say yes when it's
a hallucination asking.
Don't worry,
you're just dreaming.
What symptom did I see
in you?
A myoclonic jerk-
Boring.
An incredibly rare
neurological symptom is boring?
Am I in someone else's
subconscious?
What did we do
last night?
Was I meeting you
for a drink?
Is that all it was?
A man thinks a woman
is beautiful,
admires her intelligence,
admires the way she has to get
whatever she wants,
the things he likes
about himself.
Maybe she always had
a little thing for him.
His mind.
His blue eyes.
But someone gets
between them.
so.
They decide to meet
one night
at an out-of-the-way
little bar.
Does that sound familiar?
Do I feel familiar?
What do you feel?
Electricity.
I know
I saw the symptom.
I know the memory's
locked in my brain.
Now I know how to get it.
no.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
You need to rest.
I have yet to hear
about any study
linking electricity
and rest.
Deep brain stimulation.
It's been proven.
Electrical impulses applied
directly to the hypothalamus
could evoke
detailed memories.
My mistake,
drilling a hole
and shooting lightning bolts
into an already-cracked skull
is very restful,
it's not fatal at all.
She's right.
You need to sleep.
Brain activity spiked.
Amber.
It's me.
Random spikes are common.
Shut up.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm here with you.
The team has found something.
Can you ask her
if we can be excused?
What?
Coronary angio
was negative.
So was the tox screen.
That's what you found?
Negative tests?
I could have told you
she doesn't do drugs.
We found these
in her apartment.
Sorry.
Prescription diet pills.
Ssris, amphetamines.
Diet pills cause
structural damage
to the mitral valve,
could explain the tachycardia.
She'd have to be an addict
to take enough
for it to damage
her heart.
I'd know.
Did you know that she was hiding
them in her vitamins?
We have to warm her back up.
Get her heart beating
so we can do a ct to confirm.
No, we've been
over this.
Starting her heart
could cause brain damage,
could burn out
the heart muscle.
Test her heart
without starting it.
Crack her chest open,
reach a finger
inside the pulmonary vein,
run it across the valve.
That's the safer course?
It is if we're wrong.
When did we start assuming
we're wrong?
If this were
any other patient-
If the valve is calcified,
that's our answer.
That's our cure.
go.
Thirteen.
Who found
the diet pills?
Kutner.
You didn't even go
in the bathroom, did you?
You're suddenly mute
in the differentials.
A blow-up doll
would be more useful.
And yes,
that's the first time
I've ever implied something
negative about a blow-up doll.
It's amber.
- I don't-
- Normally, I'd be fascinated.
Today, don't care.
Get over whatever it is
and do your job.
Wait.
Look at her eye.
She's jaundiced.
Her liver's shutting down.
Diet pills don't kill
the liver.
????
Liver failure means
whatever this thing is
it's spreading, despite the fact
that she's frozen.
Hepatic and heart failure
could mean
antitrypsinase deficiency.
We can stick a needle
in her liver.
If we see fibrosis,
she's right.
Does amber drink sherry?
And the cardio fits
just as well.
But there's no way
we can tell,
since we can't take
her temperature.
I had a dream.
She was pouring me
a glass.
And since I'm a scotch,
beer, gin, and rum man...
If we warm her back up,
we should be able to tell
if she's got an infection.
Yes, we can get
a diagnosis
by letting the disease run
rampant until it kills her.
If it's spreading,
we need to slow this
even more.
We've gotta cool her down
further.
I know you love her
and you're scared
she's gonna die.
But just making her colder
and colder isn't a cure.
It's not dealing
with the reality.
Sherry means something.
Amber doesn't
even drink sherry.
House.
Can we get back-
if she did drink sherry,
it would mean nothing.
Since she doesn't,
my subconscious is obviously
trying to make some other point.
There's a sharrie's bar
on third
right off the bus route.
Wilson's right.
We need to make her colder.
Putting more ice on her
is just delaying the diagnosis.
Not on, in.
Fill her lungs
with slurry.
Where are you going?
I'm taking wilson out
for a drink.
Is this the place?
Maybe.
Hey.
I assume you are here...
For these.
Did you see me here
with a tall blonde woman?
Yeah, I think she joined you
after scotch number seven.
Did she seem sick?
She sneezed.
I gave her
a napkin.
Did you see the color
of the sputum?
I assume
sputum means snot.
Look, I see a lot
of drunk chicks in here.
I didn't have time
to stop and analyze
the color
of your girlfriend's boogers.
She's not my girlfriend,
genius.
She was hot,
you seemed into her,
and she bought you drinks.
Last night,
she was your girlfriend.
Blood in the sputum
could mean parasites.
Any recent travel?
You seemed into her?
If he had a brain,
he wouldn't be tending bar.
Sneezing's a new symptom.
Let's assume the runny nose
means an infection.
What did house
have to say?
He told me
I was raised by wolves
and that's why I use the same
hand for my fork and knife.
ooh.
Not that one.
The slurry tube.
oh.
I know
this is different.
But it's not.
Everyone dies.
She's not dead.
You're reacting this way
because she might be-soon.
Yeah, I am.
Why aren't you?
I'm an indian guy
named kutner.
Ever wonder what happened
to my parents?
I'm sorry,
I didn't-
I was six years old.
I used to like helping out in
my parents' store after school.
Guy walks in
to rob the place.
Ends up shooting them both.
Wasn't fair.
Took years,
but I had to accept
that's just the way
it was.
So you gonna help me
fill her lungs up or not?
Tell me that the liver biopsy
showed infiltrates,
minor inflammation.
Yeah.
How-?
Snot on a napkin.
Add the heart,
infiltrates...
Hep b.
Start her
on iv interferon.
I'll go tell wilson.
Good idea.
And I'll go nap
because I was concussed last night
and had a heart attack
this morning.
I'll tell wilson;
you go sleep.
Hepatitis b
is a lame diagnosis.
Oh, god,
I get less rest
when I'm asleep.
I rise from the dead,
and that's the reaction I get?
I'm sorry.
If I had known, I would have
started a breakaway jewish sect.
Hep b fits.
Why are you doing that?
Because hep b doesn't fit.
Turn her over.
We're about to start
a second course of interferon.
Which she might not need
once you turn her over.
Small of her back.
She's bruised.
Why is that significant?
Look closer.
A rash.
How did you know what was
on the small of her back?
Either I'm still asleep,
or I'm starting to remember.
Looks like an influenza rash.
The flu wouldn't be killing
her organs one by one.
Dermatomyositis.
Wouldn't speed up
her heart.
Maybe it's an allergic reaction
to the interferon.
Yes, the symptom
that I saw on the bus
was a rare interferon allergy
that flares up
two days before you take it.
How did you see
the rash down there?
I don't know.
Maybe she leaned over.
Maybe it's not a rash
at all.
It could be
an abscess.
Thirteen, stick a needle
in there.
If there's pus,
foreman's right.
Ultrasound is safer.
I'm not asking you to stick
a needle all the way through.
Taub, you do it.
No, wait, I can do it.
No, apparently, you can't.
It's not fluctuant.
Clear.
It's not pus.
Means it's vesicular.
Rocky mountain spotted fever.
We had dinner
with a friend last week.
We walked their dogs.
I guess she could
have gotten a tick.
It's treatable.
Doxycycline.
Allow eight hours for
the antibiotics to take effect,
then we warm her up,
shock her heart.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
If we're wrong, restarting
her heart could kill her.
Run blood cultures first.
The fastest way to test
is to treat.
If we're wrong,
it still should give us time
to try something else.
We are not starting
her heart
until we're 100% certain.
We're never 100% certain.
Run the blood cultures.
After we get confirmation,
then we'll restart her heart.
He's wrong.
And you know
he's wrong.
You can't change your mind
just because a family member
starts crying.
They're always scared.
I said,
run the blood cultures.
Sorry.
Wide stance.
You're right.
I'm screwing up.
Why are you screwing up?
I didn't even like her.
Did you hate her?
Not enough to want her dead.
So it's not guilt.
That just leaves fear.
A young woman dying.
A young doctor dying,
in fact.
Does that sound familiar?
yeah, I'm at risk
for huntington's.
I've dealt with it.
By not getting tested?
Dealing with it
by not dealing with it.
It's clearly working
beautifully.
You are the champion
of not dealing
with your problems.
My grandson gave me a mug
that says that.
Okay.
Enough hand-holding.
Deal with it.
Get back in there.
Or pack up your stuff.
You're screwing up this case
worse than I am.
* love, love is a verb
* love is a doing word
* feathers on my breath
* gentle impulsion
* shakes me, makes me lighter
* feathers on my breath
* teardrop on the fire
house is gonna kill
the patient.
What are you-
What are you doing?
She's up to 80 degrees.
We're gonna restart
her heart.
No, you're not.
There's still time
to undo this,
cool her back down.
You weren't taking
the safe approach.
We've got to know
if the antibiotics are working.
Her eeg's slowed.
Amber.
Well done.
We still don't know what it is,
????
this is exactly what I said
would happen.
It's in her brain now.
Brain involvement gives us
a new symptom.
That wouldn't be there
if you hadn't-
It's where the disease
was going.
We needed to know that.
Th was not your decision to make.
You went behind my back.
You went behind house's back.
Inside voices.
House wanted
to warm her up.
You just guilted him
into changing his mind.
Heart, liver, rash,
and now her brain.
Autoimmune fits best.
Crash trauma could have
set it off.
Start her on prednisone,
then we'll warm her up again.
House, if this is
some other infection,
the steroids will trash
her immune system.
He's the attending.
You're the family.
Go spend more time
with the patient.
You can't do this.
That's not a good argument.
It's not an argument
at all.
I'm sorry.
Cuddy's right.
I was afraid
to do anything.
I thought if everything
just stopped,
it would be okay.
And it's gonna be.
Taub's starting
the treatment.
We're doing everything-
Not everything.
Before you warm her up...
You said you wanted to try
deep brain stimulation.
But there's no reason.
We know the symptom,
we know what I saw.
What if it's not the rash?
What if you noticed the rash
in the ambulance
or when we were putting her
on bypass?
What if there is
still something else
stuck inside your head?
You think
I should risk my life
to save amber's.
Inserting the ipg probe
into your ventral hypothalamus.
Give me three volts.
I can't hear him.
Can't hear who?
Everything's in black and white.
Who was talking?
is amber there?
You're supposed to be jolting
my hypothalamus,
not petting it.
We don't want to overload it.
As long as I'm risking my life,
I might as well be watching
a talkie.
Increasing from three
to five volts.
Sending impulse.
You're not getting them back.
Hey,
you take my keys,
you gotta give me
a phone call.
Who are you calling?
dial-a-wilson.
I was on call.
Amber was home.
I told her to find you.
Have you pick me up.
I said to find wilson.
He's working.
And I'm willing to suffer
this indignity on his behalf.
Did she seem sick?
Not yet.
Come on. Time to go. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Need another round.
And a drink
for what passes
for a lady
around here.
What's your poison?
Nothing.
We're leaving.
We're leaving, leaving, leaving,
leaving, leaving-
Cosmos.
I remember wilson buying
cranberry juice.
I'll have another.
And she'll have
a cosmopolitan.
The obstinate drunk thing
is not flattering.
Come on.
You called for a ride.
Drink your drink,
or I'll drink 'em both.
one.
And you leave
voluntarily.
Let's go.
Hey.
We need
another cosmo here.
She sneezed.
What color is it?
Thanks.
Looks like snot.
It seems
like a cold.
Nothing else?
no.
Where are you going?
You think I paid?
House, what are you doing?
You can barely walk.
Go home.
I'll take the bus.
Hey, someone's gotta pay
for this.
hi.
You forgot something.
You don't give up,
do you?
Yeah, I'm an idiot
that way.
You doing this for me
or for wilson?
For wilson.
Well, then it's even
more impressive.
Ugh, damn, do you have
a kleenex?
I got a sleeve.
I got two, actually.
I need more than that.
I'm getting
that nasty flu.
Is that it?
The flu?
Is there
any rare complication?
no.
It would explain the rash,
but nothing else.
Unless...
What?
Don't do it.
It wasn't the flu.
It's what she did
for it.
She has
amantadine poisoning.
The crash destroyed
her kidneys.
Her body couldn't filter
the drugs.
She ods on amantadine,
explains the heart, the liver...
We just need to start her
on dialysis
and flush the drugs out.
What?
What's wrong?
amantadine binds
with proteins.
Dialysis can't clear it
out of the blood.
There's nothing
we can do.
I'm so sorry.
Amber.
Seizing.
Wilson, I need help here.
House suffered
a complex partial seizure.
The violent shaking
widened his skull fracture,
causing a brain bleed.
We won't know if there's
any cognitive impairment
until he's out of the coma.
He was right
about the amantadine.
Amber's body
couldn't filter it out.
That's what caused her heart
to beat too fast for too long.
It caused irreparable
structural damage.
Didn't matter if they
shocked her or froze her.
Her heart was dead once
it stopped in that ambulance.
What about a new heart?
Transplant?
All of her organs are damaged.
She can't qualify.
There's nothing we can do.
Nothing we could have done.
We should call
time of death.
Well, technically,
she's still alive.
Could probably survive
a few more hours on bypass.
We could wean her
off anesthesia, wake her up,
give you a chance to-
It would be cruel.
Don't-
Wake amber up.
See her again.
Tell her
what she means to you.
Wake her up to tell her
that she's-that she's-
You are waking her up
so that you can both
say good-bye to each other.
She would want it.
hey.
You're in the hospital.
I'm on bypass.
Yeah.
Do you remember
what happened?
Got on the bus.
I shouldn't have gotten on the bus. No.
No, it's not your fault.
It's not your fault.
How bad?
You had tachycardia.
It's complicated
by complete renal failure.
The tachycardia degenerated
into v-fib,
followed by hepatic failure.
The flu pills?
Yeah.
I'm dead.
I love you.
I love you too.
We should say good-bye.
She didn't even like us.
We liked her.
Did we?
We do now.
What do we say?
We don't need
to say anything.
* this my excavation and to...
* day is kumran
* everything that happens
* is from now on
* this is pouring rain
* this is paralyzed...
I'm tired.
I think it's time
to go to sleep.
Just a little longer.
We're always gonna want
just a little longer.
I don't think
I can do it.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
Why is it okay
with you?
Why aren't you angry?
That's... Not...
The last feeling
I want to experience.
* the sound of the unlocking
* and the lift away
* your love will be
* safe with me *
you're dead.
Everybody dies.
Am I dead?
Not yet.
I should be.
why?
Because life
shouldn't be random.
Because lonely,
misanthropic drug addicts
should die
in bus crashes,
and young do-gooders
in love
who get dragged
out of their apartment
in the middle of the night
should walk away clean.
Self-pity isn't like you.
No, well,
i'm branching out
from self-loathing
and self-destruction.
Wilson is gonna hate me.
You kind of deserve it.
He's my best friend.
I know.
What now?
I could stay here
with you.
Get off the bus.
I can't.
Why not?
Because.
Because it doesn't hurt here.
I let it...
I don't want to be
in pain.
I don't want to be miserable.
And I don't want him
to hate me.
Well, you can't always get
what you want.
* there are times that walk
from you *
* like some passing afternoon
*
* summer warmed
the open window *
* of her honeymoon
* and she chose
a yard to burn *
* but the ground remembers her
* wooden spoons,
her children stir *
hey, I'm here.
Blink if you can hear me.
* there are things
that drift away *
no, shh,
don't try to talk.
Just rest.
* autumn blew
the quilt right off *
* the perfect bed
she made *
* and she's chosen
to believe *
* in the hymns
her mother sings *
* sunday pulls its children
* from their piles
of fallen leaves *
* there are sailing ships
that pass *
* all our bodies
in the grass *
* springtime calls
our children *
* till she lets them go
at last *
* and she's chosen
where to be *
* though she's lost
her wedding ring *
* somewhere near
her misplaced jar *
* of bougainvillea seeds
* there are things
we can't recall *
* blind as night
that finds us all *
* winter tucks
her children in *
* her fragile china dolls
* but she'll mend
his tattered clothes *
* and they'll kiss
as if they know *
* a baby sleeps
in all our bones *
* so scared
to be alone *
感谢house又给了我们一季的快乐
希望下一季他跟wilson有情人能终成眷属
united we're strong!
欢迎参与美剧社区赈灾联合义卖 活动
具体活动详情请参见破烂熊官网