We just arrived.
Yeah.
The kid's okay on your end?
Good.
Yeah. He's very excited.
Hey, listen. I got to go, okay?
I'll call you tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Get away.
Sorry about that. Sorry.
What's wrong with him?
Excuse us.
I'd got to go back kick the hell
out of that guy.
She's old enough.
She didn't have to scream like that.
It's okay, dad.
It didn't bother me.
For the first time,
none of these people bother me.
I just think 36 more hours.
36 more hours.
How do you figure that, Kenny?
Tomorrow at this time,
I'm scheduled for surgery.
It's a ten-hour procedure,
throw two in it for prep.
36 until I'm just another
face in the crowd.
Kenny has a frontonasal encephalocele.
It's a midline deformity.
He's here to undergo a facial bipartion.
And what does that mean?
Well, we have five surgeons,
four nurses.
It's going to require 6 units of blood.
Will it fix him?
It'll repair a lot of the damage
done by...
We need a sound bite.
Would you say he'll be ready
for the junior prom?
Yeah, yeah.
That's probably true.
No, I mean I need you to say it.
Dr. Chase, we got an issue.
Heart rate's sky rocketing.
He's over 180.
He's in V-fib.
Paddles. Charge to 300.
Turn that camera off.
Is this a reaction to anesthesia?
Haven't given it yet.
Clear.
Crank it to 360.
I said turn that damn camera off!
Clear.
Transcript: swsub.com
Sync: ¤AkaZab¤ & BlueDoc
Season 4 - Episode 7
"Ugly"
A teenage boy with a cranial
facial deformity was about to undergo
a reconstructive procedure when
he had an unexplained cardiac arrest.
Good.
Good?
I mean, go on.
We have the patient on a pacing wire.
It's the only thing
keeping his heart going.
Yeah, we know, we're doctors.
- Right. It was... Just for them.
- Just be yourself.
Until we are able to figure out
exactly what is causing the heart block,
the reconstructive surgery
is on hold, obviously.
That's yourself?
Fascinating case.
I will see you again
after I have saved his life.
Have a warm bath waiting.
Are you following me?
Darnell will be trailing you
throughout the case.
Pretend we're not here.
- If I do that, won't I bump into you?
- We'll stay out of your way.
That's a joke.
See, I became a doctor because
of the moviepatch Adams.
Listen, you wanna get ahead of me?
Maybe back up, I don't know, low down,
- so I look more powerful?
- That's perfect.
Yeah?
Also my eyes look better
in rooms with summer colors.
You know what?
It's black and white...
You think I like the cameras?
You think I want the whole world
watching you check out my ass
and question my wardrobe?
Would it be better if I checked out
your wardrobe and questioned your ass?
- A little part of me...
- There is no little part of you.
Thought that maybe you would see
what great PR this could be
for the hospital,
and not make me force you
to act like a human being.
You using force on me is intriguing.
On the other hand,
cameras make people act.
Sometimes like human beings.
Sometimes just weird.
Sometimes they wear open-tip bras.
It's cold in here.
A less obvious point is that
I need my team
to be unafraid of the metaphorical fart.
That production company is covering all
the medical costs for this kid.
So either you let them continue filming,
or the kid goes home with the same face.
Sorry about that.
Private. She...
Waxes her moustache once a month and...
Sometimes gets some pretty
gnarly ingrown hairs.
So did he hire you flat out,
or are you competing
for one of the spots?
- I'm not sure what you mean by that.
- She's not competing.
She was hand-picked by House.
She's safe, like Foreman.
So that takes three spots down to one.
Where's Foreman?
- He's in the bathroom.
- Good. Come on. Let's go for a walk.
Walks look good on camera.
They give the illusion
of the story moving forward.
New patient.
16-year-old boy with second degree
infranodal heart block post-arrest.
Any reports
of lightheadedness or syncope?
- It's really not lightheadedness.
- Why did you hire her?
- Not in front of the company.
- Are we gonna be on TV?
I'm making a music video.
Come on, a little faster. More energy.
- Why are you glad Foreman's not here?
- Because he would object
to what I'm about to do.
Hey, Buddy.
You stay in there.
We'll be out here making sure
he doesn't move again.
God! Finally hear myself think.
- Our patient...
- Why did you hire her?
Because she has way more
diagnostic experience
than the other swimsuit models
I was considering.
Our patient has
a frontonasal encephalocele
with a midline cleft.
Don't stare directly at it.
So what caused big head's heart to stop?
Simple... His big head.
Increased intracranial pressure
would cause heart block.
Wrong, 16 years they've been testing
that insane noggin to death.
What about a congenital heart defec?
He has a midline anomaly on his head.
Makes sense he'd have a midline
anomaly in his heart too.
- That 16 years of testing didn't show?
- Why did you bring her in so late?
- It's not fair. The rest of us...
- Hey, you wanted fair,
you picked the wrong job.
The wrong profession.
The wrong species.
Forget the deformity.
Treat the patient like he's any
other really, really ugly kid.
Infection could be endocarditis.
Well, since he doesn't have
a prosthetic heart valve,
I assume you're thinking
he's an IV drug user?
House said assume he's normal.
Dealers don't ask for ID and
don't care what you look like.
Nice. You're right about the habit.
You're wrong about the substance.
Blackened skin under the nose
equals frostbite from huffing freon.
Freon's toxic.
Damages the heart.
Discoloration could be
acanthosis nigricans.
It's a common side effect
of these deformities.
There's also discoloration
on the cheeks and forehead.
Do a nuclear study.
If I'm right,
you'll see scarring of the heart.
I'm not part of some game, am I?
I gave up a career because
I thought this was a firm offer.
Yes. This is a real offer.
I think she might be an idiot.
- Who?
- She can't be an idiot.
She was in the CIA, for god's sake.
- The bay of pigs was a daring triumph.
- She had good ideas in Langley.
- All your ideas.
- She was able to identify
- that they were good ideas.
- Stab in the dark here.
- Is she pretty?
- She's new.
- She's nervous.
- She's a "c" cup.
She said one dumb thing
in a differential.
They all say dumb things
in differentials.
A "d" cup?
- She's no good. Just fire her.
- I can't.
I just hired her.
She left a career.
You know, that's actual guilt,
or I've got to see this woman.
- My son is not huffing freon.
- Mr. Arnold, Dr. House is like a savant
when it comes to diagnostics.
What's his genius theory?
Because Kenny's not normal,
he's doing drugs to deal with his pain?
Maybe the way to look at this
is that you are normal.
- And what's that supposed to mean?
- You're like any other parent.
Who thinks his kid can't be doing drugs.
We're doing this 'cause
my dad thinks I'm on drugs?
I was doing drugs
behind my parents' back
at your age, and I had
a lot less reason to be...
Not that your life must be miserable.
Not that I'm suggesting
that you should be doing drugs.
- How's school going?
- I'm homeschooled.
Really?
You're lucky.
- Going to school was boring.
- My dad took me out,
and it wasn't 'cause it was boring.
Well, I had a rough time in school too.
Maybe not like you, but...
You know...
I don't mean to compare our situations.
Actually, I guess I am
comparing our situations,
but only to show you how yours is worse.
- You can edit that out, right?
- So I don't look like an idiot.
Relax.
Everyone acts like an idiot around me.
What makes you think it's not an act?
- Can I have something for my headache?
- Yeah. Is that new?
16 years old.
Has the same birthday I do.
I'm gonna start the test now.
Study showed no signs
of scarring in Kenny's heart.
- It wasn't drugs.
- Well, then give me something better?
- What's causing heart block?
- Could be toxoplasmosis.
We should do an lP
to test for infection.
If it was toxoplasmosis,
we would have seen enlarged lymphs.
And because you're not an idiot,
you already know that.
Meaning you said it because you wanna do
an LP looking for intracranial pressure.
- Because it is intracranial pressure.
- I'm not done.
You thought I wouldn't notice, which
means either you think I'm an idiot...
Do I look like one?
I'm doing my hair differently...
The kid's got headaches. He's been
popping acetaminophen.
How could you possibly
think that I was done?
I prefaced that with an either.
It needs an "or". Or...
You are an idiot... Which is possible.
I'm not great at judging men's looks.
- The OR?
- And the MRI room.
Yes.
Dr. House frequently conducts
differential diagnoses
in a variety of places.
He feels that a... Change in venue,
often leads to a change
in thinking processes.
I have to go take care
of something else.
Just let me do a CT scan,
see if I'm right.
The sooner we fix the problem,
the sooner we can get
- to his reconstructive surgery.
- Yeah, who cares if you're dead?
It's how you look.
Well, since you've given me
nothing better, we're back to drugs.
The one thing we know it's not.
Decreased uptake
on the membranous septum.
Could be an artifact.
We can redo it, but...
Nothing's nothing. Do an EP study.
EP study means we have
to stop this kid's heart.
I'll set it up.
House.
You have a minute to be disemboweled?
I'm gonna thread this catheter
through different areas in your heart,
and once I've found the right pathway,
I'll apply some electrical energy.
It'll stop my heart?
It sounds worse than it is.
You'll be fine.
- Is it gonna hurt?
- There'll be some discomfort.
If you've done drugs...
I understand.
Being different's really hard.
Kenny...
It's...
More important for you to get better
than to worry about getting in trouble.
If I did drugs, that could explain
my heart problem?
It could.
Then you can do the surgery
to fix my face?
That's why we're here.
You know how famous people...
Everywhere they go,
people are watching them...
Staring?
They never have a chance to just be.
You know, and a lot of them
turn to drugs.
People stare at them because
they're beautiful, but...
Me, they just stare.
You okay?
I need to know
what kind of drugs, Kenny, and how much.
Coke,
mostly.
A lot of coke.
And then, when I run out,
I usually go to LSD...
Or acid.
Those are the same thing.
They are?
You don't do drugs, do you?
- I drink from my dad's liquor...
- We're not gonna do this test.
I need you to turn on your side.
We need to intubate.
I need some help in here!
Too bad you guys are going
for a theatrical release.
Vomiting blood would have made
a great act out.
- Likely causes.
- Mallory-Weiss tear.
No pallor, no melena.
Why are you wearing a tie?
I always wear ties.
- I'm a doctor.
- Please don't look at the camera.
Sorry.
Nasal papilloma.
Hemorrhage could have
overwhelmed the heart.
Nice lipstick.
- Thank you.
- Bad idea.
- Hemorrhage came after the block.
- House, let them do their job.
Anybody here,
more interested in the medicine,
a little less interested
in the paparazzi?
Upper GI Bleed.
Could be something he ate or drank.
Maybe a peptic ulcer.
Good.
Except no abdominal pain.
Patient hasn't lost his appetite,
and the last I checked,
the gastrointestinal tract
isn't connected to the heart.
Yeah.
- But other than that, real good.
- Nasopharyngeal angiofibrosis.
I just said it wasn't a nasal tumor.
Stomach cancer.
Tumor causes bleeding.
Body's reaction to the tumor
causes paraneoplastic syndrome
which leads to heart block.
Finally!
Someone who is not just a pretty face.
You and Taub run the scope,
find the tumor.
Could be dangerous.
If the bleeding was caused
by liver failure as the result
of the intracranial...
Liver is the one organ you can't ascribe
to intracranial pressure.
True.
Intracranial pressure
cancause liver problems.
It causes an increase
in the cavernous sinus pressure
which causes pressure
in the superior vena cava
which shuts down the liver.
- You just think of that?
- No.
- Why didn't you say any...
- Think it's change his mind?
Not a chance.
House would have undercut me,
ordered me to do a procedure
I just argued against,
and then I'd look like a hypocrite
in front of the thousands of people
and potential future employers
watching this film.
If you're right,
and we stick a scope back down
a kid with liver failure,
he could bleed again.
I know.
He just vomited blood.
Isn't that dangerous?
No. You're in good hands.
Okay.
All right.
Well, it's great how he
rebounded from that setback.
What setback?
He didn't tell you about the...
Well, it's his right.
Records were sealed.
Personally, I think he was just
tapping his foot and reaching for
the toilet paper.
Obviously, it was a witch hunt.
Do you think
they singled him out because...
No, literally a witch hunt.
Dr. House is a practicing wiccan.
It's a beautiful religion.
It's very caring.
You have an all-access pass to the case,
not my fave five, so go.
Come on, come on, let's go.
I think I'm going blind.
Hairy Palms too?
She said something idiotic again,
and I didn't even notice it.
Foreman had to point out
that it was idiotic.
She's making mean idiot.
That's cute. You have a crush.
- No, I think it's something systemic.
- Thirteen's pretty.
You're obviously okay with her.
She killed a patient.
- The bitch is pretty.
- The bitch is a bitch.
- Ask her out.
- The bitch?
- She's a bitch.
- No the one that's making you an idiot.
The story of life.
Boy meets girl. Boy gets stupid.
Boy and girl live stupidly ever after.
- Pretty girl kill again?
- Nope.
Elephant boy just
vomiting up blood again.
No tumors
in the patient's stomach, so...
But the scope caused variceal bleeding.
Took 20 minutes of banding to stop it.
Taub was right about the liver failure.
Yeah.
His craniofacial deformity
is causing intracranial pressure...
No.
Where are the nose bleeds?
Where's the labored breathing?
You're right about me being wrong.
You're wrong about you being right.
I need new ideas.
Anybody.
Does it bother you
that this kid's gonna die
'cause you won't put down that camera?
At all, you know?
Your people should be extra motivated.
I'm sure they all
wanna look good in the film.
No, 'cause now they're
too worried about looking bad.
Dr. House,
heart block plus liver failure
could mean autoimmune.
Maybe scleroderma.
Foreman,
- does that make sense?
- Not without tight skin on the hands,
muscle weakness,
and a 30-year-old patient.
Liver failure plus heart block could be
a mitochondrial disorder.
Say what she just said.
Liver failure plus heart block
could be a mitochondrial disorder?
Go look for signs
of retinal degeneration.
No, it's ICP.
You're only gonna see swelling.
Take him with you, so he can see
the degeneration too.
So before you worked here in the ER,
you worked for House, right?
- Three and a half years.
- Why did you leave?
Hey, I don't wanna be on TV.
I'm not signing a release.
- We'll blur you out.
- Take off your pants.
You gonna be able to use any of this
if I start swearing?
Did House treat you as badly
as he treats his current fellows?
Loaded question.
That's not even a word.
Fork!
Very clever.
I learned how to be a doctor from House.
Or at least a doctor who learned
how to be a doctor from House,
- if that makes any sense.
- Any you left his team because
- you couldn't stand him anymore?
- No, no.
I... I love Dr. House.
That's something we haven't heard.
I mean...
What did you ask me again?
Why you left.
I...
I loved
behing around
him...
Professionally, you know.
It was always...
Stimulating.
Not...
In an erotic sense of the word.
Fork.
They forked.
And then they spooned.
Lean forward and place
your chin on the rest.
I can't reach it.
Scooch in a little.
I'll take care of it.
Just like last time?
Maybe we should try this
the old-fashioned way?
Okay, look up to the ceiling
and try not to blink, okay?
Okay, good.
Now straight ahead.
There it is.
Swelling.
No degeneration.
It's not mitochondrial.
Swelling proves there's
increased pressure in his brain.
Absolutely.
So now we can schedule
the reconstruction.
Absolutely not.
Your test proved you wrong.
We found exactly
what I predicted we'd find.
Swelling means there's
increased pressure.
You get a gold star of David
for proving that, yes,
this kid has a big head,
and big heads cause pressure.
- But it doesn't explain the liver.
- Too much acetaminophen does.
JRA explains all of it,
including the liver.
One theory's better than two.
Treat with steroids.
If you're wrong, steroids are gonna mess
with his immune system,
put off his surgery for months.
You really wanna lose this argument
in front of the camera?
I'll speak to the father.
Dr. House believes that Kenny has JRA,
juvenile rheumatoid arthritis.
We need to start administering steroids.
Will the steroids fix it?
I don't think he has JRA.
I think Dr. House is wrong
and that the steroid treatment
could be dangerous.
I think I can get House
thrown off the case,
and get Kenny
the facial surgery he needs.
The father refused steroids
until we're sure about the diagnosis.
I am sure.
It's JRA.
And why would he even doubt that,
unless a former fellow of mine
was chirping in his ear.
The decision was his.
I merely voiced my concern.
- Why'd you take this job?
- He's got a bulging cyst.
You had a perfectly good plastic
surgery practice
- lots of money.
- Fluids aren't draining properly.
Temptation to come screw with me
just too much for you?
- There's gotta be a better reason.
- He needs surgery to drain it.
And I think I mentioned this earlier.
You're fired.
What you did was over the line.
Get out.
But don't go anywhere.
You're not fired.
Yet.
No one is firing anyone
in the middle of this case.
Not while those cameras are here,
and not while taub is the only
person that this father trusts.
Where you going?
To do what I always do in these
situations.
Treat my patient behind his back.
That's one option.
Or you can do a CT scan
of the kid's head.
If there's no midline shift,
we know taub was wrong,
and you get your consent
to give the kid steroids.
Just a warning.
We have to start getting consent
every time we do a procedure,
soon they'll be asking
for informed consent.
Didn't think you had the guts
to stage a coup.
Coup failed.
I'm scheduled for execution at dawn.
No, you're not.
No reprieve from the governor.
You're a test result away from
becoming House's frontrunner.
He doesn't care about what you said
or what you did five minutes ago.
He just wants the next good idea.
Show me 20% magnification
of the forebrain.
I look at our patient...
Soon as I saw his face,
I saw a regular kid.
One thing about being a plastic surgeon.
You don't see what is,
you see what could be.
You talk like that around House,
doesn't matter how many
good ideas you come up with.
So...
Tell me what you don't
like about yourself.
Gosh,
There's so many things.
Is Dr. Taub available?
Because he was very highly recommended.
Well, he's no longer practicing with us,
but I've taken over all his files
so if you tell me what needs work.
Do you know why he left?
He had personal issues to deal
with, so if we could just.
My goodness.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine.
Cause my Friend
had his ears done by Dr. Taub.
Should he worry that they may...
Pop back?
No, it wasn't a professional issue.
I'm sorry I really can't
go into more detail.
Shall we discuss your needs?
You know that toe next to the big toe?
Mine's bigger than my big toe.
Is there any way to shorten it?
Or make my big toe bigger,
like a toe-augmentation?
Did he lie, cheat, or steal?
You're not here for a consultation,
are you?
What gave me away?
Was it my obviously perfect feet?
Hi.
- CT shows.
- Let's go.
What are you two doing here?
Skipping three scenes.
CT's back.
He's gonna say that there's
evidence of an anomaly.
I'm gonna say he's wrong.
He's gonna go back
to the father,
and we'll all end up here.
Defect is pushing on the right
frontal lobe.
This bend is a sign of herniation.
Or it's a sign of increased pressure
from JRA.
Dr. Taub would rather distract
you from the truth with sparkly
things like 4-carat diamonds.
House.
Your partner said that you left
for personal reasons.
But your wife said you lost a patient.
Son of a bitch.
You spoke to my wife?
See, that confused me.
Why would you give her a diamond
if you screwed somebody else over?
If you screwed her over,
I mean, I could.
Get that camera out of here.
You say anything to her?
Just asked questions.
Get them out of here too.
We're doctors.
I screwed around with a nurse.
It became a deal.
My partners found out, and I resigned.
There. Happy?
If you could be a bit more descriptive,
I'd be happier.
Some people pop pain pills.
I cheat.
We all have our vices.
Taub.
I don't see it.
Stay away from the family.
House,
start steroids,
and stay away from his family.
You are ugly.
You're an ass.
I have a deformity.
I know.
That's why you're ugly.
But you're a lucky boy.
Anywhere else in the animal kingdom,
your parents
would have eaten you at birth.
Your son needs steroids.
Dr. Cuddy agrees.
Does Dr. Taub?
He's... Not a real doctor.
He's a plastic surgeon.
All he cares is that your son looks
good in his coffin.
So I'm supposed to believe you.
The doctor who cares.
You shouldn't care if I care.
I don't trust you.
Because
I don't think the surgery's important?
You're putting your trust in someone
who does think the surgery's important.
You're willing to take chances,
to risk his life
- for something he doesn't need.
- I do need it.
I can't have real relationships.
I can't even have a real conversation.
Not even with my dad.
Dad...
I know you love me.
But you don't treat me normal.
You're always protective.
The world can always go to hell.
But you never yell at me...
Even when I screw up.
I wanna be normal.
Take your steroids.
You get to live.
Then you can do your surgery.
And it'll only change your face.
It won't change who your face made you.
We're gonna get caught.
Not on film.
All their camera equipment's in here.
Where did you get those keys?
Blue, the janitor.
What?
That's his name.
His name's Lou.
Owe him an apology.
Just watch 20 minutes of the stuff.
tell me if I'm out of my mind.
Finally, we have video evidence.
Dr. House,
heart block plus liver failure
could mean autoimmune,
maybe scleroderma.
Foreman, does that make sense?
Not without tight skin on the hands,
muscle weakness,
and a 30-year-old patient.
Can I see that again?
What did you miss?
She screwed up. I didn't.
No, just the part where
she leans forward.
I think you can see through her dress.
Upper gi bleed.
Could be from something he ate or drank.
- Maybe a peptic uicer.
- Good.
- You... Thought that was a good idea?
- What am I gonna do?
Just enjoy.
I'm gonna keep her around because
she makes me an idiot?
Well, you're protected.
Foreman seems immune.
You think he's gay?
Did he become an idiot around Chase?
Nasopharyngeal angiofibroma.
I just said it's not a nasal tumor.
Wait a minute.
Rewind that. Was that thirteen?
- I can't believe I'm that guy.
- Every guy is that guy.
- I'm not every guy.
- What, is this semantics here?
Okay.
All guys are that guy.
I'm not all guys.
Cameron was smart.
You know, I'm...
Beginning to doubt that.
I wanted to clarify something
I said earlier.
"I love Dr. House."
and then I qualified it,
which, after thinking about it,
I... Didn't really need to do.
I did love being around him.
I guess
I just wanted to qualify
what I
qualified before.
- I'm looking defensive, aren't I?
- No, no. I think that's great.
Clears everything up.
It's no big deal, really.
There's a mass lesion
in the left anterior temporal
lobe surrounded by edema.
Did you just insult me in pig latin?
Dr. House, please.
Would you just take a look at this?
The defect is causing
this nodular shadow here.
You see it?
You're right.
I didn't see that before.
Come on, let's go.
I know you think you're feeling better
on account of feeling better.
But this trusted family doctor thinks
that he's found a mass lesion.
So if you could lie back down
- and struggle to breathe.
- Okay.
You were right.
I'm thrilled I'm wrong.
This is great, Kenny.
You're gonna get your surgery now.
First person I'm coming back to see
is you.
Cause compared to me,
You're gonna look like butt.
What, no comeback?
Look at that.
What?
His little finger.
It's twitching.
No, it's not.
Just give it a second.
There.
And?
He's not better.
What's wrong?
My diagnosis.
I don't know what he has.
Cancel the surgery.
New symptom.
Involuntary muscle movement.
A twitching finger is a symptom?
The body doing something
it's not supposed
is the definition of a symptom.
Kid's about to have
a life changing operation.
- He's nervous.
- Or he's not.
Or you were right.
The kid got better
when we put him on steroids.
This is JRA, and it's under control now.
Or the steroids have just tempered
his condition.
- He had a haircut, still got bad hair.
- What about lyme disease?
It explains everything.
The heart issues, internal bleeding,
even why it'd get better on steroids.
On the other hand,
if he has lyme disease,
there would be other subtle clues,
like a huge, target-shaped rash.
But thanks for playing.
Why can't you just accept the fact
that you cured this kid?
You want to stop his surgery.
You're not normal,
so you don't want anybody else
to be normal.
You don't think normal's healthy.
Could be rheumatic fever.
Also explains why the steroids helped.
It's a similar inflammatory disease.
Rheumatic fever doesn't explain
liver failure.
- Taub thinks that acetaminophen does.
- Fine. Let's test your theory.
Remove his pacing wire.
If he's better,
his heart'll beat just fine on its own,
and then he can have his operation.
If I'm right, his heart will stop.
Kutner, have the paddles on standby.
Another chance to blow someone up.
There'll be some minor discomfort,
and you'll feel a slow,
steady pulling sensation.
Are you sure his heart
is ready for this?
Absolutely.
He's convinced he's sure.
Whereas...
I care about your son
and have, therefore,
brought a professional defibrillist.
We're not gonna need those.
Dad, I feel fine.
My finger hasn't moved in a while.
Okay.
Take him off.
Here we go.
Heart rate's 85 beats per minute.
BP 110 over 70.
Is he okay?
I feel the same.
He's fine.
You're fine.
Thank God!
What do you mean, thank God?
God's the guy who gave it to him.
Thank you.
Can you tell us about the procedure?
We have to use both an extra
and intracranial approach
to get enough exposure
to reduce the encephalocele CYST
and do the bony reconstruction.
And how are you participating
in the procedure?
She's not.
They don't want me here,
because they think the kid's cured.
- I don't.
- And what do you think the problem is?
Wish I knew.
I just know that if Dr. House is right,
something's gonna go wrong.
Dr. House doesn't think he's right.
Well, then, I'll just waste a few hours
watching a surgery.
The danger is we have to reconstruct
all the way down to the cranial base.
And there are some big vessels
down there.
So what we'll do is we'll work
our way down to here.
When were these pictures taken?
About...
Three weeks ago. Why?
What do you see?
The acanthosis nigricans
was already there.
It's been there a lot longer than that.
Probably his whole life.
What about around his hairline?
What?
There's no discoloration.
There is now.
I have a new theory.
Their bad ideas
don't indicate a lack of intelligence.
It indicates an open mind,
the willingness not to be trapped
by conventional.
- You've got a problem.
- Tell me something I don't know.
You hire beautiful girls enslave them,
force them to be around you,
because you don't know how
have an actual relationship.
If they're qualified, keep them.
If not, fire them and ask them out.
You do realize that
"tell me something I don't know"
is just an expression.
13.
You think that just
because she's as beautiful, Ergo...
That because she hasn't had
a decent idea.
No, my point is she's about to enter
your office, so you should shut up.
You were right about the diagnosis.
Yes.
It was JRA.
I'm very proud.
I mean you were right about being wrong.
He's got lyme disease.
It explains everything.
Could you just hold up some fingers.
So I can see if I'm literally blind?
- We ruled out lyme disease hours ago.
- All the symptoms fit.
I am so ashamed.
Is she really that good-looking?
Apparently.
How many lives have been lost
because of pretty girls?
The target rash is hiding.
No one ever looked
at him closely enough.
She's getting uglier by the second.
We can try and pretend we're above it.
We can try and intellectualize it away,
but ultimately, shiny,
pretty, perky thingsare good,
and's ugly,
misshapen teenage boys are repulsive.
The question was
do you resent Dr. Cuddy's
interference in your practice?
Well, then I guess my answer
wasn't very helpful, was it?
Mini-stud,
stand up.
I spoke to your other partner.
- After Cuddy told you.
- No, I stayed away.
Did it all over the phone.
I asked for a reference,
said you were applying
for a plastic surgery job.
- God!
- Yeah.
He went nuts.
Apparently, you signed a non-compete.
Now, why would you agree to that?
I don't wanna practice plastic surgery.
You sign a contract
because someone's making you.
Someone's getting something from you.
What did they give you in return?
- They agreed to keep their mouths shut.
- So you gave up your chosen career
just so they'd be quiet?
I love my wife.
And you risked this job
with nothing to fall back on?
I thought you were wrong.
Sit back down.
You're keeping him
because he's a philanderer?
- Where do I sign up?
- Ask the Mormon.
I'm keeping him because
he's interesting.
Dr. Terzi, would you please stand up?
Nice.
I have treated you unfairly.
Prejudged you.
And for me to be a better person,
I have to rectify that situation.
You're fired.
You wanna...
Grab some dinner?
Maybe a movie?
Seriously.
Just days ago,
with Kenny's condition worsening,
it was Dr. Gregory House
reassuring Kenny and his father.
I care about your son.
The charming House,
who happens to be a film buff
with a soft spot in his heart for
children, told us how he got his start.
See, I became a doctor
because of the movie patch Adams.
Determined to save the boy's life
as well as...
Horror...
Well, it's nice of them to send
us an early copy.
- Not so much sent as stolen.
- In the end, it was Dr. Gregory House
who served as not only a doctor,
but a rock for Kenny and his father.
You're putting your trust in someone
who does think the surgery's important.
- House, one of those rare doctors.
- God.
Wears his heart on his sleeve...
I was saying that was a stupid
thing to do.
- It's difficult not to be moved.
- Stop it!
Suddenly I don't feel like I can trust
Michael Moore movies.
Where are you going?
Kittens to get out of trees?
Deaf kids to read to?
I owe it to the world
to make sure this evil
never sees the light of day.
Is there anything else?
Thank you, Dr. House.
Thank you.