The O.C.:
I thought you were going
to be a silent partner
Came to see my girlfriend.
What?
You need new recruits,
right? So sign us up.
Your date doesn't pay you.
That... that's illegal.
Right.
I could put off RISD
for a semester.
We could both go back together.
You'd really put off
college for me?
You take it...
It's yours...
I found you.
I just had the weirdest dream.
You were in it, I think.
I think you were in
my dream, too.
I'm really glad you're here.
Hey, I asked
you a question.
Yeah, no, it's just
some of these bugs
are really sort of stubborn.
I was using that.
Now you're not.
Gonna tell me
what's going on?
What if I told you
it's New Year's Eve
and we're on our way to Vegas?
I might hit you with this. Why
are the girls acting so strange?
I don't... I mean...
you know, I don't know.
SUMMER:
How long is it
supposed to take?
Five minutes.
How long has it been?
Okay-- four minutes
and 47 seconds.
You're lying. It's written
all over you face.
Well, then I shouldn't bluff
when we get to Las Vegas.
Look... what... man,
they're in the bathroom.
Why don't you just ask them.
13 seconds left.
Do I need to remind you
why you're even here right now?
11 more seconds.
Because you haven't
killed me yet?
What if there wasn't
enough pee?
No, because you didn't have any
New Year's Even plans
so you hijacked mine.
How many bars am I looking for?
Two, two bars.
Six more seconds.
I told you I'd pay you back.
Oh, my God, I can't look.
And now I'm collecting.
So tell me what's happening.
Oh, my God, three more seconds,
two more seconds,
one more second...
seven hours earlier
Here you go.
Last coffee of '06.
How much you hoping I don't
make that joke all day?
Not like I'll be
around to hear it.
So walk me through
your itinerary again.
You've got breakfast
with Taylor.
Back home to pack,
quick lunch, off to Vegas.
She still doesn't know
you're taking her?
Well, that's why
it's a surprise.
He's told me nothing.
And I just thought.
you know,since he went
to all of this trouble
it would be nice for me
to surprise him, too, and...
Summer, are you even
listening to me?
What? No... yeah...
every word.
'Cause you seem kind
of out of it.
I'm sorry, I'm just
still waking up.
You guys seem pretty
serious, though?
It's that old adage--
couples who have comas together,
stay together.
She won't think Vegas
is cheesy, will she?
Do you think it's cheesy
to get him lingerie?
Obviously, I'm going
to be wearing it,
but it's really for him.
Look, Taylor...
You're right.
it's way too soon
for lingerie.
Is he going to think I'm
some kind of kinky,
sex-starved, divorcee?
You're being paranoid.
Still, be careful, 'cause
people, they go to Vegas
and they come back married.
What about you and
Summer-- any plans?
Well, if it's
a typical night for us,
I'm probably in for
some Korean cinema, manga
and making new friends
on MySpace.
In other words...
No "plans"--
that's a dirty word.
That's right up there with
"responsibility" and "future."
There'll be plenty of time
for that when we're in college.
And she's on board with that?
Totally.
I hope I don't have
to kill him.
When are you
meeting Ryan?
Ooh, now.
All right, I will
see you tomorrow.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year, Summer.
Same to you.
Good luck tonight.
I'm sure everything
will just be great.
Oh, speak of the devil.
Summer.
Atwood.
Taylor.
Hi.
You looking forward
to your surprise tonight?
I am. Are you looking
forward to yours?
I am.
Ew. That's my cue.
Okay, here it is.
What is it?
Open it.
Hey.
Hi.
I wanted to talk to you
about what we're doing tonight.
Why talk when actions
speak so much louder
than words.
What is it?
I don't know.
Just open it.
Okay.
Oh, my.
Surprise.
"Jamaican me crazy."
It's funny because it's not.
Do you think I'm a whore?
What? No, no.
It's just...
I already have this.
You nut.
For a second there, I was like,
oh, major miscalculation.
No, no, no.
It's going to be
a great night.
All right, come here.
Yeah... You didn't make any
plans for us tonight, did you?
Well, I thought we would just...
What "Jamaican" up as you go?
You are
such a baby.
I'm done baby-sitting you.
Do you understand me?
I'm done.
O.C 08
-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:Allen
-=www.eastgame.net=-
JULIE:
I'm not questioning
the fantasy, Spencer.
We've all imagined doing it
with the delivery boy.
I am questioning whether we
should be paying for the pizza.
It's starting to add up.
We're running a male
prostitution ring, Julie.
Pizza's the cost of business.
Hey, who did we...?
Who'd we set Petrie Marchand
up with?
That guy you call
the Mambo King.
Oh, yeah.
My real question--
what do you know
about money laundering?
That'd be nothing. Why?
Because it's the holidays
and we're busy
and I can't keep filing all this
cash under "extra money."
I'll, um... I'll see
you later at the place.
Yeah.
That was Jimmy on the phone.
He's supposed to call
Kaitlin at midnight?
Yeah.
Well, he's hosting a party
on his boat.
And he wanted you to tell
Kaitlin he's sorry,
but he might be out
of cell phone range.
Poor Kaitlin.
I know she doesn't show it,
but I think she really,
really misses him.
Can I help you with something?
No, no.
No, I'm good.
Julie, I appreciate you handling
the bookkeeping,
but honestly,
I probably have
more experience.
Well... all the more reason
for me to learn.
I mean, what if you get hit
by a bus or something?
God forbid.
There must be something
I can do.
Some more coffee?
I got it at the place
on the corner.
Somebody going
on a coffee run?
I'll take a latte.
Hello, sweetheart.
Just thought I'd drop off
an invite to my soiree.
Yeah, Gordon, you
know, I received
like 11 of these in the mail.
Well, now you've got
an even dozen.
So read it to me.
"Gordon Bullit invites you
and a hot guest
to start 2007 with a bang."
(laughing)
That joke never gets old,
does it?
Been using it
since 1989.
So, uh...
what time do you want me
to send a limo?
You know, honestly, I'm not sure
that I'll get through
with everything here.
Damn it, hotcakes, when I
bankrolled this operation,
I thought I'd see you more,
not less.
Since I got back
from Riyadh,
we've had two dinner dates
and zero hanky-panky.
Well, it's
a new business, Gordon.
Well, hey, look, at least
let me get you
a bean counter to take care
of some of the paperwork.
Bullit, let me have that back.
Wow, you girls eat
a mess of pizza.
We work through dinner a lot.
Look, I really appreciate
the gesture, Bullit,
but I would prefer to do this
on my own, hmm?
Okay.
You coming tonight?
If I can.
Damn, woman.
(sighs)
And he requested me?
Yeah, all right, all right.
I'll see what I can do.
Okay.
Working on New Year's Eve?
Yeah, one of your homeless guys
from Thanksgiving
attacked a parking meter.
He couldn't remember his name,
but he remembered mine.
I was talking
about the sandwiches.
Oh, yeah, Ryan's putting
together a cooler for Vegas.
I'm his sandwich guy.
Cohens are natural
sandwich artists.
It's like our very own
super power.
Yeah, I don't know if
it qualifies us
for the Justice League, though.
What's up?
You've got that
"something's up"
look on your face.
Well, you know, probably
'cause something's up.
What'd you do?
More like what I didn't do.
Turns out Summer's expecting
me to make some elaborate
New Year's Eve plans.
Oh, romantic holiday plans--
definitely not a Cohen
super power.
We've got nine months
until we go to college.
This is the last time in our lives
we don't have to worry about stuff.
Yeah, yeah, the ladies don't
really buy that line, though.
You still have to show
her that you value her.
My advice...
Put some thought and effort
into making some real
New Year's Eve plans, pronto.
Well, my work
here is done.
I've got a date with
a bail bondsman.
And you and Summer have
a wonderful New Year's Eve.
And... be safe.
Hey.
Hey. You be safe, too,
in Vegas, will ya?
Yeah.
The sandwiches are
all ready. Good to go.
And if I do say so myself,
they're great.
Thank you, Sandy.
The only thing you have
to keep in mind--
make it personal.
I think I just got
the purr-fect idea.
Good man.
What was that about?
Oh, nothing-- just Summer
and I coming with you
to Vegas.
What?!
You may want to make
some more sandwiches.
I'm going to go
upstairs and pack.
You're late.
Yeah. I've been looking
for my book.
What book?
The one with everyone's
names, phone numbers.
(sighs)
I had it when
I was talking to you.
I put it down for a sec,
it was gone.
This has got to be a sign.
What are you
talking about?
Your father tried
to saddle me
with an accountant today.
What if he finds out
we've turned his investment
into a whorehouse?
Or if Kirsten finds out?
No, we need to shut
this down now.
Then... let's
just do tonight.
All right? We both
need the money.
We can manage without.
What if Neil
sells your house?
Where you going to live?
We're going to make
40 grand each.
Now, you want to close
down shop after that, cool,
but let's do tonight.
Come on.
We'll burn
everything tomorrow.
I'll light the match myself.
(knocking on door)
Frank, Frank, Frank.
Damn, damn, double damn.
Good to see you.
Come on in.
Have a seat.
Can I fix you a drink?
No, I'm fine.
So, cowboy, what the hell you doing
in these neck of the woods?
Well, you... you once said,
if I ever needed a job...
Serious? Now, don't be jerking
the Bullit around.
I'm serious.
Well, now,
that's a good thing.
And I happen to have
a couple of places
I could use you pronto.
But, knowing you, you've
already picked something out.
You're not going
to believe this,
but I saw you invested
in a dating service.
(chuckles):
You're kidding, right?
A man of your talents?
I think there's
a future in it.
Yeah, but the tricky
thing there is,
my girlfriend, Julie--
she's kind of running that.
Really?
I know what you're thinking,
but it's not like
that barmaid in Daytona.
Now, that one,
she was a con artist.
And Julie's legit?
Absolutely.
I mean, Julie's problem
is not thievery.
It's pride. She wants
to do everything herself,
and I get no chance to see her.
(phone rings)
Oh, wait. Bullit.
Oh, right. The dress shop.
Okay. On the way.
Sorry. I got to go.
Well, it was
good to see you.
You're going
to love Newport.
I'm sure I will.
Oh, and if Julie ever gets
less proud, you let me know.
I'd love to help out.
I'll do that.
Happy New Year, partner.
Same to you.
See you later.
Right.
Taylor,
you look terrible.
What's the matter?
Okay, can you keep a secret?
But I mean a big secret.
Like, a really big secret.
Yeah.
I think you might be pregnant.
Um... okay.
First of all,
if I were pregnant,
that would be my secret.
And second of all,
I'm late, not pregnant.
And how did
you know that?
Okay, when I went
to visit you in Providence,
I remember that
you had your period,
which means you should have had
it again a week and a half ago.
But the box of tampons
that you bought
two weeks ago
hasn't even been opened.
Summer, have you had unsafe sex?
Well, there was that time
where Seth visited...
(scoffs):
Summer...
I didn't want
the pharmaceutical companies
playing slumlord with my eggs.
Well, what about condoms?
Latex smells funny.
So do diapers.
Taylor!
What? Don't pretend
you're not worried about this,
because you've been
preoccupied all day.
I am not pregnant.
Hmm. Well, prove it.
Get that away from me.
Hey, you decent?
Seth, actually,
Summer and I were just having
a little girl time,
so if you could
just come back in 15...
It's so good
to see you!
Hey, wow! Look at
all this affection,
and I haven't even told you
my surprise yet.
Though, to be fair, it's
really more of Ryan's surprise.
Seth.
But, yes, the four of us
are going to Las Vegas.
Ryan is in
the car, waiting.
Ryan's taking me to Vegas?
And I'm taking you,
Mrs. What-Are-Our-
Plans-For-New Year's.
Now, why don't you
to get packed
so we can get
on the road.
Actually, Summer
and I just need
to dash into the bathroom
really quick and...
That is a great idea.
That is the best
idea ever!
Why don't you help me
pick out what to bring?
Okay.
Okay, well, I'm just going
to pack this toothpaste
because we might want it
--TAYLOR:
Hey, Ryan, can we stop soon?
Summer and I have to pee.
RYAN:
Oh, yeah? Sure. You know what?
Next chance we get,
I'll get some gas.
TAYLOR:
Great.
--Summer, I think, when we stop,
we should try out
our new toothpaste.
Um...
Breath's a little stale.
SETH:
Ryan, are you ready
for a sandwich?
Hmm? Listen, I know
we're crashing,
but I promise you,
soon as we get to Vegas,
I'm going to buy you
the best room
Sandy Cohen's money can buy.
You're rescuing me,
and I want to pay you back.
Yeah, all right.
Hey, Seth,
hypothetically speaking,
if I was your girlfriend,
and I had health issues,
would you want
to know about them?
Um... I don't know.
What kind of health issues?
Diarrhea of the mouth.
Can we just,
like, stop talking
and turn the music up
and just drive, please?
Summer, there is
something in your hair.
Let me get it
out for you.
(whispering):
What are you doing?
I think you need
to tell Seth.
No. I don't think
he could handle it.
How do you know?
Aw, crap!
Forgot my toothbrush.
I'm going to have
to use my finger.
See? He's a child.
Did you get
a toothbrush, too?
Seth!
Don't...!
Oh.
Is this...?
Mine! My toothpaste.
RYAN:
What's going on?
Nothing. It's
just this is...
extra whitening, and Seth
needs tartar control.
Badly.
(whispering):
Thank you.
Mom?
Okay, the coast is clear, dude.
Yeah. She's probably
still at work.
You sure we did
the right thing
but not buying that little
number with rhinestones?
You asked me for my help
to pick out a dress
for my mother, so trust me.
Well, I just want to make sure
she feels like a million dollars
at my party tonight, that's all.
That's assuming
she finishes work on time.
I offered to get someone in
there to help the woman out.
She flat out refused me.
You really like her, don't you?
Oh, yeah, peanut.
She's under my skin.
The whole time I was in Riyadh,
didn't once try
to peek under a girl's burkha.
So, uh...
what you got going on tonight?
Well, I'm supposed
to talk to my dad,
but his boat's out
of cellphone range.
So, whatever. It's no big.
Well, dang, girl, if you're
free, why not come to my party?
Because I'm 40?
No, because
it's New Year's Eve,
and I got not one prince,
but two coming.
William and Harry?
Mm-mm--
Samir and Abbas. Saudis.
About your age,
and not a bad catch,
if you don't mind
raisins in your chicken.
You like two-steppin'?
It's a dance we do
in Texas-- I can show you
tonight if you'd like.
You can hold
your breath for that.
All right. Well,
I appreciate your help.
You take care now.
Ignore her.
Come again?
She refused your help,
so ignore her.
It's what I always do.
Here you go.
What's this for?
In case you change
your mind, come to the party,
you might want to buy a dress
or a lollipop or something.
Yo, Frank.
Yeah, Bullit.
What's going on
this afternoon?
It's up to you.
You'll be there
when I take it?
Of course.
Let's go.
Hey, uh...
is everything all right?
You, uh... were acting
kind of strange in the car.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I just wanted to, uh,
you know, apologize.
I know this trip to Vegas
is supposed to be us,
but Seth kind
of hijacked it
to get out of
the doghouse, so
what are you
going to do?
Yeah, I know.
Uh... anyway,
you know, he, uh...
he's getting us a room.
So at least
we'll be alone.
Yeah. Uh... I don't think
that we should do that.
In fact,
I know that we shouldn't.
Uh... What...
what are you talking about?
Obviously, we both thought
that we were going to...
It's Vegas,
and there's lingerie,
and it would be great,
trust me,
but I just want our
first time to be special,
and tonight is
just not the night.
Okay? Sorry.
I got to go.
I have a question.
And let's pretend
I wasn't eavesdropping.
Are you absolutely positive
that you haven't
had sex yet with Taylor?
Not even, like a,
"I feel guilty about this
because you're kind of wasted,
but how did that
happen?" mistake?
Okay, I'll take
that as a no.
Hey, look at that.
It's a green alien. It's
crazy. Well, these windows
aren't going to wash themselves.
Seth, what's going on?
Okay, "Remove the test stick
from the foil wrapper."
Did that already.
"Position the stick
with the test windows
"facing away from
the urine stream,
"and place the
absorbent tip
under the stream
of urine."
Stream of urine, Summer.
Uh...
You need something?
Oh, no. Thank you.
Who is it?
A slutty alien. Did you pee?
I'll go outside.
Wait, wait. Don't leave me.
May I help you?
You must be Julie.
And you are...?
(laughs):
I told you she was hot.
Julie, meet
my buddy Frank.
He's gonna put your
books in order.
Didn't I say no to this?
Oh, yes, you did, but a little
birdie told me to ignore you,
so that's
what I'm doing.
Gordon...
Is no longer willing
to negotiate.
Now, let's let Frank
do his thing.
Meantime,
let's get you out of
that Pilgrim outfit
and into a ball gown, which
I happen to have bought you.
And, Frank,
if you get finished by midnight,
you come play with us,
you hear?
I will.
Oh, Julie.
It was nice meeting you.
Nice meeting you, too, Frank.
Come on, sweetie.
Why are the girls
acting so strange?
Dude, I don't, you know...
12 more seconds.
11 more seconds.
What if there wasn't enough pee?
Ten seconds.
Here, let's switch.
How many bars am
I looking for?
Two. Two bars.
Oh, my God, four more seconds.
Oh, my God, I can't look.
Three more seconds.
two more seconds...
Oh, my God.
one more second.
Okay, I can't do it.
Just don't look at it,
I can't breathe...
Okay, okay...
Sit down. Sit
down, sit down.
I can't breathe.
Here, breathe, breathe.
Breathe into this.
Breathe deep breaths.
Look, Summer, I'm not gonna
make you do anything.
It's totally your decision.
But whatever you do, it
doesn't change the truth,
and-and in a few hours,
it's gonna be the new year.
Do you want to start that year
as an adult,
with your eyes
wide open, or...
with your head in the sand?
Give it to me.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's gone.
What?!
I don't believe it.
Well, do you think
she cheated on you?
No.
I mean, I-I can't believe
she didn't tell me.
Well, I'll wash the car if you
want to go smash something.
Like maybe
that big green bug.
Hey!
Excuse me! I...
You... Follow that alien!
She stole my purse!
What?
She just stole my purse.
What? Well...
Get in the car!
She just stole it from
underneath the bathroom.
Seth, hurry up!
She's getting...
She's right there! Go!
Ryan, go! Go!
SETH:
Geez!
Can't we just buy you
a new purse and cancel
your credit cards?
No,
we need that purse.
Why?
Because...
Of the pills
that I have in there.
For the allergy I have
but never told you guys about.
It's just...
nothing serious.
And she needs to take
the pills before midnight.
Right.
And since we are
in the middle of the desert,
and nowhere near
a pharmacy, it has to be
the pills in that purse.
Sorry.
You're being awfully quiet.
There's a lot of
that going around.
Hey, I see brake lights.
look liked
SUMMER:
Did anyone get
a good look at her face?
SETH:
She's an alien-- it's not an
easy thing to lose in a crowd.
I don't believe it.
Everyone is an alien.
(exhales):
Hey, we're gonna go this way.
Okay, we'll
go this way.
TAYLOR:
But...
Come on. I promised
you some alone time.
Hey.
Mm... hey.
Spencer, let me
ask you a question.
When you paired these
ladies up with their dates,
did you know they were
coming to this party?
You don't think Kirsten's gonna
smell something fishy, do you?
No, no. I think
we're taking the fish
and slapping her
in the face with it.
She knows these women
are our clients.
Maybe she won't notice--
isn't she an alcoholic?
Recovering, unfortunately.
So did you find anything
out about Frank?
Not a lot.
He's a friend of my dad's.
I'm not sure
where they met.
He took the series seven
a month ago,
but before that, nothing.
Doesn't exist.
So what do you think?
Well, I'm thinking maybe...
CIA or Special Ops?
No, Deep Throat, I mean, what
do you think we should do?
Does he seem like
someone we can bribe?
Eh, I wouldn't bank on it--
my dad's big on loyalty.
Speaking of...
where is he anyway?
He's over there introducing
Kaitlin to some Saudi princes.
This is Samir--
and I call him Sam.
And this is Abbas--
and I call him Boss.
Oh.
You are, uh,
Kait... Kaitland?
Kaitlin.
Kaitland.
Yeah.
Okay, Kaitland.
(sighs)
He says there's
no coat-check,
and there's no one
really in charge.
Oh, then he invited
me to party
on his asteroid, which
I think means his trailer.
Maybe we should just
find Seth and Summer
and make sure they're okay.
Taylor, I...
I know. Seth told me.
Told you what?
You know... it, the thing.
Okay, let me explain...
I just wish
that you told me.
That's what I'm mad about,
not any of the other stuff,
just that you kept it from me.
Wait, wh-what other stuff?
Well, you know, that you were...
sleeping with someone
before we started dating.
Who says?
Well, the math says,
but, look, I'm not
mad about that.
See, I knew
you felt this way.
Well, I'm not... I'm not
accusing you of anything.
Yes, you are.
You are saying that I had
random unsafe sex with someone
in between
my marriage annulment
and us making
out at Kaitlin's.
Do you know how many
days that was, Ryan?
So what are you saying?
You're saying you were
sleeping with someone
while we were dating?
Is that what you think?
No! But if you were,
I couldn't be mad
because we were never exclusive.
Right. And why would
you want to be,
since you clearly think I am
a big fat divorcee whore!
Oh, my God.
Julie.
Hi. Hey.
Uh, where's Sandy?
Julie, what's going on?
What do you mean?
Well, it's just that
all our clients here
are on dates with
people that look like
they're college students--
I mean, weren't we supposed
to set up Jessica Rogers
with Dr. Weston?
Yeah, you know, we were,
but she called yesterday
and said she met someone--
that's love.
FRANK:
Hello, Julie.
Frank... uh, you're here.
Uh... Frank,
this is Kirsten Cohen,
my partner.
This is Frank...
Perry. Frank Perry.
Nice to meet you.
Frank Perry. Right. Um...
Bullit hired him to put
our books in order,
and that's what he's been
doing all night so that
I could be here.
Oh.
Does everything add up?
Yeah. Looks good.
And business seems
to be booming, so...
if I had a drink,
I-I would toast you.
Well, I'll-I'll take it
anyway. Thank you.
All right, ladies,
as you were.
Kirsten, a pleasure
to meet you.
Ah, Kiki, do you ever
feel invincible.
Why?
Oh... no reason.
Happy New Year, sweetie.
Remind me again why
we're looking for a purse
when the larger issue
seems to be Taylor
thinking she has
a baby inside of her?
And don't give me anything
about any allergy pills,
'cause I'm not buying it.
Seth, we need the purse, because
the pregnancy test is in it.
The test that we have already
taken and haven't looked at yet.
The test that we need
to see before midnight
so we can start 2007 knowing
exactly where we stand.
Can I interrupt you
for a second?
I'm remembering something
I wanted to ask you for
back in the car when I found out
the test was Taylor's.
What?
Paw.
Up top.
You're asking me
for a high five?
Can you imagine if it was
your test we're looking for?
Now, I know it seems
a little bit selfish,
but I think we're entitled
to celebrate,
so come on, up top, hit it.
Hit it.
God, Seth.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
It's really you!
Seth Cohen! I saw you
at Comic-Con years ago.
Oh.
I'm a huge, huge...
huge Atomic County fan!
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
Check it out, man--
I'm Kid Chino!
Oh, wow, that is fantastic.
Listen, I'm looking...
We got to take
a picture, man.
Oh, oh, okay.
This... is the greatest
night of my life, Mr. Cohen.
Wow, thanks a lot.
Hey, oh, it's the alien!
Smile!
Thanks a lot.
Thanks, man.
I didn't want
to embarrass you
in front of your partner,
but your so-called
dating service...
is not exactly
what Bullit thought
he was investing in, is it?
Why don't you wet your lips.
Your mouth looks dry.
Kaitland?
What?
We are boring you, yes?
Maybe it will be more pleasing
to you if we make...
kissing to each other.
Yeah, y-you guys go do that.
Okay, so just what do I have
to do to keep you quiet?
Suite 522 at the Four Seasons.
Say... half an hour.
Oh, there you are.
How's your client?
Darrel?
Well, he's better off than
the parking meter he beheaded.
I sent him to a shelter.
How has your night been?
Oh, it's just...
it's just odd.
Julie's acting strange, and...
well, we have clients here--
it's just they're not with the
dates that we set them up with.
So if I'm a little
tense I apologize.
Come on, let's work it out
on the dance floor.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
No, my fault.
Sandy Cohen.
Uh, Frank Perry.
Frank works for Bullit.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah, the Big Bang himself.
Well, it was nice
bumping into you.
And, uh, happy New Year.
You, too.
Sandy, something wrong?
I feel like I know
that guy from somewhere.
Come on.
How about that dance?
Mm.
(lively music playing)
(chuckles):
Hey there, Miss Columbus.
How are you?
Good to see you.
Hey, now, enjoy yourself.
Mom, aren't you gonna stay
for midnight?
Oh, Kaitlin, your mom
has a headache.
But you should stay-- have
Bullit give you a ride home.
This doesn't have anything to do
with that creepy guy,
does it?
What creepy guy?
They guy I saw you talking to.
You were gonna go
meet him, weren't you?
This is not what you think.
But, please, you can't
tell Bullit about this.
Mom, he really likes you.
And-and I really
like him, too.
It just...
You have to trust me
on this, okay?
(exhales):
Okay.
Happy New Year, baby.
Uh, Mom?
I miss Dad sometimes.
I know, honey.
We'll call him tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
Taylor!
Hey, Ryan.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Ryan, you think I'm a whore,
I'm gonna act like a whore.
I don't think you're a whore,
but I definitely
don't think you should
be drinking.
Why, because I might be pregnant
with my whore baby?
Hey!
How about giving that back
before I atomize your face?
How about you just back off?
Hey, what's going on?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to figure out
why my girlfriend is taking
pregnancy tests
and I'm the last one
to find out about it.
How is that possible?
Because it's not hers, okay?
It's mine.
It's my test that
is in Taylor's purse.
What?
Great. This is great.
Now I'm not gonna know
if I'm pregnant before midnight.
There's nothing like
starting off a new near
with something like this
hanging over your head.
Happy New Year, Ryan.
What?
Ryan!
Dude, it's Summer's.
I know. Come on. Let's go.
CROWD:
...three, two, one.
(all cheering)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Come on. Wait a minute!
Come back!
Come on!
Are you kidding me?!
--All right, thanks.
Nearest cab company's
in Baker.
What do you want to do now?
Oh, curl up into the fetal
position and weep.
Although, perhaps the unborn
baby metaphor...
Not really appropriate.
I cannot believe Summer
might be pregnant.
Oh, my God.
I think I saw an empty...
Uh, Seth.
Hurry up.
(laughing)
TAYLOR:
Don't worry, Summer.
I'm sure we'll pass a 24-hour
pharmacy at some point.
The symbolism window
closed at midnight.
We'll do it
in the morning.
Okay.
Taylor, I really appreciate
everything you did for me today.
I really hope it didn't cause
any permanent damage
with you and Ryan.
Oh, don't worry about me,
please.
How did I get here?
How did I go from being
an Ivy League Al Gore
in the making to a knocked-up
college dropout
with a boyfriend that forgets
to pack his toothbrush
when he travels?
How did this happen?
You know what?
It's a new year.
We all get a fresh start.
Okay? You and me
and Seth and Ryan, we can all be
whatever we want to be.
And everything negative
will be left in last year.
What's my name?
Zerk-nong
Spell it.
Z-U...
"E"!
Oh. Z... Z-E-R-
K-N
Hyphen.
Hyphen, N-O-N-G.
It was kind of mean leaving them
in there like that, wasn't it?
Yeah.
I'll call 'em,
see if they're okay.
I need to borrow your phone.
I left mine in my purse.
(laughing)
What does that spell?
Zerk-nong.
Again.
Good girl.
(laughs)
(cell phone ringing)
Oh, my God!
Run!
(horn beeps)
Hey, Mr. Cohen!
Hey!
Hey, these alien
chicks are really easy.
Hey, we need
an emergency evacuation.
You got it. Hey,
too bad we don't have
Little Miss Vixen's
magic scooter.
We have to go!
They stole my purse!
(tires squeal)
All set?
What?
You still thinking
about Frank?
I can't shake the feeling
that I know him.
I wish you did.
I'd love to know who Julie
has going through our books.
She never said anything. Nothing
about where Bullit found him?
Knowing Bullit,
it could be anywhere:
the golf course,
Saudi Arabia, prison.
You going
to follow me home?
Yeah. No, no.
I'm going to swing
by the homeless shelter
make sure Daryl made it there.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I won't be long.
You just say where you want us
to drop you off, Mr. Cohen.
The girls and I are honored
to be helping out.
Look, as scared as you are,
I'm sure Summer's
ten times more scared.
Translation: I need
to be there for her.
Exactly. And you can start
by telling her how you feel.
Well, kinda depends
on what's in this purse.
Does it?
It is going to change
whether or not
you want to be
with her?
No, of course not.
And can you imagine
ever not wanting to be with her?
No.
That's your answer.
Hey, great party.
Thank you, Peanut.
How'd it go
with the Saudis?
(blows forlorn note)
Well, they want to fly me over
to Dubai for their prom,
but I said there's no way
I want to wear one
of those Klan outfits.
(laughs)
I don't blame you.
Have you seen your mother?
I've been, I've been
looking for her.
Um, she went home.
She had a migraine.
Dang, I wish she'd have told me.
Well, I hope
she's okay.
So what was that dance
that you were talking to me
about this afternoon?
The one with the number?
(laughs)
That'd be the Texas Two-Step.
Can you show it to me?
Is the Pope Catholic?
Oh, come on, lucky lady.
It's your night.
Here we go.
Ready?
And it's one, two,
one, two, back step.
One, two, one, two,
Texas Two-Step.
We got it.
And you're turning.
I'm turning?
You're turning. Come on.
Turn this way.
That a girl.
Whoa!
(laughs)
I nearly lost you.
We got it. Got it, got it.
(knocking)
If you're here for sex, there's,
like, five guys ahead of you.
Okay, look, I'm sorry if I
jumped to conclusions tonight.
But you can't be paranoid
either about being divorced
or any of it.
It doesn't mean anything to me.
So you don't think I'm a whore?
No. No, of course not.
Good, 'cause I'm not.
Unless, of course,
you want me to be.
Is that my negligee?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I want that back.
Come on.
Before I change my mind.
All right,
but just to be clear...
Everything but.
(grunts)
(laughs)
Staring at that bunny thinking
of a baby, aren't you?
I'm sorry I abandoned you
in the desert.
I deserved it.
And it worked out
kind of well, too.
I found something that I thought
might interest you.
Oh, my God.
But I want
to say something first.
When I found out
it was your pregnancy test,
I totally freaked out
and I thought "This will
change everything,"
but then Ryan asked me
if I could imagine a time
when I'd ever not want
to be with you,
and I realized
that the answer is no.
I'm totally pregnant, aren't I?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
Is that going to, like, squirt
invisible ink or something?
No, but it will make you
engaged to me.
What?
Are you insane?
Possibly, but I'm certain
of this.
No, Cohen, we can't.
Sure, we can. We're both adults,
we don't share DNA.
You just have
to want to.
But...
I do.
Don't you think we should look
at the test first?
And have you wonder
for the rest of your life
if I proposed to you
because you're pregnant?
I'm doing this because
I love you,
I want to spend the rest
of my life with you.
You know, once you do this,
you can't take it back?
I know.
Summer Roberts,
will you marry me?
Yes, I'll marry you.
All right.
Okay, so should we look
at the test now?
Sure. Let's see
what's in store
for the future
Mr. and Mrs. Seth Cohen.
How many bars is that?
One. What's that mean?
One means I'm not pregnant.
I'm not pregnant.
Is it inappropriate
to celebrate?
No, please, please.
Saves us from having
to have a shotgun wedding.
Now we can just have
a normal one instead.
Yeah. You and me
and our normal wedding.
Should we hug again?
BOTH:
Okay.
(sighs)
Have a seat.
I'm not trading sex
for silence, Frank.
I may be a madam,
but I'm not a whore.
Good to know, but that's not
why I brought you here.
It's not?
Sit down.
So, why did you bring me here?
For information.
Information about what?
About the Cohen family.
Why?
Because I'm not who I say I am.
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
http://tlfsub.eastgame.net
And who are you?
I'm Ryan's father.