Previously on the O.C.
ll get used to it.'
You got married?
I'm just too afraid to tell
my mom now.
You're the one who walked away,
Neil.
You had the affair, remember?
Nothing happened with Gloria.
When I get back,
I want you out of this house.
It's my house.
Where's my dad?
Gone.
All I would do was hang
out with my best friend
and go tanning with
her and go shopping...
Let's be honest for a sec.
That's what this is all about.
I'm sorry I'm such a mess.
It's just... I miss my friend.
Thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
MAN:
I'm glad you came.
What brings you in?
Well, I've changed a lot
since I got to college.
New friends, new interests,
new clothes.
Well, that's
perfectly normal.
I know.
But... I think throwing myself
into all these new things
is just a way of avoiding
dealing with
what happened to my friend...
who, um... who died.
Well, grief often comes
in five stages.
Yeah, but I haven't
really been grieving.
Why is this happening?
Life is so unfair!
I'd do anything
to change things.
Please, just name it,
and I'll do it.
(sobbing):
Nothing matters anyway.
(loud sobs)
But this is so not fair!
I'm sorry, I have rage issues.
I think she would want me
to move on.
So that's what I'm going
to try to do.
I'm proud
of you, Summer.
You've made astounding
progress, and all in one week.
It's kind of a relief in a way.
Now I can go back to being me.
What do you mean
by that?
Well, this whole save the planet
thing, it was a crutch, right?
And nothing against handicapped
people, but crutches? Ew.
A lot of people do change
when they go to college.
Well, not me.
I love shopping, tanning
and celebrity gossip,
always have, always will.
But I think I have to.
If I ever want things to be good
with my boyfriend again.
Summer, just promise
you'll take it slow.
Totally.
RYAN:
Hey, man.
Hey, dude,
I know, three hour time
difference,
but, Ryan, she's going
to dump me.
It's okay, I'm awake.
Oh, good.
Ryan, she's going to dump me.
No one believes that, all right?
Summer loves you.
The old Summer loved me.
But new Summer is upon us,
and Providence is the place
that spawned her.
Summer is just dealing with what
we're all dealing with, okay?
She'll come around.
What if she doesn't?
This is my last shot.
Otherwise, the girl with the
violent temper and good hygiene
is nothing
but a childhood memory.
Careful, lady, my girlfriend's
going to be here any second.
Shut up, Cohen.
Hey, you just punched me.
My baby's back.
( piano and acoustic guitar
strumming gentle melody )
* California, here we come *
* Right back where
we started from *
* California...
California... *
The O.C.
-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:Allen
-=www.eastgame.net=-
You look good out there.
(chuckling):
Thanks.
I got to get you
on a surfboard.
Not a chance.
How about some breakfast?
I could use some intel
on Seth and Summer.
You know what, I
can't, but, uh, I think
they're doing all right.
You know? Doing the
long distance thing.
How about you?
How are you doing?
Good, good.
Better, once I get
my first day of work
under my belt.
Well, Pavo Guapo is lucky
to have you working there.
Me, too.
Now I got an excuse to come
by for your shrimp tacos.
Yeah, Kirsten warned me
about that.
You're limited
to two a week.
Oh! I knew I should have
divorced that dame.
Well, it's not forever.
You're still accepted to
Berkeley for next year.
I'm just glad you're getting
back to your old self.
You know?
Back home again.
New job.
I'm just trying to stay busy
and earn some extra money.
And hook me up with
some shrimp tacos.
Yeah, right.
I'll work on that.
I'm going to walk back.
I'm kind of sweaty.
Yeah, I wasn't offering
you a ride.
Hey, Ryan?
Hang in there.
Wow, that was a lot better
than what I was imagining
on the plane.
You were imagining it
on the plane?
Not like that.
When you called me here,
I was sure you were going
to break up with me.
Well, I know I'm not the one
that usually apologizes
in this relationship,
but I'm sorry
about everything.
I turned into a liberal zealot
just to distract myself
from my own grief.
I'm not even into
all this stuff.
So the old you is back?
In all of my artificially
tanned glory.
Thank God.
'Cause I was not sure
that the new you
and old me were
really working.
Yeah, the new me
kind of smelled weird.
Well, what would you have done
if I didn't go back to being me?
I had a plan
to coax the old Summer out.
The Valley, Season Three?
Awesome!
KIRSTEN:
I checked on Ryan.
Did he leave already?
Yeah.
He seemed to be doing okay.
I was hoping to hang with him
while Seth is away.
Poker, maybe shoot
a little pool,
but his new job is going
to make that tough.
Well, I could rack
a few balls with you.
You are so smart and sexy
and gorgeous.
But sometimes a man just needs
to hang with the guys.
Well, that I'm not.
(timer rings)
You know, Jimmy left, Caleb
died, then Jimmy left again.
Even Neil's gone.
Look, I wasn't a
pennant winner,
but at least I had
a bullpen, you know?
It's baseball talk.
I got it.
Why don't you give Jason Spitz
a call?
You're always saying
how funny he is.
Why don't you ask him
to do something?
Yeah, yeah...
I don't know.
I mean, it's a little weird
for a guy to ask another guy
to do something
right out of the blue like that.
Since when is Sandy Cohen
afraid of acting weird?
Well, Spitz is pretty funny.
He's allegedly
a scratch golfer.
He likes the Dodgers.
I could live with that.
It sounds perfect for you.
Yeah, but what am I going to do?
I'm going to give him
a call or what?
Ask him out?
Come on.
Why don't you use some
of that Sandy Cohen charm?
I'm sure he won't be
able to resist.
It's been a long time since
I been out there, honey.
What if Spitzy doesn't like me?
Are you calling him Spitzy now?
No, not yet.
Do you think he'll
go for it?
JULIE:
Well, that's very
generous of you.
Thank you, Neil.
Bye.
So how's Seattle?
Is that short, sassy lady
still bossing Dr. Roberts
around the hospital?
Neil is fine.
He's going to let us stay
in the house as long as we want.
Well, nice work, Mom.
I wish I could take
all the credit,
but it was actually Neil's idea.
He's really very sweet.
Oh, you miss him.
Well, don't worry.
We'll find you another old dude
to pay for all your stuff
and cheat on you.
Is that what I'm teaching you?
Mm, pretty much.
Well, no more.
Now that we have our housing
situation handled,
I am officially giving up men.
Good one.
That'll last a week, max.
I'll take that wager,
young lady.
And I'll make one with you.
I will not so much as bat
an eyelash at a man,
and you will stay
out of trouble.
You cannot live without a man.
not even for a week.
TAYLOR:
Morning, roomies.
Anyone want a protein scramble?
Nice to see you're making
yourself at home, Taylor.
Well, thanks for making me
feel at home, Jules.
Summer's room is
just adorable.
And I don't know how I ever
lived without a home gym.
Oh, this came for you today.
Who's Henry Michael?
Uh...
(French pronunciation:
Oh, Henri Michel?
That's just, um,
my French husband.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Excuse me.
You see? Man drama--
who needs it?
Hey, Ernesto's
looking pretty hot.
Nice six-pack.
Where?
Gotcha.
Taylor, hey.
Hi, Ryan.
Are you working at
El Pavo Guapo?
You know, that means
a handsome turkey?
That's why I took the job.
Hey, do you know when
Seth's going to be back?
I really need
to talk to him.
Sorry, gone for the weekend.
(sighs)
You know, that shirt really
brings out your eyes.
It's black.
What are you doing here, Taylor?
Just in the mood for Mexican.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe the Macho Nacho Burrito
wrap with extra guac.
And...
Oh, um, a favor.
(laughing):
No, no, no, sorry.
With Seth gone, you're the
only one I can turn to.
Well, I'm honored.
Okay, so, I'm trying
to get divorced,
and I just found out
that Henri Michel...
Oh, that's my French husband.
Um, he's coming to Newport
and I know he's going
to try and talk me out of it,
and I could really
use you there.
No.
I'm afraid to be alone with him.
I'm afraid
of his sensual powers.
Ryan, the man is
a sexual Jedi.
Whatever he asks you to do,
you just do it.
It doesn't matter
how depraved...
Okay, some people
are trying to eat here,
including me someday, so...
Ryan, please.
If I go alone, I'll be back
in France next week.
You don't know
how hard it was to leave.
Seth and Summer are gone,
my mom kicked me out,
and... I have no one else.
Look, just do me this one favor,
and I'll leave you alone.
Promise?
Knock, knock.
Hey, Summer, can you
fact-check this flier
on solar panels?
It's for the
rally tomorrow.
Che, I'd like
to talk.
Sure, man.
What's up?
I haven't been completely honest
with you about who I really am.
This is my shoe collection.
There's leather, suede,
and the occasional
calfskin boot.
Whoa, my friend.
These are my magazines.
I know which stars
pump gas just like us,
and who's on pump watch.
And this is Marissa.
She was my best friend,
um, but she died
in a car accident
on graduation night.
Summer, I'm sorry.
That's-That's really heavy.
Yeah, well, it's so heavy
that I couldn't deal, so...
I put all my energy
towards being an activist,
but that's not who I am.
These shoes
and these magazines-- that's me,
but I hope
we can still be friends.
All I can do is be me,
whoever that is.
It's, uh... it's Dylan.
The guy's a genius.
Look, Summer,
if you've found
your place in this world, I am
nothing but happy for you.
Hey.
I put some cream
in your coffee.
I figured you'd be
back on dairy.
Hey, uh, Che, this is
my boyfriend, Seth.
Seth, this is Che.
Summer, you have a twin flame.
I wish I knew you were
coming into town.
I would have made
you a bracelet.
SETH:
Oh, hey.
Uh, where I come from,
we just say hey.
Well, to borrow
your native tongue, hey.
Listen, forget what I
said about the rally.
We got plenty of warriors
for the fight.
You two, just... be.
Thanks, Che.
What's that?
It's garbage.
Hi, Jason. How you doing?
I just had a meeting
with Kaminsky.
Oh, the slowest talker
in the world.
It took forever.
Forever.
(laughing)
Good to see you, man.
Hey, uh...
you got any plans this weekend?
Sandy, I've been working
the past six Saturdays.
No, no, I didn't mean that.
I'm just saying that we could,
you know,
you and I, uh, we could do
something.
Do something?
Poker, pool,
you know, a little
small ball.
If you're free.
If not, no worries.
Can I get back to you on that?
Oh, sure, yeah.
Whatever.
WOMAN:
But I had to spend the night
with Derek.
He tore his ACL.
MAN:
Hey, it's not my fault
he'll never kickbox again.
WOMAN:
If I remember correctly,
he did kick your ass.
God, this is so disgusting.
MAN:
That was a sucker punch.
I don't know, I think you're
being too hard on April.
Derek's knee was...
it was really messed up.
No, I just... I don't
like this show anymore.
All they do is create fake
problems for fake people
just to distract viewers from
the real problems in the world.
Well, I don't think the network
would go for a sexy teen soap
set in the Damascus, but we
can turn it off if you want.
I just thought you liked it.
I'm just distracted.
I haven't been keeping up
on how much blow
Lindsay Lohan's doing.
And did you hear
about JT and Cameron?
No, what?
I don't know.
That is the point.
I'm going to go get
one of my magazines.
That sounds like
the old Summer.
I'm going to stay here
and, uh, keep watching.
You know, I have this thing
where if I start something,
I have to finish.
Is that li a disease
or a condition?
Don't really know, Cohen.
I'm reading about who got lipo.
----You know, you might
want to relax.
Distract me.
Tell me about this,
um, cage fighting.
It's something that I've
been meaning to get into.
Yeah? Yeah?
Ask me another favor,
I'll be happy to show you.
Oh, Ryan Atwood with
a side of sauce.
I like it.
You're going to have to do
better, though,
'cause right now all I ca
think of is him, my husband,
and his arms, his smell...
making love in the
barn in Burgundy.
Sounds like the perfect guy.
Why would you want to divorce?
Well, despite being
agnostic in most things,
I do believe in true love.
And this was not it.
Well, back to you and your life.
What is your favorite fruit?
Peaches.
Oh, he used to say my breasts
were like two, soft...
Is that him?
No, that's...
his lawyer.
Madam.
(speaking French)
(speaking French2)
(speaking French3)
Is everything okay?
No, not exactly.
(speaking French)
(speaking French2)
(speaking French3)
(speaking French4)
(speaking French5)
(speaking French6)
(speaking French7)
What did he say?
What's wrong?
(speaking French)
(speaking French2)
(speaking French3)
(speaking French4)
(speaking French5)
What's going on?
Oh, I just told him
you were a soccer fan.
Oh.
Yeah, I like soccer.
Sorry today was such a bust.
What are you talking about?
We totally cleaned out the mall.
Well, you threw your smoothie
at a lady on the street.
Hey, that fur did
not look faux.
Yeah, I just feel like your mind
is someplace else.
My mind is on this adorable
sweater right here.
m going to try it on'
with that bag we bought,
because how cute would
they look together?
Now, if you don't mind,
a little privacy.
Well, I enjoy watching you
take off your clothes,
I'm sure I'll enjoy watching
you put them on.
Hey, this is
a very intense process.
All right, actually
this is perfect.
I wanted to head over
to Thayer Street
and do a walking tour
of ethnic foods.
I can't be moving here if
the shwarma is not up to par.
Well, bring me a kabob.
CHE:
Hey, Summer.
Che, hey, I wanted to know
how the rally went.
We marched, we chanted,
and along the way,
we may have even opened up
a few eyes.
We'll see.
Oh, that sounds great.
Yeah, Summer,
what are you doing?
Trying on a sweater.
Hey, Seth and I are going
to watch a movie here later
if you want to come by.
No, I can't.
We're prepping for tomorrow
night's debate.
Debate?
They agreed to grant us
an audience
with the dean,
present our proposal.
Only thing not powered by the
fuel of the sun is our passion.
Uh, well, tell everyone I said
hi, and good luck.
Yeah, thanks.
So do you like it?
Huh? Like what?
The new sweater.
No.
KIRSTEN:
So you're really giving
up on men?
Men are to me, what
Chardonnay is to you.
One sip and I'm upside down
on a chandelier.
Not that you've
ever done that.
What's your point, Julie?
I'm just trying to set
a good example for Kaitlin,
develop my own interests,
maybe my career,
that is, if you'd still
have me as a partner.
As I told you,
New Matchis there for you
whenever you want.
Thanks, Keeks. I was hoping
you'd say that.
Okay, so, I have so many
new ideas about expanding.
I went online.
I checked out some office...
Oh, there's Taryn.
Wow, she looks amazing.
Did she have
some work done?
She's had something.
Kirsten, great to see you.
Julie, I'm so sorry
about Neil.
I hope you plan to sue.
You know, just because
you aren't legal
doesn't mean you're not
entitled to some sort of...
(phone ringing)
Oh, it's Sandy.
Excuse me.
Hi, honey.
Hey, guess what?
I'm not good at guessing.
I'm going out.
I'm jealous, with who?
Spitz! Spitzy to me.
He called?
He called.
How about that?
Maybe a little golf, maybe a
drink after, watch the game.
Golfing, game watching,
suddenly not so jealous.
Thanks, but I don't think
I'll be needing
a dating service anymore.
Really?
I didn't know you
were seeing anyone.
Oh, not someone...
someones.
Young ones.
Men our age are
so complicated.
Young guys just like
to have fun.
And they are so
grateful for a woman
who knows what she's doing.
Oh, so grateful, and limber.
Hey, a group of us are
going out tomorrow night.
You should come.
Uh, I'm trying to be
a role model.
Oh, mm-hmm.
I'll call you.
Did Taryn run off already?
Mm-hmm.
What's she doing?
JULIE:
Him.
Hey, Kaitlin!
We got a guy who can
hook us up with fake I.D.'s.
It's awesome.
Yeah.
I think I'll pass.
You've wanted a fake I.D.
since you were six.
Yeah, come on.
Yeah, and the guy's leaving town
next week.
Well, where is he going?
He's going to prison.
Yeah, for fraud.
Because he's awesome.
Look, you guys, I made
a bet with my mom
that I'd stay
out of trouble.
And this definitely
sounds like trouble.
Dude, not if we don't
get caught.
Dude, seriously.
Yeah, dude, seriously.
Well, with a foolproof plan
like that, how can I say no?
Garcon?
Ah! Taylor.
It's been a few hours
since your last Macho Nacho.
You must be starving.
I was thinking of the mol\.
And, um, one more
tiny little favor.
Does it involve me standing
around while you speak French?
'Cause I've already done that.
No, no, no.
I actually just need
your signature.
You see, before I can get
divorced,
I have to have someone
attest to my character.
That's in French.
It's just the usual
boilerplate.
You know, never
been to prison--
well, me, not you.
(giggling)
Never been married before,
no contact with livestock,
blah, blah, blah.
So I think I have a pen.
Uh, you know, actually,
can I sign that after work?
Just leave it here.
Sure. Yes, okay.
Thank you very much.
So you don't speak
French at all?
No, why?
Well, it must have been really
boring for you today.
Sorry.
Hey, Seth, man, what's up?
Hey, I got some extra
baba ghanoush.
Oh, baba ghanoush.
No thanks, man.
I'm all right.
Where's Summer?
I gave her a little time-out.
It's not easy
having house guests.
What?! I thought you guys
were having this great day,
purchasing luxury goods,
and eating things with faces.
Honestly, it could have gone
a little better.
I mean, you know, I support her,
whatever she's into,
but I really
need this to work 'cause...
SUMMER:
The people have spoken!
We are of one voice,
one mind
and one heart!
Yeah!
(applause)
I will not sleep,
I will not eat,
I will not rest until
this hypocrisy ends.
Solar panels on all of our
dormitories, or we revolt!
Who's with Summer?
Yeah!
STUDENTS:
(applause, cheering)
Yeah!
Hey, man, how's your French?
Old Summer's been replaced by
the real Summer,
and she looks suspiciously like
the new Summer.
So she's still in her
"Go Green" phase?
I don't think it's a phase, man.
I think this is her life
now, and it's obvious
I don't fit in it.
Uh, sorry, gotta go.
Hey, wait, I've got to talk to
you about Taylor... what...?
Didn't mean to eavesdrop.
It's okay.
Well, I knew
you were lying last night
when you said nothing was wrong.
Nothing is wrong; you're doing
what people do at college--
discovering who you really are.
Believe me,
I am as surprised as you are.
But I'm still going to shave
my legs and wash my hair,
and be the best
girlfriend that I can.
Well, you know, who can ask
for more than that?
Think of all the new subjects
we'll have to talk about.
I did explain the concept of
recycling to you in tenth grade.
See, there's lots of places
where we could use
your help, Cohen.
(knocking at door)
(playing simple melody)
Please come in. Enter.
Hey... Oh!
You're really nude.
Why don't I...
let me come back.
No! Wait right there.
I have a gift for you.
My song.
* Polar bears are dying *
* ...two, three, four *
* Good-bye. *
Wow.
That's really, uh...
Anyways, listen,
I kind of need your help.
Yeah, bro, one second.
Uh, I'm actually really
honored you would ask me.
Oh, hey, that's cool,
we can shake.
We can shake. We can shake.
And we're touching.
(cell phone ringing)
SANDY:
Oh!
Fore!
Yeah, hi.
Sorry!
Rob, what are you doing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bye.
I'm sorry about that.
My, my kid's got a rash.
I got to go to the
pharmacy after this.
Oh, sorry.
Take another one.
It was my fault.
No, no, no!
You're up.
I'll play it from
the parking lot.
I think I hit your car.
It'd be an improvement.
Sandy...
uh... (anxious laugh)
You know,
my kid doesn't have a rash.
My wife's just calling,
making sure
I'm having a good time,
you know, because I don't have
that many guy friends anymore.
Who does?
Who's got the time?
I know, it's work, family,
then more work, you know?
When did it get so hard?
Well, when we were kids,
all you had to do was ask,
hey, want to play
some ball?
And we didn't have
any cell phones.
I turned mine off.
I'm really sorry about that.
(cell phone ringing)
Oh!
I'm so sorry, man!
I'm so sorry.
It's the office.
I'm turning it off.
JASON:
I think I hit your car anyway.
I love this space
and I love the windows.
Plus it's by the beach,
so there'd be lots
of foot traffic and eye candy,
not that I'm looking.
So I'll make an appointment
for us for Monday?
Are you doing
anything tonight?
No, Kaitlin's with the twins,
working on a science project,
so I have the night
all to myself.
Well, Sandy's out with a friend.
Do you want to do something?
I don't know--
takeout and a movie?
Two women spending Saturday
night at home together.
I love it.
How very Whatever Happened To
Baby Jane.
(cell phone ringing)
Go ahead, you can take it.
No, that's okay.
Just a sec.
Hello?
It's Taryn.
You joining us tonight?
Uh, actually,
I'm here with Kirsten
and we were thinking about
maybe...
Order in and watch a movie?
Oh, honey, even with the wonders
of elective surgery,
you will only be this hot
for so long.
Have fun while you can.
Julie, you still there?
I'll call you back.
Oh, I was just going
to get some takeout menus.
Do you know what
you'd like to eat?
Kirsten, I feel like I'm coming
down with something.
I'm not feeling so hot.
Do you mind if I take a rain
check on our girl's night in?
Julie, did you just put on
lipstick?
What? No, uh...
I'm just a little flushed.
I'll call you.
KAITLIN:
Okay, I think that's the guy.
Kaitlin,
what if he's packing heat?
Okay, you guys just stay here.
Money.
Got what we talked about?
In here.
Great, so it's covered in lice
and grease.
Put your money in the hat
and try and be cool about it.
You think it's my first buy?
It's been a pleasure.
I'm available,
by the way.
That's heinous.
I don't know
about this, Taryn.
It might be too soon.
Julie, I know how you feel.
But there's one
man who can always
get me out on
the dance floor.
His name is Jose.
Jose Cuervo.
Have you met my friend
Julie Cooper-- urban cougar.
TAYLOR:
Ryan! There you are.
You know,
I think there might be
something wrong with your phone.
I called you
three times today.
Six, actually.
Oh, well, um,
did you get a chance
to look at that silly
little document?
Yeah! I did.
And I had a question for you.
Um, what does that mean?
Oh, that's just lawyer speak.
You know, just party
of the first part,
party of the second part.
So it doesn't say
we had sex, like, 30 times?
Took me like five hours
to translate that.
Sorry.
Yeah.
It's just that without
the consent of my husband,
the only way I can get a divorce
is if one of us was unfaithful.
I just didn't think you'd
sign if you knew the truth.
Yeah, well, I've got a lot of
half-eaten enchiladas to clear.
Ryan, I have to meet that lawyer
at the yacht club tonight,
and if I don't have this signed,
I'm going to have
no choice but to go with him
to France and try to work it out
with Henri Michel, face-to-face.
Which means you won't
be able to keep coming here,
which is a real shame.
Well, did you at least
read this part
where I said what
a great lover you are?
Look, Taylor... this job,
this is about all
I can handle right now.
You know?
I shouldn't have
dragged you in to this.
Yeah, that's what
I've been trying to say.
It's just that I...
...don't have anyone else.
It's kind of why I married a
Frenchman in the first place.
I mean, my mom hates me.
I don't really
know my dad,
and last year was the first year
I ever had friends.
All of a sudden, I'm by myself
in a foreign country,
and I meet this guy
who says he loves me.
He wants to take care of me
and... and...
One too many bottles
of Chateau Margot
and a view from
the Eiffel Tower, and why not?
That's how Tom wooed Katie.
Why not me?
Well, look, I'm sorry you're
going through all this.
I'm just not the guy to help.
Sorry.
Here they come.
There you are.
CHE:
Sorry we're late.
Earlier today, a caterpillar
entered my room.
I'm happy to say
a butterfly emged.
SETH:
Did you know that the
amount of solar energy
that touches the Earth's
surface in 40 minutes
is greater than all the energy
required by the entire
human population in a year?
Yes, I did know that.
It's a thing of beauty,
isn't it?
CHE:
Come on, friends.
Oh, the board only allows
students in the town meeting.
Do you go here?
Uh, no...
But I made this.
Can you just make an exception?
It's for the good of the Earth.
No, I'm afraid not.
Well, it's cool, you go ahead.
But it's your last night here.
You can't spend it alone.
Summer, everybody in there is
counting on you, okay?
I can amuse myself
for a few hours.
You're the best boyfriend ever.
Go change the world.
mp tacos.
Oh, yeah?
Looks like you're
going to get a chance
to meet one of my kids.
Hey, Ryan.
Hey.
I'd like you to meet
Jason Spitz from work.
What's up?
How you doing?
We're about to go in
and watch the game,
get a bite to eat.
Can you join us?
Uh, you know, actually,
I'm kind of beat.
But you guys go ahead.
Nice to meet you.
Good to meet you.
I'll be inside.
Yeah.
Hey, hey.
Is everything okay?
'Cause I'm guessing
not really.
I didn't get fired,
I didn't punch any of
my drunken customers,
I'd say I'm great.
One day at a time, one foot
in front of the other.
Eventually, it'll get easier.
Yeah, why, because I'll start
to forget about her?
No, no. You're never going
to forget about her.
But... life goes on.
Not the same life.
No.
But you're going to have
to make this life work.
Yeah, but I do, you know?
I got a job.
I go there, I go home.
I talk to as few people
as possible.
If it were only that easy.
Unfortunately for you,
getting mixed up in
other people's lives,
helping them out of jams,
it seems to
be what you do,
like it or not.
I'd hate to see you
turn your back on that.
It'd be like rning
your back on yourself.
Come on, join us, would you?
Get a little food, watch
the second half of the game.
Actually, there's something
I've got to do.
Uh, you guys have fun.
All right.
MAN:
Cover's 20 bucks,
just pay inside.
Let me do the
talking, okay?
All right.
You got an I.D.?
It's cool.
Cover's 20 bucks,
just pay inside.
Cool.
Sorry, boys,
not tonight.
What? Why?
I'm sorry, is there a problem
with their I.D.'s?
Because they're with me.
There's a problem
with them.
See, I have the right to refuse
entry to anybody.
And tonight that includes
dorks and virgins.
So just beat it, guys.
Fine.
Whatever, man.
That blows.
Come on,
Kaitlin, let's go.
Yeah, you can't go in
there without us.
Who's going to protect you?
See you guys later.
Need you to move aside, guys.
----SANDY & JAN:
Go! Go, go, go!
Run!
groaning)
Man.
This is great.
Watching the game,
having a beer.
For five minutes,
the sky isn't falling.
A chance to be stupid again.
Here's to being stupid
for five minutes.
(phone ringing)
Hey, honey.
How's it going?
Great. Spitz just told
me a story
about how his kid's walked in
on him and his wife
when they were playing
Strip Scrabble.
Strip Scrabble?
I'm glad things are going well.
Yeah.
So how are you doing?
You having fun with Julie?
Well, Julie had
a mysterious illness.
So I'm home alone.
I just finished watching a movie
and I thought I'd check in.
I love you.
Bye.
(speaking French)
I don't love him.
I never did.
I was just scared.
(speaking French)
Sorry I'm late.
You have that paper
for me to sign?
It won't be necessary.
I may be a lawyer,
but I'm also a Frenchman.
I know love when
I see it.
I will inform Henri Michel.
Ryan, I...
Don't worry about it.
Yeah.
CHE:
We stand before you,
an organized student body.
We have a question.
Where does this burden fall?
Hey, sleepyhead.
Hey.
Did we win?
Not yet, but Che suggested
a filibuster,
so it could go on all night.
I think we got 'em.
That's great.
Yeah.
When I showed them my cost
benefit analysis chart,
jaws actually dropped.
Of course they did.
There's all these
old people in there
that are actually
listening to me. Me!
It felt better than
when I got 70% off
that Marc Jacobs dress
with the broken zipper.
I wish I could have been there.
Instead you slept in the hallway
on your last night in
Providence.
I'm totally fine.
Listen, go back in there and
knock it out of the park.
Was that a sports reference?
Maybe.
See, I know people can change.
(knocking)
Yeah?
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you asleep?
No.
Oh, well, then my timing is
impeccable, as always.
So I wanted to
thank you.
So I made you peach torte.
Yeah, after I got married,
Henri Michel
made me take a cooking class.
Um, I failed everything
except tortes.
Tortes I rocked.
Uh, well, that's great,
but, um...
You're not a dessert guy.
Okay.
Well, um, I could make
you lunch, or... dinner.
I have to pay you back somehow.
I love dessert.
Okay.
Fork.
Thanks.
Yeah? All right.
Wow.
Who would have thought,
six months ago,
you and I, sitting here,
sharing a torte.
Not me.
You know, at graduation,
in my commencement address,
I said there's no one older than
a high school senior,
no one younger than
a college freshman.
It was one of the few parts
that wasn't in Latin.
And uh, it's true.
Because I feel like everything
I thought I knew,
everything that I expected,
is just kind of gone
out the window.
Yeah, life is definitely
unpredictable.
Yeah.
But I guess I'm realizing that
that could be a good thing.
You know?
Because it's exciting not
knowing what's going to happen.
Taylor, this is a great torte.
Really good.
Can I have the next flight
to John Wayne Airport, please?
8:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Come on.
(chuckles)
SETH:
Hey, Summer.
I know flying home early
is your move, but I stole it.
I just wanted to give you room
to keep doing
what you're doing, because
I think it's pretty amazing.
So if you don't hear from me
for a while, it's not because
I don't love you,
it's because I do.
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
http://tlfsub.eastgame.net