previously on ghost whisperer...
we're getting ready.
For what?
- For what's coming.
It's time for you
to know who you are.
And to know who your brother is.
Do you really think it was
your father in the light?
If he's dead, I have to
find out what happened.
You are so over your head.
And I really wouldn't come back.
Ever.
All right, I get it.
I understand.
I'll make dinner.
I'll do the dishes, but, uh,
you just relax. Take it easy.
Look, I offered to help.
Did I miss that?
Look at me. Doing my part,
going to get the door.
Don't hurt your hand on
the doorknob. Take it easy.
Mel, who is it?
What the hell are you doing here?
Wow.
You're angry.
I was there when you got hurt.
You think it's my fault.
You were there, smiling,
and she wasn't just hurt.
For the longest minute
of my life, she was dead.
Yeah.
You know, a part of me didn't
mind seeing you like that.
For a very long time I blamed my entire
family for leaving me locked up in that...
where I grew up.
- Too bad.
Go.
- I'm trying to find dad.
Mine or yours?
Ours.
My father's dead.
Why should that keep either
of us from looking for him?
We both see ghosts.
- Are you done?
Look, I...
I figured you'd still be in denial.
Who would want to admit that their old
man had an extra family on the side?
But are you gonna tell
me you haven't seen him?
He hasn't come to visit
you in your dreams?
Yeah, I thought so.
He's been haunting my dreams, too.
How do you think I found
out you were my sister?
Jim asked you to leave, nicely.
What are you hiding from?
We're both trying to find him.
We both have unfinished
business with him.
We... we should be
working together...
that's enough! Go!
Look.
My mother gave this
to me when I was a kid.
It belonged to my dad.
It'll mean a lot more to
you than it ever did to me.
Patient Personal Property
For you, they were family.
For me, they were just more
people he had to hide me from.
Where was your mother for all this?
She was always close by.
In the next ward
the mental hospital
This is my dad's parents
right after they got married.
And, uh,
my dad told me that
he got these cufflinks
from his aunt and uncle right
after he graduated college.
Honey, you know, gabriel could have
gotten this stuff from anywhere.
I don't trust him either.
But
I just can't shake the feeling that he might
be telling the truth about being my brother.
Why do you think that?
Too many coincidences.
Gabriel showed up right after
that dad told me I had brother.
And let's face it... my dad was
in and out of the house
for a lot of years,
so he could have had kids,
and I wouldn't have known.
Gabriel didn't get his gift from
dad, but he got other things.
Well, he certainly got your dad's
gift for tying you up in knots.
I left the lights on downstairs.
I'm going to turn 'em off.
You need anything? Tea? Water?
No.
- Ok.
So who do you think
the picture's of?
It's gotta be some
relative of my dad'S.
I mean, all these photos are his.
Well, so gabriel says.
Don't worry. I'm not taking
anything gabriel says on faith.
I just faxed a request
for his medical records to
that mental institution
he said he grew up in.
"Trust, but verify. "
Yeah, sounds good. Only my
motto is slightly different.
Trust, but caffeinate.
What will it be?
The usual. Twice the foam, please.
Ok.
Hello?
Who's there?
- Shh!
Who are you?
Why are you here?
- Please. Quiet.
They're everywhere.
Who?
They told me I was crazy.
They took my baby.
Who are you?
What's your name?
Wait a minute.
Gabriel gave this to me, and he...
he said that his mother was
in the same hospital he was.
You're gabriel's
mother, aren't you?
Help me!
First it was ray billings, then there was
the stalker guy I saw get sucked under,
and now this one, gabriel's mother.
Well, if you're asking me to tell you that
there are no dark spirits under grandview,
get comfortable,'cause
it's gonna be a long wait.
You've taken all of the smug
certainty out of being a skeptic.
I'm waiting for you to
tell me how they work.
How can dark spirits trap other
ghosts, and why are they underground?
Well?
Oh, sorry, I thought
we were waiting.
Look, the basic gist of it is that the
dark spirits feed on the darker emotions...
hate, anger, fear, jealousy,
greed, all of that stuff.
And it's very powerful emotion,
so it's hard to break their grip.
Yeah, but not impossible?
No, it's not impossible.
The things that better them are the
same things that better them in life.
All the good stuff...
love, joy, happiness,
forgiveness, melted cheese,
- way adjustable bucket seats, that dress...
great. Thanks.
- Where are you going?
You're not actually going to go through with this, are you?
- Why wouldn't I?
You're going to take
a tip from this...
this gabriel guy to go find
your untrustworthy deadbeat dad?
Your untrustworthy
deadbeat dead dad?
I'm simply following some leads.
Leads? How? Think about this.
I will. Don't worry.
I'm worried.
Hey.
I got your call. What's up?
I was trying to summon
gabriel's mother...
if that's who she is...
and while I was
waiting, I got this.
It's the treatment records from
gabriel's institution, correct?
Yeah, I asked the doctor for
copies,'cause I wanted to know the truth.
Melinda, look, I'm sorry.
I know that I can't imagine
what this feels like for you,
but there's nothing in here
you didn't already know,
outside of the fact that
he attacked other patients.
He told them he could see ghosts.
They thought he was crazy.
It's why they put him in there.
That could have been me.
No, you have a gift.
He is violent. He is mentally ill.
He's my brother. We have
a lot of the same genes.
You don't know that yet.
Actually, I do.
That's why dr. Lawrence wanted
to see my birth certificate.
He needed proof that I
was family, and he got it.
Gabriel's father was tom gordon.
He's my half brother.
And now you want to save him?
After what he did?
But this is what I do.
I help people fix
their worst mistakes.
Yes, hello.
Um, you have a guest staying with
you under the name gabriel gordon?
Well, could you check?
Sure. Thanks.
Hello?
Mr. Gordon is not answering.
would you like to leave a message?
Yeah!
No.
You know what? I'll... I'll
call back later, thanks.
So this wasn't a haunting,
it was more like a vision?
Uh, yeah.
Sometimes I get them, and
ghosts try to show me things,
and I don't always know why.
But it felt like it was real?
Oh, very.
My heart was still
pounding an hour later.
And did you get a chance
to talk to gabriel about it?
No.
The thing is this... this vision,
it was like... I think it's something
that happened to the ghost...
gabriel's mother...
and I, you know,
at first, I thought it maybe
was the moment that they
took her to the hospital,
but that wasn't right.
I mean, these guys
were rough, you know?
They had a big axe
with blood on it.
Right. Bloody axe doesn't
really say hospital, does it?
I have to find out more
before I talk to gabriel,
which is my roundabout way of
asking you to please watch the store.
Only if you promise to
tell me everything you find.
Deal.
- Ok.
I'm not hurt.
Uh, just so you know.
I'm bigger than that.
Ok. Good.
I'm a talker. I know I talk a lot.
I can't expect people to listen
to every single word I say,
and that's why it didn't surprise
me you didn't listen to me.
What do you mean? I listened.
- You listened?
Then why are we down here with all of
these creepy, spooky ghosts where they live?
Because you had some advice
from your evil twin half brother.
Look, it was your idea.
You said that we needed to
check all the town death records
and that any place where there
was a dark spirit infestation
would probably have
a lot of deaths.
No, no, no. Not...
not a lot of deaths.
A lot and lot of deaths.
And grisly, awful deaths.
And simultaneous.
Like they all happened
at the same time.
Ok, so shouldn't we check
the records like you said?
All right, I don't like
being quoted back to myself.
Especially when I'm right.
While we are looking, why
don't you go that direction,
and I will go this way?
Ok.
Let's see.
I've been looking for
you. Where have you been?
Quiet.
They can hear you.
Please tell me what happened.
I can help you cross
over into the light.
Oh, no, no.
I... I can't do that.
I can'T.
I... I don't deserve to be free.
Why?
I lost my baby.
It's all my fault.
What do you mean? What happened?
They all died because of me.
Who?
Give up.
You won't find what
you're looking for.
And what am I looking for?
It doesn't matter.
Whatever it is, you won't find it.
That's my job.
I make sure what's
buried stays that way.
Oh, my god.
What are these?
These are teeth.
"Clay 48"?What does that mean?
I don't know, but whoever these belonged
to is going to have a hard time eating beef.
She said they all
died because of me.
Who?
- The ghost.
Gabriel's mother.
You think she... what?
She killed all these people?
I don't know.
But what does she have to
do with all these deaths?
You gave those things to find dad.
Is it just about dad, or are you
looking for someone else, too?
Like who?
I spoke to your mother's ghost.
She said,"they all
died because of me. "
What does it mean?
I don't know who you're talking
to, but that wasn't my mother.
How do you know?
To start with, my
mother's no ghost.
She's alive. And insane.
And living in some halfway
house in crested butte.
Well, then, who is the
ghost that you led me to?
I mean, I have followed all
the leads in the envelope,
and that's the only ghost
I can make contact with.
If there were any ghosts attached to dad's
stuff, it was something you did, not me.
So who's this ghost you met?
You know, I'll call you.
If I find anything.
Of course his mother
wasn't the ghost.
I could have told you that.
Then why didn't you?
Ok, technically, I could not have told
you that until about a minute or two ago,
but I would have told you.
See, I have a friend that
teaches forensic pathology,
and he's been looking
at these teeth.
Did you know that these
teeth are over 150 years old?
So then how are those teeth
connected to this ghost?
He's going to run some
tests on the smoke stains
and caraway seeds that are
stuck inside these teeth.
But I'm pretty sure the message
is going to remain clear.
Never underestimate
the power of floss.
So then the mystery is, is who is this
ghost, and why did she lead us to that box?
The real mystery is, who is this ghost,
and why did she lead us to that box?
That is what I just said.
Well, what did you mean?
I mean, are you suggesting that possibly
all these deaths happened somewhere else,
and that's why there's no recorded
history of them here in grandview?
No, because ghosts usually have some
sort of attachment to where they died,
which is weird, because these
ghosts seem to be stuck underground.
Well, then, the real mystery
is, is, uh, is what you said.
What is it about this thing?
You remember it, don't you?
People did terrible
things to each other.
Do you remember your name?
He called me tessa once.
Tell me how all those people died.
You made it sound
like it was your fault.
I don't know anymore.
So many ghosts tell the story.
They each tell it differently.
What's your version?
I tried to warn them.
But they wouldn't listen.
What did you try
to warn them about?
I saw a ghost.
He was from weston.
I gave them the
warning that he gave me.
I don't understand.
Were you dead?
I was as alive as you.
So you saw ghosts
when you were alive?
Why are you so surprised?
You see me.
I guess maybe there were more of us
doing what we do than I ever knew.
Until they find out.
Then they kill us.
Is that why they killed you?
That doesn't matter anymore.
All that matters is...
Tessa, wait. Where are you going?
I... I can help you.
Find out what happened
to my baby, please.
That's all that matters.
Tessa, wait!
I thought you said you
were going to the archives?
I am.
This isn't the archives.
There's no dust, no cobwebs.
Tessa said that she was
warned by a ghost from weston.
These are the weston archives.
They're all online.
You're kidding me. Let me see.
And here come my search results.
Wait.
Listen to this.
"Rumors from grandview said residents
there became sick "with a strange fever.
"The unknown disease killed dozens,"but
not before making them insane.
The fever caused many to murder
their friends and family. "
"The worst rumor
told of a preacher "
who slaughtered his flock after
locking them up in his church. "
What church is that?
St. Agnes church on clay street.
Well, that's why the
box said "clay 48."
It was the name of the
street and the year.
Yeah, but the weird thing is I've never
heard of a st. Agnes church or a clay street.
That's what's weird to you?
The slaughtered flock... nothing?
All right, listen to this.
"Weston doctor eustace
green wrote in his diary
"that he treated patients with
symptoms "like those in grandview.
"He mentions a theory that it
might be linked "to tainted bread.
"No traces of the bread
survived to confirm his theory. "
Ergot poisoning. Of
course. That's it.
What's it?
- Ergot!
It's a toxin that's found in a
fungus that grows on grain, even rye.
The symptoms are everything
they're explaining here.
Seizures, vomiting.
The psychosis. Even gangrene.
That explains why
they lost their minds.
I think I found the
ghost who warned tessa.
"Soon after writing this diary
entry,"dr. Greene died of exposure. "
He was traveling through a
blizzard towards grandview,
presumably to treat
victims there. "
Tessa said that she was
warned by a ghost from weston.
Hey.
my girl.
You look tired.
Delia doesn't come
for another hour.
You could take a nap
before dinner if you want.
If I lay down, I will
sleep until next thursday.
Any luck confirming some of that
stuff you found in the weston archive?
I spent all afternoon
there, and I finally found
one box of grandview papers from,
like,1848, and not one of them mentioned
the deaths from the weston records.
It's bizarre.
Did gabriel ever call me back?
No. Did you expect him to?
Then I asked delia to check
her real estate sources.
You know, hoping that maybe clay
street had been renamed or something.
Came up dry there, too.
You know, it's like the
whole thing was so shameful,
the town just decided to bury it.
Bury it?
What do you mean?
Well, you know.
Hide it.
Sweep it under the rug.
Put something heavy on it.
I wonder if that's why they're
all trapped underground?
It's maybe the why,
the who, or what?
No. Wait a minute.
Hey, delia's going
to be here at 8:00.
No, no, no. Just keep cooking.
Seriously. I'll be
back in. Like, an hour.
I just... I want to find
out what else they buried.
Hello?
Tessa, are you here?
St. Agnes church.
Clay street, it's underneath.
St. Agnes church, clay street.
Sorry, jim.
Oh, my god.
Clay street.
You startled me.
He surprised us, too.
"Us"?
You lived here once, didn't you?
And died here.
Is that why you're
all trapped underneath?
Because you died here,
and then you were buried?
They didn't like the
story our bones told,
so they pretended we never lived.
Built your town
right on top of ours.
If you hear anything from her,
please, give us a call, ok?
Mel!
Melinda!
Oh.
It's you.
Is it that painful to see me?
No, no, no. I'm sorry.
We just thought you
might be melinda.
Where is melinda actually?
Because some test results came
back, confirming a theory, we...
where is melinda?
Look, I don't know.
It could be nothing.
But she said she'd
be back in an hour.
When?
3 hours ago.
This isn't like her. Ok?
She doesn't disappear.
She doesn't leave
her cell phone off.
What was the last thing she said?
We were talking about the ghost.
Tessa.
- Right.
And I said, you
know, something about
how I felt like the whole town had
buried what had happened to her.
She pops up and says,"I'm going to
go find out what else they buried. "
The archives.
Tessa, I know that you
don't remember it well,
but I need you to try.
I need you to make peace with
what happened and then move on.
It won't work.
There's too many others who
won't ever make peace with me.
Ok, so talk to them.
We'll make them understand.
No.
I can'T.
Why not?
They're not out here.
They're in there.
Tessa, please tell me what
happened in that church.
Half the town was already sick.
Brother davis, he thought he was
locking them in to protect them
from the sickness and
everyone out here who had it.
But all they brought in to
feed them was water and bread.
Later, after they'd
all lost their minds,
brother davis decided he
needed to destroy the evil.
So he started the fire.
With everyone locked inside.
He killed them all... even himself.
So what happened to
you and your baby?
When I told them the fever
was coming before it came,
and that I'd heard the
news from a ghost...
what else could they think?
I must be a witch.
Yeah, but you knew it wasn't true.
All I know is they locked
me up in that church,
dragged me away from my baby,
said I could spend the rest of my
days with the ones I had killed.
No!
It wasn't your fault.
There was no magic that did this.
It was just a disease.
No, they... they've told me
again and again and again...
well, they were wrong.
You risked your life to give them
that warning, and you were right.
Weren't you?
I wish someone could tell them.
I will.
And you'll tell them with me.
No!
Wait, please! We can't!
You don't know what lives in there.
No, please! We can't go in!
We have to.
It's the only way
you can cross over.
Hey, you guys. Look at this.
That's melinda's handwriting.
What does this mean?"S. A"?
St. Agnes church. That's
what she was looking for.
It's a map. That's
town square, right?
Yeah.
Hey...
this is recent.
Who would move these bookcases?
Come on, give me a hand.
One of them must have
gone through here.
Damn it.
There's no way we
can go through there.
Oh, my god. Jim!
Wait, if melinda went in there...
No, she's alive.
I'd know.
What is youe emergency?
Yeah, I need driscoll
country rescue and recovery.
Yes. I'll hold.
Guys, it's melinda
we're talking about.
If she wasn't alive, she'd
find a way to tell us.
It won't work.
What's done can't be undone.
Why'd she do this to us?
They're both witches.
Witches did this to us.
Witches...
look, this is a map.
I think it shows the
way she was headed.
Sir, you want to find
your wife. I understand.
But I've been in the
tunnels a hundred times.
There are no branches
where this says there are.
This is going to sound a little
strange, ok, but these lines...
I don't think these are
tunnels that you've been in.
They're something else, ok?
They're what's leftover
of old roads, alleyways...
they're what's leftover of
another town, underground.
Another town underground?
Actually, this town.
The way it was.
About 200 years ago.
Actually, there's lots of cities that
have been built on top of entire towns.
I mean, edinburgh, scotland...
they covered the royal mile.
Look, I'm sorry, but I've got to
go where I know the tunnels are.
Right.
Excuse me.
Wait a minute.
Come with me.
I know you're all angry.
I can feel that.
And I understand.
You died too soon and too horribly.
Your hearts tell you there
has to be a reason for that.
And there is.
But it's not what you think.
No evil killed you. Or witches.
It was just a disease.
What disease?
Think back.
The food brought into the
church... it was bread, wasn't it?
Bread that was made of rye.
How do you know that?
They found some.
After you died. And
that bread carried...
a disease.
And made people so ill
that they lost their minds.
Is it true?
A doctor was coming to warn
you, but he didn't make it.
So he asked tessa to
give you the message.
It couldn't be true. Could it?
That's the only reason
that she knew before you.
Could be true.
It could be true.
Lies.
Lies from another witch.
It's him.
Melinda, go!
What about the other
ghosts? They need help, too.
You're not powerful enough. Run!
Powerful...
finally.
my fault, it was my fault.
Help!
Don't waste your breath.
You'll need it.
You're not the first to come
down here and look for us.
Others have come and
been trapped, too.
I... I've watched them panic.
Help comes, but they don't
last until it gets there.
Is help coming for me?
Yes.
But it's too far away.
Ok.
Tessa, I have to cross
you over into the light.
I told you...
I can'T.
What's done can't be undone.
Yeah, but you didn't do anything.
Yes, I did.
I abandoned my baby.
If I hadn't carried that message,
I never would have lost her.
It's all my fault
she was left alone.
You can't keep blaming yourself.
You were just trying to save lives.
That's a subject you
know something about.
Don't you, melinda?
Dad?
Ok, if this is city hall,
and that's the old theater,
then the closest building to the
alley that fed into church street is...
right there.
What a coincidence.
I don't know about you, but I'm beginning
to think that there's no such thing.
How did find me?
Where have you been? Did you die?
I don't understand.
Melinda, there's no time.
I can't be here for
long, and neither can you.
I can't believe I let
myself walk into this.
I... everybody told
me to stay away.
You didn't walk into anything.
You were led here.
By who? Gabriel?
By me.
Why?
Did you want me to die?
You needed to know the truth.
Why couldn't you just tell me?
Would you have believed
any of this if I'd told you?
Would you believe anything I sd?
Ai I don't know if believe you now.
I mean, what's going on?
What is it that I need to know?
Everything.
The truth about
grandview, why you're here,
the dangers you're facing,
but also, the power that you
have and what you can do with it.
Open your locket.
My baby.
I don't know what
your mother told you,
but the real reason
why we split was... you.
It was nothing you did.
It's what you could do.
I wanted you to revel in
your gift, not hide it.
I don't understand.
The locket is not from my side of
the family. It's from your mother'S.
She wanted to bury
that part of your past,
so she packed up the
photos and the keepsakes,
and she threw them away.
I found them and saved them.
How do I know that
any of this is true?
Tell melinda your baby's name.
Julia lee lucas.
Wait. I know that name.
That's my great-great
grandmother's name.
Your daughter...
is my grandmother's grandmother?
You're descended...
from me?
You see?
Your baby was ok.
I know because otherwise,
I wouldn't have this...
beautiful daughter.
I'm sorry. I'd like...
to stay and help you
if I could, but...
I have to leave now.
But I have so many questions.
I know.
I'll come back and find you.
Soon.
Jim, have some water.
You haven't taken a
break in over an hour.
No. I'm almost
through. I can feel it.
Thank you. Is there any ice?
This is room temperature.
Damn it!
She was right. It's just
like on melinda's map.
There's some kind
of tunnel in here.
Come on. Back up. Look out.
I'm going to make this
big enough to get through.
The air's getting thin.
Your friends are close.
But they won't know where to
look if you don't make noise.
Noise?
Use your voice.
You have to call out now.
Quickly!
Hello?
Louder!
They won't hear you like that.
I can'T.
There's no air. I just...
can'T.
Which way should we go?
We're already way past where
the church is supposed to be.
You have to try.
I can't lose my baby again.
Your baby?
Don't you see?
You came for me.
You have to live.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
That's good.
Now louder.
Hello?
Did you feel that breeze? That way.
I can't believe I'm about to
say this, but I feel something.
Ok. It's not possible. I...
look, no, hey.
Maybe it is possible.
Maybe it's that ghost.
Her name is tessa.
Melinda's that way.
guys, I think we
should go that way.
Wait, wait. I hear something.
Down here!
Can you hear that?
Hello?
I'm in here!
That's melinda. Come on. Come on.
I'm down here!
Move back. They're almost here.
Mel!
Jim!
I'm coming. almost there
It's ok. Come here.
That's ok.
You know you're 12 hours late
for dinner. That is so not ok.
I... I am so sorry.
I am so sorry.
As long as you're ok,
babe, nothing else matters.
Your town is so beautiful.
It's your town, too.
I'm glad I was the one
that got to show it to you.
I wish the other spirits
beneath could see.
They will.
I'll find a way.
There it is.
Hey, it's so bright.
So beautiful.
I... I didn't think I'd ever...
- you deserve it.
Especially for what
you've done for me.
And for this town.
It's what we do.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
You and I, we...
we've seen so many people
go into the light, but...
until the end, we
never see it ourselves.
That's ok.
I think I'll wait.
That's right.
You wait.
Wait a long, long time.
Be careful, melinda.
I will.
next time I tell you to
help me with your sister...
try not to kill her instead?
So you saw her?
Can't keep this up for much longer.
I won't have to.
It's already in motion.
Soon she'll be with us.
And what if she won't?
She's a smart girl.
She'll make the right choice.
Because if she doesn't...