No, why did you want me to the basketball game?
I don't know the difference
between a field goal
and a slam dunk.
They don't have
field goals
in basketball.
That's football.
No, basketball, too
Oh, jim,
why don't you come?
Ned would love
to have you there.
Ah, i'd love to,
but i got the night shift.
You know?
Look, i wouldn't ask,
Except this is
a new school for him,
He just transferred in,
And i know
he would appreciate
Seeing a few
familiar faces there.
I'd be happy to come.
Huh! That's great!
Oh, he will
so thrilled!
Oh, i hope he gets
a touchdown!
Hey, honey, we're here.
Yeah, i saw that, mom.
Did you say hi
to melinda?
Hi, melinda.
Hi, ned.
And i have snacks
if you're hungry.
Oh, no.
Really, i'm ok, mom.
I know it means a lot
to him that we're here.
I can see that.
Is that brad? No.34
I mean,
what's the big deal?
What can he do
that you can't do?
That.
Way to go, brad!
Is that his girlfriend?
Yeah, her name's
krista.
I don't know.
What happened?
Ned, what's wrong?
Brad's points aren't up.
Something wrong
with the scoreboard.
Maybe she needs help.
"34 + gf = death."
What's going on?
34, that's brad's
number.
So "gf" is gotta be
girlfriend, right?
Yeah, brad and krista
are like this
uber couple.
What?
"Slammers be slammed?"
Wait, this doesn't have
anything to do with
that awful slam book?
What's a slam book?
It's just this
terrible website
Where students
can anonymously slam
each other. It's--Ugh.
What's going on?
Delia, get up, go!
Ok, ned, come on, let's
get out of here.Ned...
Ned, what the hell
is going on?
Tell me more
about the slam book.
It's just a way
to hurt people.
Well, it's working.
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
¹íóïõß µúèı¼¾µú11¼¯
-=Ææàãğü×öä»×é=-
·­òë£º
ğ£¶ô£º
ê±¼äöá£ºstoneiii
??? T before
the bleachers closed,
The scoreboard said
"slammers be slammed."
Well, it's obviously
a ghost
Who's a big fan
of a jump shot.
You know, as opposed
to slam dunks.
Nothing? These are
basketball references.
Why am i wasting
my time?
Ok, have you ever heard
of a slam book?
Of course i have.
The internet's
wonderful contribution
To ruining reputations
everywhere.
Yeah, these kids
just create a webpage
and tear into each other.
Everyone can see it.
You don't even have
to sneak into
the boy's locker room
To find out what
they wrote on the wall.
Not that i ever did that.
I never did that,
either. Ever.
I never had
anything written
about me, either,
Which is awful.
Zip, zero, nothing.
Is there anything worse?
Yeah, try this--
"Want milk?
Try jay baker's man boobs.
So you think this ghost
is lashing out
Because of what
somebody wrote about it
in the slam book?
Maybe. Especially
if what was written
by brad and krista.
Hey, morning.
Hey, professor payne.
Hey, you two.
Hey
Hey, ned, how are things
going at school?
Weird.
Why? What happened now?
Well, the school tnks
they have a suspect
In that gym incident
last night.
The girl who ran
the scoreboard,
what was her name?
Lucy.
Well, that means
it's not a ghost, then.
Well, it depends on
who you talk to.
The school feels
they caught the culprit.
Ned, on the other hand...
Lucy's brother died
a few weeks ago.
Yeah, he hit his head
skateboarding.
He seemed fine,
and then he just
fell asleep.
Concussions
are like that--
Totally stealth.
Oh, that is awful.
And that's exactly
why some people think that
It makes sense
that lucy did it.
You know, she was upset,
understandably.
Maybe she blames
brad and krista
Even though
her brother's death
was an accident.
What is her brother's name?
Thomas. Thomas benjamin.
Well, that's strange.
There's practically
nothing here.
Just one kid
calling him guano boy.
Whatever that means.
Where can i find a picture?
Check the school
face page. Here.
Guano boy's
better than nothin'.
At least he's not invisible.
Hello?
Do you guys even hear
what i'm saying?
I don't know if he caused
all that stuff
With the scoreboard
and bleachers,
But i know he was there last
night. This is the ghost i saw.
Really?
Mom.
What?
So if it was the ghost,
that's good news, right?
At least for lucy.
You can tell
that ned's a little
biased on the subject.
So lucy's a friend?
Don't say anything.
Uh, ned, i take it
you don't agree
With, uh, britfan20-12
who describes lucy
as, quote,
"Satan's deadly
girl pawn?"
Whoever wrote that
doesn't know her.
She's really cool.
You should meet her.
So then why don't you
introduce me?
Uh, geometry class?
I sit right behind you.
Uh, right next
to tony neil.
Spanish 2.
I sit in the back,
over to the left,
Uh, by the pencil
sharpener.
I'm sorry, i have no clue.
Don't take it personally,
i'm new at school, ted.
Ned.
I'm new, too.
That's why i thought
you might, uh--
Uh, lucy, i'm melinda.
Ned told me
about your brother,
and i'm really sorry.
Thanks. Um...
What's this about?
Well, i was at the gym
last night.
Yeah, look,
I already talked
to a lot of people
about it, so...
I don't think
that you did it.
I was there
at the scoreboard.
I'm all emotionally messed up
about my brother.
It had to be me, right?
Well, it's hard
to explain,
But i'm pretty sure
someone else did it.
Why?
Do you blame brad and krista
for your brother's death?
It was an accident.
Why would i blame them?
Whoever wrote
"slammers be slammed"
Obviously blames them
for something.
Can i ask you more
about your brother?
I heard that he died
in a skateboarding
accident.
He came home that night
and put a bag of ice
on the back of his head.
He had his skateboard
with him,
So i figured he just
wiped out again.
And then he went to sleep
and never woke up.
Do you remember
anything else?
Anything he said?
Nothing he said.
But i noticed
there was like...
Chalk on his jacket.
Like, the kind
that they use
To write the name
of the football team
on the field.
This is gonna sound
like a weird question,
But were there any
bad feelings
Between thomas
and krista--
What does the gym thing
last night
Have to do with thomas?
He's dead.
Oh, i get it, ok.
You say that you don't
think that i had anything
to with it, but...
No, it's not
like that.
Why can't everybody
just give me a break?
Lucy!
Hey. Let her go.
I'll see you guys
in a little bit.
Oh...
Aaah!
Please, please stop!
He's harmless!
Just let him fly away!
I don't get
why we can't tell lucy.
She'd be so relieved
to know that her brother's here.
For starters, she'd have
some answers for everything
she's being accused of.
Yeah, i don't know
if she's gonna be
relieved, ned.
It's a lot
for one person
to handle.
I handled it when you told me
my dad's ghost was here.
I don't want
to tell her
about her brother
Until i know
what he wants.
Officer: lucy benjamin?
Yeah?
Grandview police.
We need to ask you
some questions.
Who would put
a bat in there?
I mean, who would
think of that?
It was you.
You're the only one.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Brad: krista, take it easy.
Why would you do that to me?
I'm like the only person
in this whole school
Who's been nice
to your brother.
Why would you do that to me?
I died becau of you.
That's why.
And now you're gonna pay--
Both of you.
I just don't get
why the cops were there.
Lucy's not some psycho.
It's the world we live in now.
Schools feel like
they can't be too cautious.
Well, does thomas
have any idea
What kind of trouble
he's getting
his sister in?
Well, maybe he does,
maybe he doesn't.
We just have to find out
what he has against
those two,
And what it has to do
with the slam book.
So what do we do?
Well, usually i would
talk to lucy,
But she seems to think
i'm just another adult
Who wants to blame her
for what happened
in the gym.
Who else can we get
to talk to her?
I don't know.
I mean,
this whole thing just--
Ok, you know what,
if you're afraid
To have ned get involved
with ghosts,
Then i understand.
It's not the ghost
i'm afraid of.
What is it, then?
Nothing. I'm not
afraid of anything.
Me, neither.
What are you doing here?
Are you here
with your friend?
No.
I just--I didn't
mean to bother you.
I just wanted
to talk.
Oh, god, i'm sorry.
Um...
I haven't been
in the best mood lately.
I should get going,
anyway.
I'm really sorry
about what happened
to thoma
I shouldn't have...
said anything.
No, it's ok.
It's...messed up
How you don't really
want people to bring it up,
And then, if they don't,
It's like everybody's
already forgotten him.
Were you two
really close?
He's my big brother.
We were the only 2 kids
in our family.
He always looked out for me.
Sometimes more
than i wanted him to.
Yeah. I got a mom
who's like that.
Just, i...
Miss him so much
sometimes, you know?
And all this strange stuff's
happening,
And making it
so much worse.
Maybe i can help.
What do you mean?
Ok, this is gonna
sound weird.
Really wei, but i
can't think of a not
weird way to say it,
So i'm just gonna
say it.
I believe in ghosts.
And if you go with me,
just for a minute,
Maybe you can see
how you won't have
to miss thomas so much.
Plus, it can
help explain
All the strange things
that's been happening.
The scoreboard,
the bleachers,
The bat in krista's car.
The bat was just somebody's
bad idea of a joke.
Everybody knew
thomas was into bats.
I know
it sounds crazy.
Ok, wait, what--
What is this?
Is there a camera somewhere?
Are you gonna post
This whole little talk
on your slam book?
I wouldn't do that.
Just don't talk to me
about my brother again.
Stay the hell away from me!
These kids must spend
half their waking hours
Slamming each other online,
and nobody's immune.
That's one of the
popular girls, right?
Turns out that's not
such a blessing anymore.
I guess it pays
to be anonymous
on the internet.
Yeah. Being anonymous
is part of the problem.
These kids say things
under the cover
of a screen name
That they would never
have the courage to say
to someone's face.
Here we go.
A slam on krista
keeps it concise
and to the point.
"Liar. Two-Faced.
Phony. Bitch."
Anyone who sleeps
with krista better
get tested."
"You're not kidding.
Don't forget
the rabies vaccine."
Wow. Rabies.
Gettin' slammed already
for having a bat
in her car.
News travels fast
on the internet.
Yeah, except this was
posted last month,
Before thomas died.
And there's a few more
mentions of rabies
Going back en further.
You know what, i wonder...
What's that?
Krista's school face page.
Look at the caption.
"Here's me with
a bat house i built
with my dad."
You know,
maybe i'm wrong,
But i'm guessing
bat lovers united
Is a very small club.
Makes you wonder what else
they had in common.
Krista: i can't
handle this anymore.
"It's ok, brad's
totally clueless.
"I mean, what would
i tell him anyway?
I'm crazy about someone
who won't even give me
their name."
Signed krista?
Krista: i can explain.
Brad.
And that was sent
to every kid at school
at the same time?
Ned: yeah, how is that
even possible?
Well, if i had to guess,
i'd guess ghost.
So what now?
Well, it seems to imply
That krista was cheating
on her boyfriend brad.
Maybe he knew
about it.
I can introduce you to brad.
I'll be right there.
[Indistinct chatter]
Ned.
Hey.
Where is he?
Yeah, practice just ended.
I told him to meet you
in the team meeting room.
I'll see you later.
Thomas benjamin
had chalk on him
when he died.
He was hit in the head
with something.
I'm guessing
it was this board.
You're the one
that pushed him into it.
Brad, i don't work for the school
or the police
I'm just trying
To help thomas
and his family
get some peace.
And you, too.
But you have
to tell me
what happened.
Krista had been
acting strange for weeks.
I mean, we spe
all our time together,
But she was sorta...
checked out.
She was always online
iming her friends.
Hey.
Here's a tip--
When your girlfriend starts
closing your cell phone
around you, it's over.
I really like krista,
And i just--
I didn't want
to lose her.
I had to know
who she was seeing.
I know it was wrong,
but i read her email.
Some of the stuff
she was telling this guy
was so intense.
And the weirdest thing was,
E didn't even know
who he was.
Then i did something
really stupid
That i'll regret
the rest of my life.
I sent him an email
pretending to be krista.
I said, "let's meet."
So you arranged
to meet him here?
I just wanted to know
who the guy was.
I had a right
to face my competition,
Tell him what krista
meant to me.
Then there was thomas.
Guano boy.
Brad: i couldn't
believe it.
Where's krista?
She doesn't know
anything about this.
I sent the invite.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Look, man,
i just want to talk.
Yeah, well,
i don't want
to talk to you, man.
You gotta hear me out, man!
And that's when
he blindsided me.
[Both yelling]
Ow!
Are you ok, man?
What the hell
do you care, man?!
Get off me!
Brad: and that was it,
i swear.
He seemed fine
that night when he left.
What about krista?
How does she feel
about all of this?
Like i told thomas--
She didn't even know
i sent the email
arranging the meeting.
It's me who's to blame.
Quite an entrance.
Just some friends
from a previous life.
I don't know why
they can see me.
Then again, i don'know why
you can see me, either.
Brad told me
what happened
the night you died.
Did he mentioned the part
where he killed me?
He said that you
threw the first punch,
And that he thought
you were ok and it was
all an accident.
What if it was?
When i left him, he was
with the principal,
Confessing everything
to the authorities.
He feels terrible.
Ok, it was all
an accident
And you have
to forgive them
and go into the light.
Forgive them? Why?
Because everything
that you're doing,
All these things
you're trying to
punish them with,
These hauntings,
it's just hurting
your sister.
She's getting blamed
for everything you do.
Who's blaming lucy?
Is it the slam book?
You know how
they treat anyone
who's different.
No, the police.
Ok, the school.
You were there
when they were
questioning her.
Well, they shouldn't be
questioning lucy.
That's the whole point.
They should just
leave her alone.
Is that why you've been
doing all this,
Because you think
you're protecting her?
I always have.
I'm her brother.
I've got her six.
Thomas, please tell me
what it is that you're
protecting her from.
I can help you.
No, you can't.
No one can.
But if you don't
tell me,
I'm gonna have
to find out myself,
And what if
i'm too late?
You stay away from her.
I'm warning you.
Why won't you let me
help her?
We all got our secrets.
Including you.
Melinda: lucy?
Can i talk to you
for a minute?
Talk if you want.
I know ned told you
he believes in ghosts.
I really wish
he hadn't done that,
Because it doesn't
do you any good
unless i can prove it.
Oh, you're gonna
prove it to me?
I will if i have to.
But i think you
already know.
Really? How's that?
I think you've felt
his presence.
And i'm not just talking
about the weird things
that keep happening.
I want to know
why thomas needs
to have your six.
What?
I didn't know
what it meant,
So i looked it up,
And it's what
a fighter pilot
says to another
When he's covering his tail,
"i've got your six."
How did you know
thomas said that?
Because he said it
to me.
What do you want from me?
I want to know what
it is that thomas is
protecting you from.
Why he is so mad
at brad and krista,
So that i can get him
into the light
where he belongs.
Lucy, please.
Just tell me what happened
Between him and krista.
Were they seeing each other?
Did he send those emails?
Hi. Justin yates.
Justin who?
You don't remember me.
Yeah, why would you.
Um, ok, uh, blogger?
In shame of the devil?
We met after you won
that plaque from the town
for, uh, saving those kids.
Ok, smile.
Oh.
What do you want?
Well, i got this
really strange email
a few hours ago.
Ok.
So why don't you just
post it on your blog
And i'll read it
when i get a chance.
I know my blog
isn't exactly cnn.Com.
But a lot of your friends
and a lot of your customers
probably check it out.
And you know how
the internet is.
Once something
starts to spread...
What are you
talking about?
Here. I'll show you.
This is a video of me
rehearsing a fight
i had with my husband.
Yeah, you know,
i thought you would
say that.
Uh, the one problem is,
The video made my hamster
jump on the wheel, you know?
And, uh, remembered
these files
I kind of borrowed
from professor payne
a while back.
They were encrypted,
And i'd given up
on trying to decode them
Until tonight.
What's in the files,
justin?
In a nutshell?
You see ghosts.
And you believe that?
Not so much, really,
until i noticed
Something about the email
that the video
was attached to.
Whoever sent me this clip,
their computer doesn't have
an ip address.
And in case you don't know,
that's not possible.
Not in this world,
at least.
The world of the living.
Wait a minute, um...
What is it
that you want, exactly?
Well, in my business,
Usually when someone
sends this kind of message,
Someone wants you
to stop looking
Wherever it is you're looking.
So you just wanted
to give me a warning?
Yeah, and, uh, maybe a little
professional courtesy,
In case you find anything
interesting you want to share.
Well, thanks...
For the warning.
Good night.
You're welcome
Guilty, guilty,
i'm guilty!
What do you want from me?
I told you i'm guilty!
What were you thinking?
Keeping records
of things that
i said to you,
Things that i told you
because i thought
that you could be trusted.
And don't even tell me
that they were encrypted,
Because we both know
how little that's worth.
All right, think back.
You come to me,
i don't know you
from adam.
And all the things
that i've been studying
and wondering about,
And between you and i,
starting to doubt,
All of a sudden
they're real?!
But why write it down?
[Sighs] look, because
it was so amazing,
I had to make sure
i wasn't dreaming it!
This was huge stuff!
For you,
it's an old hat,
But let's not forget
that i'm an academic,
And you're sweet,
kind, caring,
Forgiving melinda,
right?
Don't i have an
obligation as my job
To write down
what i observe?
Remember, you're--
You're sweet, kind,
forgiving melinda.
Do you have any idea
what this could do
to my life?
Oh, come on, melinda!
What are you afraid of?
Everyone you help,
they already know
that you see ghosts!
I am afraid
of people like you.
Of becoming a case study
So that people can
understand things
That can't be
understood.
And while i'm under
that microscope,
I can't even help
the spirits that
actually need me.
You've really
thought this through,
haven't you?
My whole life.
Hey, ned,
what's going on?
Is that ned?
Tell him i'm here.
It's professor payne, ned.
Put me on--
Ned, could you please
say that again,
Because i had
someone very annoying
distracting me.
Ned: lucy just told the school
she did all those hauntings.
The scoreboard,
the bleachers,
The bat in krista's car,
everything.
What? Why would
she do that?
It's like she's trying
to protect thomas.
Thomas is a ghost.
What is she protecting him
from, purgatory?
Wait, will you just
call me back if you get
anything else? Bye.
I don't get it.
Thomas says that
he's protecting her,
She's acting like
she's protecting him.
What are they protecting
each other from?
Have you asked krista?
No. She won't return
my phone calls.
All right, well,
ever since brad confessed,
Maybe she has
a lot less to hide.
Hi, krista,
i'm melinda.
I know who you are.
Um, i've been trying
to talk to you.
Wow. Do you have, like,
zero comprehension
of the word "no?"
I do, but did thomas?
Thomas?
Yeah, i'm not trying to
blame you for anything.
I mean, i'm sure
if you hurt
thomas' feelings,
You didn't mean to.
No, i didn't do
anything to thomas.
Ok, we had a couple
conversations about bats.
That's it.
Well, you were
writing to each other.
It's no secret
that the two of you
were involved.
I mean,
the entire school
got that email.
No, those emails
weren't from thomas, ok?
So just drop it.
Well, how can you
be so sure?
They weren't even
signed.
Because, i've written back
since he died,
And...
I haven't got a response yet,
But whoever was writing me
opened them.
So if thomas wasn't
writing them, then who?
I don't know!
I gotta go.
Wait a minute.
So krista's protecting
thomas, too?
Protecting or stonewalling.
She's insisting those emails
were not from him.
Or maybe she's just
embarrassed
That she was cheating
on her boyfriend
with guano boy.
I'm not calling names.
I'm just trying
to put it in perspective.
High school perspective.
So assuming that krista
was telling the truth,
And if he wasn't
writing those emails,
who was?
Maybe there's some clue
to who sent them
in the emails.
You're right!
You're right,
that's all
we have to do.
Do you still have
that email
on your phone?
The one the ghost
was texting everyone?
Yeah, but it didn't say much.
That's ok.
Little blogger
friend of mine
Taught me that one
is all it takes.
Professor rick payne
in apologetic servitude.
Melinda: good.
I'm gonna forward you
an email,
And i need you
to use the ip address
To track down the location
of the computer that
originally sent then.
Can you do that?
Sure.
Yeah, i mean i know a geek
who knows a geek.
I knew you would.
Remember to tell
your mom
That we did not spend
the whole evening
talking about ghosts.
I helped you with
your homework, too.
Yeah, that was intense.
How much you know about
measuring volumes and planes.
[Cell phone rings]
hello?
Rick: all right,
i can get you
The internet service provider
and the physical address
Of the computer's location.
No user name, though.
I would need
a court order for that.
Yeah, but you've already
got the address?
Yeah, do you have a pen?
Uh, yeah. Ok,
write this down.
So whoever answers the door
sent those emails to krista?
I feel for him,
whoever he is.
Hi.
Lucy?
Yeah, this is
my house.
Are you looking
for someone else?
Not any more
Now's not really
a good time.
Lucy? Who is it?
Dad, this is
ned and melinda.
They're...from school.
Why don't you
come inside?
Um, we're sorry
to bother you.
We were just hoping
that we could talk to
lucy for a few minutes.
What about?
This is
my wife jill.
This is melinda
and--
Ned. Hi.
Hi.
Is this about the trouble
lucy's in?
In a way.
It's ok. I can talk to them.
We'll just go outside.
No, i don't
think so, honey.
Our daughter's
all but been branded
a serial killer
Because some kids
reprogrammed
the scoreboard.
Dad...
I don't believe
for a second
you did that.
I don't care what
you told the police
or your teachers.
Well, i actually believe
that lucy's innocent, also.
In fact, i know it.
Why don't we all
sit down?
How do you know that?
It's about
the letters you wrote.
Emails, actually.
The ones you wrote
to that kid you like.
That kid?
There's this girl
i was into.
If you're here
as someone concerned
About some inappropriate
relationships--
No, actually,
we're just here as friends.
They're here
because of thomas.
Because he wasn't
ok with it.
Not really...anyway.
Lucy, what are you
talking about?
The night thomas died.
"Meet me at 8:00.
"If you can't
make it, forget it.
I've waited
too long."
Signed krista.
Are you out
of your mind?
Where did you get that?
You saved it on the hard drive.
The hard drive that we share.
It's private.
Krista eisenberg.
She is beautiful,
she's a senior,
And, oh, what's one
little key ingredient
Missing in your wacky
lesbian fantasy?
She's not gay.
We were posting
on the same blog!
She responded to me.
She wanted my email,
And she's the one
who kept it going.
But you never told her
who you are.
You never gave her
your name.
She likes me.
She doesn't even know
she's writing to a girl!
I think she does.
Oh, why?
Because of little things
that she said.
Different stuff
that you wouldn't understand.
You can't do this.
Ok? You're comitting
social suicide.
Once she sees you,
she's gonna realize
that you tricked her,
And she's gonna
be pissed.
If she doesn't want
to be with me,
she can tell me,
And i'll handle it.
Can you handle
What she's going
to write about you
in the slam book?
What her friends
are going to write
about you?
Once you're a target,
Everyone's gonna
take a shot.
People that don't
even know you.
They're gonna
terrorize you
every day.
For the rest
of high school.
Lucy, we have got
to undo this
Before it gets out.
We're supposed to meet.
I'll go.
Ok? I'll figure
something out.
Ok?
The whole thing
was a set up.
Forget her.
Why would krista
do that?
She's the one
who kept emailing.
who wanted to meet.
Why would she
send brad?
I don't--I don't know.
Maybe she got off of
Makin' him, like...
jealous or something.
Or she thought
that, uh, maybe...
What?
I don't know,
That the whole thing
was just kind of a joke.
But your brother
was lying to you.
Krista never even knew
about the meeting.
What?
Brad never told her.
He sent that email
himself,
But he never
told krista that.
Why was thomas
so mad at krista?
Because...
He thought she never
meant anything
she put in the emails.
He was sure you were
getting set up.
He thought he was
protecting me.
He had my six.
Mom and dad,
i am so sorry.
I should have never
let him go.
Oh, baby.
No one meant
for it to happen.
No, the county is not
charging brad,
And they shouldn't.
It was all an accident.
What about all those
things that happened
at the schl?
Are you saying
you did it because
you're angry?
No, your son was.
Lucy took the blame
for those things
Because she was tired
of everybody asking
what really happened.
Ok, now i'm really confused.
But lucy never was
confused.
She knew who she was,
and who she loved,
And she wasn't
ashamed of it.
And mom and dad
were ok with that.
Just like they were ok
with me being the freak kid
Who hung out
with the bats all day.
Thomas is here.
His spirit.
What are you talking about?
He says that you loved
both of your children
Just for who they were.
They were cool
about everything,
But they have no idea
what it's like now,
For anyone who's different.
They take a few words
and, like,oison
your whole world.
He's worried
about lucy.
All the damage that
the internet can do,
Spreading
cruel words around.
I mean, look at my sister.
She's pretty, and smart,
and funny.
Everyone likes her.
No one had to know
that lucy was different.
He's saying
that you could have
blended in--
If you wanted to.
You mean if i chose to.
In my heart,
i wanted her to change.
But i was the one
that needed to change.
I was just trying
to look out for you,
But i realize now
that that's not
what you needed.
What you needed was me
to see you and to love you
for who you are.
He loves you.
He always did.
And he doesn't
want you to be anything
but who you are.
I love him, too.
I love you, thomas.
Come on.
Do you see the light?
Not yet.
I got one or two things
to take care of first.
So now they think somehow
That the computer
on the scoreboard
Looped into
the school server,
Like it was just
some wires that crossed,
Messed everything up.
So thomas set things right.
That's great.
Yeah.
And lucy's off the hook.
Excuse me.
Oh, man. She's pissed
about the ghost thing.
Do you want me
to go talk to her?
No, it's ok.
I can handle it.
Hey, mom?
Be mad at me, ok?
Not melinda.
I'm the one
that pushed her to help.
I'm not mad
at anybody.
I'm just proud of you
For wanting
to help your friend.
Lucy?
She's not really my friend.
She called me "ted."
You see,
that's what i mean.
You didn't care what
anybody might call you.
You still stuck
your neck out anyway.
Your sweet,
Beautiful neck.
I used to kiss it
when i put you to bed.
That was just
a second ago, ned.
And now you're all
grown up.
I am...
So proud of the man
that you are becoming.
Lucy: hey.
Me?
Ned, yeah, hi.
How have you been?
Good. Good, you know,
School, life.
Um, that was
a cool thing you did,
Telling me about
what you believe.
I know i didn't
make it easy.
Do you want to sit?
Yeah. Yeah, ok.
So has your friend
seen my brother around?
No, but he might
still be here.
Usually she sees them
cross over.
Hey.
Hi.
I got your email.
My email?
Yeah?
Wait, don't tell me
that it wasn't for me.
This is weird enough
already.
No, i just--I didn't...
Don't be shy.
Just admit it.
The web works
in mysterious ways.
Wow.
Busted.
Thanks for all
your emails.
So you knew?
Not for sure.
But, um...
i hoped.
You did
a good thing.
I worry about her.
I don't.
She looks like
she has good friends.
The light...
What's it like in there?
I've heard good things.
But don't go by me.
Maybe you should
go check it out
for yourself.
Justin.
Oh, uh...
Hey. Um,
I'm not stalking you,
i swear.
You said it, i didn't.
Ahh, did you ever find out
who emailed me that video
from the security camera?
Nope.
It's like you said,
no ip address.
You got your secrets,
that's cool.
It's just, you know,
it's hard not ask about
the ones i know about.
Like your travels
underneath the town.
In the tunnels
Under our beloved,
perhaps haunted, town.
Is that professor payne's
theory?
Look, i don't want
to out you.
Ok, i know what
that could do
to your life.
Why does this mean
so much to you?
Do you have some sort of thing
with the other side?
Hmm.
When the time comes,
Just remember,
i kept your secret.
What time is that?
When i call in the favor
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë