You know. Don't even call
this a short walk.
We've been going for two miles,
and that's in a forced march.
All right, when we get to the base camp,
I'll give you a nice massage.
Hey, how nice is nice?
How long have we been married?
And you got to ask.
What's someone doing in our tent?
Who's that?
I don't know.
Wait a minute. Is she a...
No, she's not a ghost. She's real.
She's a young girl.
- But doesn't she look kind of-
- Yeah. Something's not right.
There's not another campsite
for miles.
Oh, we scared her.
No, wait!
Wait a minute!
Wait!
Look, we don't want to hurt you!
We just want to help!
Wait! Don't get-
It's all right.
No, take it easy, ok?
Let me see your leg.
I'm a paramedic.
I can help you.
Let me just look at your leg,
all right?
It's nothing.
It just needs to be cleaned
and dressed.
Hey, uh, tell us your name.
You must be pretty scared, huh?
Out here in these woods all alone.
Tell you what.
I'll make you a deal.
You come back with us
to our camp, ok?
Get warm, have a good meal.
I'll split this with you.
Ok, you can have
the whole thing.
It's ok.
It wasn't very deep at all.
It should heal quickly.
You know,
we really want to help you,
but you have to tell us
a few things first, like...
what's your name?
Where are your parents?
Are you lost?
Maybe if we talk to child services back in town,
they could give us some information-
Becca.
- Your name's Becca?
- Yeah.
Ok.
Becca, so...
what are you doing here?
Are you hiding from something?
I ran away.
What did you run away from?
Your parents?
I don't have any parents.
They're dead.
Do you live in a foster home?
How long have you been out here?
I dont know. Two or three weeks.
We need to find out
where that foster home was
so that we can let them
know you're all right.
No.
Please. I don't want to go back there.
Well, we're going to do the
best we can to keep you safe,
but we need to let the
police know that we found you.
Don't make me go back there.
I'm begging you.
You know, we don't get
any cell service out here,
and if we try to hike to the car,
it would be dark before we get there, so...
Ok.
You're going to stay here with us.
We'll keep you safe.
I won't let you leave me.
What's going on?
What's happening to me?
Hey, look at me.
There's nothing here.
You're all right.
She's mine.
Becca, I know that you
don't really feel safe,
but trust me, you are.
I think the best thing for you is
just to get a good night's sleep.
I can't.
Well, then, let's talk.
Do I have to?
I know that this is
going to sound strange...
but have you lost any
friends or family lately?
Why?
I'm just trying to understand
why you're out here.
They hurt me. I left.
I'm not going back.
Ok.
Why these woods?
How have you been living out
here all this time by yourself?
I'm tired.
I'm going to go back to sleep.
Wait. Um, can you hang with me for a
minute, just till I fall back asleep?
Of course I will.
Hey, I didn't know you were so
good with teenage hard cases.
Well, it helps that I used to be one.
You? Come on.
Yeah. You remember that age.
You're always mad at your parents
'cause they didn't understand who you were.
Well, take all that, add ghosts, and stir.
Do you think that's
what happened to Becca?
Or maybe she was abused?
I don't know.
What did the ghost say about her?
He just said "she's mine. "
Well, maybe he could be a friend
or a brother who was also abused.
Could be.
Well, I guess we'll find out
when we know where she belongs.
What if we're just taking her right
back to the thing she's running from?
Don't really have a choice.
Honey.
No. Wake up.
Becca's gone.
What?
I left this in my backpack.
She must have found it in the tent.
Ok. So where could she have gone?
I don't know.
Wherever she went, she's staying,
'cause she took most of the food.
Oh, no.
What?
My car keys.
Becca
Just watch out.
She might get some traction.
Becca!
Becca, stop it!
I'll try get this side
You can't go. I need you!
I won't let you go!
Go away!
Leave her alone!
Get out of the
car- right now.
Get out of the car.
You could have killed yourself.
What were you thinking?
You saw him, too.
You can see ghosts.
So, we'll go downtown later and see if
we can get some things that fit better.
So you're not going to
call the police or whoever?
Eventually, but if you need
some more time, for now...
do you need some help with that?
I know how to use a brush.
You know, when my grandma first
told me that she could see ghosts,
I should have said, "thank god.
You know, there's finally
someone else like me. "
All I could say was,
"what is wrong with my grandma?"
It might be something
you have to get used to.
So, you said that you
were hurt by people.
Mostly with words?
Yeah, mostly.
Who?
My foster parents.
What happened to your real parents?
They died in a car crash.
How old were you when they died?
I guess I was, like, 5 or 6.
How old were you when
you started seeing ghosts?
I don't remember ever not seeing them.
What did you say to your
parents after they died?
After they died?
I never saw them.
Your parents didn't die, did they?
And you don't have foster parents.
You made it all up.
Look, you can tell me the truth.
If you do, I can help you.
And if you don't, then you're going to
go back home, and nothing's going to be-
they think I'm sick.
They take me to the doctors and
they try to make me take pills.
Ok. So then, we'll make them understand.
It won't work.
Well, you can't live in the woods
forever, and you don't have to.
Know how to make the ghosts go away?
I know something better.
Yeah, mom. I'm fine. I promise.
I don't know. Just, like, some
cuts and stuff,
but he's, like, an ambulance guy,
and he says I'm fine. So...
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
They'll be here tomorrow afternoon.
They live in a small town
outside St. Louis.
Well, what happens now?
Well, they just talked
to the Grandview police,
who said nice things
about us, thank goodness,
so I guess she'll stay
here until they get here.
How did she get that far from home?
'Cause she's a smart girl.
She took a bus 5 or 6 days and
then got off here in Grandview.
Ok. And how
about this-
another person who sees
ghosts chooses Grandview.
Why does that keep happening?
I don't know, but I don't
have time to think about it.
Right, 'cause you got
a ghost to cross over.
No. She does.
I have 24 hours to teach
that girl everything I know.
Has he been in touch with you
since you left home?
No, I met him in the woods.
But the thing to remember is that
they're more scared and confused than you.
They're stuck here, for some reason, and
most of the time, they don't even know why.
and after you've figured out
why they've stayed earthbound,
you can help them,
take care of them.
And they can cross over.
Cross over?
Yeah. Into the light.
So, how do you know
it's a better place?
You ever been there?
No, but I've felt it.
There's peace there, and knowing that I
gave them that, there's nothing better.
Hey. You must be Becca.
I'm delia.
It's ok, honey.
I won't bite.
I hear that you are
a very special girl.
Uh, you know what? There's some really
cool vintage dresses over there.
Why don't you take a look?
Melinda, you know that I believe
that you do amazing things.
I have seen you change
people's lives again and again.
- But this-
- what?
Do you really think the
best way to help this girl-
Is to give her a crash
course in being you?
Delia, she's not just running
away from her parents.
She's running away from ghosts.
Can't you teach her
how not to be afraid?
I can't stop her from seeing them,
which means that I can't stop them
from going to her with their problems.
Have you ever tried walking around with
a crowd of dead people following you?
It's not fun.
Didn't you say your mom had
this gift, and she lived with it?
Trust me,
that is not a good argument.
Melinda?
Yeah. I'll be right there.
Look, I had my grandmother, ok?
Becca has no one but
parents who don't understand.
I have to teach her
how to cross them over.
I'm not going to let her
turn out like Gabriel,
overmedicated and institutionalized.
Becca!
Look, I'm sorry, ok?
I know that this is hard.
You don't have to apologize.
I should be used to seeing them.
You have to stop running
away from them,
or else they're going
to keep finding you.
You think I don't know that?
Look, that's why you
have to face them, ok?
You just have to find
out what they need.
It will make them stop.
Ok. I'll try.
Let's start with his name.
Did he give you that?
I think it's Daniel.
Has he said anything about how he died?
Um, I think he was in
some kind of accident.
He said there were bodies around.
Was there a fire? 'Cause he
looked like he'd been burned.
Honestly, I try not to look.
He talked about that, too.
Ok. I see it a little bit, but
for her to be your mini-me,
her hair would have
to be a lot different.
This is my friend Rick Payne.
He's a professor.
He's also-
oh, my gosh! Those eyes!
Look at those eyes with that
"don't even try lying to me,
'cause I can literally see
right through you" look!
- A little strange?
- Yes.
The resemblance is uncanny.
Ok. The ghost.
He's a boy, about Becca's age.
His name is Daniel.
There was an accident in the woods.
There were lots of bodies
around, so I'm thinking...
last year plane crash.
Yeah, he probably wandered off, got
separated from the rest of the passengers.
Yeah. The woods are not
far from the crash site.
Well, that would explain the bodies.
And the burns on his face.
Ok. Well, I'll check the manifest.
I'll see if his name turns up.
What about the voices?
What voices?
In your basement.
Didn't you hear them?
No, not really.
Wait a minute. You can hear
voices that Melinda can't?
That would make her
more powerful than you.
No. That's just how it works.
In the beginning, you get everything,
you get voices, ghost energy, all of it.
And then, eventually, you learn to tune
certain things out so you can function.
Whatever she's hearing, it's
probably coming from the tunnels.
Do you still have that giant
hole in the wall in your basement?
What tunnels?
Oh, you don't want to
know about the tunnels.
Well, why not? What's under there?
What's under there? More
like who's under there.
More accurately, who isn't under there.
The amount of
trapped souls-
ok. You know what?
Maybe she should focus on the ghost that's
haunting her right now, don't you think?
Yeah, ok-yes.
I do.
What's my job again?
Check the plane manifest.
Ok.
You and I have a field trip to go on.
come on, Let's go find Daniel.
Why?
Because this is probably
near where he died.
It will help him remember what happened.
But why look for him at all?
I mean, he hasn't bugged me
in hours. Maybe he's finished.
No, he's not finished
until he crosses over-
until we help him cross over.
How many times did I tell you?
I don't like being left behind!
Becca, talk to him.
Find out what he needs.
Please, don't go.
Ask him what's keeping him here.
Why won't you just leave me alone?
They left me here.
They never said a word!
Were they punishing me?
What was I supposed to think?
Who? Daniel, who left you here?
Who is she, anyway?
I don't like her.
Becca, find out what's keeping him here.
I don't care.
I hate him! I want him to go away!
I'm burning
Hey, what do you see?
Daniel, talk to me, all right?
I want to help you.
She wants to help you!
She doesn't want to help me!
Why should I help her?
Well, then, stop hurting her, all right?
Let her go.
Hey.
What happened?
I was on fire!
It was horrible.
Look, I know how painful this is, ok?
But look at me.
I'm right here. We're ok.
There's a reason that he
told you all of that. Ok?
He was trying to tell
you what happened to him,
and with that, you can cross him over.
I don't care.
Yes, you do.
You want to help him and yourself.
I don't care about
Daniel or any of them!
You can't give up.
Yes, I can!
I'm done.
I'm never going to do that again.
Still not hungry?
You know, your parents are
going to be here tomorrow,
so we don't really have much time.
Has a ghost ever done
anything like this to you?
I've seen weird things before.
No one's ever tried to hurt me.
I know how awful this is.
But the vision, it's...
sometimes the only way they can
tell you that they need your help.
But why should I help Daniel when
all he tries to do is scare me?
Look... I know that this is not fair.
Most kids don't have to think about
death until they're much older.
But you and me?
Our lives are different.
You want a reason why
you should help Daniel?
One is because if you don't,
he'll never leave you alone.
But the real reason is because you can.
Ok.
But how?
The vision.
Tell me everything you saw.
There were bodies on the ground.
I'm right here.
I was on fire.
You mean Daniel was.
At first, his skin hurt really bad.
Then, he couldn't feel anything.
There was metal burning.
And tires.
And there were cars.
They looked like tinfoil
somebody punched really hard.
One of them was on fire.
I think that one was Daniel's.
Can you see a license plate number?
There were
letters. M-I-Y...
the number 8.
Hey...
Becca.
No. You did great.
You know what? Let's get out of here.
What do you think?
Let's go...
walk amongst the living
for a little while.
Can I just be alone?
Sure.
Hey, Melinda?
Were you ever scared?
It's never been easy.
But I had someone
who... made me feel brave.
I hope I can do that same thing for you.
Hey.
How'd the open house
for the new listing go?
Oh, people loved the cookies, but
not bites on the house.
I brought leftovers.
Thanks for covering.
Where's Becca?
She's at home resting.
Jim's there.
How's she doing?
We made some progress.
I think I know who the
little boy in the woods is.
He's looking for his parents.
2 cars hit head-on,
causing a pile-up.
There were 5 fatalities,
including a family,
Becca had seen their
license plate in a vision,
a mother, father, and a 13-year-old boy
named Daniel Asher.
That's terrible.
Daniel died at the scene.
And his parents died
later at the hospital.
You know, maybe they just saw
the light and went right into it.
And he's just been
waiting there ever since?
He thinks they're still alive?
I'm not sure.
But he needs to know that they've
gone, and he should join them.
With any luck, Becca will be
able to convince him of that.
It would really help them both.
You know what? I really have to go.
Hey.
You're back!
That's so great.
Um, you could come meet my parents.
So, I was telling them all
about how you helped me.
Now, I admit that I was just
pretending to see ghosts,
just like you did when you
were my age for attention.
Melinda. I'm Joan Cahill,
Becca's mom.
I don't even know what to say.
Honestly, I don't, either.
Honey, the Cahills were able
to get an earlier flight.
Um, this is Tony.
Tony, this is my wife Melinda.
Thank you for saving our daughter-
our whole family, actually.
Well, I don't know if I really helped.
You did.
Look, I don't know how
you got through to her,
but these things that she was
imagining, we didn't know what to do.
Frankly, I felt like we'd lost
her long before she ran away.
But... you're back now.
Right, sweetheart?
Things are going to be a-ok.
Yeah. A-ok, again.
Thanks for not busting me.
So, what are you going to do now?
Every time you see a
ghost, just ignore it?
Kind of already tried that.
- Yeah, but it will be easier now.
- How?
'Cause I know it's not my fault.
Before, I thought I had
something bad in me.
I was making them come
to me and nobody else.
They come to you
because you can see them.
And because they need your help.
Look, this is who you really are.
It's who we both are.
No.
I'm not brave enough.
You comfortable, sweetie?
You can't hear a word
I'm saying, can you?
I could sleep for about
100 years, you know?
Should we try to get a
later flight tomorrow?
No. Let's get home.
Thank god, we can throw these away now.
What were we doing, making
her take these?
Joan, wait...
she wasn't hallucinating.
She never actually saw anything.
I know. I hope it's
over, but just in case...
it's not just about Becca.
It's about that little boy in the woods
waiting on parents that will never come back.
Yeah, but Becca knows
about the light now.
So maybe she's able to help him.
And he knows about you.
He can come to you.
And what about the ghost
that haunts her after that?
And then, the one after that?
Honey, no one could have
helped her more than you did.
Yeah.
That's what kills me.
No. Get away from them.
I'd give anything just to
be with my parents again.
Oh! No, no. Why can't
you just leave me alone?
Because then I'd be alone, too.
How'd you like it if I left
you in the dark in those woods?
I begged you to.
But you didn't mean it.
Why can't you just be my friend?
Because you're dead!
You'd be dead, too, if I didn't
help you find food and water.
I looked out for you.
Every night, I was there,
and you knew it.
Ok. Fine.
You watched over me. Thanks.
Now, go, please.
I'm still protecting you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Someone knows about you
and your friend. That lady.
- He found me, and he'll find you, too.
- Who?
I'm not sure.
He wanted me to come
with him, but I wouldn't.
He said he knows where
they're keeping my parents.
I don't understand.
Melinda knows things.
You should go to her.
No. She just wants to send me away
so I'll never see my parents again.
Becca...
please.
You have to help me. only you hear voices
Why don't you let me finish that up, huh?
Go on up.
that's weird
- Hey.
- We are so sorry to bother you.
Is Becca here?
Please tell us she's here.
No, she's not.
Oh, god.
When was the last time
you saw your daughter?
Um, we were tired. We fell asleep.
Probably 3 hours ago.
We already called the police.
I woke up freezing.
It always seemed so cold
right before I hear her scream.
Becca gets night terrors.
And this time, she didn't call out.
She was just gone.
Becca say anything?
Was she talking to anyone?
I heard her whisper something.
She went into the bathroom.
She does that sometimes when
she's trying to hide from us.
Yeah, but does she say anything?
I buried my head in the pillow.
I couldn't listen.
Ok. She was probably talking to Daniel.
And if she went with him, then
she's trying to cross him.
I'm sorry. Cross him?
Just take them to the police, all right?
- I'm going to go to the woods.
- You got it.
Excuse me. What the hell is going on?
You know what? I'm really sorry
to have to throw this at you,
but your daughter's been
trying to tell you for years.
You've tried pills.
You've tried doctors.
The only thing you 2 never
tried was believing her.
Your daughter sees ghosts, ok?
And I know that because I see them, too.
Look, you both have to understand
that my wife has lived her entire life
having people tell her she's crazy.
And maybe right now,
you think she is, too.
But I'll tell you, she's the only chance
you have of getting your daughter back.
You can hear it too, right?
This is where Melinda
said the trapped souls are.
It sounds like they're hurting.
That's why we have to hurry.
Hello?
This is guardian-safe.
There's been an alarm activation
at your place of business.
Would you like us to
dispatch the police?
The tunnels.
Sorry, ma'am, I didn't hear you.
Would you like us to
dispatch the police?
No, no, no. It's my husband.
Sometimes he forgets
how the alarm works.
I'm so sorry. Thank you.
What? What?
- What?
- Hey.
In the square this afternoon, when
you told Becca about the tunnels,
didn't you tell her that she could
get to them through the basement?
Oh, gee whiz. You know, I really
thought there was going to be a
"sorry I woke you up, professor"
mixed in there.
She's in trouble, ok?
She ran away from her parents after
they heard her talking to someone.
Was it the ghost Daniel?
No, room service.
Well, we know she heard us talking about
the hole in the wall in your basement.
But why would they go into the tunnels?
Because you told her that there
were spirits trapped there.
Maybe she and Daniel think it's
the best way to get to his parents.
And by the way, the store
alarm just went off.
- Oh, boy. Sounds like Daniel's up to his old tricks again.
- What?
Remember, you asked me to
read up on the accident?
Well, the post mortem report says
that that kid's blood alcohol level
was a few notches above schnockered.
So, he was drunk?
Very.
I think your parents are down there.
Look, if you're scared, you
don't have to do this.
You can just go.
I'll go alone.
You could get hurt.
I won't leave you.
We can do this.
Becca, you here?
Becca?
Daniel?
Becca!
Becca?
Daniel?
mom, dad? are you here?
She's here, another one.
mom? dad?
Are those your parents?
You. Is it over?
Can I go now?
Who are you?
He has a gun.
Why did you all come here?
How did you find this place?
It still hurts.
We were promised.
You said...
he promised.
Becca, I'm scared.
Who are all these people?
Melinda, see?
Just a few stitches
and you're all better.
And we can stop somewhere
special on the way home.
oh, Melinda
It's ok, honey.
They're just upset.
Erwe we supposed to help.
I can't understand them.
There's too many voices.
I know.
But if you try, you can
hear what's important,
the one soul that we need
to hear most at that moment.
All we have to do is
listen with our hearts.
Where is he?
I can't find him!
Sweet girl, can you help me?
I need to find my husband.
Daniel? I'm here.
I'm here. It's ok.
No, it's not.
We can't find my parents.
I know.
I did.
I listened for them.
Then, I heard them calling for you.
- Daniel? Honey
- Daniel? Where is he?
Daniel!
I've been waiting for you for so long.
It's ok.
You can go to them.
Daniel, what's wrong?
Daniel. Come.
You said they'd never leave you.
But you didn't believe that, did you?
Not after what happened that
night before the accident.
It's my fault.
We never would have been in
that car if I didn't screw up.
My friend levI's
parents were out of town.
We all said we were sleeping
at someone else's house.
And we snuck into their liquor cabinet.
We went outside and started
taking out some mailboxes.
Someone called the police.
And then they called us.
At 2 a.m., We're picking our
13-year-old up from the police station.
Blaming ourselves, each other.
Arguing over who was supposed
to follow up with levI's parents,
still thinking every
mistake could be avoided.
If I hadn't done that, if you
weren't so tired and worried-
Daniel! That car swerved into our lane.
Dad!
It wasn't your fault.
And even if it was, we
would never leave you.
Then where were you?
Your parents died at the hospital.
We didn't understand what happened.
How could we still be here and you not?
And then, we met a man who...
told us he could bring us to you.
A man. Who are you talking about?
He didn't say his name- only that
we shouldn't go into the light.
If we did, our son would be lost forever.
We're together now.
Do you see it?
It's so beautiful.
Daniel.
Come.
I can't.
I don't see it.
He needs your help.
But how? What's keeping him here?
Just listen with your heart. Ok?
You'll find the answer.
He's staying behind because of me.
I've already hurt my family so bad.
I don't want to leave and hurt you.
- Daniel, it's ok-
- It's not.
We know that now.
Look around this place.
Who's going to watch
over you in the dark?
Daniel, if you do this...
you'll be helping Becca.
You-
you'll prove to her that
there's nothing to be afraid of.
Come on, Daniel. Just try.
See the light.
For me.
Look at that.
Mom.
Dad.
I see it.
Take care of her, will you?
Yes. Yes, I will.
We want to believe you.
You have no idea how much.
But it almost seems impossible.
If you need help explaining anything...
dad...
there's someone... a man.
He's been wanting me to
tell you both something.
He's been asking for a long time.
I was scared of him at
first because he looked...
he said he died of an aneurysm.
He said you're married because of him.
She's talking about Larry.
He introduced us, but Becca, he
died before you were even born,
he wanted you guys to meet for so long.
But you guys just kept on saying no.
And he just kept saying,
Have a little faith.
what if I don't know how they died,
or what if I don't know what
it is they're really missing?
- What if it just-
- Hey, relax. Ok?
I just saw you do it.
I didn't tell you what
it was that Daniel needed.
You just listened with your heart.
Yeah.
Can I ask you something?
When you were running away, why
did you stop here, in Grandview?
I don't know, just a feeling.
The bus stopped, and
something told me to get off.
- It was just-
- something you had to do.
Yeah.
Well, you know where to find me.
I wasn't sure if
you were still in town.
Something told me you were.
Is it really worth it, Gabriel?
To break up families just
for a few extra souls?
I mean, what could you
possibly need them for?
It's not just about gaining
or losing a few extra souls.
Of course not, unless you
happen to be one of them.
As usual,
you're missing the big picture.
What is the big picture?
'Cause you're just a collector.
And please, don't stand there and pretend
like you're doing something noble.
Wait a minute.
You didn't want them, did you?
You wanted her.
That's what drew her here, the
same thing that drew you.
Please, don't do this.
You have a real choice.
You could work with me, and we can
free all of those souls down there-
sorry. I picked another horse.
He's much faster than you.
Then what are you doing here?
You're my sister.
And you have a choice too.
What does that mean?
It means don't be so sure
you have all the answers.