[ Gasping ]
[Shouting, indistinct]
Come on.
Move around towards shore.
[Scully]
Get down!
Get down
Stay down!
You're gonna keep breathing.
Do you hear me?
[ Grunting ]
I'll be right back.
Back away.
Back aw--
[Sirens Blaring]
I need an EMT in here now.
Car 39 requesting EMT.
Come on, now.
Let her through.
- Okay.
- Help me with this table.
Give her some room.
We've got paramedics on the way.
You're going to the hospital.
You're going to be okay.
We still haven't celebrated
my birthday, Pendrill.
I'm not going to let you
off the hook like this.
Let 'em through.
Let 'em through, please.
This man has a puncture wound
to his right lung. He needs
to be intubated immediately.
You got it.
He's an FBI agent,
and he's not gonna die.
Sit down.
I'm sorry.
How did they know?
When you talked
to your girlfriend,
what did you say?
- Did you tell her
you were in D.C.?
- No.
Then there's someone inside.
- [Man]...three, lift.
- [Indistinct]
- What happened?
Who shot Pendrill?
- I don't know.
I got a call
about a federal witness
being transferred.
It's Sergeant Louis Frish.
He was the intended target.
There was supposed to be
a federal marshal here...
to put the sergeant
into protective custody.
- That order was countermanded.
- By whom?
- Louis Frish is being
put under military arrest.
- Military arrest?
For suspicion of murder
and providing false testimony
in a federal investigation.
He has testimony that
is damaging to the military.
His life is in danger.
He is not going anywhere.
The order to arrest this man
came out of the Office of
the Joint Chiefs of Staff,
who have also issued
a recommendation
on Agent Mulder.
For what?
Agent Mulder's also been put
under military arrest...
on charges of interference
with a military investigation...
into a crash
of a commercial airliner.
The military is responsible
for the downing of that plane.
They are admitting as much.
Sergeant Frish's story
is not the one they're telling.
What is their story?
I have a responsibility
for the safety of the agents
under my supervision.
I'm not going to put
another agent's life in jeopardy...
just to keep her
out in the field.
I'm fine.
I suggest you make sure of that
when you go to the hospital
with Agent Pendrill.
- I came to talk to you.
- About what?
A big ol' misunderstanding?
According to the military,
there was no misunderstanding.
So all of the sudden
they just decide
to take responsibility...
for the crash of Flight 549?
They had no choice.
Not in light of all the facts
that have come out.
Facts? Have you heard
their cover story:
that the control tower
gave bad coordinates
to a fighter pilot...
causing it to collide with Flight 549
over military airspace?
They allowed me
to listen to the recordings.
If you believe
in the coordinates
that Sergeant Frish...
gave to the fighter pilot...
were the exact path
that549 was on.
Now, they would indicate
that Sergeant Frish
and his co-controller...
could not have seen
Flight 549 in the airspace
until it was too late.
So they're saying
the tower put those jets
on a collision course.
Yes. And that they were
the only two aircraft
on the radar screen.
Realizing his guilt,
Sergeant Frish's fellow
officer put a gun to his head.
According to the air force,
Sergeant Frish lied
to save himself.
When he found out
that his fellow officer
committed suicide,
he came to us
to blame the military.
That's why they pursued him,
to bring him to justice.
And they could conveniently
lay the blame on a dead man.
Yes.
This, uh, second plane,
they say it's
a military fighter?
It was an F-1 5 Eagle, according
to an air force spokesman.
You believe that story, Scully?
I don't know what to believe.
Do you believe I got this
from an F-1 5 Eagle?
Those look like radiation burns.
Where did you get that?
At the second crash site...
in about 50 feet of water
at the bottom of Sacandaga Lake.
- You found it?
- Mm-hmm. I followed
a trail of bubbles...
down to a wreckage that didn't
look like anything that might
take off from an air force base.
What was it?
What collided with Flight 549
was a UFO...
shot down by the military,
taking the passenger plane
right along with it.
Except it can't be proven.
- Why not?
- Because they haven't been able
to find any physical evidence...
that Flight 549
was involved in a collision.
- According to who?
- Mike Malar, the I.I.C., the man
running the investigation.
- How do you know he's not lying?
- I don't.
He seems to be the one man
who truly wants to figure out
what downed that plane,
and who came to me
with information
he had no reason to share.
What information?
He found Sharon Graffia
wandering in a daze
at the crash site...
the night we left
after seeing lights
over the area.
- Max Fennig's sister.
- That's another thing, Mulder.
- She's not Max Fennig's sister.
- Well, who is she?
She's an unemployed
aeronautical engineer...
who spent time in and out
of mental institutions.
That's where she met Max.
- Why would she lie?
- I don't know.
All I know is that this plane
seems to be killing people...
as it sits there
on the ground.
Mulder,
Agent Pendrill is dead.
- How?
- Shot in an attempt
on Sergeant Frish in Washington.
He saved his life, Mulder,
and maybe mine.
All right, Scully.
Scully?
Mulder, what are
these people dying for?
- Is it for the truth or for the lies?
- It's gotta be for the truth.
If we owe them anything,
it's to make sure of that.
Excuse me, sir.
Max Fennig?
- He's over there.
- Thank you.
Remember this place?
I remember being amazed
at what some people will call home.
You have to admit, the man had
an enduring sense of style.
- Only Max Fennig and you would
appreciate living like this.
- [Laughs]
# Unmarked helicopters #
# Hovering ##
I think you were actually
kindred spirits
in some deep, strange way.
What do you mean?
Men with Spartan lives,
simple in
their creature comforts,
if only to allow
for the complexity of their passions.
Mm, beans and weenies.
What exactly are we looking for
here, Mulder?
Something to explain what
Max was doing on that plane.
What he was coming to show me
or tell me.
What makes you think
that he was coming to see you?
Max is the key to all this.
He knew that plane was in danger
even before it took off,
before it entered
military airspace.
Now, how would he know that,
and what would be worth
taking that risk?
Hi. Max here,
but of course.
This is, uh,
well, quite obviously my story,
since I'm telling it.
Anyway, um, for those of you
who know me already...
this is going to be ancient
history, but for the rest of you
this is--
well, what can I say--
the story of my life.
All I ever wanted in life
was to be left alone.
[ Scoffs ]
Don't we all.
Uh, so just my luck
that I'd eventually
become an alien abductee.
Now I'm never alone. Any minute
when I'm least expecting it--
And the worst part is
no one believes you.
Oh, well, almost no one.
So, I've devoted my life
to providing all you
disbelievers with proof.
Proof that
there are extraterrestrial,
biological entities right now...
visiting our planet
in alien ships for purposes
of a troubling agenda...
known only to certain members
of government, the FBI...
and certain high-ranking members
of the military industrial
community...
who have recovered
some of these very craft.
Not that they’d ever
admit to it publicly, of course.
Nor would they admit
that they have salvaged
some of this alien technology...
and are using it
in military applications.
No, that would be un-American.
And they won't admit it until...
someone confronts them
with irrefutable,
undeniable proof.
Some one like me.
And, uh, I should probably
mention that I do this...
at great risk
to my own health and safety.
But hey, when every day's
just another day,
you're gonna get kidnapped
by a bunch of little gray dudes
from outer space,
what’s a few CIA spooks
to worry about?
[Man]
Careful.
[ Gagging ]
- [ Gasps ]
- We found it.
[Man]
Ladies and gentlemen,
recovery and identification
of the deceased victims
in Flight549...
is at 76%.
Which is far better
than anticipated,
given the kind of destruction
that we've all seen.
We've got a total
of nearly 3,000 man-hours
logged already...
in this first wave
of investigation.
And I wish I could tell
you folks that we've come up
with something more concrete.
But the evidence...
just doesn't support
anything more conclusive...
than the air force's assertion
that the cause of this crash...
was a midair collision
or a catastrophic near-miss.
I'm gonna ask you all
to wrap up your reports tonight.
And then I want you
to go home to your families.
You've done a good
and thorough job here.
You'll be in touch with me
or someone from the N.T.S.B.
on anything further.
I just wanted to thank you all
personally. Thank you.
[ Quiet Chatter]
I'd wondered
what happened to you.
- I'd put in a call.
- You had something
you wanted to tell us?
No. Just--
Just wanted to touch base.
Thank you for your help
in leading us to the fact
of the military's involvement.
I think the facts are
still a matter of speculation,
Mr. Malar.
Listening to what you just said,
I think you do too.
The military's public claim
of fault for the collision...
and their covert actions
to promote that claim
have raised some suspicions.
Suspicions? Of what?
That the story the military
is now promoting...
is a convenience deflection
and cover-up.
- Of what?
- Agent Scully and I agree
on some of the motives,
but not exactly on the facts.
- Do you have facts that I don't?
- No, but I do have a story...
if you’re willing to hear it.
Feel free to tell me it's bull,
as Agent Scully has,
but I think it's as believable
as any story I've heard.
At least it's the only one
that can't be refuted by the facts.
All right.
There was one man who knew
what brought this plane down.
And he knew it even before
he got on the plane,
but he got on anyway.
He sat right here
in this seat, 1 3-F.
His name was Max Fennig.
There are
a number of possibilities
for Max's suspicions,
but I believe Max had been
followed for some time
before he boarded Flight 549.
And I believe he was followed
onto this plane...
by someone who wanted
whatever it is Max had carried
onboard with him.
The object that ultimately
brought down this plane,
the cause which
has alluded you.
And what was this object?
Physical proof of the existence
of extraterrestrial life
and intelligence.
The person who followed Max
on the plane...
may have been prepared to kill
to obtain this object.
Its value
greater than one human life,
greater than the lives
of the 134people on that plane.
Whether that plan was executed,
we may never know.
Because Flight549
was intercepted by a second aircraft,
an aircraft which did not appear
on the military's
or anyone else's radar screen.
What the hell is this?
Max Fennig knew immediately
what this craft was,
and that he would not
be completing the rest
of the flight as scheduled.
[Woman, Screaming]
Max would have recognized
immediately all the signs
of an abduction scenario:;
the craft taking control
of the plane and all its systems,
preparing to take Max.
But something happened.
- Something went terribly wrong.
Something unimaginable.
- Okay.
A third aircraft,
probably an F-1 5 Eagle,
was given the coordinates
for Flight 549.
- Heading one-zero-zero
and two-niner thousand feet.
- Go ahead.
The flight controllers
watched the fighter enter...
Flight549'sairspace
on an intercept pattern,
not knowing what
they had set in motion.
No way of knowing
there was a third craft
which was not on their screen.
Not knowing that for the next
nine minutes, time would
standstill on Flight549.
- [ Controls Beeping ]
- I've got something. An intercept.
My God! My God!
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
[ Passengers Screaming ]
[ Clicks ]
You're saying the man
who was sitting in seat 1 3-F
was abducted, mid-flight,
without any depressurization
of the cabin,
without any effect
on the plane?
If not for factors unforeseen,
I believe Max Fennig
would have been abducted...
and returned to Flight 549
without any loss of life,
without a trace.
Then what happened?
Flight549andthealien craft
which had taken control fit...
were intercepted...
by the military fighter
which had been given a specific
set of orders:;
to take down the UFO.
The missing nine minutes
aboardFlight549,
nine minutes that
would have been erased
from the memories...
of the 134passengers
onboard,
would prove to be the final
minutes of their lives.
[passengers Screaming]
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
You're saying, in effect,
that Flight 549...
was in a group of a sort
of UFO tractor beam?
That's a Hollywood term,
but yes.
And the air force
shot down the UFO,
thereby sending 549
out of control
when the beam went off?
Yes.
Well, where I come from,
that's what we call a whopper.
Even if it were true,
I could never in a million years
sell that to Washington,
and neither could you.
Not without the object
that Max Fennig was carrying.
Look, I-I had the same
reaction to the story as you,
but there is one logical area
that has yet to be explained.
That is that the seats
and the door...
did show
traces of radioactivity.
Now, you found nothing
in the wreckage,
no source of any emitter?
I did find something.
I think
you should look at it.
After you’d found
the first traces, I had my team
see of they could...
link the radioactivity
to a cause.
They found no other evidence.
Except for this.
- That's it?
- That's all there was.
I'm gonna have to make
my final report.
I'll include this.
- But not as a causal factor.
- It's a good story.
Maybe you can sell it
to the movies.
- Mulder, I don't know
what else you expect him to do.
- Yeah, I know.
Look, it is a good story,
but it's a house of cards
built on a shaky foundation.
You may never know
what Max was carrying.
And we may never know
who killed Agent Pendrill.
If we don't find out,
what meaning do their
deaths have or their lives?
Max will be remembered
as a...
disappointing rummage sale
or some kook on a home video.
- Where do we even start?
- How about Sharon Graffia?
She's a disturbed person,
Mulder. She wasn't even
who she claimed to be.
Yeah, but she knew Max
well enough for him to write her
thousands of letters.
Well enough for him to call her
and tell her he was gonna die.
Do you know where she is?
In a mental institution.
- I'd go with ya, but I'm afraid
they'd lock me up.
- Me too.
####[Rock]
## Unmarked helicopters
hovering##
- ####[Continues]
- [Man]Hello.
Are you a friend of Max's?
- ## [ Stops ]
- No. My name is, uh, Mulder.
I'm with the FBI.
- You're kiddin', right?
- No. Why?
Well, I manage the park.
I know Max had
some weird friends.
And I don't believe the FBI
sends men out 'cause
somebody trashed a trailer.
Any idea who did this?
Uh, no.
Is Max in trouble or something?
No. Max is dead.
He died in a plane crash
a few days ago.
Oh, Lord.
I am sorry to hear that.
Uh, did he ever mention
why he would leave
or where he would go?
No, but he disappeared
sometimes.
Had stories.
- You're sure that's
not what happened to him?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm sure.
Have you any idea
who's going to be taking care
of his estate?
- Where I should
forward his mail?
- Oh, he has mail?
Yeah, small stack of it.
I'll run and get it,
if you want it.
Please.
Here you go.
Sure feel sorry about Max.
So do l.
- Sharon?
- Hello.
How are you feeling?
You up to answering
some questions?
I'm not Max's sister.
I know.
We're not quite sure why
you lied to us though, Sharon.
Or what else
you might be lying about.
- Doesn't matter anymore.
- Yes, it does.
about what he was carrying
on that plane,
it could matter a lot.
- To who?
- To Max.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Because I could be
in big, big trouble.
Max had those same blisters.
You both were exposed
to something, Sharon.
What was it?
It was something I stole.
From whom?
Max was trying to find physical
evidence to prove the stories
about his abductions were true.
You worked as an
aeronautical systems engineer.
You stole something
from your employer,
didn’t you, Sharon?
Something radioactive.
Only because
I believed in Max.
What was it?
Max said it was
alien technology.
It was three
interlocking parts.
We divided into sections.
I had one part.
Max had another
on board that flight.
But they were taken from us.
There was a third part.
What happened to it?
I left a bag here.
- Big bag, little bag?
- Short bag, tall bag.
I don't remember.
Little bag, I think.
He's at the baggage claim.
Is this it?
I'm a federal officer.
I need a security entrance
to the terminal.
Right this way.
- Tell me, is your wife
going to be with you?
- No, I'm going alone.
[Cell phone Ringing]
Mulder.
Mulder, it's me.
Where are you?
I'm at the airport
in Syracuse, New York.
Whatever it is that Max had,
I have it now.
- How did you find it?
- Luck.
What you’re carrying was stolen
from a military contractor,
Cummins Aerospace.
- Well, what is it?
- I don't know.
I'm going to let you know
in a minute.
It is extremely important
that you do not take it
out of its container.
What's that?
I'm having trouble hearing
you on the phone.
- Did you hear what I said?
- No. Hold on. I'm going
to tell you what it looks like.
No, no, no.
Mulder, listen to me.
Do not handle it.
Whatever it is,
it is highly radioactive.
Hold on a second.
- [ Static ]
- Mulder?
[ Beeping ]
It looks like
a small superstructure...
with three circular pieces
inside.
It's hard to tell on an X ray.
Hold on.
I think what we've got here,
Mulder, is high tech
industrial espionage.
More people are trying to get
their hands on this thing
than a Tickle Me Elmo doll.
- I'm getting on a flight.
- What flight number?
I think it's 501 .
Yeah. I'm gonna need a ride
when I get there.
I don't think
that will be a problem, Mulder.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
You look like you’ve
got some room here.
Do you mind?
No. Go ahead.
Didn't mean to disturb you.
It's all right.
You traveling by yourself?
Do you live in D.C.?
There's a weapon
pointed at you right now.
I'm pretty sure at this range
it wouldn't just hit you in the leg.
If you so much as raise
your arms off your armrest,
I'm gonna test that theory.
- What if you miss?
- I won't.
Do you know what happens
when a plane...
suddenly depressurizes
at 30,000 feet, Mr. Mulder?
After the cabin fills with fog,
all light objects,
anything not tied down--
and including your weapon--
go flying toward the breach.
The pretty lady comes around
with the honey-roasted peanuts?
Presuming the pilot
is even able to keep control
of the plane,
I put on a lightweight
parachute I just stowed
in the overhead bin...
and go out
the emergency exit...
with the knapsack
you're holding.
What if the pilot
can't get control of the plane?
Then you die too.
A man, if he’s any man at all,
knows he must be ready
to sacrifice himself...
to that which is greater
than he.
I'm sure all the other
passengers on this plane...
would appreciate dying
for your noble philosophy.
Look out your window,
Agent Mulder.
You see the lights?
Now, imagine if one of
those lights flickered off.
You'd hardly notice,
would you?
A dozen, two dozen lights
extinguished.
Is it worth
sacrificing the future,
the lives of millions,
to keep a few lights on?
What is this?
Stolen property.
It's an alien energy source,
isn't it?
What is it, cold fusion,
over-unity energy?
What could be worth
killing all those passengers
on Flight 549?
The cause of that crash
has been determined
as human error.
And I'm gonna see you
pay for that error,
along with you and your employer
and the government
that finances its contracts.
Now, I want you to stand up
very slowly and move
to the back of the plane.
We're gonna go
to the bathroom.
Move.
[Cell phone Ringing]
- [ Beeps ]
- Scully.
- Hey, Scully. It's me.
- Mulder, where are you?
I'm standing outside
an airplane bathroom...
where I've got the man
who shot Pendrill locked up.
- What?
- It looks like I'm gonna miss
the in-flight movie.
It was something starring
Steve Guttenberg.
Mulder, did you get on
the flight that you said
you were getting on?
Yeah. Everything's going
according to plan.
I think you should
alert Skinner anyway.
I don't want to take any chances
getting this guy off the plane.
- I don't think you do either.
- Right.
- Hey, Scully.
My watch just stopped.
- Yeah?
What? Mulder?
Mulder?
Excuse me.
I'm a federal agent.
I want you to listen to me
very carefully. This plane is
about to be intercepted.
- Intercepted?
- Intercepted, engaged
and boarded.
I want you to tell the captain
to initiate evasive maneuvers
immediately.
put the bag down!
[ Passengers Screaming ]
Put it down on the floor.
[ All Screaming ]
Drop the bag!
Drop the bag.
Drop it!
Hey, let it go!
Let it go!
Mulder, where is he?
He's not here.
What do you mean?
You said you had him
on this plane. You said
you had what Max Fennig had.
The stolen part.
What time do you have?
1 0:56.
Would you like to tell me
what's going on here,
Agent Mulder?
I don't think you want
to know the answer.
- [ Sighs ]
- Is this man on the plane?
I think he got
the connecting flight.
[Max]
But nobody ever finds out about it.
There are scientists in Finland
right now who say they have
detected antigravity...
over the surface of a spinning
superconducting disk.
Technology that is supposedly
20 or 30 years down the road,
like over-unity energy.
Um, massless displacement
current from cold fusion
we need for space travel.
I know,
thanks to my inside sources,
that this technology,
in fact, exists.
I've seen military aircraft
that use it hovering
right over my trailer.
Why is the U.S. Government
keeping all this a secret?
I intend to expose
these facts to the people.
I mean, I'm just one man.
These tapes,
you don't mind if I keep them?
No. I think you should
consider yourself the sole curator...
of the Max Fennig Rolling
Multimedia Library and Archive.
You should probably
get tax-exempt status
as soon as you can.
This stuff could be
worth something someday.
I wanna thank you
for helping me out,
for all you've done.
Max would have
wanted it that way.
You lost somebody
very close to you.
So did you.
You thinking
about Pendrill?
I realized I didn't even
know his first name.
I actually
was thinking about, uh,
this gift that you gave me
for my birthday.
You never got to tell me
why you gave it to me
or what it means.
But I think I know.
I think that you appreciated
that there are extraordinary
men and women...
and extraordinary moments...
when history leaps forward
on the backs
of these individuals.
That what can be imagined
can be achieved.
That you must dare to dream.
But that there's no substitute
for perseverance and hard work...
and teamwork.
Because no one gets there alone.
And that while we commemorate
the-the greatness of these events...
and the individuals
who achieve them,
we cannot forget
the sacrifice of those...
who make these achievements
and leaps possible.
I just thought it was
a pretty cool key chain.
Subrip by drEAmEr(C)