- [ Beeping ]
- [Chattering]
Cover for me in case dork face
comes back around, will you ?
- Where are you going ?
- I need a cigarette.
- You had one 1 5 minutes ago.
- Forty-five minutes.
- Why don’t you get yourself one
of those patches or that gum ?
- What do you think I'm chewing ?
Then maybe you should just quit.
Ever think of that ?
Look, just cover for me, okay ?
Tell her I got a stomach bug
or somethin'.
[Woman Over p.A. Chattering]
[ Gasps, Screams ]
Thank you.
Jane, come on.
You're gonna get in trouble.
Jane ?
Hey, Jane.
[ Screaming ]
[Computer Keys Clicking]
[ Dial Tone ]
[Television Announcer]
Number51 of the Bulldogs
has just fouled out.
They lead with 4:50 left
in the second half,
Citadel on top of Eli,
83-76.
They're gonna miss--
[ Static ] this rebound.
I'll tell you that.
[Television Announcer Continues]
[ Grunts ]
[Keys Jangling]
[ Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
" Brody, Jane L."
Yeah, we've got
the pathologist's work,
but the techs haven't gone
over the crime scene yet.
- Let me see what you got.
- Your name ?
- Special Agent Fox Mulder.
- Workin' the late shift,
Agent Mulder ?
- Special Agent Fox Mulder.
- Workin' the late shift,
Agent Mulder ?
- Yeah. Somebody's got to.
- You need to sign that.
- I'm all set here.
- Finished ?
- Yeah. Thanks.
- No problem.
[ Chattering ]
Agent Mulder!
- I'm glad I caught ya.
- Who are you ?
Detective Thomas--
Ray Thomas.
I'm the one who contacted you,
who E-mailed the pictures
to your office.
I ran into Officer Robbins.
He said you'd come down here...
- to take a look at some
of the forensic evidence.
- That's right.
So, uh, does that mean
you think you’ve found
something here ?
- Something worth lookin' into ?
- I'm afraid not.
- No ?
- I didn't find anything
to recommend...
- my further involvement
in this case.
- What about the woman ?
How do you explain
what happened to her ?
She walks into a bathroom.
A minute later, she turns up--
Look, you saw the pictures.
I saw 'em.
I was told you were part
of something called the X-Files.
You'd look into stuff like this.
So if there’s really nothin'
to this, why come all the way
down here middle of the night ?
I'm just doin' my job,
Detective, same as you.
- Ah, you are home.
- Yeah. What are you doin' here ?
- I was tryin' to reach you.
Think your phone's off the hook.
- Well, I needed some sleep.
Is that why you’re takin'
the garbage out
at 4:00 in the morning ?
- What do you want, Agent Mulder ?
- I want some answers.
- Concerning ?
- The unexplained death
of a postal worker...
that somebody has apparently
gone to great lengths
to keep unexplained.
These photos were sent to me by
a detective who thought I might
have a fresh take on the case.
But when I went to retrieve them
from my E-mail, somebody had
hollowed out the files.
Then where'd you get 'em ?
- From his partner.
- When ?
After he finished questioning me
about the detective's death.
What ?
What are you talking about ?
He was killed, shot in the head,
execution style.
His body was found
near the precinct two hours ago.
possibly by the same person who
forged my name to gain access...
- to evidence
from the forensics lab.
- What do you want from me ?
- Well, I'd like your help on this, sir.
- What about Agent Scully ?
Agent Scully's in the hospital.
Has something happened
that I should know about ?
She's undergoing
some imaging tests.
Her oncologist was concerned
about some microscopy results,
that, uh, her tumor
may be metastasizing.
Anyway, I-I'd like you to take
a look at those photos, please.
Yeah, I will,
first thing in the morning.
You want me to, uh,
dump this on my way out ?
No, I got it.
[ Sighs ]
[Tires Screeching]
Was it you ?
Did you pull the trigger,
or did you have him
do it for you ?
- I'm not here
to answer your questions.
- You murdered him !
- You killed an officer of the law.
- Keep your voice down,
unless you want your neighbors
to know the hours
and the company you keep.
I won't be a party
to murder.
I wouldn't get too comfortable
on your moral high ground,
Mr. Skinner.
This only happened because
you left your job unfinished.
I handled him just like
I've handled everything else
you've asked me to do.
I've followed
your instructions.
You failed to neutralize
a potentially
compromising situation.
You didn't have to kill him.
He didn't have to die.
You're in no position
to question the terms
of our arrangement.
Then we have no arrangement.
- You'll find it's not that easy
to walk away from, Mr. Skinner.
- No ?
A man digs a hole,
he risks falling into it.
[phone Ringing]
- Skinner.
- Her body's gone, sir.
- What are you talking about ?
- The postal worker
and the photos I gave you.
Her body was stolen
from the morgue last night,
along with any other
evidence that might explain
how or why she died.
- Slow down, Agent Mulder.
- I'm sorry, but I can't.
I'm playing catch up here,
and I'm already two steps behind.
The man who impersonated me
at the forensics lab last night--
- apparently he replaced
a blood sample.
- How do you know ?
I had them run a test.
The blood sample in
the police forensics lab...
is B-positive,
as is the postal worker's.
She suffered from a mild
form of anemia characterized
by folic acid deficiency.
The blood sample
at the police forensics lab has
a normal folate serum level.
Are there any suspects ?
No, but I do have
a place to start.
The gun that killed
Detective Thomas--
ballistics has identified it
as a Sig Sauer P-228.
I'm having ballistics run comps
on all weapons...
registered to federal agents
and local officers.
- Sir ?
- Let me know what they find.
I will.
[Ringing]
- Yes.
- You can't do this.
- You sound agitated, Mr. Skinner.
- Was it my gun ?
- Your gun ?
- Used to kill the detective.
Well, if it was, I'd think
you'd want to report it
to the police immediately.
- Oh, don't think I won't.
- Then why are you calling me ?
Perhaps because you realized
that you’d be admitting
to the obstruction of justice,
criminal conspiracy
and destruction of evidence.
The consequences can be
very serious for you,
even in the unlikely event
that you were able to persuade
the authorities...
that you didn't kill
the detective.
What did you have me cover up ?
I think the less you know, the better,
under the circumstances.
I need to know
what that man died for.
He died for you, Mr. Skinner.
He died so you could have
what you wanted.
A cure for Agent Scully.
Isn't that what you want ?
Agent Scully
is in the hospital.
If you can do anything for her,
I want it done now.
I'm fully aware
of Agent Scully's progress.
If anything happens to her,
I will expose you.
I'll turn state's evidence.
I don't care
what happens to me.
Agent Scully stands to live
a long and healthy life.
I would hope the same
for you, Mr. Skinner.
[ Line Clicks, Dial Tone ]
Right in here.
The police said we could put
the bathroom back in service.
But the truth is,
no one wants to use it,
not after what happened
yesterday.
You mind my asking
what you’re looking for?
I need a hammer.
Is there any reason
you're not running this
through the FBI lab ?
This evidence is classified.
We've had some controversy
over security at the Bureau.
- I'd appreciate your discretion.
- Certainly.
Can you tell what kind
of bees made that ?
Oh, it's hard to tell with
just the comb, but I might
be able to give you an answer.
If I told you there was a chance
the bees that made that could be
lethal, would that be helpful ?
Any kind of bee can be lethal,
provided you get stung
by enough of them.
Even Africanized honey bees--
so-called killer bees--
basically have the same venom
as the European honeybee.
It’s just that they tend
to attack in swarms.
- Huh, you may be in luck.
- What is it ?
Royal jelly--
a highly nutritious secretion...
of the honeybee's
pharyngeal gland.
It's fed to the very young
larvae in a colony.
Here, see for yourself.
- Is that gonna hatch ?
- Once they pupate, I should
be able to give you...
some definitive answers.
The minute you learn something,
I'd appreciate a call.
Is this related
to that other case ?
- If you don't mind my asking ?
- What other case ?
I got a call from another agent
about six months ago,
asking me all about killer bees.
- Who was it ?
- Uh, name was Fox Mulder.
- I wonder if there’s
any connection.
- No.
Anyway, I'll call you.
Sir? You looking for me ?
I was just writing you a note.
- Where have you been ?
- First Nations Bank of Virginia.
- What am I looking at ?
- The bank is adjacent...
to the police headquarters
where the detective was killed.
Their parking lot surveillance
camera caught this image.
That man there ?
That's Detective Thomas.
This man in the baseball hat--
he was identified...
by the officer on duty at
the forensics lab as "Agent Mulder."
Can you get
a usable image off this ?
I'm going to hand-deliver it
over to Special Photo right now.
What did you want
to talk to me about ?
You were writing me a note.
I was, uh, I was just checking
on your progress.
Ms. Covarrubias ? This is
Walter Skinner-- an assistant
director at the FBI.
- Yes ?
- I was hoping you could help me.
I understand Agent Fox Mulder
has been in contact with you
about a project.
- A project ?
- A Canadian agricultural project
involving bees or bee husbandry.
Yes, but I wasn't able
to give him any information.
- Why was that ?
- The project he cited turned
up no viable evidence.
- Evidence of what ?
- Bee hives or bee husbandry.
What if I told you
I had access to that evidence ?
You have access
to these bees ?
I may. Soon.
Very soon.
[ Screaming, Groaning ]
[ Continues Screaming ]
- Agent Mulder ?
- Thanks for gettin'
down here so quickly.
- What is it ?
- A break. Maybe even a lead.
I wanted you to get a look
at this body before
somebody tried to steal it.
See these pocks and blisters ?
They're the same as we saw
on the photo of the deceased
postal worker.
- Symptoms of what ?
- Smallpox.
The first reported case
in over seven years.
[ Sighs ]
Smallpox ?
According to the coroner,
an especially virulent strain,
caused by a mutated
variola virus.
Caused how ?
I mean, how could this man...
have contracted a disease that
doesn't even exist anymore ?
From these.
- What are they ?
- Bee stingers and venom sacs...
recovered subcutaneously from
the victim 's face, arm and neck.
You're saying this man was stung
by bees carrying smallpox ?
He was a forensic entomologist.
I consulted with him
several months ago...
- about a similar fatality.
- Then you've seen this before ?
Yeah, but I've never had
any hard evidence.
Not until now.
I think that's what somebody's gone
to great lengths to try to prevent.
- Why ?
- I can only guess.
But I think that somebody is trying
to engineer a method of delivery...
for a disease that has killed
more people throughout history...
than any other contagion
known to humankind.
- If you want me to suggest
an appropriate response, I will.
- Can they be stopped ?
How can we stop them ?
We don't even know
who these people are.
And we won't until we know
the identity of that shooter.
- How close are you ?
- Hopefully, very.
I've got one of the photo techs
pulling an all-nighter
on that surveillance video,
so he can show me
something this morning.
- I told him that you’d
authorize the overtime.
- Of course.
I'm gonna go over there
right now.
Tell me what you find.
[Man]
Oh, sure. See you tomorrow.
Just grabbin' a cup of coffee.
Misty Nagatta ?
My name is Walter Skinner.
I was just getting up.
They only give us a ten-minute break,
and my supervisor's pretty strict.
I need to talk to you, Misty.
- About your coworker.
- If this is about
what happened to Jane,
I already told the police
everything I know.
Everything ?
- I don't wanna lose my job.
- You're not gonna lose anything.
I'm asking you to cooperate
in a criminal investigation.
Jane ? What do you mean ?
-Jane's death may not
have been an accident.
- What ?
She was my best friend.
I'm sorry.
We worked it out so that
our vacations overlapped.
We were going to Palm Beach.
Both of us were tryin'
to lose weight,
so we could buy
new bathing suits.
The men who came here--
they said if I talked to anyone,
I'd lose my job.
Did these men say
who they were ?
No, and I didn't ask.
They just wanted the package.
- What package ?
- Damaged packages are
routed here for inspection,
before they get reshipped.
The place where these
damaged packages are kept--
how close is it to the restroom
where you found Jane ?
It’s just the next door down the hall.
They've got a storage room.
The damaged package
that they wanted--
- do you remember
where it was being sent ?
- No, not offhand.
- Is there anyway of finding out ?
- I can look up the tracking number.
That would be
a big help to me, Misty.
And maybe to Jane.
We went through every inch
of that tape...
to find the best angle
for identification purposes.
Now, remember, it was
videotape shot at a distance
under extreme low light.
So this is the best
you could do ?
It's better than I thought
it would be, believe me.
I tried every trick that--
I'm not trying to be difficult.
This is very important to me.
I need to be sure.
I need you to print out
a hard copy of that for me.
This is the last
remaining specimen.
The bees from the scientist's house--
they've been contained and destroyed.
And the body ?
It also has been sanitized.
How did this happen ?
It's been taken care of.
The details are unimportant.
Details are everything--
much more important
than your vague assurances.
Well, you'll have to trust
my assurance that any other
breaches have been handled.
Handled by whom ?
I have a man in place--
a man with no other choice
but to succeed.
What assurance can you give us
that he can be trusted ?
We can't risk
even the slightest exposure.
He has nothing to expose,
except his own duplicity.
Should we assume that the trial run
is proceeding as planned ?
It's already begun.
[ Chattering, Laughing ]
[ Bee Buzzing ]
- Hey, it's my turn.
- No, it isn't.
Ow ! Ow ! Ah.
[ Buzzing Continues ]
Mrs. Kemper !
Billy got stung by a bee !
Mrs. Kemper!
- [ Bees Buzzing ]
- [Children Screaming]
Everyone ! Everyone, inside !
Inside ! Move it, move it !
Come on, inside !
[ Screaming Continues ]
David!
[Yells]
Oh, my God! David!
David, come on!
Quick! Come on! Run !
[ Screaming ]
[ Continues Screaming ]
- [Machines Beeping]
- [Woman Crying]
Oh, God.
- I'm sorry.
- [Girl] please help me.
- Dr. Linzer ?
My name's Walter Skinner.
- All right, thank you.
The administration office
informed me you’re overseeing
the treatment of these children.
- Yes.
- I think you’ll want
to hear me out.
- I'm right in the middle of it.
- If you’ve been treating
these children for bee stings,
-you've misdiagnosed them.
- Then what should I be
treating them for ?
- Smallpox.
- Is this a joke ?
Every child in this town
who hasn't already been infected...
needs to be vaccinated
immediately.
We don't vaccinate kids
against smallpox anymore
because there is no smallpox.
- Run whatever tests you need
if you don't believe me.
- I don't need to run any tests.
Smallpox has an eight-day
incubation period, and these
kids were stung a few hours ago.
- How do you reconcile that ?
- I can't.
[Shouting]
- [ Chattering ]
- Excuse me.
Let me know when you
come up with an answer.
In the meantime,
I've got things to do.
- Doctor !
- Mr. Skinner?
- How do you know who I am ?
- Because you contacted me.
I'm Marita Covarrubias.
- What are you doing here ?
- Your call about those bees
prompted me to make inquiries.
- Into what ?
- Seven packages that
were sent from Canada...
to a P.O. Box
in Payson, South Carolina.
I came here to find out
what was in those packages.
You're a little late
to do anything about it.
So are you, apparently.
What brought you here ?
You came to me for information,
Mr. Skinner,
but you still haven't told me
what you know about this.
My office has to answer
to the Secretary General
of the United Nations.
This is a very serious matter.
I need to know what's going on.
I think it's some kind
of experiment.
- An experiment ?
- Using bees as carriers.
And that's what
was in those packages ?
- Have you told Agent Mulder this ?
- Not yet.
- Why not ?
- I can't.
Why ?
- Are you involved in this,
- Mr. Skinner ?
I didn't--
- No, I'm not involved.
- Then what are you doing here ?
- What aren’t you telling me,
Mr. Skinner ?
- Nothing.
If you know who's behind this,
you have to come forward,
Mr. Skinner. No one else can.
Put the gun down
and move away from the desk.
- I was just calling--
- I said put the gun down !
[ Sighs ]
You don't understand.
- No. I do now.
- No, you don't.
- Is that the gun you used
to shoot the detective ?
- No.
- How does it feel to shoot
an innocent man in the head ?
- I didn't kill him !
You're a liar !
You've been working
with the Smoking Man all along.
You knew when he had
my father killed, and you knew
when they took Scully.
- Listen to me.
- I've heard enough of you.
He set me up !
He stole my gun !
Then he put it back.
Which means the police are
probably on their way right now.
- I don't believe you.
- Look at my desk drawer,
Agent Mulder.
Look at it !
Why would I force my own lock ?
If I lied to you--
I have lied to you, and I won't
make excuses for those lies.
But there's a reason
I did what I did--
one that I think you’re in
a unique position to understand.
I advised you against a certain
course of action some time ago...
concerning Agent Scully.
I didn't follow my own advice.
Give me the gun.
How soon will you be able to
determine if that’s the weapon
that killed Detective Thomas ?
As long as it takes me
to put one of these slugs
into a scope and run a comp.
This is the slug we recovered
from the detective's body.
You see this stria
here and here ?
They're rifling patterns,
imprinted from the barrel
of the same gun.
So this is definitely
the murder weapon ?
If I were called to testify,
I’d say without a doubt.
So where'd you find it ?
In a sewer grate,
around the corner
from the crime scene.
- Mm.
- Sometimes you get lucky.
- Sometimes you don't, right ?
- What do you mean ?
The serial number--
it's been filed clean off.
Now, unless forensics pulled a print,
this gun's virtually untraceable.
[Skinner]
Leave it off.
I'm starting to get used
to the dark.
- Is this part of our deal ?
- We never had a deal.
- No ?
- Agent Scully is dying,
and you haven't done a thing.
- You think that's funny ?
-Just enjoying the irony,
Mr. Skinner.
Only yesterday you said
you wouldn't be party to murder.
And now here you are.
Yours isn't the first gun
I've had pointed in my face,
Mr. Skinner.
I'm not afraid to die.
But if you kill me now,
you'll also kill Agent Scully.
You have no intention
of saving her. You never did.
Are you certain ?
I saved her life once before
when I had her returned
to Agent Mulder.
I may save her life again.
But you’ll never know if you
pull the trigger, will you ?
[phone Ringing]
Now, unless you intend to kill me,
I'd like to answer my phone.
[Ringing Continues]
[ Ringing Continues ]
Yes.
He was just here.
He threatened to kill me.
I'm sure Mulder
will be contacting you.
He'll want to know if Skinner
has seen all there is to see.
I'll tell him what
you want me to tell him.
Tell him
what he wants to hear.
Subrip by drEAmEr(C)