-[Distorted Voices Arguing]
- Fox.
- Wake up. Fox.
- Samantha?
Shh. They'll hear you.
[Woman Crying]
No... she's my child.
Shh.
[Woman]
No!
[Woman Crying]
- [ Yelling, indistinct ]
- No!
[Woman Crying, Distorted]
That's my baby!
Get away!
I'm afraid, Fox.
I'm afraid.
[ Ringing ]
Hello?
- Scully.
- Mulder, what time is it?
I don't know.
It's almost 5:00 a.m.
Is something wrong?
- I think so.
- Where are you?
I think I'm in a motel room
in Providence, but--
- Where?
- Rhode Island.
What are you doing there?
I don't know. There's--
There's blood all over me.
- Are you hurt, Mulder?
- I don't think so.
I don't think it's my blood.
Mulder?
[Water Running]
- Mulder?
- Yeah?
You okay?
I can't get warm.
You're in shock.
Dry yourself off.
I'll get you a blanket.
- Do you feel sick?
- Nah.
Nauseous or dizzy?
No, but I woke up on the floor
with a pounding headache.
- Were you here alone?
- I think so.
I don't know.
I don't remember... anything.
Track my finger.
- Do you know what day it is?
- Uh--
- [ Exhales Deeply] No, what day is it?
- It's Sunday.
What's the last thing
that you remember?
I was in my apartment.
I talked to you on the phone.
- That was Friday.
- I've been here since Friday?
I don't know, but you packed a bag.
There's a change of clothes in there.
[ Shivers ]
Do you feel any pain?
- Did you receive a blow to your head?
- No. No.
- Did you take anything, Mulder?
- Are you sure you didn't cut yourself?
- Yeah.
Where's your weapon?
I don't know.
Two rounds have been fired.
I don't remember that.
Mulder, I need to
get you to a hospital.
You have to be examined
by a neurologist.
You have had a serious
cerebral event.
It could be a viral infection or
the early stages of encephalitis.
If there was a crime committed,
I need to know what happened.
Mulder, the first thing that you need
to do is to take care of yourself.
Mulder, listen to me.
We are going
to figure this out,
but first we have
to determine the cause.
You cannot take something
like this lightly.
If this is an aneurysm,
it could drop you in a second.
- Are these your keys?
- No.
You checked in alone
around noon on Saturday.
The manager's got no record of any phone
calls made from the room. No visitors.
Then how did I get here?
You drove.
He's got a license number
of a car registered.
- Do you have those keys you found?
- That's not my car.
There's blood
on the steering wheel, Mulder.
The car is registered
under a David Cassandra.
- The address is here in Providence.
- Who's Amy?
That's what I'm gonna find out, Mulder,
but first I'm gonna check you out...
because you have no business
even walking around here.
No. If I've shot someone, if my weapon's
been used in a crime, I need to know.
You are taking a big risk.
I feel strongly about this.
I know you do,
but it's my risk.
- Can I help you?
- Are you Amy?
No, she's not here right now.
- Is this David Cassandra's house?
- This is David and Amy's house.
- And who are you?
- I'm the housekeeper.
- Who are you?
- We're with the F.B.I.
- Why do you have Amy's keys?
-[Scully]possibly.
- Is Amy or David reachable?
- They're out. I don't know where.
That painting
behind you--
Do you think I could
take a look at it?
Yeah.
Who painted this?
Amy.
-[Scully]Mulder, what's up?
- I know this house.
- How?
- I've seen it before.
Does this house have
any special meaning to Amy or David?
It's her favorite subject.
It's the house she grew up in.
Actually,
it's all she paints.
I've been to that house.
When?
I don't know,
but I've been there.
[Scully]Do you know
anything else about this house?
-[Housekeeper]It's out in Chepachet.
- Where's that?
It's about 20 miles from here
on Route 8.
My parents had a summerhouse
out there when I was a kid.
If you’ve been here, Mulder,
I don't think it was recently.
The place looks abandoned
and completely overgrown.
- [ Gasps ]
- Mulder?
Mulder?
Can you hear me?
- Mulder? Mulder? Mulder? Mulder?
- [ Groaning ]
[Couple Arguing]
[Arguing Continues]
You're a little spy.
[Woman]
No! No!
[Scully]
Mulder?
Mulder, can you hear me?
- What happened?
- I don't know. It just hit me.
You fell to your knees and grabbed your
head like you were in terrible pain.
You were completely
no responsive.
- Do you remember any of that?
- No.
- I remember what I saw.
- What do you mean?
I had a very vivid flashback
to my childhood,
except I was there.
- Do you remember anything else?
- No, just that it was very real.
Your heart is racing.
What do you think it was?
It was some kind of seizure, some kind
of acute physiological disturbance.
I couldn't tell if you
lost consciousness,
but it was definitely
some kind of clonic event.
Kind of an electrical
storm in the brain.
Brought on by what?
That's what a specialist
is gonna have to tell you.
I feel really good right now.
Mulder,
you are not really good.
I think I've
been here before.
- In your childhood?
- Maybe.
I don't think anybody's
lived here in a long time.
I'm gonna check upstairs.
Mulder.
There's a gunshot wound
to her heart.
This must be
Amy Cassandra...
and her husband.
They'd like to ask you some questions.
I told them about your condition.
- You don't have to speak to them.
- You mean not without my attorney?
Mulder, I refuse to believe
you had any part in this.
I had those people's blood
on my shirt, Scully.
I was missing for two days.
I have no recollection of my actions.
There were two rounds
discharged from my gun.
I had the keys to this house,
the keys to their car.
Do the words "Orenthal James Simpson"
mean anything to you?
How you feeling,
Agent Mulder?
I'm a little confused.
Your partner here says you're suffering
from somekind of a seizure,
that you had one
right here in the yard.
What brought you to this
house, Agent Mulder?
I don't know.
- I think I may have come here as a kid.
- You think?
My parents had a summerhouse
in Quonochontaug, so--
But you don't know anything about
David or Amy Cassandra, the victims?
I don't ever remember
meeting them, no.
So you're saying
the first time you saw them...
is when you walked in this house, using
their keys and found them on the floor?
That's what I'm saying.
We got plenty of prints in that house,
some with blood on them.
We're gonna run those prints,
Agent Mulder.
Is that the story you want
to stick with?
For now.
Would you like to come down to the
station and elaborate on that statement?
Agent Mulder's not going
anywhere but to a hospital.
Okay... but we're all
going down there together.
Agent Mulder, I'd like you
to ride with us.
Mulder, I'd advise you
not to say anything more,
not until I take a look at those bodies
and the forensics reports.
Amy Anne Cassandra,
caucasian female.
Birth records indicate
her age at 62 years.
The subject is 1 65 pounds,
67 inches in height.
Preliminary exam indicates cause of
death due to a gunshot wound to chest.
Powder burns and flashing
at the point of entry...
approximately four inches
below the clavicle,
indicating the shot was delivered
at point-blank range.
Dorsal beveling of the shoulder blade
is visible at the exit wound.
The surrounding tissue
is jagged and torn.
- No other signs of trauma present.
- Did you see this?
Yeah, from the scabbing,
it looks like a preexisting,
-superficial puncture wound.
- Do you mind?
- What are you looking for?
- I'm not sure.
Do you have a magnifying glass?
Thanks.
I want to make sure that
in addition to the autopsy,
you also do a craniotomy
and a histological examination.
- It's clear what killed these people.
- I think it is too,
but what I'm more interested in
right now is why they died.
[Door Opens]
What's that?
Have you jogged your memory, Agent
Mulder? You want to change your story?
No. Why?
Because I have evidence here that
contradicts what it is you've told us.
I haven't really
told you anything.
You told us you haven't been
to that house since your childhood...
and that you didn't know
Amy or David Cassandra.
And you're telling me that what's
in that bag is evidence that I'm a liar?
I'm not saying
you're a liar, Agent Mulder.
I would like to believe
this memory lapse was real...
and you murdered these two people
in some fit of blind insanity.
- What's in the bag?
- It isn’t your gun,
which in our preliminary forensics
analysis seems to be the murder weapon,
judging from the slugs we pulled
from the floor and the wall...
and the execution-style
point-blank range.
- Is any of this coming back to you?
- No.
- Can I see what's in the bag?
- Be my guest.
There are two blood types
on that shirt, Agent Mulder:
one matching Amy Cassandra's,
the other matching David Cassandra's.
Is that your shirt,
Agent Mulder?
Yes.
Can you explain how blood of two people
you claim not to know got on your shirt?
No.
What about the prints
in the house?
Were they my prints?
You're not gonna get
a confession out of me...
because I can't answer your questions
because I don't remember.
You have the right to remain silent.
You give up the right to remain silent,
anything you say can and will be used
against you in the court of law.
You have the right
to speak with an attorney...
and have an attorney present
during questioning.
If you so desire
and cannot afford one,
an attorney will be appointed for you
without charge before questioning.
Do you understand each of the rights
I have explained to you?
Mulder...
I'm gonna get you out of here.
You're a doctor,
not a lawyer, Scully.
- Did you make a confession?
- No, only to my own ignorance.
Detective, before you go through all
that, I need you to consider evidence...
that I think casts doubt on Agent
Mulder's involvement in this crime.
- What kind of evidence?
- Medical evidence.
The toxicology report
on Amy Cassandra indicates...
there was a rapid-acting anesthetic
called ketamine in her system.
" Ketamine"? That's a veterinary drug,
isn't it?
Typically, but when ingested
by a person it can cause hallucinations.
- So?
- So I went to the hospital...
to go over Agent Mulder's
medical charts and blood work,
and there are traces
of the same drug in his system.
- How would that get there?
- Probably injected.
There was a small bruise from an
injection on Amy Cassandra's right hip.
I think if you were examined again,
we would find a corresponding puncture.
- Given by whom?
- I don't know,
but the presence of such
a powerful drug...
could explain his memory loss
or the blackouts.
Given the weight
of all the other evidence,
I think that’s all
it explains.
Scully...
you don't have to do this.
Mulder, you have to help me out.
There is nothing here that
points directly to your guilt.
Unless somebody can show me,
with absolute certainty,
that you were holding the weapon
that killed those two people,
the rest of the narrative is
far too convenient and suspect.
The drug in your system already
suggests other explanations.
That I was partying
with a few senior citizens?
You’re jailing
an innocent man.
Yeah, well, this way he won't
get lost for two days...
and do something else
he won't remember.
-[Gunshot]
-[Man]Shot fired!
I'm a doctor!
Somebody call the paramedics!
He's dead.
I need to speak
with Detective Curtis right now.
Did this officer have a history
of depression or mental illness?
He'd been remanded from his beat
assignment to a desk job a year ago.
His former partner had complained
on a number of occasions...
about his tendency toward
extreme irritability...
and confabulation
of the truth.
- How do you mean ?
- The man we're talking about...
had become something
of a joke on the force.
One of those guys
who believes in...
extraterrestrials,
stuff like that.
Do you see these photos?
[Curtis]
Yeah.
- Does this mean anything to you?
- Should it?
I think it speaks
to a pronounced mental illness.
The compulsive
and repetitive act...
of removing his own image from
these photos leads me to believe...
that he not only believed these stories,
but he was traumatized by them.
You told me this was gonna help explain
something about your partner's crime.
What's that?
Amy Cassandra.
Both your officer
and Amy Cassandra...
had identical puncture wounds
at the top of the frontal lobe.
In her autopsy, Amy Cassandra's
was a deep puncture...
through the cranium
to the dura mater.
- My officer had the same thing?
- Yes.
I think your officer
knew of Amy Cassandra,
and somehow his suicide
is linked to her death,
which leads me to believe that what
we're dealing with here is not murder.
It's something else.
It's possibly even a suicide pact.
You're gonna have to
prove that to me.
[ Groaning ]
[Arguing]
Not Samantha!
[Yelling Continues]
No, not my baby!
Guard!
I need to talk to someone!
According
to the corrections officer,
Agent Mulder kept
everybody awake last night.
He's demanding
to talk to you.
He finally shut up
about an hour ago.
Did he say about what?
I think your partner's memories
are coming back to him.
I need to talk to him alone
if you don't mind.
I heard you didn't
get much sleep.
I didn't kill those people.
Scully.
I know that.
I think I've gathered enough evidence of
your innocence to get you out of here.
- From where?
- The forensics reports.
The shirt you were wearing did
have the victims' blood on it,
but the blood splatter pattern doesn't
match the point-of-entry detail.
In fact, Detective Curtis
and his team...
have been able to put together
enough contradictory evidence...
to make a statement
to the press...
saying the Cassandras' death
was as a result of a murder-suicide.
- But I was there.
- Yes.
And I still don't remember why.
I think I have an idea
about that too.
Amy Cassandra believed
she was an alien abductee.
- And I contacted her?
- Yes. Apparently.
According to an article
I read on Amy,
she had begun psychiatric treatment that
was effectively recovering her past.
The repetitive behavior exhibited
in those paintings that we saw...
was an expression
of that treatment.
But why shoot herself
and her husband?
I can't say
definitively,
but judging from an almost
identical suicide...
of a police officer who was receiving
the same psychiatric care,
I believe the victims were suffering
from Waxman-Geshwin syndrome.
The symptoms of which
are trance-like states...
leading to vivid dreams
about the past,;
dreams that are more detailed
than the conscious mind can recall.
It's also called
Dostoyevsky's syndrome...
because the Russian novelist
was suffering from it too.
What was I doing there
and why didn't I do anything to stop it?
I can't explain that.
I've arranged for your
arraignment in one hour.
I think that by then Detective Curtis
and I will have gathered...
enough forensics data
that you’ll be released.
I still need to know why
though.
This is the office of the psychologist
that treated Amy Cassandra.
- Have you been here before?
- I don't know, but we found my car.
It's been here a few days.
What was the name
of that psychologist?
[Knocking]
Hello.
Dr. Goldstein?
My name is Fox Mulder.
Have we met?
I don't believe so.
My receptionist says
you're from the F.B.I.?
Yes, we're investigating
the deaths of Amy and David Cassandra.
We understand that Amy
was a patient of yours?
Yes.
Please, sit down.
I was very upset
to learn about Amy.
She was a troubled woman
who'd struggled through...
an unfortunate period
of darkness in her life.
Are you referring to her belief
that she was an abductee?
This term "alien abductee"--
Although I recognize there is
an associated syndrome...
and a rather remarkable collection
of shared experiences...
for those who believe
in the phenomena,
my treat of Amy was simply
an aggressive method...
to access buried
or repressed memories.
How do you mean
"aggressive"?
I use a method of therapy that simulates
an electrical impulse in the brain...
using light and sound.
Did you also use this treatment on
a police officer named Michael Fazekus?
- Yes. Why?
- Mr. Fazekus shot himself in the head.
Oh, my God.
Is this an accepted form
of medical treatment?
It's unconventional,
but it's not invasive.
Are you familiar with
Waxman-Geshwin syndrome, Dr. Goldstein?
- Yes.
- Did you know Amy suffered from it?
Waxman-Geshwin,
if you know anything about it,
is not necessarily
a destructive condition.
In fact, Amy,
after undergoing treatment,
experienced periods of extreme
happiness and creativity.
But you had no idea,
you had no indication...
- she might have taken her own life?
-[Goldstein]No!
Of course not.
I have been in practice
forover40years.
I have a very good ethical
and professional reputation...
if you’d care
to check.
That won't be necessary.
I know what you do.
- [ Closes Door]
- I have been here before, Scully.
I met Dr. Goldstein
with Amy Cassandra.
This man is lying
about more than that.
I think that he administered
the ketamine to Amy and to you.
I think you were treated by him and your
blackouts, these seizures, are a result.
I think you’re right.
Why would you do that,
Mulder?
Why would you undergo something
as crazy and dangerous as this?
- [ Groaning ]
- Mulder? Mulder?
[ Echoing ]
Mulder? Mulder?
My baby!
Mulder?
I'm fine.
No, I am not going to
take that for an answer.
You do not belong at work. You need to
be somewhere where you can be monitored.
You are a danger to yourself
and a danger to me.
- Are you hearing me?
- Give me the car keys.
No, you're not driving. You're not doing
anything until these symptoms go away.
Scully, I don't want
these symptoms to go away.
Whatever's happening to me,
whatever treatment I've received...
is allowing me to go back
into my unconscious.
The truth is in there, recorded,
and I've gotten access to it.
What happened to my sister,
the reason she was taken,
it's beginning to become clear to me
and I need to know that.
- Now give me the car keys.
- To go where?
To my mother's in Greenwich.
Okay... but I'm driving.
- Fox.
- I need to speak to you.
What's happened, Fox?
Why have you come here?
You've kept things from me.
Kept secrets.
- What's the matter with him?
- He's undergone a treatment.
He believes it's helped him
to remember things.
Remember what?
You told me when they took Samantha,
it was because you had to make a choice.
But that's not how it happened.
It wasn’t your choice to make.
What do you want
to hear from me?
I want to know what happened
that night on Quonochontaug,
and I need to speak to you
privately.
You had some kind
of relationship with him.
- Who?
- You know who.
The man who worked
with my father.
The man who came that night when I was
1 2, and forced you to choose Samantha.
- No, Fox--
- You betrayed my father, your husband.
- Never.
- How far back did it go?
How dare you!
How dare you come here and accuse me.
Who is my father?
What do you want,
to kill him again?
Just answer the question, Mom.
Just answer the question!
I am your mother, and I will not
tolerate any more of your questions!
You're bleeding, Fox.
[Car Door Slams]
[Car Engine Starts]
What did you do to me?
- I told you--
- You treated me.
I asked you to treat me
to recover my past.
- I did nothing wrong.
- You put a hole in my head.
- A slight electrical stimulation.
- You triggered my memory.
- Yes, as you had hoped.
- Now I want you to finish the job.
Let's do it.
I want to remember.
You're a spy.
[Mrs. Mulder]
Fox?
[ Groaning ]
- Fox.
- [ Mrs. Mulder Crying ]
- You're a spy.
- Why?
Fox?
[ Panting ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Gasping ]
- Not Samantha!
- Fox!
[ Groaning ]
[ Whirring ]
[Banging,
Footsteps Approaching]
Dr. Charles Goldstein?
Dr. Goldstein, you're under arrest.
Please keep your hands where they are.
Bag those gloves as evidence.
Someone read him his rights.
[Officer]
Hands behind your back, please.
Where is he?
Mulder?
- Where's Mulder?
- He's not here.
- Did you ask Dr. Goldstein?
- Goldstein wouldn't say.
- Stop that car!
- Hey! Hold it, Dan!
Hold up!
Open the back door.
What did you do to him?
I know he came back here.
This is the only place
he would have gone.
Did you treat him?
Damn it! Answer me!
- Yes.
- Where is he now?
I don't know where he went.
What was the last thing
he said to you?
He said he was going
to exorcise his demons.
[Car Approaching]
- Agent Scully?
- Yeah.
- Frank Imhop.
- Hi. Is he in there?
Saw the light go on a couple minutes
ago. Gotta be somebody in there.
- We got here as soon as you called.
- All right.
That man is armed. He is a federal
officer in need of medical attention.
He is not himself.
Now I'm going in there.
If at any time he should flee that
house, tell your officers not to shoot.
Mulder?
Leave me alone,
Scully.
- [ Groaning ]
- Mulder, it's me.
Scully, leave me alone.
[Indistinct Voices]
Fox.
[ Gasping ]
[ Continues Gasping ]
It's all falling into place.
- Put down the gun.
- No, don't try to stop me.
- Please, Mulder.
- [ Gasps ]
Wake up, Fox.
[Mrs. Mulder]
No! She’s my baby!
[Glass Shattering]
[Samantha]
I'm afraid, Fox. I'm afraid.
- Get away!
- Are you gonna shoot me?
Is that how much
this means to you?
Mulder, listen to me. You have
been given a powerful hallucinogen.
You don't know that
these memories are yours.
This is not the way
to the truth, Mulder.
- You've got to trust me.
- Shut up!
Put down the gun.
Let it go.
-[Gunshots]
- We've got shots fired! Move!
[Gunshots Continue]
[Scully's Voice]
Although cleared of any wrongdoing...
in the deaths
of Amy and David Cassandra,
Agent Mulder still has no recollection
of the events that led to their deaths.
[ Typing ]
His seizures have subsided with no
evidence of permanent cerebral damage,
but I'm concerned that this experience
will have a lasting effect.
[ Continues Typing ]
Agent Mulder under took this treatment
hoping to lay claim to his past,;
that by retrieving
memories lost to him,
he might finally understand
the path he's on.
But if that knowledge
remains elusive,
and if it's only by knowing
where he's been...
that he can hope to understand
where he's going,
then I fear Agent Mulder
may lose his course...
and the truth she's seeking from his
childhood will continue to evade him,
driving him more dangerously forward
in impossible pursuit.
Subrip by drEAmEr(C)