Previously on "Private Practice".
what do you say we just
see how it goes.
tonight?
He stood me up.
You and me,friends
with benefits,tonight.
What time should I come over?
You're not some random
girl from the internet.
With you it doesn't mean
nothing. It never will.
All right. Get out.
I am so sick and tired of being the
only person in this practice who thinks!
is Violet here?
Uh,no,not yet,but,um. oh,okay.
Oh,Morning. You've got a.
Morning.
Hi. Good morning.
Hi, uh, here you go...
-Naomi?
-Uh,yeah. She's right.
Is Naomi.
what's up with everybody? Was there,like,a car
accident on the way to work or something? What.
Or something.
-Milk?
-Oh,thanks.
They're behind closed doors.
Who?
The women.
If they're gonna talk about
us,we should talk about them.
Yeah.
Let's talk.
Let's talk smack.
I just need ten minutes with naomi.
I need ten minutes with naomi first.
-Naomi?
-Nai?
She slept with cooper.
She slept with pete.
Cats out of the bag,all that.
-She didn't sleep with pete.
-She didn't sleep with cooper.
-How did you know that?
-How'd you know that?
-There are no secrets around here.
-I know!
Ooh,there are secrets.
I mean,I didn't know.
Neither one of you? Really?
I didn't. I didn't know.
That's all I'm saying.
Pete literally stood me up.
I don't get stood up. I'm addison.
Uh,which means something.
in places where.
things mean things. I was humiliated.
Were you completely naked?
Did you stand in front of him like a peeled
banana while he looked over your best parts?
Because I have good parts,and
cooper passed on them.
I have good parts.
Damn right,you do. And so do I.
I like your breasts.
You have a good ass.
Thank you. I like it.
The point is we should not
be having sex in the office.
who's having sex in the office?
No one.
No one,that's the point.
It gets complicated.
You just. you. you don't
know where you stand.
What do you think
they're saying about us?
You know what?
Who cares?
Yeah. Who cares?
the guys are still in the kitchen.
How am I gonna get my
coffee? I need my coffee.
Can we skip the morning meeting?
What do we do in that meeting anyway?
-There is no morning meeting today.
-Thank you.
Because charlotte king is
coming by to walk us. all of us.
through the safe surrender program.
-That's today.
-Yeah.
I signed up with pete.
I am in control.
I work here.
I'm moving on.
But I'm getting my
coffee from downstairs.
-Oh,small nonfat chai latte.
-Frappuccino,extra whipped.
-blame the guy up front.
-Sorry?
The guy at the front of the line,he
just ordered a coffee with,like,
seven descriptive words in front of it.
you should blame him
if you're running late.
Oh,I work upstairs. I just
have a meeting to get to.
Not a big deal.
Well,you can go in front of me.
you look important. I'm.
I'm guessing this meeting
won't go on without you.
thank you.
I'm carl,by the way.
Addison.
stop me now if you had amnesia or
you were bleeding to death in an E.R.
-Addison,I.
-no? Good.
Here's the deal.
I take full responsibility
for last night.
I was warned repeatedly,by you,no less,
and I should know by now that when someone
tells you who they are, you should believe them.
I can work with you,but personally,you've
been downgraded to acquaintance. I'm moving on.
Fair enough.
-We have coffee here.
-Shut up.
What is wrg with everybody?
Okay,safe surrender rundown.
montgomery,you and pete are the go-to team.
Am I wrong? That's what I have here.
No,that's right. We
volunteered last week.
Good times. Happier times.
so the cell phone,that's all they need?
Well,for the next 48 hours,all calls placed to the
safe surrender hotline will be rerouted to that phone.
Don't stray far from
here or from each other.
Fine. That's fine.
These calls are from women who
want to give up their babies?
Most of 'em have given birth already,and
they can't or don't want to keep their babies.
They call from school
bathrooms,friend's places.
They're too scared to go to hospitals
where they have to provide their names.
so we arrange for a place to meet them,they
surrender the baby to us and then what?
You can bring the babies back
here. Dr. Freedman can do the exaMs.
And if the babies are healthy?
Then you call social services.
And most important,don't
forget the bracelets.
One to the mom,one on
the baby's wrist or ankle.
If the birth mother changes her mind,she
has two weeks to reclaim the child.
The biggest victory for safe surrender is when
that baby's placed with someone who wants 'em.
If it's the mom,all the better.
That's all I have time for.
Any questions,call me.
Nothing charlotte king likes better
than bossing people around,huh?
Practically glowing.
Cooper,safe surrender saves
hundreds of babies a year.
It's really an amazing
thing that she's doing.
How did you feel about the
homework I gave you last week?
Well,I didn't think ias an "imagine
yourself on a warm beach" kinda guy.
But?
But every time I
started to feel anxious,
I thought about the
mediterranean,it worked.
Well.
maybe you're ready
for some more homework.
Bring it on.
Let's identify something that
would've triggered you in the past,
something you'd like to try again.
Done. I,um.
I met a woman today,and we
exchanged business cards.
I think I'm ready to try dating again.
We didn't forget how.
I tell ya that.
no,we did not.
I think we,uh.
-yeah,we didn't forget.
-Nah.
so.
what do you think?
What do i think?
Yeah. I just. you know,you.
you laid it on me,so,uh,that
gives you the right to speak first.
-What,I laid it on you?
-Ah,well.
what,because I jumped you,and
you were helpless to stop me?
Well,I didn't say that.
I just. was. was this a slip up,like.
like. like a one time thing?
Or,uh,w-would you.
want more here?
I don't know,sam.
I-I don't know. For once,I
hadn't thought it through.
You know,the practice we barely
got through it after the split.
I know.
And,uh,maya.
I mean,it's not.
not fair to Maya.
We. we got divorced for a reason.
So,um.
I think it was just a slipup.
Yeah.
I,uh,I thought that,toO.
Okay,good. Good.
-Okay.
Hey,uh,there was a
message on your voice mail.
Your priest called?
You have a priest?
Uh,had. Uh,we used to.
Okay,yeah,well,he wants to see you,so.
me?
Uh,both of you,together,as soon as
possible. It sounded kind of serious.
What'd you do,commit a mortal sin?
god's trying to tell us something.
It's a coincidence.
No. We. we have sex,and then the
day after,our priest summons us?
That's the fires of
hell,sam. We had sex.
Just don't mention we got a divorce.
I don't need a lecture.
-Play it cool.
-yeah,everything's cool.
Thank you so much for coming.
We had sex,and. and we're divorced.
Oh,Naomi.
I'm sorry. He's. he's. he's our priest.
I can't lie to him.
I,uh,I-I.
I'm gonna let that go for now.
I'm also gonna overlook the fact that you two have
been christmas and eastering it for the last ten years.
look,I called you about one of the nuns.
It's sister helen. She's sick.
Well,don't know what it is.
She's 86. She hates hospitals.
I thought of you two.
Sam,this is your area.
Naomi,I thought having a woman
would make her more comfortable.
H-has she been ill for a while?
Uh,sister amy would know.
The sisters have been
sequestered alone together for.
-sequestered?
-For three weeks.
St. Mary's is our mother house.
We spend most of the year
on missions around the world.
So this is the one time of
year we get to see each other.
This is the first time I've been outside
these walls in the last three weeks.
All right. So,please.
Father mark?
No,I'm not supposed to enter.
No one from outside the sisterhood,but they
need you. You're good catholics,you're doctors.
Well,doctors at least.
Go on. I'll. I'll wait for you here.
oh,it's all right,sister helen.
She's a doctor. It's all right.
when did she start feeling bad?
A week or so ago. She said she
felt like she was getting the flu.
She's the only one of us who doesn't
complain of aches and pains,so we noticed.
Sam?
What's this?
It's definitely not the flu.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-Âí¿ËË¹
Private
Practice  Season 1 Episode 8
Still don't want to talk,cooper.
But I want to talk.
Well,there'a world wide web
out there waiting for you.
I'm sure you can find
someone who will listen.
I can just grab the peanut butter and.
men.
They're overrated.
Dating is overrated.
-Sex is.
-don'T.
Don't say something you're gonna regret.
hello,addison montgomery.
Carl. Hi.
Yes,I would love to have coffee.
But I am on call for work today,so.
you sure?
Okay,then. Uh,yes,I will.
see you later.
B-bye.
-I have a date tonight.
-You don'T.
you don't want to move too
fast,addison,not with a guy you barely know.
Unhand me,woman.
I'm getting my date on.
it would help if we could
precisely identify the rash.
Yeah. I don't have my derm atlas on me.
Wait.
Sister virginia,could you,um.
-oh,yes,of course.
-Thank you.
-Sister.
-Okay.
Here we go.
I'm gonna send it to dell.
See if he can't find
someone to identify it.
how is she feeling?
Well,we may need to get
sister helen to a hospital.
We'll do everything we
can to keep her here.
But we can't treat her until we know
what kind of an infection she has.
Yeah,and we're also gonna need to check
the other sister to see if it's contagious.
You ever seen a rash like this?
Can't say that I have.
I'm tracking down an infectious disease
specialist to see if we can get an answer.
Um,I'm done with my patients for
the day,but I'll be back later.
Uh,ring me if we get
a safe surrender call.
I'll be just down the
street. I've got a thing.
A thing?
Yes.
Well,don't drink. Friends don't
let friends drink and save babies.
I think addison has a dateonight.
Well,good for her. She's
getting back on the horse.
-I'm about to have a date tonight.
-Really?
Yeah,with canóuhandleóme441.
What? I don't believe in dwelling. I
believe in getting back on the horse.
Well,I'll leave you to it.
He's a lucky guy.
-Who is?
-Addison's horse.
you. you feel a little clammy.
I'm fine.
I spend most of the year
ministering to people in uganda.
You ought to see what
I'm exposed to there.
I'll weather sister helen's cold.
Sister virginia,please.
so sister helen's temperature
is 103,her resps 26.
Yeah,and now sister
virginia's getting sick.
And dell still hasn't come
up with anything on that rash.
All right,I think we should just
get sister helen to a hospital.
I'll call the ambulance.
I already did.
Uh,they're 20 minutes out.
Okay.
We make a good team.
Yeah,we do.
and then I moved to L.A.
-And lived happily ever after.
-yes.
The life of addison montgomery
in ten minutes or less.
Well,you can have 11 minutes.
Don't need it. Here goes.
Uh,never been married.
Never had kids.
Want to get married.
Want to have kids.
A man without baggage.
that is rare.
Well,I.
have a little baggage to confess.
I'm,uh,a patient of Dr. Turner'S.
I've been seeing her almost a year,
and I can say,without a doubt,that
she's made me a better man.
Okay.
It's,um,it's refreshing
to meet someone who'S.
interested in being a better man.
-Really?
-Yes,really.
oh,I have to take this.
Exse me.
Hello.
Her name is darcy.
She id to wait,she'd meet us.
Darcy?
It's a girl.
she's not.
she isn't crying.
I can take a look at her.
are you bleeding?
Darcy,why don't you let us
take you back to the clinic?
No,you just have to take it and
go. My mom's upstairs sleeping.
Your mother was here in
the house when you were.
I crawled on the top bunk and played my
steo really loud to cover the contractions.
You cut the cord.
I clipped it.
See? With a barrette.
You made the right decision by calling.
Darcy,why don't you give me
just five minutes,all right?
I'll do an exam very quickly,make sure
theraren't any problems,and then you can go.
darcy. It's a little
late to have friends over.
Sorry,mom.
you have to go,now.
Take my rd and a bracelet.
Your daughter has a matching one.
I. just go.
In case you change your mind.
I won'T.
-Sam.
-The ambulance is here.
Sam. May I show him,please?
I felt fine.
naomi.
Yeah,I know. I see it. Th is not
just sister helen and sister virginia.
Sam.
hey,no,no. Don't come in. Don't co in.
This building is a hot zone.
We have to lock it down.
Until we figure out what this
is,nobody comes in,nobody goes out.
I am not leaving them.
Okay,shut the door then. Shut the door.
Ambrose spoke to the C.D.C.
They said we were right to lock down until the
hospitals can prep some isolation units for them.
Or. us.
What do they think this is?
Uh,probably a viral contagion.
Considering where these nuns have been.
dell forwarded the pictures on to
an infectious disease specialist,
so we'll know as. as
soon as he hears back.
How long until the iso unit's prepped?
Six hours.
Three more sisters have a fever.
So that makes 8 of the 12,and.
I'm not feeling too good.
Still don't think god's
trying to tell us something?
You don't really think we're being
punished for what we did last night?
what,just because we may have some
rare,tropical probably deadly disease?
The morning after we have sex?
Well,if we are sick.
I'm glad we got some.
how sentimental.
That was a joke. I was joking.
I mean,I gotta say,that kid did a pretty
good job of giving birth in a bunk bed.
I did a primary check,and
she's fine for now.
Her lungs are good,heartbeat's strong.
We'll get cooper to do a
well-baby check tomorrow.
Or you can call him now.
Cooper's,uh.
out on a date.
Oh,god. He's doing his.
get back up on the horse thing.
Addison is,too,right?
You. you had your date?
How did it go?
It's okay,violet.
I know carl's your patient. He told me.
Oh,good.
Good.
Uh,baby blankets. We need baby blankets.
oh,hey,you know,that. that might
be the,uh,the guy,the nun rash.
So you're dating one of violet's
patients? A psych patient?
Oh,please. This is L.A. You're
weird if you're not seeing a shrink.
You all done,kiddo,huh?
Okay.
Good girl.
You sure you don't want me to call
social services to come pick her up?
No,no,no. That's okay.
Uh,I'll stay here tonight.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.You know,
shshould get to feel
wanted,at least for one night.
Yeah.
Oh,yes,little girl.
That's a little baby.
uh,7 and 7.
More on the first 7,less on the second.
Charlotte king,as I live and breathe.
oh,no,you don'T. That's saved.
Big date?
Not a date.
Far from it. I'm just
meeting someone. Scoot.
I don't want him to see you
and think you're here with me.
What timdid he say?
9:00 P.M.
Mm,I'm meeting someone at 9:00,too
a blonde,petite.
We met on the internet.
What?
No.
oh,god.
Oh,my god.
No,no,no. We should laugh about
the unfortunate coincidence.
Laughing is the way to go.
Let's be clear. This never happened.
Or the opposite of laughing.
Yes,sir. I just got it.
Okay.
I see,yeah.
I'll call 'em right now.
Holy crap.
a patient of yours is dating addison?
I'm not allowed to
discuss it. You know that.
Yes,you are.
Our patients know we share files.
Well,we don't if we don't have to.
Okay,but on a scale from one
to ten,how bad is his thing?
Moving away. Not talking.
Are we talking a three?
Like I'm afraid of seagulls and
I'm considering hypnotherapy?
I'm closing the door. I'm
closing it in your face.
Oh,it's bad,huh?
We're,like,way beyond mommy issues here?
Ethics,pete. Look it up.
Sam.
She's tachycardic at 130.
I n't get a blood pressure.
She's in septic shock.
We gotta get her to a hospital,I
don't care if they're ready for us.
no,we gotta get everybody to a
hospital right now. Dell just called.
-What is it?
-It's typhoid.
how is sister virginia?
Well,she's still not responding,and
her blood pressure is very unstable.
Typhoid? I didn't.
I-I thought that disappeared
in,like,the early 1900s.
You know,it's.
it's a common disease in exactly the kind
of third world places where the sisters work.
It's transmitted through
skin-to-skin contact or food.
So you think one of the
sisters caught it on a mission?
No,and that's what's troubling.
The incubation period
is two weeks at the most.
And these sisters were
sequestered for longer than that.
So how did they get exposed?
Excuse me just one second.
I spoke with health services.
There have been no other
outbreaks of typhus in this area.
And all the food in the
convent tested clean.
So if it's not the food.
sam,somebody had to have had
contact with an outside carrier.
Well,all the sisters are claiming
that they've been completely isolated.
Nobody in,nobody out.
Sam,what are we saying here?
That one of these nuns.
we're saying that somebody's lying.
You're not ready to date. Y-you're
certainly not ready to quit therapy.
But I feel fine. I feel good.
This is you going off your program.
Hi.
Okay,I'm. I'm just leaving
some flowers for addison.
She's sleeping,so.
make sure she gets these,okay?
Thanks.
seizure?
Addison's date last night was with a patient
of violet'S. Now violet seems worried.
No way.
Awesome. What's his deal?
Well, if it was nothing, she would say.
You know you'd say.
Just a hint.
You don't have to
tell us the whole--
he calls himself "trunk."
okay.
Well,when I think "trunk," in relation
to a guy,not necessarily a bad thing.
elephant's trunks,very large tr.
oh,is he freakishly
large? Is he hideously.
I can't tell you!
Trunk.
Flowers.
How you holdin' up?
Good. Little hungry.
A lot tired.
And I can,um,I can only find one shoe.
every time I tried to put her
down,she started screeching like a bat.
Okay,you realize I didn't
actually give birth.
Uh,from your psych patient.
He just dropped 'em off.
Oh,that's so sweet.
Here,give me the card.
the thing is,I think carl
might have some probleMs.
Everybody has probleMs.
Violet said his nickname is "trunk.
" I don't know what that means.
I think it means.
he's not addison montgomery
material. That's all.
No.
You don't know what my material is.
You've never even seen
my material,remember?
So.
mind your own business.
She isn't getting any better,is she?
No,not yet.
Her lungs are congested.
Pressure's borderline.
I'm putting all the sisters on
an aggresve course of antibiotics.
It's a dangerous disease,but the cure rate
is very high for those with mild cases.
Thank you,sam.
Father,uh.
naomi's gonna be asking
the sisters some questions.
Oh,of course. Anything you need.
Uh,is there anyone you
think we should speak to?
Uh,a sister that might have had contact with a
typhoid carrier in the time they were sequestered?
From the outside?
Maybe a sister was meeting
with someone secretly?
No,no. I can't imagine
someone would lie about that.
Well,people keep secrets,father.
Believe me.
I got a page from the E.R.
Dr. Violet turner.
Oh,hi.
Um,yeah. You have a patient here.
Uh,we were able to remove the
foreign body nonsurgically.
He's on pain meds now.
Seems to be resting comfortably.
Is he gonna be okay?
Yeah. Oh,yeah.
Yeah. He's,um.
he's lucky he didn't
perforate his bowel.
Just one question for you.
you got any idea whose shoe this is?
Given the circumstances of her
birth,this is a very,very healthy baby.
yeah,did you hear that?
I heard we have something to celebrate.
You rescued a baby?
yeah,um,what exactly happens,uh,once
social services takes her?
It's out of our hands.
She'll be placed in foster care
while they start the adoption process.
Come here,batgirl. Yes.
Yes,it's time for a little stroll,huh?
Little stroll around the office? Yeah.
Batgirl?
here's a question. cotton
balls at st.Ambrose.
do you.
uh,triple size.
Hospital grade.
Right. More cotton per ball.
good-bye,Dr. Freedman.
Good-bye,canóuhandleóme.
I didn't mean to take her shoe.
You took her shoe,carl.
And you did what you always do.
Yeah.
You need to come back to therapy.
Because this is not a
good way to live,is it?
No.
One more thing.
Uh,can you tell addison I can't see her?
She's great. She's perfect.
But I don't trust
myself around her shoes.
how do you give up your baby?
how do you give up your whole life?
I mean,falling in love,a family,all
of it,just to go live in a convent.
That's why somebody's lying.
This girl. darcy.
she carried her for nine months.
I've had her for one night.
one night.
and the thought of her being thrown
into some foster home is killing me.
You can't have this baby,addison.
I know.
I named her.
Batgirl.
Okay. you just can't have kids.
oh,nai,I wish you were here.
It's been such a weird day.
Oh,tell me about it.
I'm interrogating nuns.
I wish I were there,too.
damn it. I gotta go.
Bye.
come in.
I thought I heard you in here.
batgirl can only sleep
in total darkness.
O-okay.
Um,can I talk to you?
it's carl.
Carl likes you very much,but he
wanted me to tell you that he.
he's not gonna be calling again.
I don't understand.
He has a medical issue
that worsens under stress.
What te of issue?
It. it doesn't matter.
Why do you call him "trunk"?
Oh,you know about that?
Okay,uh,well,that was very.
unprofessional of me to say that.
Uh,a trunk is a place where you
might put all sorts of things,
things you might have,uh,taken,or
borrowed from another person.
in an anatomical sense.
Oh,god.
where is my shoe?
We. we can talk about this. It
is nothing to be disturbed by.
It. it's an issue of control.
I am going to get up,and I'm
gonna walk out of this room,
and you and I are never,ever,going
to speak of this again.
I would like that very much.
No change?
no. I'm sorry.
If it's all right with you,I'd like
to give her the sacrament of the sick.
Oh,yeah,of course.
"The graced peace of god our father
and the lord jesus christ be with you.
" "Through this holy anointing,may
the lord,"in his love and mercy,
help you "with the
grace of the holy spirit.
May the lord.
-the way he looks at her.
-I know.
"Save you and raise you up.
don't be mad,but I
called social services.
I meant to call. I just.
forgot. That'S.
good.
I can help you pack up her stuff.
Thanks.
come on,baby.
How long till they get here?
there you go.
Oh,batgirl.
okay.
I'll be back as soon as i can,okay?
Safe surrender hotline.
did she say where,exactly?
No,she just said marine park
past the first parking lot.
Addison.
The baby's not breathing.
There's no pulse.
Let'continue to bring up his temp
with warmed oxygen and fluids.
More saline bags.
What's his core temp?
Core temp is 95.
uh,let's do another round of epi.
Come on,little guy.
Come on,baby. Don't do this.
asystole.
Addison,you've been at
this for almost an hour.
okay.
I'm gonna call it.
Time of death. 10:42 P.M.
We got there as soon as we could.
It's over.
We tried.
It's over,Pete.
-Addison,we did everything we.
-it's over. The baby's dead.
|W tough day.
yeah.
I used to get off on 'em,the tough ones.
When I was a resident,I used to
think,I got through this,I survived.
And the next one,I'll
survive even better.
I don'T.
It's days like these where
I slip and make mistakes.
Bad mistakes.
These long.
crappy days just.
I just need
something,someone,and I end up.
falling off your wagon.
Whoever your wagon may be.
We have to get back to the practice.
This is the last time
I'm offering to talk.
Cooper,it's not that I
don't want to talk to you.
I-I can'T.
Of course you can. That's what we do.
I know.
But?
Allan obliterates my heart,and you
tell me that he doesn't deserve me.
Some girl named trixie
uses and abuses you,
and I listen to you and I
tell you you're being stupid.
I-I will always be able to
talk to you about someone else.
But I can'T.
I can't talk to you about you.
I-I don't know how to talk about us.
Not like that.
Then talk to me about something else.
Whatever's on your mind.
I went to the E.R.
Carl.
shoved one of addison's shoes up his.
yeah,okay,okay.
Well,you know,you asked.
That's what was on my mind.
maybe carl will nd a girl
who enjoys what he does.
So. so that. that's the answer?
My job has no point?
Freaks should just be with other freaks?
Are you talking about us?
About me?
No.
no.
Uh,sister virginia's doing better.
She,uh.
her pressure has
normalized since last time.
father,we'd like to
test you for typhoid.
Me? I feel fine.
Carriers are asymptomatic.
You wouldn't know you
had it until it spread.
Well,I've done missionary work all
over the world,but that was years ago.
That doesn't matter. This disease
can stay dormant for years.
You think.
you think sister
virginia got it from me?
I know you say you don't
go in the convent,but.
if you had direct contact with her.
I would sneak in at night,and we.
no,you don't have to say.
I would sneak in,and we would.
cook.
Cook?
I couldn't boil water before
she arrived. Never had to.
But then I would see her,and she
was just so graceful and smart.
When no one else was around,I
would ask her for pointers.
It's been years now.
And we have never touched.
I know it was forbidden.
She'd be away on missions,and I'd just.
part of me was always waiting.
For the next time you could be together.
I missed my friend.
all this pain because of me,I just.
oh,no,no. You. you couldn't have known.
We'll get you on a course of
antibiotics,you'll be fine.
Thank you.
Sam,naomi,uh.
we all make choices.
The two of you made a choice.
I know. I was there.
And so was he.
I just want you to know that
as far as,uh,we're concerned.
you will always be married.
darcy,are you okay?
You're the doctor
who. you took the baby?
Ma'am,we were offering
your daughter a safe option.
It's called safe surrender.
She's actually protecting
herself and the baby.
She made the right choice to
call. It was the brave choice.
You think we'd ever let
her give this baby away?
My god. This is my grandchild.
I didn't even notice.
I-is she okay?
She's a very healthy baby. Here you go.
Okay?
Got her? Yeah.
hi.
Hi.
Her name is melanie.
My daughter's name is melanie.
That's a perfect name.
Father mark said we're still
married in the eyes of god,
so technically,what we did
the other night,not a sin.
Oh,really?
Yeah,that's what the father said.
Which means if we were to do it again.
charlotte.
I'm going home,Dr. Freedman.
Come have a drink with me.
What?
No.
Come on.
I am not having sex with you just because
I wrote some things on the internet.
No.
A drink. Not sex. Absolutely no sex.
I could get you that drink now.
Not yet.
Ask me again in two hours.
Ahh,yes,ma'am.
You heading out?
I don't think I can be in this day.
Any longer.
You shouldn't be alone tonight.
I won't be.
I'm sorry. I know it's
past neighbor time.
Come in. It's cold.
Uh,can I get you
anything? Some tea or wine?
Wine.
I called naomi,but,uh.
no one answered.
You want to talk about it?
it was,um.
a night,you know?
Just a night.
And,uh.
then I c-called naomi,and she
wasn't home,and I-I just couldn'T.
go home yet.
Hey.
Private
Practice  Season 1 Episode 8
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync:YTET-Âí¿ËË¹
Proudly Presents