- What, are you following me now?
- You wouldn't call me back.
You didn't call me at all.
I didn't know you were here...
- For now.
- Working for Charlotte...
- And sleeping with my best friend again.
You really should knock
before you walk into a doctor's office.
It was funny. Twice I come to town,
twice you walk in on me.
- I have a patient.
- I know.
Jane williams...
30 years old, 33 weeks pregnant.
Ambulance just brought her in.
She's having a stroke.
- What, how...
- Good, you're both here.
You've met my new neurologist.
Your patient has neurological problems.
I called him in.
Okay... Tim, can you tell me
what happened?
She was eating breakfast,
and we were arguing.
Suddenly her orange juice drops.
It just falls out of her hand, and
there's orange juice everywhere,
and Jane can't speak.
The baby's heartbeat is normal.
Jane, I'm Dr. Montgomery.
Can you understand what I'm saying?
Are you in any pain?
Jane, it's okay.
If you understand what he's saying,
nod your head.
Good. Just try to relax.
We're here to help you.
When did this all happen...
the orange juice and the not talking?
I don't know.
An hour ago, maybe longer.
I need you to be as exact as possible.
It's important.
An hour...
an hour and 20 minutes ago.
Good...
Then we still have Time.
She didn't have a stroke.
She's having one right now.
And if I can stop it
in the next hour and 40 minutes,
there's a pretty good chance that I can
prevent any permanent brain damage.
And what about the baby?
If you treat Jane, what...
what happens to the baby?
Private Practice S02E14
Second Chances
Did the fight cause this?
Strokes can just happen, often without
warning. There are no predictors.
- You two...
- The divorce has been ugly.
She hates that this baby keeps me
in her life.
At was the last thing
she said right before she...
she wished that she wasn't pregnant
so she'd never have to see me again.
Good news.
There's no evidence of a bleed,
which means I can perform
an endovascular clotvacuation.
Excuse me just a minute.
I don't want you fishing around
inside her brain.
You should use T.P.A.
to bust the clots.
It's contraindicated in pregnancy.
No, it's not, not in the studies
I've read, and I'm the ob-gyn.
Oh, I know.
Double board certified.
- Stop. Archie.
- Archie?
I guess you are mad.
T.P.A. is rolling the dice.
The procedure is something I can control.
And if Jane's life were at risk,
it might make sense.
But the stroke isn't gonna kill her
or the baby,
- and what you're proposing could.
- All right,
- what about her quality of life?
- The baby is 33 weeks.
Its lungs aren't fully developed.
It needs more Time.
T.P.A.Offers that.
I'm a good neurologist, Addie.
Some might say I'm a great one.
You used to say it.
We have a little over an hour
to stop this stroke,
and I am telling you
that we can save both of them.
You got it?
One sticky bun from damn those donuts,
one bagel with onions from canter's,
a fruit bowl and a maraschino frapp?
- from the juice collective.
- Where's my coffee?
- You can't have coffee, Violet.
- I'm not giving up coffee.
- Maraschino?
- They were out of pomegranate.
Oh, my god.
Did you get two?
That's for Charlotte.
An apple fritter makes up
for you refusing her marriage proposal?
I didn't turn her down.
I delayed on your advice.
And speaking of advice...
pregnancy cravings
are not a license to eat poorly.
It's not a pregnancy craving.
I'm just hungry.
Page 156... read all about cravings,
which, by the way,
is what you are having.
Page 336... people who are not pregnant
should butt out,
which, by the way, means you.
You know, I couldn't find the page
I was really looking for,
which is the one that says
it's important for you
to tell the father
that you are pregnant.
I don't know if either one of them
wants kids.
I don't know if I want kids.
Don't you think it's time you found out?
- You have to tell someone, Violet.
- I did. I told you.
Everything okay?
What's... wrong?
I don't think I can talk to you
about this.
What, Nai?
You can talk to me anything.
It... involves another man.
shoot.
Addison caught me and Archer
having sex in his new office,
which is on the fourth floor
of Pacific Wellcare.
Sam, are you...
So you need to...give me advice.
Right, right.
Okay. So...
Are you worried about Addison
finding out
that you are sleeping with her brother,
or are you worried about everybody
finding out
that you kept Archer getting a job
downstairs a secret?
Both.
But... really,
I'm worried that she's gonna guilt him
into not having sex with me again,
because the sex is really good.
- Are you okay?
- No... I have a girlfriend.
So I'm good.
- How's it going with Sonya...
- Really...
it's incredibly...
she's... she's making me wait.
We... we're waiting...
until she's ready.
But... but she's ready now, so...
Take your inhaler.
Nai, I'm not a virgin anymore.
All right.
I never thought we'd get here.
We're friends.
Yeah, we got here.
Friends.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah. Is Dr. Wilder in?
I have an appointment.
No. He's actually
running a little bit late.
You okay?
I must look pretty crappy?
No, I just...
I had a rough morning, you know?
One of those mornings.
But is Pete gonna...
gonna be here soon?
Why don't I just show you back
to his office?
- He should be here any second.
- Oh, great.
When I got the call
about Terri's accident...
I was so stunned.
She was so...
so excited when she foundut
she was pregnant.
She and Mark...didn't think
it was ever going to happen, but...
you made them believe.
I'm so, so sorry about what's happened.
You know, it's just...
one stupid guy...
drinks and drives, and...
my whole family's gone.
I came here today
because Terri
and Mark died without a will.
The extra embryos
they had leftover...
the ones you have frozen?
They've been left to me.
Were you interested in donating them?
I'd like them.
For myself.
I want to have a baby...
my daughter's baby.
Hey, Keith.
Dell said that...
Dell, get me a two mix of narcan
and call an ambulance.
Keith.
Can you hear me?
I called 9-1-1. Here...
Is there anything I can do?
How long has he been using it?
He came to me a few years ago
for help with stress.
He's a real state agent.
He lives and dies by the Market.
Last year, the Market crashed.
Addiction took over.
The guy's a total mess. He lost his job,
his wife. He's got hep-C.
Trifecta.
I've been treating him for free,
but I think the real reason he comes is
because I give him clean needles.
You started a needle exchange program?
Sam, I know this guy.
He should not die in the streets.
Right now, this is the only way
I can help him.
What the...
- How did I...
- I found you on the floor.
- You O.D.'d.
- Oh, I feel like crap.
I know you feel bad,
but we got you breathing again.
- We got an ambulance coming.
- My head. It hurts.
Easy. Just relax.
Why don't you lay back down?
- What, are you trying to kill me?
- Nobody is trying to hurt you, Keith.
We're just trying to help.
You all right?
They seem like a nice couple.
They're divorced and they barely speak.
Well, I guess they spoke long enough
to conceive.
Speaking of not speaking, are we really
gonna have a fight about Naomi again?
- You think I'm mad about Naomi?
- Oh, good. You're not mad.
This is you not mad.
Like the time I loaned your cashmere
sweater to Crystal McCullogh.
She puked on it.
She puked up strawberry daiquiri
all over my sweater.
But you weren't mad.
I wasn't mad that you loaned it.
I was mad that you lied.
And I'm not mad about Naomi.
I'm mad that you took a job
with a practice
that is trying to bury me.
You knew about and
you didn't have the guts to tell me.
Wyatt left, chasing some ridiculous
amount of pharmaceutical cash.
So Charlotte needed a big name.
Who better but me?
Why are you here, Archer?
There were some things in New York
I wanted to get away from.
Like?
Stalker ex-girlfriend?
Publisher who knew where you lived?
There's always something.
After the way we left things,
I wanted to try again, make it better.
Look, let's do this case.
See how much you enjoy working with me.
- As long as we do it your way?
- Well, that would help.
It's the right way, Addie.
I'm just concerned.
Look, I know I'm a 52-year-old litigator
and not a 19-year-old cheerleader,
but... my gynecologist
started me on hormone therapy,
and he thinks I'm ready
for implantation.
Yeah, but it's not just age.
The stress of losing your daughter,
that takes its physical toll.
And it doesn't exactly make you
an ideal candidate for I.V.F.
Terri wanted to bring
a baby into this world,
more than anything, and I can do that.
I can bring her baby into the world.
Well, your gynecologist was right.
You are certainly ready.
But having your own grandchild?
- You're still grieving, Sharon.
- This isn't about grief.
This is about honoring my daughter.
- I've never seen Keith that bad.
- Yeah, well, at some point,
you're just gonna have to call
the police and let them handle it.
I know how you feel
about addicts, Dell...
I'm not being punitive, okay?
I'm not mad.
It's just obvious
that the guy needs help,
and you tried,
and it's not working, and
at least in Jail,
he'll have to go cold Turkey.
- Jail isn't the answer for him.
- I don't know.
- I think Dell's right.
- Thank you.
Keith needs to be in a program.
I've talked to him about it before.
I know he has it in him to get clean
with the right kind of help.
You really think you can get through
to this guy?
I think I should try.
Jane, I know
that you want to talk to us,
and I know that you're scared, but all
these people here, all this equipment,
is to help you get better.
I'm gonna give you some sedative,
enough to keep you comfortable,
but I need for you to be awake so
that we can test things as we go, okay?
I need you to trust me.
My sister trusts me. So can you.
- Your baby is doing great.
- Stay with me, Jane, okay?
We're gonna get you through this.
Brought you a peace offering.
Your favorite:
fritters, warm apple,
deep fried for your
southern taste buds.
We have breakfast here, Cooper.
Well, maybe you can skip
breakfast here, and we...
Look, I understand you're angry,
but you can't not talk to me.
I'm sorry I said no
about the marriage,
but I did tell you I wanted
to spend the rest of my life with you.
Can you tell me what I did wrong
that's so unforgivable?
If you really don't get it,
I can't help you.
- Well, we have to talk about this.
- No, we don't. And we won't.
So save the rest of your earnest little
"i can make it all better" act,
and leave, okay?
It's good, isn't it?
See, this is fortuitous,
finding you here.
We need to talk,
and you've been avoiding.
Avoidance isn't good for anyone, Violet.
I'm not avoiding you, Sheldon.
I've just been very busy.
And... I have a patient waiting, so...
- Hey, cooper. You going back up?
- Oh, good. You guys are talking.
- At least someone's talking.
- In fact, we're not talking.
We're talking, Sheldon.
I love talking to you.
I love spending time with you.
I'm just...
Busy. I know.
Cute kids.
Over there, Sheldon.
- Don't you think?
- I guess,
in small doses.
I'm not really a kid person.
They don't seem to like me.
So you don't have kids of your own?
No. God, no, thankfully.
Well, you must see them
in your practice.
I bet you're great with 'em.
You know what I find?
I'm okay with kids in short bursts.
Beyond that...
well, it's not a problem, is it?
- Are you miserable or starving?
- Both.
- Anything you want to talk about?
- This is doing the trick.
- Terri Hughes' mother came in today.
- Why?
We have Terri and Mark's embryos
in our freezer.
And she wants them implanted...
in her.
- I don't know what to do.
- I do. Say no.
Well, I know there are issues with her
carrying her own grandchild and her age,
- but Sharon seems to think...
- I'm not interested in Sharon's reasons.
Terri was my patient.
I'm interested in what she'd think.
And she would never,
ever want this.
How can you be so sure?
Terri hated her mother.
Giving that woman another child...
Terri's child...
would've been her worst nightmare.
I'm twisting the coil,
capturing the clot.
A few more minutes
I'll beable to pull it outta there,
returning the blood flow
in your brain back to normal.
- Can you keep her still, please?
- She's having uterine contractions.
Well, you're gonna have to stop that.
- I will. Draw up terbutaline.
- Quickly, please.
You just focus
so you don't nick a vessel.
Jane, I know you're in a lot of pain,
but I need you to stay
as still as possible.
- We're running out of time.
- Just give it a minute.
- Heart rate's up.
- 120. 140.
It's a side effect from the terbutaline.
Just a few more seconds.
Stay with us Jane.
Okay?
Contractions are slowing.
Captured the clot.
Removing the coil...
and injecting the dye.
Oh, isn't that a pretty sight?
No, no, okay, all right.
Do you think it's ever appropriate
for a mother
to be implanted with the embryos
of her daughter?
I was dreading the choice between power
berry and dragonfruit vitaminwater.
Look, okay, mothers act as surrogates
for their daughters all the time.
If Sharon wants a baby so badly,
let her adopt.
Sharon doesn't want any child.
She wants their child.
She doesn't deserve it.
Well, I don't like it any more
than you do.
- But if I don't do it, she's just...
- Well, she just...
she just goes to another doctor
for implantation, right?
I mean, they're her property.
By law...
I'm not saying they should be.
She's 52.
There are very few doctors who could
successfully impregnate a woman her age.
If Naomi says no,
then the problem ends here.
But isn't getting older women pregnant
part of the beauty of I.V.F.?
They get to have Time,
have careers and still be moms.
And what does that mean for their kids?
I mean, can you imagine volunteering
to be team mom in soccer in your 50s,
or going prom dress shopping
in your 60s?
I don't know. Maybe the
fact that Terri hated her mother
makes the decision for me.
I don't have to worry about age
or grief.
She should not be a mother.
People become parents at different times
in their lives for different reasons.
It's not always ideal,
but if this woman is willing
to make a good faith effort
to be the kind of parent she knows
she should've been before,
why would we be against that?
Isn't that what this baby...
any baby... deserves?
Pretty good team, you and me.
No, we are not a good team.
I made a life here, Archer,
away from bizzy, away from Derek.
I'm trying to figure out me.
And I can't do that with you...
- judging everything that I do.
- I will be supremely supportive.
You don't know
how to stay out of my life.
You never have.
And when I needed someone
to make Phil Davidson pay for leaving me
out at the lake, that was great.
But now,
when I'm struggling to find my footing
in this place that's mine...
I miss you.
I miss you, but this isn't a visit.
You're in my city.
You're in my building.
You're sleeping with my best friend.
I mean, you're...
you're in my patient's brain!
I'm not moving in with you, Addie.
I just wanted to be closer.
You have to go.
I love you, but you have...
you have to go.
- You know, this is crazy, Charlotte.
- What, riding the elevator?
With the masking and the sarcasm.
It's like we take one steps forward
and two steps back.
I want you to talk to me.
Do you not see that we are
a perfect match
and you're screwing it up?
I got embarrassed and humiliated.
So don't tell me
about screwing things up.
You think it's easy for me
to look you in the face
after I sobbed in your lap
like a 12-year-old girl,
asked you to marry me
and got turned down?
- You shouldn't feel humiliated.
- Well, it happened, and I do,
and there is nothing you can do
about it.
- He's dead, isn't he?
- No, Ellen. It's...
it's not that.
I'm sorry to startle you.
I'm looking for Keith.
Come in.
He stopped by my office this morning.
He O.D.'d. I helped him,
and then he ran off.
I haven't seen him in months.
I'm surprised he even came to you.
He...
- he can't afford it.
- We have a deal.
He stops by so I can keep an eye on him.
I give him clean needles
so he doesn't spread...
You're helping him get high.
- I'm helping him stay safe.
- It's enabling.
I should know,
because I was queen of enabling, but,
it doesn't work.
I had to cut him off,
for his good and for mine.
He's an addict.
I know. It's a horrible disease.
Well, call it a disease if you want.
It's politically correct. I get it.
But he chooses to shoot up.
And I choose not to have
anything to do with him.
This man...
this is my husband...
the man I loved.
I'm trying to help you get him back.
It's not up to you, Pete.
It's up to him.
And he's beyond help.
How's she doing?
Archer was able to stop the stroke.
He woke her up, but there's swelling.
So she's still paralyzed on the side.
She hasn't been able to talk yet,
but he's very hopeful.
- And the baby?
- Everything's looking good, Tim.
Did you wanna...
go in there and see her?
She doesn't want me here.
I'll let her family know
that she's okay.
What do you think about me
staying over tonight?
I don't want Maya to wake up
and see you here in the morning.
I could sneak out early.
I'll sneak out.
I am sorry, but I can't.
But I will make it up to you.
Tomorrow night?
Yeah, actually, I can't.
- I have a date.
- You have a date?
- With another woman?
- Well, I don't date men.
- I support the choice, but...
- Funny.
- Funny guy.
- You're upset.
No, I'm not upset.
I'm not. I'm just...
I'm surprised.
- I thought that we were...
- We are,
and it's great.
It's amazing.
But I'm not your boyfriend.
I didn't say you were my boyfriend.
Look...
I'm the good-time guy.
I'm your good-time guy.
And you should enjoy
the good-time guy,
'cause the good-time guy
is good.
You want to go again?
I'll do things that you never heard of.
Okay, but you have to leave right after.
Good-time guy will go,
right after this.
Just a minute.
- This is unexpected.
- I know.
I could a called.
Maybe I should a called, but...
I didn't want you to say no.
To what?
W should be able to talk about our...
situation.
I'm sorry. Situation?
You know what I like most about you?
How easily we can talk about things,
how in sync we are,
how we get each other.
I get that there's a problem,
I just have no idea what it is.
You're here, talking to Violet.
- And you're here.
- I got some gyros,
and I needed some advice.
But you guys are here talking,
which is great. So I should go.
- Thanks.
- No, don't go.
Gyros for three it is.
- I can wait.
- I'm sorry.
- I need you to decode.
- Sonya's here.
Tell her to call 9-1-1 if necessary.
All right?
You're a father.
You can't afford to die for sex.
I got this... All right. What do you...
what do you need decoded?
It's Archer. What's a good-time guy?
A guy who you have a good time with.
Speaking of which...
So do you think I'm the type that
would be okay dating a guy like that?
Well, you were okay sleeping with
a guy like that twice already, so...
I am a divorced woman with standards,
and I have no practice at dating.
I mean, is this what people do?
Is this what you're doing?
Are you being a good-time guy?
No. I...
Sonya is not a good-time-guy girl.
That's... that's why she made me wait.
- So I'm trashy?
- No, you're not trashy.
You are a queen.
You are an african queen.
Who are you calling an african queen?
You are an african earth mother...
Who just happens to be
with a good-time guy.
It's-it's okay. It's different.
I mean, is it different?
Because it... feels trashy.
Look, okay, I gotta run.
So just... go with the flow.
- Is she naked?
- Almost.
- You're nervous?
- Yes, I am, very.
Sonya really likes you. Okay?
You already won her over.
Just go for it.
Go for it.
I've made you wait long enough.
They found you down at the beach.
Well, I hope I remembered my sunscreen.
This isn't funny, Keith. You're gonna
have to stay here for a while.
You know I hate hospitals.
You have bacterial endocarditis.
It's an infection. The kind
'caused by using dirty needles.
I gave you new needles
whenever you asked.
You have hep-C.
This was to prevent the spread.
- What did you do with the needles?
- I traded them.
I didn't share the dirty needles.
You traded my needles for more drugs?
I don't want to be like this anymore,
okay? I'm trying. I am.
And I haven't done well, but I can.
I can. I know I can,
as soon as I get out of here.
The bacteria is eating away
at your heart, Keith.
Do you understand that?
The hepatitis is destroying your liver.
If you leave now, you will die.
- You mad at me?
- You...
are a grown woman...
having sex with my brother.
But still...
you are a grown woman.
Do you think that...
a responsible grown woman like me,
... can also be the type of woman
that goes out with... the good-time guy?
Is that what he's calling himself,
yeah?
And I don't know. Can I?
Here's my advice...
be careful listening to my brother.
Things don't tend to end well
for the women in his life,
and you are my friend.
- What, are you mad at him?
- You know, he comes here, and...
It changes me. He pushes me,
and I start acting like a teenager.
I mean, I am a competent woman,
and when he's here, I feel like...
The little sister.
You know what?
I'm not blaming him,
but part of the reason why I asked Kevin
to move in with me
is because Archer kept badgering me
about our relationship not working
and how I was dating out of my element
because Kevin's a cop.
S.W.A.T.
So I made a choice to prove him wrong,
and he was right.
And I hate that.
Why don't you try and have
a different relationship with him?
Look at me and Sam: married,
divorced and then awkward,
and now we are actually talking
to each other about our love lives
- with other people.
- You are?
and if Sam and I can get past all that,
surely you and Archer can.
I gotta go.
She called 9-1-1.
Sweetie. I'm sorry.
My daughter hated me. I know that.
I have no idea what she told you
about me, but
I imagine it wasn't flattering.
Well, I could say that
that is privileged, but...
I don't think that would help
either one of us
to understand what's going on here.
So, yes.
Terri had negative feelings.
That's why I'm not sure
what you are asking for is a good idea.
I do corporate litigation.
I'm good at my work. I love it.
And when I got pregnant,
everyone told me,
"don't worry. It'll be amazing.
It'll change your life,"
and it did, but it wasn't amazing.
It was hard and exhausting, and...
it didn't make me feel
anything like work ever did.
So Terri's sense that you resented her,
it had some basis in fact?
I loved my daughter very much.
But she...
she changed my life from
being in control and fulfilled
to feeling constantly overwhelmed
and inadequate.
But, Sharon...
listen to yourself.
If motherhood for you was more
burden than blessing,
why would you want to subject
yourself to that again?
Because I want it
to be different this time.
- But what makes you assume it could be?
- The pain.
I've lived with it every single day
while she was alive
not being what she needed.
I kept thinking that at some point,
I would be able to...
make the relationship right.
I can't bring Terri back, but I...
I can...
have the child that she wanted...
and give it love and...
and attention and...
the support that she would've...
that she deserved...
that every child deserves.
I am capable of that.
Jane, you're in labor.
I need to deliver the baby now.
- It's early, but I think it'll be okay.
- I...
- need...
- It's okay.
I'm gonna take care of the baby. Okay?
I was surprised you called.
Look, the baby is in distress, and
Jane's not dilated, but I can't wait.
I've gotta do a C-section now,
but she's still on blood thinners
fromour procedure.
I need to reverse themor
she will bleed out.
That'll put her at risk for another stroke.
The baby can't survive without surgery.
What if I do a C-section with a spinal?
Can you do an intraoperative E.E.G.,
Monitor the neuro status?
That sounds like a good plan.
We're gonna get you up to the O.R.
- Tim...
- I already called him.
Go ahead.
I want you to hear me out.
I told you once, Cooper, no more
talking and expressing. It's done.
You know what? It could be done.
It could be done and over.
And there wouldn't even be that
much mess, you're not pregnant,
we don't live together,
there's no vacations planned,
and I don't have one thing
at your house,
and god knows you wouldn't leave
so much as a t-shirt at mine.
But emotionally,
I'm not ready to let go.
We are so not the cute couple...
in and out of each other's pockets,
finishing each other's sentences-
but we're still a couple.
We're us.
And I love us, and I...
am nowhere near ready to give up.
Even if you are, I'm not giving up.
Well, won't that be lonely?
Will you sign a 51-50 for Keith embry?
He's a drug addict.
You can't lock up an addict
and force them into treatment.
It's more than that.
He's living on the streets,
He's got no job, he's not eating,
he's got no clothes...
Grave disability.
Okay, you've done your homework.
You think it's a bad idea?
I think it's better
when people want treatment.
Forced treatment is problematic.
And with addicts...
he'll just lie to you.
- But if he stays on the streets,
he's gonna die.
- Maybe,
but 72 hours in a psych facility
isn't gonna change that.
72 hours to evaluate, then they can
choose to do a 14-day hold,
- and then 30 days.
- Does he have a support system,
a wife or kids?
He has a wife, but no kids.
Thank god. That'd be a disaster.
Well, kids can inspire things
in people that adults can't.
I mean, if he'd had kids...
I mean, wouldn't it make a difference
if you'd had kids?
I'm past that window.
The sad truth is, it's
probably better that Anna and I
didn't have kids.
I'm too selfish, and...
I get angry.
So...
will you sign the 51-50?
You know, I think when you...
force something on someone that they
don't want, they'll never fully commit.
So if he doesn't want this for himself,
he'll just walk out the door.
The...
baby...
Almost there, Jane.
Hang in.
Any bleeding?
Persistent oozing around the edges.
Any changes in her E.E.G.?
- No. She's fine.
- Bovie.
Jane, I'm gonna take the baby out now.
Lap pad,
and have an intubation tray standing by.
what'S... wrong?
He's not breathing...yet.
Laryngoscope and a suction catheter, now.
He's aspirated meconium.
How much time do I have?
You've got about 30 seconds.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Stand by with a 3-0 endotracheal tube
and a ventilator.
- 20 seconds, Addison.
- Come on, breathe...
He's okay.
He's gonna be okay, Jane.
I think I was wrong...
- about Sharon using Terri's embryos.
- What about Terri?
Well, I was thinking about Terri
growing up, about
how she must have felt, and how
kids intuitively know
if their parents resent them.
But I was also thinking that...
that children only see one side,
and that if a parent understands their
feelings and really wants to change...
I actually think Sharon will be
a different mom this time around.
And she's not just trying
to replace her daughter?
It's not guilt?
Maybe the fact that she's committed
to being a good mom...
maybe that's reason enough
to give her a second chance.
Keith, what the hell are you doing?
I gotta get outta here.
I'm just... I'm... going crazy.
I'm sorry, Pete, but I just...
I got to, man.
You need to stay.
I need you to get better.
Ellen needs you to get better.
She still wants her husband back.
- I can't be that guy anymore.
- You can.
I am not gonna sit back
and let you hurt yourself, Keith.
You have a real chance to get clean.
I can't.
No... Wait...
You're gonna be committed to
the psychiatric ward of St. Ambrose.
They have doctors here who specialize
in treating addiction. They can help you.
Oh, you son of a bitch.
You son of a bitch.
All right! Hold on a second...
If it's gonna work, he has to want it.
He can get there.
He's not beyond help.
He's not.
Here we go.
Wait... Wait, please.
Please wait.
What if I'm making a mistake?
What if...
what if... I can't do any better
this time? what if...
What if... I'm just destined
to be a bad mother?
You're not destined to be anything.
You have a chance
to be whatever you want.
And if the person you were before
wasn't working,
you can change it, and...
you can be the kind of mother
that you think
that that baby, that Terri's baby
deserves.
And if you commit to that
and you decide that it's what you want,
it'll be amazing...
for both of you.
This is the chance you wanted, right?
Then take it.
He's beautiful.
Breathing on his own,
you did good, Jane.
You want me to hand you the baby?
I'm...
glad... you're here.
Here you go.
Hi, baby.
Anxiety, induced asthma.
What do you have?
For Sam?
- I don't need anything.
- Yes, he does. Sonya is a problem.
- We haven't...
- Sealed the deal.
Well, we've tried. But I just,
I get nervous, and...
and then I start to wheeze.
Butterbur and dried I.V. steep it
in hot water for five minutes.
One big glass should help reduce
bronchoconstrictions for a few hours.
Good luck.
- what?
- It's just...
after everything you two have been
through, you're still... you're...
you're friends.
- Is that weird?
- No... It's great.
I think so.
She'still not talking to you?
I opened my soul, and...
nothing.
Pete doesn't want kids.
Sheldon doesn't want kids.
I don't want kids...
you know? I mean,
what business do I have having a kid?
Me...
raising a kid by myself
that I don't want
- and wouldn't know what to do with...
- Well, you're not alone.
Every night, I wake up in a cold sweat.
I lay there panicked
that i'm gonna wait too long.
I'm gonna wait too long...
and then it'll be too late to have an abortion,
and then I will just be stuck
and I'll never be free ever again.
I don't know what to do. I mean, all
I know is that unless you're bringing me
sticky buns and gyros and burgers, I...
I'm lost, cooper.
I mean, I see you, and I feel better,
but most of the time, I walk around
lost and...
alone and scared.
Well, then I will be here.
Whenever you need me, I will
be here, and we'll sit and we'll eat
and we'll figure this out.
We'll work through everything, and...
make it okay, together.
You'd do that for me?
I'd do anything for you.
I am not glad
that you are working for the enemy,
and you're gonna have to learn
to stay out of my personal life,
but if you want to be here, then...
This is gonna be fun.
- I thought you had a date.
- I canceled.
So...
- no good-time guy?
- I don't know.
All I know is that I was getting ready
for a date, and I realized that
I would rather be with you.
So I'm more than a good-time girl?
Now I never said that you were
a good-time girl.
Good-time guy, that's me.
No, you...
you're a keeper.
You let me in?
Where's your child?
She is at a sleepover.
Well, then let's get you...
naked.
Peace offering.
Cornbread chicken casserole.
Mama used to bring it to the neighbors
to make peace after
Landry and Duke let their pigs out.
it's the only thing I know how to make.
I screwed up, Coop,
and I want to make it right.
So...
I was thinking,
you wanted me to move in
a few months ago. Maybe now...
that's the right thing to do...
a good first step.
What's the matter?
You goin' somewhere?
I'm moving in with Violet.
Transcript : Ydy
The Mc Dreamy Team
pour www.forom.com