Corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com
She's my patient...
Lauren Woods, 33 weeks.
Can you tell me what
happened, Lauren, anything?
Coast guard fished her
out of Santa Monica Bay.
- Did anybody see anything?
- Already in the water when she was spotted.
- Michael? Where's Michael?
- Hold on, Lauren. Hang in there.
She's in v-tach. Get her
in trauma surgery two.
All right, sounds like
classic VSD consistent with
a large defect between the
right and left ventricles.
- This is new?
- Never been there before.
The stress from the accident
probably blew the underlying defect open.
- Pulse ox is dropping. Her lungs collapsed.
- Needs a chest tube.
- I got it. - All right, put her
under. Prep for an emergency c-section.
The baby's in severe distress.
Pressure's dropping.
- She's throwing multiple PVCs. -
She's back in v-tach. Crash cart.
- Lost her pressure. - All
right. V-fib. Charge to 200.
- Addison, we gotta get that baby outta there.
- Almost.
She's in cardiac arrest. Addison, now.
All right, clear.
Hey.
I guess you're going to the
St. Ambrose thing tonight?
No choice. William White's being honored.
He writes my checks. You?
Oh, no.
I used to like parties, but now...
I don't know. The big crowd...
Guess that's all part of the crazy, huh?
Avoiding dull speeches,
big egos and drunken colleagues?
Maybe not so crazy.
Are you being nice to me?
Maybe.
A little.
Morning.
Did you get a chance to look
at the data I e-mailed you
on my, uh, human cloning project?
Human cloning.
I've decided it's time to clone people.
- Yeah, well, I'm trying to work.
- Which is all you've been doing lately.
It's easier here than at home.
Home is lonely, and, uh... work is good.
You know, I could help...
with work mostly.
The emotional stuff...
I'm a little crippled.
Thank you.
Naomi.
I, uh, I...
Um... I'm sorry. Am I interrupting?
Yes.
No. No, we were just working.
I just wanted to say thank
you in advance, for tonight.
I really do appreciate it.
Well, I am honored, really.
Sucking up to the boss.
No, I am presenting William with his award
- at the ball tonight.
- You're coming, right?
- Got my dancing shoes on.
- Good. Good.
Anyway, I just, uh...
wanted to express my gratitude.
I'm sure your speech will be tremendous,
impressive as always.
How's Lauren?
Uh, she's sedated, in ICU.
Echo showed a persistent VSD in her heart.
She needs surgery, and I can't
do that until she's stable.
- How's the baby?
- Her lungs aren't mature enough. She's having a hard time.
You were good in there this morning.
Did you get in contact with her husband?
I tried.
Okay, well, I'm gonna
go check up on Lauren
and then go back to the practice.
Sam.
Can we just... will you talk to me?
I'll keep you posted on Lauren.
"No" is not an option.
Addison's memo said
everybody goes to the ball.
All right, well, I'm
gonna go ahead and pull
the "wife died, single parent card," so...
- I'm out.
- Oh, I was attacked.
You may have read about
it? Yeah, it kinda gives me
- carte blanche to ignore all memos.
- No, no, no, no. People, you know, life happens, we move on.
We use big, gaudy events like this
to move on with our lives.
Me? Broke up with my girlfriend.
Yeah. Small potatoes, maybe,
but I'm really looking forward
to getting out there and...
And forgetting about the past.
- You ever gonna grow up?
- Oh, I hope not.
I'm feeling so much
younger and freer lately.
Yes. Hey, can you tell Dell and Violet
that this thing tonight
is a command performance?
Oh, it is. We all go.
We're gonna brush our teeth,
we're gonna put on expensive clothes,
we're gonna go to this fancy party,
and we're gonna have fun.
We're gonna have fun, okay?
Yeah, so...
see you there.
Hey, Sam.
Sam. Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
I have no idea how to plan
a pregnant 15 year old's wedding.
- There's no guidebook. I checked.
- Well, it's a wedding.
It's not traditional, I know,
but hopefully it's the
only one she'll have.
- She... she just wants it to be special.
- No, what she wants is a fairy tale.
And to be honest, I'm not
feeling very happily ever after.
Well, find a balance.
You know, nice but not too big,
everything tasteful, elegant, but...
appropriate.
- What?
- You're hired.
- No, Sam...
- Look, Maya's gonna come over. She's gonna drop some stuff off.
You take a look at it, tell me
if you think it's appropriate.
Could you? Pl... Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Paige...
Says you've had a fever
for a couple of days.
Doesn't seem to be affecting
your texting fingers.
- That's good.
- Sorry.
- How's the new school?
- It sucked for a while, eating alone every day.
But I have a lot of
friends now, so it's good.
Good. Friends are good.
You definitely have a fever.
And you look... a little yellowish.
Let's look at your glands.
I just need to take a look.
Okay.
How'd you get that?
Um, I don't know. It
w... it was just there.
It looks like a bite.
You got a wild little
brother I don't know about?
It was probably my curling iron.
I've burnt myself with it before.
Paige, did somebody bite you?
No. I'd know if someone bit me.
The nurse said she's coming to?
In and out. Her sats are low.
I was just adjusting her oxygen.
Lauren. Hey.
Your baby was born. It's a girl.
Her lungs are weak, but
she's hanging in there.
I'm still working on her, okay?
- The pressure... I can't breathe.
- Okay.
Hi, Lauren. I'm Dr. Bennett.
The reason you're feeling pressure
is because your heart isn't
pumping like it should.
We discovered a hole in
between your two ventricles.
As soon as you get
stronger, I'll do surgery.
- We can fix this.
- Is Michael here?
- Has... he seen the baby?
- We haven't found him yet.
The coast guard is still
searching the water.
Was... was he in a boat with you?
Is that what happened?
Lauren?
No.
He...
left.
He told me he didn't love me and he left.
How did you end up in the water?
I thought that if I jumped,
the undertow would take me.
I wanted to die. You
shouldn't have saved me.
I w... I want to die.
I don't want to feel better.
I don't want surgery. I
don't want to be fixed.
What happened, Lauren?
W... what happened with
you and your husband?
That's just it. I don't know.
We were gonna have a baby. It was fine.
And then I came home,
and there was this note...
a note...
saying that he left.
Most of his things were gone.
And I don't know why.
I waited for days for
him to come back or call.
I just felt empty.
I couldn't think. I couldn't breathe.
And I just wanted it to be over and done
so I wouldn't feel that anymore...
and I wouldn't be alone.
Well, you're... you're not alone anymore.
You have a baby upstairs.
And I almost killed her.
You can't force me to
have this surgery, can you?
Uh, well, I... I think we'd
all like you to want it.
Well, I don't.
Just tell them that I refuse.
A human bite?
She's denying it, but
she's got teeth marks
- and her liver's tender, she's got a yellowish pallor.
- Well, it's certainly a unique way
to transmit hep b. And
if the test confirms it,
we're gonna have to find out who it is,
- 'cause they're sick, too, in more ways than one.
- You think it's, like, a sexual predator
who likes biting young
girls, he's got her scared?
Maybe it's abuse. What about her mother?
Mean, biting her? I doubt that.
Maybe it's some sort of s&m thing.
She's 13 years old.
Who goes around biting 13 year olds?
Try vampires.
- Funny.
- I'm serious.
Do you not live in America?
Do the words "Twilight"
- and "New Moon" mean nothing to you?
- They're... they're fictional.
Not to teenage girls who think
the bite of a vampire's
a sign of eternal love.
How could you let some boy bite you?
I knew that you shouldn't be hanging out
- with that Amber and Ashley and what's her name.
-They didn't do anything.
You have hepatitis.
You're in the hospital.
You're 13 years old.
Paige, I think we're gonna need
to know the name of the boy,
because he may be sick, too.
- You'll tell 'em who it is, now.
- Angie. Angie.
How could I have missed this?
Why don't you go and grab a cup of coffee,
and let us talk to her? Thanks. It's okay.
You don't understand.
He's my soul mate.
We're bound together for all of eternity.
- We love each other.
- Well, that's nice, but it shouldn't involve
- biting so hard that it draws blood.
- Yeah.
It's just a sign of what
we are to each other.
And he's not sick, so you
don't need to do anything.
He might not be sick now,
but he's carrying the disease,
and it could be damaging his liver,
which is very serious.
If my mom knows who he is,
she'll never let me see him again.
So if I get him to come in,
- will you promise not to tell my mom?
- W... she should know.
She can't.
So you promise... or I'm not telling.
- You can't promise not to tell.
- That kid bit her.
- He drew blood. He got her sick. Her labs are getting worse.
- I know, but it's her boyfriend,
and they were necking
in some perverse way.
It's sexual. It's not violent.
It's like any other consensual
sex act a minor tells us about.
We are bound...
doctor-patient confidentiality.
Your dating habits aside...
- sucking blood is not sex.
- Your lack of dating habits aside,
you heard what she said.
- She thinks she's in love...
- She's 13.
Bottom line is, it's
sex. It's not violence.
We can't do anything about
it. I'll make her the promise.
We'll get the kid in here.
I'll see if he's sick.
We'll figure it out from there.
You know, we could always seal his coffin,
expose him to sunlight.
Without the surgery, she will die.
Which is why you have to 51-50
her. Not having the surgery
- is just another way for her to attempt suicide.
- Well, legally and ethically speaking,
refusing treatment isn't the same at all.
And she's depressed. She's not crazy.
She tried to kill herself and
her baby. That's not crazy?
- No.
- So she tries to kill herself, fails,
- but gets close enough that she might actually get her wish?
- She agreed to try antidepressants.
That might help. Though I think
she probably only agreed to it
- 'cause she's hoping he'll change his mind and come back.
- Well, we can't wait for the antidepressants to work.
- She'll die. We have to force the surgery.
- No. Her depression makes that a bad idea.
It doubles her risk of dying on the table,
and it's dicey enough as it is.
All right, then I'll...
I'll go find Michael,
- get him to come here.
- What, you think it's that easy to just make him love her?
His wife is dying. He has a baby.
There could've been a thousand
reasons why he walked away.
- I'm gonna go find him.
- Good luck trying to change his mind.
We've been calling, leaving messages.
I know. I got them.
Your wife and child are in the hospital.
Lauren's refusing to have a
surgery that could save her
because you're not there.
- She said you left out of the blue.
- Ou... out of the blue?
Look, this didn't just happen.
I tr... I tried to get
her to see for a long time.
She just didn't...
she didn't want to see it.
She didn't want to listen.
Then she got pregnant, and
I tried to make it work.
- But I just... I... I can't.
- What about the baby?
I never wanted a baby. She knew that.
And I... I... look, I tried to
be okay with that, but I'm not.
I don't love her anymore.
Okay, Michael, look, can
you just be there for her,
- just for now, just until she's a little stronger?
- Look, I'll support the baby. I told her that.
But if I... if I go back,
she's just gonna do it again
the next time I go,
and I'll never get away.
Look, what I did to Paige,
it's not a bad thing.
It just signifies that
our souls are connected.
Yeah, but your viruses, too.
It's a health hazard.
So I do need to know...
if you've done this biting
thing with any other girls.
- Of course not.
- I'm just asking, you know, doctor to patient, just us.
I don't mean to embarrass you.
Look, you may not understand this,
but...
We're destined for each other.
I would never betray that.
I've walked this earth for 2,000 years,
searching for her.
Yeah.
Um, I've used a lot of lines in my day.
- I'm not buying that one.
- Well, I'm not asking you to.
Okay, I'm gonna need to know
the names of all the girls
- that you've done this biting thing with.
- Paige told me. You can't tell anyone.
- No, but I can tell her what a little schmuck you are.
- And you think she'd believe you?
She and her friends love
all this vampire crap.
- Tell me who else you have bitten.
- No offense, but bite me.
- Hey.
- You have a minute?
- You okay?
Ugh. One of my patients
has hung her entire
life's happiness on a man.
He's gone, and now she wants to die.
Well, she wouldn't be the first person.
Why do women let men do that to them,
let 'em get inside their
head and make 'em crazy?
And they make us feel really
good when it's... good,
and then... they make us want to
- curl up in a little ball and die when we can't have them.
- We are talking about your patient, right?
How's that speech going for tonight?
Oh, ugh. William White...
I mean, how do you write a
speech about a billionaire?
- You write about the man, not the money.
- Yeah, I know, but it is William White.
You know, that's a man
who could get into your
head and make you crazy.
- You know... you know what I think?
- William White?
William White?
No.
All right, there... there was a look.
Uh-huh.
And a... moment.
- And he touched my hand.
- Oh! He likes you.
Oh...
All right, there was... there
was definitely something.
But I just...
I can't decide whether
it was exciting or...
Sexual harassment-y or...
All the more reason to
go tonight, to find out.
I mean, that's what these events are for.
- And there's an open bar. I mean, you get drunk, get lucky.
- Yeah, but the idea of getting dressed up
and... and pretending to enjoy myself
- with everything that's going on, it's just...
- Oh, come on. It'll be fun. We could both use it.
William White.
Hey. Your fever's down.
- That's good. How you feeling?
- Great.
Good. I told you Seth couldn't get sick.
He's too strong. I must have
gotten this some other way.
Okay, um, Paige, there's
no good way to say this,
so...
he's been biting other girls.
It doesn't work that way.
These other girls could get sick.
- He said they were your friends. We need to know who they are.
- Seth wouldn't do that.
- My friends wouldn't do that to me.
- Well, Paige, he...
- You don't get it.
- Paige...
Stop trying to turn
this into something bad.
Oh, I gotta admit, Sam, I'm lost.
This is all very pink.
Yeah, she wants, uh... pink candy almonds
with "Maya and Dink
forever" stamped on them.
So I'm trying to find...
So I guess the, uh,
- the horse drawn carriage is out?
- Okay.
Wait. A hot air balloon...
those are her ideas.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Wow, wedding stuff, huh?
You need a hand?
Uh, no. We're good. We're good. Thanks.
What's up?
I just wanted to talk to you about Lauren.
Did you talk to the husband?
Yeah, he doesn't want anything
to do with her or the baby.
- Do you want me to go with you to tell her?
- We can't.
What, you can't tell her?
You think it's better
to give her false hope
- that he's gonna show up?
- If it gets her into surgery, yeah.
Oh, good. All right.
So then we lie to her,
- I fix her heart, then we break it again.
- But she'll be alive. Unless you have a better idea.
I mean, this way we have time
for the antidepressants to kick in.
I mean, maybe he'll change
his mind and come around.
Oh, do you really think
that's gonna happen, Addison?
You really think that she
should wait around for that?
Violet, can you give us a few minutes?
Yes.
Really, Sam?
You're gonna be this guy?
I tell you we can't be together,
so you're gonna be the guy who punishes me
- for doing the right thing?
- Oh, please. "The right thing"? You're afraid of Naomi.
I am not afraid of Naomi.
- I don't want to be a cheater again.
- We are two grown, single adults.
Please tell me how that is cheating.
Because I would be
betraying my best friend.
She's my ex-wife.
She does not get to decide
what happens between you and me.
She does not get to decide.
I decide. You decide. You're scared.
- I am not scared, Sam.
- You're scared because you know that this could be real.
Nothing's standing between us.
I'm not married. I don't live in Seattle.
This could be real, and you
don't know how to do real.
N... no, no, that is not it.
This is about Naomi. She's my best friend.
- You divorced her, Sam. I'm not willing to do that.
- She... she would understand.
- If you were honest with her, she would get over it.
- Oh, what planet are you on?
Y... she won't even forgive her own child
for getting pregnant by accident.
You're planning a wedding by yourself.
You really think she's gonna forgive us?
So my ex-wife gets to dictate
who I can and can't sleep with?
Good. Great.
Perfect.
Sam, please...
William White has shown us all
what can be achieved when
there is a strong will
backed by a kind heart
and deep pockets.
His generosity is...
I love Naomi,
but is this speech gonna
end while I'm still young?
I can't believe I'm here,
stomaching this about William White.
It's a fund-raiser for
the hospital, Charlotte,
- your hospital. - William remains
a small-town boy at heart...
Well, some things never change.
Cooper. 2:00.
Such a whore.
You okay?
Not like I care.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our man of the year, Mr. William White.
Nice speech. Mm.
I'm gonna go work the room.
Our doctors are just not that much fun.
- Tell me about it.
- Now have a drink
- and tell us what you really think about him.
- I meant what I said.
Right, after he forced
me down your throat?
Uh, figuratively speaking.
Or maybe you've forgiven him
after you've realized I'm not so bad.
Admit it. I'm not so bad.
Hell of a speech.
I'm not sure I'm worthy. It was, um...
Thank you.
I heard what you're going through...
with your daughter.
- The assistants talk.
- Yeah. Um... well, I, uh,
I, uh, I just want you to know that it...
- It's not going to affect my work in any...
- I'm not worried about your work.
Okay. I'm worried about you.
Oh, no. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Are you?
Yeah.
I am. I'm... I'm...
I'm...
Well, you know, y...
All right. You know what? I'm furious.
And I'm on edge.
I'm uncomfortable in my skin,
and all I do is work all day.
All I do is mix sperm and
ova into petri dishes all day.
All I do is make babies for people
who would do anything
to have a baby, you know,
people who are praying to have a baby.
And my stupid child goes
and makes one in an instant,
and I just kinda want to scream.
I want to scream because it's
just, like, it's crazy karma.
And I, uh... and it's like
life spanking me in the face.
And I'm just trying to push through.
And, you know, I'm just
eating too much cake
and doing as well as I can, you know?
And then you show up here
today, and... and you're my boss,
and... and I think
you're flirting with me,
which is... because if
you're not flirting with me,
then clearly I can add
delusional to my list of flaws,
and, uh, also fired, because
I just said that out loud.
But I'm just spending
so much time these days
keeping my mouth shut and
not talking about things
and pretending that
things aren't happening,
and... and I just can't
do that anymore, you know?
'Cause I learned a long time ago
that in order to make speeches in public,
sened up,
so I had to drink three martinis
before I could get up
there and make the speech,
and also two glasses
of wine, and so now...
I'm just a little loose right now.
I'm just a little loose
and a little furious,
and, um, that's... that's kind
of where I started talking.
- So I'm... I'm gonna stop.
- Okay.
I don't know where to start. Um...
First...
I'd be furious, too.
Second, I... I don't think it's karma.
I think it's just life.
And third...
I am flirting with you.
You are?
Is that okay?
Uh...
Yeah.
Come on, let's dance.
Word is I'm pretty good on my feet.
Cooper was just telling
us this great story
about this time when he was
- in Fort Lauderdale on spring break...
- Yeah.
And he got thrown into
jail for stealing a boat?
Yeah, well, you should get
him to tell you about the time
his mother caught him in his closet
- with an issue of "ladies' home journal"...
- Okay, okay, yeah. It's good seeing you.
Oh. What?
Did that help?
- A little.
- Okay.
Violet, you came.
Well, uh, I'm drinking fruity drinks
with umbrellas in them.
- I... I would give you this one, but it's for Dell.
- Oh, that's good that he's here...
And you're here.
You're done being mad at me, huh?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Forgiveness is... that...
- That's very big for me right now.
- Me, too.
You...
You know I'm still messed up, Pete.
I mean, I'm better.
But I'm... I'm not...
- I mean, I... I can't...
- I know.
Okay.
Well, I...
Yeah.
Why does this suck so much?
'Cause we're screwed up.
'Cause people have screwed with our lives,
and now we're... stuck.
You think they're having fun?
Maybe. Or maybe they're stuck, too.
They're just better at hiding it.
Yeah. Like Sam.
Sam is planning a wedding
for his pregnant
15-year-old daughter.
Naomi's pretending that's not happening.
Cooper and Charlotte are,
uh... well, they're too crazy
to realize that they're
still in love with each other.
And Addison... I... I don't know.
- I don't know what's going on with Addison.
- Addison's, uh, uptight, twangy all the time.
- She's rubber
band-y... - Yes.
- You know, like a rubber...
- Yes.
Yeah. She's uptight and weird.
- Very... very weird. I don't know.
- And Pete...
Well... I guess that's all on me, huh?
I should probably take
this thing off, you know?
I mean, after everything Heather did,
I should just take this thing off.
I should just take it off and pawn it.
I just want to move on.
Well, moving on's not that simple.
I mean, that ring connects
you to something good,
for you and for her and betsey.
To take it off is hard.
This is all hard.
I know.
Having a good time?
Ugh. Like gum surgery.
You want to tell me?
No, because I always tell
you, and you always listen.
And I don't want to be
that girl who only
comes to you for whining.
Plus, it's complicated.
Oh, I'm so tired of complicated.
Why can't more things be... easy?
You know what the problem
is? We expect too much.
We just expect to be happy.
What gives us the right?
You think?
Well, either that or we try too hard.
I mean, I never wanted a kid. I got one.
I... I didn't try for it. I just got one.
The best thing that ever happened to me.
So you think we find
happiness by accident?
Maybe.
What if you find it and you can't have it?
You're getting a little
close to home there.
Oh, sorry. Ugh.
What are we doing here?
All I want to do is go home,
kick off these incredibly painful shoes,
eat pizza and watch some really bad tv,
where people's lives are
more screwed up than mine.
Yeah.
Simply place the rhinestone or stud
in the slot...
push down and...
Do you think this is just
the depression talking?
I don't feel depressed right now. Do you?
No.
Wait. Wait.
Do you think it's the alcohol talking?
I'm sober.
I know. I kind of am, too.
Okay, but we are definitely not doing it.
Really?
Oh, we are so doing it.
Get naked now.
Okay.
That was fantastic.
We're good.
We're great. Yeah.
We... we have, like a... like a thing...
Like a you-and-me
thing with the sex.
I know. Ooh.
We're like...
We're like olympians, gold medalists.
Oh, ooh, wouldn't that be
good if that was a thing?
There's something I have to tell you.
I'm still in love with Violet.
I think...
I'm in love with Sam.
Oh, yeah.
- Had to humiliate me last night, huh?
- With what's her face?
Yes, what's her face,
the perfectly nice woman I was talking to.
- Talking?
- Yeah. You know what? I didn't throw her in your face.
We work together. This is gonna happen.
And we need a truce. We need a truce.
- Otherwise, we're both gonna go crazy.
- And you think you could truce?
Show of good faith.
- You were right about the vampire.
- Of course I was.
I had to tell her her immortal
beloved was biting around.
- Nice. Break her poor little heart.
- Actually, no.
- She didn't believe me.
-She's 13 years old.
She wants to believe in the fairy tale
we've all been Fed as little girls
- about knights and princes and vampires.
- Last time I checked, vampires aren't from fairy tales.
They're from horror stories,
and this is health issue.
The bloodsucker must be stopped,
except Paige won't tell
me the names of her friends
- who have been biting ar...
- You really don't get women and heartbreak, Cooper.
This girl's about to get
smacked upside the head
by the first real one of her life.
Why don't I talk to her?
Pretty sure I know
where she's coming from.
Hey.
The baby's doing better.
Lung function's improving.
Lauren is still refusing surgery.
Well, we know those medications
don't work overnight.
So...
you and Sam...
is there something the rest
of us should know about?
Is there a problem with the practice?
Oh, no. No.
There's... there's not a problem, no.
I've never seen you two so hostile.
- Is it the wedding?
- It's nothing to worry about.
You know, I think I'm gonna
take the baby down to see Lauren,
show her that she has
something to live for.
- I... I wouldn't recommend that.
- Why not?
I... depression isn't not understanding
that you have something to live for.
It's knowing that you
should feel differently,
but it's so bad
that all you want to
do is curl up and die.
That's where she is.
You think she doesn't understand
that she has a beautiful baby up here?
So what do we do? We let her die?
We wait. We hope.
We keep trying.
I know how it is, Paige, honestly.
You love somebody. You want 'em
to love you back the same way.
You think love should
be magic and perfect.
But real life isn't like that.
You don't know him.
I know guys like him.
I know he's biting
other girls besides you.
S... Seth would never lie to me.
Men lie to us all the time.
And we lie to them.
Sometimes you do it to protect
yourself or the other person.
Sometimes it's how you
try to get what you want.
And sometimes it's just easier.
If you think love means
never lying to each other,
you're not ready for it.
It's hard.
I know it is.
You get bit. You think it's for life.
When you find out it isn't, it hurts.
It leaves a scar.
But we need to figure out who
the other girls are, Paige.
We can't help 'em if we
don't know who they are.
I don't want to be alone again.
I know.
Hey.
I need your advice, um...
What, did somebody die?
Uh, nope. Getting married.
I'm... I'm helping Sam.
I... I hope that's, uh...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's... it's, um, it's good.
I'm, you know, glad he's
not going through it alone.
Um, that's... that's not
what the advice was about.
Um...
William?
I saw you two on the
dance floor last night.
Oh. Y... uh...
Well, um,
what... what... what exactly did you see?
I saw my friend, who's been
going through a rough time,
enjoying herself in the company
of a charming, rich bachelor.
Do you like him?
I don't know.
I mean, I'm flattered.
- And I don't care about the rich.
- Doesn't hurt.
No, it doesn't hurt, but, uh...
I don't know.
I mean, I... I... I
thought he was one thing,
and turns out maybe
he's, uh, more than that.
Then maybe that's what you need.
Oh, Naomi.
You can tell me to butt out, and I will.
But this wedding, it...
look, it's all wrong.
But it is only gonna happen once.
And I would hate to see
you stuck... on the outside.
She's in pulmonary edema.
Lauren, Lauren, listen to me.
I found Michael, and he's not coming back.
You have to face the truth.
You want him and you can't have
him, and I know that's awful.
Lauren, we all lose things that we love,
- but we have to find a way to move on.
- I don't know if I'm strong enough.
Look, your baby fought
like hell to survive.
She's one day old, and she found
the strength, and so can you.
You have to do the surgery, Lauren, now.
Okay.
All right, I'll get a team to scrub in.
There's someone here to see you.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
- Hey.
You did good work.
Yeah, the... the repair went well.
I'm, uh, I'm happy for her.
Sam...
Are we gonna get past this?
I'm trying, Addison.
Hey.
I'm just, uh, picking out flowers
and... linens.
Who... who knew that there were, like,
ten different shades of pink?
No more than 50 guests.
St. Mark's for the ceremony,
and afterwards, a small,
tasteful reception.
Call Mark's Gardens for the flowers.
No taffeta or sequins anywhere.
Uh, Tasha at Rene Strauss
can pick out a dress
that is appropriate and
not ridiculously expensive.
Palisades catering can do a buffet.
And, uh...
sparkling cider instead of champagne,
seeing as the bride is pregnant and...
the groom is underage.
Naomi...
Uh, that's all I can do.
Okay? That's, uh, that's...
that's all I can do.
Okay.
I wish I could do that...
Just some gesture that
would put me past all this.
You could.
I could.
But I can't.
Heading out?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, sorry.
It's just been one of those days.
Well, maybe you should get
a glass of wine with me then.
Oh, I don't... I don't know. I...
Naomi, I really enjoyed last night,
dancing with you.
Why are you interested in me?
I mean, what, why?
Well, I could give you
all the standard answers,
like, you're beautiful, smart, funny,
but that's just what people say.
Why?
You make my heart beat faster.
You just... do.
Oh, g... I got problems, William.
Don't we all?
Well, I do like wine.
Do you think we're ever gonna...
What?
Not...
be in love with other people?
Who... Violet?
And Sam.
I don't know.
Maybe this is okay.
Maybe this is better.
Love hurts.
But this... doesn't hurt.
This feels like...
happiness.
Yeah, yeah.