I feel like I've been through a war.
Parasites... My brother,
had parasites in his brain, and...
Epic, epic war
I know but the good news is
that we won.
Archer is nearly himself again.
Nearly?
What? something wrong?
God no! No...
Everything is fine.
All parts are working.
- Okay, my brother my brother....
- Sorry.
It's just that it's...
It's good. Really good.
- Yeah?
- I...
I think he's my boyfriend.
He sleeps over every night
and he calls constantly.
He's been talking lately Addison.
I think I have a man.
Archer is comitting.
I'm getting another bottle of wine
Yes please.
Archer! What do you...
Is this your wife?
Are you married?
But...
He has a girlfriend.
Who is here.
Damn it!
I'm sure you're a very nice person, but
maybe a little bit old to get filled up on the doorway
but now it's all the best.
Good bye.
You...
You've got to get the lipstick
off of your face
This is pre or post sex?
I hope you used a condomn
you ****
I'm in trouble right?
Hey Dell, can I call...
Yeah, is she...
she okay?
Great, I'll be right there, thanks bye
Addison, anything to eat?
Hi, I'm edible.
What are you doing here?
Hi
Okay you two, you just
do whatever...
the two of you do.
I gotta go
Come on... Bare down.
One more big push.
It's a fast labor, I'm sorry
I thought I could be doing it solo.
You're doing great.
Come on Lea you're almost there.
- I can see his head.
- All right, the baby is coming.
Come on Lea! Come on!
Got it.
Matthew. He's here.
I want to hold him.
I want my little boy.
What's wrong?
- It's not a boy.
- What... ultrasound was wrong?
It's a girl?
I'm not sure.
Private Practice S02E17
Wait and See
I know this is impossibly hard
and we don't have
all the answers yet, but
your baby have something like a penis,
There's also a vaginal opening
The baby's heart and lungs
and brain are very healthy
and that's important for you
to understand
But what is it?
We'll run some genetic
and hormonal tests
I consult with my collegue Dr Bennet
she's an excellent endocrinologist.
- We're gonna get you answers.
- Well, until then...
what do we tell people?
What are we...
What are we call him?
He's Mathew... He's...
He's supposed to be...
he's supposed to be Mathew.
Why did you go to Seattle?
I'm sorry. It's just...
it's running through my mind on a loop
like a song I can't stop humming,
so I have to ask.
Seattle.
- Why did you go?
- Archer's surgery.
Look, Naomi likes to pretend
like she has it all together,
Well she's an Ivy league
educated doctor with...
the best shoe collection I've ever seen
- so she does have it all together
- Usually, but...
Archer getting sick,
In fact, she need a shoulder to lean on.
Is it?
I think it's great.
You've managed the impossible
You've maintain
a good relationship with your ex.
It's just why I like you.
I like you too.
- You're not a good guy.
- Yes, I am.
I was wondering, I run a
couple's therapy group and
my co-leader's down
with a stomach bug and
I think it's very important
that we have a male and,
a female therapist
You know... Role modeling
Communication modeling
and... I wondered if you'd like to
fill in.
I know, not such a great idea
considering
No, no, I... I think it's good.
I like working with couples.
Are you sure?
- What time?
- Our conference room, at one
- Lunch time
- Okay, see you then
How is it?
the baby?
- It's fine.
- Good.
That's good that it's fine because...
I would really apreciate
if we didn't talk about this right now,
because I don't know if I can handle it.
I'll see you later
Oh, you've got that look that "it's
impossible to decide for Violet" look.
Look, I've just given up.
I'm going cool.
Not cold, just cool
The hell of it with cold.
Therapy should be interesting.
You and Violet
are in therapy?
No we're doing therapy,
together, it's a...
- couple's group.
- You're leading it?
- As a couple?
- Yes, we are.
Good luck with that.
You should have seen the look
on their faces, it was awfull.
like this is their fault
Are you okay?
No, what...
What do we tell them?
Well, I...
wish I had a good answer,
but the baby does have 11 beta
hydroxylase deficiency
- What is it?
- It is an enzime deficiency
that causes an over production
of testosterone in the baby in-utero
That's why the baby has
both male and female sex organ.
- The caryotype is XX
- So the baby is a girl?
No, it's not that simple.
Yes, genetically, it is a girl, but...
30% of these cases, these kids
orient towards male.
So we can't tell the parents
what sex the baby is?
Well, they have to choose and then we
can surgically correct the genitalia.
You just said there is
a 30% margin for error
Post-op, the healing is faster
and it leaves the genitelia functional.
All, suported with hormon therapy.
But what if they choose wrong
and the baby oriented the other way?
Exactly, we shouldn't have them choose
the gender now, but not do surgery.
Let them raise
the baby as a boy or a girl
and then when the baby becomes
an adolescent, he'll make up
- its own mind.
- That's the problem.
Living in an it.
everyry sleep over, every swim party or
lockroom is gonna be a cause for panic
Maybe it should be, whatever it is
and not what everybody wants it to be.
While I was out,
I've been missing all the fun.
Half and half body parts.
- Inter-sex baby.
- Kinda like worms.
Some people think gender is hardwired.
So what do we do? It's not
gonna change the outcome.
Me, I found that freakish
but I'm a boy.
- How was your first day back?
- It's perfect now
Good morning dr King
Move in with me Cooper.
I know you care about
Violet and the baby,
and I understand
why you wanted to move in with her.
But you can still be there for both of them,
without living at her place.
Violet is afraid to be alone.
-So I need to be there for her.
- I'm your girlfriend.
And I'm here for you
and living with Violet...
doesn't change that.
My patience only gets so far.
He's a boy, but...
it could also be a girl.
My god.
What are we supposed to do?
How do we decide?
Well, the odds say that your baby will
most likely identify as a female
so we can do corrective surgery
and give the baby
the appropriate genitalia.
You want to take my baby, my son,
and cut off of his penis.
Alternately you can
choose the gender now
raise the baby and then
when he or she matures
you reevaluate.
And hide this for his entire childhood?
What do we tell him? How do we even
begin to explain this to a little kid?
But that... not everybody the same,
that is okay to be different
It's not okay.
kids are cruel
one kid sees him in the bathroom
everyone's talking and tease him
and that... that's what kids do.
- that's not the life we want
- we need to make this right
We need to put this behind us
behind him or her
and make it right.
What's the best way?
I like women.
I like a lot of women.
but I am not married to Naomi, and
she is not the mother of my children.
Naomi sat by your side
while you had surgery,
she held your hand. You, upstairs,
sticking your tongue down her throat,
seeing her every day, letting
her believe that you two
have something together...
- I thought I was dying.
- You are...
you are asking me to lie for you.
you are making me feel dirty
and cheap, and I'm 10 years old again
telling Mother
that I went out for ice cream with daddy
when really I'm sitting in his office
while he's screwing his secretary
down the hall.
I'm too much of a snob
to screw sretaries.
You think this is funny?!
I think that you're one to talk. I seem
to remember something about you
doing your husband's best friend
behind his back.
That was once.
I slipped once.
So you're like... you're like
an alcoholic? You're on a program...
"God grant me the serenity"
and all that crap?
You are so mean
when you know that I am right.
You know what? I am mean when
I want you to mind your own business.
- I won't keep your secrets for...
- Yes, you will.
Montgomerys look the other way
when it is none of their business.
Now there's a sight for sore eyes.
I got patients lined up for weeks
waiting for you to get back.
- Well, that's me... money in the bank.
- I like money in the bank.
What?
I like your brother.
He's my golden boy.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. I just...
- I had to see you again.
- This is the fourth time this week.
Well, I checked your schedule.
I know you have an opening.
Come on, Pete. Just a quickie.
I feel like Paul doesn't share much
of himself with me either.
- He hardly wants to have sex anymore.
- I get home from work,
I'm tired, and you don't seem
that interested.
but when I ask you what's going on,
you won't talk to me.
I want to know what's going on with you
up here.
See, there's your first mistake,
thinking much of anything goes on
for us guys up here.
You know what I think, Greg? I think
we guys like women to think that.
maybe we think it ourselves,
but part of that is that we don't
look at ourselves, don't ask ourselves
what we're thinking or feeling.
Exactly. I mean, the truth is,
all of us have things going on inside.
I mean, right now,
everyone in this room,
Sheldon and me included,
have a thousand things going on.
And the trick is to open yourself
to that and to share it.
That's... not to say,
of course, that there aren't
pieces you want to keep
to yourself.
You don't want to lose yourself
in a relationship.
But the beauty of good communication
is that when you share...
share what you're thinking, good
or bad... you both feel better,
maybe help each other.
Ryan and I used to have that.
Back in high school when we met,
we talked about everything.
And now all you want to talk
about are the kids.
That's not true.
But I'm there with them all day.
You don't want to know about that?
That's my world.
I know it's hard, here, in the group,
but talking...
it really will make things better.
I love seeing you,
- but this has gotta stop.
- I can't stay away.
Whatever you do, whenever you put
your hands on me, I swear, it's...
- magic.
- It's not magic,
- and it's not...
- I've been reading up a lot
on reiki therapy, healing hands.
It's supposed to be incredible.
- Let's try it.
- I'm not a specialist at reiki.
- I can't do that.
- You can do whatever you want to me.
As a doctor,
- I can't keep pretending this is okay.
- Come on. Just one more time.
It's been taken care of. If you could
just file it, that would be great.
You know what? We haven't been speaking
for two weeks. I...
miss you. Don't treat me
like the pervert next door.
If you lived next door,
we wouldn't be having the problem.
I want to get past this. We need to
get past this.What's it gonna take
- for you to forgive me?
- I don't know,
I'm working on it.
We walked past your wall of pictures...
all those kids... happy and sweet
and... normal.
and that's what...
- our baby should be.
- And surgery can do that.
Surgery can give your baby
gender-distinct genitalia, yes.
And we can know?
We can stop saying...
"it"?
Great. So let...
let's do that.
Can we do it soon?
I can book an O.R. for tomorrow.
Afterward, we'll
supplement with estrogen
she'll be as healthy as possible.
No... that's not what we want.
It was clear to us from the second
we saw his face... he's...
- He's Matthew.
- But...
only 30% of these babies
orient toward male.
You said you don't know.
We know.
He's our son.
You're gonna give us our son.
I just saw Ryan and Eleanor
in the stairwell.
- You mean Ryan and Sasha?
- No, I mean Ryan and Eleanor.
They were communicating,
lip-to-lip.
- Did they see you?
- No, they were too focused.
I can't believe this.
Maybe it's a cry for help.
An affair in a stairwell after
marriage counseling is a cry for help?
They haven't been able to communicate
in their own relationships, so they
do this awful thing where they could
get caught because they want
- to force the communication.
- Only we can't tell on them.
It's not like they disclosed this
in session.
- I don't think the waivers apply.
- I'm not suggesting outing them.
- I'm just saying we get them to tell.
- How is exposing an affair
- going to improve communication?
- So we let the secret
keepestering till
it poisons every aspect of the group?
It'll become the 800-pound gorilla
in the room.
As therapists, we need
to acknowledge that gorilla
- and take steps to deal with it.
- We don't know what they feel about this.
We don't know what they think about it.
They could be in love. This could be
- a onetime thing.
- Which is why we need to talk to them.
What I think... as bad as this is,
getting them to confess could be
the break through the group needs.
I was surprised that you changed
your mind about doing the surgery.
Well, I can help them.
You know, the Thompsons, they are
desperate to change their situation,
for them and
for the baby.
And...
you made a very good case
that surgery is the only way
to really do that.
I did, but...
a boy?
- The odds are stacked against that.
- Gender's not my choice. It's theirs.
And they want him past this.
They want him better, and I can help.
Speaking of better...
I was thinking of borrowing Archer
for a few days.
A weekend in Palm Springs.
You know, sleeping late,
getting massages...
What?
- Do... you think that's a good idea?
- A trip with me?
No... I mean, just, you know...
healthwise.
He... he can go back to work, but...
going to a spa is strenuous?
But I mean, you know Archer. I mean,
he's... gonna want to play golf,
tennis.
He'll... push himself.
- You don't want me to go.
- No! I do... it's just...
Why rush it? Because I want to go away
with my boyfriend,
like a woman,
like a woman with a lover.
Lover?
Lover. I like that.
That's a lot better than boyfriend.
He's my lover.
What do you think?
Lover.
Yeah, it sounds stupid.
It sounds like a soap opera.
- It's not...
- What about paramour?
Arch, come on.
We're gonna be late.
You really need to learn how to knock.
- I'm sorry.
- No. That's...
- that's just what I get.
- You okay?
- Don't touch me.
- 'Cause my sister walked in?
We just... we never should've...
I never should've done it.
Where are... Archer and Addison?
Addison's waiting for him
at the office.
It's his first day back. He's got
a lot of work to catch up on, so...
Charlotte's probably holding
his feet to the fire.
Where's Archer?
He... he got stuck at the office.
I don't
think he's gonna make it.
Aren't we here
celebrating his first day back?
Well, maybe I should call him.
He was with a patient when I left.
I'm gonna get a drink.
- What can I give you?
- Scotch, neat.
What...
- How come you're not with them?
- I decided I like the quiet.
- Me too.
- Here you go
I thought you'd be in a great mood.
Archer's back at work,
things are back to normal.
You'd think.
What?
Can I tell you something...
and you can't tell...
you can't tell anyone?
Anything.
Never mind. Forget it.
Don't do that. Don't...
don't shut yourself off from me.
- You don't need to see my crazy.
- You don't think I have crazy?
Do you feel left out?
I feel...
broken.
Archer is cheating on Naomi...
which is wrong on so many levels, but
mostly because he's gonna hurt her.
He will, and there's nothing...
I just... I can't...
It's okay.
You're okay.
What do I do?
People make their own choices.
You can't do it for them.
- But it's not... I don't think it's...
- Sorry I'm late.
You're here.
- You want to talk about this?
- Will it help?
Then what's the point?
Don't...
don't be this guy.
Don't be this limited, short-sighted,
not-good-enough guy,
- please.
- Look, I like Naomi.
I really do. It's just...
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
Why don't you apologize to her?
You know, I hated him.
I hated dad for years.
Past tense. Hated. What, do you
love him now? Now he's your hero?
I am him, Addison. I am him!
Like father like son. Whatever he passed
down to me, I'm missing a gene.
You don't think I want to be better?
you don't think I want to be a good man
- in a storm? I don't have it in me.
- That's a cop-out.
Maybe it is,
but it's honest.
Do you usually do this,
have us come in alone?
Sheldon's never done this before.
Well, sometimes I find things
that are best served outside the group.
What's going on?
I saw you in the stairwell yesterday.
- Oh, god.
- It just happened.
After the first session, Ryan and I,
we started talking, and...
it was easy.
Everything you said about communication
that we couldn't do with our spouses,
the two of us could.
Are you gonna tell?
You can't do that.
Can you?
You might think that keeping
this a secret is a good thing
and that holding it in is better, but
I think it would be best for both of you
to go home,
talk to your spouses and
work together to try to figure this out.
You came to the group
to work on your marriages,
to make things better.
Is that still what you want,
to work on your marriages?
We want to be together.
and if telling our spouses is the
first step to a new life together...
We'll do it.
Instead of wanting to save
their marriage, they're just
- willing to walk away.
- Maybe it's a good thing.
I mean, if it's not working,
why force it?
I don't know what's worse... to be
faithful in a loveless marriage or to
- cheat to find true love.
- What are we talking about?
Keeping secrets.
That's tough,
keeping people's secrets.
That's why it's better not to.
I mean, if...
if you care about that person,
you just tell 'em,
- bottom line.
- Especially in a marriage.
The bond between a husband
and wife is sacrosanct.
Like the bond between a parent
and a child.
- How is the Thompson baby?
- I'm operating today.
The parents want a boy, and I think
it's important to respect that.
What about what that kid wants?
He's a little young
to make that decision.
I hope you make the right one.
Are you hungry?
Frustrated.
Charlotte acts like I'm
cheating on her.
I mean, here I am trying to be
the good guy... all I get is guilt.
I'm... I'm really not the person
you should talk to about this, Cooper.
Talk to her.
We need to talk.
stop treating me
like I've done something horrible,
like taking care of my friend
is cheating on you.
- You don't know...
- You don't know.
All I've ever wanted to do
is make you happy.
I can't do that
if you're shutting me out.
Please.
You ready to do this?
I'm sorry we left so early
last night. It's...
I just... I think Archer's just so glad
to be healthy again, that we...
I'm sorry. No, never mind.
I know...
some details I just have to keep
to myself.
I asked him about going away, and...
we're thinking maybe next weekend.
and I came up with a name for him.
"Beau."
He's my beau. You know, it's simple and
it's a little old-fashioned, but still,
I think it's better than "boyfriend."
I can't do this.
Is something wrong?
You said it was gonna be hours.
I can't do this.
- I'm sorry. I can't do the surgery.
- Is the baby sick?
- The baby is fine.
- That's just it.
The baby is fine. But you, Naomi,
we all want to change the baby
into a him,
into something that he's not.
So you... you just want
to leave him a freak?
- He... he's not a freak.
- He is if they don't do the surgery.
Please, you gotta do this.
Give us our son.
I can't. I can't do it. I won't.
If you want a boy,
you can still have a boy.
You can take him home and...
and call him Matthew and
love him and accept him
for what he is and raise him so that,
when the time comes,
he'll make the choice that's...
that's right for him.
and mean while, what, our...
our kid should hide? Be
- embarrassed, humiliated, what?
- We could protect him.
What do you think it'll be like
to be a 6-year-old boy with a vagina?
Imagine being a 20-year-old
woman without one.
We'll... we'll find another surgeon,
someone who will do this.
She's right.
We need to think about this.
It is too important to just
- hurt him this way.
- Him. That's right, him.
That in there, our baby,
it's a him.
and leaving him like this,
it's not right.
- I don't want to make a mistake.
- Well, I can't... I can't do this.
All right? I can't do this.
I can't... take
that home and hope it turns out right.
I can't...
I can't change that diaper
every day and...
I can't do this.
I can't. I can't.
Did yesterday's session...
bring up anything?
Ryan came to me.
He... said he wanted to talk.
I was surprised.
It had been so long.
And he had this look on his face.
And he started to tell me
all the things that were wrong
and how he was feeling,
and I guess...
It's not all him.
It's me.
It's us.
We talked for hours, and then..
We had sex.
- Sasha, come on.
- We did.
We can talk about it.
For the first time in a long time,
we had sex, and it was great.
Something about it felt
new and
better
and different.
I guess because I felt like
he was there.
I know that this might be...
uncomfortable,
but it might be helpful
if you could tell us how you feel.
Well, it wasn't what I thought
I'd be saying.
But we talked,
and I remembered what we had
and what we can still have.
I had an affair.
What the hell just happened back there?
I don't understand what just happened.
You agreed to do the surgery and...
- This isn't about the surgery.
- Well, what is it?
I thought...
that he could be a different person.
After
everything he went through,
after almost dying, I thought...
he could be a different person.
I wanted to believe that so much that
I almost cut into a baby
to convince myself
that people can change,
that I can change them.
but I can't.
Archer's cheating on you.
And I'm sorry.
Who was it?!
Someone I know?!
Tthis may be hard to hear, Paul,
but sometimes
an affair isn't moving away,
it's reaching out...
- For the wrong thing.
- It's reaching out
towards someone who seems
like an answer.
But they're not.
They're a crutch, a way to
fill the void
of something that's missing,
the person that you really love.
The person I really love?
I thought I had lost that with Sasha.
I was in the same boat you are.
Maybe we all are in the same boat.
But isn't it...
isn't it worth another chance?
.I think I made a mistake
- I don't care.
- But you should,
because if you want anything to change,
you have to work at it.
You... haven't shared yourself,
and I...
I understand that.
how can you share yourself
if you don't know what you think
or you don'tnow what you feel, and
it makes you feel pathetic and crazy
and bad? And you think that if you
share that, then
they might decide that...
you're as crazy
as you feel you are.
But we're...all of us...
we're... we're human.
We make mistakes.
I have,
I know Eleanor has,
and I bet you have, too.
But if you can talk to her
about this,
if you can open up with her,
Then I... really think you can work
through this and make things better.
You know what?
I'm done.
I'm afraid that Carol will leave me,
just like Paul did.
When you come home at night
and you talk about how great the guys
are you work with,
I feel small...
insignificant.
I know who I am and what I am...
but it scares me that
you'll realize you could do better.
You should've talked to me.
Because I want you.
I love you.
This has got to stop.
When I'm with you,
what you do to me...
These days, it's the best day
I ever feel.
Look...
I want to try this new herb...
red clover. It's supposed to put
years on your life
and take years off your face.
- I know what you're gonna say.
- You have cancer.
I know that.
Stage II lymphoma.
God, I know that.
You don't have to say it.
I do.
I love that you come to see me.
You're one of my favorite patients.
But I've referred you
to the best oncologist in town,
and you won't go.
You have to go.
I tried.
I made it to the waiting room.
But those people are so frail.
I mean, they're bald or worse...
bad wigs
and chapped skin. I c...
- I can't be like that.
- They're sick like you are,
but they're getting the right treatment,
they are trying to get better.
What if they don't?
Then they don't, but their eyes are wide
open. They know they can't cheat fate.
They're fighting,
the way you should be fighting.
I don't want to be the one...
who dies.
Then be the one who lives.
He's gone.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home, to New York.
Are you saying good bye
to Naomie.
Don't tell her about Charlotte.
that would hurt her
Archer you're living without a word,
- Don't do this.
- Bye Addie.
I love you.
I want to see how you're doing.
Mitch is gone...
I don't know how I'm gonna do this alone
* *** with blue
Matthew
Mitch was so excited.
You know...
I know, You want to...
save him from...
all ****** go througt, but...
I think you're doing the right thing.
I hope so.
You do not get to just cut and run
just because you're afraid
of not knowing what comes next.
There are people that love you
and that need you.
Why are you here yelling at me?
because its not okay
to just walk away
and pretend like it doesn't matter.
to have something incredible
and not even see what is right
in front of your face...
your wife loves you,
and you have a healthy child,
who, yeah,
has some issues, but so what?
Everybody has issues.
You need to be there for them,
- love them.
- Well, I don't know if I can.
Grow up.
Be a man.
You need to...
not hurt
the woman who loves you.
Well. nice surprise.
I slept with Archer Montgomery.
I just...
thought you should know.
You don't get to just walk away
from me after telling me that.
How dare you?
How dare
you do this?
- It's just the way I am.
- That's crap!
You did the one thing you could
to push me away, to make me
make the choice and not you.
guess what.
That's not gonna work.
I'm not going anywhere.
You want to sleep with some guy
to hurt me, to make me back off?
Too bad.
I'm here.
I'm storming the freakin' castle
for you, and you so
underestimated me. What,
you thought I was so weak that I'm gonna
walk away because my pride got wounded?
You are mine.
and I'm not walking away
because you're scared.
God.
I am so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
This one...
I can overlook.
This one.
But you have to think long and hard about
testing me, because next time, I'm gone.
You better dig deep,
dig deep in your soul
and grow the hell up
and be in this relationship
Right now.
I wanted to thank you
for what you said today.
- I don't think I got through to Paul.
- you got through to Greg
and Carol, and we saved a marriage,
maybe two.
Trying to figure this stuff out
is hard.
I mean, they come to us,
they're on the brink already.
If we turn two out of three...
I say we won.
It was a shock.
I mean the pregnancy.
It was... it was...
unplanned, and I don't often do
unplanned.
So this whole
thing is unfamiliar territory for me.
And I'm just trying to...
roll with
- it the best way I can.
- I know, Violet.
And I don't expect you to
confide in me.
But if you do need me,
I'm here for you.
You taste good.
Really good.
What's wrong?
What did you just call me?
What?
You just called me Naomi.
No, I didn't.
- No, I didn't.
- You did.
You warned me.
I thought...
I really thought Archer had changed...
or that he could.
I'm sorry.
I know he's your brother, and...
I know I shouldn't.
- It's not right to say it, but...
- Say it.
I hate him.
Me, too.
Transcript : Ydy
The Mc Dreamy Team
pour www.forom.com