He is not talking to me.
I am not not talking.
He is barely talking.
I was married,
a long time ago.
I told him but he seems to think I
didn't tell him soon enough.
Well, that's... none of my business.
Hello.
Oh, I thought we were saying hello.
We're not.
Kitten.
My name is Addison.
I thought we could have a drink.
It's 9:00 a.m.
Well, I thought we could talk.
Are you dying?
What?
Do you have cancer,
renal failure, a brain tumor?
Are you you dying?
I came to see you.
Well, here I am. You saw me.
So now you're leaving?
You are.
I'm at the Carlyle.
Come on, Dr. Wilder.
It's not as bad as it looks.
The cancer has spread
From your abdomen
to your liver to your lungs,
and you've kept your optimism.
My colon's good...
like a teenage vegetarian.
Neil?
All my tests are perfect.
The baby looks good.
And Dr. Montgomery assures me it's a girl.
So you better revise your list of names.
There's nothing wrong
with a girl named Doug.
Besides, doctors are wrong all the time.
All right, Pete, you know what
the blood has to tell you.
I need six weeks.
I need to be there.
I need to hold our little girl.
Well, it's like I said, mind over matter.
Your attitude is great. There's
nothing more I could ask for.
Well, I'm asking.
I'm asking for more.
I know you can't save him,
but... I need you to tell me.
He's gonna be alive when she's born.
I need my little girl to have a father.
She has taken a lover.
A lovah.
And he's old? Good-lookin' old.
But from the way she looked at him,
I'd say he's not her lover anymore.
She never said anything about a guy.
I am not talking about it.
So, uh, everybody have a good weekend?
Well, I did... good weekend.
It was very eventful.
Got married.
Uh, I know what you're gonna say.
Uh, it's... it's fast and... and crazy...
Whoa. Where'd you meet her?
I... I didn't. Uh... I married Heather.
I know what you want to say,
but I know what I'm doing,
and... and she's cleaned up,
and... and Betsey's really happy, really happy.
So it's great. I had a...
I had a great weekend.
Where is my son?
Evan Dawson. I'm his mother, Lynn Jarvey.
I'm sorry. I don't...
My son was kidnapped. You saw him.
You treated him here, and I
think you know where he is.
Uh, yes, I did treat him...
A while ago,
and I don't...
It wasn't Evan, though.
Is it maybe Porter?
He may have told you that,
but that is my son.
His father kidnapped him,
and I want him back.
Wow. Um, I'm sorry.
I hired a private investigator
who says you traced his insulin pump.
You called his pediatrician.
You knew he was kidnapped
before he was hospitalized.
Mrs. Jarvey, let me assure you,
I treated your son, and then he left.
I don't know anything about a call.
I don't believe you.
You didn't believe your son either.
From what I remember, this boy told me
he was being abused by his stepfather.
I'm assuming that's your husband.
You may think that you're helping my son,
but you don't know me or my husband,
and I'm telling you, this did not happen.
I am his mother. I would know.
Evan is a 13-year-old boy
with severe diabetes
who got an infection
because he was living in his father's car.
Who knows how they're living now?
Please, Dr. Freedman,
if you know something...
I don't want my son to die.
I wish I could help. I'm sorry.
Damn it.
Problem?
My patient is dying.
His wife is due in six weeks,
and he's running out of time.
Intra-abdominal sarcoma
with liver and lung mets.
Well...
He has a few weeks at best.
What I thought.
Unless you want to try something new.
What, prayer?
No.
Better. Me.
Okay, sacrilegious, maybe.
But I've been working on
some new procedures
to inhibit tumor growth.
Maybe give your patient
enough time to meet his baby.
Neil Delhom?
It's that bad? I just saw him
and Margaret in the lobby.
It's that bad.
But I want to make it better.
I have read your protocols
on tumornhibitors.
They're not without side effects.
What kind of side effects
are we talking about?
They run the gamut,
but bottom line is, your patient's dying.
I can give him a better
quality of life than death.
Going somewhere?
Out.
You may not want to talk to me,
but I remember Evan Dawson from a year ago
when I covered for you.
And?
And if you know where they are, turn them in.
I don't and I handled it. I gotta go.
Basically, I put a radio transmitter
into your liver
and use a probe to heat up the tumor
and blast the cancer cells.
Margaret.
I know this is a lot to digest.
We spent two years
trying to have this baby...
Hormones and needles
and doctors telling us,
"that's all I can do."
now we're having the baby...
It's just not fair...
What's happening to Neil.
This... this c... this can help?
All our preliminary studies are excellent.
And you're recommending this?
I'm...
I'm concerned.
I... I want to throw everything
that we can at this,
but I also want whatever time
that you have to be... livable
for both of you.
Well, you asked for more time,
for your daughter to have a father.
Dr. Fife...
He's your only shot. I say take it.
It's cool. We're studying robotics.
Wow. That's big-time.
Uh, the pump looks good. It's clean.
You do have a slight fever,
though, so I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna take a little blood.
It might be an infection.
How you feeling otherwise?
A little tired, but mostly good.
You can have a taco on me.
You want me to get lost?
Kinda, yeah.
You just... just give us a minute, bud.
So, um, this isn't just a house call.
No.
Uh, Lynn came to see me.
Does she know we're here?
Does she know we're in L.A.?
I don't think so,
but she hired a private investigator.
She thinks I know something.
We have to leave. We have to Leave L.A.
I didn't say anything to her, and I won't.
You don't have to run
on my account.
We're settled, you know?
We're making a life.
Is she still with Ted?
Yes.
How can a womaoose
a man over her own son?
I don't... I...
So just be careful, Frank.
I'll let you know if anything
comes back on these labs.
A marriage intervention?
That's why we're here?
Is there even such a thing?
It's codependence, Pete.
Dell is facilitating her addiction
by taking her back
every time she gets clean.
And there's a child at stake.
I still can't believe it.
I mean, Dell is married.
Is he happy?
I... I think he's in denial.
He married the mother of his child.
Couldn't that be a good thing?
Okay, I have a patient
who actually needs some help.
Pete, will you...
Keep an eye on Dr. Fife?
He worries me.
He worries me, too,
but I don't see any other options.
So are you in?
Oh, there he is. Hey, hey.
Where were you?
Hi.
What? Uh, nowhere. I was just,
you know, doing a thing.
You ready to talk to Dell?
Oh, yeah, sure.
No time like the present.
Don't tell me you're getting involved.
It's Dell.
So I hear congratulations are in order.
Thanks.
Something you wanted?
Can we talk to you for a minute?
Cooper Freedman?
Uh, yeah, hi. I'm Dr. Freedman.
We have a warrant for your arrest.
Please put your hands
behind your back, sir.
No, no, no. There... there
must be a mistake, officer.
What's going on?
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you...
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'll call the lawyer. I'll be right there.
If you cannot afford a lawyer,
one will be appointed to
represent you before any...
This is a printout of all the calls
to Lynn Jarvey's cell phone
in the past two hours.
The last one came from
a pay phone here in L.A.
from her son Evan.
He asked his mom
to stop looking for him
so you and his dad
wouldn't get into trouble.
You've given material assistance
to aid and abet a kidnapper.
Carries a sentence in California
of 5 to 11 years.
I'm not entirely sure what
it does to your medical license,
but I'm thinking it can't be good.
I don't want you.
Tell me where her son is, I let you go.
I think I'm gonna wait for my lawyer.
There's really evidence
in a box of tongue depressors?
All right, so give me a call.
What do they want?
They think that Cooper
knows where this kid is,
that he's been in contact with him.
This is ridiculous. It's been a year.
Yes, but it's Cooper.
Do you really think they're wrong?
I don't know.
Uh, Cooper did know that
the boy was kidnapped
when he was here last year.
He traced the boy's insulin pump.
And you knew about this?
Well, it was his patient, so it's his call.
Doesn't mean he knows
where they are now.
Well, look, Charlotte is
with the lawyers right now.
They're gonna work something out.
Cooper gave medical service
to a patient who needed it.
That's what he's supposed to do.
What jury is gonna convict him for that?
It's almost in place.
Grab that. Steady it.
You and Dr. Bennett are from
the warm-and-fuzzy school of medicine.
I'm from the get-things-done school.
No reason you can't do both.
Is that why you took my side over Naomi's?
Move to the left.
My left.
Actually, I was...
concerned about what was best for my patient.
And Naomi isn't.
I'm not putting words in your mouth.
Just following the logic.
Dr. Bennett cares about her patients,
but she sometimes cares more
about getting her way,
at least when it comes to me.
I hadn't noticed.
Yes, you did.
Now sit back and watch science in action.
it's gonna be fine.
Just bail me out, and my lawyer
is gonna figure out a way
to get me outta this.
They won't set bail
until after the grand jury
hearing tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
I'm not worried about me being in jail.
It's Evan. He might have
a kidney infection.
You saw him and you lied?
Lower your voice.
Oh, it's okay when you lie?
You lying about your marriage
and me helping a patient,
it's completely different.
You're in jail, Cooper. Give this kid up.
I can't send Evan back to
his stepfather to get abused.
If he's sick, he's gonna need antibiotics
before he winds up
needing to be hospitalized.
No
I need you to pick up his labs...
I am not committing a felony
to protect your patient.
I need you to pick up his labs,
and I will get him whatever he needs
as soon as I get bailed out.
You owe me this.
Hi. You want to
close the door and sit down?
An intervention? We're really doing this?
Well, we were both there
when Heather took Betsey.
And we were there when
she came back on drugs.
We saw what that did to you.
So... so this, um, this "marriage,"
this is part of your pattern with Heather.
She... she gets you to trust her,
and then her addiction kicks in,
and then you get hurt.
And I... I know how difficult it's been
for you to balance working
and being a single father...
Oh, oh, yeah.
Sometimes, when we get overwhelmed,
we look for the easy answer.
Yeah.
Trust me. It hasn't been easy,
okay? We've been wking on it.
Yeah, well, you kept it secret.
Yeah, 'cause I knew you wouldn't approve.
Okay.
Look, s... sometimes it's hard to
hear advice from other people.
Yeah, yeah.
It... it's scary. But... but you
at least need to listen.
Y... you think I should take relationship advice
from you, Violet, really,
about what's best for my child,
about whether or not I should
be with someone that I love?
Dell-...
I'm... I'm not sleeping
with my colleague's brother.
I'm not getting divorced
and... and leaving my job.
I married my daughter's mother.
Now... I appreciate that you care,
but I need to get home to my wife.
That went well.
Yeah. Yeah, that was... that was good.
Thank you.
You're late.
You look good.
The California air has done you well.
Martini, dry, no olive, for the lady.
And for the gentleman,
vodka tonic, lime, no ice.
Thank you.
You remembered.
I've been mixing your drinks
since I was 8 years old.
It's not something
you forget.
That's coarse.
A lady never downs a drink
in the company of a gentleman.
Well... you're not a gentleman.
You're my father.
So... what's her name?
Who?
Your mistress. I mean,
I'm assuming you have a mistress in L.A.
Why else would you be here?
Addie.
I mean, you didn't come
when Archer was dying.
That wasn't important enough
for you. So I'm thinking,
there must be a prime piece
of ass here on the west coast
to get the captain to fire up
the old jet and come on out.
Well, uh... I see you have changed.
The Addison I know didn't use that language.
Well, the California air has done me well.
I'm a whole new girl.
Does bizzy know you're here?
There was a point when you
liked spending time with me.
I told you the last time,
I'm done. I was finished.
And then you have the nerve to come back...
That was just an argument.
No, that was me getting away from you.
I can't imagine why
you're behaving like this.
Oh, you can't imagine, huh?
So let's see.
Was it the tennis instructor with the legs,
the blonde from your office, four of my nannies,
three maids, oh, Jolie, my french tutor,
Louise, the chef?
There were so many,
I can't remember. Can you?
You don't talk to me that way.
I'm your father.
Oh, I do talk to you that way. I do.
After 39 years and a very
intense year of therapy
after my husband left me
for doing exactly what you do,
I do talk to you that way.
Now does bizzy know that you're here?
Your mother thinks I'm in France.
And once again, I'm supposed
to lie to her for you.
Addison, I came here to see you, to...
We're family.
We're done.
She got a lot of nerve, bringing him in here.
It's ironic... he doesn't have to hide.
I wonder how much he's gonna set bail for.
Whatever it is, we'll pay it.
Cooper...
I'm okay.
All rise.
All present in the state of
California vs. Cooper Freedman.
Be seated.
Dr. Freedman, you were present
at a grand jury hearing this morning
where yore asked questions
as to the whereabouts
of Evan Dawson, but
you refused to answer.
Is that correct?
Yes, Your Honor.
At the urging of the district attorney,
I am prepared to grant
immunity from prosecution
if you provide the grand jury with the location
of Evan Dawson and his father.
With that said, if I send you
back to the grand jury,
will you answer all questions put before you?
I'm sorry, your honor, but I can't do that.
Where is he?!
I need my son!
Dr. Freedman, the court holds you in contempt.
I am remanding you to the custody of
The los angeles county
sheriff's office until such time
as you agree to come forth
and answer to the grand jury.
Motion for bail, Your Honor.
Denied. No bail.
He sits until he talks.
Charlotte.
Get out.
Are you okay?
they beat him up.
Who does that?
Who hits someone and...
He takes care of children, for god sake.
You're upset.
I'm angry.
I mean, I know he'd do
anything for his patients.
He'll cover up whatever it takes
to keep them safe, but...
This is wrong, and...
And what?
Nothing.
Oh, come on, Charlotte.
I'd think you'd be a better liar than that.
I usually am.
I'm upset, okay?
I mean, I'm a damn fine liar, but...
He wants me to do something.
And I shouldn't.
But he wants me to.
He knows where they are, doesn't he?
It's against the law, Charlotte.
He can't do that. You can't do that.
Evan has a kidney infection.
He needs antibiotics.
Charlotte, you can't do anything.
I know.
I mean, why should I?
He lied to me. He lied to all of us.
So why should I help?
Look at the blisters.
He woke up screaming.
They gave him morphine for the pain.
It's not so bad.
It is. It's horrible. What's wrong with him?
It's called hand-foot syndrome.
It's one of the side effects we talked about.
I want it stopped.
I... I can't put him through this.
No. I... I... I want to be there.
I want the chance to be there.
I don't care what the side effects are.
Neil.
You heard me, Pete.
We keep going.
Neil's going into liver failure.
He's dying, but he was always dying.
The man is in excruciating pain
because of your treatment.
That's all you can say?
We should probably take him
off the protocol.
What is wrong with you?
The results we get from his treatment
will help refine the protocol for the future.
I... I... I can't believe you can just sit there
and... and pretend that this is a good thing.
I have a patient
who is holding out hope,
hope that we gave him,
and now I have to go
back out there and tell him
he'll never see his child.
Well, if that's the problem, I'll tell him.
What? Isn't that what you want?
No. That's not what I want at all.
Hey. You want to tell me what you're doing?
Uh, um...
What are you doing, Addison?
I'm getting Cooper out of jail.
He knows where Evan is.
He asked Charlotte to go
to them, and now she left.
So you're going through Charlotte's stuff
to see where she went?
What are you... you're not some...
This isn't your job to begin with.
Yeah, well, Cooper's a doctor.
It's not his job to harbor fugitives and lie
and put someone else in the middle of all this.
You know, cover-ups don't work. They fall apart.
They cau collateral damage.???????????????????????
People get hurt.
You been all worked up
since this guy showed up,
and whoever he is... it's the captain.
Oh. I always liked your father.
Yeah, well... you don't really know him.
Got it.
Wait. Addison, just...
talk to Cooper, talk to Charlotte.
Don't go around them.
The police don't want them, Sam.
They want Evan and his father.
Look, I get why Cooper can't talk now.
He'll hate himself forever.
Charlotte's the loyal
girlfriend, so she can't do it.
I'll do it. Cooper can be
the hero. I'll be the bad guy.
All right.
It isn't anything you did.
Infections are more common in diabetics.
Look, we sure appreciate it.
I know it's... it's way beyond the call of duty.
Is Dr. Cooper okay?
He's okay.
You need to take the
antibiotics three times a day.
It's very important to take all of it, all right?
Dad?
How'd you get me out?
They found Frank and Evan. I was with 'em.
Cooper, I'm sorry.
What, did... did they follow you?
No. I was careful.
Cooper.
If you touch him, I swear to god...
Stay away from us.
Charlotte...
Did you tell anyone? Did...
Addison.
The necrosis is so severe,
it caused a blockage
of your bile duct in your liver...
what he's trying to say is...
Unfortunately, the treatment isn't working.
we have to stop.
No.
There's just nothing more we can do.
I'm sorry.
We made a choice.
We can't be angry at you.
I am. I am pissed.
I want to break things I'm so pissed.
I accepted the cancer.
I even accepted the death.
But...
at least we should've had time...
time to be a family,
even if for just a little bit.
there is one more option.
Not for you.
For you.
We could deliver the baby... now.
Oh, hey, Heather.
Hi.
Uh, Dell is picking up Betsey from school,
and I have a meeting.
Oh, good. Good. A meeting, that's good.
Is this part two of the intervention,
coming to see me?
So Dell told you about that.
Yeah, he told me.
He didn't want to, but, um, no secrets.
It's part of the program.
I can't live that way.
That's good.
Look... I understand.
I'm the first one to tell you, this is scary.
I mean, we were both
worried that it was too soon.
I know I have to earn his trust.
But I love him,
and he loves me,
and Betsey is happy.
And that's the most important thing, isn't it?
Well, um, I'm... I'm not sure it is.
I mean, she's a child whose
family was broken apart.
So of course she's happy
to see you together again.
But you don't think I'm safe.
I... I'm... I'm worried about all of you.
I'm afraid, too.
Not a day goes by that I
don't think about using.
But when I was in rehab,
I thought a lot about...
when Betsey was born.
And I was clean, I was happy,
and we were a family.
When I'm with her
and when I'm with Dell,
I'm at my best.
I think I can do this.
I... I want to do this...
because they're the best part of me.
Look, I have to get to the meeting, so...
Oh, of course, of course. I'm, uh...
I'm sorry to have bothered you, Heather.
All right, bye.
Did you not understand
what was happening?
that I had made a choice?
I understood
that you chose to break several laws,
putting yourself, your girlfriend
and this entire practice at risk.
I confided in you, Addison.
I didn't ask for your help.
No. You were having
moral qualms,
and I saw you coming down
on the wrong side of them.
You gave Evan to his abusive stepfather.
He was terrified. You put him
into the hands of his attacker.
I have to trust that the courts will sort it out.
It's not mine to do or yours, either of yours.
Oh, you are not that naive.
They're not gonna get it,
the father goes to jail,
and this kid gets beaten,
and our practice is okay.
Yay, us. Cooper, enough.
Hey, are you in on this, Sam?
I'm not taking sides.
Well, I did. I took a side.
So did I, and I'd do it again.
Addison, this... we need you to deliver
Margaret Delhom's baby
Before her husband dies.
Uh, Gabriel Fife. Heard great things about you.
Yeah, uh, Addison Montgomery.
What happened?
Dr. Fife tried an experimental treatment.
It didn't work. Neil doesn't have much time.
Margaret still has six weeks
left. I can't deliver yet.
Babies come in at 34 weeks all the time.
Do an amnio, check the lungs.
If they're mature, what's the problem?
The problem, Dr. Fife, is that human fetuses
are supposed to grow to 40
weeks before we yank them out.
You yank them out?
You know, I thought the great
thing about being a doctor
was we could make things
happen that should happen.
Well... he's fun.
Are you really on board with this?
I don't know.
Neil wants to meet his daughter.
Margaret wants to be able to tell that baby
that her father held her and loved her.
And that baby, she's gonna want to know it.
And I know all the reasons we
shouldn't deliver the baby now.
But I keep thinking about...
when Violet was attacked
and how I didn't know
if I'd ever meet Lucas.
I didn't know if I'd ever meet my son.
And I know...
that I would've done anything to meet him.
Easy.
Jail sucked, Sam.
It sucked, and it was for nothing.
Well, coulda been worse.
It wasn't worse.
Well, that's good.
Yeah.
That's good.
Ow.
Hello.
Evan?
I know Evan says I stabbed him, but I didn't.
I told you, I didn't hurt him.
You left your son alone with his abuser?
No.
Get out of my way.
No, you're not touching
my son.
Me? You're worried about me?
I told you.
You didn't believe me.
You didn't believe Evan.
I screwed up. I screwed up, okay?
But you're not touching him. Just...
I got this. Okay. I'm sorry.
Uh, I'm Dr. Sam Bennett.
I understand how you must be feeling.
Let me just go in there and give your son
the best medical treatment he could get.
Okay? Please.
Just let me help your son.
Are they gonna let my dad outta jail?
Uh, I don't know. But right now,
I'm concerned about you.
Am I... Gonna be okay?
Absolutely.
Dr. Bennett?
Get me 4-0 nylon, 1% lido with epi
and a suture kit.
It's one thing coming after me.
I can tell you to back off.
But going to my wife is inexcusable.
I... I came to see you.
Well, then you shoulda walked away.
I am so sorry if I upset her. I...
No, you upset me, all right?
I mean, maybe... maybe I hid it.
Maybe I should've let all of you know
when we started seeing
each other, but I didn't,
because I was trying to figure
out how I was feeling by myself.
I get that.
Everyone gave you space
When you were trying
to figure out what you wanted.
Besides Pete, no one got in your business
about the choices you've
been making about Lucas,
choices, by the way, which we don't all support...
You giving up your child.
But we, you know, we love you
and we respect you, and we
know this has been tough,
and we're just trying to be supportive.
So if... if you don't like
what I did, it's fine. Okay?
But respect it. If you can
respect Cooper for... for
committing a crime and putting
his career on the line,
I would think you could respect me.
You want me to tell Cooper?
I will.
Give me a minute to talk to Evan.
All right.
Now you said your stepfather did this to you.
But your wounds are all even, Evan,
and they're superficial.
They're called intention marks.
There's no way he did this to you.
You did this to yourself.
Why would you hurt yourself?
If I had proof...
that Ted hurt me...
they'd have to let my dad outta jail.
You can't tell anyone.
Please.
You want Ted to go to jail?
Let's find real evidence.
Tell me what he did to you.
Tell me everything.
We'll take x-rays, find proof.
We will put that son of a bitch in jail.
You can tell me. Anything.
I can't.
Why not?
I didn't mean for all this to happen.
I just wanted Ted to go away.
So I told my mom Ted hit me.
It was one lie to keep my parents together.
Only my dad believed me, and she didn't.
So he took me away.
And once I started,
I... I didn't know how to stop.
So I kept lying and lying.
I didn't know what else to do.
I... I didn't know what else to do.
Aah! That's good, Margaret.
Okay, one more push. Ready?
On the count of three.
One, two... and three. Push. Push.
Okay. Great.The.
Is she okay?
She's perfect.
Evan's okay.
Turns out, uh, his wounds were superficial.
Intention wounds.
He faked 'em, Cooper,
to get his father out of jail.
It turns out there was never any abuse.
He lied about all of it.
No. Unh-unh.
No, I know this kid. That's not...
this chart doesn't prove that.
You think I'm making this up?
Why would I do that?
You told Addison. You, who can
keep a marriage a secret,
Couldn't keep this to yourself
when someone's life
Depended on it.
People lie, Cooper.
I lied. You lied. He lied.
No. This is a good kid. You...
you, what, you bullied him?
You're a miserable bitch, so you bullied him?
You're trying to take
what you did and... and...
just because you are a liar, it
doesn't mean everyone else is.
I know he lied because he told me he lied.
And you can call me
all the names you want to,
but it doesn't change that.
I met a guy, I fell in love and I married him.
And it ended badly, and I don't
like to go back there.
I was a different person.
And I am with you now.
And there are things I coulda told you,
could tell you, that would make it easier,
but... I don't want to go back there.
That is why I don't talk about it.
We were gonna get married.
And you gave me a big speech
about the big white wedding
and who you were
and what you wanted and... and
how it was gonna be hard for you
to walk down the aisle without big daddy.
So either you've already
walked down the aisle
without your father
or you'd already had your
big white wedding with him.
You lied, Charlotte.
You lie.
Hey.
I heard Evan's dad is getting out of jail,
that Lynn is dropping the charges.
He's a child, Addison.
My job is to believe him.
That's what I do. I believe people.
At least... I did.
I wish I could... trust,
but... I've been burned too many times.
And that's why you didn't believe me?
I don't know. Maybe.
Well, I'd do it again.
I know. Because you
protect the people you love.
Yeah. And you may think
we were doing the same thing,
but you were wrong.
Even if I lied to you,
even if Evan lied to me, you were wrong.
You don't always know better.
I thought you'd want to know,
Neil Delhom got to meet his baby. I know.
You feel good about that? Don't you?
I am happy for them.
I think you are happy
because you pushed the envelope and you won.
Chalk one up for science.
What does it matter?
I got it done. Did you?
You take risks. You push people.
Only you don't have to pay
the price if you fail.
Of course I do. Failure costs me everything.
It costs my patients everything.
And what about what it cost Neil
to put him through that?
Yes, a man will die who was gonna die anyway.
But if it had worked, a lot
of people would've lived...
still might from what I've learned...
and all of them, they matter to me.
What?
Nothing.
It's just, you wouldn't
know it to look at you,
that you care.
Sorry I'm not more user-friendly.
Me, too.
This is a congratulatory plant...
an... apologetic,
congratury plant.
I'm so sorry, Dell.
I... I should not have talked to Heather.
But... but I'm glad I did.
She seemed good.
She's doing everything she can for Betsey.
You have done an amazing thing for your daughter.
You know, I, you know,
I love my daughter, Violet.
But getting back together with
Heather, that wasn't for her.
I love Heather.
We fell in love again.
And you're really happy?
Yeah, I am.
Well...
You deserve it.
Violet.
So do you.
Can I come in?
You always get the best room.
I'm a Montgomery.
Do... do you want to...
Oh, no.
Yes.
I was thinking about
how I used to take you
out on the boat when you were little,
just you and me,
and I'd teach you how to sail.
We'd sail together.
Those were our bestimes.
Yes.
They were.
I want more best times,
just you and me.
You're not my family.
I have a family.
They come to work with me every day,
and we care about each other.
We take care of each other.
And when we lie for each other,
it's for a reason, it's for good,
it's for lives saved.
They're my fily,
not you.
I'm sorry, but...
But you came here.
I don't forgive you.
But you're here.
I am.
I'm here.
Sync by ReHelen - corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com