so, um... i was thinking
of new ways to generate
business for the practice.
how about... billboards?
right?
what? bad idea?
what?
i don't know, sam. i mean, i cut
expenses, right? i cut expenses.
even still,
profit's only up 2%.
so, i mean, the consults
should help. don't you think?
yeah.
right?
yeah, they should.
this is a lot of pressure,
a lot of pressure.
hey.
what are you doing here
so early?
running.
you're running like you're
trying to get someplace.
naomi still isn't talking
to me outside of work.
and that makes you run?
i'm her... friend.
friends are supposed to talk.
so yeah, i'm here, running,
avoiding the office.
i had to force myself
to go in.
yeah,
the office has been odd.
it's kinda like we're
going through a divorce,
only we have to
keep living together.
you running
to get somewhere?
no, i...
do you think i'm old?
tell me you did not
sleep with that temp.
(ighou.u hey, it seemed like
thod t ta good idea at the time.
yeah, well, at least
you're getting out there.
me? two dates seems to
be my limit. the cop?
he didn't call after
our last date, so i called him,
left him a message,
a horrifying,
embarrassing message.
probably scared him off.
not that i care.
you know, i'm...
glad to not be talking
to him.
well, at least he didn't
tell you you were old.
although... she did say
that i was great.
i'm fine.
you ever feel like
you're not pulling your weight,
everybody at work is talking
about you behind your back?
how the hell
did my perfectly arched back
make you think of that?
um... loofah to scrub,
scrub to surgery,
surgery to patients,
patients to my lack there of.
we're drowning. i'm drowning.
i am making us drown.
and when the raft
is sinking,
who do you think
gets thrown overboard first?
oh, the pediatrician
who can't bring in the bucks.
stay here and drown.
i'm going to work.
dell?
what are you doing here?
i work here.
wow.
gotta pay the rent...
eat and-
what are you doing here? uh,
where's-where's the patient?
i, uh, am the patient. i-
i hurt my knee. it's- okay.
it's not... just, uh... you didn't want
to get this patched up at the office?
well, you know,
well, it's just a silly-
it's just-
they're very busy there.
you know, it's great. it's great
that you're here, you know?
hospitals are great.
it used to be my happy place.
how's, uh, how's everyone?
you mean how's naomi?
she misses you.
montgomery.
so you're good?
yeah.
dell works here.
who?
blond, receptionist.
he was the talking human
who greeted you
when you came to the practice.
never mind. i just had a
surgeon called away last-minute.
patient needs a-a myomectomy.
you interested? can't.
got a whole fun-filled day
back at the ranch.
come on, montgomery.
you love surgery.
it's messy and bloody,
and you get to save lives,
not to mention the coin.
i'll give you
your own o.r. for a day.
no. no.
i... am off to work...
fun-filled work.
here you go.
good luck to you. okay.
hey.
it took you 45 minutes
to write that prescription.
consults are supposed to take
15 minutes max.
you're a stalker, sam.
15 minutes, $180, 4 consults
an hour, $720 each hour.
do i look like
a money machine?
you look like you could be
working a lot faster.
i agreed to do consults. i did
not agree to do malpractice.
and i'm not gonna write
a prescription
every time someone's doctor
or therapist
says they need prozac.
i need to do a history
- do the history, all right? just do it in 15 minutes.
did someone shove rocks
down his pants
on the playground?
he-he's compensating-
all this bossiness.
i liked him better
when you were in charge.
i'm sleeping with him.
you're-
sleeping with the enemy.
so let me get this straight-
he went behind my back
took my job, made me feel like crap
- and now you're sleeping with him.
yeah. what's wrong with me?
w- what's wrong with you?
uh... you're-you're-
you're a traitor,
and you are letting him
run all over you
and change everything
about this place-
he sits there
and he asks me questions
about the practice,
like what should he do,
as if these aren't things
that i hadn't thought of when i was running
it. he's using you as a sounding board?
i can't stand it
and-and...
dell's gone and addison...
i have no one to talk to.
i- i-i know it's wrong,
it's just that sam
has this way of-
you know what?
i don't want to know.
no, no, no, no, no. it's just that he really
- i don't want to hear it.
i- i'm just saying that he-
well, don't say.
that's what we do.
we're a family,
and this practice is our home.
the life we save
could be your child's...
your wife's...
your husband's.
at oceanside wellness,
our family
takes care of your family.
morning.
sorry. not in the mood.
hey, nal.
hey, i-i saw dell today.
he's working at, uh,
st. ambrose.
dell's working
at st. ambrose?
coop. hey. morning.
yeah, not now. can't talk.
you're still talking to me,
right?
no time.
no money, no time.
i'm gonna go do a surgery.
surgery brings income.
it is messy and bloody
and a whole lot more pleasant
than being around here.
okay. thanks.
morning.
how are you, addison?
i'm great. and you?
how are you, mr. scrub cap?
hi.
you having a tough time?
i hate
this time of year-
brush fire season.
everyone's a little on edge.
panic attacks again?
no. no blackouts,
no nightmares.
mostly i'm handling it good.
i was out
at the 1,500-acre burn
in santa cruz last month.
everyone made it out, but it was a lot like
- malibu.
yeah, i saw the news.
you should be proud of yourself
for making it through, though.
post-traumatic stress
takes some people years.
yeah, well, all that stuff
you gave me-
herbs, exercises,
acupuncture-
it helped, but the stress
started creeping up on me,
every time i saw my men
go into the fire.
but you got through it.
i did, because i found
something else to...
help me cope.
so what's the problem?
i'm wearing bras...
panties now.
i need you to cure me.
addison.
oh, hey. it's you.
s.w.a.t. guy.
yeah, hey, hey.
uh, listen,
about that message i left...
yeah,
that was, um-
humiliating.
no, i-i liked it.
yeah. oh, god, well...
that explains a lot.
you torture women to the point
of them calling you
and leaving horrifying messages
because you like it.
you're... you're sick.
yeah, i'm sorry.
i've been working like a dog.
i get on a case and...
i promise to do better.
i came to woo.
woo?
i got sprinkles.
this is you, wooing?
this is me being charmed
by your rambling
and incoherent message...
and asking you to lunch.
yeah.
i'm-i'm off to surgery.
don't write me off.
get to know me.
okay, uh, your doctor
sent me over your file.
you've been
having trouble sleeping?
on a good night,
i get four hours.
i figured sleeping pills
might help.
any idea of what's
preventing you from sleeping?
two jobs, past due bills,
a teenage son...
oh, a teenager. that will
do it right there, huh?
and how long has this been
going on, the insomnia?
uh, since my husband died
last year.
but lately, it's worse.
anything changed?
aren't you just supposed
to write a prescription?
sure.
i think it's important
to understand
what's behind the insomnia,
to talk about it.
i, uh...
you know, i, um,
i really-
i just need to sleep.
linda, the-the medication
will help,
but whatever's keeping you
from sleeping,
it's not
gonna take that away.
talk to me.
see if i can help.
i'm afraid of him.
afraid of whom?
my son.
i think he's a sociopath.
he killed our dog.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
片名private practice
第2季第3集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人id
校对：个人id
时间轴：夏
i just-
i found it in the garage.
he was wrapped in a blanket,
and i think his neck was broken.
and it was just a little beagle. why do you
think jesse would do something like that?
i don't know.
did you ask him?
yes, and he just looked at me.
he gave me this funny look.
but he's the only one who had access to the garage.
is he ever violent? have you ever seen this before?
no. see, that's the thing.
he was so...
but when
his father died, he changed.
he got, um, cold.
like he...
he doesn't react.
he doesn't laugh.
he doesn't cry.
he just has this cold,
hard stare,
and i-it just...
you know, he's my own son,
and i can't-
everyone has their own way
of responding to grief.
it's not grief.
i- i just need to sleep.
i'd like to talk to him.
no. i-i really want
those pills.
linda, you don't need the pills.
you need some help.
let me help.
fishing, the boat,
the sun on the water...
if any of my guys find out,
it's gonna be
the end of me, done.
keep trying to relax.
focus on fishing.
it doesn't work anymore.
i need the panties and bra.
how did this start, frank?
it was just knee-highs
around the house at first.
and then i got my hands
on a mail order catalog,
and... pages and pages
of pretty little things-
lace bras...
silk panties...
garters.
i see what you mean.
i have to live with these guys
24 hours at a time.
i almost got caught
twice already.
if they find out...
my credibility...
they won't trust me.
they won't listen.
and if i have to look
at a man's family
and tell them he's not
coming home because-
cross-dressing could go
to something deeper,
something a therapist
could help with.
no.
i can't tell anybody else.
frank, i'm-
please.
look, i trust you.
you helped me before.
i know you can help me now.
you have to...
or i'm... done.
how'd it go?
the fibroid's history.
it was nice to be back
in the saddle again.
i have a newborn with
a diaphragmatic hernia
being airlifted in.
don't you have someone else?
i do have patients.
double board certified
neonatal surgeons
aren't exactly
walking the streets, montgomery.
look, i hate to take you away
from all the fun at the office,
but on the bright side, you get
to save a life and work with me.
okay, i'm in.
charlotte, that newborn
being airlifted...
you don't have somebody else.
you knew i'd say yes. i hoped.
you're wooing me with surgery.
i am.
hey, did you hear about dell?
he's nursing at st. ambrose.
so now you want to talk
about dell? well, yeah.
naomi
- hey, nal, addison's staying
at the hospital
to do another surgery.
could you cover her patients?
uh, sure.
cool.
sam.
yes. good ol' boss sam,
you will be glad to know,
i have a new patient.
hey, one new patient.
maybe we can build
a new wing.
what about you?
don't you have a consult?
i can't do it.
my morning consult-major drama.
it may take the rest of the day,
so cancel everyone else
you had booked.
i know he's only a year old,
but you wait all this time
to have a baby,
you want him to be perfect,
and i'm-i'm just really worried
that he's-that-
that there's something wrong
with him, you know, with...
his head.
his head?
what's wrong with his head?
it's... big. not "big for
a 1-year-old body" big,
but "big for anybody's body"
big.
babies are sometimes born
with large heads,
but if you give it some time,
they usually grow into 'em.
it's not-
it's a really big head.
okay. let's take a look.
hey there, little fella.
you know, just to be
on the safe side,
i'm gonna run some tests, see if
there's anything going on.
so your mom said
it looked like the dog's neck
had been broken.
any idea how that happened?
it-it was in your garage.
any idea about that?
it was a beagle, right?
dodger?
your mom said you had it
since, uh, you were 6.
is that right?
okay. the dog's
too loaded a topic.
uh...
why don't we talk about
your father?
were the two of you close?
did he coach
any of your teams?
i hear you're
a great baseball player.
okay, i get it.
you don't want to be here.
a lot of people
don't like to talk
about difficult things.
but i have a job to do,
and that is to find out
if there's a problem here,
and to do that,
i need for us to talk...
about anything.
i want to get to know you,
jesse.
can i go now?
please.
dell?
hey.
so you're working here?
you look nice...
in your scrubs.
what are you doing here,
naomi?
i just came by to say hi.
it's great to see you.
we've missed you.
i've missed
- i really can't talk right now. i got a ton of patients.
dell.
i'm sorry. i gotta go.
i just saw this kid who had
a head the size of...
it was ginormous.
it was huge.
which is bigger,
ginormous or huge?
is it...
who's the truant?
consult's son.
he won't talk,
so i'm lettin' him stew.
is stewing a real
therapeutic technique?
usually works with you.
what's he stewing about?
his mother thinks he killed
the family dog.
oh. step one, right?
i mean, that's what they say
about serial killers, am i right?
oh, he's not a serial killer. i-
well, not now. i don't
even know if he did it.
is the mom lying?
she believes he did it.
i- i don't know his side
'cause he won't talk to me.
he-his father's dead,
his dog is dead.
he's got a lot of reason
to be angry.
you know, his mother thinks
he's a sociopath.
she goes on the internet, she puts together the signs
- is he?
i don't know.
i guess i could test him...
give him the m.m.p.i.
it would be so much easier
if he just had a pipe bomb
in his book bag.
you know-do you know how rare
a true sociopath is?
you don't want to be the one
that missed columbine.
you don't want to talk.
i get it.
leaves me
with a problem, though.
i have concerns about you,
and i'm not comfortable
with just watching you
walk out that door.
don't talk to me.
just fill this out.
true/false.
or we can sit here
all day.
okay, just so we're clear,
this is not a date.
this is a sandwich
between surgeries.
point is, it's getting
to know each other
without all that date crap.
mm.
tell me about this case
you've been working on.
you know, the one
that's kept you from calling.
i watched two people die.
it kinda made for a bad week.
yeah. i have been having
a run of those myself.
not people dying, just people
not talking to me...
mm-hmm.
people not talking
to each other.
all the people in my office
are walking around pissed off,
and nobody's talking about it.
that's why i'm here...
cutting people open.
getting out your hostilities.
actually... you put
a scalpel in my palm,
and i feel centered.
all the other problems
in the world just fall away.
it's hard to explain.
well, you can explain it to me
tomorrow night
when i take you out.
you're taking me out?
i am.
on a date?
yes. you're not going anywhere.
pregnant lady
with ovarian torsion.
o.r.'s ready. you up for
it, montgomery? yeah. mm.
yeah, no, go. cut people open. all
right. i'll see you, um, tomorrow night.
tomorrow night.
okay.
you know, we could use you.
sorry. excuse me?
here.
you could be a surgeon.
i could keep the o.r. full
and the board happy.
it's a symbiotic relationship.
i have a job, charlotte.
you're a surgeon, addison.
i'll think about it.
big.
how big?
mount rushmore big.
i'm thinking, like,
paget's disease
or acromegaly
or tuberous sclerosis.
i mean, this poor kid's
gonna be, like, a bobblehead
if i can't fix him.
at least he won't be
wearing a bra.
unless it's to give
his head more support.
i keep telling you,
it's not that unusual.
it's a coping mechanism, and
you said he's coping. yeah, but-
i got a maybe sociopath
who maybe killed his dog
who maybe i should lock up.
you got a bra and panties. you want
to trade? what happened with your test?
it's inconclusive.
does he like to smash things?
yes. does he feel anger? yes.
the only way to know
if he's a true sociopath
is to do a comprehensive
clinical evaluation,
and the kid's not talking.
so based on this test,
he doesn't meet the criteria
for me to hold him.
he's not a clear danger
to anyone.
there's not
a credible threat...
except i still don't know
what happened to the dog.
does anyone
have anything helpful to say?
yeah. at least
he doesn't have a big head.
or wear panties.
i've resected the cyst.
i just have to
detorse this ovary.
montgomery, they need you
in nicu now.
baby you worked on before,
0-2 sats are dropping.
crap. okay, let me just finish
ligating this vessel.
let me just take a look at
the baby, make sure it's okay.
done.
go ahead and close her up.
doctor.
oh, uh, she's fine.
i untwisted the ovary,
removed the cyst.
the baby's doing well.
they're gonna be okay.
is there any way i can- i
can g- not now. maybe later.
what about if i just
- i'm in the middle of an emergency,
but i'll come back to you. how
many surgeries have you done?
four.
what about your knee?
can't even feel it.
wow. you're a badass.
what, all you thought i did
was deliver babies?
hey, nal. so what's up?
i, uh, just finished
going over the budget.
i can't believe
there's all this paperwork.
i feel like
i'm doing six jobs now,
and none of 'em
is seeing my patients.
yeah, well, it's, uh,
it's tough being the boss.
what do you think about hiring a marketing
consultant? if you think it'll help.
right?
mm-hmm.
all right. thanks.
can you believe him?
i mean, does he not think
that i did the exact same things
when i was in charge?
only i wasn't stupid enough
to try and do it all by myself.
at least i had dell to help
me manage to run things
so that i could see patients.
i saw him today-dell-
at the hospital.
it was really weird-
i have a patient.
i gotta go.
so you're telling me
he's normal?
one test over one hour
is not gonna answer that,
but this does evaluate personality and
psychopathology. what about the dog?
he won't talk to me
about that right now.
but maybe if the two of you came in together, then
- no, i can't confront him.
you told me
to bring him in here.
you said that-
that you could help me,
and now he knows that i'm scared
of him. it's- no, i didn't tell him-
he's smart.
you think he's not
gonna figure this out?
look, i can't...
he had that dog
for ten years, and he...
he didn't
shed a tear when it died.
he snapped its neck
and hid it in the garage,
and he didn't shed a tear
because he didn't care.
linda-
i can't sleep.
i lie awake with a h-
with a hammer
under my pillow
because i'm afraid of what
he's gonna do to me.
and now you're telling me
that you can't help me?
you told me
you would help me.
you should have
given me those pills,
'cause i could've buried it.
i need you
to help me, please.
i'm afrid of my own son
dell.
um, i know
you were busy before,
and, uh, i had to see
some patients.
and i thought
you might be getting off.
i'm doing a double shift.
i took you for granted.
i didn't listen,
and i should have.
you were trying to help me,
and i didn't let you.
i want you to come back.
i have a job, naomi,
a place where i'm respected.
the practice has been...
adrift, dell,
since you left.
i've been adrift.
you know, i'm not talking
to addison,
barely talking to sam,
and violet doesn't want
to hear from me.
you're not there...
to talk to.
no. no, i'm here,
doing things i love
and-and learning a lot
from people who aren't
afraid to teach me. dell.
i'm working, okay?
i work here.
excuse me.
i think
he's happy here, nal.
it seems like a lot of people are
happy here. just trying to do my part.
that's nice.
thanks for doing that for me
when i was in charge.
you never asked, naomi.
that's the problem.
you never asked.
you're in a good mood.
your montgomery's a real star.
cash cow for me today.
she's really
making me look good.
i'm glad someone does.
stop mopin'.
i don't like mopin' sex.
i have a kid with a big head,
who, as it turns out,
has nothing wrong with him,
except that he's going to be
mocked and ridiculed
and looked down on for the rest
of his life. and that's your fault?
no, that's me. i'm the one
who doesn't fit in,
who's gonna be
first out of the practice
because they don't want me
on their team anymore.
i am the bighead kid. oh, my god. you
are pathetic. you are crazy and pathetic.
a big head's not a problem.
it's a virtue, moron.
you know who had a big head?
lincoln, j.f.k., elvis,
einstein.
plenty of people have big heads,
and they don't sit and mope
that they have a big head.
so don't you sit and mope
that you're a pediatrician.
do your job, do it well,
and screw everyone else.
you're the bighead kid.
more power to you.
can we get
our clothes off now?
hmm?
oh, i rescheduled
your consults for tomorrow.
no.
n- no?
life is not 15 minutes, sam.
this woman and her son cannot
be fixed in 15 minutes.
well, i'm sure you did
everything that you could.
not yet. tomorrow i'm going
to the kid's school,
i'm talking to his teachers
and his counselors,
and i am trying to get answers
to the questions
he won't talk to me
about today.
cost-effective? no.
but if it helps the kid...
i'm sorry
if this does not fit into
the new way of doing things.
where's the fire?
it's no joke.
my fire captain,
he's in the e.r.
hey, hey, pete.
hey.
what are you doing here?
firefighter patient.
i got paged.
what about you? you've
been here all day. yep.
you ever gonna come back
to the practice?
maybe. one day.
see you.
good luck.
dr. montgomery,
the ovarian torsion you fixed,
her pressure's down
to 80 over 40.
post-op crit's 26
and dropping.
she's bleeding out.
what about the baby?
it's in distress.
open the o.r.
extensive
partial thickness burns,
but he won't let anybody
touch him except for you.
he's over here.
i'm here, frank. i
couldn't let anyone see me.
okay. get me a blood gas kit
and run a carboxyheme level.
i need a chem panel, c.b.c.
and chest x-ray,
and set me up
for a subclavian.
5- story blaze...
beam came down...
everybody get out okay?
you're not getting air,
frank.
you gotta stay with me.
hang on.
i'm almost there.
you're gonna be okay.
no.
i'm done.
are they okay?
oh. your wife had some,
uh, post-op bleeding,
but she's safe, and the baby should be
fine. when you came out of surgery before,
you said they were fine then. they were,
but then your wife started hemorrhaging.
i had to go back in. and it's not
because you ran out to some other surgery?
no. no. it's not.
what about now?
i mean, you're-
you're saying she's fine now,
but how do i know?
right now, your wife,
she's doing as well as she can.
she's a fighter.
she's gonna come through this.
what's her name?
excuse me?
my wife's name.
you keep talking about "she"
and "her" and "your wife,"
and you're running
up and down this hall,
and you're popping in
and you're cutting people open,
and you're talking about her
like you know her,
but you haven't mentioned her name. i...
i don't know her name.
it's heather.
her name's heather.
and this is the third time
she's been pregnant.
we lost two babies before.
she keeps redecorating
the nursery,
hoping that
that's gonna change things.
it's red now. who... who ever
heard of a red nursery?
but her students-
her students told her
that it would be good luck,
and she wanted
to believe them.
you operated
on her twice today.
you should've known her name.
a few weeks, you should be
you'rup and around.frank.
and then what?
i told you, i'm done.
i can't believe that's true.
i'm resigning.
these guys depend on me.
if they can't
feel comfortable with me,
if they think i'm a freak...
we all feel stress, frank.
you more than most.
but you know what? you found
a way to deal with it.
some people drink too much,
some eat too much,
some people... run.
i wish i had a thing
that worked.
when everything around you
is falling apart
and you need
to keep it together,
a thing is good.
so i wear
a bra and panties forever?
maybe if you talked
to someone,
maybe if you didn't shoulder
all of that stress yourself,
it might be better.
fine. i'll go to therapy.
but it's still too late.
you run into burning buildings
and save lives.
how many of your men
have you gone in after?
if it's me...
i don't care
what you're wearing
as long
as you get me out alive.
6 surgeries in 24 hours.
what's it like?
to be a surgeon?
to be the best.
i came here to get away from
a bunch of people not talking,
and i ended up
being the one not talking...
not talking
to a single patient.
i cut 'em open, sewed 'em up,
and i didn't have any idea
who they were.
that's not a doctor,
and it's certainly not
the best.
thanks for the job offer,
charlotte,
but i have a job, a home.
i've run every lab
i can think of.
there's nothing wrong with
miles' head. so it's...
that's just the way he is.
your son's fine,
and he may grow into it.
what if he doesn't?
you must think i'm awful.
i should be elated that my
son is fine, it's just-
he's different.
yes.
me? i was slow.
the other kids could all
run faster. i hated p.e.
my best friend brad, he had
two teeth that never grew in.
he's the c.e.o.
of a fortune 500 company now.
i see a lot of kids,
and they're all different
in one way or another.
he'll be picked on.
maybe.
maybe he'll be a bully.
maybe he'll be president.
you know, a lot of
the presidents had big heads-
j.f.k., lincoln.
he's on mount rushmore now.
thanks.
you made my mom cry.
what did you ???
i- i told her that i
didn't think i could help you
if you wouldn't talk to me.
what are you doing here?
i'm trying to figure out what you
won't tell me. no. you let this go.
my job is to help people,
and i-i want to help you.
and i am not gonna stop
talking or asking questions
until you answer some.
what happened to the dog?
what happened to the dog,
jesse?
jesse... you loved
that dog, didn't you?
you loved that dog,
you didn't shed a tear,
and i want to know why.
tell me why.
do you know how much it costs
to put a dog down?
do you?
he had cancer.
it was thousands of dollars
to treat him,
and she was gonna do it.
my dad's cancer
almost bankrupted us,
but she was gonna do it
because she couldn't bear
to see another thing
die again.
she didn't want me to
have to go through it again.
we couldn't afford it.
it was $385 to put him down.
we didn't have that either.
so i did what i had to do.
it was my dog...
and i killed him...
because my dad said
i had to be the man.
i had to be responsible.
still here?
just leaving.
naomi wants me
to come back.
she misses you.
she just wants me to come back
for her, not for me.
dell, when a friend asks you
to step up, you do it.
it's just what you do.
you're part of the family.
yeah.
i'm the part of the family
they're embarrassed by.
that is not true.
you ran away.
you got your feelings hurt,
and you ran away.
now you may have reason,
but hiding out here,
avoiding your problems,
not talking to the people
that need you...
how are you ever gonna get
what you want?
talking is important...
okay.
because when you don't talk,
when you don't say what's on your mind
- what are you talking about?
i meyo, you-youd old me
not to talk to you about sam,
and when i tried to talk to you
about dell, you walkedy.way.
bee use you were using measasr.our.dd
m i'm yot yodd add,on,
not anymore.
i used to be,
before addison got here.
and then you just started...
talking to her.
you hurt my feelings.
and... i know
i'm a therapist,
and i'm supposed to say
that it's all right,
but it's not all right.
and you can't just make me
your addison again
and think
that makes it all better.
work it out with addison.
and for god sake,
stop sleeping with sam
unless you can tell him
how wrong this all is,
his stealing your job
and using you
as a sounding board.
and then come talk to me...
when you want to talk to me.
you came back.
yeah.
so is this the new you?
you gonna hide out
and do surgery
and leave
your old friends behind?
i wish i felt like my
old friends were my old friends.
you did what you had to,
telling sam,
breaking your word to naomi.
i never said that.
i thought i should say that.
thanks.
please
well, this is nice.
it's nice, yeah.
us... as friends.
now that we're past all that,
you know, awkwardness.
yeah.
it's good.
and if we keep at it
for a few months,
we could be old friends.
dell.
yeah.
i hear you're in charge now.
what's this?
it's a list of demands-
what i need to come back.
patients? supervised. i need the
hours for my midwife's license.
sorry, no.
sam.
hey, he walked out.
and it's been worse
since he's been gone.
no. we can't afford it.
can you give us
a minute, please?
naomi, we can't add staff-
i am talking now.
you took my job.
you went behind my back,
conspired with my best friend,
took over the practice,
and now you think you can just
unilaterally make decisions,
or worse-run ideas by me
like none of it ever happened.
well, guess what, sam?
i don't want to hear your ideas.
i'm not your sounding board,
and i am not going to help you.
you find somebody else.
at least i was smart enough
to find the person
who is standing
right outside your door.
you start today.
you see patients only supervised
by naomi or addison or pete,
and we see.
i can live with that.
you resume being office manager.
vendors, filing,
equipment leasing,
scheduling, ordering supplies-
that's yours.
that's what i need
from you.
and one last demand.
it's not on the list.
i want scrubs
in a better color.
i'm a man. i'm not wearing
those damn pink scrubs.
welcome back, dell.
good. you're here.
can you
get your clothes off?
what's wrong?
nothing.
there's something wrong.
i can tell.
we don't do
the talking thing, cooper.
yes, we do. you yelled at me.
you confirmed i had a big head.
it made me feel better.
let me yell at you,
make you feel better.
i'm not letting you
get a piece of this
until you start talking.
i offered addison a job...
and she turned me down.
can you
take your clothes off now?
you like knives.
i like guns.
centered?
wow.
all that not talking...
talking is overrated.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入