Your family,
Whatever that means-
If you're single,
If you're married,
If-if you have kids
Or if you want kids-
Your family should be
The most important thing.
And your family is
The most important thing to us.
What are you doing?
I'm supporting
My eating disorder.
What are you doing?
Oh, using handbags to fill
The sexual void.
Emotional health is as important
As physical health.
I create a safe place to talk.
Well, i am avoiding
Sam's kisses.
I'm avoiding dell's kisses.
I am avoiding being kissed.
I'm gonna donate my lips
To chocolate.
Yeah, well, the cop
Still hasn't called.
Two weeks, no call.
These lips? Dry.
Virgin lips untouched by man.
I am having sex
With bottega veneta.
I put my hands inside
A woman's body,
And i fix what's wrong.
But every woman's body
Is different.
Every woman's story
We get our bonus checks
This week,
And i say we blow it all
On mnemba island.
It-it's zanzibar, coop.
It's unsullied.
Let's go sully it.
Cooper?
Are you listening?
I'm gonna have to
Call you back.
How do you know
You're doing what's best
To take care of your child?
Who's gonna help you
If the baby won't eat,
Isn't gaining enough weight,
Has a fever?
That's my job.
Come here to me... Now.
I use eastern medicine
To prevent illness.
I solve problems
Before they start.
So i wait outside addison's
House for, like, 2 hours.
She didn't show up.
I don't wait outside
Women's houses.
She should be waiting outside my house.
Does she even know you're interested?
She'll know. I'm on it.
She has you on a string.
Yeah, you get anywhere
With naomi?
Hey, that-that's-
That's not the point.
Okay, i'm not on a string.
Pfft.
I'm in charge.
I'm-i'm in control.
I got this.
Yeah, how do you
Have this?
I don't know yet.
A doctor's office
Should be a sanctuary.
The care you receive should
Be personal. It's good.
that's what we do. We're a family...
Really good. Naomi did a good job.
It looks like it cost way more
Than she said it would cost.
Is this gonna affect our bonus checks? I need my
Bonus check. You're gonna get your bonus checks.
We sound professional,
But is it just me,
Or is it a gap ad for medicine? Yeah, we're
Branded. We're a brand, like a perfume.
"my symptoms"-
A fragrance for men.
Dell, what'd you think?
You cut my line.
I wasn't even in it,
Not one single shot of me.
your wife's...
Your husband's.
at oceanside wellness...
Our family
takes care of your family.
I really need my bonus
Check, sam. Yeah, bonus check.
Yeah, sam,
Bonus checks.
Everybody's getting
Their bonus checks.
She's avoiding me.
I'll talk to her.
Nal,
The video looks good.
Yeah, it's, uh, uh,
Gonna run on the internet,
In the lobby
On the monitors,
And i also lined up
A group of dentists
Who are gonna show it
In their offices.
It cost a lot of money, but you
Spend money to make money.
That's the goal
- make money. You okay?
Yeah, i'm fine.
Your files...
And these.
Thank you, dell.
If you have some time later, i
Think we should have a meeting.
I have, uh,
Wall-to-wall patients today,
So...
Okay.
He try to kiss you again?
Did sam?
'Cause i'll punch 'em.
Verbally, i mean.
I can do verbal punching for
You. I would do that for you.
Nal, are you-what's wrong?
Nothing, i am fine.
I've got patients.
What happened
To the paper cups?
They're not justifiable
Environmentally.
Mugs-are they justifiable?
The dishwasher.
Hey, cooper. Guess who's
Been to the travel agent. Oh.
Look, zanzibar. Don't you
Feel drunk just looking at it?
I don't know if i can go away
This year. We go away every year.
I have a patient.
We'll talk about it later.
Dr. King.
Dr. Freedman.
I assume you're here on
Important hospital business?
I am.
Well, let's... Talk.
Can i tell people
About us?
What?
I mean, just violet.
It's getting secret-y,
And i don't really do secret-y,
And my bonus check comes
This week.
You want to pay me
For the sex?
I thought we could use
The money
To go away together...
On vacation.
You and me on a... Vacation?
Yeah, like a normal couple.
I tell violet everything.
She's like my sister.
She's like my hot sister,
And we use our bonus checks
To go away every year.
But i think if i went away without you
- do not say it.
I might miss you.
Cooper.
Yes. Either get back on
Top of me and shut up,
Or keep talking and watch me
Walk out that door.
-==ææàãğüàöô°çãçé•îï×==-
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-=ææàãğü×öä»×é=-
•­òë:
Ğ£¶ô:
Ê±¼äöá£º²ı¸ùã»å® seed
Â¼öæ£º¸öèëid
There is a lack of paper
Cups. Dell's going green.
So what are you doing with your
Bonus? Maybe buying paper cups.
Do you want to go out sometime? Out?
On a date.
Well, that's...
Uh... Do you think
That's wise?
Uh, is there someone else?
Yes. No.
There was a person, uh,
An officer of the law,
But we never connected.
So, no, no, there's
- there's no one else. Okay, then.
Think about it.
Hey, uh, molly madison is on her way in.
She was just here a couple of days ago.
I- oh, nervous mommies.
I do not have time
For nervous mommies.
Hey, addie. Can you see
A patient for me?
She's in room, uh...
Four.
Yeah, i have time.
Thanks.
Thank you.
What's her story?
She's just got the jitters.
It'll be ten minutes tops.
So, uh, pete asked me out.
Do i go? No, i mean, do i go,
With the dry, untouched lips and
All? I'm making human life here.
Patient.
I will see her now.
Thank you.
Hi.
You... Asked me out,
And then you blew me off. Hi.
I didn't blow you off.
I had training
For the s.w.a.t. Team.
I'm s.w.a.t. Now.
You show that to all the
Girls? No, just the cute ones.
Mm. But i'm here now. I'm available.
I have a patient.
And you are just a stranger,
Some guy i met, you know,
And i don't get blown off.
I am not the kind of woman
You blow off.
You have your pride.
I have my pride, yes.
Go away.
Go s.w.a.t. Something.
Molly, eric.
Hi, i'm dr. Montgomery.
Where's dr. Bennett?
She has another patient.
We need to see dr. Bennett.
Well, why don't we just see
If i can find out
What the problem is first?
Let's see-
27 weeks pregnant,
Ultrasound from two days ago
Looks good,
Oh, it's a girl,
And... Placenta positioning
Looks good.
So what's the concern?
I- i need to have this baby.
Well, everything's on track.
No, that-
That's not what-eric.
We need to have this baby
Now. Today if possible.
I'm-i'm sorry.
I'm not understanding.
You're only
Six months pregnant.
Well, you have to induce
Or do a c-section
so that i can
Have this baby today.
It has to be born.
Please just-
He'll die if you don't.
He-he is dying, damn it.
I'm sorry, who is dying?
Our son jason. He's 7.
He has
Acute lymphoblastic leukemia.
The baby's cord blood's the only
Thing that can save him.
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
Ë½èëõïëù µú¶ş¼¾µú1¼¯
You're avoiding me.
I am not avoiding you.
I've just been busy-
Running the practice
And raising our daughter.
Always keeping the trains
Running on time.
Trains or no trains,
We will talk.
Hey, do you have a minute?
No, act-
No, she does not.
What?
Molly and eric madison.
You selected the embryo that
Matched their dying son...
And implanted it.
Selective i.v.f.
You chose a genetic match
For their dying son
And impregnated her?
Yes. I-i do not understand
What the problem is here?
The problem is that
She's carrying a child,
Except to her it's not a child,
It's an organ donor.
To her, she's growing organs
For her sick son.
Not organs.
The umbilical cord blood
Is going to be collected
At birth, processed,
And then infused into her son to save his
Life. Same thing, nal. Morally, ethically-
It's a gray area to grow
A child's genetic match.
This is done all the time
As a backup.
But he is dying now,
And she wants her daughter
Delivered
Three months premature
With no regard
For the baby's health.
Oh, god. I didn't...
They-they had
A partial match donor.
The partial match
Has pneumonia.
Addison...
That means...
Their son has had
His immune system stripped
In preparation for the donor.
He's in the hospital right now,
And if he doesn't receive
That cord blood
Within the week, he dies.
Well, what did you tell 'em about
Delivering the baby? I said no.
Why?
Thank you for the update,
Dr. King.
You're welcome,
Dr. Freedman.
Hey. I was just coming-
So on mnemba island,
There's no phones,
There's no computer,
There's no television.
Our bonus checks will be put
To very good use.
Um, i don't know. Maybe.
We can touch monkeys, cooper.
We can touch monkeys.
Yeah, okay. You made that
Last part up. I have patients.
Well, i have patients, too,
And as i am seeing them,
Part of me will be conjuring
Images of touchable monkeys.
Dean.
Hey, dr. Freedman.
How you been?
Good.
How about you? How you
Been? It was a good month.
That's what i like to hear.
Dell, the new patient
Gowns blow. They keep ripping.
Yeah, we're working out the kinks with some
New vendors. What's wrong with the old vendors?
And where are the-
Dishwasher.
Yeah,
Everything looks good.
Everything at school good?
Good. I have a girlfriend.
Amy. She's amazing.
Well, good.
You taking it slow?
We haven't done it... Yet,
But she's going on the pill,
So we will soon.
Believe me when i say
I will not be
The first of my friends.
Oh, i know, but, um,
Condoms, okay?
Hey, s.t.d.s don't care
About the pill.
Condoms are your friend-
Lots of condoms.
Or better yet, you know,
Wait.
If this is the girl, you ought
To enjoy the time before,
Because once you're on
The other side,
you can't go back.
Hello.
You just heard "blah, blah,
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah"?
Dr. Freedman,
I'm gonna have sex,
And i really like her.
It's not all skanky.
It's right.
I, like, love her
And everything.
Well... Now i go back
To my condom speech.
So i am your friendly
Neighborhood
Condom pusher man.
Condoms.
If you can save their son by
Delivering the baby, i don't-
6- month preemies are at risk
For brain bleeds, blindness,
Hearing loss, not to mention
Respiratory distress.
And no one would advocate
Bringing a child
Into the world before
She's ready, and you know it.
Did you even consider the fact
That this little girl
Is arriving into a family
Unwanted?
What happens when she discovers
That the only reason
She was conceived was to save her
Brother's life? We are talking about
Saving this family from
Suffering the death of a child.
You gave them hope they shouldn't have. I
- i'm trying to save a child's life.
You discuss this stuff
With us.
When any of us come into
An ethical gray area,
We all discuss it.
We decide as a practice
What to do.
I meant to, all right?
I... I just forgot.
Since when do you
Forget anything?
If i could get one guy
To do a colonoscopy
With no complaint...
I mean, like i'm happy about
Going all up in there.
What are you looking for?
I'm trying
To leave you a note,
But i can't find a pen that works.
Well, what's-what's the note?
How i can't find a pen
That works.
Dell has decided to go green-
Tissue paper gowns,
No cups, no pens.
I'm all about saving the planet, but he's
Killing me. You want me to talk to dell?
We both know
Who dell listens to.
Is this naomi's idea?
I have no clue
What naomi's ideas are.
My woman's giving me trouble.
Your woman's giving you trouble.
These women, cooper.
What?
14-year-old kid, i've been
Treating him since he was 5.
Now he's found this girl-
He likes her,
They're gonna have sex.
That's hardly a shocker.
Wait, don't tell me you're getting
All nostalgic. It's dean miller.
Oh, man. Why does that
Name sound familiar?
Because we debated whether
We should take him on
As a patient.
He's the kid who-
He's h.i.v. Positive, but that wasn't the debate.
The problem is, he doesn't know he's h.i.v. Positive.
His parents won't tell him,
And he doesn't know
He could kill that girl.
He thinks
He has a kidney condition,
And he's doing quite well.
I mean, the majority
Of his symptoms are from the antiviral
Cocktail. How do you keep something like that
From your kid for 14 years? It
Was before the prognosis changed.
They didn't think
He was gonna be alive
Long enough to understand. So
That explains the first six years.
I'm not allowed to tell him
About the h.i.v.
I'm not allowed
To tell the parents
Anything that dean tells me.
Doctor-patient confidentiality
All around. So you can't
Let 'em know about the girlfriend.
No, or that they're gonna do it.
This is a good kid.
He would not endanger this girl
If he knew, and he doesn't.
His hormones are full roar,
Right? He likes the girl.
He wants the girl. He's gotta have
The girl. We've all been there.
Yes, we have.
Anyway...
You know what?
I gotta try to get
His parents back in my office.
He loves bugs.
And he sneaks ladybugs
Into the house in his pocket.
He likes meatballs...
And french fries.
And he's still
Afraid of the dark,
But he thinks
He's too old to admit it,
So i have to pretend
To forget to turn off
The light at bedtime.
And he likes to read. And all
He wants for his 8th birthday
Is to never go
To a hospital again.
He-he's a wonderful boy.
I can see that,
But, mrs. Madison, i can't.
In good conscience, i can't
Deliver your baby early
Because i'm sure
She's wonderful, too.
We are good people and-and we
Didn't go into this lightly-
Having this baby-
And we will love her.
We will. It's just,
We don't know her yet.
And... I-i know jason.
I've held jason.
I- i've smelled his skin.
I- i know jason.
I'm so sorry.
I- i've checked you out.
You're a specialist.
If-if anyone can deliver
A premature baby safely,
It's you.
I wish i could help,
But there's nothing i can do.
How can you
Look at my 7-year-old son
And know he's going to be dead
In a week and do nothing? Please.
Addison-
Don't talk to me.
Addi-
Don't say anything, please. Just don't.
Addison, i was not trying to manipulate you.
I just thought if you saw him,
Maybe you would realize
That you can help them.
I can't help them!
You gave them hope
They shouldn't have,
And now i am the bad guy.
Addison.
I told you
Not to say anything to me.
Hey, i really do need to
Talk to you. Not now, dell.
Are you okay?
What's going on?
Has there been bloodshed?
Because naomi is in the kitchen
Just inhaling the candy supply.
Come on. It was low to begin with.
Well, dell refuses to buy any new candy.
Wait, he's withholding candy?
He told me to "make due"
With the sweet tarts from last halloween?
Well, nobody can handle the old sweet tarts.
We need chocolate. No, i told-i
Told dell that he had to get-
this has nothing to do
With candy.
I can't do anything.
I can't save that child.
I can't deliver the baby.
To the best
Of my medical expertise...
I cannot do... Anything.
Don't beat yourself up.
It's not your mess. It's naomi's.
Wait, you mean the madisons?
Because naomi did
What she thought was right.
You do what you need to do
To save your family.
She had no way of knowing
The donor would back out,
And now it's too late. But we always
Discuss these things as a group.
Naomi went ahead and did this
Without talking to anybody.
So maybe
She's off her game.
She's seeing a record number of patients a day
- she's been really on edge lately.
Yeah, it's not like her.
Well, guys, i mean,
She does everything.
We just...
Eat the candy.
She's hiding something.
Has anybody even asked her
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
This i can
Do something about.
Who'd win in a fistfight,
Naomi or addison?
Not in the mood
For a lecture.
Oh, i'm not gonna lecture you.
I'm just gonna block the exits
Until you decide to tell me what's going on with
You. Well, we're gonna be here a very long time.
I can wait.
What, they're not
Even saying anything?
They're just standing
There. A test of wills.
A battle of champions.
Uh-huh.
You guys are so mature. Oh,
Yeah? You mentioned a fistfight.
That's true.
Cooper.
Dean's parents are here...
Thanks.
And everyone else.
There's a lobby
Full of patients...
In case anyone is interested
In working here
Or running this place.
There's a girl dean likes,
But sex is a long way off.
I've had pregnant
13 year olds
Whose parents
Have said the same thing.
Dean needs to know
His h.i.v. Status
Before he starts experimenting.
And he will.
What i'm saying is,
You can't afford to wait.
You have any idea what it's
Like for h.i.v. Kids?
A kid in chicago got shot.
Another kid, they tied him to a car
Bumper. That's before people were educated.
Nobody needs to know but dean. He's not
Old enough to deal with this, not yet.
You want them to be children
As long as it lasts.
Things are so sweet,
They can still be anything.
As soon as that's over-
I wish it could be longer,
But it can't.
You say people are educated?
They'll understand?
If it was your kid,
You wouldn't be so sure.
Could you honestly live with yourselves
- do you not hear me?
If he gets another kid sick,
What happens when he finds out
That you didn't
- we will do what's best for him, and don't you overstep here.
You're not leaving me
Much choice.
Say one word to dean,
And i-i'll take your license.
I will sue you
For everything you've got.
Nal... Come on.
You can tell me anything.
It's not like you to get
The madisons pregnant
Without discussing it
With the rest of us.
Now i know you must have
Had a good reason.
You have a good heart.
Just talk to me.
They paid the practice
$80,000.
and i don't have
A good heart.
They had cash,
And we needed the money,
And so i took it
Even though
I did have reservations,
Because naomi always keeps
The trains running on time.
What, uh, what do you-
What do you mean? What-
I keep the trains running
On time. That's what i do.
I run things.
I mind the details.
Only this time, it...
Just got away from me.
What got away from you?
You can't tell anybody.
You cannot tell the others. You have
To promise. What, um, okay, i promise.
What, are you-you're talking
About the practice?
We own the building.
And-and i saw a chance
To refinance the mortgage,
And i thought...
Now the balloon payment
Is due,
And no one is billing enough,
And there isn't enough.
There is never enough.
And so i used the last of
The money to make the video.
Naomi-
We are broke, addison.
If things keep going
The way they have been,
The practice is finished...
Soon.
All right, screw them.
We let them come after me.
They really think
A jury's gonna back them
When they're perfectly happy
To let their son infect some nice girl from the
'Burbs? The law says they have the right to do this
How they want to do this. I'm taking
My chances. I'm gonna tell dean.
If they sue,
They sue the practice.
Why don't you think about
Someone other than yourself?
Whoa, naomi. Coop's just trying to do the right
Thing, here. He's talking about getting us sued.
There are
Responsibilities here.
So you think that family
Has the right
To hide important information
From each other?
Sometimes people hide things for good reason.
Hiding things is no way to protect them.
it is when you're the
One in charge. Whoa. Whoa.
Everybody breathe. Cooper's
Gonna figure out a way.
He always does.
Mm.
Hey.
Is it wise?
Huh?
Our date.
Oh.
Um, i haven't had time-
Can we talk
About this tomorrow?
So you, uh, you ready
To talk yet?
No, i am not ready
To talk...
About anything.
Good night, guys.
Okay.
Wait, hey-
Good night.
These women.
Shots.
Yeah.
Cooper always
Figures out a way?
Cooper does not always
Figure out a way.
You know what's gonna make you
Feel better? Mnemba. Mnemba.
Monkey touching.
i got the pamphlets right here. Violet.
There's pretty girls
In the pamphlets,
And they might do dirty,
Trashy things to you
When i'm in the spa.
Is that what this is about?
A girl? Is there...
Cooper do you have a woman
That i don't know about,
A non-cyber woman?
There's no woman.
Then what is it?
It's bonus time.
We always blow half of it
On sunburns
And hazy memories, coop.
Violet, don't count on me
This year.
Want to play
Naughty little schoolboy?
Mistress and butler?
I could be the warden,
You could be my prisoner.
How about...
Boyfriend and girlfriend?
Damn it, cooper.
You really know
How to dry a girl up.
Okay, first of all,
It was a suggestion.
And second of all,
I lied today.
I told violet a lie. I told her
I wasn't seeing anybody.
Would you rather
Lie to violet
And play naughty schoolboy
With me,
Or tell her the truth
And play with yourself?
Why do we
Have to keep it a secret?
'Cause y'all are one big
Incestuous family,
And i'm not joining
The family.
This isn't that serious.
I'm sick
Of keeping secrets,
And i'm really sick of keeping
Secrets from my best friend.
So... Maybe you should
Just go.
I'm wearing
Crotchless panties, coop.
No, no. No.
I am not your toy.
There's a lot of other things
I could be doing,
You know, better things.
I could be traling. I could be
Touching monkeys in mnemba. Mnemba?
Zanzibar.
And you could be with me
If you weren't
Pathologically allergic
To human relationships.
Crotchless panties.
Hey.
Did naomi say anything
To you?
What...
What do you mean?
In the kitchen, did she
Tell you what was wrong?
Oh, no. I-i think she's
Just tired. I think it's me.
I've been pressuring her
To talk about us.
I just wanted a second chance,
And i don't think
She wants to give it to me.
I think this is her way
Of telling me that...
It's over between us.
No, sam. I'm sure
That's not what it is.
Then what is it?
It's like i said.
She's just... Tired.
All right.
Yeah, yeah,
That's fine. All right.
Addison...
He has no idea
What is going on with you.
If you-
No. No.
This is dr. Montgomery.
This is dr. Bennett.
We'll be right there. I'll
Drive. I'll call charlotte king
To get you surgical privileges
At the hospital.
Dell, cancel my patients
For the rest of the day.
You said
This was an emergency.
I thought that meant there was
Something in his labs.
No, he's fine.
Dean... Your mom and dad,
They still think of you
As being a kid.
Well, i am...
Mostly a kid.
Yeah, but you're not a kid.
That's not what i see.
That's not what i hear
From you.
I think everybody needs
To know the truth here.
We're fine with how things
Are. Then i have no choice.
I have to reveal something that, legally, i'm not
Allowed to. I thought we were clear about this.
Come on, honey. We're
Going. Dean, your parents-
Stop!
This is not your place.
This is my child,
This is my little boy,
And i will do what's right.
Dean's planning on having sex
With his girlfriend.
Mom.
No...
I trusted you.
Why would you do this?
Why is this such a huge deal?
It's not the end of the world.
What's going on?
Dr. Freedman,
Could you step out?
Yeah.
What happened?
She's not dilated
Or effaced,
But her water broke
An hour ago.
Plus, she's bleeding,
And the baby's showing signs
Of distress.
I've gotta get
That baby out now.
Naomi, if you collect
The cord blood,
I have a team standing by
Ready to transplant.
Jason's prepped and waiting.
Yeah.
What did you do?
Her water just broke.
I am the best chance
Your baby has of survival,
But i will walk out
Of this hospital right now
And leave you, your baby
And your son's lives
To some nervous o.b. Resident
If you lie to me again.
i am sick of lies.
What did you do?
I broke my water myself...
With a knitting needle.
I need an o.r.
Call anesthesia,
Make sure we can get a spinal,
And notify nicu ???
Is the baby okay?
Taking out the placenta...
And the umbilical cord.
Who's closing?
Over here.
Get in here.
Is the baby okay?
Apgar's 4. 3-0 e.t. Tube and a
Straight blade. Wait! Is the baby okay?
No. No, she is not okay.
Please. I'm sorry.
Please just save her.
Please.
I am doing everything i can.
Molly,
Eric and i are leaving.
Jason should have his father
With him just in case. Okay.
I'm sorry.
Okay, maybe we should-
Stop! Enough!
What am i gonna tell people?
"sorry, i forgot i have a.i.d.s."?
You don't have a.i.d.s. Okay, h.i.v.-
H.i.v.-
You take care of yourself,
You're gonna live
A long, healthy life.
You knew,
And all this time,
You didn't tell me.
I thought you were my friend.
I couldn't tell you
The truth before.
And now i will tell you
Everything you need to know,
And i swear...
I'll do everything i can
To help you have the life you
Want. But you can't. It's too late.
We had sex last night.
It's too late.
Cord blood's on its way
To jason and...
Oh, damn.
I'll see if i can get
The parents up here
To say good-bye
Before she goes.
Wait. We're gonna try
Liquid ventilation on her.
That's highly experimental.
Yes. Have you ever done it before?
No, but i'm about
To do it now.
The fluid expands her lugs
So they don't collapse.
We're simulating the womb.
Keep an eye on her sats.
If they go up,
We know it's working.
Montgomery, sats are falling.
Give me a second.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
There we go.
Montgomery, where the hell
Have you been hiding
All my medical life?
Aww, i like you, too,
Charlotte.
Hi. I came by to check on
The madisons.
How are they doing? Mom's
In recovery from her "c."
Jason's receiving
His cord blood infusion.
Montgomery's keeping
The baby alive
Through sheer force of will.
It's a mess.
You ever miss
The good old days,
When life and death was decided
By god instead of doctors?
Well, we'd be out of jobs.
But, man,
It would be good, though,
To just not be in control,
To just let go, let god.
I could travel.
I could go to africa.
I could... Touch monkeys...
Or whatever.
How's jason?
We'll see.
How's the baby?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Okay.
You did the right thing.
I know.
You did what you could.
But that doesn't make it
Any better.
Nope.
I have to talk to you.
Dell, i don't have time
For your stuff right now.
It's gonna have to wait. You know, i-i've
Been covering for you the best that i can-
The bills, the late notices,
The vendor calls.
And while
You're working overtime
To stop the hemorrhaging,
I've been trying to catch
The things you forget
And the stuff you don't see.
Okay, i've been
Keeping your secrets
And i have been hiding
Your mistakes,
And i just wanted to say
Something so i could help you.
I- i thought that you-
I know what you thought.
You thought i... You thought
I wanted to talk about us.
But i get it.
There is no us.
So, um...
Daily patient schedules,
Phone sheets, vendor lists
And my keys to the offices.
Dell, what...
I quit.
Naomi's running the practice
Into the ground.
I wasn't thinking.
Something has to be done,
And i can't be the one to do it.
I'm new here.
I haven't earned the right.
And she's my best friend.
Well, i'm her husband.
Was.
I was her husband.
Now i'm not anything so-
Sam,
Something has to be done,
And you have to be
The one to do it.
Yeah.
You're here late.
I'm catching up
On patient notes.
Me, too.
Want to know the truth?
I'm trying to remember
What i did
Before cooper got a life?
It's ridiculous.
He used to need me,
And now i need him.
I'm trying to figure out
What it is about addison
That makes me act like
A 14-year-old boy.
It's humiliating.
I gotta start
Sleeping around again.
Do you want to come
To zanzibar with me?
Pretty girls in zanzibar.
I've been.
You can touch monkeys there,
You know.
I knew it.
You can't tell anyone
About us.
But i will consider a vacation-
Somewhere close,
Somewhere i can
Flee from easily,
Like napa or palm springs.
I'm here.
I came crawlin' back, okay?
I'm crawlin'.
In crotchless panties?
In no panties.
You know where i live?
I'm a cop. I-i know
Where everyone lives.
Funny. Um...
Listen, i have had...
The worst day, so-
Well, we could go out.
We could go out and have fun
In a casual way
That is, uh, fun and casual.
I know i'm some guy
You barely know,
Some total stranger who's not
In your world but i-
No, no, the "not
In my world" part is good.
So?
Show me the s.w.a.t. Thing
Again.
I just...
I just want...
Can we just be us again?
I just need something
To work.
Dede!
Le)
Is is my girlfriend amy.
What you said yesterday
About answerswg questions...
We have a lot.
Well, why don't you all
Come into my office?
Thank you.
Dr. Montgomery.
I did what i had to
To save my family.
You would do the same thing
In my situation.
I heard you kicked liquid ventilation
Ass yesterday.
Oh, i did okay.
So?
Pete, i can't.
Things around here
Are about to...
And i am seeing someone
As-as of last night, so-
I got it.
I'm sorry, pete. I...
Not wise.
Hey.
Are you ready for this?
She came over last night.
She came over last night,
And we...
I'm supposed to do this now?
What's the alternative?
You do what you have to do.
You do what you have to do
To save your family.
Okay?
Okay.
Here we go.
Hey. Uh, i need to see you
In the conference room.
I can't.
Now.
It won't take long.
Oh, thank you.
Bonus time.
Amen.
So, um... Mnemba?
I think i'm just gonna go
On my own.
You know,
Do the single girl thing.
Yeah?
Okay.
Okay, so, uh...
It's that time of the year.
Bonuses.
That's very funny, sam.
What's the deal?
Is this-
This money came, uh, from
My personal checking account.
It's $100 apiece.
Uh, it's all i had to give.
If... If you want more,
Uh, earn it.
The practice is broke.
We don't bill enough,
We don't see enough patients
And we always expect naomi
To do everything.
So... We're broke, people.
You told him?
You knew?
Addison-
Wait, hold up.
Naomi, what happened?
Wait. Don't look at naomi. You look at
Me. Sam, i don't think this is the way to-
If there are any questions as to
How the place is going to run,
From now on, you look at me.
As of this moment,
Naomi is relieved
Of her administrative duties,
And i am taking charge
Of the practice.
Sam
- okay, i actually don't think this is legal.
We've all been here a lot longer than addison...
I actually think that if you looked at the bylaws...
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë