- Morning, SARAH.
- Good morning, Sheriff.
- Coffee?
- Yeah, two.
- One black and one with milk and...
- Three teaspoons of sugar.
Yes, I know.
Good memory, SARAH.
I locked it in the system preferences
after the third night.
Yeah, but not
that you're counting, right?
I could do that all day.
Call in sick.
I can write a note to your boss.
- You are the boss.
- Yeah, temporarily.
And as tempting as that sounds,
we're testing this new
supercollider at GD today,
and if all goes well,
we actually could prove
the existence of dark energy.
That old bag.
That old bag is the key to understanding
the laws of the universe.
You should come.
It's gonna be quite a show.
Not the kind of show I care for.
Okay, we can save that show
for later.
Hands where I can see 'em.
Good morning, Zoe.
I should probably go.
- I'll see you later?
- See you later.
Have a good day.
Go ahead.
I know it's killing you.
No, she's adorable.
You can't give me grief about Lucas.
Yes, I can.
It's not the same thing.
What's with the sweats?
Dive meet at 1:00
for Pilar's biotech final.
Since when do you dive?
Since I stupidly agreed
to be her guinea pig.
Novice divers controlled
by neural-muscle remote.
- You don't have to come.
- Are you kidding? I wouldn't miss it.
My God.
What's wrong?
I got offered early admission
to an undergrad pre-med program
at Harvard.
You... that's fantas...
But that's not for, like, two years.
Everyone at Tesla applies early,
and they only accept
a few people for admission,
and they picked me.
- But, I mean, you have a B- average.
- Which is like an A+ in the real world.
And it's not all about GPA.
Someone wrote a letter on my behalf.
They did?
It starts next semester.
Can you believe it?
It's soon.
Are you okay, Sheriff? I'm picking up
a spike in your blood pressure.
I'm excited.
I'm freaked out. But I'm excited.
- Thanks, dad.
- Yeah.
- I have to go call Lucas.
- Sure.
- It's amazing, right?
- Yeah.
My God.
Yeah, it's...
huge.
It's devastating.
We were going to apply
to the same schools.
She is a special candidate,
and there was only one spot.
- I'm special.
- Yes, you are.
But it's not just about IQs,
and, besides, you know,
you can join her next year.
This just wasn't part of the plan.
Well, life rarely goes
according to plan.
I mean, take Kim's ship.
I lose it 20 years ago.
And it returns with enough data
to unlock the secrets
of the universe,
and I get to share it
with one of my best students.
I appreciate the opportunity,
Dr. Deacon,
but all the data in the world can't take
the place of the woman you love.
I'm sorry.
I meant Zoe and me and...
It's okay.
Really.
Check out the scan
of our solar system from Kim's data.
Look at the distortion on
the northern edge of the heliosphere.
Could that be what I think it is?
Nemesis.
- It's not the end of the world.
- Easy for you to say.
This is an amazing opportunity.
You should be proud of her.
I am proud.
I just got blindsided.
I thought we had
another year together.
Fresh muffins.
- Get 'em while they're hot.
- I love muffin Monday.
I can't.
Sarah said that I have
to watch my blood pressure.
The end of the world is coming.
The people have a right to know.
And with you around,
it'll end sooner than later.
And that doesn't help.
You can't do this, Fargo.
It's putting us all at risk.
- Who did what?
- It's what they're about to do.
Ignore him.
It's not us this time. It's Nemesis.
Nemesis?
Is that like a supervillain
from your fantasy justice league?
Oh, it's real.
And that is an awesome name.
Nemesis is a neutron star theorized
to be in binary orbit with our sun.
It crosses Earth's orbit
every 65 million years,
causing an extinction-level event.
Like a killer asteroid?
That's not even the half of it.
The tidal stresses
from the star's gravitational pull
could cause a sudden reversal
of Earth's magnetic poles
and unleash earthquakes, tsunamis,
total global chaos.
The world could literally be
turned upside-down.
All right, I'll check with Henry.
How much time do we have?
If we're lucky, maybe 2,000 years.
2,000.
See, that's not so much a problem,
so next time, don't bury the lead.
Exactly, kids.
Sheriff, the real problem here
is the supercollider
these guys are about to test.
It'll wipe us out long before
nemesis gets the chance.
Histrionic much.
That thing makes the hadron collider
at CERN look like a slingshot.
Mark my words, some things
should not be messed with.
Like the laws of physics.
For once, Larry makes a fair point.
So the laws of physics are in peril,
my daughter's moving out,
and the world's coming to an end?
I say, have the muffin.
I'll have the muffin.
Easy, Fargo, that's a $10 billion
piece of equipment.
You break it, you buy it.
All right, that's it.
Radio isotopes are in place.
Ready to smash some unstable atoms
together at nearly the speed of light?
You know, when he says it like that,
it doesn't sound like a good idea.
Okay, kids.
Here we go.
Isn't this exciting?
If we find dark energy,
we could prove the existence
of the Higgs boson,
discover the nature
of quark-gluon interaction,
maybe even find
a true unification theory.
I love it when you talk nerdy to me.
Particle velocity is at 0.50c.
.70.
.80.
Should we be wearing safety goggles?
Don't worry about it.
I'll protect you.
.9.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
- The field sensors are off-scale.
- Power surge in the delivery arm.
Damping rings are destabilizing.
Projet-SG (1.00)
You okay?
Everyone okay?
Why are we talking
like chip and dale?
Liquid helium cools the magnets
surrounding the collider tunnel.
- The ring hit the supply line.
- You think?
I'll shut off the line
and open the surface vents.
I knew we
should have worn safety goggles.
Safety goggles are good.
- Now what the hell happened?
- Fargo happened.
My part went flawlessly.
You screwed up
the containment field calibration.
I checked them a dozen times.
They were spot on.
They're not now.
Yeah, take a look at that.
This can't be right.
There was a high-voltage spike
in the damping ring stabilizer.
- And it just snapped?
- No way.
The stabilizer unit, it's shielded.
Something or someone did this.
But this is a critical test
in proving the laws of physics.
Who would want to stop it?
I think I might have an idea.
You can't say I didn't warn you.
That's why we're here, Larry.
You think I messed with the collider?
Are you insane?
Just following leads.
You seemed vocal
about wanting to shut it down.
Freedom of speech.
Just because I thought it was a stupid
idea doesn't mean I'd act on it.
You did hijack Martha.
One tiny lapse in judgment.
And I never hear the end of it.
Truth is, I should file
a complaint against them.
For what exactly?
Contaminating my experiment.
My fem-bot prototype
was working perfectly...
Do I really want to know this?
She was working perfectly
before I went to get my coffee,
when I came back
after the collider accident,
she was completely non-responsive.
Maybe she's just not that into you.
How could the collider affect
your mechanical girlfriend?
You think they call it dark
energy because it's friendly?
They have no idea what it can do.
The embedded controller's fried.
No wonder the balance was off.
I'm just glad you're okay.
Actually, Julia, I'm not.
My brush with death
and this Nemesis thing
has made me realize
that life is short and fate is cruel.
Especially around here.
There are so many things
I want to do before I die,
and I know we haven't been
together for very long,
but I'd like to do them with you.
What did you have in mind?
I made a list.
Feel free to add to it.
Skydiving over lake Archimedes.
Bungee jump off the Da Vinci bridge.
- Go on a high-speed chase?
- I figured Jo could help us out.
I mean, she'd probably enjoy it.
Fargo, what is that?
No, it's an incredible opportunity.
I just...
I just need a little more time.
Bye.
Let me guess. Time share in Boca.
Actually, a job opportunity.
After Allison gets back from maternity
leave, I am officially unemployed.
What is it?
A private funder is building
a new ultra-large radio telescope array,
- and they need someone to run it.
- Congratulations.
And where is it?
Australia.
That's far.
And you're considering it?
They made me the job offer
a week ago.
So before you and I...
You okay?
You could have mentioned it before.
At the time, it didn't have
anything to do with you.
So...
Right.
The collider accident may have been
more serious than we thought.
Larry says that dark energy
might be the cause.
Okay, well, first of all,
the accident was contained.
And second, can we get back to us?
You know, I really have
to deal with this collider thing.
Well, don't worry about it.
I got everything under control.
Not a word.
Come on.
- Hey, Julia, what's going on?
- I don't know. Please hurry.
Hey, Martha, what's up?
I am.
Of course you are.
- It's gotta be a gravity anomaly.
- Well, or a Fargo anomaly.
What button did you push this time?
Can you not recognize a victim
when you see one?
You know, he's right. There's nothing
in this lab that could cause that.
Maybe he brought it in with him
from the lab that exploded.
The collider has nothing
to do with gravity.
The dark energy?
You don't know what that does.
You can't track it around
on your shoes.
Guys? Can we maybe focus on
getting me down before gravity returns?
It's okay, honey, I got you.
You know what, Fargo, why don't you try
pushing yourself away from the ceiling?
No luck.
- Missed it by that much.
- Oh, my God, Fargo, are you okay?
Remind me to cross base jumping
off the bucket list.
Yeah, let's get you
to the infirmary.
Who knows what
you've been exposed to?
I have an idea,
but I wanna talk to Zane.
It's not the collider. I've told you
everything there is to know.
I just need to talk to Zane.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for the next event
in the Tesla biotech dive finals,
the 10-meter board.
Our first contestant,
Samantha Welke,
will be attempting
a 2 1/2 forward pike
with a 2.1 degree of difficulty.
Samantha's dive will be controlled
by Kelsey Hess.
Damn, she's good.
But I'm better.
I'm not gonna get electrocuted
or anything, am I?
Relax. It's a subcutaneous,
nuclear, neuro-stimulus system,
totally waterproof.
So much more advanced
than skin contact.
Wait, subcutaneous?
What the hell?
The biometric sensors
need to be injected
into all of your primary joints.
Damn it.
The sensors will read the signal
from my remote to control your body.
All you have to do is relax
and score a perfect ten.
Well, you didn't tell me
about the pain.
I can't believe this could be
our last dive final.
Pilar, it's our first dive final.
So, not so sentimental.
Okay, but everything we do now
could be our last everything.
At least you care about that.
Lucas couldn't be bothered.
Oh, God,
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Ready to warm up?
Oh, God, this is really disturbing.
Jack, don't walk away
from me like that.
I'm just trying to do my job,
so I can get to Zoe's dive thing.
You know, and my watch is broken.
Yeah, I know. I heard about Harvard.
- Are you okay?
- Well, it's every dad's dream, right?
Can we talk?
What do you wanna say?
- I mean, you knew you were going away.
- I haven't decided if I'm gonna leave.
- You didn't mention the job offer.
- I haven't accepted it yet.
I'm having a rough day,
so what do you want?
What do you need?
What do you want?
Whatever makes you happy.
Tell me you figured out
this dark energy problem.
Well, theoretically, the power surge
could have produced
a negatively-charged strangelet,
or possibly a monopole,
or maybe even
an itty, bitty black hole.
Itty, bitty black hole?
Yeah, but none of those things
happened.
Including a dark energy leak.
Well, you seem pretty certain.
How do you know?
Because the stabilizer froze.
It broke down
before it even started.
It crashed before it smashed.
You satisfied I told you
everything I know?
- How's Fargo?
- Melodramatic and anemic.
- I'm glad to hear it.
- No, actually, he's quite anemic.
He's been taking iron supplements
all of his life.
Wait,
iron.
I mean, that fits, right? Everything
that was metal got stuck to the ceiling.
Wait, so Fargo was a human magnet?
Something produced a wellspring
of electromagnetic energy,
and I suppose
Fargo got caught up in it.
What time did the collider
break down?
That would be 10:06.
That's the same time
that my watch stopped.
What if whatever messed it up
also messed up the stabilizer?
An intense electromagnetic energy field
could have frozen your watch gears.
And the stabilizer gears
on the magnetic damping rings.
Call me if you find out anything.
I'm late for Zoe.
Tough break.
I'm having second thoughts.
You already got into Harvard.
The rest of us have to prove ourselves.
So mush.
Okay, okay, I'm going.
Oh, God,
please don't make me belly flop.
Next up, the team of Zoe Carter
and Pilar Reed.
Zoe will be attempting
a back 3 1/2 somersault
with a 2.9 degree of difficulty.
Wait, she can't do that, can she?
She doesn't have to.
I'm controlling her every move.
Nuclear neuro-stimulus technology.
Nuclear?
Hold on, hold on, stop, stop.
You're okay.
I think I know what caused it.
This is a satellite image
from the time of the anomaly.
Now you see that red patch
over the Tesla pool?
That is a hot spot
of electromagnetism.
Intense, electromagnetic fields
can cause
hydrogen and oxygen atoms to split.
And would that make the pool
look like it was boiling?
You have two highly combustible
gases ignited by the transmitters
under Zoe's skin and, bam.
And this is
the same electromagnetic field
that pinned Fargo to the ceiling?
Probably. There's a whole band
of it fluctuating over Eureka.
I saw a computer simulation...
Fargo's computer simulation
of what happens
when Nemesis passes the Earth.
But that's 2,000 years from now.
What if somehow
Nemesis is already here?
I am sorry I missed your meet.
I heard
your performance was explosive.
Funny.
I think my dad was really panicked
for a second there.
I don't think
that's gonna change anytime soon.
You know, it's hard to protect
your kid from across the country.
Yeah, I guess.
And, like me,
he's gonna miss you...
A lot more than he lets on.
He tried to be cool about it,
but I could completely tell.
You should talk to him.
Yeah, you're right.
I was just so excited to tell Lucas,
but he couldn't be bothered to care.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
I heard what happened.
I feel like a jerk that I wasn't there.
But I had good reason.
Can we talk?
Please?
Are you sure you don't need
to throw up again?
I think I got it all
out of my system on the way down.
At least you get to cross
skydiving off the list.
You know, I'm thinking maybe
we can scratch off
anything to do
with plummeting to my doom.
You know, Fargo, there are things
that we can put on the list
that don't involve mortal danger.
Such as?
I thought this didn't involve
mortal danger.
Everybody down.
There's no way a neutron star could
be anywhere near our solar system.
Not the real Nemesis.
A man-made copy.
The similarities are remarkable.
This growing electromagnetic field
has all the properties of a massive
magnetic polar disturbance.
How massive are we talking here?
I'm in the middle of something here.
So am I. All the metal at Café Diem
just took off flying.
- It hit Café Diem.
- Tell her it's dissipating.
It's dissipating.
Hang on, Jo.
I'm not the one hanging.
Cross knife-throwing
off the list too.
Never mind.
We're good.
Keep me posted.
- Café Diem. Where's it heading next?
- No way to tell.
The magnetic field shows fluctuating
energy that comes and goes.
It's the same effect we see over time
when the Earth's magnetic poles reverse.
But magnitude stronger and faster.
Right now it's localized in Eureka.
But if the energy keeps building,
it won't be for long.
If it's only happening here,
then someone here must have caused it.
So what I need to know
is who could have created
a mini death star.
Well, they would have to have
detailed knowledge of Nemesis
in order to replicate the effect.
Please.
Give me a little credit.
Credit.
Maybe that's what they wanted.
Credit for what? For starting
an extinction-level event?
Or stopping one. Saving the world
looks pretty good on a resume.
But it's 2,000 years away.
They would have
to have access to Henry's data.
What kind of novice would
attempt something so dangerous?
A novice who doesn't want
his girlfriend to leave him behind.
I can't believe
I almost lost you today.
But you didn't.
And you won't.
I don't know.
Harvard's a long way from here.
I want to be with you always.
Me too.
That's why I've been working so hard
to keep us together.
I mean, I want to be with you.
No distance can take that away.
- Dad.
- Sheriff.
And now my perfect day is complete.
Please don't blame him.
It was my idea.
Tell me you're talking
about electromagnetic energy.
Oh, I think she is.
Is this a micro-electromagnetic
pulse simulator?
Pulse amplifier.
At least it's supposed to be.
I haven't gotten it to work yet.
- Well, don't be so sure.
- What?
Come see for yourself.
Henry, the machine isn't even on.
It's on stand-by.
It worked.
I mean, it worked.
What is that?
That is a new magnetic pole.
You mean, like the North Pole?
It's about to be.
This is very, very bad.
How in bejesus' name
did you create a new North Pole?
Ignore the crazy man, Lucas,
and just talk us through it.
I used the data from Kim to build
the simulation of the forces
that Nemesis would create
when it passed Earth.
To measure the relative change
in gravitational pull.
Right. Then I designed
the electromagnetic amplifier
to lock our planet's poles in place
so they wouldn't reverse.
But my test failed.
Well, not so much.
There have been magnetic problems
all over town,
including what happened
to Zoe at the pool.
But my amplifier isn't even on now.
And it's only a scale model.
It doesn't have enough juice
to cause something like that.
Unless there was a boost
from somewhere else.
The explosion from the collider.
I think your amplifier threw off
the magnetic stabilizers.
And that surge in electromagnetism
fed back into the strength
of the amplifier,
creating a loop
of building energy, and, voila,
a new North Pole.
I swear, I had no idea.
You are gonna have to tell Santa
that he needs to move his workshop.
Lucas, what were you thinking?
That you were leaving.
And I couldn't handle it.
I thought maybe if I came up
with a solution to Nemesis,
then Henry would write me
a recommendation letter
like he did for you,
and then we could go together.
I'm sorry. You know what,
I meant to talk to you about it,
and I just forgot.
I'm sorry.
All right.
How do we shut it down?
I don't know.
I mean, we're witnessing
a electromagnetic runaway.
Lucas lit the match
flamed by the collider
and now fueled
by the Earth's own magnetic field.
If we can't break the cycle,
the planet will experience
the same thing Lucas
was trying to prevent.
A spontaneous polar reversal.
Guess this would be a bad time
to ask for that recommendation.
That's a new one.
What's up, Jo?
Small issue.
The new magnetic pole
is gaining strength.
That looks bad.
That is the buildup
to a spontaneous polar reversal.
Fluctuations in the magnetic field are
causing random surges all over town.
Point taken.
Well, but the surges
aren't that random.
Look at the energy output.
They all have a negative charge.
If we could create
a controlled burst
of positive electromagnetic energy,
we might be able to cancel that out.
How do we do that?
Well, we'll load a tactical missile
with a positron payload
and launch it directly
into the center of the pole.
It's a piece of cake.
Just had to say it, didn't you?
The town's grid is down.
That presents a small problem.
And by small
you mean insurmountably large, yeah?
Anything outside of GD
that runs on electricity or batteries
is affected by the pole.
Cars, computers, tactical missiles.
All our normal delivery
vehicles are useless.
How about
an abnormal delivery vehicle?
What the...
And now I know the world's ending.
You ever hear of knocking?
No!
Obviously.
What are you doing?
Living life to the fullest, Sheriff.
- Now did you need me or...
- You, no.
Martha.
When everything was on the ceiling,
she was unaffected, so...
It's because she's made
of nonmetallic composites
and rad-hardened electronics.
Close enough for me.
Martha, Fargo, come.
With me.
Okay, just one second.
How much longer?
We're loading
the positron beam emitter now.
Give us five minutes.
Let's hope she doesn't miss.
Dad, wait.
I told you to stay in the rotunda
until we fix this mess.
If you send in martha,
she'll fry my amplifier.
Your amplifier caused this problem,
so I'm thinking that's a bonus.
You don't understand.
The amplifier's off.
But when martha hits the pole
with positrons,
the EM pulse over my garage
could turn it on.
So if it surges now,
it'll only make the pole stronger.
Like throwing napalm on a campfire.
We're screwed?
Not if we reverse the polarity
of my amplifier.
It would then emit a positive charge
and increase
the punch of martha's positron beam.
Exactly.
Okay, tell me what I have to do.
The pole is centered above the garage,
so you'll never reach it.
It's the eye of the magnetic storm.
And the effect
is 100 times stronger now.
Then I'll take off my jewelry first.
A field this strong
can affect brain function,
causing a synaptic misfire.
A complete loss of motor control.
Then maybe you can give me a hand.
I'm done.
Okay, you're all set.
Dad.
I don't want you to go.
The feeling's mutual.
Me going off to college
and you risking your life
are hardly the same thing.
It's my job.
And if I don't risk my life,
then you won't have a college
to go to.
None of this would be
happening if I wasn't leaving.
God, if something happens to you...
Zo, I'm gonna be fine.
The first thing you've got
to do is find Lucas's amplifier.
This should be fun.
That's it, right there.
I feel like Frogger.
Stop stalling already and move.
Don't boss me, blondie.
What is that for?
For saying blondie
like it's a bad thing.
All right, I'm here if you need me.
Jack, the pole is gaining strength.
You have to move fast.
You think?
For your sake, Lucas,
this better work.
Jack, are you okay?
Perfect.
Can't move my legs.
Or arms.
The field affects his nervous system.
He's losing muscle control.
Hang on.
I'm gonna help you up.
I don't like this at all!
Jump!
Hang on.
Sorry, sorry, I'm just getting
some electromagnetic interference.
We lost the signal again.
How will we know when to launch?
I'd say that's a good sign.
- Oh, non.
- What?
They've launched the drone.
You've got to reverse the polarity.
And get out. Martha's on her way.
It's right in front of you.
Got it!
There's a dial
on the left side of the housing.
Turn it clockwise until it stops
to reverse the polarity.
Come on, Tess.
A little closer.
I can feel my legs.
It's working.
The amplifier's weakening the field.
Martha's almost there.
Run.
Are you there?
Dad, please say something.
I need a vacation.
You did it, Jack.
I had a little help.
I need a vacation.
Bet you never thought you'd be happy
to see them doing that, huh?
I'm not sure if happy
is quite the right word.
We dodged a major bullet today.
Yes, and he helped.
We also wouldn't have needed help
if it wasn't for him.
That's true.
But what he created will be
essential to saving the planet
when the real nemesis comes.
You can come up for air anytime.
That was quite a day.
It's never dull.
That's what makes this so hard.
And I'm sorry
for making it even harder.
The reason I didn't tell you
about the job offer
was because I didn't know
what this was between us.
It's the perfect job for you.
I know that.
And I've always wanted
to visit Australia, so...
Then come with me.
- I can't come with you.
- Why not?
Zoe's leaving.
Jo can handle things here.
We could have something.
Would you think about it?
In the meantime,
if you hate it,
you can come back.
I can come back even if I don't.
Yeah, you can.
Sure this is all gonna fit?
I'm making Lucas pack
all the spillover in his car.
So, MIT did end up taking him.
Yeah, with Henry's recommendation.
You know, it turns out
the guy has a lot of pull.
I just think he knows talent
when he sees it.
I still can't believe
our little girl is leaving home.
Sarah, don't worry.
The holidays will be here
before you know it.
You don't want me to come with you?
It's sort of a dad's rite of passage.
I could help.
I know, but...
I think this is something
I have to do on my own.
And God knows what havoc they'd wreak
while you were gone.
You know,
I'm actually really gonna miss it.
Part of me just kina wants
to call the whole thing off.
You're gonna do great.
You really think so?
I know so.
Thank you.
For what?
For...
never giving up on me.
That was an option?
Hilarious!
I am gonna miss you like crazy.
But I'm so proud.
Well, you know, if I hate it,
I can come back.
You can come back even if you don't.
May I walk you out?
How you holding up?
I'm okay.
Really?
I think sometimes change is good.
I was about to grab a vinspresso.
You want to come?
Yeah, go ahead. I'll catch up.
And there was a package
that came for you.
I put it on your desk.
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SEE AUSTRALIA...
LOVE, TESS.
I was just about to call you.