- It looks like a snow globe.
- It's a storycatcher.
You hold it in your hand,
you look into the lens,
and you describe a memorable event
about living in Eureka.
- Have we had any of those?
- No, nothing comes to me.
So it's basically
a glorified video recorder?
More like a brain recorder.
It creates a wireless neural connection
through the optic nerve
to see memories as you recall them.
Can it help you find something lost,
like a wallet?
You're cute. No, it's for the Eureka
time capsule project.
All the stories will be collected
and preserved in a living video diary.
So no pressure?
Okay, so what am I supposed to say?
Maybe something about
your first time in Eureka.
Your arrival
was definitely memorable.
Thanks, Vince.
That's a nice way to put that.
Well, I've kind of blocked
all that out of my head, so...
Here, let me refresh your memory.
Here we go.
When you first got here,
we didn't exactly click.
- Pretty impressive, Jo.
- It's deputy Lupo.
- Where'd you learn to do that, anyway?
- US Army, special forces.
That explains some things.
What things?
Nothing, none of my business.
You got something to say, say it.
It's just the whole tough-girl image.
I mean, it's fine and everything,
but some guys might find it
intimidating.
Unless you're into chicks.
That's fine too.
Stop talking.
Like a little blonde
ray of sunshine.
Well, you know, on the plus side,
if this whole waitressing thing
doesn't work out,
I can always fall back
on my life of crime.
That's a good plan.
So now that's recorded on this?
As you talk, it translates
your synaptic impulses into images
that can be downloaded
onto my computer in my lab.
So they're, like,
happy little memory balls.
Yeah, just like that.
And this is fun,
but I got birthing class with Allison.
Oh, yeah, she's in
for the home stretch, huh?
Yeah, I'm on call 24 hours a day.
Can I get another story thing?
I think mine overloaded.
You think? You've been the center
of every disaster this town's ever had.
Not all of them.
Death ray, homicidal smart house...
- Force field bubble.
- Keep a tally. We can start a pool.
- That's not funny.
- Come on.
- I got to go.
- Wait, wait. Don't forget yours.
Think of something good, will you?
I'll try.
Anyone else talk about me?
That's classified.
- I thought you were closing up.
- Do I have to do everything?
- How's it going?
- Hey, I just tried to page you.
Why... You didn't get my message?
I must've left it at the cafe.
That pager has an encrypted signal
that could reach you in a cave in China
if I go into labor,
but only if you don't lose it.
I'll pick it up
after the birthing class. How's that?
See? That was the message.
Class has been canceled.
They do a sonic cleaning
of Global Dynamics once a year.
The entire facility is shut down
for the long weekend.
But it's graduation day.
I've been practicing my breathing.
Well, you'll get to use it soon enough.
Hey, and it's my breathing.
Right.
Oh, boy...
You know, this place is gonna
seem empty without you.
Well, I'll only be on maternity leave
for six weeks.
I'm sure that
you won't even miss me.
What is a sonic cleaning, anyway?
Only the most sophisticated
sterilization process ever created.
- Carter, this is Dr. Kinison.
- Hi. How are you?
Why are you yelling?
Dr. Kinison pioneered
an acoustic cleaning process
that will sterilize this facility
in 48 hours.
I like that way that... sounds.
Final checks, Dr. Blake.
We've got three stragglers.
Ashe, Bubay, and Fargo.
I'm sure they're still locking up.
We have to make sure
that any biological experiments
have been removed or contained
and any volatile GD projects
have been secured.
You know what? You can help me.
Excellent. You can practice
your breathing on the way.
Attention, sonic cleaning
to commence in 90 minutes.
Please evacuate the building.
Let's check the mainframe
and see how other people remember me.
Show me Douglas Fargo.
Memory output, halo engaged.
Begin transmission.
This is Eureka!
- Fargo, what are you doing with that?
- Nothing.
Never seen it before.
I found it in my pocket.
- But you did turn it on.
- Yeah.
- Why?
- It's what I do.
Go.
Primary firing sequence initiated.
Weapon will deploy in 24 hours.
It's the mummy queen!
They're not backing away
from the vehicle.
Happy place, happy place.
You're a great bodyguard, Fargo!
Welcome, I'm a self-actuated
residential automated habitat...
SARAH, for short.
Is that you talking like a girl?
What are you doing?
Dr. Kinison...
I was just grabbing this
for Dr. Fontana.
You better clear out.
Sonic sterilization will turn you
from a solid to a liquid
in no time flat.
Point taken.
Files updated.
Dr. Bubay.
Why are you still here?
The cleaning's about to start.
Right. I have this nagging feeling
there's something
I was supposed to do.
Like securing your experiment?
That sounds familiar. Now...
What experiment
would that be exactly?
I guess that experiment.
Projet-SG (1.00)
Unbelievable. What happened?
If I had to take a guess,
I'd say that
someone's chemical mixture
became unstable and ignited.
You're supposed to monitor these things
so that this doesn't happen.
In my lab, sure.
This is your lab.
You and Dr. Ashe are GD's
finest seismic chemists.
I know the name,
but I can't place his face.
- Her. Her face.
- She's your partner.
You created
an aliphatic polyurea prepolymer
that could revolutionize
earthquake safety.
An ali... alip... what?
- Unbreakable glue for brick mortar.
- What a great idea.
Say, can I get in on that project?
Okay, we have an off-site infirmary.
I'll have him checked out.
All right, I'll find Ashe.
Maybe she knows what's going on.
Come on.
God, trying to think
of something worthwhile to say
just highlights how little
I've really done.
You're overthinking it, Zo.
Really? That's easy for you to say,
Dr. Three PhDs.
- I mean, I'm not even a scientist.
- Well, Vincent's not a scientist,
and I'm sure he's got a unique
perspective on this town, right?
Actually, I have a PhD
in molecular gastronomy.
See? Okay, you know what?
You just go first.
All right, Vincent, what you got?
All right.
You think Iron Chef is exciting?
They got nothing on cafe Diem.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
Everybody down!
Invisible drone on the loose!
You may want to lay off
the vinspresso, Sheriff.
Oh, boy, I think I got everything.
What took you so long?
I was lost. I'd still be in there
if your Cylon-shuttle thing
- hadn't shown me the way out.
- What Cylon-shuttle thing?
It was just behind me.
You guys go in the corner.
Go. You guys, down.
Really?
Jo, stand down.
You remember me?
Piggybacks?
Good times.
- Very surprising...
- Martha's here.
How did she...?
Look out!
That's the story
you're gonna tell for all posterity?
What?
Beats the hell
out of a book of recipes.
Oh, Lord.
Dr. Ashe.
Oh, great.
I seem to have lost my lab.
You've...
Do you still know
what a prepolymer glue is?
Of course.
In fact, just now I had an idea about
a new kind of aliphatic-based epoxy.
Yes, yes, I was just talking
to your partner about that.
But I don't have a partner.
Dr. Bubay? He's got red hair,
sort of looks like Opie.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Look, my name is
Sheriff Jack Carter, right?
I need you to come...
- Is this yours?
- Thanks.
I was wondering where that was.
Why don't you come with me?
We're gonna check you out, okay?
So I spoke to Henry.
They're suffering from lacunar
amnesia... Selective memory loss.
So they can remember their work
but not each other?
Well, so far, but if the pathways
in their striate cortex get infected,
this could turn
into retrograde amnesia.
So what could cause it?
It seems odd that they'd suffer from
the same thing at exactly the same time.
I don't know. Trauma, injury, maybe
exposure to chemicals in their lab.
All clear, Dr. Blake.
I found Fargo in lab 511
and hustled him out.
That's Tess' lab.
What's he doing down there?
Is that where she keeps
the time capsule thingy?
Yeah. Why?
Can you hold the cleaning
till we get back?
- No problem.
- Oh, thanks.
There you go.
Well, I don't understand.
I found one of Tess' memory balls
inside Dr. Ashe's pocket,
and Henry said
that Dr. Bubay has one too.
Everyone has one.
Is it possible that
the recording of these memories
- somehow makes people forget them?
- It doesn't work that way.
The neural link copies memories
to the storynest.
It doesn't erase them.
It's through that that you guys
can watch the recordings?
Well, you just input a memory
and put the halo interface on.
Awesome.
Sterilization protocols initiated.
- You told me to put it on.
- No, no, no, not you.
Kinison must've started the sonic
cleaning. I'll hit the fail-safe.
Tell me the fail-safe
didn't just fail.
Well, it should've been activated
as standard safety protocol.
Warning, sonic sterilization
to commence in 60 minutes.
What does sonic sterilization do?
Well, it fires a blast
of coherent phonons
that vibrate any organic matter
at a subatomic level.
Sounds uncomfortable.
It will completely dismantle any germs,
allergens, or biological impurities,
including us.
No one's answering.
Everyone's left the building.
Let's try to call someone outside
the building. You want to try Henry?
Section Five blocks
standard cell signals...
Security issues.
Warning, sonic sterilization
to commence in 50 minutes.
There's a way to contact someone.
The GD communication network
shuts down
to minimize electrical
interference during the cleaning,
but the fail-safe should've sent
an emergency alert to Kinison.
Let's hope he can hear it.
You're beeping.
Right. Sorry.
- Could I get a refill, please?
- Sure.
- I wonder what that means.
- Here you go.
Jo, your soup's coming right up.
I ordered soup?
White bean with truffles?
Sounds good.
You okay?
Aside from being painfully average,
yeah, I'm super.
What?
She's having a little trouble thinking
of a story for the time capsule.
Because I haven't done
anything that exceptional.
As entertaining as they may be,
no one wants to hear about my mistakes.
Well, you know that mistakes
make exceptional possible.
Well... well, here, look.
For example, when you
and your dad came into town,
I was tinkering in my garage.
Here goes nothing.
That failure changed our approach
to creating artificial gravity
for space travel.
So here in Eureka,
mistakes can lead to new directions.
Sometimes the wrong path
leads to the right path.
So just give it time,
and you will find your own path.
Thanks.
When did I order soup?
I just don't understand how Kinison
could forget that we're down here.
Well, everyone was given
a storycatcher, right?
My God, including him,
which means the amnesia is spreading.
- We have to get out of here.
- We're gonna break our way out.
Through a titanium door that can take
20 tons per square inch of pressure.
Why is everything
such overkill with you people?
Well, it's supposed to keep us safe!
Oh, my God, I'm sorry. I just...
I just don't know how this happened.
It's okay.
I mean, we're gonna figure it out.
But first...
I'd like to figure out
what Fargo was doing down here.
How do I use this?
I just put it on?
Yeah, just close your eyes
and say a name.
Show me Douglas Fargo.
There's only one memory,
and it's a shared dream
with Fargo as a hero.
What were you expecting?
Lots.
He never met a button
he didn't push.
He is pathological.
And I mean, Fargo was irritated
this morning
when he found out that people's
memories were gonna make him look...
Like Fargo.
What would make him think that?
Well, me.
Great. Good job.
You're right. Dozens of files
have been deleted from the mainframe.
If he erased memories from the storynest
while the connection was still active,
it could start wiping
people's minds.
Okay, do we need him to fix it?
You know, actually, if the neural
connection is still active,
I might be able to use the storynest
to make contact
with people outside of GD.
Great. And you know how to do that?
Yeah, I have to access the mainframe,
then I should be able to...
What?
I'm sorry, what was I saying?
Warning, sonic sterilization
to commence in 30 minutes.
- My God, we have to get outta here.
- That's what we're trying to do.
You don't understand. The sonic cleaning
will dismantle any organic matter.
On a subatomic level.
Yeah, that's right.
Who told you that?
You.
Right before you started
losing your memory.
All right, one more time.
We're about to be vibrated to death,
and not in the good way.
This is crazy, Carter.
I am not losing my memory.
That's the fourth time you've told me.
You check your right pocket again?
What...
Where'd this come from?
That's from Tess' project.
You recorded your memory, and now
you're starting to forget your life.
This is crazy, Carter.
I am not losing my memory.
Warning, sonic sterilization
will commence in 25 minutes.
Sonic sterilization?
We have to get outta here!
Allison, you got to focus.
You were attempting to access
the neural net to make a call for help.
- Okay, that's really difficult.
- If anyone can do it, it's you.
- You are the head of Global Dynamics.
- I am? When did that happen?
Oh, my God, when did that happen?
There you go.
If you can't remember your life...
- Then let me show it to you.
- I can remember my life just fine.
Allison, trust me.
You do have kind eyes.
I want you to put this on.
Close your eyes,
And say, "Show me Jack Carter
and Allison Blake".
Show me Jack Carter
and Allison Blake.
We just never hang out.
I don't know what's going on with you.
What's going on with Allison?
No, Allison, don't!
- What are you doing?
- No, I'm just trying...
- I think that I can. Let me just...
- Stop it. Stop the...
A kiss for luck?
- Thought you were into young brunettes.
- No, no, I'm into old brun...
- Didn't come out right, did it?
- No, no.
Actually, you know what?
I could use you.
I don't know. I'm not a piece of meat.
I mean, I got feelings, emotions.
Time's a-wastin'. Drop them.
There'll be no pant-dropping
without a nice dinner
and many, many cocktails.
Allison, can you hear me?
I can do more than hear you.
Sorry.
Can you put that away?
- I'll let you buy me a cup of coffee.
- It's free.
Well, in that case, I'll buy.
I think this is definitely
becoming our thing.
We don't have a thing.
We might.
Well, I remember your face.
I just can't place your name.
We work together, right?
Well...
We more than just work together.
You're my friend,
and you're our birthing coach.
And...
You even gave me a pager so that you can
reach me 24 hours, around the clock.
What?
You gave me a pager.
It has a super signal so that
it can reach me in a cave in China.
- Do you remember that?
- Yeah, I remember that you forgot it.
Right, at Cafe Diem. Now...
Is that on the same network as GD?
No, I think it has
its own frequency.
Great, give me yours.
What for?
We have a shot
at getting outta here.
Vin, I'm still waiting
on that cordon bleu.
My goodness, that sounds delicious.
I'll take one.
What?
Dr. Kinison, please,
that PDA is driving me crazy!
What are you talking about?
That.
That's not me.
For the love of God...
"911, trapped in S5-L511. Help"?
What are you talking about?
It's my dad's pager. He got this
from Allison. She says she's trapped.
What's S5-L511?
That's Section Five, Lab 511.
That's my lab.
But they just shut GD down
for a sonic cleaning today.
Tess, my dad didn't come back
after that birthing class.
Have you guys seen
Allison or Carter?
- Who's Carter?
- Allison?
Are you serious?
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Henry, we have to get to GD.
Something is really wrong.
Sorry, what's GD?
Kinison, you need to use your PDA
to shut down the sonic cleaning at GD.
There are people in there.
Sonic cleaning?
Okay, never mind.
- I'm gonna borrow this. Is that okay?
- Sure. It's not mine.
Zoe, come on. Let's go.
- What was all that about?
- I have no idea.
So you come here often?
Warning, sonic sterilization
to commence in 20 minutes.
Well, hopefully,
somebody will find my pager.
Well, watching the memory helped.
It did?
We can focus on the ones
that had the most impact,
and those memories
could bring back others.
Well, the strongest memories
are tied to emotions.
Well, we've definitely been witness
to a lot of those.
All right, well, you better show me.
Allison Blake and Nathan Stark.
- I swear I was just about to call you.
- You're moving back to Eureka?
Moved, actually, yesterday.
Same office, same house.
Surprise.
- Thank you.
- Now you're official.
- I've made up my mind.
- So have I.
Hey, guys.
Kind of busy.
- I need to talk to Allison.
- About what?
Global needs you.
I need you.
Really?
Carter's right, the two of you
do work well together.
You just know
how to ruin the moment.
And I won't be happy
until we're together.
Marry me, Allie...
Again.
You ready?
Momentous, huh?
I'll always be here for you.
You know that, right?
No matter what.
Are you okay? You look...
pale.
Where's Nathan?
I remember.
I thought
I was gonna lose you there.
You'll never lose me.
Warning,
sonic sterilization to commence
in 15 minutes.
Allison, if that page
didn't reach anyone,
you're the only one
who can get us out of here.
So...
Okay, I'll try.
You're crushing the bones
in my hand.
That was a contraction.
I just started my labor.
Oh, boy.
If we don't get out,
there's gonna be three of us.
You were saying you thought you could
call for help using the neural net?
Yeah, if I could remember
how it works.
Breathe, just like in class.
I know, Carter.
Classes were for you, not for me.
Sonic sterilization
to commence in 12 minutes.
- This is really bad.
- Well, we've been through worse, so...
That is an unfortunate
choice of words.
We've been through a lot,
and I need you to remember everything
if we stand a chance of getting out.
Okay, show me more.
Say, "Show me Eureka".
Show me Eureka.
Here's to scientific leaps
and the beginning of the universe.
Three, two, one...
Nevermind!
Vince, freezer!
Hang on!
- We're at 1,000 degrees.
- You have to do it now.
I'm trying!
How hard is it to push a button?
You wanna do it?
You're right, we've had
some rough times, but this is worse.
But I'm getting my memories back.
Warning, sonic sterilization
to commence in ten minutes.
And that's not helping!
You can do this. You can do this.
What do you need?
Just give me the keypad. I'll try.
Wait, get this thing off of me.
- Wait, you know what to do?
- Check your lab for Allison and dad.
- While I shut off the sonic cleaning.
- Wait, hold on. I don't have clearance.
You had to override security
just to get me through the front door.
Okay, come here.
Press your thumb down right there.
You now have complete access
to section five.
- Really? Awesome.
- Just don't touch anything.
I'll be in Allison's office.
I've tried to override the system,
but this isn't working.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We will...
find another way.
This isn't how
I pictured things going.
I know.
It's...
bad timing.
I'm really happy that you're here.
I'll always be here for you.
No matter what.
You know, this isn't how I pictured
it going for us either.
Bad timing.
- Dad.
- Zoe, how'd you get in here?
Tess violated
about a dozen security protocols.
Awesome. Where is she?
- She's shutting down the cleaning.
- Thank God.
Sonic sterilization
to commence in five minutes.
- You said she was shutting that down.
- She was.
- Where were you when you two split?
- In the rotunda, five minutes ago.
It takes five seconds
to get to my office.
Something's wrong.
You better go find her.
And I'm in no shape to move.
You have to stop the sonic cleaning.
I'll stay with her, go.
Time the contractions.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Come here.
Are you okay?
Thank God.
How's it going?
Hi, I'm Tess.
And you would be...?
Totally screwed.
My name is Jack.
And Fargo...
You know Fargo. And...
He messed with something of yours
called a storynest.
Now, what it's doing is making
the entire town lose their memories.
You have two minutes to shut off
a sonic sterilization.
Sonic ster...
Your name is Tess Fontana.
You run section five,
and right now you are the only one
who can save the lives
of everyone in this facility.
Okay, you're really starting
to freak me out.
Do you even remember
arriving in Eureka?
Do you remember being caught
in another dimension?
Another...
- Globidium.
- What?
Do you remember the meteor shower?
Go on.
It was you and me.
We were on the hood of my jeep.
I held your hand.
- It was dark.
- Okay, wait.
Wait, this is starting
to come back to me now.
Keep going. Give me more.
Give me...
Anything?
- Sonic sterilization...
- We have to shut off the sterilization.
29...
28...
27...
26...
25...
Hold on, it'll come to me.
It could be a code
or a sequence or a protocol.
- You tend to love protocols.
- I love protocols.
18...
17...
- What? What is it?
- Kinison's PDA.
13...
I think if I swipe it, maybe...
10...
9...
Sonic procedures canceled.
Sterilization protocols deactivated.
- That's it?
- I'm sorry. I just forgot.
This isn't over.
Unless we permanently reverse
what Fargo has done,
everyone is gonna lose their memory.
- Fargo, he's at the cafe.
- Get him here as quick as you can.
- Where are you going?
- I got to deliver a baby.
A baby?
- So how far apart are they?
- 90 seconds. You're in transition.
How in God's name do you know that?
Tesla's sex-ed classes
can be pretty thorough.
I'm gonna have to start pushing soon.
Don't forget to breathe.
Yeah, you too. Here we go.
- You sure you're up for this?
- I'm your partner.
I got him.
- You could warn a guy.
- How'd you get his memory back?
Remote Halo.
Jo's storycatcher had some doozies.
And now I remember all my failures.
Thanks for that.
Just fix it so I don't forget
the birth of my daughter.
Now's your chance
for redemption, Fargo.
But I'm not exactly sure what I did.
She started doing something with
the neural net, the neural connection.
Right. Maybe we can reverse
the neural flow.
That is making it very difficult
to concentrate.
I'm sorry for distracting you.
Okay, she's coming.
Ready?
Push.
Oh, my God. I see her.
What are you doing?
Trying to generate
a large-scale upload.
If it works, all the recorded memories
should be transmitted back to everyone
in one giant burst
through their storycatchers.
Fargo, that is brilliant.
Or it'll permanently erase them.
- I don't want us to forget this.
- We won't, we won't.
- All right, this is it.
- You can do it, Allie.
You can do it, Fargo.
But what if I push this button
and permanently erase
the greatest scientific minds
of the 21st century?
Push the button, Fargo!
- It's a lot of pressure!
- Push the button!
But Eureka might forget itself.
Push the damn button, Fargo!
One more time.
She's almost here, okay?
Big push.
What are you...
All right, easy, easy.
Crap.
Get everybody out of there now!
- These are the moments we'll remember.
- Not if we're lucky.
- When did you get here?
- I'm not sure.
But you know what?
That soup smells good.
I'll get you some.
Has anyone seen my PDA?
- I think you did it, Fargo.
- I did, didn't I?
Take that, posterity.
Oh, God.
Say hello...
to your daughter.
Hey, there.
That was amazing.
You were amazing, both of you.
I don't even remember.
Hey, that's not funny.
She is beautiful.
What's her name?
This is Jenna,
Jenna Stark,
after Nathan's mom.
Well, hi, Jenna.
I guess I'm officially
on maternity leave.
You've earned it.
So what do you think, Tess?
You think you can handle this place?
Me?
Well, you're already doing
a great job in section five,
and clearly you can handle a crisis.
Yeah, I'll try to keep those
to a minimum while you're gone.
Well, I'd appreciate it.
You okay?
- That's a memory I wish I could forget.
- We will pretend that you did.
She's so wrinkly.
I mean, but cute.
I know, I know.
You okay?
I'm better than okay.
I think I might've found my path.
So much for the time capsule.
Yeah, well...
When you fix it, I think I know
what memory I'd like to use.
What's that?
I think this one.