May I help you find something?
I got it covered. But thanks.
Actually, you can
help me find the back door.
Well, it's by used games,
but you're really not supposed
to go out that way.
I won't tell anyone if you won't.
He's on the move.
FBI! Zane Donovan, get your hands up!
Freeze!
Excellent response time.
You guys take Lake Street?
Went up by Lincoln Park. Less traffic.
Yep. It's me.
I think I got a live one.
Probably not the best idea.
That comes out on the pistol range.
Please tell me you're my lawyer.
No. But I think I can
keep you out of jail.
What'd you have in mind?
You wanna hire this guy?
He's the best in his field.
Oh, yeah, if screwing up is a field.
We need a particle physicist, Carter,
and he's the most
promising one out there.
He was accepted
to MIT at the age of 13.
Expelled. Accepted at yale. Expelled.
Cornell. Oh, guess what? Expelled.
Not before winning the Spadaro
Foundation Award for superstring theory.
He set the bar so high, they haven't
even bothered to give it out since.
Here's a resume highlight.
"Just stole $3.1 million
"from the U.S. Border patrol account
for drug interdiction."
Allegedly.
And can't we just agree that
the war on drugs is really
a moralistic assault
on individual liberty, hmm?
- Or not.
- Hello, Zane. Welcome to Eureka.
- Good to see you, Sam.
- Right back at ya, Doc.
So we got one brainiac at
the standard recruitment rate
$25,000.
25,000 for this guy?
For 30, I'll throw in
dinner and a movie.
But I won't go past second base.
I'm not that kinda boy.
I'll give you a check.
Be a sweetheart and make it cash
And throw in some singles.
I'm chasing down
a paleontologist in vegas.
Well, who's this guy,
and how do I get his job?
Sam lovejoy,
Global Dynamics' talent scout.
I'm the guy who assembled
this dream team of intellectual prowess.
So you're the guy I can blame
for all the crap I deal with.
I just find 'em. What you do
with them after that is not my domain.
- He's all yours, Sheriff.
- Don't want him.
Well, you got him.
- Allison, just...
- Technically, he's still a prisoner.
- He's your responsibility.
- Until when?
Until you think he can be trusted.
So...
What do you do for fun in this town?
The Projet-SG Team
presents:
Timing:   Golgi, Linwelin,
Moochie, Ricana
Transcript:   swsub.com
Edition:   Golgi, Linwelin,
Moochie, Ricana.
Proofreading:   Golgi, Linwelin.
- Saison 2 | Episode 1 -
E=MC?
Obsession with firearms can be
a sign of unfulfilled sexual appetite.
I'm not saying that's you.
But if it is, I'm at your service.
Jo! Don't shoot the prisoner. Don't...
- If I just wing him?
- No.
Down. Allison wants him at GD alive.
Better use these then.
Bracelets.
They're geodetic coordinate
transceivers...
They'll show his location
within one meter.
And if he tries to run,
it's also got a restraint field.
An emergent graviton field generator?
- Very cool.
- If he tries to escape, hit the button.
Oh. What button?
Got a button.
Gimme that.
Arm.
- Where we going?
- Just go.
At least you know it works.
Your doctoral thesis was on
the origins of the universe, right?
- The first one.
- Hey, is this the new kid?
Who you calling kid, Spartacus?
- Cocky. I like him.
- You would.
I have something to show you.
Holy crap.
You actually built it?
What, exactly, did we build?
A chaotic inflation device.
It will recreate the origin singularity
in this observable containment field.
The big bang.
Supercritical ignition will take place
24 hours after we start the device.
And if it works, it will show us
the first moments of the universe.
And potentially rewrite every
cosmological theory we know.
Uh, I don't mean to be a wet
blanket, but won't that
blow up the planet?
Didn't think of that. Good you're here.
But seriously, this thing's going to
pump out a ton of hawking radiation.
And it's gonna go supernova.
So please tell me you have a plan.
You can just shut it off?
Well, actually, no.
Once induction is started,
it's essentially a runaway
cyclotron bomb.
That's a bad plan.
Relax. We have four generators creating
a layered particle field
that will contain the explosion.
- And one of us...
- Heads.
Me... Will be in the lab
continuously to adjust the field.
And as long as
the current density doesn't go
below 200, the field will hold.
I'm checking the levels
on the containment fields.
- No.
- Carter, it's okay.
We want Zane to feel comfortable.
He's part of the team.
Thanks, Dr. Blake.
I really appreciate that.
I don't know about
the rest of the team, but I'm starving.
So what's for lunch?
When the device ignites,
field must be at full strength.
So let's go through
the containment protocols again.
- Got 'em right here.
- It'll hold.
Well, I don't want to take any risks.
Scientific leaps require risk.
That's why GD is here,
to pull together great minds
so we can take risks.
Those self-esteem classes
are really helping out, Nathan.
- Got a great team.
- Well...
It's safe.
Here's to scientific leaps
and the beginning of
the universe.
Vincent, baby, gimme a bird on a raft,
keep off the grass,
and pin a rose to it, will ya?
Chicken on toast. Onion, no lettuce.
Sherrif?
Hey, Vince,
gimme two breasts, all wet...
J-just
chicken on a plate.
Two chickens on a plate.
- How's our boy doing, Sheriff?
-  He's behaving.
The best ones are always wild like
a porcini mushroom.
Tough, sometimes, sure,
but that's what gives this town flavor.
I was that way once. Ah, grazie.
- You miss it?
- Sure. These are my people, my peeps.
I been to every state of the union,
and this is the only town I fit in.
This is my family. You know, I...
I happen to have a knack of finding
new members of that family.
If you could find a member
without a felony record,
that would be just super.
Thanks, Vincent.
Where's he going?
Ow! What the hell?
I was getting napkins.
Sorry.
My bad.
I'm not eating that.
What? It's chicken.
You know how chickens are raised?
- Don't. Just let me enjoy my meal.
- Jammed together
in a windowless warehouse,
wading in feces until...
They get decapitated.
Or pecked to death.
When you eat that chicken,
you're eating all that hate.
Come on. I have to sleep in here?
At least you're not wading
in your own feces.
GD has an apartment for you,
but you're a criminal.
Don't deserve it.
You may think I'm a criminal,
but my mom loves me.
She wouldn't appreciate
you insulting her boy.
Enjoy your stay.
And... don't bother. It's unpickable.
Ithaca lock company.
Sloped tumblers.
Nice.
Can I at least watch tv?
The Mariners are playing the Yankees.
Sure, sure. It's gonna be a good game.
No pay channels.
Right.
Current density, stable.
390 electrovolts.
In 24 hours, we'll get to see
how the universe began.
Any historic words?
Let's light this candle.
- Are you sure you wanna do that?
- I didn't have any lunch.
Pork rinds have over 960 milligrams
of sodium per serving.
All right, you know what? New rule.
No one's allowed to say
anything about what I eat.
Whatever you say, Jack.
I can hear you judging.
Oh, hey, what's up?
You and your job can be really annoying.
Yeah. Tell me about it.
You know, Jasper Cole
was gonna ask me out.
But he didn't.
Because of you.
Yeah, that's right, Zoe.
I'm controlling him with my mind.
No, 'cause you're the Sheriff,
I'm the Sheriff's daughter.
And I have this big,
fat label right across my head,
and that's all anyone sees.
- I hope you're happy.
- Honestly?
If being the Sheriff's daughter keeps
you date-free for a couple months...
- Months?
- Or years. Then, yeah,
I'm pretty happy.
- How are you, dad?
- Pretty good.
Yeah, no, pretty good. Yeah.
That's right.
Right?
Morning. You want some breakfast?
How...
This panini press
makes rocking quesadillas.
- Who...
- Magic of the Internet.
This works like a wireless keyboard.
The IR Signal talks to
the receiver in your computer.
Took some curveballing getting
the pad togo on the web, but
had delivery guys flying
in and out all morning.
Give me that. Give it to me.
- You're sending all this stuff back.
- The restocking fee's gonna be killer.
Who paid for all this?
About that. You really shouldn't leave
credit card info on your hard drive.
That's just poor security.
Oh... My... God.
Watch him.
On the upside, I got them
to raise your credit limit.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Don't even try.
You may get to him,
but you won't get to me.
Jo Lupo.
- Yeah?
- I got 19 boxes from Liza's lingerie...
And can I just say God bless?
I had to guess the size.
You should really try everything on.
I'll make popcorn.
You don't really need him, do you?
I dunno.
Who?
Zane Donovan.
You... you can find some
other particle physicist, right?
Somebody without a felony record.
I suppose so.
You gotta go tell Allison...
So I can take him back to the Feds
and start rebuilding my credit score.
- Okay.
- Great.
What you doing?
Watching.
That looks bad.
Shouldn't you be watching this
instead of that?
This is funnier.
Didn't you say that if we were
below 200 we were in trouble?
Hey, I was watching that!
Am I wrong? Shouldn't we
make these numbers go up?
Maybe that'll help.
Maybe?
See ya.
He wasn't acting like Henry. Couldn't
remember what he told me yesterday.
- And where the hell is Stark?
- I don't know.
You were saying how
dangerous this experiment is.
What happens if Henry's
asleep at the switch
when the big bang goes boom?
It's bad, isn't it?
Yeah.
Do my shoes match my dress?
- What?
- Just look at me for a second.
- Wait... No. I'm sorry.
- No, it's...
How do you feel?
Hungry.
Do you feel like
you're thinking clearly?
What was the question?
You gotta focus for me, okay?
You gotta get on your phone,
and you're gonna have to call
a meeting of experts.
Good. Good.
Wait. A meeting with who?
Anyone involved in that experiment.
It's gonna explode
if you don't keep an eye on it.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Oh, Wait. Do I need to push 9 first?
Carter, I'm kind of busy.
Can't run here every time you call.
Thank God you're normal. Started
to think I was the smartest one here.
We got a major problem.
People are regressing.
They're starting to act dumb.
Dumb?
So what's the protocol? What do we do?
Only one thing we can do.
Pull my finger.
What do you mean,
they're stupid?
I mean stupid. Like... Stupid. stupid!
Carter, you can't catch stupid.
This may be my favorite
conversation of all time.
Look, something happened to Allison
and Henry and Stark and who knows else.
But it happened  in the middle
of that chaotic inflation thing.
You left that thing running
without anyone watching it?
We got it covered.
- Sort of.
- Sort of?
You gotta clear out that building
before that thing blows.
- It could take out the whole facility.
- Don't worry about it, we'll fix it.
What? We always fix it.
We don't always fix it.
Henry does it sometimes,
or Stark, or Allison.
I'm just saying, we usually have
smart people to lean on.
Hey, I'm smart. I'm plenty smart!
I mean... science smart.
Don't get snappy.
- OK, you're coming to GD.
- I'm not touching that experiment.
If I start pushing buttons, I could
accelerate the decay of that field.
- Need the guy who designed the machine.
- You said they're all dumb.
We need to figure out why. Let's start
with a list of all the people affected.
How you feeling?
You feel dumb?
No. You?
How could you tell?
Might be just affect the people at GD.
I'll head up there,
you pull evacuation plans.
You should help.
- How you holding up?
- Well, people keep calling.
I was making a list
of scientists for you.
Okay, here it is.
Everybody on this list works for
a different department at GD.
What do they have in common?
- Well, they all work here.
- Thank you. Yes.
Very helpful.
Have you shut down all the...
dangerous projects?
No. That's a good idea.
I'll write that down.
No, no, no, I'll do it!
I'm the head of Global.
- Okay. I know, I know.
- Just listen, I...
Look, I pulled all manuals from the...
the c-chaotic thingy, and...
I don't understand any of it.
We're gonna figure this out. I promise.
I'm scared.
- I feel like I'm losing myself.
- Why don't you stay here?
S-sit down, and you stay at work.
And I'll go find a doctor.
A normal doctor. Okay?
We're gonna sort this out.
I hope.
Excuse me. Are you...
dumb?
Sorry. What's the square root of 3,006?
- Don't know.
- Apologies.
I was never any good
at combinatoric math.
But if you threw me a couple of
Chomsky nominal form equations,
- I'm your gal.
- Great.
There's a dumb virus going around, you
gonna help figure out what's causing it.
A dumb virus?
Yeah. Wish I could. But, see, I'm a vet.
And if you brought me a marmoset
with cognitive decline,
I'd be happy to help. But...
I... no. I...
don't work on people.
- Today you do.
- No. You don't want me to.
It's not good.
You're wearing one of my presents
under there, aren't you?
Come on, you can tell me.
Okay.
I deserved that.
This is nice work.
How did you get enough phase power
for the field and the biometric lock?
Redox battery?
No. It's a nano-titanite cell.
Sweet.
How do you keep the amp load
from shorting out?
It's a dielectric waveguide.
Nice.
Hey, do you have the specs
on that chaotic inflation test?
Why?
Why don't you let me take a look
at the containment structure for you?
And if I'm helping you,
maybe you could help me.
And here it comes.
There's only one thing
I want from you, Jo Jo.
A sandwich.
Yeah, the Geneva Conventions state
that I get a sandwich for lunch.
And you'll read this.
And help.
Yeah.
Marco!
- Marco!
Polo.
One of you says Polo.
The game is Marco Polo.
God.
- Polo!
Tell me you found something.
Well, I'm not sure,
because this really isn't my field.
However, everybody I've tested seems
to have a critically low level of GABA.
I didn't know I had any GABA.
Gamma amino butyric acid.
It's a neurotransmitter.
Okay, and if you don't
have enough, it...
- Lowers intelligence?
- It could, yeah.
Critically reduced levels cause
Alzheimer's disease in monkeys.
Okay, so where's it coming from?
- Air conditioning, water coolers...
- I have no idea.
And our neuropharmacologist
is currently playing candyland.
Okay...
Gather everyone who's thinking straight,
meet me in the conference room... Fast.
Conference room.
All right, we got a botanist,
a math theorist, a chemist,
a nutritionist,
and a... lepi... potomus.
- Lepidopterist.
- Right.
Butterflies.
Fantastic.
All right, everyone, if you wanna gather
around, I trust you've been briefed.
You all know that the big bang device
is in danger melting down.
And the people who built it
are incapacitate. So...
who do we have who can help
with this experiment?
You know, it's not their field.
You need a physicist
or maybe a molecular theorist.
Great, we got a room full of geniuses
and all we can do is eradicate plant rot
and do triage on a butterfly.
Let's switch gears.
All right. What we have to do
is cure someone who can help us.
If we can find out what's knocking down
the GABA, maybe we can reverse
the mental decline.
Right? So, who can help
with that? Anyone?
GABA knockdown...
- You. What do you do?
- Epigeneticist.
The butyric acid cycle could be affected
by any number of factors.
Enzyme overgrowth,
- radiation exposure, a virus.
- Radiation can cause this?
If it disrupts the TRNA synthetase.
Okay, well, the chaotic thing
- was pumping out a lot of radiation.
- No. I don't think so.
I've done studies with radiation
on animals before,
and that device would have to be tuned
to a precise wavelength
in order to cause this effect.
What if somebody
was tuning it on purpose?
- Ooh. Well, it's possible...
- They'd have to know
big bang nucleosynthesis
and string theory.
Yeah.
I have a guy in my jail cell
who might know those things,
and he'd think it was pretty hilarious
to turn everyone at GD into a moron.
Alright. Work on curing Allison
and all the others.
Any of you with a medical background,
you go with Dr. Glenn.
The rest of you...
Start learning physics.
Carter, we got a problem.
Tell me about it.
No, it's about Zane.
Are you sure you locked the cell?
Of course I locked the cell.
We gotta find him.
Well, we can track him with these.
Or even better...
He got out of the bracelet.
He... How?
By mistake...
I may have told him
how to hack the lock.
All right. Thanks, sergeant.
The state police are on
every road out of town.
They'll find him.
No, they won't. He's good.
He knows how to hide.
Well, we've got the GD computer.
It's running probabilities
for any escape route,
every phone call he's ever made,
every map he's downloaded.
No one in this world knows any better
than this computer.
Someone might.
That's awesome.
I know.
Hey, where is everybody?
Carter had me send 'em home.
Something about a... chaotic...
Something or 'nother.
Ah, was it that thing I helped build?
Yeah.
I remember something like that.
You okay?
Not even.
Can't keep a thought in my head
for, like, ten seconds.
Car's busted.
Nothing to do.
That's bunk.
Still the smartest guy I know.
Not saying much.
What if this doesn't get better?
I guess we'll just be dumb together.
You know, breaking
and entering's just a bad idea.
Well, I must say I'm impressed.
What did you do, refocus
some of your satellites to pick me up?
Figured 50 miles from Eureka
was far enough.
No. You vacationed here
when you were ten.
I figured it's off the main roads,
a place to hide out
for a couple of days first.
Well, I guess my FBI file was
more detailed than I thought.
It's not in your file.
Then, that computer of yours must
have an amazing predictive algorithm.
Didn't use a computer.
I called your mother.
You called my mother?
I need to know what you did.
Okay.
You were right.
That cell has a damn good lock.
I had to order a new master key
off the Ithaca lock web site.
They run a pretty tight ship.
I had to give your social
security number.
That's not what I'm talking about. What
did you do to the big bang experiment?
- What are you talking...
- What did you do to make them stupid?
- That's crazy!
- All right, this isn't a joke anymore.
Okay? This is serious. I need
them back on their game.
You think I would intentionally
mess up that experiment?
- Yeah. And I'm running out of options.
- Well, I wouldn't.
Because it's beautiful.
If that thing up there works, it's...
It could change the laws of physics.
Then why are you running from it?
As I see it, there are two sides.
You're with me or you're against me.
It's your problem. Why should I help?
Because if you'd stop being a selfish
jackass for more than 5 seconds,
you might discover
you could be a part of something.
A community.
What makes you think I give a crap
about finding a community?
Because we all do.
And you're smart enough to know that.
- He's just standing there.
- He's thinking.
Well, he doesn't look like
he's thinking. He looks sick!
That's because containment's
down to 14%.
When that chaotic device blows,
that field's gonna fail.
You got 43 minutes to find a way
to make it stronger.
Yeah, so figure it out.
And the answer is...
Clear the building.
- Anyone who's still here, get 'em out.
- Non essential personnel are gone.
Focus, all right?
You're one of the top guys here.
You not only won
the Spadaro foundation award,
they don't bother to give it anymore.
Yeah, they stopped giving it out because
someone stole Mrs. Spadaro's money.
They hacked her system.
Even I couldn't find how.
If I couldn't help her,
I can't help you.
It would take me 18 hours
to rebuild that thing.
And if it blows without containment,
it'll cut right through the metal
shielding and gut the building.
Well, you're all we've got.
So...
Could you bring in more shielding?
That's good!
It would take at least 100 tons
of metallic hydrogen sheets.
- That's not good.
- How about another field
around the field or double it
or reinforce it with something?
- Duct tape!
- Yeah, like duct tape.
It's a layered particle field.
The only way to reinforce it
is with another layered particle field.
- Keep going.
- Like an emergent graviton field.
- The bracelets.
- They're in the car.
Go! I'll crack the control circuits.
Well... So does that mean we're good?
All right, we're going to build a second
force field to contain this one.
I need binned gradients
and a way into the aiming circuit.
Danger... Containment level critical.
- Guys, this is where you say something,
- I think it was...
- Red.
- Or red-like.
- Yeah, definitely.
- Fantastic.
- Found it!
- Awesome!
We're in business.
Here! Got 'em.
- How much time do we have?
- Not much.
- Not helping.
- What else do we have to do?
The bracelets generate
charged gravitons.
If I can jack into
the aiming circuit, get the
timing, I might reinforce
the field to contain the explosion.
I have not a clue
about anything you just said.
He's gonna contain it.
- What?
- I'm sorry, Jack.
I just realized this is how
you must feel all the time.
Thank you, Henry. Very kind.
I think you want to turn on
that extra shield now.
No. I've gotta time it right.
I overcranked
the snot out of this thing.
The field only lasts three seconds.
Not yet.
Don't let me die in this crap town.
Now!
So that's what all the fuss was about?
Are you kidding? It's the big bang,
the beginning of the beginning.
This data's gonna keep
physicists busy for 50 years.
It kinda looks like a scoop of...
rainbow sherbet.
I think it's... It's pretty.
Not as pretty as you.
Oh, that's so sweet.
How are you feeling?
Kinda hungry.
The machine's off. Why is everybody
still acting like a moron?
Because the experiment wasn't the cause.
Are you sure?
The experiment
produced hawking radiation.
And all of these tests prove that
doesn't affect brain tissue.
Um... So what's causing this?
I don't know.
And I don't know how to reverse it.
So what do we do now?
We don't give up.
Okay.
I called the CDC and the NIH.
They're on their way.
Good! What are those?
The CDC is
the Center for Disease Control,
and the NIH is the National...
Something of Health.
No. Anyway... Dr. Glenn
is gonna be taking all the...
affected people to GD
for some tests.
You're a real good friend, Jack.
I just...
I just feel bad 'cause
I keep things from you.
- What are you talking about?
- The Beverly stuff.
You know...
What she did to Kim.
What did Beverly do to Kim?
Maybe you could find out.
You're really good at that stuff.
Yeah, sure. Sure.
How... That's... That's cool.
- Can I try?
- Oh, yeah.
Stay with me. We're talking about Kim.
You... You can have
a turn right after me.
Sheriff, come here! Come here!
Yeah. Hey... Sam, good.
We could use a boost of brain power.
Meet my latest and greatest...
Madame Ofenskaya.
- Charmed.
- Nice to meet you.
She's pittsburgh's best astrologer.
Slap her to a telescope,
you'll be talking to aliens by Kwanzaa.
Don't you mean astronomer?
What's the difference?
Oh, crap.
Well, you can get in line for the yo-yo.
Now Sam's got it, he didn't go
anywhere near that experiment.
Right.
Hey, Vincent, can I get another
chicken san? It was dee-lish.
Oh, sorry. We're fresh out.
Vince, you can order some more.
From where?
From right there.
You are smart!
And you're not.
- And he's not.
- Can I...
Let me yo.
- I wanna...
- No, no.
Henry... did you have
some tasty chicken yesterday?
Sure. We all did.
Right. I didn't. Neither did Zane.
I'm a vegetarian.
Oh, please, Sheriff.
That sounds kinda nutty.
Maybe. But everybody who was
affected had your chicken.
Do you use growth hormones?
Tetracycline, nafcillin?
My chicken is completely organic.
Right, okay.
Maybe something's getting
into their feed.
I need to see your livestock.
- Where's the rest of them?
- He's the only one.
Took me seven years of somatic
cell transfer and
DNA stripping to make Chester.
He's a clone?
He has ears, you know.
Little rhode island red,
mix in some golden
montazah, a dash of lakehorn and...
He's the perfect bird.
Aren't you, chester?
Yes, you are!
If you only have...
If...
If you only have one chicken,
then where's the meat come from?
Oh, this may be the grossest
thing I've ever seen.
Where do you think chicken comes from?
From chickens.
Chickens that have been murdered,
but not anymore.
The avian holocaust is over, my friend.
So you're growing independent
parts from stem cells?
It's a breakthrough.
I used to clone the whole chicken.
Now I just grow the parts
people want to eat
so I don't have to kill anything.
If you're growing...
Meat with no brain,
then... Is it safe?
It's perfectly safe. It's organic.
And with my new grow lights,
five times as productive.
I just installed them.
Maybe your grow lights
are making the meat
five times as stupid.
So, disconnected from the neural net,
the only way you can make these...
Pieces of meat grow
is if you flood it with bicuculline.
Yes, but that's organic.
It's a plant extract.
The grow lights enhance the process.
But it's also a GABA blocker.
- GABA. Hey...
- Yes.
It's depressing the GABA production,
and it's causing the cognitive decline.
Oh, my god.
I had no idea.
Do we have to tell Chester?
He'll be so ashamed.
That'll do it?
The sulfonate should
flush out the biculline
and bring the GABA back into balance.
- Maybe.
- Well, why wouldn't it work?
Because I'm winging it here.
Maybe is the best you're going to get.
I'm gonna be okay. I...
I have to go first.
They're my people.
Don't worry about it.
She's very smart.
It'll work.
Okay, this might hurt just a little bit.
I'm actually not very good with people.
I'm used to giving shots to mangabeys.
What's a mangabey?
No idea.
Hold on. There. Good.
You know, as scary as it was being dumb,
it was also kind of liberating.
Speak for yourself.
What, you found nothing
positive in the experience?
Maybe one thing.
So, all the facts of the world
at your fingertips again?
Hen oida hoti ouden oida.
Either that's very profound,
or you're badly brain damaged.
What's the project status?
Well, everyone at GD wants
to get their hands on the data.
- All big bang whores.
- They'll have to wait.
You get first crack at it.
After Nathan, of course.
- Thanks.
- Well,
if you will excuse me,
I've a building full of people
who are behind on their work,
starting with those two.
And you can get going
as soon as Carter thinks
you're ready to be on your own.
So... Any idea when that might be?
When you're too old to run.
Nah, go.
Find the secrets to the universe.
I think I'm gonna get some pie.
- Vince, can I get a slice of pie?
- Sure.
Wait a minute.
I keep one bomb from exploding,
and you think you can trust me?
No, it wasn't that.
It's was Mrs. Spadaro.
Turns out she's giving
her award this year because
someone made
an anonymous gift to her foundation
of $3.1 million.
You gonna turn me in?
There's a federal statute
protecting the anonymity
of charitable donations. So...
Mrs. Spadaro's money is safe.
- Thanks, Vincent.
- Yeah.
Thanks. I guess you want these back.
I'm sure you'll find some use for them.
Thanks.
The ballet.
What?
Take her to the ballet.
But if you get out of line,
I will make those cuffs permanent.
Thanks for the tip.
It's all right.
You okay?
I'm 16. My parents are divorced.
And I live in the weirdest
small town on earth.
Yeah, you know, I'm awesome.
You're also the sheriff's daughter.
Oh, yeah. Than for reminding me.
Honey...
People use labels
to make their life easier.
You know, which is fine. But...
You define who you are.
You have to...
Break people's expectations.
Oh, my god. That's Jasper.
That's cute?
Yeah.
Okay, you know what?
It's time to break expectations.
No, that's not what I meant.
That's your dad.
Yeah, but...
he's cool with me going,
if you still want to.
To my parents' lake house
for the weekend? Sweet.
I mean, if you still wanna go.
Oh, my god, yeah. I mean, I'm so there.
No, you're not.
Yeah, Sheriff?
I'm watching you.
He's... He's not being serious.
http://projet-sg.net