Previously on Eureka...
- Jack?
- Abby? What are you doing here?
Zoe.
That's my mom.
I asked you to wait.
Has she spoken to you?
- What?
- You told her.
This is so like you!
I don't wanna look like the bad guy
because you come and take away my kid.
What are you talking about?
We had an agreement
when you came to live here.
A year, and then you were
supposed to come back to LA with me.
You've already ruined your own lives.
Just leave mine alone.
Were you seeing Kim?
More during the months leading up
to her... To the accident.
So you never visited her lab?
No.
Hey. What's up?
Noise complaint from the neighbors.
What neighbors?
The ones three miles down the road.
Exactly what kind of noise are they
complaining about three miles down...
- Never mind.
- Yeah.
Oh.
Hello?
Ah, excuse me, sir?
- Yes?
- Hi,
I'm sheriff Jack Carter, and you are?
Busy.
What is it that you need?
Listen, Dr. Bajanian,
we've had a noise complaint,
and we're gonna have to ask you
to keep it down.
But I'm working
on simultaneously configuring
the position and momentum of electrons
so they'll no longer be
conjugate variables, thereby debunking
Heisenberg's uncertainty principal.
And as exciting as that may be,
we're still gonna have
to ask you to keep it down.
Fine.
Looks like you have an oil leak.
That's ununseptium,
a highly volatile halogen.
Whose effects on human skin
have yet to be tested.
Right. So not an oil leak.
Carter!
I told you to watch your head.
No, you didn't.
Okay, you know you need
special permission
to use transuranic elements
- outside of Global, right?
- Of course.
Okay, so let me see your permit, Doctor.
I'm sure they're on file, Deputy.
While we go check that out,
we're going to, uh,
have to ask you to still keep it down.
Thanks for your time.
Henry, are you sure about this?
- Allison...
- I can set you up in a brand-new lab
- with twice the space.
- Kim's lab will do just fine.
Then at least let me have someone
clear out all the old stuff.
No, you said you were gonna leave it
the way it was the day she...
At least until
I had time to go through it.
I did and I have. It's just...
This has to be hard for you.
I see it as a chance to stay close
to her, continue her work.
You know, we used to finish
each other's sentences. So...
Okay.
So Abby, you're heading
back to Los Angeles?
Yep, this is it.
I'm sorry to see you go.
Oh, no, you're not.
Sheriff Carter and Zoe will miss you.
No, they won't.
Perhaps if you weren't
taking Zoe away...
SARAH, forgive me
if I don't feel the need
to justify my parental choices
to a talking bunker.
Fine. Don't let the door hit you
on the way out.
You wanna piece of me?
Are you, uh, threatening the house?
She started it.
Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I got a headache.
- Where's Zoe?
- She's in her room. She's okay.
She's using a virtual therapy
device that Beverly gave her.
It's called an ATS.
I'll tell ya, the things
this town comes up with...
Oh, yeah, it's a great place to live.
I mean, it's sort of full
of mind-blowing opportunities
and brilliant minds
at the top of their game.
And the schools... amazing.
Yeah?
Are you really okay with this?
We had an agreement.
I know.
But I don't want you to do
that thing that you do,
you know, when you say you're okay with
something and six months after that,
we're at my parents'
50th wedding anniversary
and you've had one beer too many,
and you ask my mom if the ball-buster
gene comes from her side of the family?
You threw out my baseball cards.
We were having a baby.
We needed the room.
I had a 1989 upper deck
Ken Griffey, Jr. Rookie card.
Do you have any idea
how much that's worth now?
No, and Dear God, before you tell me,
let's just try and swing this
right around to my original point.
Are you okay with me
taking Zoe back to LA?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Okay.
'Cause the end of the semester's coming,
and I'm gonna come back to get her.
So... I'll call ya.
Zoe!
How many times have I asked you
not to leave your stuff lying around?
Zoe.
Zoe?
Hey!
- I'm talking to you here.
- Hey, I'm getting my head shrunk here.
Well, shrink it after you're done
cleaning up your mess, okay?
Is that the, um...
IRS thing from Beverly?
ATS.
She's out of town and...
She thinks it'll help me confront my
inner fears and resolve my anger issues.
How's it working?
Well, I'm still pretty pissed, so...
Do you wanna talk?
No, actually.
I want you to leave me alone.
Okay, that's... The exact opposite
of leaving me alone.
I know you're upset.
But your mom really misses you.
We agreed to shared custody.
And I think that, um,
if you don't give this a shot,
you will regret it.
Custody.
Meaning ownership.
Meaning I have no say.
Zoe, your mom loves you a lot.
Well, you know, I gotta give her credit.
At least she's willing to fight for me.
I'm gonna go clean up my stuff.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
Uh, rearranging furniture.
What are you doing here?
Well, I said I was taking
the afternoon off, not quitting.
- Okay.
- Okay, so everything back in its place.
Go.
Sure, why should I get
to be by the window?
Hey, um, did you pull those,
permits I asked you to?
What?
The permits for, um,
Bajanian's contraption?
What are you talking about?
I swear, sometimes...
I wonder if you even listen to me.
I feel like I'm talking to myself.
Jo?
Hey, Sheriff. What can I get for ya?
Uh, nothing right now. Have you seen Jo?
- W- who?
- My deputy.
Oh, you got a new deputy? That's great.
I didn't get a new deputy.
I have a deputy.
Deputy Jo Lupo.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Is he cute?
Okay, now you're just bugging me.
I really need to talk to her.
Uh, listen, maybe I could help.
Has anybody here ever heard of a, uh,
deputy Lupo?
Sorry, no. Not me.
Sorry, Sheriff. I don't think anybody
here has ever heard of her.
The Projet-SG Team
presents:
Timing: Golgi, Linwelin.
Transcript: swsub.com
Edition:   Golgi, Linwelin.
Proofreading: Golgi, Linwelin.
- Season 2 | Episode 4 -
Games People Play (v. 1.0)
Henry?
Jack.
Oh, there you are.
Here I am.
I thought you'd be at Global today.
No.
- Jack, you need something?
- Do you know a woman named Jo Lupo?
No, don't think so.
Okay, this is really
gonna sound strange.
I have a deputy named Jo Lupo.
Small, but surprisingly strong.
Bit of a gun nut?
I had a conversation with her
today, I turn my back for two seconds,
and she's gone.
Like vanished, and no one
in the town even remembers her.
I think everyone is playing
a trick on me, right?
So I go to her house, and, uh...
You know, the name
on the mailbox is changed,
and there's a family with, like,
12 kids living there,
and the house is a different color,
which is a bit far to go for a prank.
A bit, yeah.
You think I'm losing it, don't ya?
Um... You think you're losing it?
I know this woman! You know this woman!
All right, maybe something's
affected your body chemistry
or altered your neural pathway somehow.
Were you exposed to anything?
Yeah, I visited a guy,
he was, uh, playing with...
a new,
atlantic element.
- Transuranic?
- Yes! Yeah, that's it.
- Would that do it?
- No.
- Okay. What else have we got?
- Well, um...
Maybe...
Maybe you fell into some freezing water,
and, uh, you went into hypothermia.
Or you suffered a trauma,
and that sent you into shock.
Wha...
- Yeah, I hit my head.
- With what?
A heavy, metal object.
How many times?
Repeatedly.
Well, see? That would have some effect.
So if that's our problem, get an MRI.
Henry, I've had a concussion
before, that's not it.
Do you remember Occam's razor?
Yeah. uh...
Simple things, uh, are true.
Close enough. So you are
either part of some...
theoretical, unknown, scientific
discovery where people
vanish from our world and memories,
or... you suffered a head trauma.
When you say it like that...
Get an MRI.
Yeah.
I'm not saying that you can't have one.
I'm just asking why do you want one?
It's not a big deal. It's just,
I bumped my head this morning
and Henry thought it'd be a good
idea if I had it looked at.
You having any dizziness,
nausea, headaches?
No, my head was pounding
earlier, but it's fine now.
Actually, it's
totally fine now.
Problem solved.
What's he even doing here?
He works here.
He was fired weeks ago.
Okay, brain scan it is.
Run an EEG and draw blood.
No, I just need an MRI, thanks.
Relax, it usually only takes me
two or three tries to hit a vein.
You're pretty talented.
- Really?
- No!
Do you know anyone
who'd be working on a...
really intense, unknown,
theoretical scientific discovery?
You mean like a class eight project?
Yes. Let's talk about those.
Sorry, all class eight research
is classified.
Oh, you know what else
should be classified?
A certain assistant's
american idol audition.
- What?
- No, no!
Zoe promised me to delete that.
What's it gonna be?
Fine! Gimme an hour.
All right, so put the gown on,
and all metal objects
and jewelry in the tray.
All right.
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
Just got a lot on my mind.
You know, you can always
talk to Beverly.
First of all, no.
And, second of all, she's out of town.
No, she's not.
I just saw her at Cafe Diem.
R... Well, then why's she having
Zoe do therapy from home today?
I don't know, but...
is Zoe okay?
Actually, not so much.
No.
Abby's taking her back to LA
at the end of the semester
as a part of our custody agreement.
And are you okay with that?
Yeah.
- It's complicated.
- Well,
what do you think you
should do about this?
I don't know. What can I do?
I don't know, but if someone
was gonna take Kevin away from me,
I would feel like my world was ending.
Let's get this over with.
- Hey, how's your head?
- A waste of time.
The MRI was clear.
Well, I wouldn't rule out
your injury just yet.
It might not be me, though.
I mean, it might be a, uh,
class eight project?
And what do you know
about class eight projects?
Mainly that I'm not supposed
to know about them.
That's true. I don't think
that's your problem,
most of that research is theoretical.
I know, I know, and I know
what I'm asking isn't probable,
but is it possible?
Yeah, well... It might have something
to do with meta-material technology
or vector decomposition or
cellular irradiation.
- Okay.
- But none of those things
could remove someone
from the world's consciousness.
Unless...
it was some kind
of transdimensional travel.
Okay, let's go with that. What's that?
Movement between parallel universes.
Right... So you're saying that
Jo got zapped to another universe?
Or maybe you did. Theoretically,
every universe is different.
But the closer they are, the more alike
they are, with maybe just a difference.
A green sky instead of blue,
- cats chase dogs or...
- In a town of 3,000 people,
one isn't where he's supposed to be.
Exactly.
We should talk to Nathan about this.
He's good with this kind of thing.
Great! Thanks.
You're welcome.
I was starting to worry
if it was something to do with me.
Well, that's where
the smart money still is.
Funny.
Henry?
Henry!
You wanna run that by me one more time?
People are disappearing
into this crazy light,
and nobody remembers them but me.
- People like...
- What difference does it make?
You're not gonna know who
I'm talking about anyway.
- I'm gonna double-check your MRI.
- There's nothing wrong with my head.
Well, what you're describing
simply is impossible.
There's no technology that could create
such an anomaly. Not even in Eureka.
Well, how about, um,
many-materials technology
or, like, the cell phone radiation
or decomposing vectors?
And now you're just
putting words together.
Okay, I don't know what I'm talking
about, but Henry said that you would.
- Henry...
- Henry Deacon. The...
How do you not remember...
He was a friend of yours.
I have a lot of friends.
Actually, not so much.
But we'll table that.
Um, I think it has something
to do with me,
okay? People interact with,
people I know, but whatever it is,
we must figure it out before it affects
the 3,000 people in this town.
You see, now I know it's in your head,
because Eureka's only half that size.
That means it's spreading.
Nathan, you gotta help me.
- Okay.
- Great. Where do we start?
You go home and get some rest.
And I'll start by
double-checking your MRI.
Come on.
- Zoe?
- Hey, what's up?
Hey, uh, where are you?
- Home. Why?
- All right, stay put.
- What's happening?
- I don't know, but if you see
a big flash of light, I need you to run.
Just get away from it,
- and you call me, okay?
- Seriously?
Seriously, um...
I'll be in touch. Gotta go.
Fargo!
Fargo.
- Did you get it?
- Yes.
But you can't tell anyone
I showed this to you.
If you don't show it to me,
there might not be anyone left to tell.
I have no idea what that means.
Ah, you don't have to.
Why do you need it anyway?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
Huh, Stark's on this list.
Of course he is.
He's done more class eight projects
than anyone else at Global.
And this guy, I know him.
Saw him this morning.
Uh, Dr. Bajanian?
Yeah, he's a quantum physicist.
Any chance what he's doing could
punch a hole in another dimension?
Not likely, but when you start dealing
with subatomic particles,
the typical laws of nature
no longer apply.
Okay. Thanks.
And, um...
You got a great voice.
Don't let anyone tell you different.
Hey! Allison.
- What's going on?
- I need you to come with me.
There's a noise complaint,
outskirts of town.
This guys is using an element he
doesn't have permission to use.
- So make him get a permit.
- Yeah, well,
I'm not supposed to know this, but
he's one of your class eight scientists.
Carter, everyone knows who
the class eight scientists are.
Fargo said he's working with atoms,
and I think this guy Bajanian
could be a really serious threat.
- Who?
- Bajanian.
Weird guy, lives
on the outskirts of town.
I know who Bajanian is.
Who told you that he works with atoms?
Fargo.
Oh, man.
Hey, Sheriff.
Soup?
Ya hired Larry the kiss-ass?
- Okay, Carter, I have work to do.
- Alisson.
Whatever this guy's doing,
it makes people disappear,
and I seem to be the only one
who's noticing.
Please.
Please come with me.
And watch your head.
He's got this big booming machine
with lots of little things spinning...
You'll see.
Dr. Bajanian?
This can't be happening.
Can I help you?
Where'd you put it?
- Sorry?
- Where?
The machine with the lights
and swirling?
Could you be a little more vague?
The thing you built to find out
how fast the electrons are moving.
I was right here this morning. I saw it.
What were you doing in my lab?
I know you're up to something.
I'm gonna figure out what it is.
Miss Blake.
I'm sorry about the intrusion,
Dr. Bajanian.
Let's go.
Carter, there's nothing here.
Move!
Not again.
I can't believe it got him too.
What are you talking about?
You have no idea of what happened?
I know you dragged me out
to an empty lab.
And you're starting to scare me.
We gotta get outta here.
- Where are you gonna go?
- I'm not sure.
I'm glad you thought this through.
We'll get Kevin, we'll get Zoe,
and we'll get out of dodge
while we still can.
Avoiding the issue isn't going
to help resolve it.
When the issue is that the people
I care about keep disappearing,
I'm willing to do whatever it takes.
Listen to me.
I trusted you. I need you to trust me.
Let's just go back to the office,
I promise, we will figure this out.
You wanna help? Here.
One of the 20 people on that list
knows exactly what's going on.
Help me figure out which one.
Carter, there is nothing written
on this piece of paper.
Please.
I know that I can help you.
Carter, we need to slow down
and talk about this.
I'm telling you, we gotta leave.
It's spreading.
We can't stay.
Carter, just drink some water
and calm down.
- You're dehydrated.
- I'm dehydrated? You gotta kidding.
Just drink the water.
- I'm fine.
- Just drink it!
- Why the hell do I wanna drink...
- So I don't have to do this.
I'm sorry.
It was for your own good.
How are you feeling?
Like somebody stabbed me in the back.
And then stabbed me in the neck.
I'm sorry, there's nothing else
I could do.
You were practically hysterical.
I expect it from Stark.
Not so much you.
Stark?
Ex-husband Nathan Stark.
Egomaniacal bane of my existence.
That does sound like
someone that I would marry...
But, no, I've never heard of him.
The only way to fix the problem,
is to recognize that you have one.
What is that? AA?
- Carter...
- Allison, don't I...
I mean, apart from the...
Remembering people
that don't exist thing,
don't I seem rational to you?
The former seems to negate the latter.
- Why are you talking like Beverly?
- I'm just trying to help you.
Then think this through with me.
How many offices are there at global?
- Over 1,000.
- How many people work there?
- Maybe 100.
- Doesn't that seem odd to you?
We're in a transitional period.
Or your mind is reaching
to justify what's happening.
I could say the same for you.
Okay.
But you gotta let me go get Zoe.
I can't deal with losing her.
I won't.
Okay.
Thank you.
Allison, come here.
Don't let it touch you.
Allison, move!
Everything's gonna be all right.
- SARAH, door.
- Is everything okay?
Not even close. Zoe!
Zoe!
- What's going on?
- Hey, sweetie.
Um, get your shoes on,
we gotta go, okay?
- What's happening?
- No questions, just go.
All right?
Okay, great.
SARAH, how many people
live in Eureka right now?
My current calculations say two...
You and Zoe.
Okay, thank you.
Back to the beginning.
Zoe!
- Zoe.
- I'm coming.
What do you remember about this morning?
What do you mean?
Okay, your mom was here,
you and I got in a fight,
you threw the thing at me
and you left, right?
Okay, mom has never been to Eureka,
I don't member getting in a fight,
and I don't know
what thing you're talking about.
The thing.
The therapy thingy... The ATS.
What?
For the love of...
I was sitting here.
And...
I had it in my hands.
And I stood up.
Dad.
I never put it down.
So?
So...
Then I go back downstairs and
I see you on the couch.
And I say that I'm
going off to the office?
Okay, that I remember.
But nothing before that?
Nothing that you've mentioned.
So that's our first shared memory.
- I have no idea...
- What I'm talking about.
That's the problem.
And the only way to solve a problem
is to recognize that you have one.
Okay, you sound like my therapist.
Or a therapy device.
Right, like the same you had, the one
I have no recollection of putting down.
I mean, I must've tried it on, right?
That's why everybody
sounded like Beverly.
Except you.
This is gonna be hard to swallow.
I don't think any of this is real.
Okay.
I think that I'm...
We are...
in a program.
And...
I don't know how to find my way out.
Dad, you're freaking me out.
Dad.
Dad, can you hear me?
Please wake up.
I'm so scared.
Please.
- Oh, sweetie.
- Mom.
I drove back as fast as I could.
What happened?
I was doing my therapy on the ATS.
And Dad walked in,
and we got in a fight, and...
I threw it at him, and
for some reason, he put it on,
and when I walked back in,
he was shaking and he wouldn't wake up.
And I shouldn't have thrown it at him.
Honey, it's nobody's fault.
But can't you just take this off?
We're afraid that disconnecting him
could send him into paralytic shock.
So what is happening to him?
Actually, we're not sure.
The, ATS was developed
in collaboration with Beverly Barlowe.
But we've never had this happen before.
It's a virtual version of Eureka,
down to the very last detail.
The user's subconscious issues
come to life in the game.
Normally, they're aware
of what they're experiencing,
and they can leave the program
at any time.
We think the concussion may have caused
a glitch in the mainframe,
that Carter is unaware
that he's in an altered reality.
Is his life in danger?
Someone answer me.
Yes. It is.
So let's get Beverly down here
and fix it.
Well, we can't reach her.
So we sent Henry to her house to find
any information that can help us.
Beverly, this is Henry.
I'm in your house now.
We really need your help.
So when you get this message, call!
Dad, where are we going?
If this isn't real, there has to be
a way out, right?
- Like an exit sign?
- Yeah, I'm not that lucky.
You said this therapy thing
is for confronting your fears,
- working out anger issues...
- I don't remember that.
- Yeah, well, you said it.
- And I'm not angry.
So maybe confronting fears
is the way out.
Yours or mine?
I'm wearing the thing,
so i'm guessing mine.
Okay, so what are you afraid of?
Right now, that.
What is that?!
That's what's been taking people.
Dad, what are you doing?
Confronting my fear.
I am so sorry. Are you okay?
I'm...
Yeah. I'm just, uh...
- Looking for a cup of coffee.
- Allow me.
I cook when I'm upset.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
What are you all doing here?
We're here for Carter and Zoe.
All of you?
Yeah, I mean...
He's our sheriff, and she's our girl.
- Did you find anything else?
- Just another ATS Device.
I can take it apart,
we can see the mechanics.
- Well, if he can hold on that long.
- Yeah.
Hey, honey.
There's a whole lot of people out there
who are worried about you.
You wanna come say hi?
Not right now.
You gonna eat?
He wouldn't leave me.
I'm not gonna leave him.
- Dad.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
Why aren't we running?
We don't have to.
You're gonna go. It's gonna take you.
I'm gonna stay with you.
Dad! What's happening?
We're losing him.
Wait!
He's fighting.
- Dad!
- Jack, you're all right!
I thought I'd lost you.
Oh, no, never. No.
No, no, no.
I knew you wouldn't leave.
I'm here.
Looks good.
Looks very good.
Well, great.
Henry said you could have visitors?
Yeah, yeah, that'd be great.
Okay, guys, come on in!
You look great.
Zoe, hi.
Hi. Abby!
Hey, good to see ya.
Hey, Chris. Thanks very much.
I really appreciate it.
Thanks for that.
Hey, thanks for that.
Hey, thank you so much.
How many of you are there?
Hi.
Hey.
Hey, how you feeling?
A little strange.
You know, I have all these...
memories and...
feelings about things
that never happened.
Well, that's gotta be pretty surreal.
You have no idea.
Anyway, I just stopped by
to see if you were okay.
To see if I'm okay?
Yeah, this is your
first day back in Kim's lab.
I know that's a big deal.
Jack, it's fine. Really.
I mean, you're the one
we should be worrying about.
They told me...
The therapy thing was forcing me to
deal with my feelings about losing Zoe.
Apparently I have...
abandonment, entitlement,
and intimacy issues.
- Ha, congratulations.
- Thank you.
Even though that wasn't actually you,
you helped me a lot in there.
I don't know what I'd do without you.
Me too.
I should get going.
Abby's taking off, we gotta talk
before she goes, so...
All right, well, good luck and...
thanks.
Yeah.
You wanted me to stop by.
Yeah, yeah, I think we should talk.
Yeah, I know.
I'm happy here.
Yeah, I know I complain about it, and...
It definitely has its quirks.
- Yeah, that's one way of putting it.
- Yeah.
But...
I belong here.
- And I'm doing some good.
- You do. And you are.
And I think this place
has been good for Zoe.
You know, I think
she fits in here somehow.
Well, maybe that's 'cause she
doesn't fit in anywhere else.
She has some good friends.
Yeah, I've noticed that.
And I would never ask you to...
you know, not take her.
That wouldn't be fair to you or Zoe.
- Jack, listen, I...
- That being said...
I can't go...
months without seeing my kid.
Can't even go days, really.
So... I'm...
gonna ask for my job back in LA.
Really?
Yep.
It's funny, you remind me
the man I once married.
So what do you think?
I think this place needs you.
And it wasn't until today that
I realized just how much Zoe needs you.
And I can't take you away from here.
I can't take her away from you.
- But...
- This is where she needs to be.
Thank you.
I love you, Jack Carter.
SARAH, door.
Good evening, Sheriff Carter.
Will the former Mrs. Carter
be joining you for dinner?
Relax, SARAH, she's gone.
What a shame.
Sarcasm doesn't become you.
Is...
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry, I meant to have
all this cleaned up
before you got home.
Oh, it's okay.
It doesn't matter. Leave it.
Your mom and I had a talk.
I told her how much you love it here,
and...
That you... You wanna stay.
And I told her that I would
respect our agreement.
What did she say?
Oh, she seems to think that...
I need adult supervision.
So...
If you're up for the task...
I think I can handle it.
I never wanted you to leave.
I never wanted to go.
Dad...
Thank you for...
fighting for me.
SARAH, what are you doing?
That was such a beautiful moment,
I thought musical accompaniment
seemed appropriate.
Yeah, on second thought,
LA's not looking so bad.
Well, you're stuck with us now, so...
what do you say... burgers, Cafe Diem?
Sounds good.
Oh, SARAH, knock it off.
http://projet-sg.net