What he's trying to tell you
is that... I'm pregnant.
I have a new puzzle for you to solve.
This complex is massive.
- Prewar. What, late 30's?
- I believe.
It's before Eureka was built.
What's down there?
Ever since you got to this town,
you've been looking for something.
Tell me what's going on.
No.
- I have to what?
- Oversee the mayoral election.
This is the official polling place.
It's not a big deal, Carter.
- Well, now why can't Jo do it?
- Because Jo's not your lackey.
Well, the town charter says
that voting security
falls on the highest ranking
law enforcement officer.
That would be you.
Unless you promote me
or become otherwise incapacitated.
The Mayor's seat has been open
for over a year.
The town needs a voice.
This is a very important service card.
How important can it be?
I mean, my daughter's backing
her 17-year-old boyfriend for the job.
Eureka doesn't discriminate.
Some of our smartest citizens are teens.
So instead of working,
I have to sit here
and count ballots
for some doogie Mayor?
No, actually, your sister
volunteered for that job.
It's a bad idea.
Lex becomes really obsessed
with politics.
And her mood swings
are already out of hand.
Actually, she's really into it.
And you should be more sensitive.
- Your sister's pregnant.
- I'm Mr. Sensitive.
Like...
What... Paper ballots?
Digital voting machines
are way too easy to tamper with.
And campaigns get really competitive
around here.
Okay. I'll do it.
I'm... I'm...
- Thank you.
- Mr. Sensitive though.
Oh, my goodness.
What a beautiful baby.
Love that shirt.
There we go.
More Vinspresso?
Remember, vote Vincent.
Great. They love you!
I can't believe I let you talk me
into this. I hate politics.
We're the glue that holds
this town together, Vincent.
It's time we had a voice.
Smile.
- That's great, thanks.
- All right.
Now back to kissin' babies.
A vote for Lucas is a vote
for youthful innovation.
Oh, here's his ten point plan.
Kylie, can you help me pass out
some more buttons, please?
Then can we work on our lab project?
What's more important, Kylie,
homework or changing the world?
I don't know, Zoe.
- I've never been much of a leader.
- Which is why you have me.
That baby face of yours promises
idealism and hope
for all the minors of the town.
And I am going to help you deliver it.
- You mean manipulate it.
- Tomay-to. Tomah-to.
Sheriff Carter.
Halo Herrera.
Nephrologist, concerned citizen,
and future mayor of Eureka.
Well, you don't see
that combo platter everyday.
I'd like to talk
about your endorsement.
I'm getting coffee.
- Could...
- Not your lackey.
Well, I...
Mr. Herrera is it?
I would love to endorse somebody, but...
But he's already promised
his endorsement...
- To my candidate, right, Sheriff?
- Actually...
Eureka needs a mayor who understands
how a company town works.
Why? So your boss can have some Global
Dynamics puppet to sell out the town?
How many people
is Thorne gonna fire?
So Vincent is the best candidate,
he's all about nurturing the community.
Guys! I just want my coffee.
Vincent, get Sheriff Carter
a Vinspresso on the house.
It's already on the house
and bribery is a crime.
Yeah.
Nice try, Fargo.
Do we amuse you, Herrera?
Watch and learn, kids.
Folks, would everybody
follow me outside?
I have something
that will entertain and amaze you.
Okay. I'm done.
Now can we talk about our project?
I've got some damage control to do.
- Why don't you just get it started?
- But we're supposed to work together.
We will after you've shown me
what you've got.
- So you're letting me take lead?
- That's right.
Now get to work, partner.
Leave professional politics
to the professionals.
- Told you it gets competitive.
- That's just wrong.
- Big news, guys.
- Yeah, what's up?
Those ancient security cameras
we saw in the bunker,
I pulled the negatives before Thorne
locked the place up again.
It's 35 millimeter.
We just have to find someone
old enough to develop it.
What?
The latest next gen technology
Zane's been developing for our sponsor.
Overengineered to keep you cool
in the hottest situations.
It's amazing what the greatest minds
and a big old corporate check can buy.
Too bad we can't buy
the next mayoral election.
Just kidding, Allison.
I would, however,
like you to endorse Dr. Herrera.
Well, won't that be seen
as Global Dynamics taking sides?
Maybe. But on the other hand,
having someone to smooth
ruffled feathers during the next round
of cutbacks isn't a bad idea.
Well, I prefer to make up
my own mind.
You should also think
about what's best for Global.
We need a personal relationship
with the town.
One that shows
that we're all on the same team.
Are you and I on the same team, Eva?
Of course. I'd like to think
we're also friends.
Good.
So why don't you tell me
what's in the bunker under Tesla.
We found bariogenic radiation.
Zoe and her friends are very lucky
that they weren't infected.
That's why I'm ordering
a thermal cleaning
of the entire facility.
You realize you'll destroy
any organic material that's left inside.
Our first obligation is to the town.
Excuse me.
Make sure you vote.
This is Allison Blake.
I need some records from the archive.
What a time suck this is.
How did we live before digital?
I never knew you had
an artistic side, Carter.
I'm a man of many facets.
Check out the date stamp.
1939.
I thought Eureka wasn't
founded till 1950.
Well, it wasn't.
What were they doin' down there?
Well, whatever it was,
they tried to bury it for good.
Look who we have here.
- SARAH, lights.
- Certainly, Sheriff.
That was yesterday?
Thorne's been lookin' for somethin'
ever since she came to Eureka.
How much you wanna bet
it's in this room?
So what is she up to?
That's gonna have to wait till tomorrow.
The debate's about to start.
- You prepare your opening remarks?
- What opening remarks?
Hello. Hello.
Is this on?
Hi, everyone.
Welcome to debate night.
- I'm Sheriff Carter and I'll be...
- Cut to the chase!
We want issues, not filler!
Thank you, Lexi, for your wildly
inappropriate enthusiasm.
So without further ado,
I give you your candidates.
And if elected,
I'll bring the same principles
to the mayor's office
as I do to Café Diem.
In short, you want it, I got it!
I promise to bring a voice
to the pre-teen prodigy
that the establishment too often sees
as just another pretty brain.
Times are changing
and Eureka must change with it.
I will protect the tenets
on which this town was founded
and help usher in a new day
for Eureka.
It's a new day all right.
Season 3 Episode 7
Here Come the Suns (v 1.00)
Team Projet-SG.
http://projet-sg.net
Just another days in Eureka.
Well, it's a mini sun.
Really?
Took you all night
to come up with that?
No. It took us all night to rule out
any GD experiments as the cause.
- So now we have two suns.
- Just like Tatooine.
- Tatu-what?
- Geek speak.
The good news is it's stable holding
its position at about 1,000 feet.
We're not lighting the entire state.
The last thing we need is a spotlight
on the town the whole world can see.
Well, agree.
But it's 6:00 AM.
And 90 degrees.
How do we turn it off?
I'm not sure yet. It has to be
some kind of fusion reaction.
- Sounds dangerous.
- No, not necessarily.
Based on its containment,
I'd say it's deliberate.
Who'd want to make
a second sun on purpose?
Maybe the guy who was trying
to make a big bang at the debates.
Oh, cloud guy.
Herrera.
Eva wanted me to endorse him.
- Such a hidden agenda.
- What do you mean?
Zane found some security photos
of her sneaking around the facility.
- What's down there anyway?
- Well, nothing for long.
She ordered a thermal cleaning.
Can we stop it
till we get inside?
No, she's forbidden access.
The whole place is classified.
Something's goin' on.
You go talk to Herrera.
I'll look into it.
Yes, Allison Blake.
She asked for me?
Okay. I'm on my way.
- Hot enough for you?
- Yeah.
What's with the umbrellas?
He likes to be prepared?
Did that just come from inside?
That would be yes.
You changed your mind
about that endorsement?
Not really.
What is this?
This is the end to drought,
which we may be needing
sooner than later.
Welcome to my cloud farm.
Cloud farm?
Yeah, that's...
That's what he said.
I'm taking Cloud City to a whole
new level with nanotech hydration.
Cumulus, stratus, cirrus,
I can create 'em all.
Like you did with the cloud gag
yesterday.
Nice, huh?
I found a way to hydrogenically infuse
the atmosphere so I can sculpt clouds.
The commercial applications
are limitless.
Well, I'm more concerned
about your sun stunt.
Sun? No, no.
I'm a cloud guy. Not that I don't
mind the bump in the polling numbers.
People love a spectacle.
Yeah, but you have to admit
the timing was suspicious.
Have anyone from Global
come and review my record.
My life is an open book, Sheriff.
I'm beholden to my constituents.
Gotta admit, it's a hell of a show.
Zane.
Just the man I'm lookin' for.
Save your breath, Fargo.
I already know who I'm voting for.
I'm offended. You think I'm only here
to get your vote?
- You're not?
- No.
I also want a favor.
It is roasting out there.
A candidate has to project
cool confidence
under the most extreme conditions.
I hear you're beta testing something
that can help with staying cool.
- Yeah, I might be.
- Give me enough
to get through the election and if...
when Vincent wins,
I'll name a park bench after you.
Tempting, but no.
I don't do politics.
But good luck with that.
Based on these sun scans, I'd say your
competition's definitely heating up.
I was testing the voting machines
and I got dizzy.
I know you're not an OB.
Not really a fan
of western medicine.
- But I trust you.
- Well, I'm flattered.
I'm sure you have much bigger
issues to deal with.
Yes, and I have people
to deal with them.
So let's put your mind at ease.
So Carter says you've always
been interested in politics.
He said I'm obsessed, didn't he?
No.
Jack thinks the system is broken.
But I think it's up to us
to make the system work.
Well, this little guy's system
is working perfectly.
Here. Want to take a look?
It's amazing.
- What, is something wrong?
- I think I figured out
why your hormones are so
out of whack.
You're getting a double dose.
Lexi, you're having twins.
Both boys.
Two sons?
Two suns.
Why didn't I think of that?
- Because it's crazy.
- It's brilliant.
Lucas, I don't think you appreciate
what's at stake here.
I mean, the mayor's office
oversees City hall.
- So?
- So...
That includes the Sheriff's department.
You could be my dad's boss.
- And I thought he hated me now.
- It's time to step up our game.
When the world hands you suns,
make sunscreen.
Iced mocha, folks.
Stays cool as Vincent will be
when he takes the oath of office.
Suits? It's over
100 degrees out here.
Some candidates can handle the heat
better than others.
Nice gimmick.
We're just helping the voters
stay refreshed
so they can make a cogent decision
at the polling booth.
We're just trying to protect voters
from harmful UV rays
so they won't be blinded
by indecision.
- Iced mocha! Get it while it's cold.
- Sunscreen, people.
Vote lucas and say no
to premature aging.
Zoe, I've had a small issue
with our class project.
Bigger priorities at the moment, Kylie.
Here, grab a box.
No. I think this is something
you're really gonna want to see.
This better be good.
Okay, Fargo,
what's the big emergency?
The corruption
of the democratic process.
Everyone knows Herrera's
in Thorne's pocket.
And now she's harassing
my candidate. Look.
- What are you talking about?
- It's my wall of fame.
Thorne took it.
She redacted all the photos
of Eureka's founders.
She doesn't want the voters to see
how connected Vincent is
to this town's history.
- Why would she do that?
- Why?
Herrera checked out.
There's nothing in his background having
to do with solar energy or fusion power.
Great. So we got two suns
and no suspect.
And now apparently
no air conditioning.
Get anything off Herrera?
Other than a creepy politician vibe, no.
No, nothing.
- What did you find?
- Well, I ran some scans.
The sun has all the properties
of a main sequence dwarf star.
The big question
is its energy source.
Well, I might be able
to shed some light on that.
I ordered copies of all records
having to do with the hidden facility
under Tesla.
Now, of course, Eva's either
had them redacted or they don't exist.
But she forgot one thing.
Accounting.
Oh, somebody messed up
their lunch receipt.
The DOD keeps track
of every penny that they spent.
So I thought I'd see
where they were spending in 1939.
Check out the stuff
they were ordering.
Deuterium. Tritium.
These are heavy hydrogen atoms.
Yeah, and the essential elements
in building fusion bombs.
So Thorne dug up
an old bomb testing facility?
We gotta get into that room before
Thorne does her thermal cleaning thing.
To do what exactly?
To figure out whether something
down there is causing what's up here.
Hurry up.
It's over here.
Kylie, it's a billion degrees out.
I don't have time to play house.
Excuse me.
I'm nine and I'm a junior.
I don't play house.
Then what are we doing here?
Take a look.
Kylie, can you remind me
what our assignment was?
Build a working model
of the solar system.
Took that a bit literally, did you?
How'd you get all the planets
to orbit like that?
They are not the problem.
The sun's a little off.
We are so getting an "A".
One small issue.
I can't make it stop.
So we're not getting an "A"?
Yeah, not so much.
You know what, a controlled fusion
reaction like this takes real talent.
Well, it wasn't even that hard.
Take a gravitron field generator,
surround it in a little reactor plasma,
heat and serve.
Served up kind of a big helping,
don't you think?
Well, we're a little off
on the plasma density.
We? Oh no, no, no.
See, I didn't do this.
And I'm gonna need you
to resign from the campaign.
We can't afford the scandal.
Thanks for the support, partner.
Henry, I got a town
full of cranky people
who need some sleep.
You got any ideas?
Yeah, make it do
what it's supposed to do.
It should've started
to dissipate by now.
Well, it's... It's getting
some fuel from somewhere.
Chances are it'll burn itself out.
But in the meantime, I'm gonna go back
to my garage and research just how fast.
- Thanks. Let me know what you found.
- Can I come? I want to help.
I think you helped
enough already today, don't you?
I tell you what, you can take
atmospheric readings, okay?
Great.
So what convinced you?
Oh, Eva had all the old photos
removed from Café Diem.
Add that to the mass redaction
of old GD records...
And making Jo shut down
the Eureka museum.
And having me and Henry
dig up this place.
They're all windows
into Eureka's past.
Windows Thorne seems to want shut.
Let's find out why.
Focus on our constituents.
No swag for seniors. We're on a budget.
Hey, Kylie, look, about earlier.
- You mean when you sold me out?
- You made a second sun.
- You told me to take the lead.
- I was being nice.
Like all politicians,
you'll say whatever it takes
to get what you want.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have work to do.
The radiogenic detection field
reads negative for fusion products.
That good or bad?
It means we're not being radiated.
Rats.
That's definitely
a good thing, Carter.
No, I mean, literally.
Rats.
- You got somethin' you want to say?
- No.
Okay, come on.
Henry said that the second sun
was getting fuel from somewhere.
- Is it down here?
- Well, if it is, I'm not finding it.
Can't believe this place
has been under us all these years.
It's like a door into Eureka's past.
Look at this.
That's the door we saw
in the security photos.
All right,
- let's unlock it.
- My specialty.
So how long do you need?
This long.
These old school locks are no match
for a 20 zettahertz processor.
Okay.
This is a bit of a letdown.
Why order a thermal cleaning
of an empty room?
Good point.
Maybe it wasn't always empty.
Can I see the light scanner thingy?
One biotelemetric
dispersion scanner.
Yes. Okay. Coming up.
This baby reads patterns of movement
left behind by organic materials.
All right,
let's see who's been in here.
Look at that.
The dust layer means
that these prints are old.
But these high heels
are definitely new.
So are the military boots.
Looks like they were
moving stuff out.
Like what?
- Like them.
- Oh, my God.
- Are those...
- Bodies? Carter, hand me the scanner.
These bodies were removed
in the last 24 hours.
We have to find out who they were
and what they were doing down here.
And why Thorne
was trying to hide them.
This facility is classified
and scheduled for thermal cleaning.
Yet here you are
violating direct orders.
I'd except this kind
of insubordination from you, Sheriff.
- Thank you.
- But from you two...
I've always had a bit of trouble
with authority.
As far as I'm concerned,
this just became an active crime scene.
Oh, this is out
of your jurisdiction, Sheriff.
I'd be happy
to have the DOD remind you of that.
And I'd be happy to tell them why.
- You tryin' to bluff me?
- No, he's not, because he's leaving.
- We all are.
- No, actually.
- We're not.
- Carter, we crossed the line.
Let's not make it any worse.
- You sure about this?
- Sorry.
Okay.
- I can't believe Allison backed down.
- Yeah, me neither.
Now Thorne has all the evidence.
I wouldn't say
all the evidence.
I yanked the chip from the dispersion
scanner before they took my stuff.
We can see images
of everything we scanned.
Nice.
That's definitely not good.
Really?
Based on my initial data, it should've
burned itself out hours ago.
That doesn't look like
it's burning out.
It looks like it's getting hotter.
I'm melting.
It's midnight and 110 in the shade.
- People are getting pretty testy.
- Yeah, me included.
It reminds me of tornado weather.
I have a really bad feeling
about this.
Well, just keep everybody calm
and preferably indoors.
Roger that.
Kylie is gathering atmospheric data.
I should know something soon.
All right.
Zane's working on it too.
And in the meantime,
Thorne's wiping out
any evidence that connects
her to these bodies.
- Any idea who they were?
- I'm getting conflicting information.
How so?
From the surveillance photos,
their approximate age
is somewhere between 35 and 45
when they entered the room in 1939.
- All right. With you so far.
- The organic residue that you scanned
establishes that they also died
in 1939.
So they were buried there
for 70 years?
Yeah, here's
the really puzzling thing.
Common sense says they were
around 40 when they died.
But based on these readings, their
biological age is somewhere around 80.
I want someone posted outside
that facility at all times.
Nobody comes in
until after the thermal cleaning.
Let's get the bodies
ready for transport.
Transport?
To where?
I'm afraid it's classified information,
Allison, as is everything in this room.
And I'd really appreciate it
if you leave now.
You said that you considered
us to be friends. I do too.
So why don't you just tell me
who those men are?
I know what it looks like
from where you stand,
but it's not what you think.
These were good men
who gave their lives for this town.
And it could've been prevented.
You make it sound
as if you knew them.
It's time for you to go now.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because I have to.
Dr. Deacon, there's something
I think you're really gonna want to see.
Well, please tell me
you didn't make another sun.
No, I've been trying to figure out
how to extinguish the first one.
- You mean the second one.
- Semantics? Really, Sheriff?
Could we just...
Kylie, what did you find?
Well, I've been doing
readings all over town
and the upper air is saturated
with excess hydrogen.
- Is that bad?
- Well, not by itself.
But mixed with Kylie's project, hydrogen
could cause a whopping fusion reaction.
Well, how whopping are we talking?
Well, depending on the source
and how much is left, big.
Look, I don't know
where this hydrogen is coming from,
but I promise I didn't do it.
That's okay.
I have a pretty good idea who did.
There's no way
my clouds caused this.
Well, it's not the clouds themselves.
It's what's inside of them.
- It's a whole lot of hydrogen, right?
- Well, not that much.
Maybe 1,000 liters at standard
temperature and pressure.
Well, you've been outside.
It's plenty.
How was I supposed to know someone'd
be creating a stellar fusion reaction?
Hello. You live in Eureka.
I guess this means
I won't be getting your endorsement.
Well, it's...
Just stick to the problem.
Is this how you deliver
the nanos to make your clouds?
Yep. A single stage booster
that fuels the cold accelerant
mixer for better saturation
and heat dispersion.
- Nice.
- We gotta fix this.
Can you reverse it?
You mean exsanguinate the excess
hydrogen from Eureka's lower atmosphere?
- Yes.
- No.
I mean, I can make any shape
you want,
but once the clouds have seeded,
natural hydration processes take over.
I say we enjoy the extra sunlight
while we can.
It'll burn itself out soon enough.
You were saying?
It should've extinguished itself.
But it didn't.
That's because Kylie's sun...
Ingenious though it is...
has evolved from a dwarf star and
is developing into a red super giant.
- Which means?
- Instead of burning out,
it's blowing up big time.
Not my fault entirely.
It's not stopping there.
The sun flares are just the beginning.
And we only have a few hours
before it goes critical.
Okay, what are our options?
If we can
launch a dispersion module,
a concentration of iron atoms
fired directly into the sun's core
- should cause it to implode.
- And imploding's a good thing?
Yes. Once the sun's incapable of fusion
reaction, then, we'll all be safe.
What if it doesn't work?
We all get front row seats to
a supernova way bigger than Hiroshima.
And Eureka becomes
a mile deep crater.
That's too risky.
We need to evacuate now.
Y... Jo's already started.
But this is also the most advanced
research complex on the planet
and we have an opportunity to save it.
And I'm already developing
a compound to trigger the implosion.
- And I'm working on a delivery system.
- Towns can be rebuilt. People can't.
Which is why we're evacuating the people
while we're trying to save the town.
You might be comfortable
risking lives, but I'm not.
Make sure everybody gets out
while there's time.
Eva, we have a chance
to save decades of research.
That wasn't a request.
It's like she wants to see the place
go up in flames.
I think she might.
Well, what now?
Let's go, people!
Move! Move!
Shuttles are waiting outside.
Let's go!
You know what, after the election,
we'll have the influence around.
- Maybe I can up your pay rate.
- Don't make me use the stun gun.
You heard her, Fargo.
Keep moving. Everybody move.
But we're just making sure
his constituents are safely away first.
How come you two aren't drenched
like the rest of us?
Oh, a worthy candidate is always
cool under pressure, Sheriff.
And it's classified.
However, I could be convinced
to share my secret for, say,
your endorsement.
This is mine.
Both of you on the bus.
Go. Go!
Everybody move! Keep goin'!
Sounds like we're using sunscreen
to beat injustice.
- Just smile and look pretty.
- Zo, what are you doin'?
You gotta go.
Guys, please.
Not yet. Latest election polls
only show Lucas down by two points.
You wanna score points with the voters
or with your girlfriend's old man?
No contest, sir.
- That'll work.
- Vote Lucas!
All right, everybody's cleared out.
Any luck?
- We're locked and loaded, Sheriff.
- XRT online and ready.
It'll take two people to get
the module in position for launch.
I can do that.
- I can do that on my own.
- No. I'll go with you.
No. I'll go with you.
I know this baby best.
Okay. All right.
You three get to an evacuation site.
- Nice work.
- Thanks.
- Be careful.
Could you keep an eye
on Lex and Zoe?
Of course.
Just come back safely.
Thanks.
We're at a safe distance from town.
We can move everyone quickly
if we need to, but with...
ten evac camps for 2,600 people.
Things are gonna get crowded.
How are you feelin'?
I just wish someone
would do something about the heat.
I hear your pain.
This town needs a Mayor
who can be cool in a crisis.
And if I'm elected,
I promise I won't sleep
until darkness falls again
on Eureka.
Oh, please.
You don't need stale
campaign promises.
You need ideas that are fresh
as baked bread,
which by the way,
Vincent also provides twice daily.
Say no to half-baked science
and overbaked bread.
- Lucas is your man.
- Can't bake his way out of a paper bag.
- Like cloud makers...
- What is wrong with all of you?
Eureka was founded
to protect the greater good.
You're worried about votes.
You should be worried about lives.
You cannot be a leader
if there is no town to lead.
So I suggest you get
your priorities straight.
That was beautiful.
Having fun yet?
Driving headlong into a fiery death
is everybody's idea of a good time.
Sometimes I think it's his.
Carter, could we have a minute?
Sure.
Jo, you're supposed to be miles away
at an evac camp by now.
I should risk my life more often.
I prefer you didn't.
Come on, Josefina,
don't go all serious on me now.
It's too late.
- I thought we agreed to evacuate.
- We did. What are you still doing here?
None of your business.
Don't play games.
I'm not.
I think Zane's device is gonna work.
- Probably.
- If you don't die first.
That is part of the job.
And the men in that bunker
would know that.
Whatever it is you think you know
about what you found or about me,
it's wrong.
Maybe.
But I'm just gettin' started.
If there's one thing I learned in life
is that nobody should be left behind,
no matter what the reason.
And that includes you.
I'm duty bound
to enforce this evacuation.
Jo, make sure
she gets out of town safely.
And no, that's not a request.
That looks pretty bad.
You sure the rocket can handle it?
An untested delivery system
aimed at an out of control mini sun.
What could go wrong?
Ready?
It's fried.
I'll call Allison.
Okay, Carter, what's wrong?
Zane's module. Electronics are fried.
Do you have any spares lying around?
GD has plenty
of short range booster assemblies.
We just need to adapt them
to the XRT's specifications.
- We'll never make it back in time.
- There is another way.
Dr. Herrera's hydrogen seeding device.
It uses similar boosters to the XRT.
But my greenhouse is too close
to that sun.
And there's no way
they'll ever survive the heat.
Well, hold on.
Maybe there is.
- What are you thinking?
- Well, like Fargo said earlier.
We just need to stay cool
under pressure.
I've been workin' on
this heat protection formula for weeks.
- Sure that'll work?
- It's a prototype.
But it's overengineered to respond
to increased body heat and adrenaline.
Takin' on a supernova
so we should have plenty of both.
All you gotta do is slather it on.
We should have a good 10,
maybe 15 minutes
before we combust.
Fantastic.
That's gettin' worst.
- Then why are you slowin' down?
- I'm not.
You smell burning rubber?
Gonna have to run for it.
Dude, it's like 2 zillion degrees
out there.
- Okay, I'm game.
- You do anything normal for fun?
I play a wicked game of yahtzee.
Put that gel on thick
if you know what's good for ya.
You ready?
I feel like a lobster in here.
Temp's climbing.
If we stay long, we'll boil.
Find that rocket.
- It might help if I could see anything.
- Keep looking!
Got it! Got it!
Yep! Right!
This way.
And...
set.
We only get one shot at this.
I don't wanna miss.
Using GPS to target?
- I was gonna eyeball it.
- Oh, stellar.
Whatever happens, it's been fun.
No, it hasn't.
Push the button.
Take a look at that.
That is quite a sunset.
So you managed to pull it off.
You sound disappointed.
Someone cancelled the thermal cleaning.
I wonder who.
You may have the backing of the DOD,
but these people still work for me.
- And you work for me.
- Not without an explanation.
- Those bodies...
- Are my concern.
You're asking me to trust you,
but you're giving me nothing.
Well, I'll give you some advice.
History has a way of haunting you
no matter how far you run.
This is mine and I'm putting it to rest.
So you stay out of my way.
Listen, whoever wins,
it was nice doing battle with you.
After all this,
I don't even care who wins anymore.
- As long as one of us buries that guy.
- Amen to that.
Hey, partner.
Thanks for the save.
Fiery death not popular with voters.
I caused it.
It's the least I could do.
My fault too.
I got so caught up in everything
when I should've been helping you.
- This time I'll make it up to you.
- This time?
Well, we have to make a new model.
And someone should make sure
I don't destroy the universe. So...
Partners?
- Glad to see you're okay.
- Me too.
- Look, about before...
- It's cool, Jo.
It was a crisis.
You were caught up in the moment.
No, I wasn't.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Way to go, Sheriff.
So how's the...
Itchy.
Hope that means it's healing well.
Listen, what...
you and Zane did
was a brave... mythic.
Maybe selfish.
- I'm growing attached to the town.
- This town,
is fortunate to have you
to protect it.
- I'm just doin' my job.
- And... Thorne?
I'm workin' on it.
May I have your attention, please?
'scuse me.
Everyone, can I have
your attention, please?
Everyone.
Quiet!
Thank you.
All the ballots are in.
It was a very close race.
But after a late night surge
at the polling booths,
our new mayor elect is...
Mr. Henry Deacon.
Seriously?
No, wait.
I wasn't even on the ballot.
I kinda started a write-in campaign.
And someone gave you
their official endorsement.
You're welcome.
I don't know...
- What to say.
- Say that you'll take the job
because Zoe's boyfriend
is the runner up.
Clearly this is a surprise.
I'm not one for making
campaign promises.
But I will say this.
What makes Eureka special
is not the ideal behind it,
but you. This community.
This family
that I'm very proud to be a part of.
And it's this family
that I promise to protect
no matter what.
Thank you.
See.
Sometimes the system does work.