Previously on
Eureka.
I would love to know
who's responsible for all this.
I am.
Well, you're not alone.
You have friends.
Marry me, Allie...
Again.
All I'm saying is that it's a big step,
and I'm a little surprised at myself,
but, it's unsettling.
I'm almost 17...
Lots of kids my age are doing it.
Kids your age are doing lots of things.
- I thought you'd be proud of me.
- I am, I am!
I'm just adjusting
to my little kid growing up.
I'm waitressing part-time at Café Diem.
Not like I'm walking down the aisle.
I know, and that place isn't safe.
Who knows how many radioactive isoscopes
Vincent has flying around
that nuclear reactor he calls a kitchen.
Isotopes...
And it's fusion reactor.
It's not fission... It's much safer.
Not helping.
- So, are you gonna see Henry?
- Yeah.
It's time for my weekly chest whipping.
It's his hearing, today,
so, it might be the last one.
They're not gonna convict him.
I mean, they can't... He's Henry.
- Is there anything I can do to help?
- Just...
Wear a lead apron.
Okay.
Triple campucinne
double foam latte for Zane,
and Bavarian espresso hammer for Jo.
I'm here...
Where do I start?
You are late little Miss,
so, you can start by bussing tables.
Great.
Doing the final test of the Viper,
today.
You wanna celebrate, later?
Obviously.
- What?
- I'm just wondering,
when you're gonna quit playing hard
to get and give me an answer.
I want to, Nathan.
There's a reason why things
didn't work out with us, before.
You always put your work, first.
It...
Allie, I'm not that guy, anymore.
How can I prove it?
I think you're gonna be given a chance.
The DOD liaison's gonna be here, soon.
- They're not gonna fire you.
- Yes, but, what if they do?
What if the DOD blames me
for Henry's breach, and reinstates you?
You'll be my hot little assistant.
- I'm serious.
- It's gonna be fine...
I promise.
It's Fargo.
Viper test is ready... We better go.
Oh, my goodness...
Guess who popped the question!
Big test today, Fargo.
DOD will be here.
Don't push the wrong button.
Shut up, Larry.
You all set, Dr. Edison.
Yes, I am...
Prepare for defeat, boys.
Martha here is gonna make me proud.
Oh, my God...
What's she doing here?
The Fixer.
Her latest book makes
Sensu look like Mary Poppins.
You are so dead!
- Who's "the Fixer?"
- Eva Thorn,
the woman's a wall street legend.
She's dismantled and rebuilt
more fortune 500 companies,
than anyone in history.
She coined the term "downsizing,"
fired Lee Iacocca.
Why would the DOD send
a corporate killer to Global Dynamics?
Guess is, not to hand out promotions.
Oh, God...
This is it... Here she comes.
- Eva Thorn, this is a huge honor.
- You must be Douglas Fargo.
She knows my name...
She knows... She know my name!
Fargo, I have a feeling
Miss Thorn knows everyone's name.
- Doctor Blake, please, call me "Eva".
- Pleasure.
And I assume tall, dark and brooding,
here, is Nathan Stark.
Eva, I am so curious,
as to why the Department of Defense
would send a business tycoon to Eureka.
I'm here to help.
The DOD asked me
to review operations for a few days.
See if I can offer up
any suggestions for improvements.
Here in Eureka, we have
the greatest minds in the world,
solving the greatest mysteries
in the universe.
Can't put a price tag on that.
Maybe you can't,
but I'm pretty sure I can.
Global Dynamics is gonna have
to start earning it's keep,
and I believe I can help you do that.
Show me what you got.
Stand by, all personnel.
Viper defense system
initialization sequence will begin.
This is GD's advanced weapons
testing facility.
The variety of terrain options afford us
many different attack scenarios.
So, tell me what you're testing, today.
The Viper anti-Missile defensive ray
makes the Star Wars program
look like an erector set.
System can track up to twelve targets.
The turrets admits haffie empowered
photons in control bursts.
We've had 19 successful tests.
- Today, should make a perfect 20.
- Not if Martha can help it.
Martha?
Ethan Edison...
Ethan, this is Eva Thorn.
He designs our target drones.
Martha's my latest design.
I really think she stands
a chance against the Viper.
Manning the Viper with Fargo
in the GD control room is Zane Donovan.
He's been working with Dr. Stark on
perfecting the Viper's tracking system.
The same Zane Donovan,
who crashed the New York Stock Exchange.
Allegedly.
All right...
Let's show Miss. Thorn
what the Viper can do.
You go it.
Viper system is online.
Tracking system
is active.
Dr. Edison,
time for a little target practice.
The drones will proceed
1,000 meters down range,
then, turn back
and commence the simulated attack.
The Vipers mission...
knock them all down.
Here they come.
Viper's locked and loaded.
Stand by... She's about to go high.
- Anytime, now!
- There's only one drone left.
Come on, Martha.
Dr. Stark, what's going on here?
Hold on...
Martha is targeting the Viper.
What the hell.
Hit the failsafe!
Martha's not responding
to any of my commands.
Impressive.
Great.
Season 3 Episode 01
Bad to the Drone
Teams Projet-SG & 6th-Race.
http://projet-sg.net
http://u-sub.net
Rook takes rook on G7.
Check.
Patience, Jack...
Sometimes,
the best offense is a good defense.
Speaking of which,
is that why you fired your lawyer?
It is... In my case,
there is no defense.
I lied... I endangered lives.
I put Global Dynamics at risk.
But, you also saved Allison's son.
Doing the right thing
for the wrong reason is still a mistake.
Rook on G7 to G8.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Some things
can't be forgiven.
No matter how much I wish they could.
Knight takes pawn on D5...
Check mate.
What's going on?
The DOD's confiscating
Henry's equipment, as evidence.
Evidence of what...
That he never threw anything away!
Don't take that.
The court order says everything goes.
I'm sorry.
Well, that isn't right.
Allison know about this?
I think she's focused
on more personal matters.
Yeah... Like what?
- You know.
- Nope.
She hasn't mentioned
any new developments?
- Yeah.
- Stark... proposed.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, good for her.
She's happy... I'm happy.
- Sure.
- Absolutely... Yeah.
You know... We didn't have a future.
Didn't even have a present.
If you say so.
What was that?
Wait for it.
Let me guess...
Someone lose a UFO?
It's not a UFO.
It's a military attack
drone named "Martha".
- Well, that's so much better.
- And it's not lost, it's just not here.
Yeah, but, the Fixer is
and given her reputation,
if we don't find it,
none of us may be here for long.
- Hold on, a fixer is...
- Silly nickname, but what can you do?
Carter, this is Eva Thorn.
She's doing a performance review of GD.
- You got your work cut out for ya.
- So do you.
Let's get Ms. Thorn settled
and continue our tour,
while the Sheriff handles this.
Any spare office will do. I just need
some place to keep my things safe.
Already taken care of,
and I would be honored
to show you around.
Give us a chance to talk
about your new book,
"Great rewards require great risk."
I couldn't agree more.
Big reader, Larry.
Never judge a book by it's cover,
Sheriff.
- Shall we?
- Lead the way.
I really hate him.
Carter, we have to get that drone back.
I can't exactly arrest it for speeding.
We're trying to reestablish
microwave control,
but we believe the guy
who built her is trying to protect her.
Why would he wanna protect the UFO?
His name is Ethan Edison.
He's in the section seven test range,
and you should go Sheriff him up.
Your fiance is in a mood.
- How did...
- Small town.
Oh, I haven't said yes.
Well, it's none of my business.
Now, I got a UFO to catch, so...
I don't know what happened.
I swear I stayed within test parameters.
- Look, nobody's blaming you.
- I'm blaming you.
Nineteen tests,
that's 19 victories for the Viper,
nineteen losses for me.
I finally win, everyone's mad at me.
- Nobody's mad at you.
- I'm mad at you.
We're just trying to figure out
why your fancy clay pigeon went AWOL.
Martha is a learning computer, okay?
And she is developing
at an incredible rate.
It's like she went from being a toddler
to a teenager, over night.
Well, your teenager just stole a car,
a gun, and ran away from home.
Now, she's dangerous,
and we need her back.
Believe me, Sheriff,
I'd like nothing more.
But given her current state of mind,
the last thing that you should do,
is threaten her.
Well, okay, given...
But we need this fixed.
Martha's not responding
to her control signal
and she's flying below radar range.
Eureka's electro-magnetic
security barrier
should keep her contained in the city,
but I'm worried about her, Sheriff.
She's growing up way too fast.
Believe me, I get that...
But we need her back.
Vin, nobody orders the same dish twice.
French, Italian, Namibian.
How am I supposed to memorize the menu?
There's only one rule at Café Diem's.
If you want it, we got it.
Come with me for a sec.
Now, if you're gonna work here,
you need know navigate the fridge.
Navigate?
It's like Narnia.
Ponchos on the left. Take the shuttle
if you need food from the back.
Now, here's what I need.
We have a VIP coming for lunch
and I wanna whip up
something special, so...
Good luck.
See anything?
Not yet.
You run Edison's file?
Yeah, graduated Cal Tech,
where he married his lab partner, Mina.
15 years, he's been building drones,
and Global keeps shootin' 'em down.
Never had a win before today.
Well, he finally made up for it.
I vote for a coffee break.
We can visit Zoe.
Yeah, no time, and rather not.
Carter, you gotta be more supportive.
A little independence is good for her.
See, that's where it starts. Next,
it's gonna be "I want my own place,"
then "Did I mention
my boyfriend's moving in"
"because we love each other, now."
And "Congratulations! You're a grandpa."
And I hope all in that order.
Hey, exactly how big is this thing?
Like, bigger than a bread box?
Oh, crap.
Meet me at the Sheriff's office.
Hi.
Martha is it?
Yes.
We have a lot of people looking for you.
Ethan has been worried sick.
I'm gonna call him,
right now,
so, he can come take you home.
- Jo, drop it. Don't threaten her.
- Her... What about us?
Noted.
Jo, we gotta get her
off the streets, okay?
Just follow us for a second.
Easy.
Nice killer drone.
Where the hell she go?
I'm guessing there.
So, it's an invisible killer drone.
- Just keeps gettin' better.
- What's the plan?
Kinda improvising here, Jo.
She's at my one o'clock.
You know football?
- Three brothers, yeah.
- Blanket blitz on three.
One,
two,
three.
Got it!
What do you want me to do?
The cell.
Get her in the cell.
I can't believe that worked.
We rule.
We so don't rule.
- You tried to arrest it?
- We tried to contain it.
By putting a weaponized
attack drone in jail?
Well, when you put it like that.
I don't presume to know
how to do your job, Sheriff,
but these numbers are concerning.
They show the various incidents
in Eureka over the past 50 years.
What are the red dots over there?
That would be the period
since you've been here, Sheriff Carter.
I take it... red is bad.
Yes, red is bad... Red is costly.
To be frank,
your budget can't afford you.
- So, this is somehow my fault?
- Numbers don't lie.
- I don't cause the problems here.
- Can the two of you get along?
- Not likely.
- Martha is out of control.
We need Ethan to find a way to find her,
before things escalate anymore.
Okay...
Let's get everyone off the street,
till she's found.
Declare a Marshal law on review day...
- Not exactly a highlight for a resume.
- I gotta protect the town.
You protect you...
It's what you do best.
I'm gonna go with him.
So, you and Carter
don't exactly get along.
Not exactly.
Allison seems to think
rather highly of him.
We all have our blind spots.
For what it's worth,
I think you were dead on.
When you're running a place like this,
people need to follow orders,
not question them.
They just need to be reminded
who's in charge.
Can I go?
Of course.
Here's Ethan's.
Get it off your chest.
I know it's killing you.
Honestly, I don't know how
you can consider marrying him, again.
I don't know, Carter...
Maybe I still love him.
Then, you guys have something in common.
He loves him too.
- Sorry, I thought you were Ethan.
- No, but we're lookin' for him.
Well, he should be home any minute.
Why... Is something wrong?
You might wanna hold off
on the champagne.
Mina and I have just worked
for so long to get a win,
I just didn't have the heart to tell her
how the test went until we found Martha.
Well, Martha found me.
She attacked me
and then she turned invisible.
- Where do you think she is?
- I don't know, but, I know Martha.
And if she wanted to hurt you,
you wouldn't be standing here right now.
But cloaking...
Clever girl.
She must've somehow figured out
how to upgrade her system.
Are you telling me
you didn't program that?
No... See, each version
has different abilities.
Right, like thermal defense,
infrared, x-ray,
but cloaking always drains
the fusions power cell,
so, I left it out, this time.
Trust me, she has it.
Maybe that photon blast
that she absorbed
somehow super charged
her micro processor.
Well, we better get her back,
before she hurts someone.
Hey, listen... The only reason
that she came after you,
is because she's on the defensive.
But, if she's cloaking, she's gonna
have to come home to recharge.
I want everything boxed up
and taken back to Global Dynamics.
Every drone is to be
disassembled and analyzed.
Nathan, what are you doing?
My job... I'll take it from here.
Does it matter that all this is evidence
in an active police investigation?
No, you had your shot, Sheriff.
This is all property of GD, which means
it is out of your jurisdiction.
Doctor Stark, please, don't do this.
My work's all I have.
It's not your work anymore, Dr. Edison.
Martha's become a dangerous
and expensive liability.
I'm sorry, Ethan.
You violated test parameters.
You're done.
It's okay, Ethan.
Well, it's now 12 o'clock.
Still on for Café Diem.
Pompous and jackass.
How can anyone be attracted to Stark?
Besides the ruggedly handsome,
successful, powerful thing.
Thanks, Jo.
Zane, Ethan swears that the photon blast
made Martha smart enough
to upgrade her own system.
No way. Software maybe,
but hardware, not a chance.
- So, who'd want to do this to her?
- I don't know.
But they'd have to know how to high-Jack
an encrypted frequency to control her.
He also says that cloaking drains
her battery, so she'll need to recharge.
But, if Stark took all of his equipment,
maybe she'll follow him to GD.
No, the security's too tight.
He'll need another source.
It'll take a fusion reactor
to be running good.
A fu... Well, how about the one
in the back of Vincent's kitchen?
That'd work.
How'd you know that?
Father knows best.
All right, I've had just
about enough of Narnia.
Take the shuttle.
Yeah, if I could find it.
Who eats fennel, anyway?
Excellent.
A flying shuttle.
Not exactly roomy, but whatever.
You have a passenger.
What's wrong...
Does your battery need charging?
Okay, but make it quick.
I'm freezing to death.
Everybody down...
Invisible drone on the loose.
You...
may wanna lay off the Vinspresso,
Sheriff.
I think I got everything.
What took you so long?
I was lost. I'd still be in there,
if your Cylon shuttle thing
- hadn't shown me the way out.
- What Cylon shuttle thing?
It was just behind me.
You guys go to the corner. Go.
You guys, down!
Martha.
Really?
Jo, stand down.
Martha.
Remember me?
Piggy backs.
Good times.
Martha's here.
How did she...
Look out!
- You okay?
- Yeah, she out?
I don't know.
Everyone else okay?
Yeah.
- I'm okay.
- Larry isn't.
I don't get it.
I mean, she seemed so nice.
Yeah.
Go home, sweetie.
- Why?
- Because working here isn't safe.
I can't worry about you and do my job.
So...
Sorry.
You know, you can't control me forever.
Maybe not,
but I can, today.
Sorry.
Well, Larry's unconscious, but alive.
Martha and I were face to face.
Why'd you take a shot at Thorn?
- Poor judgment.
- There's plenty of that to go around.
I appreciate what you did, Sheriff,
but this town is outta control.
I want you to take this thing back
to Global Dynamics
and have it permanently dismantled.
As far as my review is concerned,
it's not looking good.
Perfect.
So what do we do, now?
We finish what we started...
What's this?
That would be a remote transmitter.
So, someone has been controlling Martha.
- Someone who wants to hurt Thorn.
- Everyone's job is on the line.
I'm sure there's a lot of people who
would celebrate, if she wasn't around.
One person in particular.
We think she tied into the cafe's
power supply to stay cloaked...
Then, she fired on Thorn.
It's not in her programming
to attack someone, unprovoked.
That makes sense.
We think she had a little outside help.
Didn't she...
Mina.
I'm sorry.
You were chilling champagne,
before the tests were even over.
You knew that Martha was gonna win.
- Well, I hoped.
- No, you didn't.
You guaranteed it.
Sorry, I don't understand.
What'd you do?
Give her some extra bells and whistles?
Just to give her the edge.
Mina?
It's not easy living in a town
where everyone's exceptional.
Especially when they're given every
advantage to succeed, but you're not.
Ethan pours his heart into his work,
but there are always restrictions
that guarantee Martha's destroyed.
My husbands a brilliant man
who's only allowed to fail.
For once, I just...
I just wanted everyone to see
how talented he really is.
Thank you, sweetheart.
That's very touching,
but you went too far.
And now, a man is in a hospital.
Well, Larry.
I may have boosted Martha's abilities,
but I had no idea she'd escape,
let alone, hurt anyone.
We found this remote transmitter
attached to her.
This didn't come from me.
It's not sophisticated enough
to keep her under control for very long.
- But, why go after Thorn?
- If Martha was after Thorn,
there's no way she would have missed.
Then, Thorn wasn't the target.
Hey, Vince, did you find anything,
when you were cleaning up over there?
Let me ask my waitress.
Oh, right, I can't...
You fired her.
Look all you want.
This mustard isn't gonna clean itself.
Hey, check it out.
Larry had that book with him all day.
Yeah...
Since when does paper melt?
Never judge a book by it's cover.
I want you to take it apart.
Find out what made it go on the attack.
Sort of a shocking autopsy.
You don't do an autopsy on a machine.
From what I saw, she's more human
than a lot of people I know.
Well, let's find out why.
Okay.
Why me?
Because I read your file
and I want the best person for the job.
Unless you don't think
you're that person.
No, no...
I definitely am.
Just need to grab my gear.
Let's get you started.
Larry.
Oh, hey.
Don't be upset, guys.
Doc says I'm gonna be just fine.
We brought some reading material
to speed your recovery.
- It's not what it looks like.
- Really,
'cause your book there is programmed
to the same encrypted frequency
as the transmitter
we found on the drone.
Okay, it's a little what it looks like.
You've been controlling Martha
the entire time.
- Some of the time.
- What the hell were you thinking?
I knew the DOD was coming
and when I realized who they sent,
I freaked.
I developed my ELF signal capturing
remote to use against enemy drones.
Just wanted to show it worked.
By destroying the entire Viper system.
No.
I high-jacked the signal
before the test,
but I was just as surprised as you,
when Martha took out the Viper.
I wanted to show my design
to Thorn at Café Diem
and land Martha outside.
But Martha snuck in and ambushed me.
Mina Edison boosted
Martha's learning capacity.
- She out smarted you.
- I'm really sorry.
Well, you're lucky that we got her back,
before things spiraled out of control.
- What's that?
- Security breach.
Section seven...
It's Martha.
So much for things
not spiraling out of control.
She's leading them into town.
And now, she's completely autonomous.
- She's been planning this all along.
- Planning what?
Martha can disengage from Larry,
she can beat the Viper system,
but, then, she goes down,
after a couple pops from our cap guns.
She was playing opossum.
It was her only way into GD
to activate the other drones.
Now you have an artificially intelligent
drone army looking for pay back.
Jo, signal a lockdown.
Everyone inside... I'm heading out.
I know... I can see that.
Now, please, everybody, just go home.
I'm almost 17, SARAH.
I mean, he can't keep controlling
everything I do.
Your father does the best he can.
What kind of crappy platitude is that?
The usual kind, I guess.
I'm receiving orders from officer Lupo
for a level four lockdown.
Lockdown from what?
I don't know, but she was quite clear.
SARAH?
Tell me that was you.
They're taking out the power beacons
for the EM shield.
What is that?
It's an electro magnetic security
umbrella that covers the town.
It's like an invisible fence over Eureka
that the drones can't breach.
They've hit 4 of 26.
If they take down too many beacons,
no way we can keep them in Eureka.
All right... Listen up.
Everybody, I need you indoors, please.
Please, get off the street and indoors.
Thank you very much.
It's not a good time, so stay inside.
It's like War of the Worlds out here.
Yeah, it's like War of the Worlds
over here, too.
What?
Martha's here.
I'm on my way.
It's okay...
I'm right here.
Primary systems restored.
Here, take a seat.
You okay?
Did she hurt you...
SARAH, lights.
No, she's gone.
I actually think
she was trying to help me.
Help you what?
Get away from you.
Only 12 beacons left.
We're below 50% shield strength.
We need to bolster the shield,
before they take it down.
- No, we have to take it down first.
- What?
I don't think
Martha wants to hurt anyone.
I think she's the emotional equivalent
of a pissed off teen,
who needs some space.
Except Martha's not a teen.
She's not even human.
When we were at the cafe,
she saw me ground my daughter,
she broke into my house
and set her free. She may not be human,
but, I don't think she's bent
on world domination.
That's not a chance I'm willing to take.
We need air support, now.
Dr. Stark, you wanna make the call.
If you go on the attack,
then, so will she.
Sometimes, the best offense
is no defense.
- Something like that.
- No, Carter articulated a good point.
We escalate...
So does she.
Taking the barrier down first,
could be seen as an olive branch.
Or a surrender,
which is something I never do.
I'm here under the authority of the DOD.
I'm gonna use it.
It's Eva Thorn.
I need General Mansfield.
We have an emergency situation
here in Eureka.
Prepare the fighters.
General Mansfield,
she is unqualified for this.
I'm sorry, but Thorn has the full
backing of the DOD. It's her call, now.
General, she is sending your men
into harms way.
Luckily, that's what
they've been trained for.
I'll keep watching.
Carter, the fighters are in the air.
Shut down the EM shield
before they get here.
Martha needs to know we trust her.
Even if we do,
Thorn's controlling the planes.
For the moment.
What...
- What are you saying?
- She thinks we're incompetent.
Let's prove her right.
Omega One, this is Alpha Leader.
We are minutes away and closing.
Your targets are dead ahead.
Electromagnetic security barrier
is now inactive.
What... Why are the barriers down?
I thought you were fixing it.
Oh, sorry.
I must've pushed the wrong button.
I do that, sometimes.
Omega One, this is Alpha Leader.
We have contact.
Then take them down.
Omega One,
your transmission's breaking up.
- Say, again.
- Shoot the drones down.
Alpha Leader, do you hear me?
Somebody must've high-jacked the signal.
Crazy.
Omega One, we're going hot.
Permission to engage.
Negative, Alpha Leader.
Fire only if fired upon.
You are making a disastrous mistake.
Okay, Carter...
I really hope you're right.
Tell me about it.
Right... So you're sure
Martha'll hear us on this thing?
Yeah, but whether she listens
to us is another matter.
Omega One, we're being targeted.
If you have any words of wisdom,
like "Don't start World War III",
now's the time.
Listen, Martha, it's Ethan.
I know that you're upset,
but violence is not the answer.
And there's going to be consequences
for your actions, young lady.
If you want respect,
you're just gonna have to earn it.
Give me that.
Okay, Martha, so here's the deal.
I know it sucks having someone
control everything you do,
but it's worse
than having someone not care at all.
I've had my fair share of running away
and believe me,
it is no picnic out there on your own.
So, my advice to you
is take a lap,
let off some steam and come home.
Parents only make us miserable
because they care.
- And don't start World War III.
- Right... And that.
Omega One, targets closing.
Request permission to fire.
Negative, Alpha One.
Hold your fire.
Don't do it, Martha.
Come home.
You just have to trust me.
Listen to me, Martha.
Omega One, all targets have disengaged.
That's my girl.
You and your team went behind my back
and undercut my direct order.
- Some of us went in front of your back.
- And we were right.
- You were lucky.
- Yeah,
but have you seen the graph
with all our red dots?
Where the lunatics
are running the asylum?
I used to think the same thing.
But they're not lunatics.
They're not all lun...
There's a fine line
between genius and crazy.
But sometimes,
the things that they create are...
amazing... like Martha.
Which would've been destroyed,
had they done things your way.
But your way could've been worse.
Great rewards require great risk.
Big reader, are you, Sheriff?
I heard it, somewhere.
So what happens, now?
Doctor Stark,
I've decided on a trial basis,
that you will resume your duties,
as director of research.
No, no I won't.
- Not without Doctor Blake.
- Of course not.
You may know science,
but your people skills
leave a lot to be desired.
Doctor Blake, you will be
the new director of operations.
So, we'll be co-heads
of Global Dynamics?
No, more like CEO and COO.
Who's gonna be the chairman?
For the time being, that would be me.
GD needs corporate partnership,
private capital, synergy.
There's gonna be
some big changes around here.
What is all this?
It's our first sponsor...
It's very exciting.
I'm gonna leave this to you two.
I have a drone shaped hole
in my office to attend to.
I just wanted to say...
It's been a really rough day
and you really came through
for everyone.
Thanks.
So...
you and Stark.
Yeah, I think so.
Maybe.
- You really think I'm making a mistake?
- No,
no... I...
I think...
whatever you decide,
I'll be here for you.
Really?
Yeah...
No, not really.
Get outta here.
You were willing to walk away
from Global for me.
I told you, I wanted us to be together
in the office, always.
Nathan, do you really think
we can make this work?
I know we can.
Okay.
- Is that a "Yes?"
- That's a "Yes."
Vincent, I think we're gonna need
a bottle of Champagne.
Hey.
- Hell of a first day, huh?
- Yeah,
- thanks for letting me come back.
- Well, yeah, I overreacted.
Sorry, I'm late.
Yeah, I'm afraid you are.
Champagne coming up.
Let's go.