First day with the new boss, huh?
And the new desk.
Jealous much?
Just because Blake inherited you
doesn't mean she has to keep you.
Not if there's a better candidate
for the job.
The better candidate
already has the job.
Oh... we'll see.
This transition has to go smoothly.
The D.O.D. brass in town.
The computer reboot.
Lot of pressure to perform, huh?
No room for screwups.
That shouldn't be an issue
for you, should it?
Midterms today, right?
Those were last week, Dad.
Yeah... I know.
You haven't told me how you did yet.
Oh, yeah, um...
B...
B- plus...
F...
B- minus...
A.
Well, A's great.
Yeah, it's for P.E. You get it just
for putting on the stupid shorts.
And... and, uh... and the...
F?
The make-up exams are today,
so you can relax.
I am relaxed.
- I didn't even yell.
- Which is killing you.
Yeah, it really is.
But... I got an F once.
Yeah, eighth grade geometry.
No time for story mode
'cause we really need to go.
Yeah, but, you know, keep...
"Nose to the grindstone.
Don't get discouraged. "
Something about walking
3 miles through broken glass,
uphill, both ways,
and just keep trying.
Close enough?
Uh, yeah...
it was 4 miles, but...
- Did you get her anything?
- Get who anything?
The woman you have
a crush on is becoming
the most powerful person in Eureka,
so you might want to get her something.
I don't have a crush on anyone.
S.A.R.A.H., door.
Okay, what's with all the looks
and the "Ms. Blakes?"
I was "Allison" until yesterday.
And you're taking over
Global Dynamics today.
Things are gonna be different.
- Has General Mansfield arrived yet?
- A few minutes ago.
He wanted to personally supervise
the change in command.
- And you handle biometric verification?
- And the retinal scan.
- Once you've replaced Dr. Stark...
- Succeeded Dr. Stark.
Once you're in charge,
Global's core computer systems
will immediately begin
the eight-hour reboot,
audit, and reset.
Everything but external security and
nominal desktop functionality
will be offline.
It's kind of like a snow day.
Normally it would've been
six months before we did the shutdown,
but with the accident
in Section Five and the transition,
the D.O.D. decided to move the date.
So, I guess I'll meet you inside.
- I was going to call you this morning.
- Hey, busy day.
I get it.
Again, I'm sorry about the way
things came down.
Don't be.
It wasn't your call.
After you.
Dr. Stark, if you would place your hand
on the scanning device.
And now the retinal verification.
Retinal scan confirms a match.
Ms. Blake.
And a match on Ms. Blake.
Dr. Stark, if you would type in your
master password on the touch screen.
And now by keying in your own password,
you'll become the new head
of Global Dynamics.
Transfer is complete.
Global's computer reset will begin...
now.
Global Dynamics computer shut down.
In nine,
height,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
The Global Dynamics
computer system is now offline.
Eight hours to reactivation.
The Global Dynamics
computer system is now offline.
Eight hours to reactivation.
When the computer does
a shut down like this
all operative projects are suspended.
All transportable protypes
are stored securely here in the vault.
There's an automatic inventory
as soon as the system comes back online.
Looks like some of this stuff
has been here for a while.
That's because we store
abandoned projects here as well.
We got organic, electronic, A.I....
you name it.
Your job will be to make sure
it all stays safe and sound.
You got some pretty big shoes to fill.
I got over 20 years
without a single loss.
What's supposed to be here?
You have got to be kidding me.
It's a big improvement.
It is missing something, though.
What is that?
A little parting gift.
My parting,
not yours.
Thank you.
Now you're official.
You don't have to leave, you know.
It's not like you were fired.
I don't know.
This place, what it did to me...
gotta admit, it's kind of nice
not having all this
resting on my shoulders.
Was it really that bad?
Ms. Blake,
I'm afraid there's been
a breach in vault security.
A theft.
It's...
a category red device.
The Projet-SG Team
presents :
Timing:   Golgi, Loky, Ricana
Transcript:   swsub.com
Edition:   Golgi, Loky, Ricana.
Proofreading:   Golgi, Loky.
- Season 2 | Episode 2 -
Try Try Again (v 1.0)
Oh, Sheriff Carter, General Mansfield.
- Sheriff.
- Hey,
so, what do we got?
Time warp, black hole, random quantum...
not that that ever happens here.
A protype for a next-generation "macaw"
is missing from the vault.
It's not a bird.
It's Multi Application Combat
Armor Alternative.
M.A.C.A.
- Personal force field generator.
- Oh,
a personal force field.
Uh, do you have a picture or something
so I know what I'm looking for?
Unfortunately, no.
With the computers offline,
the only thing I can tell you is that
it's a category red.
- I assume red is bad.
- Red is catastrophic.
Handled incorrectly,
a category red device could...
take out this entire facility.
Mansfield.
It needs to be found.
What are you doing?
Stop screwing around.
I'm not screwing around. I...
just...
- doing what we do.
- No more of that.
Okay.
I'll go find your catastrophe.
Thank you.
Yes?
Uh... Nice name plate.
It was a gift from Nathan.
You were gonna say something?
Uh... no.
I mean, you know... congratulations.
Thanks.
How are you doing, Henry?
Okay.
Considering.
Are you sleeping all right?
Really, I'm good. I...
just want to get back to work.
- At Global?
- Yes.
- Why?
- I want to continue Kim's research.
I can't get her back. I can at least
honor her memory
by finishing what she started.
And how do you feel about science now?
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Well, you've been pretty vocal about
how you think Eureka has lost its way.
That noble ideas have turned
into weapons of destruction.
Science has failed you.
And now it's cost the life
of the woman you loved.
Science hasn't failed me.
The approach to it has.
And that's what I want to change.
Nathan Stark's experiences made him
want to leave Global altogether,
yet you want back in.
Nathan and I are very different people.
I don't see how his decision
has anything to do with
my wanting to get back to work.
So you think you can
put this tragedy behind you?
Never.
But I can be motivated by it.
That's good.
Anything?
Naw.
With the main computer down,
I can't access any security footage.
Did I mention I'm one day away
from retiring with a perfect record?
Twice, yeah. Look, do you know who'd
want one of these force field things?
Yeah, me, right now!
All right, Victor. Think.
Who was down here this morning?
I don't know. A lot of people.
This is the GD storage vault.
With the computer about to shut down,
this was a busy place.
Well,  how about someone new?
You said you had a trainee.
Yeah.
But he got here later.
There was this one guy, though.
A shifty, weaselly,
suspicious kind of guy.
Um, thick, black-rimmed glasses?
Yeah!
I shoulda known.
Attention.
This is a reminder
that the Global Dynamic
computers will be offline
for the next eight hours.
You're not Fargo.
I'm Larry.
Hey, Larry. Um, I need Fargo.
You and a lot of people,
including Ms. Blake.
He went to the bathroom
about an hour ago,
never came back.
Not the best way
to impress your new boss.
Looks like something made an impression.
- You gonna stick around?
- Oh, I intend to.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, there.
Anybody here?
No.
Yeah?
Whatcha doing?
Hiding.
Found the missing mech...
uh, ma...
- macarena.
- Fargo, look...
turn that thing off and take it back
to the vault right now.
I can't turn it off.
I can't open it up.
- Can't drop it.
- You probably don't want to do that.
And they can't take it back.
Personal force field!
Hardly catastrophic,
but very impressive.
Except for the not being able
to turn it off part.
What are you doing with that?
Nothing! I've never seen it before.
I found it in my pocket.
But you did turn it on.
- Uh, yeah.
- Why?
Um, because it's what I do?
Ridiculous as this may sound,
I happen to believe him.
I don't think anyone else
would pretend to be that stupid.
Oh, great.
Sorry!
Oh, why is this happening?
It's pretty amazing. I mean,
you've only had the job for what...
like, an hour?
- Actually, an hour and...
- Okay! I need this thing turned off.
- Are you sure?
- It might be safer for-
Please, just figure it out.
All we have to do
is to figure out who took it
or better yet, who built it.
But you gotta level with me.
Are you sure you don't know
anything about it?
- I wasn't here when it was developed.
- Who was?
Oh, crap!
Stark, need your help.
Carter, no.
It's about Fargo.
Fargo?
Yeah, you know, uh... glasses,
sort of accident-prone.
Yeah, yeah. What about him?
It seems he got caught
in some sort of, uh...
force field thingy. He got it from
the vault and he can't turn it off.
You talking about the M.A.C.A.?
Not that coherently, but yes.
What do you know about it?
I know that it was category red
and it was terminated.
Well, Fargo unterminated it.
And we can't get any information from
Global 'cause the computers are down.
- What do you know about it?
- Not a lot.
It's before my time.
Do you know anyone
who was associated with it?
Maybe.
Wow, someone's going
a little overboard on the firewood.
Chopping the wood
could be very therapeutic.
You never swung an ax in your life.
Swung a lot of things that
would surprise you, Sheriff.
What does that even mean?
There's Dr. Todd.
Don't get many visitors up here.
Well, we would've called but...
I don't have a phone,
so I guess you didn't take the hint.
Ultrasonic fishing rod?
- Pulse stuns the fish.
- It's painless.
Catch and release, I hope.
Unless I turn up the power.
I try my best not
to kill things anymore.
Yeah, we need some information
about your M.A.C.A.
If I tell you, will you go away?
Well, we have a situa...
All right! Enough!
Someone at GD messed
with it and is in trouble.
The M.A.C.A. was my project
five years ago until
I stopped working on it.
Because it had problems?
Because a man died.
We were having containment
issues with the power source.
Sometimes the power surged and
we couldn't stop it. And other times,
the biological backup would
activate spontaneously
and start drawing power
from the environment.
But we thought we'd solved it within
tolerated level. We thought it was safe.
What happened?
We were wrong.
The field around the test
subject started to grow.
After
three hours, it was as big as a house.
We calculated that after four hours
it would never be contained.
It would've taken out Global,
everything in it.
It would've taken out Eureka
and everything in it.
A force field growing at that rate?
It'd have displaced everything
in its path. Towns, cities,
nothing would've stopped it.
It's funny how four hours
can change your life.
- When you said you had to contain it...
- We dropped it...
and the man inside it into Section 14.
A two-mile-deep pit
that we used to
test nuclear weapons in the '50s.
And then we dropped in
a three-megaton bomb after it.
That was my last day at
Global Dynamics and my first day here.
I'd like you to leave now.
I'd like to get back to my fishing.
Dr. Todd,
I'm really sorry, but
we need some help here.
We need you to tell us what we can do.
You can say good-bye to your friend.
Thanks
How long since Fargo
turned on the generator?
Maybe two hours.
That only leaves us two hours.
It's not a lot of time.
That experiment was five years ago.
You tell me that Global hasn't come up
with anything that can counter this?
Drop me at Henry's.
Still can't let go, huh?
Can you?
That's why I'm leaving Global.
- But I can't leave just yet.
- Why not?
I got work to do.
You get anything?
Uh, yeah.
Hey, Fargo.
Uh, you're gonna be okay...
just as long as the...
force field doesn't grow.
Oh, my God.
You can't stop it, can you?
Uh, not yet.
But if we don't give up,
you can't either.
I really have to go to the bathroom.
Of course you do.
Do we have any suspects yet?
No, unless you count this long list
of people around here
who find Fargo as annoying as we do.
Hey, that's not...
Oh, yes it is.
It's not so much who finds Fargo
annoying as who on this list stands...
to gain from what happened.
Like this guy.
Hey, Larry. Seen Fargo yet?
- Sure haven't.
- Well, I have.
See, it seems that somebody
stole something from the vault
that's gotten him
into a whole lot of trouble.
Trouble like maybe he won't be able
to return to his job for a while?
Trouble like the person who did this...
is gonna go to jail.
How do you feel about jail, Larry?
- Wait a minute, you think I...
- Motive seems clear to me.
You wanted this job, he got it.
Now you're here.
Did the guy in the vault
say that I was down there?
A lot of people have been down there.
Well, I wasn't one of them.
- Check the logs.
- I can't.
Not for 6 hours.
Not till the computers come back online.
- Well, that's convenient.
- Yeah... it is.
Isn't it?
I'm not even cleared for that section.
Hold on. We're not through.
Carter.
I think I found something.
I need you to bring Fargo
to Henry's garage.
- I'll be right there.
- Have a lead?
Um, I'm not sure yet.
Gotta go.
- He has an idea.
- So do I.
Open Section 14,
authorize the transfer
of the nuclear device.
- These things take time.
- Not yet.
Carter's never let me down.
You were right, Carter.
Something has changed since
Dr. Todd first tested the device.
We developed the next generation
non-lethal carbon
nanotube antipersonnel weapon.
I call it a goo gun.
It's for crowd control.
If fires an epoxy-like foam
that sticks people in their place
until they're collected later.
That's what
the first generation could do.
This baby could stop a jeep.
So I'm thinking...
If we can cover
Fargo's force field with it,
- we may be able to restrict its growth.
- Yeah, for how long?
Hopefully long enough for
Global's computers come back online.
Dr. Stark, are you smiling?
Course not.
You ready?
Does it matter?
I'm still alive,
in case anyone's interested.
Mission accomplished.
Yeah, all we have to do now...
Right.
What's happening?
The force field is still expanding.
And I'm all out of ideas.
The fact that Henry and Nathan
together came up dry, not encouraging.
I'm gonna need to take a look at
the hard copy backup of vault inventory.
- Why?
Just a hunch.
But I think it might not be an accident
that the theft occurred
when the computers were down.
I know that you're trying,
but I think you need
to prepare yourself.
- For what?
- For what's coming.
Time is running out...
for Fargo, for Global...
For you.
What are you implying?
Nothing.
Forget it. It just...
you seem different today.
Yeah, well, l am different.
Part of the job description.
Yeah, well, I'm not.
But like you said,
we're running out of time, so...
- I'm having Fargo moved to Section 14.
- Wait a minute...
It's just precautionary,
but under the circumstances,
I don't have a choice.
Look, if you want the hard copy,
the records are located in Section Three
along with every other record
from the history of Global.
The record section is big.
How big are we talking?
Big.
Oh, my...
Attention all Section 14 personnel.
Please make sure
you are wearing your radiation badges.
How fast is it growing?
Well...
It's not that bad.
Just hang in there.
Easy for you to say.
I know where we are.
I know what Section 14 is.
That pit's 10,000 feet deep.
It's the only place we have
that's big enough to hold you.
That's all.
Hi, Fargo.
Henry.
So... how are you doing, Fargo?
I've been better.
Allison thought that you...
might want to talk.
Right, bring the psychiatrist in
to hear the dead guy's last words.
I didn't say that.
You didn't have to.
You know, I do have some last words.
Some things I want to get off my chest.
Good. I'm listening.
You better get a pad.
There's gonna be a lot to write down.
- How are you holding up?
- I'm not the one to worry about.
I can worry about you both.
Nuke on the way?
Not yet.
Does Fargo know?
We have 30 minutes.
Carter's working on something.
And if that doesn't pan out?
Half an hour, I'll have no choice.
Hell of a first day.
Yes, it is.
Email to Allison Blake.
You are the most
intoxicating woman I ever met.
I used to dream of you
catching me asleep
on your desk late at night.
Send one of those to Jo,
and substitute "jail cell" for "desk".
Oh, and...
send one to yourself
substituting "couch".
And see if you can work
the word "tempestuous" in there.
Now, Sheriff Carter.
You really tried to help me
on my last day, and, um...
for that, I don't know how to thank you.
- That's actually quite tou...
- If only you were better at your job.
Victor!
Leaving a little early today,
aren't you?
About half an hour ahead
of your regular schedule?
What are you talking about?
What do you know
about my regular schedule?
A lot.
We know a lot about
everything you do, Victor.
Jo and I just spend
a little quality time
looking through your vault records.
You didn't know we could do that
with the computers down, huh?
Come on, you wanna do honors?
Move ! Let me through !
Clear the way !
It's okay.
All right, Victor.
Here it is.
You not only stole the generator,
you stole a lot of stuff in the vault.
And you knew you were safe
until the computer reboot
forced the next vault inventory.
Once you found out
that they were gonna
shut down the computers early,
you knew you had to find
someone to frame.
- And who better than Douglas Fargo?
- I have no idea what...
We'll have all the proof we need
with computers back online,
but by then, a man will be dead.
And that'll be your fault,
and that's murder.
If you talk then
it'll be too late for you...
and too late for Fargo.
He wasn't supposed to turn it on.
Well, it's Fargo!
Of course he turned it on.
Who was buying the stolen equipment?
Who wanted the force field generator?
I don't...
I need to know who paid you to steal it?
Do they know how to turn it off?
You don't understand.
I didn't sell the technology.
I just sold the parts.
I picked something that would fit
in Fargo's pocket.
I never intended to sell it.
I just needed a fall guy.
What are we gonna do now?
Yes, this is Allison Blake.
I'm authorizing
a priority one mobilization, Section 14.
Yes, that's right.
Bring in the nuclear device.
Allison, can I have a word
with you please?
You're cutting this awfully close.
We're trying to save a life.
Rushing isn't gonna help.
This is the kind of decision
someone in your position
has to be prepared to make.
I'm aware of that. And questioning
my approach doesn't make it any easier.
It's not about easy, Allison.
It's about having faith
you made the right choice.
Do you have faith?
You did everything you could.
More than anybody else.
Not that it matters.
Fargo's still gonna die.
Four hours really can change your life.
You're right.
Uh, Fargo activated
the generator four hours ago.
Dr. Todd said that
after three hours, the...
the force field was as big as a house.
- It's nowhere near that big.
- It's growing more slowly.
- The power supply is unstable.
- Maybe it's the way it was handled.
Or... or stored.
It sat right here
for five years until today.
- Could've been touching this.
- Yeah, whatever this is.
This could be the answer but
without access to computers...
Jo has the inventory. We got it
from Section Three this afternoon.
We still can't compare the field's
growth rate to the first experiment.
All that data is in the computer.
And one other place.
Dr. Todd, do not zap me with that thing.
I guess I wasn't clear about
not wanting any visitors.
No, you were clear,
but it's different now.
I still want to be left alone now,
you're still bothering me now, so?
The force field is different.
It's growing more slowly.
It's been four hours and
Fargo still fits in Section 14.
If it slowed down,
maybe it can be stopped.
Let us take you back to Global.
Help us figure this out.
There's nothing I can do.
Dr. Todd, your device was stored
next to another protype
that created a magnetic field.
Is there a possibility
of some sort of power drain?
Look at the specs.
Check the test records.
We don't have the specs, we have you.
I know how you feel.
Believe me.
We both made mistakes at Global.
Lost people who trusted us.
But today, we got a chance
to try and make things right.
- How long has it been?
- Five hours.
You're right. Something's slowing
the field's growth rate.
- You're generating a magnetic field?
- Generating it isn't the hard part.
It's the modulation that's tricky.
Do you want to check my readings?
I never thought I'd say
the phrase "last chance"
so many times in a single day.
Allison...
why has he not been lowered
into Section 14?
- We're exploring one final alternative.
- You have missed the cut-off.
There was a firm deadline in place.
- Um, I'm aware of that.
- You are risking this entire facility
and everyone in it on one man.
That is not a logical choice.
That is an emotional one.
Well, sir, that's your opinion.
Yes, and if you do not reconsider,
I will have no choice but to remove you
as head of Global Dynamics.
Actually, sir,
I'm afraid you can't do that.
- I beg your pardon.
- Protocol states that no transfer
of power or relief
of duty can be effected
when the Global computer systems
are down.
Security concerns. So...
you can't fire me
for another three hours.
You do understand that once
that force field gets to be too large
to leave this facility it will also be
too large to fit into that hole.
And at that point, containment
will be out of the question.
Let's hope that doesn't have
to happen, sir.
I think I'm starting to like
the new you.
It... it's shrinking!
Look, the light's fading.
He's right... the field is contracting.
The mag field's affecting
the power source.
Wait, the light's out!
Then why is the force field still there?
Wait,
- now there's a red light.
- The alternate power source
- has been activated.
- How?
Told you it draws power
from environment.
What environment?
There's no one in there but Fargo.
Exactly... it's biological power.
His body is the power source.
Fine. The field is shrinking which
means we can use
the computers when they-
You don't understand.
Power requirement is tremendous.
Finding the source
is the default priority.
- Which means?
- It'll kill him.
So what do we do?
We're not gonna let
that thing kill Fargo.
I'm gonna kill him first.
Fargo's the battery
that powers the force field?
- Essentially.
- So to collapse it,
we need to shut that battery down.
- What?
- Just... just for a second.
How? Nothing can get through the field.
We can hear him, right?
It'll pack quite a punch.
The sonic pulse will target
the area just like a bullet.
We hit Fargo's heart,
it will stop.
- You're gonna what?
- Is the defibrillator ready?
- Ready to go.
- Right.
- Let's do this.
- Hold on.
l am the one with the most marksmanship
titles in special forces history.
- Right, good point.
- Yeah.
Let...
Locked and loaded.
- Fire when ready.
- Now, is that when I'm ready, or...
Clear!
Damn it! Come on. Just...
Come on, Fargo.
You all right?
Who ripped my shirt?
He's fine.
Good job, Carter.
Wow, that didn't even leave
a bad taste in my mouth.
Oh, give it a second.
Yep, there it is.
Thanks, Dr. Stark.
I feel closer to you
than I ever have before.
Well, no good deed goes unpunished.
Seriously...
what you and Sheriff Carter did was...
- a miracle.
- No, we just didn't give up.
No one did.
Thanks for killing me.
Any time.
If you happen to get an email from me...
Yeah, I already did.
Done here?
I'm glad I was wrong.
I hear there's a two-for-one deal
at colossusjobs.com,
if you want to get your resume
up with mine.
I think I'm safe here.
At least for another day.
You did good today.
Handled the situation
better than I would've.
Not better, just...
just differently.
Nathan...
Global needs you.
I need you.
Really?
And Carter's right.
The two of you do work well together.
You just know how to ruin the moment.
Just think about it.
Well, maybe you should think about
how well you and I work together.
You have a lot of faith in yourself.
I do.
Me too.
Attention.
Global Dynamics computer systems
are now back online.
Full functionality has been restored.
Good evening, Sheriff Carter.
Hard day at work?
Eh, they've been easier.
Hey, Dad.
Hey.
Catch any bad guys today?
Uh, yeah, as a matter of fact, I did.
How was the make-up exam?
You know how you're always saying,
"Try, try again"?
Yeah, well, never more than today.
Well, I did.
And I passed.
You are now looking at
the proud graduate of Driver's Ed.
So when do you want
to take me out driving?