You are heading down
a dangerous path.
You don't have a job --
Victoria:
Your honor...
She does have a job.
She works for me.
How did we get the funding
for the movie?
My father and I
put up the money,
Because I believe in you.
The movie shoots
in a week,
And we don't have
a costume designer,
Which is why
I'm asking you now.
We just broke up.
I want to direct.
You were at the top
of the list.
Better get to work.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
This is yours.
Just maybe don't give it
to taylor.
So, let's make
someone's favorite movie!
yeah? Let's go.
Okay. What?
David left me.
Smart move.
You're not seriously looking
to me for sympathy, are you?
I really liked him.
Yeah.
And nobody's
ever left me before,
Especially not a guy
like david.
And what's that supposed
to mean?
It's not like he's a super big
catch or anything.
Oh, look, 9 across --
"superficial bitch."
T-a-y-l-o-r.
Language.
Oh, come on.
This happens every morning.
Maybe you should get up
a little bit earlier.
And maybe you should make more
when you take the last of it.
I didn't. Quinn did.
No, I didn't.
Who ate all my cereal?
Quinn.
Taylor.
Sorry, buddy, taylor likes
to take things that aren't hers.
Sweetie, we have
plenty more cereal.
So, hales.
Huh?
David broke up
with taylor.
I'm glad you find
my heartbreak amusing.
I'm sorry.
You guys broke up?
Oh, no.
Nathan:
Okay, come on, jamie.
Let's go out
for breakfast.
Good idea.
Bye, mom.
Bye.
Quinn: Way to go, tay.
You scared off
half the family.
No, you did with
your morning breath.
Haley: No milk?
Are you kidding me?
Well, somebody's
trying to win
The super-assistant award
this morning.
Morning, victoria.
Double nonfat macchiato --
should still be hot.
Aren't these pieces
amazing?
I've already steamed, priced,
and displayed
The rest of the shipment --
look.
What?
Are you...
How are you feeling?
I'm fine, really.
This isn't the manic work
of drug-doer millie.
I'm just really,
really trying
To prove myself
to you and brooke.
Promise me that if things
get hard,
You don't disappear
into some dark alley.
You can talk to me.
No dark alleys for me,
I promise.
No, the advance can't be
50% applicable,
And you know this.
Come in.
Uh-huh.
Well, it --
it's because it's standard
In these types of deals.
All right,
clay's got all the good stuff.
What do you want?
Um, can I mix fruity ones
with cocoa ones?
That's gross.
Go for it.
What's up, nate?
How you doing today, scott?
Hey, boy.
Ah, too many girls at our house,
not enough cereal.
All right.
Glad to see your priorities
are straight.
Cereal first.
Thanks.
Whew.
I'll be outside.
Got crazy
endorsements -- crazy.
Clay's got
all the good stuff.
Yes, he does.
Cocoa.
Hey.
Hi.
How's everything going?
Uh, okay, I guess.
I'm struggling with the dialogue
in this scene.
It --
it doesn't feel honest.
What's the scene?
Um...
It's the one
where he leaves her.
Oh.
Well, I think
all girls understand
The moment
there's another girl.
So maybe it's about
what they don't say.
Actually, I was thinking
he doesn't say enough, you know?
I mean, she's got to know
that he loved her,
But if she doesn't,
He needs to find the words
to convince her.
And what are those words?
I don't know yet.
But I'm gonna find them.
I mean...
The movie depends on it.
Right.
Well, then,
I should get back to work.
I know.
I mean, give me a break.
What are you guys
doing here?
Uh, we are out
for breakfast.
You're hiding
from taylor.
Hiding? No.
Yes, we ar
yeah.
Don't answer it.
Really, bitches?
Language!
You're hiding.
I get it.
Uh, no, we aren't.
We were just leaving.
Whatever. I guess it'll
just be me and mom, then.
Well, well.
Hiding from taylor?
Grandma!
Hey, handsome!
Ooh!
Mom, what are you
doing here?
What, I can't come to see
my three favorite daughters?
We all know you don't
like taylor that much.
Oh, lord,
some things never change.
Get over here. Mm.
Nathan.
How are you?
How are you,
sweetie?
Good to see you.
Can we make her sexier?
I mean, not slutty,
just sexy...Er.
Yeah.
We'll tuck this and...
No, I like
the sleeves up.
Slutty. Um, I'm gonna
take up the hem.
Okay, whatever you think.
Rehearsal in 20?
Yeah, we'll be ready.
You didn't have to do that,
with the sleeves.
I know.
It looks better
like this.
Oh. Right.
I need you
to pick one.
Uh, I like them both.
You decide.
Try this one on while I fix
what you're wearing.
Brooke, I'm sorry that you
and julian broke up.
Okay.
I'll try this on.
Hey, be careful.
Lydia:
Isn't it about time
For you and nathan
to have another one?
I mean,
you're not getting any younger.
Very funny.
Neither is quinn.
Oh, thanks.
I always thought
that you and david
Would have lots and lots
of babies.
Yeah, that's
taylor's department now.
What?
Tay and david?
Well, not anymore.
He broke up with her
this morning.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm happy,
and he's happy.
Taylor's unhappy.
That's all that matters.
Clay's kind of cute.
Clay's amazing.
Well, that's good.
And what about you, mom?
You okay without daddy?
I am today.
You like it?
I'm not flower-friendly.
Everybody likes flowers.
I didn't say I dislike them.
I simply can't keep them alive.
Flowers in a vase
are better.
They last a limited amount of
time, and no care is required.
Are you scared?
Of what?
Of being
my girlfriend.
Look.
I'm not your girlfriend,
Anthe odds of that happening
Are about as good as me
keeping that orchid alive --
Slim to none.
And let's be honest.
You're the one that's scared.
You're talented, and yet
you won't make a record.
I'd just like to know why.
It's too personal.
, "it's too personal."
Are those supposed
to wash it all away,
The "I'll always love you"s,
the "I don't blame you"s,
The "forever"s?
Cut. Let's go again.
Julian, this is
the 14th take.
She's not getting it.
We're into a couple
of meal penalties.
We got to move on.
It's -- it's an important scene,
dad. She'll get it.
I'm so sorry. I ju --
I can't get there emotionally.
I'm trying, but --
it's okay.
No, it's not okay.
I ck.
No, you'll find it.
They're your words.
You wrote them because they mean
something to you.
Okay, I know you
can do this.
Just --
just s the line to me.
sure, help me.
Clean me up.
Make me immaculate.
Fill me up with your promises
and words and lies.
Okay, say it again,
but just stay with me.
Let me help you.
Mnh-mnh.
Say the line again,
but look at me.
Look at me.
Just stay with me.
sure, help me.
Clean me up.
Make me immaculate.
Fill me up
with your promises.
Okay, roll camera.
We're gonna tail-slate it.
Again.
Elise, let me help you.
Sure, help me.
Clean me up.
Make me immaculate.
Fill me up with your promises
and words and lies.
Elise, please.
Tears, max?
Are these supposed
to wash it all away,
The "il always love you"s,
the "I don't blame you"s,
The "forever"s?
Cut.
Check the gate.
That's perfect.
Okay, mark.
Good job.
You did it.
No, alex did it.
Okay.
You're feeling a bottle
of something,
But you should stick
with water.
It's safer emotionally.
You want to talk about it?
I took a job
to be near my ex.
It's painful.
But it's worse
to be away from him.
sorry.
I don't mean to be
the sad, pouty girl
Who comes in,
dumps all her problems on you.
U are talking
to a guy
Who wrote an entire album
about a girl --
Every song.
What happened?
She's with
someone else now.
How did you know
it was over?
You know,
for the longest time,
Whenever I would see her,
Even after we weren't
together amore,
She would tell me
that she missed me.
Ani would look
into her eyes,
And I knew she meant it.
Then one day,
she just stopped saying it,
And I knew she was gone.
I went in for one drink
And told my daughter
to stay in the car,
That mama
would be right back.
Excusee. Hi.
Would you mind signing this
reallyuick?
It's just a court thing.
You n't have
to explain.
Oh.
You know,
it might help you to stay.
It's okay. It was just
a small driving incint.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
There you go.
Quinn's told me a lot
about you.
All good, I ho.
Mm. You make her
very, very happy.
You knowhat worried look
she gets?
It's gone.
She means the world
to me.
I was sorry to hear
about your wife.
I lost my husband, too,
a few years back.
Quinn mentioned that.
I'm sorry, too.
's hard, isn't it,
Learning to live
without them?
Yeah.
It's hard mang
new memories,
You know,
like it's not fair to them.
I think it not fair
to them not to.
I mean, they'd want that,
wouldn't they?
They'd want to know
that we faced their absence
With dignity and grace.
Yeah, well, the truth is,
I'm not sure I've been
thatracious about any of it.
You're still here,
aren't you,
Still finding your way?
That's about as much grace
as anyone can ask.
Oh, haley,
I'm so glad you're here.
You're chipper.
I don't think you've ever been
happy to see me.
I need you to convince grubbs
to record.
Um, I-I'm sorry.
My mom's in town, so I'm gonna
be spending the day with her.
Since when do you need my help
convincing someone
To do something
they don't want to do?
You're great at that.
It's true,
but this one is different.
He called me...
His girlfriend.
That's so sweet.
It's not sweet,
and don't confuse the issue.
He's good. He's really good.
And our label could use him.
You totally
have a boyfriend.
go get him, tiger.
He's not my boyfriend!
Whoa, this is cool.
It's exactly
like uncle lucas' house.
Hey, there's
my first a.D.
Oh, cool.
So, I need
some background footage
Of the set
and behind-the-scenes stuff.
Think you can handle that?
So, you working hard
or hardly working? "shrek 2."
dude, that's your movie quote?
That's, like,
a common expression.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Wow, "shrek 2."
I like "shrek 2."
Hey, bitch.
Hey.
Oh, you're cranky.
No, I'm not.
I'm fine.
Okay, sort of cranky that I have
to go to these meetings.
It's a bunch of losers
with serious problems,
Like leave-your-kid-
in-the-car
Or burn-your-house-down-'cause
you're-so-wasted problems.
Mine -- not so big.
Right.
Whatever.
How's being
a movie star again?
Try worst actress ever --
14 takes this morning.
Not awesome.
Julian was great,
but I'm just --
I'm really frustrated.
You'll be okay.
You're alex dupré.
Man: Alex,
they're ready for you.
Okay, thanks.
Yeah, well, hopefully alex dupré
figures it out
Before she brings
down the whole movie set.
Later, bitch.
Oh, millie.
Those people
at the meetings --
Their problems started out
not so big, too.
So, I want the camera
to circle right while zooming,
As if we're being drawn
into them.
Then I want
to slow the movement
And end on a tight close-up
of alex -- no cutting.
Got it?
Nice shot, hitchcock.
It's "vertigo," right?
Hey, beauty.
I have the suit sample.
gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
I die. I love it.
Yeah?
I'd love it
with a slimmer leg,
An eighth of an inch
on either side.
Got it.
So, I'm thinking
We'll be ready to unveil
in about a month.
You are good,
alexander coyne.
No, you're good,
brooke davis.
Brooke, they're doing
last looks.
Okay.
And you look hot.
Wow.
Do you, uh, need any help
with that?
No, I'm good,
but feel free
To go make the adjustments
to that suit, now.
Or you could just stay
and do it later.
Okay.
Really?
She is pretty hot.
Another guy
hypnotized by alex.
She's like
a freaking siren.
Hey, there's no woman as
alluring as you, brooke davis.
I think I should
get back to work.
Good idea. Hey.
I appreciate you
being around.
I know you didn't sign up
for a lot of this.
Yeah, no worries.
I'm here
for whatever you need.
So, alexander's
kind of a tool, huh?
If by tool, you mean
really good designer.
Yeah, tool.
Wow, and I was
just gonna tell you
That you did a really good job
with alex on that scene today.
And then I was
Maybe gonna tell you
that you're a natural.
I don't know if a natural
Would need 14 takes
to direct one scene.
Don't be so hard
on yourself.
Is this too hard
on you?
I'm okay.
Julian,
can I talk to you?
Yeah.
I was just leaving.
I see you're driving
that truck.
What happened
to your mercedes?
I sold it.
To help finance the movie?
Mm-hmm.
You shouldn't be risking
everything on this.
Look, I got to get
back to work, dad.
Then I'll get to the point.
Alex has to be better,
Or we're gonna be
in serious trouble here.
She will be.
Your coffee,
sir.
Thank you.
Jamie, you bug,
You are exactly what I need
to brighten my day.
What are you doing?
Jamie: Capturing
behind-the-scenes footage.
Oh, well,
make me look fabulous.
Hi.
How you doing?
Well, you know, working
on the ex-boyfriend's movie
In the ex-ex boyfriend's house
is kind of weird,
But I'm managing.
What's going on
with the ex-boyfriend part?
We're trying to be friends.
And he's okay with that?
He's fine. I'm fine.
Everything's
gonna be fine.
All right,
well, let me know
If you need me to knock
some sense into the guy.
Thanks.
Woman: Kind of slow in here.
Oh, these are cute.
Ah, there's this.
Can I help you find
anything?
Oh, no,
we're just looking.
Okay.
Hey, uh, aren't you the model
for clothes over bros?
Yeah. Well, I was
for that campaign.
Why are you
folding clothes?
Oh, um...I do a lot of things
for the company.
Well, let me know
if you need anything.
Okay.
Thanks.
God, she looks
so plain.
I know.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
I think shirt.
Hi. You got a sec?
Yeah, of course.
First of all,
I, um --
I just want to thank you
For everything
you've done for me.
It means --
Well, it means a lot.
Don't worry about it.
What's going on?
You sold your car.
How much money
did you put up?
Alex --
julian, how much?
All of it.
Julian,
what if I let you down?
Then what?
You're not
gonna let me down.
But you put everything you had
into this movie.
Why did you do that?
Man: Two minutes!
Because you put everything
you had into this script.
And it's good.
And you're good.
Okay? You're not
gonna let me down.
Oh, haley.
It is such a beautiful home.
I am so proud
of you and nathan.
Thanks.
I feel really lucky
to have him and jamie.
And it's great, you know,
'cause all the stuff
doesn't matter so much.
It's just -- although
I'm really grateful to
have all the extra space
Now that quinn and taylor
are here.
Well, it's an important role
being your sisters' keeper.
They're lucky to have you.
Well, I'm glad
that you're here
Because I don't speak taylor
fluently,
And I really need you
to translate.
Taylor has
always been rebellious.
That girl follows her heart
without thinking twice about it.
Or once.
So...What's going on, mom?
What brings you to town?
I'm just checking in
on my babies.
I started with the oldest,
finished with the best.
Mm. Nobody told me
you were coming.
Well, that's because
I wouldn't let them.
I'm a big fan
of surprises.
Oh.
Now, come on.
Fill me in on everything
that's been going on.
And don't leave out
the good parts.
Okay.
Well, jamie's going
to a new school, and...
So, let me
get this straight.
You don't want to make a record
because it's too personal?
That's right.
Personal sells albums.
Personal wins grammys.
People can --
Okay, well, most people
can relate to personal.
They want to hear the songs
with the words
That they're
too afraid to say.
So...When you're ready --
Ahh -- man up...
And make a record with me.
I can't believe this looks
exactly like uncle lucas' room.
Hey, remember that time
he had a mohawk?
Nathan: Yeah.
That was cool.
You miss him?
Yeah.
I miss lots of people,
I guess --
Aunt peyton
and uncle skills and quentin.
And grandpa dan --
I miss him a lot.
Yeah, it's hard
when you miss people.
But, you know, if you miss them,
it means you were lucky.
It means you had
someone special in your life,
Someone worth missing.
Yeah, I guess.
I just don't like
the missing part so much.
Yeah, me neither.
Not fair. True.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my god.
You remember this?
This is horrible.
Oh, mom, look at my hair.
You gave me
the most awful haircut.
It wasn't terrible.
It was cute, baby.
Look at you,
with your little face
And those
great big glasses.
She was teased for that haircut,
like, every day.
Yeah, I cried
for like a week,
And then I wore a mop head
around the house
To have princess hair.
Haley was such a pudge.
I was a baby.
You're supposed to be fat
when you're -- give me that.
Do you remember
When you used to stuff your bra,
like, a lot?
Mom, you have extras
of this?
Uh, I think I have pictures
of just about all of it.
Oh.
Are you okay, mom?
Um...I'm sick.
look at me.
I swore I wasn't gonna cry,
But, boy,
these tears are stubborn.
Mom, but you're gonna be
okay, though, right?
No. I'm not.
What do you mean, mom ?
What's wrong ?
I have cancer.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's pancreatic.
And that means that even
with aggressive treatment,
I wouldn't have
much time left.
But there has
to be options, right?
There aren't, quinny.
Well, you have to try.
Okay, now, I have made
my decision.
And what I want to do is
I want to live
the rest of my life fully,
With my family,
not in some cold hospital.
Mom, you need
to be doing
Everything that you can
right now.
Haley, I have come
to terms with this,
And this is how
I want to do it.
You're giving up.
No, I am not giving up.
I'm gonna die.
Mom, don't say that!
I can't change that, okay,
So I've accepted it.
How? How do you
just accept it, mom?
You have to fight.
Because I want to enjoy
the time I have left.
Like you've been enjoying
every day since dad died?
You're giving up,
and you know it.
You're committing suicide.
I mean, maybe quinn
can take a picture of it,
And we can just add it
to this stupid box.
Taylor. Tay.
Here's my wardrobe.
Thanks.
I -- I shortened
the dress for tomorrow.
It'll look pretty.
All the clothes
are really great.
Rough day, huh?
I've had plenty of those.
Yeah.
Guess they're going around.
Well, I'll see you
tomorrow.
Alex.
You're doing good.
You think?
Thanks.
How's my first a.D.
Doing?
Get some good footage?
Tons. You want to see?
Hit me.
I got a lot
of aunt brooke.
Jamie, bug,
You are exactly what I need
to brighten my day.
What are you doing?
She's pretty great.
How about you
hang on to this,
'cause you'll need it
next time you visit set?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Sweet.
Okay, well, oh, wow.
Make me look good.
Hi.
Hey, you.
Baby?
What's wrong?
my mom. My mom.
She came to tell us
that she --
that she was dying.
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Not really, no.
Would you like
to talk about it?
What is there to say?
You want me to say
I'm mad?
I'm mad.
This is not fair.
You say "I have cancer,"
and my whole world changes.
What am I supposed
to do with that, mom?
When I need advice on how to be
a good mother to jamie,
I call you.
When I need advice
on how to be a good wife,
I call you.
When I'm sad or mad
or happy or whatever,
I call you,
and I need you to be here.
And I am always, always gonna be
a part of you, baby.
But you are a wonderful mother
and a wonderful wife
All by yourself.
I'm...
Baby, you are
incredibly strong.
Think about everything
that you have faced.
And no matter how difficult,
You have always found
the graceful way to handle it.
Well, you are going to have
to find that strength now.
I don't want to.
I don't want
to be strong for this, mom.
I need you to be.
And your sisters --
they need you to be.
We...
Are going to have
to be strong
For everybody else
who can't be.
Mom?
Why did you call me here?
You should be home resting.
I'm sick, quinn.
I'm not a child.
Yeah, but you've had
a long day.
It was a perfect day.
This space...
Has your name
all over it.
Your photographs --
It's time for you
To open a studio
and a gallery.
So I've paid
the first six months' rent.
Okay, but, mom,
you know that --
no. No, no, no excuses.
You can do this,
and you need to do this.
Your work, baby, is important,
and it's good,
And you need to believe
in that.
Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
Are you scared?
I think...
That knowing that
your dad is there helps.
Is he, though?
I mean...
Does that place even exist?
Oh.
Of course it does.
I'm just gonna miss
all of this.
I love you.
You're gonna say
goodbye, right?
Taylor,
you're making a mistake.
Tay. Taylor, please.
I'm not gonna sit here
and watch her give up.
Does everything always
have to be about you?
Do you have to be
so selfish all the time?
She's the one
that's being selfish.
Are you kidding me?
She needs us right now.
No, what she needs
is to fight.
And you need
to stop acting
Like you know what's best
for everyone,
Because you don't.
If you leave,
you're gonna regret this.
Maybe. Maybe I will.
But I'm not gonna stay here
and watch her die.
Hey.
It's not supposed
to be like this, you know.
She -- she's supposed
to watch us
Get married
and have kids
And watch our kids
grow up and go to prom
And --
and graduate high school.
This is not --
this is not fair.
I know.
I'm really glad you're here.
me too...
'cause I don't think I could
handle it without you.
Lydia: Hey.
Knock it off.
Mm. All right.
Let's have a little wine.
Where's taylor?
Taylor is not coming.
She left.
And I tried to get her to stay,
but she wouldn't,
Not even to say goodbye,
so I'm sorry.
It's okay.
No, it's not.
It's not okay,
because you need her right now,
And we need her, and it's not
right for her to do this.
You know what?
Everyone...
Has to deal with this...
In their own way.
It'll be okay.
Millie: Marvin?
Marvin?
I am not plain.
I'm fine the way I am.
I'm fine.
Hi.
Um, my name is millicent.
And I'm new here.
And, um...
I don't really know what to say.
but I keep
telling everybody I'm fine,
And --
And I'm not fine.
Well,
you were good today.
Good -- not great.
I'm letting everyone dow
Need someone to get drunk
with you?
It's water. And I don't
get drunk when I'm sad.
I sleep with boys.
You want to get
out of here?
Do you really have
to think about it?
No, I was just -- I was
giving you a chance to
change your mind.
I don't do that,
either.
Well, okay, then.
Let's get out of here.
How you doing?
Taylor's gone.
She left. She...
My mom says
I'm my sisters' keeper.
But I couldn't
make her stay.
I'm not the glue.
My mom is.
When she's gone,
everything's gonna fall apart.
Hey.
Okay, come here.
I'm scared.
Okay, okay.
I'm heading out.
You okay?
Yeah.
Tired.
Well, for what it's worth,
I think you're doing great.
Thanks.
Coming from you,
that...Means everything.
Hey, brooke.
I miss you.
Coming from you,
that means everything, too.
Brooke: Jamie, bug,
You are exactly what I need
to brighten my day.
What are you doing?
All right, buddy,
it's time for bed.
Okay.
Mm.
Yeah, all right.
Hey, dad.
Yeah?
I was thinking I might want
to be a director
Instead of a basketball player
when I grow up, or maybe both.
As long as you're happy.
Is mom coming up?
Mom is gonna spend
some time
With her mom tonight,
all right?
Okay.
Night, buddy.