Millie was right.
Alex dupré is the perfect choice
To be the face of the new campaig
Alex, millicent huxtable,
clothes over bros.
Welcome tree hill.
Thank you.
I want you to move
your stuff in, okay ?
This is our house now,
not just mine.
Quinn, what actually happened
between you and david ?
He used to s the world
exactly the way i saw it.
He just doesn't anymore.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my wife and the love of my life.
That night after your big game
against memphis,
We had that party.
We were pretty wasted that night.
Yeah. So ?
Well, that was three months ago.
She's three months pregnant, nate.
What do you want from me ?
Huh ?
Hi, nathan.
You need to stop this now,
okay ? Do you hear me ?
Why are you doing this me ?
Cl : come on.
- - captions by vitac --
www.vitac.com
Caions paid for by
warner bros. Television
Brooke, i'm shaving.
Got to go. I'm late. I have
a big day. I love you. B.
I'm gonna kill you, mout
Alex ?
Oh, well, at least she's awake.
Alex, come on !
We got to go !
Oh, my god.
Keep it down.
I'm so tired.
Millicent : you've been out all night ?
I have to sleep.
T the shower.
I leave it on.
I like the sound of the rain.
Now i have to sleep.
Go away.
No, no. Alex, you have
a photo shoot in, like, now.
You have to get up.
I can't hear you.
I'm asleep.
Oh, there's a sheep.
Hello, counting sheep.
You're funny.
Well, there goes your counting sheep
With your half-million dollars.
Bye.
Can i just say that i hate you ?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, it's cold !
You shouldn't ve left it on,
you jerk.
Man, that guy's such a jerk.
You don't do that to no brother.
No.
Nah, you want to strip down
And parade your little flaccid
business around the apartment,
That's cool.
Go ahead with your naked ass.
But this time,
you done went too far.
It's cheap, it's mean,
and it's crossing the line.
Okay, time to man up.
Emergency situation.
Life or death.
What do you do ?
Who do you call ?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, yo, jamie scott.
I need your help.
Mcfadden.
You're friends
with nathan scott, aren't you ?
Yeah, old friends.
Why ?
Anything going on with him ?
He's in a contract year.
Right. Whatever.
A friend of mine was
having lunch yesterday.
He said he had some sort
of a misunderstanding
With a woman in a restaurant.
Okay.
It might be newsworthy.
You're kidding, righ
Well, i haa disagreement
yesterday at lunch with jerry
Over who got the last slice
of key lime pie.
It's not exactly news.
And you're not exactly newsworthy.
He is.
Check it out.
Mouth, if there's nothing there,
there's nothing there.
But i fired you'd want
to be the one to find out.
You know i didn't
do anything, right ?
I did not sleep with her
or do anything else.
You have your arm around her.
I get asked to take
a lot of pictures.
You have your arm around her
at a party
With a beer and a smile.
Haley -- i get it, nathan.
You got married in high school,
And you had a son at graduation,
And yodidn't have time
To go out and party
with your friends
And... drunken sluts
with perfect teeth.
I just took a picture with her.
That's all.
But it looks bad, nathan.
And she's smart enough to know that.
You should be, too.
Dan : what they see
is who you'll be.
Entertainment is news.
Gossip is news.
Rumor is news.
And the truth --
Well... that'negotiable.
Or is it ?
You see,
i say the truth is absolute.
I say the truth is not afraid.
And the truth is --
You're a murderer ! A murderer --
that's what you are !
Go ahead ! Tell them the truth,
dan ! Tell them what you are !
You're a murderer, is what you are !
How do you sleep at night ?!
How do you look at yourself
in the mirror ?!
Murderer ! Murderer !
Murderer !
Man : should we cut ? Mrs. Scott ?
Rachel, should we cut ?
No. Keep rolling.
But the guy called him a murderer.
Man #2 : he called the guy
a murderer.
So ?
He is one.
Hey, i'm so happy
we could make this work.
Haley's been showing me
a ton of your work,
And i am such a fan.
Thank you, brooke.
You know, i wear your designs
quite a bit,
And i really feel like
i can capture the energy
That you're after
with all the new designs.
Plus, i am so excited
to shoot alex dupré.
I mean, what is she like ?
Wow. She's like...
That.
Alex, what happened to you ?
Jet lag.
Jet lag, my foot.
You flew in from new york.
Are you hung over ?
I-i just need my pills.
Excuse me ?
You just got out of rehab.
What is that ?
What did you just take ?!
Vitamins ?
No. No.
Give it.
Ew.
They're just vitamins, you hags.
Hags ?
Half a million dollars.
Sit.
You might want to start with
a little lying-slut remover.
Millicent : this is
our rejuvenation cream.
It does wonders for jet lag,
but it smells a little bad.
Whatever.
You know you farted.
I did not fart.
That's too bad,'cause i just did.
Tell me again
what this thing look like.
What's that magical thing called ?
I think they call him puff.
The magic dragon ?
Yeah, that's exactly what
it looked like -- a dragon.
But it was like puff's evil twin.
Oh, man.
Cool.
See, mouth knows i'm scared
of creatures, right ? Mm-hmm.
That's why i know
he did this on purpose.
You think you can catch it ?
We can catch it.
You can catch it.
The new cameron crowe film, right ?
Perfect. Yeah.
Okay, thanks for letting me know.
Hi. Are you gonna work
on a cameron crowe movie ?
No, that was the video store.
I'm just renting one. Oh.
I got coffees.
Mocha double latte, extra foam.
Thank you.
Mocha double latte, no foam.
And coffee, black, two sugars.
I called haley.
Oh, thanks.
Julian.
Quinn. You made outn my bed. Hey !
Hey, so did you.
Sorry about that.
Hello.
Hot p. a. Boy.
Hi.
Oh, you must be alex.
You must be yummy.
What'd you get me ?
You get chocolate,
perfect for alleged jet lag.
Word's on the street.
And the entertaient trades --
Barely read.
Mmm.
I like him.
Yeah, well, you got a little
competition on that one.
Please, you're way too old for him.
So...
200 grand and she signs
a confidentiality agreement.
She goes away, and you have
noing to do with the kid.
I already have nothing
to do with the kid.
It's not mine.
Why is she doing this to me ?
Because u make a lot of money,
And because you're in the middle
Of a very public
contract negotiation
With a team that cares
about its image
And the only team
that you want to play for.
Which leads me to this.
Maybe we pay her.
Tell me you did not just say that.
I did, because i'm your agent,
And i wouldn't be a very good one
If i didn't least
point out the fact
That she could do
a hell of a lot of damage
If she went public with this
or filed a paternity suit.
It's not true.
I'll take a blood test.
And by that point,
the damage could be done.
Nate, your next contract
could be worth
$18 million to $20 million minimum,
Not to mention the endorsement deals
That are predicated on the fac
that nathan scott is a good guy,
He's a good father,
and he's a family man.
She's lying.
So she's lying.
You know the way it works, man.
They print the accusation
onhe front page
And the retraction on t back.
If i pay her,
then i'm saying that i did it.
I disagree.
I think you're paying a little
for a lot, and that's all.
And all i'm saying is
that it's a valid option
We should at least consider
before she... goes public.
Great.
Here comes the press.
Hey, nate, clay.
Hey.
Nate, can i talk to you ?
About what ?
Clay.
I'm cool.
I'll catch up with you. Nate...
I justant to talk
to an old friend, okay ?
Okay.
How you doing ?
That depends.
Aryou here as a reporter
or as a friend ?
Well, it depends on what's going on.
My station manager
had a friend in the restaurant
Where you had lunch yesterday --
Said you were upset about something.
Yeah.
Listen, if you need
someone to talk to,
I'm here as a friend, off the cord.
Off the record ?
The's a girl who's threatening
To file a paternity suit against me
Unless i pay her a couple
hundred thousand dollars
To keep her quiet.
Ez, nate.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I didn't do it.
I don't even know her.
Good. I'm glad.
Does haley know ?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do about it ?
I don't know.
Nothing.
Look, i shou get back,
But you let me know
if you need anything, okay ?
Ye.
Mouth...
Thks.
But, lk, if this thing
turns into something --
She files a paternity suit,
whatever --
You do what you have to do.
I hope it doesn't come to that.
Yeah.
Me too.
Okay, i'm good.
Why don't you two step in
for a couple of test shots ?
Sure.
Come pose with me.
Hold it.
He is so cute.
With big hands.
He probably has a rely big thingy.
You do know that's
brooke's boyfriend, yes ?
As in "serious boyfriend."
She dates a p. a.?
He's not a p. a.
He's a producer.
Yeah, she dates the p. a.
No, you said he's a producer.
Mnh-mnh.
As in movie producer.
No, i didn't.
Julian.
Juan.
Oh, my god, he's julian baker.
I heard that they were dating.
Damn.
Okay, she's ready.
How do i look ?
Oh, fabulous.
I didn't ask the help.
How do i look, millie ?
You want my opinion ?
Of course.
You're the only one who tells me
the frickin'truth around here.
You look amazing.
I know.
I'm such a slut.
All right, bitches.
Let's do this.
I hate her.
Yeah.
Let's talk about today's disruption.
That man wasn't wrong.
We were talking about the truth,
And what he said... was true.
I am a murderer.
But i won't hide from that.
I can't hide from that.
I step...
Into the harsh light...
Of the truth.
Because when you stand
in the light...
Audience : you get yourself right.
You find forgiveness.
You find happiness.
You find le.
I found love.
You all remember my producer, chel,
O also happens to be my wife.
I remember the night we met.
It was so romantic.
Incredibly romantic.
Dan scott ?
Nice ass.
Our courtship was old-fashioned...
Whew !
... chaste.
T bad for a guy with a bad heart.
Well, spend the night, and
we'll see if you can kill me.
It'll cost you...
A lot.
It's okay.
I'm rich, and i'm dying.
Rks for me.
He had all of the things
i was interested in.
So did you, sweetheart.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, man.
You sure you don't want
to use the net or something ?
That thing is terrible.
I think i'll be okay.
So, how come mouth
wants you to move out ?
It's just that he want this place
All to hisself with millie.
You can move into miss lauren's.
Yeah, i -- wait, listen, man.
Now, we gonna catch
this thing or what ?
I'm not so sure anymore.
I might need a little convincing.
Forget it.
Okay.
I guess it'll just have
to stay in the bathtub.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Okay, okay.
Uh, here's 10 bucks.
Which is just enough
to catch a mouse
Or maybe a guinea pig.
Now, that's dragon money.
Okay, wait here.
Okay.
Wait, hold on.
Be careful.
Look out !
I named him percy.
You're doing great, alex.
Do you need anything ?
Just some more water, please.
Thank you.
You're looking at that thing
Like there's a ghost calling you.
There is.
Husband troubles.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
You know, you and julian
seem so happy.
Mm, we are.
But i think he's bored
out of his mind.
He just gave up a movie
to be with me.
And i'm sure he's glad that he did.
You know, in our case,
i think part of the problem
Was knowing what to give up
for each other
And what to hold onto for ourselves.
Yeah.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
I know.
I just wish there was a way
to make all this go away.
There is.
You want to pay her ?!
You know full well this lying
whore didn't sleep with nathan,
And you want to pay her $200,000 ?!
Whoa, i don't want to.
I simply suggest
that it was an option.
It's not an option, clay.
And while we're suggesting things,
Let me suggest
that you are a he reason
Why this is happening right now. Ok.
You love it --
the parties, the women --
And you love having nathan alongside
you more than anything else.
That's not fair.
No ?
The picture -- the one of that woman
Draped all over my husband --
What party was that at,lay ?
Who threw that party ?
I'm not saying you don't
love him,'cause i know you do,
But you love having him at your
side more than anything else.
You could have protected him
from ts.
How, haley ?
He's a grown man.
So are you.
Start acting like it.
I don't think it's very fair --
That mouth wants you
to move out, i mean.
Man, how could you even
look at that thing ?
Ugh !
It's cool.
's gross.
That's what it is.
You sure it ain't gonna get out ?
I'm sure.
All right.
Anyway, thanks for
seeing things my way, man.
Good looking out, bro.
I just think it's your place, too.
That's what i'm ying.
Well, what did he say ?
What ?
When you told him this was your
place, too, what did he say ?
Oh, well, i didn't exactly
get to talk to him about it.
Look, i didn't have time.
He stripped off his drawer
And i had to fight fire with fire.
You guys are weird.
Anyway, he already know
that if i move out,
Miss lauren gonna want me
to move in with r,
Or g a place of our own,
And i do not need
that kind of pressure.
Well, don't you like miss lauren ?
Of course i do.
I love miss lauren.
Well, if you love her,
Why wouldn't you want
to be with her ?
Dude, i brought you over here
To help me catch
this little dragony thing,
Not to give me grief
about my commitment issues.
Now, come on.
Let's get you home.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
What about the thing ?
What about it ?
Its name is percy,
and it eats bugs and stuff.
No, no, no, no, no.
You catch it, you keep it.
I already have chester.
Maybe you can trade percy in
at the pet store
And get something else.
Either way,
you should talk to mouth.
He is your friend.
I'm sorry.
Everything you said was true.
I love nate and you and jami
And i should have done better
by all of you, and i'm sorry.
We're not paying her.
And if that's what you decide,
then of urse we're not.
But it's not my dream,
and it's not your dream.
In part it is,
but this i nathan's dream.
He's worked so damn hard for it,
And he deserves it,
and i just want to protect it --
I me, for him and for you.
This isn't fair.
I know it's not,
but if paying this woman
The money he makes
off one commercial
Protects jamie from all of this,
If it keeps his name safe
and his career safe
And u both finally get what
you've been chasing forever,
I think it's something
we should consider.
It's not fair, hales.
But nonef this is.
Dan : do you lieve in redemption ?
Rachel : i believe in money.
Ory, anyway ?
Just hang out in strip clubs,
waiting to die ?
Could be worse.
Could be better.
Lucas'novel.
Yeah.
Reminds me of who i used to be.
You do know
you're the villain in this ?
The villain has power.
I'm in here.
I'm naked on the river court.
I know. Page 88.
It's bookmarked.
So, what's with the
self-help books ?
Best seller.
People are so lazy.
Instead of changing
their bad habits,
They just buy a book.
No, people aren't lazy.
They're afraid.
They're afraid of dying
Without leaving their mark
on t world.
'cause they're lazy.
What about you ?
Hmm.
I left my mark on the world.
I just can't seem to die.
But i do know one thing.
If people saw my life,
They'd feel a lot better
about theirs.
You want tget out of here ?
I can't.
Re you can.
We both can.
Hey.
Don't drink that.
I need you.
Hi.
Thanks for the trades.
I was going crazy withounews
from the real world.
This is the real world, alex.
Not for us.
Well, it's too bad about
your lt movie falling apart.
U were good in it.
Oh, my god.
Those wigs made your head so itchy.
After every take,
i was like, "uhh !"
Oh, crap.
I'm stuck in my extensions.
A little help ?
So, how come you're not doing
that movie in new zealand ?
Ow. I slept
with a couple actors on it.
And a few crew guys.
Maybe at the same time.
Anyway, how me you're not doing it ?
I'm...
just looki for something else.
Well... i have something else
you might like.
Thanks.
P. s. -- you're totally cute.
Hey.
Hi.
How's she doing ?
Your sister ?
She's amazing.
And believe it or not,
This knucklehead actress
might actually be wortit.
Oh, great.
How you doing ?
Good.
Haley ?
Not good.
Everything was going so great
for us,
And this woman comes along
And just turns our whole world
upside down.
Hales, you know i've been in
the tabloids as much as anybody.
They lie all the time.
And people will give nathan
the benefit of the doubt.
You know that, haley bob.
Alex : unless he did it.
My best friend katie
accused this guy
Of getting her pregnant,
And it turns o he totally did it.
He had to give her
like a butt load of money,
And then she got an abortion
And bought the raddest fur coat.
Like way rad.
We need a drink.
Yeah.
Not you.
Millicent, come geter !
Mcfadden.
Hey, what's the story
with nathan scott ?
Nothing.
There is no story.
Here's my problem with paying her.
It's not the money.
I mean, it is the money,
but what if it comes out
That we paid some pregnant lady
to buy her silence ?
She would never be abl
to talk about it.
She'd have to sign
a confidentiality agreement.
What gonna stop her
from doing that ?
I mean, since wee clearly dealing
With such a trustworthy
human being. Right.
Quinn : i don't understand.
The woman claims
that she's pregnant, you know,
And that nathan's the father,
but in this day and age,
You can prove that kind of thing
so easily, you know,
With an amniocentesis or
eventually a blood test, so...
He didn't do it.
He said he didn't do it,
so i believe him.
Okay, of course, but then --
Look, she's hoping that nathan cas.
E's pregnant,
she doesn't have any money,
And she knows that nathan scott
has a lot to lose,
So why not take a shot ?
I say you call her bluff
And don't pay the dumb bitch a dime.
That's what i said,
but it's gonna go public,
And it's gonna affect jamie,
And nathan's basketball contract
is up for rewal.
Millicent : hi.
Hi.
Hi. hi.
I'll be right back.
Alex, you can't drink those.
Fine !
But love tequila.
Used to.
Here.
You drink them,
and i'll just have the lime.
No.
Please ?
Pretty, pretty, pretty please ?
Mmm.
Ugh !
Nice !
Are we drunk yet ?
We're buzzed.
Oh, i miss being buzzed.
Okay, don't tell any of the boys
that i'm sober.
That way, if i do anything slutty,
I can still blame the booze.
Thank, millie. See ya.
So, the photo shoot went well ?
It went great, acally.
This one's kind of good
at her job for being a james.
Former james.
Possibly future james.
But thank you.
You know, i used to make haley
bob pose for me all the time.
Remember, hales ?
Sorry.
I'm sorry, you guys.
I really appreciate this,
but i'm gonngo talk to nathan.
I'll catch up with you later.
Hey.
I'm here for anything.
I know.
Thank you.
I'll see you at home.
Ok.
You know what ?
I should probably go
get some work done.
Do you want to go ?
No, i think i'm gonna stay here.
Do you want to talk about it ?
Truthfully,
i want to drink about it.
Okay.
You did great work today, quinn.
Thank you so much, brooke.
Yeah.
Mouth.
Yeah, ha ha, very funny.
You got me good, too, man.
No, i did not scream
like a little girl.
No, i did not.
Yeah, well, you would scream
like a little girl, too,
If a reptile ambushed you like that.
Look, anyway,
i want to call a truce.
So, we need to talk when
you get home later, all right ?
No, it was just something
jamie said.
So, i guess i'll see you later,
And i guess i'll try
and explain it to you.
All right, bro.
All right.
Late
How am i gonna explain this to him ?
Maybe you won't have to.
I... i hate that
somebody can do this to you
And get away with it,
nathan -- i do.
But...
You're the one who fought
as hard as you did
To get where you are now,
And you're the one
who never gave up yourself,
So...
If you want to make
this hole thing go away,
Then you do that,
And i won't speak of it again.
Let me get a dixie
and a shot of tequila, chilled.
I love tequila.
Used to.
Doesn't go too well with rehab.
Alex dupré, right ?
Right.
And you're that boy who owns
the big house on the beach.
I'm the boy that rents
that big house on the beach.
Clay.
Hi.
Uh...
Go ahead.
Just do it quick.
I miss that.
The kissing or the drinking ?
Yes.
Quinn : wow.
You're a piece of work.
My sister's in tears,
my brother-in-law's unemployed,
And you're sucking face
with dumb girls at the bar.
Wow, your husband must be
so happy right now.
I'm sorry.
That was unfair.
Yeah, it haseen one of those days.
How you holding up ?
If i was one of your clients,
i'd be listed as "day to day
Aren't we all ?
Nate.
Okay.
I'll take care of it.
I got toun.
Hey, clay ?
I hope you know what you're doing.
You too.
I can be in your bed in 20 minutes.
Make it 30.
Quinn :eally ?
You're that guy ?
I am tonight.
What's on your mind, baby ?
Oh.
I'm sorry what happened today
with that man in the crowd
You work so hard for me and --
and the show, and i just...
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
I hired hito do it.
Why ?
Because you can't hide
from what you did, dan.
And because whenever we shine
a light on your mistakes,
You fight back,
And that inspires people.
Besides, it makes for good tv.
Hi.
Alex.
What can i do for you ?
You said you were loing
for something different.
Look, alex, i --
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking i'm hot,
and you're also thinking
The dumb actress
just gave you a stupid script,
But it's not stupid,
and i'm not dumb.
Okay, well, i'm a little dumb,
But i know a good script
when i read it.
Okay.
I'll take a look.
Hey, when i said i had
something different for you,
You thought i meant me, huh ?
Um... no.
Some other boy gets me tonight.
But we can totally meet up after
if you want.
Chuckles ]
That's okay.
I'm good.
Yeah.
I'll bet you are.
David : answer it, quinn.
You're gonna have to
talk to me sometime.
Well, at least you're wring pants.
Look, if i move out,
Lauren gonna want me
to move in with her.
So what ?
You love lauren.
I know, but, look,
first we move in together,
And then she gonna want
to get married.
And, man, we even ain't
even gotten into that yet.
Look, i'm not even sure
if i ever want to get married.
And i'm not saying that i don't
love lauren, because i do.
I'm just not sure
what i want to do yet.
Well, you shld have said that.
Yeah, well, you should have asked.
You're a good roommate, skills,
and a good friend.
You stay as long as you want,
all right ?
All right.
I didn't expect her
to be such a mess.
I'm sorry about that.
No, me too, but i'll tell you
what -- the camera loves her.
She looks healthy and smart...
Happy.
Hmm.
I appreciate you meeting me.
I just want what's fair.
Yeah.
This is, uh...
This is the amount
that we're willing to pay
To make this go away.
It's empty.
That's right.
It's empty because
you're a lying bitch,
And we're not paying you a dime.
Go to hell.
He talked to her.
It didn't go well.
It's gon get worse.
I should talk to jamie.
Sync by honeybunny www.addic7ed.com