Previously in "One Tree Hill"...
Millie was right.
Alex Dupre is the perfect choice
to be the face of the new campaign.
You do know that's Brooke's boyfriend, right?
- She dates a PA?
- He's not a PA, he is a producer.
I know what you're thinking.
But I know a good script when I read it.
Ok. I'll take a look.
Quinn, what happened
between you and David?
He used to see the world exactly the way I saw it.
He just doesn't anymore.
You're gonna have to talk to me sometime.
There's a girl who's threatening to
file a paternity suit against me,
unless I pay her a couple hundred
thousands dollars to keep her quiet.
- What are you gonna do about it?
- I don't know.
What are you gonna do about it?
Nothing.
The amount we're willing to pay to make this go away.
It's empty.
It's empty because you're a lying bitch
and we're not paying you a dime.
One Tree Hill - Season 7 Episode 4
Believe Me, I'm Lying
You missed another workout.
It's four in a row.
Should I be worried?
I haven't been in the mood.
Look, I get that, but you can't
lose sight of what's in the line.
Right now, your job is to stay in shape.
Am I gonna have a job, this year?
- What's going on with my contract, Clay?
- I'm working on it.
- Should I be worried?
- We're gonna get it done. I promise you that.
Why haven't we heard anything?
I told you, man, things are in process.
I'm not talking about my deal.
This girl, Renee...
It's been three days since we told her
we won't gonna pay her anything.
You think she decided to back off?
I doubt it.
Don't come out.
And we're prepared for that.
But until then, you can't just sit around
holding your breath until it happens.
Alright? I need you to get your
head back in the game, Nate.
Alright?
Ok.
Let's go.
Dude, good find! I love this stuff.
Here's my official cereal selecter. Say that 3 times fast.
Cereal Selecter. Cereal Selecter. Cereal Selecter.
Nice.
- This has too much sugar. Keep working.
- I knew it.
Too much sugar?
Ok, I've seen you eat 5 balls
of Count Chocula in one sitting.
That was on a dare from Taylor, and before I became a mom.
You'll see, you're gonna have kids some day.
Dude, hand over that crystal ball.
I have a few questions for it.
You know, I have a question too.
What happened with you and
David at Tric? It's been a few days.
He wants me to come home and I told him
I need more time to figure things out.
Now we're talking.
Too healthy. Keep looking. It's out there.
For your information, these cereals
have everything you need.
That's the thing, I might have everything that I need
that doesn't mean that's everything that I want.
What is that smell?
That would be sandalwood.
Seriously, with the incense?
It's relaxing.
It's giving me a headache.
Sorry. Are you nervous about your big day?
If you're referring to the fashion show that we've
poured too much time and money into,
then, yeah.
I'm not gonna lie, I'm nervous about it.
Well, you shouldn't be. You're Brooke Davis.
You're starting to sound like
Victoria, and that's weird for me.
Do you have a new script?
Oh, that's the script Alex gave me the other
night. I was just writing down some ideas.
- I thought you didn't like it.
- I don't.
But the story's pretty good. There might be something there.
Well, you don't have to do
this for me. I don't even like Alex.
Oh, I'm not doing it as a favor.
I know a good idea when I see one.
Besides, people love a comeback story, and Alex
is a good actress when she finds the right role.
So, it's worth a look.
Ok.
I'll see you later.
Hey, Brooke Davis...
you look beautiful today.
Please be awake, please be awake.
Alex!
- You're... ready.
We have a job to do, don't we?
Yes, we do.
It's called "being professional"
which I'm kinda known for it.
Used to be. Oh, my God,
you look hot by the way.
Now tell me I look hot too bitch, because I do.
- You look hot too, bitch.
- Thanks.
Ok, right.
Even though it's incredibly riventing
watching you lift weights,
I think I'm gonna head out.
What time do you go to the fashion show tonight?
I don't know. Whatever. You going?
Do I really want to watch a group
of hot models parade on stage?
Getting early, buddy.
You're doing good, Nate.
It's about 20?
I'm at 27.
You know, you don't bring the bar on your
chest every time, we don't count those.
I'm watching you.
Hello?
Ok.
Yeah, we knew there was a chance of that.
Thank you.
I don't care what you say. That was 30. I'm done.
The story burn out, Nate.
It's out there.
Where?
What you got there, little man?
What's a love child?
I bought every copy I could find.
I'm sorry, Hales.
- You don't have to keep apologize.
- Yes, I do.
I'm responsible for this family and it
kills me that you have to go through this.
We are going through this, Nathan, together.
We knew this was gonna happen. We made a choice
and I still think it was the right thing to do.
Has Jamie seen this?
He was the one that found it.
He's just such a good boy. He doesn't understand
why somebody would lie like this.
Is he home?
No, he went to the park with Quinn.
I thought it'd be good for him to spend
some time with his friends right now.
"The first time we were together, Nathan
couldn't get enough, and neither could I."
- Naughty naughty!
- Shut up, Chuck, it's not true.
Yeah, right. My mom says they don't put
stuff in these magazines unless it's true.
- Your dad's hosed.
- He is not.
Yeah.
I think I should be allowed enough
time to figure out exactly what I want.
- I mean, don't I deserve that?
- Yeah.
But David doesn't see it that way,
he just wants to work it out.
What if I don't want to work it out? What if I can't?
Then what?
Boys...
Refresh my memory.
Did I not asked you to look into
the Nathan Scott situation
and find out if there was a story?
I did, but there wasn't.
The why does the National Informer have one?
The National Informer? Are you being serious?
Oh oh, look at this: alien babies on the rise.
They scooped us on that one too,
maybe you should hire them.
Maybe I will.
Come on, Charlie, this isn't news.
Right now it's nothing but a
rumor in some low-rent tabloid.
But as soon as we report on that,
we validate it. It becomes news.
It's not fair and it's not what I do.
What you do is what I tell you to do.
Or else you can go drag the ratings
down at someone else's station.
Quinn did a really great job with
these, Alex looks beautiful.
Yeah, now all we have to do is pick one.
The winner goes in tonight gift bag.
So which one's the winner?
- I was kind of hoping you'd pick.
- Millie...
this is your decision and I want you to make it.
You're good at it.
Ok. That's go... this one.
Perfect.
Ok. Millie, even though you are completely
in charge of tonight's fashion show
I decided to bring in a little experience just to help
everything runs smoothly.
- Please don't freak out.
- Please don't tell me you invited...
Well, well.
Hi boss.
These are lovely.
Here's your winner.
I already picked this one.
I guess it will have to do then.
She's quite percy you know.
Woman your husband slept with.
- At least the baby will be adorable.
- Why would you say something like that?
What? The National Informer isn't
a reliable source of information?
My mistake.
You got time for a brother-in-law?
David, hi!
- Oh, it's good to see you.
- It's good to see you too.
- It's crazy out there.
- Yeah, we're having a fashion show tonight.
And the Noisettes are playing, so, it should be fun.
Maybe I'll stop by.
You know, Quinn's gonna be here.
Does that might ?????? to stay away?
No, no, that's not what I meant.
I would love for you to come, I just feel like
it might be a little awkward right now.
Could you give her a message from me?
Just tell her I miss her,
and that I love her.
If she ever wants to talk to me I'll be
right here, I'm not going anywhere.
- It was good to see you.
- To see you too.
Okay.
Bye.
Millie.
This... just came for you.
Hi, Mrs. Davis. How are you?
I'm sorry. Have we met?
Yeah, many times.
I used to date your daughter.
Every time that I said "hello",
you asked me if we'd met.
Well, until next time then.
"To Millie: I'm sorry I can't be there for your
big night but I can't wait to celebrate.
I'm proud of you. Love, Marvin. "
Sweet.
You know where this would
look perfect? In your car.
Nice flowers! Who's the old lady?
The old lady is Brooke's mother.
Victoria, this is Alex Dupre.
She's the star of tonight
show. Alex, Victoria Davis.
So you're the former actress we're overpaying.
Oh wait, Millie told me all about you.
How you were this evil bitch
who used to run everything here,
- but now you're just an evil bitch.
- I didn't say that.
In those words.
Well, I'll let you get back to not making movies.
You are fun.
Hey, Haley Bob. Have you seen these?
Yeah, they are gorgeous.
I could not help noticing that you
signed yourself as Quinn James.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I thought it was a good idea.
You know, kinda like a fresh start.
Fresh start?
You know what I mean.
You need to tell David how you feel, Quinn.
He came by here today and he wanted
me to tell you that he loves you
and he misses you,
and he'll wait for you. And he meant every word of it.
All I wanted more than anything was to
tell him that you felt the same way.
Yeah, but that's not your place, is it?
No, it's not. It's yours.
Just tell him the truth, Quinn. He's still your
husband, even if you don't love him anymore.
If you owe him anything at all, it's truth.
Jamie Scott, you're late.
I am?
Aren't you here to help me
pass out these gift bags?
- Sure. What do I do?
- Put one of those on every chair.
Just... put my son to work?
Absolutely. Clothes Over Bros
has a long history for child labor.
I'm just kidding. I thought...
it might help take his mind off things.
- You read the National Informer.
- No.
But I heard about it.
I only read those things when I'm in them
'cause I'm still waiting for that story
to come out about and Johnny Depp.
Nice.
Seriously, Nate, I've been on
the tabloids a thousand times,
and it's never been anything but rumors and lies.
Look...
all you can do is weather the storm
don't feed the flame and make it worse.
And eventually they'll move on to somebody else.
I just have one question.
How do you explain that to a seven-year-old?
Quinn told me the guys were
teasing you this morning.
Want to talk about it?
Chuck said that I was gonna
have a brother or a sister.
I promise you if you ever do
have a little brothers or sister,
it would be from your mom and me.
Why is she lying?
Cause sometimes bad people forget
the difference between right and wrong.
And these people, sometimes...
they like to take advantage of good people...
like us.
Do you ever forget?
No.
And you know why?
'Cause every time I'm not so
sure I'm doing the right thing,
I take a look at this picture of you and your mom,
and it reminds me of everything that's important to me.
And it always helps me do the right thing.
Ok?
I need you for about 10 minutes.
There's a reporter here from
Visual Lyrics Magazine
and she wants to ask you a few
questions about Red Bedroom.
I'm not really up for an interview
today, Miranda, okay?
No, it's not okay.
This label needs is starving for some good
press, and it's exactly how you get it.
So if that means to take a
few minutes to kiss it at last...
you get up and do it.
The truth is, this reporter has influence
and we don't want her on our bad side, okay?
Ten minutes.
Vicki.
Brooke didn't tell me you
were coming in for the show.
Consider me Millicent training wheels,
and don't ever call me Vicki again.
Sorry. I thought we were bonding.
You thought wrong.
Tell me... how's your father?
- It's Paul, right?
- Yeah.
Has he taken a lover recently?
What just happened?
Sorry. I thought we were bonding.
You thought wrong.
You know, my daughter seems so happy lately.
In fact, she seems happier that I've ever seen her.
I'm assuming I owe that to you.
Are you starting to approve of me?
Don't be silly.
She could do so much better.
Good bye, Julian.
Say hello to Paul for me.
You tell him if he's ever in search
of a lover, to give me a call.
Please stop saying "lover".
Everyone knows about Mia Catalano.
What about Haley James Scott?
When does your next album come out, Haley?
We've been working hard so, hopefully soon.
Maybe I'll send you some tracks see if you like them.
I'd like that.
Now, let's talk about your
reaction when you found out
your husband not only had an affair
but has got another woman pregnant .
Sorry, Angela. Time's up.
You promised me 10 minutes,
Miranda. It's only been 5.
Well, you forfeited the other 5 when
you asked that stupid question.
- The question was relevant.
- No, it was personnal.
Now, if you really wanna get personnal,
we can talk about that time
in the Hamptons three years ago,
when you got drunk and soiled yourself.
Now, that was a messy situation.
Look, that never happened.
You just made that up.
Oh, then I'm sure you're sympathetic to Haley's situation...
since her husband's affair was also made up.
Off you go.
We'll look forward to reading your column.
What if she hates us?
Who reads "Reviews" anyway?
Excuse me.
Those waters are for the models, not the help.
Oh, no, I'm not...
Supposed to be back here. I know, sweetie.
You see this, is where the pretty people play.
You don't qualify.
Makenna Gage, right?
Oh, my gosh, you're so pretty in person.
All the other girls are such skanks.
- I'm Alex, by the way.
- I know who you are.
I love your movies.
I'm actually doing some acting down
too, but I still model on the side.
Oh, I knew that we had
something in common.
You remember that movie you
did about the double agent?
I auditioned for your part.
Well, they told me I was too hot.
No offense.
Oh, my God.
We should totally do a movie together.
Totally. We would have so much fun.
You party, right?
Of course you do. You have to try
these, they're so kick-ass.
I usually take three, but you
should probably only take two.
Give me four.
Hi, David.
Quinn.
It's good to see you.
You too.
This reminds me of this park where we first met.
You know, I almost proposed you there.
Really? You never told me that.
I had the ring. It was a bveautiful night.
You were a little drunk, so I've been
asking myself the chances to ask.
So what happened?
I decided to wait for a better moment.
Well, that's us isn't it?
Always waiting for something.
That's not true.
Remember that job in San Francisco?
You didn't take it because you
felt something better might come.
And it did.
I know it did.
And you were right to wait.
But that was two years of our lives we could have
been experiencing something exciting and new, and...
instead we just put our lives on hold.
I didn't realize you felt that way.
I didn't at the time.
You know, we made that decision together,
and I was fine with that decision then.
The person I am today wouldn't
have waited those two years.
Ok.
I understand that, but I can change too.
I can be whoever you want me to be.
I won't wait you change for me.
It's not fair.
I want you to be you because,
you're a wonderful person.
So is this the part you tell me you love
me, but you're not in love with me?
So that's it?
There's nothing I can do to save our marriage?
I'm sorry, David.
I think we should get a divorce.
That is the sexy group. You girls look amazing.
And when you're out there,  don't worry, they
will be staring at you, they will be staring at me.
Wait.
Where is the red cocktail dress?
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8... 9!
- Why am I counting nine?
- Because there's nine of us.
Where is Makenna?
Someobody wake her up.
Good luck, I saw her swallow a
hand full of pills. She's such a cliche.
Victoria, please, tell me you can fix this.
This is Millie's show, remember?
I'm sure she has a backup plan.
Yes, I do.
We double up one model. The first girl on stage
changes and goes out in the final piece.
Ok.
Okay, that works... what about the final work?
- We loose one piece from the collection.
- That's unacceptable.
- Millie can handle it.
- Well, clearly she can't.
No, I mean Millie can do it,
she can take Makenna's place.
Me? I'm not a model.
She's definitely not a model.
Neither am I, but I'm still going out there.
She's gorgeous, she's got better legs than Makenna
and let's face it, and she's your only option.
Unless, of course, you want to
go out there with your walker.
Millie, strip down.
Chop chop.
Chase, I thought you managed this place now.
Mostly. But, I kinda miss being back here.
I invented a new drink, you should
try. It's called "the brain hemorrhage".
You know there's already a drink
called the brain hemorrhage, right?
I'm sorry, man. I'm sure yours is much better.
Damn it! I'll get you a beer.
Ok.
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
Listen, the press are gonna be here
later, so I want you to practise
two very important words...
- "No comment".
- What if I do make a comment?
Maybe just... tell my side of things?
I'd be careful about that, it's just
a game you don't wanna play.
So, what do you think? It's not bad, eh?
It's delicious, it should be illegal.
This is the worst drink I ever had.
- Brain hemorrhage?
- Yeah, good call on the beer.
How are those nerves holding up?
I'm about to be judged by fashion critics
who had to fly to North Carolina
and love to witness failure.
Well, then I guess they're gonna
be disappointed tonight.
I brought you something that's
gonna relieve all your stress.
You got me a present?
Sandalwood.
It must have broken in half on the way over here.
Oh well, I guess this will have to do.
You still nervous?
For what?
Where am I?
I want to thank you all
for coming here tonight.
Those of you who traveled
down here to Tree Hill.
I know we're not in New
York but this is my home
and this is the place that inspired the line,
so I hope you enjoy it as much as we do.
Now, to kick us off, we are thrilled to bring you...
Noisettes!
Hey.
- I'll be right back.
- Ok.
- Hey.
- Hey!
The show just started.
- Fine.
- Good.
Did you talk to David?
Yeah.
I don't want to hurt him, Haley.
This is what I have to do.
You okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
This is Brooke's night.
I can't do this, what if they laugh?
Nobody is gonna laugh. Your hot ass is
about to pull the roof off of this place.
- Millie, are you ready for this?
- I don't know Brooke,
it doesn't feel right. I'm not a size zero.
- What did you just say?
- I said I'm not a size zero.
Of course you're not.
Millie, I have an idea,
I just need more time.
I got this.
Is that Millie? She looks gorgeous!
So, you were clearly the crowd favorite tonight.
When did you come out with this
idea to put yourself in the show?
Well, the truth is, one of our models...
One of our models, Alex Dupre
she was brought in specially
to headline this collection.
She was a fabulous choice,
but we had this little surprise
planned for several months.
Clothes Over Bros is a line for real women.
Zero is not a size.
We're just thrilled that all of you
responded the way we hoped you will.
Thank you so much for coming.
I'll give it to you... you're good.
I know.
Hey Alex, is Brooke around?
Oh,she's somewhere receiving praise.
I thought you were avoiding me.
Why would I avoid you?
I don't know. Maybe because you
haven't read the script I gave you?
Oh, I read it.
You want my honest opinion?
Of course.
It's not that good.
Which part?
The beginning, middle and end.
Ok, uh... what did you hate about it?
I didn't say I hated it. The
writing just needs a little focus.
But somewhere underneath all the clutter,
I think there is a really solid story there.
I wouldn't mind meeting with the writer. I got a few ideas.
I wrote it.
- You wrote what?
- That clutter filled messy you hated.
- No, I told you, I didn't hate it.
- You said it wasn't good.
I also said it has potential.
And if that's your first script...
I am really impressed, Alex.
If you're serious about this, I would
be willing to work with you on it.
But only if you're committeed.
I would love to commit to you, Julian.
- We're totally gonna make this movie.
- Okay, hold on.
Let's get the script in shape
first, after that we'll see.
Ok.
I forgot.
How'd it go with the famous
actress? Was it oscar worthy?
- It was just sex.
- Right.
You know, I'm trying to figure out if this is the person you really are
or just the person you want
everyone to think that you are.
Maybe a little of both.
You look like you need a drink.
Yes.
I want one of those blue
drinks, those look good.
Chase...
another brain hemorrhage.
It's called a brain blaster now.
Right, just make sure it's extra blue.
- What's this?
- That's the last minute changes.
- Who made them.
- Charlie.
We're alive at three...
two...
Miranda.
Listen...
I just wanted to thank you for
what you did earlier.
I felt a little blindsight in there, and...
it meant a lot that you stuck up for me.
I'm just being consistent.
If they're not willing to let you use
personal issues as an excuse to get off work,
I am certainly not gonna let
some bitch come in the way.
Ok. Well, whatever your motivation was, thank you.
You're welcome. And besides,
I've I always hated that cow.
And Albert Pujols continued his
torrid summer by knocking in 4 runs,
as the Redbirds drop the Phillies 8 to 5.
And finally...
that is the night in sports.
Go to commercial, go to commercial now.
You just keep walking McFadden.
You're off the air.
- What took you so long?
- Sorry.
Running low on Jagermaister and Sambuca.
Is he being serious?
Yep, never mind that. Just sit back and
enjoy this delicious blue masterpiece.
- That's really good, thank you.
- You are the boss.
Oh my God, you're so evil.
I'm sure I'm gonna have nightmares about
this drink. Why would you do that?
So now we can say we both went throught it.
Can I talk to you?
David.
Look, this isn't the time or place for this.
- You're my wife, Quinn.
- And you're drunk.
Just go home and sleep it off,
ok? We'll talk about it later.
- No, I want to talk about it now.
- No, I don't want to.
- I want to talk about it now.
- No.
You need to back up.
And you need to stay out of this,
this is none of your business.
I'm making it my business, alright?
You think you're having a rough day.
Damn it, Clay.
Fighting over a girl... huge turn on.
I was just defending a friend.
Well, that's good to know,
I was getting a little jealous.
You know, I'm still turned on though.
How about I come over later
and take care of that hand...
and any other body part that
might need special attention?
Maybe some other time.
You did great tonight, Alex. I'll see you.
Nathan Scott!
Do you have a comment regarding the allegations
made about you in the National Informer?
Yes, I do have a comment.
I'd just like to say, I'm very proud of my friend Brooke Davis.
Tonight she reminded all of us just how talented she is.
As for the other stuff, no I have no comment.
Thanks.
I hate to admit it, but
Millicent really did pull it off.
Yeah. And Alex really pulled it off her.
- She did. That was a good idea.
- Thank you.
I tell you what's not such a good idea...
letting that girl got to close to Julian.
Alex?
He just read some script she gave him.
- Julian is a good guy, mom.
- Yes, he is.
And I have a feeling she wrecked
a few good guys in her day.
Hey, Alex.
Listen, I just wanted to thank you
for everything you did for me tonight.
I still can't believe that was me.
- Hum, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Hold on, bitch.
There's no way I'm letting you go home.
There's an after-after party that
nobody's invited to, except us.
- You're going.
- That's not really my scene.
It is now. Look, don't worry I'll have your
cute ass home before the sun comes up.
And if you hate it, we'll leave.
Come on, come on.
Please? Say yes.
- Yes.
Let's go. Come on.
Hey, Millie. It's me.
I kinda had a bad night, so
I was really hoping to talk to you.
You always make me feel better.
Anyway, I'm sure the show is great
and I can't wait to hear all about it.
I'll wait up. I love you.
You know, even with all the
models on this stage tonight
the most beautiful woman
at the show was backstage.
Thank you.
No, I was talking about Victoria.
I'm thinking of setting her up with my dad.
Apparently she's in search of a lover.
- What just happened?
- Don't ask.
Ok.
I saw you talking to Alex. How did she take it
when you told her you don't like the script?
Actually, it turns out, she wrote
it, and she needs some help.
So I'm gonna work with her on that.
Who knows? Maybe we can get it in a good
enough shape and make a movie out of it.
I don't know how I'm gonna do this.
I don't know how to let you go.
I don't know how to keep you.
This isn't you, Quinn.
Maybe you're right, David.
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
Is this the life you want?
Fancy parties, celebrities?
Or is that the life you think you want.
Maybe a little of both.
I want you to go home, David.
I think it's time we move on with our lives.
You need to go home and let go of me.
I won't.
You're gonna have to.
You know, you're... working hard to
convince yourself that's it's over,
but you'll never love me again.
But nothing you do is gonna
make me go with hope.
You'd be better off letting me go.
- Give me a ride?
- Sure.
Where to?
Your place.
You sure you wanna do this?
He'll never forgive you.
Just drive.
What are you doing here?
He doesn't love you.
Honey, you don't know
what you're talking about.
He told me while we were making love.
Get the hell out of my way, slut.
Maybe I am a slut, but that's
what Nathan liked about me.
He had me do all kinds of things to him
that he said you would never...
You're gonna pay for that one.
Transcript by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com