I killed my brother.
Her heart rate's dropping.
Come on, karen.
Just breathe.
Come on, haley,
just breathe.
You're doing good, baby.
You're doing so good.
I'm right here.
Come on, mom.
She coded.
Mom!
Karen?
Oh.
Yuck!
Who's that?
Don't you know?
She's our daughter.
Mommy! Daddy!
Come play with me!
Goodness.
What flower is this, mommy?
This is a lily.
Oh, she's beautiful.
Just like her mother.
Mommy, come with me.
You should go
watch over her.
I'll wait for you.
It's okay.
I'll be right here.
Come with me, mommy!
Look for me in the lilies.
Stats and vitals rising.
We got her back.
"Now is the time
for us to shine,
"The time when our dreams
are within reach
"And possibilities vast.
"Now is the time
for all of us...
...to become the people
we've always dreamed of being."
Aah!
"This is your world.
You're here."
It's a boy.
Ohh!
"You matter."
Oh, my god.
Just relax.
You're a dad!
You did so good.
We have a son.
I want to see him.
Hi.
Hi, baby.
"The world is waiting."
Welcome to the world,
james lucas scott.
Look, that's your daddy.
He's so beautiful.
That's your daddy.
Unbelievable.
He's only mellow
when we play rap music?
What happened to the classical
music i played for nine months?
I got a confession to make.
Every time you fell asleep,
i went to old-School hip-Hop.
That's my boy, isn't it?
That's my boy.
You like some
old-School hip-Hop, huh?
Yeah.
Hi, keith.
It's us.
Her name is lily.
Lily roe scott.
Hi.
I'm gonna be seeing you in her
every day.
You've got to be kidding me.
Again?
I guess.
Huh.
Doesn't look like
anything's wrong.
You sure it won't start?
Peyton?
Oh, the car's fine.
I was just
feeling sentimental
About the first time
we spoke.
Feeling
sentimental,
Or avoiding packing
For your trip to los angeles
with brooke tomorrow?
I don't want to go.
I mean, i do want to go.
I'm just --
I'm gonna miss you.
Come on, look.
At least you know
what you're gonna do.
You still
haven't decided yet?
I just didn't see this
other thing coming, you know?
Can i help you?
I don't think so.
I just keep telling myself
That there will be some
significant moment
When i will know
what to do.
How about you?
Can i help you?
Yeah.
Remember when your mom
was in the hospital,
And you asked me just
to lie with you and heal you?
Yeah.
I think i could use some
of that healing before tomorrow.
I can do that.
So, you know,
there's a big party tonight,
Kind of a last hurrah
for all the seniors.
I know, but what are we gonna do
with the baby?
Cue
the crazy grandmother.
And f.Y.I.,
If either of you ever calls me
"grandmother" in public,
I'll use my gun.
Which is at the range,
Safe from the most beautiful
baby boy in the world.
Next to you, nathan,
of course.
Oh, who am i kidding?
You are the cutest.
You, you, you.
Go.
I'll watch him.
Oh, i don't know.
We're underage, mom,
And there's gonna be
drinking, alcohol,
Probably some drugs.
You're going to the party,
and you're going to have fun.
We insist.
Now go.
Bring me home some drugs.
Isn't grandma funny?
Isn't she?
Wow.
So, what's the deal
with this party, anyway?
At midnight, the tree hill high
computers change over,
And the juniors
become seniors.
So, what happens to us?
We're gone.
I don't want
to be gone.
Well, you got
until midnight.
Hey, let me
ask you guys something.
Does it look like
i'm wearing a blouse?
I like it.
Uh, it's a little...
Great.
I'm the blouse man.
It looks like i'm competing in
men's ice dancing, doesn't it?
No, it looks like you're winning
men's ice dancing.
Stop it.
It's fine.
I'm just playing.
As long as you don't have
wine coolers in that bag,
You're good.
You know what?
You guys go ahead.
I'm gonna, uh,
grab my jacket.
Ahh.
Hey, listen.
I'm gonna stay
out of your way tonight
'Cause i know you got a lot
of people to say goodbye to£¿£¿
Before you leave tomorrow.
Maybe
i don't even have to go.
I mean,
what do interns do anyway?
They, like, answer phones.
I already know
how to answer phones.
Look -- Hello?
You're going,
and you're gonna have fun.
Okay, we'll have fun.
Just, maybe i should give deb
one quick call just to check in.
Hales, come on,
i miss the boy, too,
But we're not gonna be
those crazy, obsessive parents.??
You need to enjoy one last night
with all your friends.
Okay, i won't call.
All right.
Tonight's gonna rock.
Tonight's gonna suck.
I can't believe
they're gonna erase us.
No, i see possibilities
in a night like this.
It's your last chance
to tell someone you love them,
Maybe apologize
to an old friend,
Try something new.
Tonight has greatness
written all over it.
I can feel it.
Okay.
Name.
Brooke davis.
I'm sorry.
I've got strict orders
not to admit brooke davis.
Excuse me?
Whose stupid party
is this, anyway?
Mine, bitch.
And your fat ass
isn't invited.
Aah!
Oh, my god.
Well, if it isn't
the only guy
To ever leave me in a hotel room
before the sex.
Well, well.
Come here.
Oh!
Where you been?
What are you doing here?
Well, where i've been's
a long story.
What i'm doing here's
pretty easy.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
??Hang out with her
too long,
You're gonna end
up in honey grove.
I need to borrow you.
Come with me,
boy and friend.
Where???
Someone's playing
spin the bottle.
Spin the bottle?
What are we -- 13?
Shut up.
God.
Look, if you ask me,
it's really stupid
That we all ever stopped
playing spin the bottle,
So quit being so grumpy.
Hey, you'd be grumpy, too,
if a girl you had history with
Just showed up
out of the blue.
Mouth.
You were saying?
Uh...
Hi.
Hey, deb, hi.
It's -- It's me.
I -- I'm sorry to bother you.
I just wanted to --
Check in, yeah.
Everything's great?
Great. Okay, good, good.
All right. Thanks.
Oh, also, can you
just not tell nathan that i,
Um, th i called this time --
Or last time?
Thanks.
Also, uh, before you go,
He really likes his little...
Giraffe.
Ow!
That's foroaking me
at the last party.
The bitch slap, i deserved.
That's for flicking me
in the back of the head.
I'm gonna miss this.
Is that nathan scott, big-Time
college basketball player?
Small-Time
college basketball player.
Well, whatever, but...
Congratulations, man --
On everything.
How's fatherhood?
It's awesome.
How's brotherhood?
Awesome.
She's beautiful, £¿£¿man.
Handsome kid.
Looks like his uncle.
We got to go see him.
Yeah, i know.
But what do you say
to your father the murderer?
Whatever we say,
we just get it over with.
I'm tired of carrying it around
and avoiding him.
Let's do it tonight.
Let's stop
running from him.
Okay.
Okay,
we'll go later tonight, then.
May need
a few drinks first.
Lucas...
I'm sorry
i didn't believe you.
I'm sorry i was right.
Brooke davis,
look to your right,
And you'll see
the hottest guy at the party.
Hey...
Hi, tutor mom.
How you feeling --
You having fun
or you worried about the kid?
Um, i am...
Worried --
About you, too.
I'm gonna miss you
this summer.
Okay, don't.
Don't do that.
Don't make me cry
'Cause i'm barely
holding it together as it is.
Nathan and i want you
to be james' godmother.
Okay, that's gonna do it.
Haley.
I would be honored
to be his godmother,
And i promise you that,
unlike my ungodly mother,
I will so kick ass
at this.
I know you will --
As long as you don't say
"kick ass" around him too much.
Right, sorry.
Like your leather.
You're shelly, right?
Yeah. Uh, we had
current events together, right?
Right, yeah.
Hey,
i just want to tell you,
I think clean teens
is really cool.
Thanks.
I...
kind of ended it.
Oh.
Well, it's
still really brave of you.
I totally would have joined
if i didn't love sex so much.
That's a joke.
Yeah.
Man, clean teen wardrobe
sure has changed.
I want back in.
Look at this.
It's like a clean teen reunion.
All we need now is chase, but
honestly, he's not that clean.
He appreciates
the art of a dirty text message.
I don't suppose
the clean teen dances much.
Oh, please.
I was doing the whole slut thing
long before you, bitch.
What?
It's catchy.
Mm-Hmm.
You believe in miracles,
skills?
'Cause there's no way in hell
a couple of vagabonds like us
Walked off the river court
and won the state championship.
Yeah.
Hey, you know
My joint ain't too far
from u.N.C. This year, right?
We gonna be boys
for life.
Hey, you guys play
nathan and whitey next season?
December 9th, 3:00,
And i plan to score
at 3:01, 3:02, and 3:03.
-You gonna be there, right?
-We'll see.
"We'll see"?
??Kill all that
"boys for life" talk, dog.
Matter of fact,
we ain't even friends right now.
Right.??
Be right back.
All right.
Let's go see dan.
You sure?
Yeah, i'm sure.
Why? Aren't you?
I don't know.
Scott.
Visitation.
I have a daughter.
Her name is lily.
And someday,
when she's old enough,
She's gonna ask me
where her daddy is...
Who he was...
And how he died.
And on that day,
I'm gonna look
into her beautiful eyes...
Eyes that don't know
of malice...
And jealousy...
And evil...
And i'm gonna say...
"...Your father loved
his younger brother very much,
"And that brother took him
from you for your entire life.
He made sure you would never
know your father."
Karen.
£¿£¿
So, you ready
to leave tomorrow?
Hey, what's wrong?
I don't know.
I just, um...
I know
moving on is a good thing.
I guess i'm just scared.
You know?
High school's safe,
And i'm not sure
i'm ready for the real world.
Um...
For the past few months,
i've been writing this --
I guess in part
so i could remember it all.
But, um...
...here.
"She was
fiercely independent.
"Brooke davis...
"Brilliant
and beautiful and brave.
"In two years, she'd grown more
than anyone i had ever known.
"Brooke davis is gonna change
the world someday,
And i'm not sure
she even knows it."
You're gonna do great,
brooke.
The world
doesn't stand a chance.
Thank you.
Hey, shelly.
Nice moves.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, shelly...
nice skirt.
So, you gonna let me
slide you out of that
At church camp again
or what?
Come on...
Slut.
What did you say?
Mouth, it's okay.
No, it's not okay.
Oh, no?
Whatever, geek.
What are you doing?
Do you believe this?
You know,
i was gonna take it easy on --
Yeah, me, too.
He's sorry.
You look great.
Oh, my gosh.
Nathan,
your baby is so beautiful.
He is, isn't he?
Hi. Sorry.
Can we just have a second?
Congratulations,
haley.
Thank you, reese.
, we need to go home.
Why? What is it?
I know we promised
we wouldn't do this,
But i called
just to check in on the baby,
And deb's not answering the phone,
????
And she's not answering
her cellphone either.
Let's not freak out, okay?
It doesn't mean
my mom's not on top of it.
Your mom the former drug addict,
attempted murderer,
Who dropped a loaded gun
in the caf\?
It wouldn't hurt to check.
Right.
I thought about calling you
a million times.
Are you mad at me?
No.
I just stayed away
because you asked me to.
No, uh,
clean teen shirt, huh?
No.
It was time to end it.
I was just trying
to find my place, you know?
Yeah.
You'll always
be important to me, shelly.
Mouth.
I like the skirt.
Hey, you.
What have you been up to?
Flirting with lucas.
Oh, yeah?
How'd that turn out?
Meh. So, so. Love triangles
are so high school.
Seriously.
We made it, didn't we?
Through all the tragedy
and jealousy and confusion...
We made it.
Yeah.
Hos over bros, right?
I love you, p. Sawyer.
I love you, too,
b. Dav.
Almost midnight --
End of an era.
Four years of high school
And zero girlfriends
for junk and fergie.
My girlfriend's canadian.
Man, whatever.
What you
thinking about, marv?
I'll be right back.
Hey, mouth, what's --
Yeah, dog!
That's my dog!
I always wanted
to do that.
Sorry.
Um...did you --
I-I said you could hang out.
I didn't say you could make out.
Do you see what happens when
you leave me alone all night?
I mean, seriously,
Thank you for letting me
say goodbye to all my friends,
But you're the one
i want to finish the night with.
I was hoping
you were gonna say that.
How about you kiss me
till i have to leave tomorrow?
It's a start.
Come on.
Hmm.
Deb?
Mom?
Shh!
Mom, what happened
to the phone?
I unplugged it.
Why?
Because the two of you
were driving us crazy.
The two of us?
I might have called
a couple of times.
Six times.
You crazy, obsessive parent.
You called eight.
I missed him.
And he's fine.
But go back to the party
and have fun.
You have the rest of your lives
to worry about children.
Trust me.
All right.
You want to go back?
Yeah.
Hey, hold on a second.
You're gonna be a great mom,
you know that?
Actually,
you already are a great mother,
And that's very sexy.
Really?
We don't have to
go back right away.
You're absolutely right.
Did i mention is was
the greatest night of my life?
Well, you said it was a night to
be great and to try new things,
So i figured
we'd do both at once.
You're gonna change the world
someday, brooke davis.
Yeah, so i've been told.
Be gentle with me.
I don't want you to go.
What?
I'm sorry.
I just --
I've been trying
to put a good face on.
God, i love you so much,
peyton.
So you want me to stay?
Yeah.
Then i'll stay.
No, you won't.
Just --
I want you to stay.
But i n't let you.
And do you know why?
Because
i've told you before...
You are destined
for greatness.
And it starts
tomorrow morning.
It's not gonna matter
anyway --
Whether i stay or i go --
With us...
'Cause i'm gonna love you
forever, lucas scott.
Yeah, so am i.
Hey, where
have you guys been?
I don't know.
Around.
Hey, um,
you got a sec, luke?
Yeah.
All right,
let me see that baby.
Oh, god.
Not bad, huh?
Good work, buddy.
I made that.
So, tell me
That was the greatest
60 seconds of your life.
Stop.
It was great.
So great
you're gonna stay?
Mmm...
not really that great.
Suddenly i feel used.
But it's okay,
Considering
i've been used by brooke davis.
Shut up.
You know i'm lying.
I am gonna miss you.
I already do.
You've become
such a big part of my life,
Sometimes i think it's strange
that i didn't know you till now.
It's okay.
Put me in your heart
and go see everything, brooke.
And then come back to me.
I'm sad.
I am sad. I --
It just hit me today
That you and i have been
together
Pretty much
every day of our lives,
And we're gonna
have to say goodbye soon.
We're not gonna --
Hales.
Look, i just -- I really want
you to know that i love you
And there's a reason why
our son's middle name is lucas.
You had keith,
and james is gonna have you.
And, um...
Nathan and i would like
for his uncle lucas
To also be his godfather.
Thank you.
I would love to.
I just --
I hope he learns how to
follow his heart like you do.
I'm really
gonna miss you, luke.
No, you're not.
What do you mean?
What's so funny?
Do you want
to hear a secret?
Oh, luke.
Hey.
Where you been?
Having sex.
You're funny.
Um...
I have something for you.
Turner gave it to me.
Happy graduation.
You told him the truth,
didn't you?
Maybe.
You know, of all the schools
i got suspended from...
I'm glad
i graduated from this one.
Me too.
I've been thinking
about dan.
Yeah?
Why should we go see him?
You mean tonight?
No, i mean --
I mean at all.
I mean...
He's had control over us since
we were born.
These are our lives,
not his.
I say
we go on without him.
I say...
We never go see him.
Ever.
I know it sounds horrible
to say, but, uh...
I'm okay with that.
I mean, i got a great wife,
i got a beautiful baby son,
And i got
a hell of a brother.
Yeah...
Hell of a brother who's...
Gonna be your coach.
Whitey offered me
an assistant-Coaching job.
I'm gonna take it.
What?
When did you decide this?
About the same time
i became a godfather.
That's great, man.
We'll do it together.
By the way, make sure
you play well on december 9th.
If skills beats us,
He's never gonna let us hear
the end of it.
Yeah.
12...11...10...9...8...
What's going on?
It's almost
midnight.
...5...4...3...2...1!
We're seniors!
Oh, high-School kids.
Let's get out of here,
you guys.
Where to?
I know a place
open all night.
Let's roll.
Girls versus boys!
Sorry, guys.
Ah, ah, ah
Okay.
We're not gonna do this.
We're not gonna get sad.
Nothing's gonna change now.
We'll all be friends forever.
I know it.
Look, in four years,
we're gonna be right back here.
You know,
done with college or...
Wherever we go.
Right?
Yeah.
Hey.
Ready for a rematch, or you
afraid you're gonna get worked?
Oh, ho, ho.
Do you really want
to end your night with a loss?
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen,
And welcome
to another historic night.
You sure
you're up for this, old man?
I could do this forever,
little brother.