Previously on "One Tree Hill"...
How bad will it get if they
find out about you and Daunte?
I won't play anywhere.
Duke rescinded your
scholarship offer.
I applied for an internship
with Sire Records.
That's great.
It's in Los Angeles.
I was wondering,
why'd you leave Clean Teens?
I thought if I joined Clean Teens,
girls wouldn't be interested in me,
and then maybe I wouldn't
have my heart broken again.
And then I came along.
What are you gonna do --
shoot me?
Yes, just like you
shot my uncle Keith.
- Karen?
- Do not touch her!
She could be having
a miscarriage!
I swear to god,
I will kill you!
Graduation Day
at Tree Hill High...
a day when we officially leave
the refuge of high school
and begin our real lives.
But what of those lives?
As we go into the world,
what matters most?
Is it about the
things we create?
The things we achieve?
The awards we win?
Is it about who we
are when we fail?
What's more important --
what we become or
how we become it?
- Mom, are you okay?
- She could be having a miscarriage!
Do not touch her!
That is my mother!
I swear to god,
I will kill you!
Get out.
Lucas...
She could lose the baby.
I missed on purpose.
I will not miss again.
You're making a
terrible mistake.
Get out.
Mom, it's okay.
I'm gonna get you
some help, okay?
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
I know.
Still, it just came earlier
than I thought it would.
What? Graduation?
No.
The day I realized I was
never gonna play again.
I called every school that showed
interest in me as a player.
Nobody wants a point-shaver.
Luke.
- Hey.
How's Karen?
What are they saying?
She's unconscious.
She has something called "eclampsia."
It gives her seizures.
What does that
mean for the baby?
It's pretty serious.
They said the next few hours are
critical for the both of them.
I just want her to be okay.
She will be. Your mom is tough.
Why don't I go to your house
and pack some things for her?
Okay.
Does Peyton know you're here?
You mind if I call
her and let her know?
I -- I don't want you to start worrying
and putting too much stress on yourself.
Thanks. I'll be fine.
Haley...
you didn't happen to
mention to anyone
that I had a gun in the house,
did you?
Yeah, I told Lucas
earlier today.
- Hey.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Aw, come on.
We're gonna be graduating soon.
We all know graduating plus partying
equals Brooke Davis minus her clothes.
But we're not all graduating.
Rachel should be here.
Hi.
How's she doing?
Not so good.
The doctor says what she
has could attack her kidneys
and her lungs -- everything.
- Hi, Peyton.
- Hi.
Do you mind giving me and
Lucas a moment to talk?
Yeah, I'll go get
us some coffee.
Thanks.
What, are you on drugs again?
Are you?
Because there's a bullet hole in
the wall of your house, Lucas,
and nearby, I found a shell casing
from a 9-millimeter handgun.
I happen to be missing
a 9-millimeter handgun,
one you knew about.
There's a police officer
about 40 yards down the hall.
You want to talk to him,
or you want to talk to me?
You'll think I'm crazy.
I don't know if
anyone's told you,
but I'm about as crazy as you
can get without being committed.
Try me.
Dan killed Keith.
It wasn't Jimmy Edwards.
It was Dan.
He got into the
school that day,
and he shot Keith.
And there was a witness, but...
she's gone now.
Dan killed Keith, Deb.
I believe you.
You do?
Dan thought it was Keith,
not me,
who tried to burn him
in the dealership fire.
Oh, my god, what did I do?
Who else knows?
- My mom, but --
- Where's the gun, Lucas?
There's a reason you didn't shoot him,
and you know it.
It's not the way.
I won't leave her side.
If Dan tries anything,
I'll be right here.
You should go see Peyton.
It's okay.
Lucas...
I'm sorry, truly.
But justice will be served.
I promise you that.
Subtitles : Willow's Team
Transcript : Raceman
www.forom.com
How's your speech
coming, Haley?
Not great.
I'm trying to write
about how we all should believe
in the good things in life, but...
it's feeling a
little false today.
I think I'm gonna
take a year off.
I can work nights and take care of
the baby while you take classes.
What about college?
Without a scholarship,
we can't afford it.
I'll just save up,
and I'll go next year.
You'll go this year and play basketball.
We're not giving up on that yet.
Every college in America has.
You know,
Skills is playing college basketball.
Maybe he can talk to
somebody for you.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
- Hey.
Hey, how's Karen?
No change.
Is there anything
that we can do?
Yeah. It's your last day
as high-school students.
You can go and be kids
for the rest of the day.
No, I'm not leaving my mother.
If anything changes,
I will call you immediately.
I promise you.
That's a good idea, Luke.
You should go home,
get some food, take a shower.
Yeah, you do kind of stink.
Come on.
You'll call me?
- First thing.
- Okay.
Lucas.
Stay away from Dan.
Understand me?
Yes, ma'am.
All right.
Brooke?
Hey. Thanks for coming.
Thanks for calling.
Are you okay?
I don't know. Karen's still in
the hospital, and there's...
something else.
Okay... I think.
I think I'm gonna turn myself in
for stealing the calculus exam.
The day before graduation?
I know.
It's just...
I was looking at the honor
wall at school, and...
I don't belong up there...
you know?
There's nothing honorable about
letting your friend take the blame
for something you've done.
All right, I love you for that,
but what if they don't let you graduate?
I mean, Rachel's already gone,
school's over.
What's it really gonna change?
The way I feel about myself.
And you just said you love me.
I did not.
Did so.
You just said,
"and I love you for that."
So what if I did?
And what if I do?
Hey, babe.
Got some good news.
So, my parents want to have your parents
over before graduation tomorrow --
a little quiche,
maybe some lawn darts.
Baby, quiche and lawn darts?
Do your parents know
my parents are black?
They don't know you're black,
so probably not.
Stop it. Race has never been an issue
to my parents with any of my friends.
But was you having sex
with any of your friends?
Do you really think it's
gonna be a problem?
Maybe not for us,
but for our parents, it usually is.
I'll just have to tell them,
and if it's a problem,
they're not the parents
I raised them to be.
Hi, Nate. Bye, Nate.
- What's up, man?
- What's up, dog?
You hear about Luke's mom?
Yeah.
Figured I'd give the family some space,
you know?
Anything I could do?
Not for them.
Maybe for me.
Yeah, listen, man,
I talked to my coaches, dog,
and I don't think
it's gonna work out.
Oh, that's all right, man.
I figured.
But Haley mentioned to me that if
you didn't get your scholarship,
there's a job waiting for you in
the factory where your dad works.
Yeah.
I thought if you weren't taking it,
maybe I could?
Yeah, I mean,
I could talk to pops.
Can you go by there today?
Yeah, whatever it takes.
Just give me a call.
- Cool.
- All right.
- Thanks a lot, Skills.
- No doubt.
Hey, yo, Nate.
Sorry things ain't working
out for you on the court, man.
Yeah, well...
It's the risk I took, right?
Commit a crime,
sometimes it catches up to you.
Lucas?
I understand you're really
mixed up about all this.
You're saying you
didn't kill Keith?
Is that what you
want me to believe?
Yes, Lucas. That's what I want
you to believe with all my heart.
That's never gonna happen.
You realize I'm in a
lose-lose situation here.
If your mother doesn't wake up,
then I'll never gonna forgive myself.
If she does wake up,
then she'll never forgive me.
Unless...
unless, maybe...
somehow, you're mistaken.
No chance.
I know what you did.
And you know what you did.
And maybe you'll never pay for it,
but I promise you...
my mom's gonna know it, too.
And what about her child?
Keith's child --
another kid raised without a father,
like you?
I had Keith...
until you took him from us.
And I'll be there
for his child,
but you won't be.
Ever.
I'll make sure of that.
You know, a lot of people go
to therapy to deal with stuff,
but I say a good root-beer float
can fix just about anybody.
Fixes me up.
Your parents coming
back for graduation?
No, they would rather come
back when the baby's born,
so I'll see them soon.
How about your dad?
Actually, I think I'm gonna take
that internship in California,
so he's just gonna meet me there in,
like, two weeks.
Peyton, that's awesome!
I'm so glad you decided to do that.
You're gonna do great.
That's cool.
Did Lucas say he's coming back here
before he goes to the hospital?
Well, I'll get out of your hair,
as much as I hate to...
slurp and run.
So good.
Come in.
I was just getting ready to go.
Oh, good. Hey, I got good news.
Skills hooked me up.
- With his team?!
- No, with his dad.
He got me that job at
his father's factory.
- Well, Nathan, that's...
- It's good money, Hales,
but it does start today, so...
So much for the last
day of being a kid, huh?
Miss Davis.
A bit early for graduation,
aren't you?
I'm the one who stole
the calculus exam.
I'm really glad you came back.
I missed you.
You think we could just stay
here for the rest of the summer?
Mmm, yeah, there was a chance of
that till I took that internship.
It's okay. I'm glad you did.
Yeah, it's gonna
be a long summer.
Nah, it'll fly by.
You know, I --
I really do appreciate you
being supportive about all this,
but a little bit of disappointment
would be good for my ego.
I just want you to
be happy, Peyton.
You have so much
magic in you...
But everything's okay?
I wish we never left that hotel room
in Honey Grove, 'cause you're perfect,
and we're perfect,
and that night was... perfect.
Well, saying that just
earned you another one.
I think I got to get
back to the hospital.
Can I come with you?
Sure.
Just --
...let me hold you for
a couple more minutes.
That's what's gonna fix me.
Mr. Scott.
Mr. Taylor.
Charles. You ready
to go to work?
- Yes, sir.
- Right answer.
Follow me.
You know anything
about what we do here?
Uh, not really.
Is it shipping of some sort?
Of some sort.
We manufacture the steel
that goes to building those freighters
you see coming in and out of the cape.
At least, that's what the company does.
We mostly just work.
But if hard work doesn't scare you,
you'll do fine.
Hard work doesn't
scare me, sir.
Another right answer.
Let's, uh, lose that "sir."
It's "Charles" or "Chuck."
Your name is Chuck Taylor?
Like the shoe?
More like the guy who's gonna
work your sorry ass to the bone.
Grab the other side of that pipe,
Nathan Scott.
Yes, sir, Chuck --
Charles -- sorry.
And that's the truth about
how I passed calculus,
so I'm guessing there's all sorts
of mean stuff you have to do now.
- Well, I --
- Just, before you do,
can I say something?
You know, when I was a freshman,
I wasn't a very good person.
I mean, sure, I was popular and
dating seniors, but as a person,
I was pretty lost.
And over the last four years,
I've been forced to grow up.
I stopped letting
boys define me,
and I started believing in
myself and in my potential,
and I ran for
student-council president,
and I designed a clothing line,
and somewhere along the way,
the lost, little party girl
became the girl on
the wall of honor.
And...
I know what I did was wrong,
Mr. Turner. I know.
But the girl I was when
I came to this school...
I'm not so sure she would have.
And isn't that the
point of high school?
Isn't that what you guys have been trying
to teach us for the last four years?
Actually, we've been trying to
teach you not to cheat in calculus,
but the rest of it is
certainly important, too.
I imagine you've been feeling
a good amount of guilt
over letting your friend
Rachel take the fall.
Yes, sir --
I mean, even though she told me to
and she's done all sorts of things
over the last year that would
have gotten her expelled anyway.
Yes, I have, so that's why I
felt that I should come forward.
You know, Brooke,
I must seem ancient to you.
Your teachers probably
seem irrelevant.
But one day, you'll look back,
and things won't seem so...
"us against them."
I assume you're
going to college?
Yes, sir. I -- I hope so now.
- To study...?
- Fashion.
Not engineering?
Or anything requiring
intensive calculus?
No, sir.
Good.
Go graduate.
Really?
Are you serious?
Thank you. I-I don't even --
Principal Turner!
Look, if you suspend her, I think
you're really making a big mistake.
- I don't mean to barge in like this --
- Shut up.
Chase, I love you for this,
really, but, shut up.
Um, I'm sorry. We'll --
we'll just go.
Go.
Thanks.
Deb?
Dr. Hudson, what's happening?
Your mom's condition's
worsened, Lucas.
And we can't be aggressive with the
antibiotics because of her pregnancy.
So how do you help her?
I want to prep her for surgery
and deliver the baby by caesarean.
And then everything
will be okay, right?
With my mom and the baby?
We have to take one
life at a time, Luke.
Right now,
both lives are in danger,
but if we act now,
we can save the baby,
and we'll have a much better
chance at helping your mom.
I want to be there with her
when you deliver the baby.
Of course.
Mom...
we're gonna try to
help you, okay?
Just... come back to us.
Hey, coach.
Um, are you looking for Nathan?
No, actually,
I was looking for you.
Care to take a little walk?
Uh... yeah, sure.
How's Nathan holding up?
Better than I am.
Skills helped him get
a job at a steel plant.
I don't know. I just --
I feel like it's way too early for him
to let his fire burn out and just
give up what he wants, you know?
How about what you want?
Look, Haley,
you asked me to help Nathan.
I'm not sure I can,
but if I do...
it's gonna take you away from
all the things you want to do.
I remember he said
something about Stanford.
Coach, I would go
anywhere with Nathan.
I would go to whatever
school will take him.
As long as our family's together and
he's doing something that he loves,
I'll be happy.
You'd make that sacrifice?
Yeah, wouldn't you have
done the same for Camilla?
Well, sure I would have,
but I never had to.
She always did the
sacrificing for me.
Okay.
Let's take a break.
State championship wasn't that long ago.
You can't be out of shape.
I'm in game shape, just not "steel
beams for the rest of my life" shape.
You do this every day?
No, I've been in
management for years.
I just wanted to see
what you were made of.
And, by the way, this doesn't have
to be for the rest of your life.
A lot of successful people never
got scholarships to college.
Any of them point-shavers?
Yeah, how'd all that
go down, anyway?
I was in over my head.
I just needed money, and...
the rest was a perfectly
orchestrated series of screw-ups.
You, uh... you regret it?
Every day.
'Cause you got caught.
Look, Mr. Taylor,
you seem like a good man.
But the thing is,
I made a mistake,
and now I'm paying for it.
Those 32 minutes should not define
me for the rest of my life.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Now all you got to
do is believe it.
Let's get back to
work, All-Star.
All right, let's do it, Chuck.
Oh, by the way,
I'm supposed to be meeting
my son's girlfriend and her family
tomorrow. Anything I should know?
Your parents don't
know Bevin's white?
Never came up.
And her parents don't
know you're black?
Look, they serving quiche, dog.
Can I go to this thing? 'Cause it sounds
like it's gonna be an awesome disaster.
Great, laugh it up.
I'm just playing around.
It's probably not
even a big deal.
I mean, if I were her parents,
I'd be more worried about you being you
than you being black.
Oh, priceless.
"Mr. Turner, if you suspend her,
you're making a huge mistake!"
I was trying to help.
I know.
You were very cute.
I couldn't just stand by
and let you not graduate.
Besides, it got you
to say you love me.
- I did not.
- Yeah, you did.
You told me to shut up,
and then you said,
"I love you for this, but go."
So what if I did?
So what if I do?
Hey.
Are we really gonna do this?
You mean kiss? I hope so.
No, I mean...
get all blissed out on
each other, like...
right before I leave for the
summer and we go to college.
Why not?
'Cause it's gonna suck
when we're apart?
Yeah...
but it's gonna be
great when we're not.
Besides, I'm gonna send you
the dirtiest text messages.
- Promise?
- Yeah.
You're so sweet, promising to type
me filthy things with your thumbs.
Hey, anything for
the girl I love.
Nathan?
- Hey.
- Hey. How'd it go?
Fine.
Will you listen to this part of my
speech and tell me if it works?
Yeah, sure. Let's hear it.
Okay.
"Now is the time
for us to shine,
a time when our dreams are within
reach and possibilities, vast.
Now is the time for all of
us to become the people
we've always dreamed of being."
Stop! Stop!
It's a girl!
It's a girl?
Lucas, say hello
to your sister.
Hi.
Look how beautiful she is.
Yeah, I'm afraid to move,
or I'm gonna break her.
You're not gonna break her.
Want to hold her?
Yeah.
Okay. Support her head.
Come here, you.
Oh. Let's see her.
Wow. I'm officially
scared to death again.
How's your mom doing?
She's still unconscious...
but stable -- they said she did great.
Hey, I was wondering if you'd be
able to step out for a minute?
Go ahead. I'll watch her.
It's just a minute.
I'll be right back, mom...
and you... and you.
Unbelievable.
Okay. I wanted to give you
this before graduation.
Okay.
I got something for you,
too, but it's at the house.
Actually, that's not from me.
That's from your mom.
She just hid it with me
so you wouldn't find it.
What book is it?
It's my novel.
Your what?
She had it bound for me.
I didn't even know she
knew I was writing it.
When did you --
I guess there's not too much your
mom doesn't know about your life.
"Lucas, I'm so proud of you.
Your words are wonderful.
Don't be afraid to share
them with the world.
Follow through and finish this.
Remember...
'There is a tide in
the affairs of men.'"
That's "Julius Caesar."
Do you remember when
you gave me that book?
Wow.
"Julius Caesar."
"There's a tide in
the affairs of men --"
or something like that.
"Love, mom."
I really need her to be
my mom again, Haley.
She will be.
I know it.
Pretty soon, you'll have a
beautiful baby of your own.
Trying to freak me out, mom?
And, by the way, if you can't make
it to graduation, that's okay.
At least dad will be there.
No.
If you see your father,
I want you to stay away from him.
Why?
Nathan...
this is gonna be hard
for you to hear,
and the timing is horrible,
but you're my son,
and I will always protect you.
Mom, what's going on?
It's about your uncle Keith.
Daddy, what's going on?
We had a slight
change of plans.
What do you mean?
Your mother wanted quiche,
but I hate quiche.
Well, I have
something to tell you.
My boyfriend's black.
That's okay, honey.
My son's black, too. We deal with it.
- But --
- Bevin Evan Mirskey,
you are in so much trouble.
Why?
Because if you had introduced
us to Antwon sooner,
we would have met
his parents sooner.
Hi, baby.
Antwon! Get your butt out here
and introduce us to your
beautiful girlfriend!
All right, everyone,
just step back and observe the master.
Here we go.
I was looking
forward to quiche.
You see?
Hey, baby.
See? I told you it wasn't
nothing to worry about.
Hey, mom.
I just wanted you to know
how good you did today.
You and Keith.
She's so beautiful.
You're gonna be proud.
But, you see,
you got to wake up...
because she doesn't
even have a name yet.
You never told me
what it was gonna be.
Luke?
Hey, we should probably get going if
we're gonna make it to graduation on time.
I kind of just...
thought I'd skip it.
Okay.
Before you do,
I think there something you should see.
If you skip graduation,
we're all gonna skip with you.
Even me, Luke.
Remember what you told me about how
much I'd regret it if I skipped prom?
You were right.
And I think your mom would want you
to graduate with all your friends.
You can wait here,
or you can wait there.
It's all the same waiting.
I promise you I'll call.
You should go.
Come on, Luke.
We can't imagine doing
this without you.
Yes!
Dad.
I know you've been
a bad guy, dad,
and for a long time,
I wondered if you'd ever change,
but lately,
I've seen you change.
I've been so proud of you.
But now they're saying...
they're saying that you
killed uncle Keith, dad.
Mom said it,
and Lucas said it, too, but...
I know they're wrong, okay,
because I know you could
never do something like that.
So just --
Dad, just look me in the eye
and tell me that they're wrong,
and I promise, I'll stand by you,
because I love you, dad.
Just tell me they're
wrong, please.
I can't do that.
What happened to you?
What happened to you, dad?
The day Keith died, you died.
You understand me?
My son will never know you.
You stay away from my family,
and you stay away from me!
Nathan.
First time I've ever
come to Keith's grave.
I was visiting with Camilla...
looking for some guidance,
and I asked her to
send me a sign.
I looked up, and I saw you.
You know, there's a crummy little
school about three hours from here.
They haven't had a winning
basketball season in over 30 years.
Gym smells terrible.
Nobody goes to the games.
A man would be a damn fool to take
their vacant coaching position...
or a damn fool that just
won the state championship.
You're gonna coach
another high school?
College.
Took the job this morning.
How would you like to
play for me next season?
Thank you, coach.
Don't thank me.
Thank Haley.
So, without further ado, I give you
Tree Hill High's graduating class.
Chase Adams.
Richard Asplund.
Angela Brown.
Brooke Davis.
Sarah Huddleston.
Marvin McFadden.
Robert Moore.
Bevin Mirskey.
Peyton Sawyer.
Robert Maxwell Scanlon.
Jessica May Scarlow.
Lucas Scott.
Nathan Scott.
Antwon Taylor.
Ferguson Thompson.
And graduating in absentia,
Rachel Gatina.
And finally,
this year's class valedictorian,
Haley James Scott.
Distinguished guests, parents,
and this year's
graduating class...
My best friend reminded me of
a quote by William Shakespeare
that seems appropriate.
"There is a tide in
the affairs of men,
which, taken at the flood,
leads on to fortune.
Omitted,
all the voyage of their life is
bound in shallows and in miseries."
Mayor Scott, would you like
to hold your beautiful niece?
"...On such a full sea
we are now afloat...
...and we must take the
current when it serves,
or lose our ventures."
I think that what
that quote means
is that life is short
and opportunities are rare
and we have to be vigilant
in protecting them --
and not only the opportunities
to succeed, but...
the opportunities to laugh,
to see the enchantment in the world,
and... to live.
Call Dr. Hudson!
She's crashing!
'Cause life doesn't owe us anything.
As a matter of fact, I think that
we owe something to the world.
And if we can just believe...
I'm sorry. I have more. I just...
think I'm having my baby.
Subtitles : Willow's Team
Transcript : Raceman
www.forom.com