As long as she doesn't
find out about us.
I have other responsibilities, a wife, my
job. I shouldn't have to worry about you...
I gotta go. I'll talk to you later.
Can I help you?
Hey, Dad. I didn't wanna interrupt
your phone conversation.
No, it's just somebody about a case
I've been working on.
- What can I do for you?
- I've been thinking.
I've been putting in some long hours and
some extra work, and I was wondering...
...if I could have a raise. Also, they
raised my rent, and I've been kind of...
I've grown fond of living indoors.
I wish I could help you, Harrison...
...but such a quick pay bump,
and for my son.
- You understand how that would look.
- Yeah, I figured.
You can't blame a guy for trying, huh?
Right.
Okay, so you get eight days
of Christmas?
Tyler, for the last time,
it's called Hanukkah, all right?
If you call it Christmas one more time,
I'm gonna shove a menorah up your...
Secret Santas. We should
open up our nondenominational gifts.
Great idea. Um...
- Ave, you go first.
- Yes.
- Drum roll.
- I got...
...a comb.
And I'm gonna guess
that it's from Tyler.
Hey. What happened to the secret part?
FYI, buddy,
the "under 10 dollar" rule...
...that's actually not a contest to see
how far under 10 you can keep it.
I know these two are
going home for vacation.
If they survive the ride
to the airport together.
But what about you?
What are the Davies up to tonight?
Well, it looks like, as usual, my family
Christmas Eve will consist of me...
...my brother, Harry, and a toast to the
rest of the family who couldn't make it.
Well, on the bright side,
there's less cleanup.
- But more therapy.
- You know what?
Coal for you in your stocking.
That's all you'll get.
My people, we don't do the stockings.
None of that.
What is going on with you? Normally
you're all "bah humbug" and grinch-y.
This year, I'm all about the holiday spirit,
the tree trimming, the church.
- Hell, I might even sit on Santa's lap.
- Lucky Santa.
Lucky me. You know,
I mean, I shouldn't even be here.
But you saved me.
And I know it sounds dumb,
but every day is a gift.
Even a day like Christmas.
Dad's doing it again.
- It?
- It. It.
- He's having an affair.
- What? Why?
I don't know. I guess he's not
getting everything...
...out of his relationship with Jordan.
- Ew. No.
I mean, what makes you think
he's messing around?
Oh. Well, there's the
secret phone calls.
There's the long lunches
that are not on the calendar.
- And then there's the apartment.
- What apartment?
Okay, ever since Dad started acting
all suspicious, I started following him.
- Harry.
- What?
Three times a week he goes to this
place. He spends, like, half an hour...
...45 minutes, then he leaves.
Look, I know Dad's got
a less than stellar track record...
...in the fidelity department, but I don't
think we should jump to conclusions...
...until we have proof.
- I know.
I know. You're right.
I know what I'm bringing
for Christmas dinner.
- What's that?
- Proof.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Someone killed Santa?
I know. It's pretty creepy, huh?
But I think he died of natural causes.
He must be one of those gentlemen
from the mall or something.
I came by to grab something,
but do you need me to bag personals?
No. All he has
is a black bag of presents...
...that's already been processed.
We're lucky. The holidays is one
of the most violent times of the year.
- But he's our only fatality brought in.
- Lf he's the only dead guy in town...
...what are the odds Saint Nick's
gonna open his eyes and whisper:
"Ho, ho, help me."
- City Morgue.
- Hey, Davis, it's me.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna be
a little late for our dinner tonight.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, I'm at the youth center...
...for our department's
community relations program.
There you go.
And we hired a Santa to bring some
presents to the underprivileged kids...
...and the guy hasn't shown up yet.
And the kids
are gonna be so disappointed.
He's just gonna be another person
in their lives who's let them down.
Yes.
Carrie, I think I might know
what happened to him.
Really? What?
- He's probably stuck in holiday traffic.
- Yeah, you're probably right.
- Anyway, I'll get there as soon as I can.
- I'll see you later.
Well, hey, if it makes you feel
any better...
...you're welcome
to join me and Harry tonight.
No, that's okay. It's been a while
since I've spent the holidays with a...
With a woman, so I think I'll just...
I'll wait for her.
- All right. I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Merry Christmas.
I wish I could make her understand,
but that's not possible.
If she finds out,
there's no telling what it'll do to her.
The most important thing
right now is that she trust me.
Hi, Dad.
Help me.
Harrison, you're late again.
And frankly, I'm running out
of expletives, so here's the deal.
I have the night off,
and I'm not spending it waiting for you.
So as un-festive as it sounds...
...you can find me at the lab,
catching up on work.
I'll be the one cutting out a spleen
and pretending it's yours.
Next time I talk to you,
you better have a good reason...
...for standing me up
on Christmas Eve.
Harrison, will you let me explain?
Jack. You work with Jack Harper.
I thought you were having an affair.
- What are you talking about?
- Those calls.
Those calls weren't about your wife,
they were about Tru!
Look, I heard Tru mention that this guy
Jack was harassing her.
So I'm trying to protect my daughter.
- Since when is that a crime?
- How about when it's a damn lie.
All right, you want the truth?
Well, it'd be a nice change of pace.
Jack Harper contacted me with some
very strange stories about your sister.
He told me she had this...
...gift. Then he told me
to meet him here today...
...and that's what I was doing.
- So that was the first time you met him?
- Yes.
I've seen you go to that apartment
three times this week.
Dad...
I always knew you were smart, son.
Tru was better with the books,
but you, you know people.
You have no idea
what you are dealing with.
Then tell me,
what am I dealing with?
Look, I wanna
be honest with you, son.
And I want you to understand...
...what is at stake here.
- But you gotta promise me one thing.
- What? What is that?
You will not mention to Tru
what I am about to discuss with you.
It'll be a cold day in hell
before I promise you.
I am so sorry to hear that.
Dad.
Harrison, I'm so sorry.
- Whoa. You scared me.
- A room full of corpses, and I scared you.
Sorry. What are you doing here?
I thought you were out decking the halls.
I was, and then it dawned on me.
Nobody should be alone on
Christmas Eve, not even our friend here.
You know, we haven't
had a chance to talk...
...about how you're feeling.
- About?
I just mean, sometimes
a near-death experience...
...can have a strange effect
on people.
Honestly, I feel great.
I feel better than great. It's like this
huge wake-up call for me, you know?
A chance to reevaluate my priorities.
- In what way?
- Having them, for instance.
I'm not gonna have priorities.
I'm gonna do everything.
You know? Do whatever I want,
devil-may-care.
I like this new Jensen,
but I gotta tell you...
...I never really saw you
as the devil-may-care kind of guy.
Well, maybe not everybody's
as they seem.
Come on, Tru. Come on, Tru,
answer the phone please. Come on.
Got a text from Avery and Tyler.
Their flights are cancelled.
They're spending
Christmas Eve at the airport.
Oh. That's probably my brother
with some lame excuse...
...on why he bailed on me.
Help me.
'Twas the night
before Christmas, again.
- Avery, it's Tru.
- Hola, chica. What's up?
I'm not gonna go to breakfast.
- Work emergency.
- Work emergency. Right.
You're gonna either need to get
a better job or a better excuse.
Right. But, hey, I was just thinking.
You and Tyler should call
the airline before you go...
... in case they cancel your flight.
No one wants to spend Christmas Eve
in an airport.
Yes, thank you.
Happy Holidays, Tru.
You too.
You woke me up yesterday too.
- Rough night?
- No.
Unless we're careful,
it's gonna be a rough day.
- Harrison followed you to my apartment.
- Thank God it's a new day.
The point is, just be careful around
your son today. Be nice to him.
Find out what he knows.
You know how this works, Richard.
We're not gonna get another chance.
- Hey, boss.
- Harrison.
What can I do for my boy?
Well, I've been thinking.
I've put in a lot of work, some
extra hours around the office and...
...I was wondering if I can get a raise.
- A raise?
- I really think...
- Well...
...you certainly deserve it.
Let me take it to the partners
and see what they say.
Hey. Wow.
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
- Who killed Santa Claus?
- Natural causes.
Knowing you, he's gonna
open his eyes and ask for...
I told that joke yesterday.
He was supposed to deliver toys
to kids at the youth center.
- That's where Carrie is.
- I know.
She's gonna miss dinner trying
to keep from disappointing them.
- Lf he didn't ask for help, then who did?
- A cadaver.
- Which drawer?
- Not here. At school.
- Those bodies have been dead for...
- Six months. I know.
That's why I came here
to talk to you first.
I mean, I didn't rewind
to six months ago.
So why would a body
that's still dead ask for my help?
- One advantage to your predicament.
- What's that?
Well, the clues are always
on the body.
And for the first time,
you have a body to work with.
For the record, she was dead
when I got here.
- Duly noted. Now, get out.
- Already on my way.
Looks like I got the day off.
Because you're good, Davies.
But you're not that good.
Stale corpse, no clues.
Hey, what if I was to offer to help you
with your job today?
What if I was to offer
to help you kiss my ass?
That's funny. No, but really,
think of it as a holiday truce.
What harm could I do? There was
only one fatality yesterday...
...and that one already
"ho, ho" happened, am I right?
Come on, there's no one to save.
There's no one to fight over.
I might even be helpful.
Jack, there is no way
I would ever accept your help.
You try and be a nice guy...
Merry Christmas to all,
and to all good luck.
So you asked for my help.
Who are you,
and what do you want from me?
So you talk to them too?
You have this way
of catching me off guard.
Wow, so you blew off breakfast
for schoolwork.
When you said work emergency,
I just assumed that you meant...
I just feel I've been getting behind,
with all the classes I've missed.
Right, right, right.
Then why is it that you're working on
another group's cadaver instead of ours?
- Checking up on their work.
- I do the same thing.
You picked a good one too.
You feel that?
- It's like her skull is cracked.
- Exactly.
And you see the small pinpoint blotches
around her eyes?
- Petechial hemorrhage.
- And you said you were falling behind.
- So this woman died from asphyxiation.
- She was murdered by it.
Probably fell postmortem,
led to the cranium fracture.
A lecture the professor gave
one of the days you were gone.
He said it was pretty rare to find
a body that met an unnatural demise.
Well, not in my line of work.
Anyway, I've got some last-minute
shopping to do, but thanks for your help.
Any time.
Later.
Let me guess,
you think Dad's having an affair.
- I still hate it when you do that.
- Well, I hate it when you stand me up.
You didn't show last night.
What happened?
Well, it's hard to say
without me reliving the day and all.
So, I guess we already talked
about Dad's phone calls...
...and this thing with the apartment?
- Yep.
I think he knows I'm on to him,
because he's been way too nice.
- Like he's hiding something.
- Relax, Harry.
- Not everyone lives a secret life.
- Right, just you.
Goodbye, Harr.
Come on.
It's a black sack with presents in it.
Yes, I understand the irony.
Yes.
Can you just tell me when it's gonna
be released from processing, please?
- Uh... Okay, thank you. God.
- No luck?
You'd think being the medical examiner
that I'd have some pull around here.
I know you want
to help Carrie and all...
...but technically,
those gifts were his possessions.
Which he was gonna give to the kids.
I think that it would be easier if I told
Carrie how I know it's gonna happen.
Okay, sorry.
Any word on that cadaver?
All I know is the woman who asked
for help was murdered.
I mean, I don't even have a name,
not to mention that the identity...
...of all anatomical gifts
are confidential.
So to make a long story suck,
I got nothing.
You know, there is one person
that would be able to help.
Someone who saw
what the victim saw when she died.
No. No.
I mean, are you crazy?
- I can't trust him after what he's done.
- You said it yourself.
You have nothing.
Beggars can't be choosers.
Can be smart enough to not buddy up
with the Reaper.
Ordinarily, I would agree with you.
But since no one's gonna die today,
what harm can he do?
I'm sorry, Tru.
I'd love to help you. Really, I would.
But I'm afraid I'm gonna have to hear
you say those two magic words.
- Please, Jack?
- Ooh.
Sorry. Those weren't the magic words
we were looking for.
- I knew this was a bad idea.
- Come on, Tru.
I just wanna hear
you say it one time.
- "Help me."
- Would you settle for "Bite me"?
Not if you want what's in here.
- Help me.
- I thought you'd never ask.
Come on.
I don't see why we couldn't carpool.
For someone who's dedicated
to saving lives...
...you should really take better care
of the environment, Tru.
I've got this thing about
not getting into a car...
...with a guy who kills people
for a living.
So, what are we doing here?
You wanted to know what I saw in the
victim's last day. Time for show-and-tell.
Most of it was pretty mundane. A sunrise
through a window, a taxi meter...
... a young girl with pigtails.
Something that looked like curtains...
... with red flowers on them
blowing in the wind.
And then this broken fence.
I figured what better place
to begin than with the end.
The last thing I saw
was falling off here.
Looks like we weren't
the first ones here today.
What's your money on,
coincidence or connection?
Only one way to find out.
Yes, hi. I just received the most
beautiful daisies, but the card fell off...
...so I have no idea who they're from.
I don't want the person to think that
I'm being rude by not saying thank you.
Yeah.
Ann Moore is the only person
who bought daisies so far today?
- Thank you so much. Okay, bye-bye.
- Impressive.
Thanks for your help, Jack.
That's it?
Well, I needed a place to start,
and now I've got one.
It's nothing personal.
Actually, it's completely personal.
Yeah.
- Hi. Ann Moore?
- Yes.
I'm from Hudson Medical School.
I'm doing a survey...
...of people who donated
a body to science.
- Now is not a good time.
- It'll only take a few minutes.
- I need to identify a cadaver recently...
- Honestly, this isn't something I want...
...to spend Christmas Eve talking about.
If you'll excuse me.
What my colleague failed to mention...
...is that we pay for this information.
Come in.
This money couldn't come
at a better time.
- Things have been awful tight.
- We're just glad to be able to help.
So you're here to ask me
about my sister, Allison?
Yeah.
This is her.
Do you mind if we ask
what happened to her?
She was murdered.
Six months ago,
by a man named Russell Marks.
They worked together and were
having a relationship on the side.
That is, until Allison
found out he was married.
That night, she went over
to tell him it was over.
It was the last time
anyone saw her alive.
I finished cleaning my room.
Okay, hon.
Go get ready for church.
That's the girl I saw in
the cadaver's memory.
- Pretty girl.
- Allison's.
My sister was a single mom,
so now I am too.
Miss Moore, if it's not too much, do you
know what happened to Russell Marks?
Well...
...he was arrested.
But the jury felt that there
was a lack of evidence.
"Reasonable doubt," they said.
I can't believe that he...
He gets to have a life...
...shop for presents,
trim the tree with his wife...
...while Allison's body lies
in some dark, cold room somewhere.
Where's the justice in that?
I'm sorry.
Is there anything else?
Cambria and I have to go to church.
Saint Matthew's is always
so crowded on Christmas Eve.
No, that's it.
Thank you very much.
I don't even get a thanks?
I was brilliant back there.
Does the fourth Horseman of
the Apocalypse need a pat on the back?
Whatever. The fact that I'm still here
means that you need me.
And that makes me feel
all warm and fuzzy inside.
Well, be careful. You wouldn't want
the ice around your heart to melt.
Cute. But seriously, what's next?
Since no one's life needs to be saved,
how do we help Allison Moore?
There are a lot of ways
to save someone's life, Jack.
- Stopping death is only one of them.
- That sister of hers seemed to have...
...a significant ax to grind
with Russell Marks.
- Maybe she was looking for payback.
- But no one dies, remember.
- No one has to.
- So you're saying attempted murder.
- Because if she got caught...
- Then Allison's daughter would be alone.
Thus, the "Help me."
We should find this Russell Marks today
and get there before Ann Moore does.
Hey, Tru, I gotta talk to you about...
- What the hell is he doing here?
- Nice to see you, Harrison.
Harry, it's okay, I got it under control.
What's up?
Come here a second.
Okay, I had a talk with Dad, asked him
point blank, "Are you having an affair?"
- And?
- He had an answer for everything.
Yeah. What did I tell you?
But then he said that that apartment
was where he meets his L.A. Partners.
But get this.
I got an old poker buddy.
He works for a car service
that handles the firm.
Those L.A. Guys aren't due till
next week. See, something is going on.
Tru, I can feel it.
I'm gonna give you two privacy.
You know, that would be just perfect.
What, are you crazy?
Why you all sleeping with the enemy?
There's no "sleeping."
He's helping me.
Bottom line, you can't trust him, Tru.
He's probably screwing you right now.
Richard, I hope you're getting this.
Your son is still suspicious.
You'd better get on this, or...
...we're both screwed.
Your brother was a tad frosty
to me back there.
Is everything okay with him?
You tried to kill him a few months back.
Were you expecting a hug?
A short memory,
the key to a happy life.
Ah!
- Can I help you?
- Hi, Mrs. Marks.
My name's Jack Harper. We're actually
looking for your husband. Is he at home?
Russell isn't speaking to the press.
I think he's made that perfectly clear.
We're not from the media. We're with
the Neighborhood Watch program.
We're actually just looking
for volunteers.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
We're newlyweds.
We just moved in down the block.
I'm sure Russell would love to help out,
but he's out doing last-minute shopping.
But then I'm meeting him
at Saint Matthew's.
If you're looking for volunteers, church
is always a good place to find people.
- She's right.
- Thanks for your advice.
- Maybe we'll see you there.
- Okay. Good luck.
- Guess who else'll be at church tonight.
- Something tells me we should be there.
That's kind of cute. That's nice.
I like it. Are those the eyes?
- Santa's not coming, is he?
- Yes, he is.
He is. It's just, you know
how those reindeer can be.
- That's very nice.
- Miss Allen, you promised us.
I know. I did.
It's just that sometimes things
can happen, even to Santa.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
- Who do you think that is?
- Santa!
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
- Davis?
- No, it's Santa.
- What are you doing?
- Explain later. Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Come on,
who wants to sit on Santa's lap?
Okay. Santa wants to make sure...
...that everyone's gone
to the bathroom recently, yes?
- Yes.
- Really?
Really? Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Are you even allowed in here?
I'm not the one screwing with
the big guy's plans.
If anyone's getting struck by lightning,
my money's on you.
Okay, so tell me the truth.
Why are you really helping me today?
As far as I'm concerned,
as long as the dead stay dead...
...there's no harm in giving
a little help to the living.
Or maybe I just didn't want
to spend Christmas Eve by myself.
There's our man.
Mr. Marks? We don't want
to cause any trouble...
...but we're friends of the Moores,
and you should know...
...that Ann and Cambria
are gonna be here today.
Look, Ann is still very angry
about her sister's death.
Rather than disrupt the services,
we thought we'd forewarn you.
Look, I appreciate what you're
trying to do, but I'm an innocent man.
- And I need to move on with my life.
- And what about Allison Moore's life?
- Thank you for your concern.
- Russell.
I'm gonna go enjoy the services
with my wife now.
Excuse me.
Well, that went well.
I'm starting to think the jury
was right about Marks.
- What makes you say that?
- If there's one thing I know, it's killers.
Once you take a human life, it's like
a smell that you can't wash off...
...no matter how hard you try.
And that guy...
...he ain't got the funk.
Ho, ho, ho.
What would you like for Christmas?
- A ferret.
- A ferret?
Okay, I don't think
I have any of those.
But have you ever considered
a bone saw?
To cut wood
for a really neat tree house.
- Thanks, Santa!
- Yeah. Ho, ho.
And what about you?
What would you like for Christmas?
A bone saw.
I think I'm all out of those.
But how about a splatter guard...
...to keep blood
from splattering on your face.
- You're the coolest Santa ever.
- Thank you. Ho, ho, ho.
And for you, there's a rib separator.
And how about some forceps.
I guess all I can do now is keep
Ann Moore away from him.
Yeah, well, if that's the case, then...
Showtime. There she is.
Come on, we're going home.
- That's it?
- Nothing happened.
- Maybe it hasn't happened yet.
- All right, we gotta split up.
One of us follows Ann,
the other stays with Russell.
Okay, I'll stay with Russell.
You follow Ann.
But if anything happens to her,
so help me, Jack.
Helping you is what I'm doing, Tru.
What do you mean, you can't stay?
Don't we have other things to talk about?
Hi, Dad.
- Harrison, what are you doing here?
- I could ask you the same thing.
Well, I guess you've already
spoiled the surprise.
- Surprise?
- I just signed the lease.
Merry Christmas, son.
It's all yours.
What? This place? What is...?
I may not be able to give
my new employee a raise.
But the partners can't say anything
about a father giving to his son.
I've been working on this for weeks.
But you almost blew the whole thing.
- I'm sorry. I was thinking...
- Forget it. Forget it.
It all worked out.
Oh, wow.
- Merry Christmas, Dad.
- You too.
Jensen.
Hey, stranger.
What are you doing here?
I guess I just wanted to see what it is
I've been missing out on all these years.
And pay my respects.
Who's that for?
That's for my uncle.
He died of a heart attack last year.
And that's for my cousin, who
passed away when we were little kids.
You know, think about this.
If things had gone differently...
...you might be lighting one for me.
- But things didn't go differently.
There but for the grace of Tru go I.
So...
...who's that one for?
Nobody.
I gotta get back to the lab, so I'II...
- I'll see you later.
- Hey, Jensen...
...Mr. Gorenstein doesn't need
the company tonight.
So I say you ditch the lab...
...and you join me and my brother
for Christmas Eve dinner.
You know, in the spirit
of doing something new each day.
Okay. I'll try.
Way of doing this.
- Hello.
- All right, I followed Ann home.
She's not doing much except
the crossword puzzle. How's Marks?
On his way home.
We must have missed something.
Maybe Allison Moore's "Help me"
had nothing to do with revenge.
Hold on.
Cambria!
Tru, I think I know who
Allison wanted us to stop.
It wasn't Ann.
It was her daughter.
Do you know who I am?
Of course.
From the trial, right?
That's how you know?
Is there anything I can do for you?
You can admit
what you did to my mom.
Look, Cambria, I think you should...
You think I should what?
Forgive you?
Or make you pay for what you did...
...before you have a chance
to do it to someone else?
Please, honey.
I loved your mother. I would never have
done anything to hurt her.
- No, that's not true!
- I was ready to give up everything.
My job, my marriage,
just for a chance to be with her.
Cambria, do you remember me?
I'm a friend of your aunt's.
This isn't what she wants.
She's angry. She misses
your mom just like you do.
But this isn't the answer.
We don't get to decide
who lives and who dies...
...who's guilty and who's not.
That's not the way it works.
- It's out of our hands.
- You don't understand.
He killed her and got away with it.
And nothing you do here
is gonna change that.
Look, it won't bring your mom back...
...and it won't bring your aunt
any more peace.
No one's gonna die tonight.
You're not even gonna hurt him.
You'll miss, and then the only one
who will pay is you.
What's going on?
- My God, what is this?
- Honey, go back inside.
Something that looked like curtains
with red flowers blowing in the wind.
Maybe it wasn't curtains.
You don't know what you're
talking about. I won't miss.
Okay, and if you don't,
then you've just killed someone.
That's something you're gonna
have to live with every day...
...for the rest of your life.
Isn't that right, Mrs. Marks?
What's she talking about?
L... I have no idea.
Cambria, don't make an innocent man
pay for someone else's crime.
I know this is a lot to ask...
...but hopefully you won't need
to press charges.
No.
I think she's been through
enough already.
You're just gonna let her go?
What about us?
Haven't we been through enough?
You're saying she should pay for trying
to take your husband from you?
- Exactly.
- Just like Allison Moore, right?
You need to talk to your wife.
Russell.
I did it for us.
Don't tell me.
Tell them.
Thank you for everything
you did today.
I would be more thankful if I understood
how you knew to actually do it, but...
Davis.
I've been thinking about what the best
thing is to give you for Christmas.
I think the best gift
I can give you is...
Is the truth about my life.
What do you mean?
You know how you were asking me how
I knew Santa wasn't gonna show up?
Yeah.
It's an interesting story, really. Um...
It's one that I'm not supposed
to talk about.
Davis, you know
that you can tell me anything.
Yeah, I know that. It's...
This is about Tru.
So I gotta ask,
why call the cops about Mrs. Marks?
The case was closed.
Why put the family through that again?
You know how you said if there's
one thing you know, it's a killer?
Well, I know victims.
I know what it's like to lose someone
and not know who took them from you.
I guess I owed a girl
who lost her mom.
I gotta tell you, it was cool
to wear the white hat for a change.
So you're admitting
that I'm the good guy?
Do you know why they gave the white
hat to the hero in the Old West movies?
It made them easier to light
for the camera.
The color of the hat
is not about right or wrong.
It's about what you choose to see.
- Well, I'm this way.
- And I'm this way.
- So I guess I'll be seeing you.
- Until the day you quit.
Or you do.
Well, it was fun while it lasted.
It was.
Merry Christmas, Tru.
Maybe I just didn't want
to spend Christmas Eve by myself.
Hey, Jack.
Okay, this doesn't mean
that I've forgiven you...
...and this changes
absolutely nothing between us...
...but I've always had this feeling that
no one should be alone on Christmas Eve.
Oh, look who finally showed up.
- Hey.
- Twice in one day. What a treat.
Relax, Harry, okay?
Maybe this wasn't such a good idea.
What, pass up the chance
to meet all your friends?
I wouldn't miss this for the world.
- What was that? If it's a call for...
- Look... Merry Christmas, for now.
Okay?
- Hey.
I hope you don't mind.
I brought Moe and Curly.
Yes. We took your advice,
and we called the airlines...
...and our flights were cancelled. So...
We'd be spending
Christmas Eve in an airport.
Uh-huh. So Jensen is not the only one
who owes you one.
It was just a hunch.
Yes. Merry Christmas.
Hey! Davis, I thought you guys were
having your own holiday dinner.
We did. But then Davis said that Harrison
has a habit of standing you up...
...and we didn't want you to be alone.
- Are you okay?
You never called me to see
how things were with Jack.
- Oh, right. Yeah, how did that go?
- Fine.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah. It's probably just the eggnog.
Well, we'll talk later, okay?
When are you gonna tell her
that I know the secret?
No, seriously, it's got cuffs.
Right here.
We have the best dad
in the freaking world.
He got me an apartment.
He got it pimped out, everything.
- Mighty generous.
- No, not generous, well earned.
Hey.
- Jack Harper.
- Hi.
Yeah, this is my dad, Richard.
Richard, Jack.
- Nice to meet you.
- You work with my daughter?
- A competitor, actually.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Long day?
Aren't they all?
In my endless pursuit
of the holiday spirit...
...there's one thing I haven't done yet.
- What's that?
Oh.
- Wasn't he supposed to be one of yours?
- Give it time.
And what about the mole?
She's got him.
Merry Christmas.
- I'm gonna go.
- Yeah.
There's the guy making out
with my sister.
Enough with the making out.
Don't you go all guardian on me now.
Come on, guys,
it's time to make a toast.