I'm going for sexy
but. but,uh,not slutty.
Smart but not boring.
It's a little.
P.T.A.Mom-bake sale.
Is it really?
Who. who is this guy?
Do you like him? Is he cute?
He asked me out on a date.
I-I haven't been on a
date since c-college.
He could be a homeless troll for
all I care. I love him. I love him.
I love him because I'm going on a date.
oh,he's here.
Will you please just. just tell
him I'll be down in a second?
All right.
Coming.
Cooper and I are next door at sam's playing poker and
having some drinks. I thought you'd want to join us.
You want to join us?
You're a little bit drunk.
And you,too,could be a little bit drunk.
You're drunk and you're flirty. Go away.
Or.
I could come in,and we could actually
get to know one another outside of work.
You're attracted to me. You admitted it.
Yeah.
Well,I'm not attracted to you anymore.
Good night,pete.
You're attracted to me right now.
What'd you do with my date?
That wasn't your date.
It was my date.
My unsuitable,flirty,drunk.
oh-so-attractive
date.
you have a really packed day,so
I had them add an extra shot.
Oh,bless yoU.
Today's files. And,um,I
think 7-down is "requited.
" Nice.
Thanks.
So.
how'd it go?
Not so good. I am so out of practice.
All I could talk about was. was
uteruses and. and sperm and eggs.
I think the guy thought I was
trying tget a baby out of him.
He left skid marks,he
drove away so fast.
It's not easy getting back out there.
I had a date last week.
It was a complete nightmare.
The guy spent the whole
night asking advice.
You're dating?
Everybody's dating.
except me.
Good morning,addison.
okay,I've got angie padgett and her
husband ray coming in for a follow-up.
She's ovulating,so the
fertility issue may be with ray.
I see that marilyn sullivan's coming in?
it's actually her daughter tess.
She fell down and hurt her arm.
She did,again?
Uh,I'll drop by.
I've,uh,got some
samples of this new M.S.
I can pitch in if
anybody needs me today.
Me,too. I'm booked,but,you
know,just all routine stuff.
Hey,you. you want to help
me get angie pregnant?
Man,I wish that was
as dirty ait sounded.
yeah,being able to make a couple
happy,that's the good stuff.
You will love the fertility game.
Yeah,I will.
Okay,on the count of three. One,two.
I'm sorry. How'd this happen?
I missed the curb when I was
walking home from the bus.
I'm a klutz.
She reads while she's walking.
One time,she nearly
wandered into traffic.
You should talk. I
mean,you read at the movies.
Only the ones you drag me to.
Okay. Well,reading. good.
Reading while walking. not so much.
Dr. Sam,the famous writer.
No,you're the one.
You're the one. That thing in the
"times magazine" last week was great.
I sit on my ass all day. I
have a lot of time to think.
here.
-is everything okay at home?
-Yeah.
Still just the two of you?
No,mom does a lot of
dating 'cause guys dig M.S.
'Cause this bruise on your arm,it
looks like someone grabbed you,hard.
You know,if something wasn't right at
home or school,I might be able to help.
I suck at walking. That's the crisis.
Don't freak out on me,Dr. Freedman.
All right.
Good news,angie. Your tests
came back. Everything is fine.
you are fertile. And you still
have plenty of viable eggs left.
Okay. That'S.
I was worried.
Great. That's great,honey,but,um,does.
Let's not race to any conclusions.
We're just gonna run some tests on
you,ray,and then we'll go from there.
Okay. Two doctors.
I'm sensing twins.
all right. Let's start
with a sperm samplE.
uh,Dr. Bennett in? Sam?
Yeah,but he's busy with a patient.
Can you call him on the,uh,the.
intercom?
Yeah. Is it.
Does it not look urgent?
I walked here. on foot.
Okay.
I don't know if you can count
insomnia as hospital business.
I've h three hours in three days.
Place wouldn't run without
me,not that you care about the.
the.
-yeah.
-This is what I'm talking about.
Aphasia.
Yeah,that comes with sleep deprivation.
Obviously I cannot do my
job if I can't m-m-make.
-words?
-Words.
All right. Any shortness of breath
when you lie down,chest pains?
No. And no.
I've run all the tests.
thyroid,everything.
It's. it's all fine.
Yesterday I parked my car. somewhere.
-sorry.
-It's not funny.
If this got out at st. Ambrose.
All right,now I can
prescribe a sleep aid.
No pills. They don't work for me.
Well,there are some new options.
No pills.
I had a little problem.
-What kind of a problem?
-The kind I'm not talking about anymore.
Can you help me or not?
Yeah,okay.
Uh,well,I guess we could go with the
alternative route. I could speak to pete.
Fine.
Send me to the quack.
I don't want to date.
I mean,I do,but I want someone with
purpose,someone real,someone who wants a future.
Someone who wants kids?
-Is that desperate?
-No.
No,it's not desperate. It'S.
-focused.
-Right?
My point is,you are out there looking.
I mean,even violet is out there looking. Maybe
I should be out there looking for what I want.
Yeah,and what you want
is a husband and kids.
Dr. Bennett,Dr. Montgomery.
Angie. Ray's up,uh,at the
lab still,but good news.
his tests are viable.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Yep,there should be no reason why
the two of youcan't get pregnant.
Oh,no,no,no. I was hoping.
you all right?
When ray comes back,you have
to tell him he's infertile.
I'm sorry?
You have to tell him it's his
fault we can't get pregnant.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-Âí¿ËË¹
Private
Practice  Season 1 Episode 6
you've been lying to your husband
about trying to have children?
Not exactly. I just.
i just was on the pill for years.
And then I got a cervical cap.
That's lying.
I have my reasons.
Which are?
I just. I don't want to have kids.
Look,ray. he comes from a big family.
He's good and kind,and
he adores me so much.
How can you tell someone who loves you like that
that you don't want to make a baby with them?
I'm sorry,but we can't lie
to him about his test results.
Then what am I gonna do?
Talk to your husband.
It's more complicated than it sounds.
I think the lie that you've been
telling is far worse than the truth.
No,it's not.
there you are. I'm all done.
What now?
Now.
now we go home and keep trying.
Okay. Good-B.
Can I just say.
-whoa?
-Right.
I always thought sleep was for the weak.
Would you put that thing away?
Now I just lie there. It's torture.
Insomnia is not caused by how you sleep.
It's caused by how you
live. And this isn't helping.
No e-mails.
Close your eyeS.
try to relax.
It's hard to relax when you're
sticking quarters on my head.
I'm stimulating the sleep
center of the brain with magnets.
So.
you went to medical school,suffered
through residency like the rest of us.
You could be saving lives right now.
Why did you ditch the good
stuff for magnets and hoodoo?
What I do is the good stuff.
Now shh.
move it,coop.
There's people who actually
pay me to lie on that couch.
I'm reviewing tess sullivan's
film from her last doctor.
-She had a humerus fracture when she was younger from a fall.
-Okay.
Except as I suspected,she actually
had a spiral fracture of her humerus.
You know how you get that? Someone grabs
your arm and twists it so hard,it snaps.
So someone hurt her on purpose.
More fun facts.
these records from before tess and marilyn
transferred here,she had multiple falls and accidents.
Cooper,if it's abuse,it's
usually the adult in the house.
Marilyn?
Her daughter loves her. Everybody
loves her. Sam loves her.
doesn't mean it's not happening.
And now I have to call child protective services
to protect my patient from sam's patient.
you're afraid of killing
people,aren't you?
Excuse me?
That's why you waste your
time with the new age stuff.
You're afraid of killing someone.
I'm lying here wide awake.
The thought occurs. That's all.
Okay,look.
it's almost 6:00. I'm gonna send you
home with a cd of music and meditation.
Try it tonight and report back.
Great. Next you'll be
giving me "baby einstein.
"  no.
No. There's no way marilyn
sullivan would. would hurt tess.
She's always coming in
with scratches and bruises.
Maybe it's. it's a kid at school.
I talked to the school. That's not it.
-Well,it's not marilyn.
-Why?
Because she's funny?
Because she's a writer?
No,because she's decent. All right?
She's handling her disease,her kid.
The woman is two years away from a
wheelchair. You can't just do this on a hunch.
What about the next time,sam?
What,I ignore this and the next time
tess ends up in a hospital or wor?
Unless you are absolutely sure,you have no
business putting these people through this.
If you're not sure,you're
meddling,not helping.
-you're here early.
-Yeah.
Yeah,thanks.
you have reached the los angeles county department of
children and family services child protection hotline.
hey,she's back.
-Who?
-Angie.
Liar-liar-pants-on-fire
angie.
Well,what. what do we do?
We throw her ass out of our practice.
Come on.
-Hey.
-Okay.
-Thanks,dell.
-Here you go.
angie.
I know I shouldn't have come back,but I looked up Dr.
Montgomery on the interne you're a genetic specialist,right?
Yes.
Well,I thought about what you
said,that it's better to know the truth.
So you told ray that you
don't want to have any kids?
No.
Not that.
Angie,I don't think
we can help you here.
You have to. You have to help me.
I need to know. I
need to know the truth.
The truth about what?
I need you to tell me
whether or not I'm dying.
huntington's disease?
-It's a genetic disorder that causes.
-a degeneration of brain cells. We know.
So then you know how horrible it is.
You lose control of your body,your brain
atrophies,you can't talk,you can't eat.
You just slowly die in this.
this shell.
My mom had it.
My grandmother had it.
And you think you might have it?
If her mother had it,she has a
50-50 chance of inheriting the gene.
And if I have the gene,I have a 100%
chance of dying from the disease.
But you've never been tested?
I just wanted to live my life.
And then I met ray.
And he doesn't know that
you could have huntington's?
I wasn't looking to get married.
It was just dating.
And then we were in love. And then.
I had waited too long to tell him.
And he loved me so much,I
didn't want to scare him.
I didn't want to scare me.
-But now.
-he wants to have children.
I can't have a baby knowing
I could pass this on.
I can't have a baby if I'm gonna die.
Last night,ray and i
were watching tv in bed.
And he was thinking up baby names.
And my heart started to hurt.
physically hurt.
I want to think up baby names.
I want to grow old with thiman
and our kids and our grandkids.
And I thought.
maybe I don't have the gene.
Maybe I won't get sick.
-Maybe.
-maybe knowing the truth is better than hiding from it.
I want the test.
I want to know.
I want to live.
Haven't you people heard
of an expiration date?
No,no,no. Those are. those are.
noodles don't go bad.
Oh,she's back. What.
Throwing away people's noodles.
I'm here because. surprise.
Can you keep your hands
off my food,please?
-Did you make the call?
-Yeah.
Hey,violet,we have a patient
we may need you to see. Angie?
She still lyingto her husband?
It's a little more complicated than
that. She might have a terminal illness.
De's preparing an exam room,and I'm
gonna draw her blood in a few minutes.
-You need to eat.
-I can'T.
Can you imagine? She finds the perfect
guy,she's got a great marriage,they want kids.
she was living the dream.
Not everybody has that dream.
Violet doesn't believe in children.
She acknowledges they exist because they
scream in her restaurants,but that's about it.
I used to be like
that before I had maya.
I was,and then I had her,and.
I'm not saying it's a dream.
but it's. it's pretty darn close.
You really don't want childre look,
not everybody is cut out for it.
And it is incredibly hard for a woman
to admit that she doesn't want kids.
'Cause they're basically
admitting they're men.
Oh,okay,no. Just because
you've apparently moved in.
it's not a disease,you know?
A woman can be alone
and be fulfilled,very.
Try saying that like you mean it.
Why isn't she sleeping?
Pete's working on it. Excuse me.
Uh,angie's set up in exam room two.
Uh,the sullivans,from yesterday,they're.
they're back and they're very angry.
I asked you to wait.
He did the right thing,sam.
You don't know that!
excuse me.
There's a social worker in our home.
He called a social worker on me.
Once I suspect,legally,I
have to call the authorities.
But you're wrong.
what does he think,the handicapped
woman beats her daughter with cane?
I-I think he was just worried
a-about the nature of tess' injury.
I know you didn't fall off a curb.
I help my mom when she
has a flare,all right?
She fell down,she grabbed
my arm,and it got tweaked.
I fell.
I reached out and I grabbed
tess' arm. It was an accident.
Then why didn't you just say that?
Because. people like Dr.
Freedman get the wrong idea.
Has that happened before,people getting the
wrong idea? You've had a lot of injuries.
She has M.S. She falls.
But my mom would never hurt
me on purpose. She wouldn'T.
she's my whole world. I would
never hurt her,not on purpose.
Please believe me,sam.
She's my girl. If they
take her away from me.
I believe you.
If they take me away from
her,I won't forge you,not ever.
I like the name margaret for a girl.
We could call her maggie or meg.
Or henry for a boy.
angie,if the tests come back
positive,you'll need to tell ray.
Do you have children?
No.
But you want them.
I do.
Have you thought of baby names?
Carson.
it works for a boy or a girl.
Don't piss dell off.
He was weighing in on a case. I
call that overstepping his bounds.
I need him here to
keep this place running.
Is that all you need him for?
What,you heard I went on a date,and
now you're gonna take it out on dell?
No,but you guys got some
kind of a thing going.
There's no "thing. " Do I like
that a cute boy thinks I'm pretty?
Yes.
Could I ever take it seriously? No.
He's a child,sam.
Just.
leave it alone.
All right.
shouldn't you be in
there,administering your heang touch?
Shush. It might be asleep.
It?
You're enjoying this,aren't
you,seeing me tortured?
Mm,it is satisfying.
hey,why did you come to my
house the other night? Really?
I thought we could have fun.
I'm not looking for fun.
sam told me that you're
the marrying kind of woman.
I am.
I've been married.
I don't plan on ever
going down that road again.
So if you want fun,I'm here.
-If you want more.
-I should.
-look elsewhere.
-Addison.
it's not working! I'm not sleeping!
and still satisfying.
Go.
Make it sleep.
Obviously you'll be expected
to testify,Dr. Freedman.
Now tomorrow is the hearing.
That's fast.
We move fast. We have to.
Now if the judge decides it's an unsafe home environment,
the girl would be taken immediately into foster care.
-What about the mother?
-What about her?
Well,if tess gets taken away,marilyn
shouldn't be left alone. She has M.S.
That's not our department's
concern. Our concern is the child.
I should say,um,tess is pretty
insistent that there's no abuse.
Well,that's not unusual. The child protects
the parent,even rationalizes the behavior.
And what if tess is telling the truth?
That's why there's a judge.
But the medical testimony carries a lot of weight,and
I'm sure Dr. Freedman did not make this call lightly.
Angie,this is,uh,Dr. Violet
turner. She's our psychiatrist.
I thought you were just
gonna tell me my test results.
Oh I have it.
I really have it.
But as of now,you have no symptoms. You could
go years before you show any sign of illness.
Illness?
You mean dementia,violent
rages,wetting myself?
A lot of research they're doing with
repression proteins is very promising.
Hopefully,in time.
oh,I don't have time,Dr. Bennett.
Time is the one thing I don't have.
I've got a great life,an
amazing husband,but no time.
Damn it. I am so out of time.
I know this is a lot to process.
But you're not alone.
You have ray.
No.
No,I knew what I was getting
into when I took that test.
that stupid,stupid test.
-angie.
-why don't you stay?
We can talk.
I can't,but thank you,all
of you,for trying to help.
Well,what about ray?
-What do you.
-don't worry.
I know what I have to do.
-I'm begging yoU.
-Oh,no.
I have tried acupuncture,massage,pressure
points,melatonin supplements,aromatherapy,sound therapy.
And I can tell it's not working
because she's still bitching at me.
Charlotte needs a shrink.
-Yeah,agreed,in more ways than one,but.
-squeeze her in.
I.
this is co-op
medicine,and I'm referring.
You need to co-op. Now.
90% of sleep issues are psychological.
Fine. Shrink away.
When you sleep,do you toss
and turn,thrash around a lot?
How would I know? I'm asleep.
Yeah,I realize that.
Well,that. that's where a
partner could be helpful.
Uh,the last time you
slept with someone else.
was years ago.
So you haven't had sex in.
I have sex.
-They just don't sleep over.
-Ever?
Are you asking because you're
interested in my well-being,
or because you're secretly thrilled to
find someone who's as alone as you are?
Just because I don't want a child?
I'm fine.
I am better than fine,in fact. I.
let's just stay on you.
Dr. Montgomery.
Hey,ray. How are you?
-How's angie?
-Gone.
She's gone. Angie left me.
I came home,and I found
her packing a suitcase,and.
she said that her appointment here
was like some kind of wake-up call,
and then she just left.
And that's all she said?
here,uh,ray,why. why don't you.
I don't understand. She spends two minutes with the
two of you,and then throws in the towel on our marriage?
-Ray,please calm down.
-No,I want to know.
What the hell did you say to my wife?
It smells like christmas in here.
It's an ayurvedic sleep remedy
that might knock charlotte out.
-What did you get?
-Intimacy issues,severe.
She tries to alienate anybody who might
get close,even people she asks for help.
Sleep's triggered when you comfort
yourself into a self-sedated state.
And people like charlotte.
chances are nobody ever really nurtured
her,taught her how to self-soothe.
Nurture her,pete. Be kind.
people have babies in this bed?
We change the sheets. Promise.
Go ahead and close your eyes. Relax.
You're smiling like an idiot.
I'm staying positive.
oh,brother.
People need connection to stay
healthy,positive connection with another human.
look,I don'T.
I don't need your pity positivity.
I don't know what violet
told you,but I connect,okay?
Yeah,when?
-None of your bus.
-business,right.
You know what? Maybe.
I'm not the guy to help
you. Maybe you need someone.
who I can't irritate.
Find that man for me,and I'll marry him.
My family didn't believe in displays.
Of affection?
my mher.
there was the occasional sloppy
kind that followed cocktails.
And since then?
Who has time for that kind of thing?
I'm sorry,charlotte.
Do you want to try again?
Why not?
My hair's already shot.
Can you drop these at the lab for me?
thanks.
Um,ahem,marilyn sullivan
called for you again.
I'm not allowed to speak to
her until after the hearing.
Don't start,man. There's
nothing vague about the law.
-I suspect and. -tess
wrs long sleeves a lo -
what?
Well,even when it's,like,95
degrees outside,down over her hands.
And does she ever look at you,I
mean,like,really look you in the eye?
-Not really,no.
-Right.
When she has appointments without her mom,she shows up
early,she hangs out after,like she doesn't want to go home.
I've seen that.
How do you know all this?
Uh,because I did the same thing
when I was in her situation.
It's what you do.
All right,I'll get
the lab right on this.
Fascinating.
She's been here all night?
She snores?
God,asleep,she looks almost harmless.
Mm,like a sleeping tiger.
Don't wake the tiger.
I have to go,um,and put my
tie on for tess' hearing.
He needs you.
He put her to sleep.
-He actually did it.
-yep.
Angie's here.
She finally responded
to our phone messages.
Well,we got her to come
back. That's something.
-Any ideas on what we say to her?
-No.
You said the baby making game
would be fun I am not having fun.
Oh,god. Me neitheR.
Not with this one.
Mm,it's not. it's not fair.
Good people should get
to have what they want.
I was heading to the airport.
You said there was something with ray?
Ray came by to see us yesterday.
He was worried sick about you,not
to mention confused and hurt.
You didn't tell him,did
you? You cannot tell him.
Angie,he is your husbD. He
deserves to know the truth.
let him thinkI left him.
Let him hate me.
Then he can move
on,find someone,be happy.
He's happy with you.
But. he's gonna.
I'm gonna get so sick.
I'm gonna die.
I don't want to die.
Angie.
you have a disease.
And you will die. That's the truth.
Hiding it from ray is
not gonna change that.
But the bigger truth. the better truth.
is that you are alive now.
You're living,and you should get.
you should get everything
that life has to offer.
You should get what you want.
You should get to have a
child and a family and ray.
Just because you're sick doesn't
mean you don't get to live your life.
Go home.
Tell ray the truth,tell him what
the future is,and let him decide.
A person.
should get to have a whole life.
Didn't allan wear yellow ti. did
you bring me one of allan's old ties?
I bought this tie for you.
Today you become a man.
Yeah.
What are you gonna say?
-You shouldn't really be.
-what are you gonna say?
I'll tell you if you
roll up your sleeves.
So whatever.
She hits me a little.
But she's sorry.
Afterward,I mean.
She's really sorry.
And it's not like I couldn't
hit her back. I mean,look at her.
Oh,tess.
But I don't need to hit her.
She needs to hit
someone. Her life sucks.
tess,everyone has pain.
So why can't this just be mine?
what time is it?
It's about 12:15.
-Tomorrow?
-Today. Well,y-yes.
Today is your tomorrow.
Oh,my god.
oh,my god.
This is. oh,god.
It'll wash out.
I mixed you a tonic to take home with you. It
should help you fall asleep more easily tonight.
I don't need your potions.
Really? It kinda seemed like you did.
Don't throw yourself a party.
You don't have me figured out.
I said some things when I was
loopy. Probably just hit a wall.
I hit a wall and.
it happened to be here.
Okay.
Dr. Freedman,would you please explain to the court
the injuries you've noticed on tess over the last year?
Sorry. That's all right.
sorrY. Thanks.
In the last year,um,two lacerations,multiple
contusions and abrasions.
plus the recent wrist fracture.
And in your opinion,is there any way that the injury could have
occurred other than by the intentional twisting of the child's arm?
No,there's not.
Thank you very much,Dr. Freedman.
Wait,can I. can I just
say one more thing?
-Sure.
-Okay?
I've known tess for a little while
now,and she is a great kid,so tough.
She doesn't let anybody see her cry.
I don't even know if she does cry.
But it doesn't matter how strong she is.
Some things,a kid should
never have to take.
Being hurt,being hit by someone who
is supposed to love and protect you.
you don't have to take that,tess.
You can't take it.
Because once you let yourself shut
down like that,you're not a kid anymore.
Uh,I'm. okay,I'm done talking.
You can return to the gallery.
Thank you,Dr. Freedman.
They're taking her away from me.
I can'T. Not now,marilyn.
It's not right. I'm her mother.
I'm her mothersam.
right. You're her mother.
Don't tell me you believe them.
I'm not evil. I made a mistake.
I love my daughter.
That kid.
all she wants is her mom.
I didn't want to see it.
and I should have.
I should've.
excuse me.
We know we don't have
an appointment but,uh.
no,please.
Come in.
So,um,the fertility tests,they came back
fine for both of us. So we can make a baby?
We want to share what life
I have left with a child.
And we were wondering if there was something you
could do to make me pregnant sooner rather than later.
Because angie doesn't
have a lot of time.
I just want to make
sure that you understand.
oh,I. I understand.
Angie will die.
sooner than we want.
Angie will,uh.
but that's the future.
And I don't care what happens
tomorrow or in a few years.
We have this now. We have us now.
there is still the risk that
the child will have the gene.
We know.
We're willingto take that chance.
I mean,if everyone who had the
gene was never born,I never.
I never would've met angie.
But I really.
naomi,they want us to
help them make a baby.
A person gets to have her whole life?
A person gets to have her whole life.
So you're a convert now?
just covering my bases.
Well,I am sure pete
appreciates your gratitude.
Pete doesn't need it.
He congratulates himself
enough for all of us.
but damn.
the n has good hands,doesn't he?
What would you be doing
right now if you were angie?
You mean I-if I knew.
knew how limited your
time was. If you knew.
pretty much what I'm doing right now.
Check you out. all zen.
also known as margarita number two.
I'd be on a plane to somewhere
spectacular with maya.
What about you?
I.
I don't know.
I'm going for more serenity.
Baby girl.
thank you.
liar.
Where's your power tie?
Oh,I took it off. I didn't
want to throw up on it.
Plan on throwing up tonight.
Cooper. because of you.
tess knows that an adult saw her
and cared enough to protect her.
How many times have we
met marilyn sullivan?
Did you ever think that.
yeah. That's why people who shouldn't
have children shouldn't have children.
And you count yourself among
those people. You're crazy.
-You would never.
-well,who knows?
I don't think anybody who
had a child ever thought
,oh,boy,now I have something I can hit.
Violet,you are the most
caring,generous person I know.
Yeah,and the most neurotic,the
most self-involved.
look,you're telling me that if you
met the right man and fell in love.
and he wanted to,you
wouldn't even consider it?
You would.
Um,sam told me about
how you helped with tess.
If you ever want to
talk or need some help.
m okay.
You do a lot for the practice.
You are the practice.
You keep it running. the way you deal
with the patients,the way you care.
Your dream is what started
it in the first place.
-And sam'S.
But I do it for you.
Charlotte king says.
you have good hands.
what?
I-I.
okay.
It's okay. I was just.
-no,no,no,no.
-Just,um.
having some fun?
No.
I don't want fun,and a person
should get what she wants.
What does that mean?
Good night,pete.
What does that mean? You
can't just kiss a person and.
od night,pete
Private
Practice  Season 1 Episode 6
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync:YTET-Âí¿ËË¹
Proudly Presents
you're in it now,man.