Come on.
That is the worst runway walk
I've ever seen. She's not fierce.
Eliminate her.
I told you, when the models
are walking, do not call.
Doug
Come upstairs.
Upstairs.
What's going on?
Where's Karen?
She's in there.
She's been so sick, so sick, and...
I didn't know who to call.
You're still my therapist.
It's gonna be all right.
I killed her.
I killed my wife.
- You did that on purpose.
- Come on, man.
If you didn't suck
you wouldn't get hit.
I don't suck.
I played on a team, man.
- You suck. Say that to my face.
- I am saying it to your face.
You suck!
- We need women.
- Word.
- I hate racquetball.
- Man, she's working in our building.
Charlotte is working in the building.
I can't get away from her.
Naomi... she's right down the hall.
You think that's easy?
You know, I wish she would just die.
No, not in a bad way. Just like...
slightly dead.
You know, then I wouldn't have to see
her face. She'd just be a memory.
You ever wish Naomi dead?
That's... the mother of my child.
Yes, I do, actually.
When she had sex with that guy,
I wished she was dead.
- All right, let's go again.
- I got you.
Hold up.
- What's up, Violet?
- She's calling you?
She wouldn't let me call her when the
models are walking. Why is she calling you?
- Traitor.
- I'll be right there.
Just a few more notes to make.
- Ten minutes tops.
- Don't worry about it.
I figure I could get 5 miles
in before bed.
You ran this morning,
and you don't run.
Who are you, and what
have you done with Meg?
I am bored.
I'm out-of-my-head bored.
I'm running bored.
You know what I do all day? Nothing.
And after that, nothing,
and then a little more nothing.
I mean, what do people do all day
who don't have jobs or kids?
'Cause I can't spend all my time
running around the neighborhood.
My thighs are killing me.
I'm freaking out here.
I know it's frustrating
being in a new place,
trying to figure out where you fit in,
But don't run.
- You know, get a job.
- A job?
Now why don't we...
hurt your thighs a little more...
In a non-running way?
- I'm going home.
- You're not going home.
I don't want to... just...
Would you just stop bathing me
like I'm an invalid?
You got shot.
You want to be both shot and dirty?
I'm serious. I don't want to be your
responsibility. I don't want to be...
- I don't want to be a burden.
- You're not a burden.
Kevin, look at me.
You're not a burden.
Let me take care of you.
Karen was out of her head
with the pain. The blood...
She was always spitting up blood.
Her condition was fatal. You know that.
And she was begging me to help her,
so I just...
I did. I helped her.
All right, Karen was sick for months,
and I know that she was dying,
but there were so many other ways
that you could've
helped her... palliative care,
- pain management.
- She didn't want that.
She was done. She just wanted to go.
So you shot her in the head?
- Doug is been through a trauma.
- They had a troubled marriage.
He said he was gonna leave her
before I diagnosed her. Karen was...
- she was helpless.
- It's not like that.
Time to go.
I was only trying to help her.
So you're his shrink, and...
who are you?
Dr. Bennett is...
was Karen's doctor.
Karen was suffering from kidney failure
secondary to wegener's disease.
She was sick. I get it.
Did he ever talk about hurting his wife,
wanting her dead?
- Well, I... when we...
- Well, whatever he said is privileged.
- So you're okay protecting a murderer?
- I'm protecting my patient.
What about you, Dr. Bennett?
You gonna stay silent, or are you
gonna protect your patient... Karen?
We're leaving.
The elevator's mine. You can have the
fourth floor, but the elevator's mine.
I'll give you one more day
to calm yourself down,
Then we're gonna discuss this
like grown adults.
Tell you what, Charlotte,
go to hell.
My god. He shot her?
Wait, he shot her shot her?
- As in killed her shot her.
- Killed who?
- Doug Adams murdered his wife last night.
- He did not murder her.
- He said she begged him to do it.
- Oh, god, that poor man.
- That poor woman.
- Then it was a mercy killing?
- Dell gets it. It was euthanasia.
- It was a bullet to the brain.
Look, I know Doug,
- and he is not the type to...
- There is no type.
Regular normal people are driven
to murder every day. Right? Love?
Love will do it every time.
Twisted, sick, messed up love...
- Charlotte king is still alive, right?
- I'm just saying, the impulse...
We all have it.
I didn't know you were coming here.
- Can I talk to you?
- Sure, give me one second.
Not you. You.
What did I tell you
about the elevator?
I'm not talking to you.
- My day is made.
- I need a favor.
That's rich. You open a practice right
underneath us, and you need a favor from us?
I'm not coming to you
from pacific wellcare.
As chief at the hospital
where you retain surgical privileges,
- I'm hoping we can be civil.
- What is it?
- Don't engage.
- Breathe. I can be civil.
What is it?
Full-term pregnancy. Eight months ago,
she was in a car accident.
Doctors did everything they could,
but...
- She's comatose.
- And in an early labor.
She just... moaned.
That's good, right?
She hasn't done that since
right after the accident.
Moaning is a good sign
that she's starting to respond.
- I think it's just a sign of labor.
- Sean, the neurologist told you,
She's nonresponsive.
She wants this baby so much.
We found out she was pregnant
the day before the car accident.
I think it was the happiest day
of her life.
The baby's in a breech position.
Our O.B. tried E.C.V. to try
to turn the baby, but...
She's down too low. I need to do
a C-section. You wanna book an o.R.?
She needs to go through labor.
She needs to deliver this baby herself.
She can't.
The breech position puts the baby
at risk for a prolapsed cord,
Which would cut off
the baby's oxygen supply.
The head could get trapped, potentially
causing brain injury or worse.
A woman in Kentucky, situation just like
Alena, having the baby, it woke her.
Alena needs to deliver this baby
naturally, on her own.
She has to.
Alena is going to wake up.
And we're gonna be a family again.
Private Practice S02E08
Crime and Punishment
- He is going to kill his own child.
- He loves her.
He sat here every day.
- He wants her back.
- She's not waking up.
"Rip van winkle's" a fairy tale.
Don't tell me you're going sentimental.
Hardly. Just...
- I find him touching.
- I need to do a C-section.
I need to get the baby out now,
or both mom and baby could die.
We can't make him.
We can't force him
to let us cut her open.
Look, maybe if you talk to him,
get to know him.
He warms up to you,
and then you help him understand...
That's your job, Charlotte,
as chief of staff.
My job as consult
is to get the baby out.
- I have a practice to get back to.
- So do I.
We...
Have to work together
to help that family.
- We do.
- I'll put her on terbutaline
to temporarily stop
the contractions,
but that'll only get you through
the end of the day.
I'll consult legal.
See if there's any way we can override
the father and do the "C" without consent.
He could've left, and he didn't.
Why now?
She was gonna die in what,
in six weeks, three months?
You think after years and years
and years of this marriage,
- He would shoot her now?
- They had a volatile relationship,
all right? Now you may have seen
his side, but I saw hers. And she...
- she was not suicidal.
- Well, Doug was not homicidal.
Except for the gun in his hand.
- I don't think it was like that.
- Well...
Well, the cops are gonna want
a statement from both of us, and...
I'm gonna tell the truth.
Well, if Doug gives me permission
to talk to them, so am I.
The actual truth or the truth
that you want to believe?
It's... No, it really...
It's fantastic. I'm serious.
- What's going on?
- I like her, Pete.
I went down to the Venice family clinic
today to offer my services.
Turns out they have a huge overflow
of patients, but not enough exam rooms,
but with NaomI's help,
we found some room here.
Here at... Oceanside Wellness?
When the clinic has too many patients,
I'll see 'em here.
Addison's always talking about how,
with Charlotte's practice opening,
We need to expand our community
outreach and raise our profile.
Meg is the perfect liaison. Plus,
she's willing to let Dell shadow.
Oceanside Wellness gets to generate
possible future income,
and I get to avoid going stir crazy.
Everyone wins.
- Welcome aboard, Meg.
- Thank you.
All right, I have to go find
Dell and get set up.
See you later?
Is it always this slow?
Only when someone stops it.
Are you okay?
You're not claustrophobic, are you?
Just impatient and in a bad mood.
Anything I can do?
Occupational hazard.
I'm a therapist.
And to be honest, I'm a bit nervous.
Interviewing for a new job, you know?
- On the fourth floor?
- Yes, you work there?
- No. I pushed 5, remember?
- Right.
Well, if you need to talk,
- if there's anything I can do.
- You know, I'm a shrink, too.
I think I can handle it.
I'm Shel...
I'm Sheldon Wallace.
Is there anything else you need?
This is perfect.
Better than I'm used to.
- Can I just say, Dr. Porter, that...
- Meg, please.
I just know I'm gonna learn so much
working with you.
Well, I bet you could teach me
a few things, too.
Candy stash... under the microwave.
See? That's critical information.
Well, Dell, it looks like our first
patient together is Renee Olsen.
I was referred to Dr. Porter for...
- termination.
- I'm sorry?
Termination.
Abortion?
It's not like I don't want her here.
I just don't...
Want her here.
She just did it.
She didn't even ask me.
Welcome to my world.
It's not like she
went behind my back.
- She just...
- Went behind your back.
Stop finishing my sentences.
You know, she's a good doctor.
She's gonna be fine.
Did anybody know
Meg was gonna be doing abortions?
Look, I know I'm not a partner
in this practice,
and you guys might all be
okay with this,
but I want to go on the record
for saying that I'm not.
- Not okay with what?
- Meg working here.
Nai told me. Pro bono clinic.
I think it's great.
- She's doing abortions.
- And?
Wait, you men have
a problem with it?
Not as men.
- We respect the choice, but...
- I don't.
- I'm not commenting.
- We just didn't know.
- You didn't know what?
- Meg's doing abortions here.
She's what?
Nice digs you got in those exam rooms.
They're palatial compared to grass huts.
What?
You should've told us you were gonna
be doing abortions. That's all.
Everybody without a vagina, leave the
room unless you want to fight with me.
- This is a problem?
- I run a fertility clinic.
And I'm in the business
of helping women to get pregnant,
- Not...
- Wait.
Abortion is legal in the United States
of America, Naomi.
Are you against choice?
I am not gonna argue Roe V. Wade
with you. I am just saying,
they have never been done here
and they should never be done here.
It's a valid medical procedure
for women in need.
Not for me,
and not for this practice.
I'm sorry....
I have to run.
I don't have a problem with it.
We said she could work here.
She can work here.
- I'm ready for Renee.
- She's gone.
What? Where?
I don't know where.
I just know that she's not coming back.
Well, what happened? Is she okay?
Except for the part about her planning
to kill her baby.
- You talked her out of it?
- I just told her what I thought, okay?
I have work to do.
I got a message that you're ready
for me to do the C-section.
I told you no. I meant no.
- We want you to do the C-section.
- These are Alena's parents.
I called them after I had legal
do some checking.
Turns out Sean and Alena
are not married.
He has no right to make decisions
on her behalf.
We were gonna get married right after
we found out about the baby.
I mean, just because we didn't...
I am still family.
Don't you think we want her back?
But she's not waking up.
If you need to do a C-section
to help the baby, then do it.
The parents have
the legal authority.
I will schedule a C-section
for this afternoon.
Dell shamed a young woman
for wanting an abortion.
You offered abortions to patients
without consulting anyone else.
I'm a doctor. I don't need to consult
anyone about my medical care.
You're a doctor who's working with
six other doctors who have
opinions about cases and about
the reputation of their practice.
I'm screwing up your reputation?
That's what this is about?
You completely disregarded
everyone else who works here.
So, yes, that does reflect on me.
This is my domain.
Fine. I'll go.
It's off.
Baby daddy went to court to get an
injunction as guardian over the baby.
- Not gonna be any surgery, not today.
- What?
No, the patient is prepped
and ready to go. Damn it.
- So what next?
- I'll see if I can convince a judge to
get over here and clear this up.
If the baby lives long enough.
- Can I ask you?
- What?
You betrayed him.
So how long is he gonna make me pay
for my crime?
He's angry.
I don't see that ending anytime soon.
- You're in love with him.
- I am not. I just...
I am not.
This doesn't make us friends. We're not
friends. Don't go getting any ideas.
I have no intention
of being friends with you.
They're saying I murdered her.
I didn't. I helped end her pain.
Sam says... he thinks...
When was the last time Sam saw her,
two weeks ago?
And for what, maybe half an hour?
He didn't see
how walking up a flight of stairs
got to be more than she could take.
I did. I had to listen to her moan
in pain when the drugs wore off
and panic 'cause I thought maybe
she had died from a nosebleed.
- Well, there were other options.
- I did what she wanted.
Look...
I know Karen and I
had a lousy marriage.
I don't even know
if I loved her by the end.
But I did care about her.
I just wish you had called me first.
We could've talked about it.
My lawyer says they're going for
first-degree murder. I can't...
do you know what it's like in here?
Please.
Please help me.
I waive all privilege.
Whatever it takes. Just tell them.
Tell the police...
Tell them I didn't murder her.
You know me.
Do you think I murdered her?
Is it true that Pete
found out that Meg
was doing abortions
and asked her to leave?
- Not exactly.
- 'Cause if that is true,
- that is ridiculous.
- What, Pete asking her to leave,
or doing the abortions?
Well, don't tell me you have a problem
with Meg doing the abortions.
- What?
- I spend all day every day
trying to help women
make babies who...
who stopped believing that
they ever could.
I can't believe this is such
an issue for you.
I... wish that I had known
a doctor like Meg
or a place like our practice
when I needed an abortion.
I had two.
I had a very...
misspent youth.
I made some mistakes.
- You don't have to tell us.
- I wasn't going to,
- but I'm not ashamed.
- I was.
I had one.
And I was embarrassed and scared.
I was everything
a woman shouldn't be.
Well, I fertilize eggs every day, and I
believe that life begins at conception.
- So what, it's murder?
- I believe what I believe.
Well, I believe that things
aren't so black-and-white.
Well, you know,
you don't do what I do.
I deal with the aftermath.
I deal with women who've had children
who shouldn't have.
Maybe we should talk
about something else.
What are you doing here?
I just
thought y might be in the mood for
a drink after a hard day at the office.
No, thanks.
Get out from in front of my door.
Move.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll do the time.
Whatever you want,
But I am sorry.
Just...
go home.
I need time...
to think.
So I thought in my
hotel room with the
crisp white sheets and the
- travel-Sized toiletries.
- You didn't have to do that.
You have two modes... off and on...
and when you're off...
Peter, you get cold.
You're closed, you're shut down.
It's like you're
punishing me for something
that I didn't do.
You never used to be like this.
The man I knew...
we used to share everything.
So what happened?
What happened to you
between then and now?
The clinic is good.
What you do for people is good.
I overreacted.
Come back.
Good morning.
Not so good. The district attorney's
gonna subpoena Karen's medical records.
You okay?
I was up all night
trying to figure this out.
And I cannot get the image of Doug with
that gun in his hand out of my head.
So then you do think
it's possible that...
I don'know. No.
I just...
I wish there was somebody
I could talk to, somebody who knows
about this kind of thing. I'm kind of in
uncharted waters here.
I think I know someone
you could talk to.
Sit down.
Sorry. I don't mean to bother
you while you're recovering.
Please... bother me.
So... Doug Adams killed his wife.
How do I know if it's murder
or assisted suicide?
Doug has had no difficulty with impul-
sivity or anger control his entire life.
He was submissive to his wife.
I've never found any indication
that he was remotely violent.
In fact, I would be hard-pressed
to concoct a scenario
In which he had the temerity
to strike out against his wife
unless she instructed him.
You don't think he got scared to leave
and took the easy way out?
Killing Karen would never be
the easy way out for him.
I just don't think Doug
murdered his wife in cold blood.
In all my years on the force, do you know
how many women I've seen kill themselves
or asked to killed with a gun?
None.
What's best for the child
is to have a mother.
What's best for
the child is to be alive.
I will not hear shouting.
You want me to defer
this to the courtroom?
We can put the attorneys together and
have'em drag it out until it's too late.
I want to hear from you.
The baby's in imminent danger.
If I do nothing,
it could suffer
irreversible complications.
And the hospital's position?
You support dr. Montgomery?
We want to give Alena every chance.
That said, judge,
we don't dispute dr. Montgomery.
It is her only chance.
Alena is our daughter. If we thought
for one minute we could have her back...
I have two choices, Sean.
I can rule on this,
Or you can withdraw your objection.
I'd rather it come from you.
- You look like you're in a hurry.
- Thanks.
Look, I'm sorry about yesterday.
Ah, we all have bad days.?
Today any better
Actually, no.
- I don't suppose you want to talk about it.
- Yeah, it's complicated.
Transference?
Psychosis?
I'm kidding.
Murder.
Or manslaughter.
That's... big.
You must be good.
You'd think.
You know the best way
to cheer yourself up?
- Cheer someone else up.
- Oh, is...
is that your brand of therapy?
What is that, Jung or Freud, or,
- or fortune cookies?
- It's Mark Twain, actually.
You like Twain?
You see? There you are.
You've cheered me up.
People who like Twain
always cheer me up.
Did you get the job?
I got the job.
- We need to talk about renee.
- I'm busy.
We work really hard
to create babies here.
We are in the business of
bringing babies into this world.
I don't know you very well.
I certainly don't know you
well enough to judge you
for this. But you don't know
Renee very well,
Yet you were quick to judge her.
What... Was she raped?
Would it matter if she was?
Would that make it okay?
I mean, does that make her
more or less worthy?
We don't get to know why.
That is her business.
That's her choice, Dell.
That woman agonized
over a difficult choice,
Made it and came in here.
I guarantee you she was already worried
about people out there judging her
only to have you
make her feel ashamed.
But we are medical professionals.
It is part of our job to support her
once she has made
the hardest choice imaginable.
- You're not allowed down here, sean.
- I know. I... look, I just... I can't...
I made her laugh.
I made her laugh, and she looked
away from the road and...
I caused it.
I was responsible for her coma.
I don't want to be responsible
for her staying like this.
Please,
I know what the judge said...
I need a miracle here.
I'm asking for a miracle.
You have to stop punishing yourself.
Sean, you didn't make
that accident happen.
And you don't make miracles happen.
But I do.
I'm about to go in there
and deliver your miracle, Sean.
And I know that this isn't
the path that you sought out
Or the one that you and
Alena saw for yourselves.
But this is your baby,
the baby that alena wanted, and the one
that she would want you to raise.
So I'm gonna go in that O.R.
and I'm gonna bring out that miracle.
Did you talk to the d. A.?
- What did he say?
- You know, I didn't talk to him yet.
I wanted to talk to you more.
I was worried about you...
Here...
Thinking about what you did,
What you had to do.
It must have been awful.
It was.
To do that to someone you loved
And to have her ask for that...
For her to ask you to use a gun...
Karen wanted it to be quick.
She was afraid
That something else wouldn't work.
- She was just in so much pain and...
- I know all about her pain, Doug.
But what about your pain?
I want to know about your pain.
- Come here.
- You're antiabortion.
I am.
Unapologetically.
Do you think it makes a difference why
a woman would want to have an abortion,
- Like rape or...
- I think it matters why it bothers you.
What do you mean?
If you're against it for religious beliefs
or personal beliefs, that's one thing.
God or something in your soul
is trying to tell you something.
I refused to even learn how to perform
the procedure in medical school.
I couldn't. I just... I couldn't.
But if abortion bothers you
for other reasons...
What?
Look, I don't want to be responsible
for swaying you to the other side.
Did your child's mother,
did she consider having an abortion?
You tried to talk
her into getting one.
And now you look into your daughter's
beautiful face, and you feel guilty.
We went to the clinic,
and she wouldn't get out of the car
And I yelled at her.
I yelled at her, and,
you know, now I just...
I just can't believe
I yelled at her.
Then I think you are not
against a woman's right to choose.
You're just punishing yourself
for the choice you almost made.
- I've told you everything.
- You released her.
You gave her everything she wanted.
So you should feel like
a weight has been lifted.
But you don't, do you?
It's hard to feel that way
when I'm in here.
It must've been hard...
Her in pain, yelling at you,
Wanting you to help her. She made you
feel awful every day of your life,
So you must have thought that by
helping her, the pain would go away.
But it hasn't
Because the truth is
still eating away at you.
I couldn't take it anymore.
You need to let it go, Doug.
Just let it go.
She kept... yelling at me...
For me to do things for her.
She would say things to hurt me.
She would lie in that bed
and throw things at me
And call me an idiot and a weakling and
tell me everything I was doing was wrong
When all I wanted
to do was help her.
And the more she would yell,
the more she would bleed.
And there was blood everywhere,
And I couldn't take her
and I couldn't take the blood,
And...
and I stopped feeling sorry for her.
And all I thought about
Was that I should have left her,
But I couldn't leave her now. I couldn't
just walk out the door, but I couldn't stay.
I couldn't hear her yell anymore.
I couldn't hear it.
So I took the gun...
And I stopped it.
I stopped her.
You murdered her.
I put her out of her misery.
You put yourself out of your misery.
- I tried calling.
- I know I got your message.
I am so sorry for
the way you were treated.
Dell was out of line,
and I apologize. I'm just
- glad you didn't ignore my message.
- Well, I did ignore it. I mean,
I listened to it,
But I wasn't going to come back.
- Well, I don't understand. Why are you
- Dell called me.
Oceanside wellness performs
its first abortion. Wonderful.
- She's throwing multiple p.V.C.S.
- Bolus her with 100 of lido
And start a 2-Milligram-Per-Minute
drip. Lap pad.
Lost her pressure. V-Fib.
She's going into cardiac
arrest. Get a crash cart.
She's throwing an embolus.
Start C.P.R. Epi.5.
Let's go. The baby?
Got her.
Charge to 200.
Clear.
Okay. You ready?
You ready to see daddy?
She's beautiful.
She has your nose...
- And Alena's eyes.
- I'm so... So sorry for your loss.
I'm afraid you can't.
It's against hospital regulations.
I want her to meet her mother,
And I want to say good-bye.
This is our daughter.
Look what we made.
I don't know if you hear this
a lot from us, but...
Thank you.
I hope you know she made
The best decision she could for herself.
I just always thought medicine
was going to be about helping people.
It is.
I'm proud of you for doing what you
thought was right, but I just can't.
Not now.
We're on the same time schedule.
- Can I ask your professional advice?
- Sure.
Step into my office.
Well... let's say you have a client,
And this client
has been through hell.
And it's a client that you like,
You really like.
And they've done something...
wrong.
Or maybe they've done something right
For the wrong reasons...
I'm not making any sense, am i?
Did anyone get hurt?
You have your answer...
Don't you?
I'm...
I'm Violet.
Violet turner.
You asked what happened to me
Between then and now.
I have a dead wife that I hated...
Hated...
Until the moment she was gone.
And if I could...
Take back the hate...
It killed a piece of me.
There's a piece of me that no
longer exists because of her.
- So when you feel threatened...
- There are very few women that I trust.
You trust the women here...
I'm doing the best I can, okay?
He's going to prison
for a very, very, very long time.
Poor Karen.
I feel so guilty that
I ever believed in him.
Are you at all religious?
In church,
when someone dies...
We light a candle to rember them.
What are we doing?
Trying to forgive ourselves.
Can I get in on that?
A baby died today.
Long day?
Let me make you something to eat.
You must be starving.
You took care of me.
Now let me take care of you.
I'm fine.
I made a miracle today.
Transcript: YYeTs
The Mc DreAmy Team
pour www.forom.com