No. In and out.
You gotta breathe in, too,
not just out. In.
In... Okay, not...
not like a vacuum cleaner.
Like a normal person.
Relax.
That's easy for you to say. You're not
gonna have 8 pounds of flesh and bones
- coming out of your...
- kay, I don't...
- no visual.
- This is visual enough for me.
The point of me staying over
wasn't to wake up next to a pillow.
- You can always leave.
- I know, but I agree to adult
sleepovers in this carnival
because I get my itches scratched
when the sun comes up,
- usually.
- Charlotte, I will be...
- right there.
- I'm going back to the room.
If you're not there
by the time I'm naked...
Come on. She's bluffing.
Keep breathing.
Thank you.
- No Phillip today?
- He couldn't get off work.
On the upside, he promises me
a bigger budget for the baby's room.
But I don't mind. It's not his thing.
Malcolm's better at it.
One of the perks of being a nurse...
I get to fill in for my brother.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Again.
- We'll talk about this later.
- Hey, Malcolm.
Fellow nurse man.
She fires you, we'll take
our business elsewhere.
How long have you been like this,
short of breath?
A week maybe.
I walk up a flight of stairs,
and I feel like I need to take a nap.
Since Phillip has diabetes,
do you think this is related?
- Gestational diabetes or something?
- No, there's no association.
Your blood sugar's fine.
Let me just have you sit up.
Well, maybe it's the baby weight.
I mean, look at me.
I'm as wide as a highway.
You're beautiful.
I'm gonna listen to your lungs.
Deep breath.
Good. Again.
What?
- What is it?
- Dell, get an ambulance for me.
I don't want you to panic,
but I hear a little bit of fluid
in your lungs,
which could indicate
a problem with your heart.
- Phillip... is he here yet?
- I called him. He's on his way.
Oh, perfect.
There are 40 heart surgeons
in this hospital.
I didn't know this was your case.
I just responded to the page.
So did you get a chance
to look at my patient's echo?
Diffuse myocardial dysfunction.
- See, that wall's barely moving.
- Oh, my God.
- Both mom and baby could die.
- I'll do everything I can to save them.
Doctors thinks H.M.O.'s
are about denying health care,
about how little help
you can give people who are sick.
While H.M.O.'s make a mint.
You're right,
most doctors do think that.
- I think that.
- Thank you.
You know how few people
would say that to my face?
You... know, you're... very charming,
but I'm... I'm just...
Thank you.
I'm having a hard time figuring out
what you think I can do for you.
I mean, my...
practice is never gonna be
part of an H.M.O., not ever.
Good. Neither would I.
I got out.
- Took the money and ran.
- Ah, you proud of that?
Most of my life I've been a rich ass.
Then over the past year,
I watched my best friend die...
A.L.S.
He suffered...
a lot.
Medicine failed him.
I failed him,
and it changed me.
I want to start
a state-of-the-art medical practice,
change the way medicine works,
change the way doctors work.
I'm not at liberty
to discuss details, but...
I want you to run it.
Mr. White, I'm...
well, I'm very flattered, but I...
It's William, and...
and just hear me out.
I've done my homework, Naomi.
You are the preeminent
fertility specialist in the area,
you helped fund one of the first
whole wellness practices,
and in the past year,
you've had to deal with finances and
internal power struggles. It's not
even really your practice anymore.
- It's... still my practice.
- Maybe,
but is it what you want?
What if you had access
to cutting-edge technology,
to the best scientists
and researchers
at your fingertips?
Top doctors in
every specialty under one roof?
- I have the best doctors now.
- Think bigger, Naomi.
I'm talking about,
say, the guy who created
the first embryonic stem cell.
I'm talking about giving full wellness
care to people who can't afford it.
You set the agenda, then hire whoever
you want to make it work
so you can focus on what you do...
being a doctor,
making life.
You know, my ex-husband and I
built our practice from the ground up.
And...
leaving it, is...
it's something
I would never entertain.
Entertain it now.
I'm offering you the chance to do
what you've always wanted to do
with no money worries.
What's the downside?
Private Practice S02E21
What you do for love
Hey, Nai. You...
you free for lunch today?
Maya hit me up this morning about
taking her someplace cool for summer.
I'm thinking we could...
figure out our summer schedules.
No, I can't.
How about tomorrow?
You having lunch
with Duncan again?
No. I just... I'm busy.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Everything's great.
Thank you.
I know testing urine is a crappy job,
but jeez, Sam, lighten up.
What is it, another U.T.I.?
Well, yeah, you do have
a urinary tract infection,
but you also tested positive
for chlamydia.
Now the good news is
that it's treatable,
so I'm gonna give you a prescription
for sulfa for the U.T.I.
And doxycycline for the chlamydia.
Now do you have any idea
how you might have contracted this?
Bill.
- He's been cheating for a while.
- I'm sorry.
How did I let my marriage
come to this?
This is not your fault.
Now if you need help
in dealing with this...
I'll figure it out.
That's what I do. I
figure things out.
I always tell my students,
stay focused on the problem,
the answer will be clear.
I need to get away...
from Bill.
It sounds so easy to say, doesn't it?
Well, it's tough to know
when you're ready for it to be over.
Well, I better pull myself together
and get back to school.
Donna, if...
No, just... give me the prescription.
I'm gonna be okay.
Okay.
Big Ben has a big appetite.
- I'm an eating machine.
- Six slices. Up here.
Thank you so much.
That was yummy.
Sorry, ma'am.
Excuse him.
Somebody calls me "ma'am,"
- I just want to choke them.
- Oh, that's okay. I've been...
I've been called worse.
Lisa, this is Violet.
Violet, Lisa.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
How many weeks are you?
- 35-ish?
- Well, you've got the glow.
Being a parent, nothing compares.
So I've heard.
I'm really looking forward to it.
See you later?
Nice. She's...
I like her.
You need help with that box?
- Her heart's just not working anymore?
- It's called cardiomyopathy.
The heart muscle becomes inflamed.
In this case, the added pressure
on Janine's heart from the baby
caused it to progress rapidly.
From all the tests, it looks like
it's been going on for a while.
I'm afraid that the damage
is irreversible.
You didn't see this?
You've been there.
- Honey...
- You're my brother.
- You're blaming me for this?
- Come on, stop. It's nobody's fault.
Janine's right. I think
we need to focus on the solution.
- So what do we do?
- She is going to need a new heart.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna die.
No, that's what you're telling me.
I'm pregnant and I'm going to die.
How fast can we get a heart?
We need to notify U.N.O.S.,
get her on a list. It could take time.
- How long can her heart hold out?
- It's impossible to tell,
but not for long. The pregnancy
is making your heart work harder,
which is why,
Janine, I think that you need
to consider termination.
Janine, at 20 weeks,
the baby can't survive,
and we need to relieve
some of the pressure on your heart
- until we find a new one.
- She kicks.
She kicks me.
She's alive in there.
Please.
We can't take that kind of risk.
Janine, I want this baby
as much as you,
but we need to buy you more time.
You're not listening, Phil.
- She doesn't want to lose the baby.
- No, I can't lose the baby.
You have to save us both.
I'm begging you.
Hey, Bobby.
- Bobby, it's Dr. Cooper.
- My body's on fire.
Okay, you're having
a severe allergic reaction.
We need to figure out
what you've been exposed to,
so where have you been,
what have you been eating?
- I don't know.
- Bobby, you're gonna have to try
to do better than that.
Look, if you took something
you weren't supposed to,
you're not gonna get in any trouble
but you need to tell me.
Look, you need to check him for pills,
check his pockets,
check everything he came
in here with.
Draw up 125 solu-medrol
and 50 of diphenhydramine.
Is he gonna be okay?
I'm Bobby's teacher. I found him.
Did you see anything
when you found him?
- Has he been taking anything?
- Mrs. Keating, thank you.
Is bobby okay?
He's having a severe allergic
reaction to something.
We're trying to figure out what.
He's in here. You should go in.
- What's... going on?
- My student, he's in there.
The sulfa you gave me,
and the doxycycline,
I gave him both, and he's reacting. You
have to tell the doctor what he took.
- No. Donna...
- You can't tell them.
You can't tell them
Bobby and I are...
I'm sleeping with one
of my students.
She's not a vulture.
She's not a predator.
- She was confused.
- I have no sympathy,
- except for the boy.
- How's Bobby?
He's, you know, he's stabilized.
He's alert.
The rash is not progressing.
- Stevens-Johnson syndrome?
- Yeah, he reacted to the sulfa.
He's lucky. People can't just
give other people
their prescriptions.
She was trying to help him.
What did he end up telling his parents?
He said that a friend gave him some
pills so he could stay awake, study.
Now they're just happy
that he's doing better.
Bobby is a minor.
This is statutory rape.
She should not have slept with her
student, all right? Absolutely not.
But he's gonna be 18 in what,
like, a month?
You spoke to him.
It was consensual.
I mean, he said he made
the first move, but...
That does not absolve her,
and it doesn't absolve you of your legal
duty to report this, to protect him.
But in a few weeks,
it won't be a crime.
What good is it gonna do
either of them if I report this?
She's gonna lose her job,
her credentials.
- He's gonna end up humiliated...
- He'll be a rock star.
- Mary Kay Letourneau... hot.
- That boy was 13 years old.
So by comparison,
Sam's patient's done nothing wrong.
What... 17 year old hasn't wanted
to sleep with one of his teachers?
Donna was in a position of power,
- and she abused that.
- Why assume a 17 year old
isn't mature enough
to know what he wants?
Because he's being forced
to grow up too quickly, to...
to make decisions about his life
that he's just not ready to make.
- Think about yourself at 17.
- I was mature, all right?
Heather wasn't. But thank you, Naomi,
for the free therapy.
All right, if this were Maya,
- and a 35-year-old male gym teacher...
- Well, I would kill him,
but that's not the... look, I know that
there's a double standard here,
but it's different when it's a girl.
It... It is.
- It shouldn't be.
- Look, I hate abuse,
but I don't think that's what
we're dealing with here.
Donna is not a criminal.
Now as long as she doesn't
see him again,
that's all we want,
isn't it?
Even if she gets the new heart,
he won't look after her.
He's not gonna take care of her.
- You're talking about Phillip?
- He sends me in his place.
Who does that? Even now,
he's in the lobby on his Blackberry.
This is his baby, his wife.
He should be here for her,
you know?
There still isn't a heart, but
Janine is at the top of the list.
I've also got a call in
to the head of U.N.O.S.
Janine's blood type "O," so am I.
It's the most common.
- It shouldn't be so hard.
- That works in her favor,
but organ donation
is a difficult process.
- Supply can't meet the demand.
- I want to do something.
If I could... give her my heart...
We're gonna find you one.
How long do Janine and the baby have
to find a heart
before they die?
48 hours.
- Isn't that someone else's job?
- I can't stop. Nesting.
I see mess or clutter
or things out of place...
She seems nice.
- Lisa. And her kid is cute.
- Yeah, I like them.
What? What's wrong?
I just...
I hate it that you're maybe
carrying my baby,
and I didn't tell her.
- Do you think you should?
- You think I shouldn't?
you're happy. And I'm all
for full disclosure, but
do you think you should
tell her something
before there's anything to tell?
Sorry, Pete. Were...
you two in the middle of a...
Just finishing.
- Are those for me?
- No, for me, from a patient.
She's in love with me.
Her name is Anita.
I started treating her a few months ago.
She was painfully shy.
She wanted me to help her
be more assertive with a coworker
she had fallen in love with...
you know, she...
she didn't know how to talk to him.
And as she realized
how easy it was to talk to you,
- she channeled her love to you.
- Classic transference.
Clearly.
- You... don't have to say it like that.
- Like what?
Like a woman couldn't fall
in love with me unless it was a
- therapeutic mistake.
- I didn't say that.
I can be very charming, you know.
I know.
Well... I was just saying that...
that it happens,
that it's part of the process.
Are you having your own feelings?
This is not about
countertransference.
I mean, granted, my love life is...
At best,
complicated right now, but
I just wanted to talk
to a colleague, I guess,
go on record if nothing else.
But also to see if you had any...
secrets.
I hate to fail.
I think, you won't
fail.
She's... lucky to have you, Sheldon.
And can you really blame her?
Dell, I'm going out for lunch, so if
my 2:00 gets here before I do, will you
just put her in a room for me?
What else would I do?
Later, we're...
gonna have a talk.
- And I mean a come-to-Jesus talk.
- You're not my mother, Naomi.
You're not even my boss.
Everybody's patience
is wearing thin, Dell.
- What?
- Hey.
Naomi won't push this.
I will. Leave.
Take the day.
Get it together, Dell.
I'd just found out
about Bill's affair...
from his e-mail.
There were lots of e-mails
from different women
and pictures.
They were all so young.
And I was feeling old...
and insecure.
And Bobby?
He just got ansferred into my class.
The way he looked at me, it just...
it just made me feel better.
He'd find reasons to stay after,
and I'd help him with his homework.
When we wanted a break,
we'd just start talking...
for hours.
I tried to get him to focus
on girls his own age.
- He kept coming back to me.
- I know, but you're the adult.
- You should've stopped him.
- I love him.
Look, I know it's wrong,
but when I thought something was
gonna happen to him in the hospital...
This is a crime,
and we should be reporting it.
Yeah, bottom line... you...
can't see him anymore. If you do...
Yeah, don't.
Okay.
I hate heart transplants.
You're basically waiting
for someone to die
to save the person who you want
to live. It's horrible.
To have to sit and wait and...
- sit...
- And not be in control.
You can only do so much.
And if... you've got a baby,
a baby who could die, you're content
to just chalk it all up to fate?
- Then it's on me.
- Exactly.
We are the ultimate narcissists.
Life and death is all up to us.
No wonder so many doctors are
insufferable.
Am i?
I think you're one of the good ones.
When they brought him in,
I recognized him and I paged you.
It's Phillip, Janine's husband.
He's comatose, no corneal reflexes.
Type 2 diabetic.
Tox screen was negative.
- What happened?
- Glucose was initially less than 10.
Looks like an insulin overdose. E.E.G.
shows no evidence of any brain activity.
He's brain dead. Oh, my God.
Do you think...
What?
He's an organ donor.
- Can I help you?
- I'm fine, thank you.
I like the atmosphere...
open, friendly, comfortable.
What are you doing here?
I told you I was not interested.
I figured I'd check out exactly
what you're holding on to.
Well, that's not
a very good idea, so...
Because of the other Dr. Bennett?
I read his book. Don't worry.
As far as he knows, I'm a patient.
I doubt he thinks that I'm trying to
get you pregnant, and... you should go.
Lunch tomorrow?
- You are pushing.
- I'm a man who knows what he wants.
- Aren't you popular these days?
- What?
- The guy you were just talking to.
- No. He's just... he's a patient, so...
Good night, Sam.
Good night.
I can't...
I can't breathe.
I can't think.
What am I gonna do without Phillip?
Janine, I know this is
unthinkably hard,
and none of us could possibly
imagine.
It... it's awful.
But I need you to focus right now.
I need you to focus on the baby
that you're carrying,
the baby that you
and Phillip created,
because if you don't do this,
you both could die.
My husband is dead.
And you want me to take his heart
to save myself?
- To save both of you.
- I can't.
How could I?
Janine, listen to me,
it's hard for anyone to fathom,
but the heart is a machine.
A heart is tissue that provides
a hugely important function.
It is not your husband.
You're not taking from him.
He is providing for you.
It's what he'd want.
You know it is.
Phillip's death is tragic,
but it's giving you a chance.
Now you need to get over your fear
and do this,
if not for you, for the baby.
And for you.
He's my brother.
And I haven't even digested that,
because...
I know that there's something
more important right now.
We can't save him.
We can save you.
Once the heart's out, we've got
four to six hours to get it in.
Montgomery, Barnes, hold it.
Don't you dare touch him.
You're not removing his heart.
How is she?
Donna?
I don't know.
You know, we need to focus on you.
We're gonna get you better.
I keep texting her.
She won't answer.
You know, I get it, Bobby.
People fall for their teachers.
It wasn't like that. I didn't have,
like, a crush on her or anything.
We started talking,
and it was real.
I mean, have you ever talked
to a teenage girl, Dr. Freedman?
It's like deciphering code.
This was a real conversation.
- Even so, given the age difference...
- Why are people so hung up on age?
Donna.
- You're not supposed to be here.
- I know. I just...
Hey, could you give us a minute?
- No, I really can't.
- Please.
- We had a deal.
- I want you to go.
- Mrs. Keating?
- I just wanted to...
make sure Bobby was feeling better.
- Dr. Freedman, is there a problem?
- No, there's no problem.
She's here to see me.
I think you need to go, Donna, now.
I never meant to hurt him.
- I don't understand.
- I love her.
- You're sleeping with our son?
- Leave, now.
- I'm sorry.
- Now.
What?
You know the woman you met
this morning... Violet...
the pregnant woman?
Yeah.
We're... we're not together,
but...
there's a... chance that it's...
My baby.
Look, I...
I like you,
and I want
to start things off being open.
She doesn't know who the father is?
You know...
It's a long story.
What are you thinking?
Do you know how hard it is
for a single mom
to find a man who's smart
and funny and...
likes kids,
someone who likes me and my son,
who doesn't just
think he's in the way?
I like you, Pete.
This feels good
and right.
So it's not the end of the world.
But I have Ben,
and I have to protect him.
So I guess what I really
need to know is,
what are you thinking?
Where's your head at, Montgomery?
Woman needs a heart, can't find one.
Suddenly her husband drops dead.
Bam, you got one.
Awfully convenient.
Yes, it's very coincidental, Charlotte,
and perhaps we could ponder
just how coincidental it is
if we had time,
- but we don't.
- His wife is deteriorating.
She needs that heart now.
If we wait, she'll die.
Insulin overdose is a well-known
cause of death in diabetics.
Accidental overdose or on purpose?
Because this hospital will not condone
suicide to provide organs
or be party to destroying evidence
if it wasn't an accident.
I want someone here
from the M.E.'s office
to collect trace evidence from the body
and find me a cause of death
before you touch him.
If that man was murdered,
and you destroy evidence
- We don't have time, Charlotte.
- Well, make time.
I'm not letting a murderer get away
just so you can have his heart.
- You've got to go home.
- I know,
but I can't. He needs me.
I need him.
No, this has got to end.
Now his parents are...
- What were you thinking?
- I screwed up, Sam.
You ever do that? You see the train
wreck and you just keep going
because it makes you forget...
- everything?
- We all do,
but you've gotta turn back.
- You gotta turn back now.
- Donna Keating?
- Yes.
- You're under arrest
for statutory rape.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
He's been in there
for over an hour, Charlotte.
You gotta get him outta here.
You need to wait.
He's doing his job.
- Her pressure's dropping.
- Baby's showing signs of distress.
We gotta do this now.
- Do you have everything you need?
- I'll be done shortly.
You've taken his blood, you've taken
photos, you've scoured his entire body.
Can't you get the rest of what you need
after we take the heart?
- I'll take that as a yes.
- Charlotte?
Charlotte.
- Do it.
- Let's go.
I'm gonna scrub in. Have him ready
for incision in three minutes.
- Love is a bitch.
- For you or for lolita's brother?
I know this is crazy, but...
- I think Donna really loves him.
- Turning into a romantic?
I've always been a romantic.
Oh, now that... really hurts.
That really hurts me.
- You can take it.
- No. I'm talking to you.
What? It's... polite. What?
Who was that guy
by the elevator last night?
What are you talking about?
Woman, look,
I was married to you for 12 years,
all right?
I know when you're hiding
something from me.
I mean, if you want
to blow off Duncan, I'm all for it.
Just don't
- hide it from me.
- Duncan and I are fine.
I thought we were good...
- Telling each other everything.
- We're good,
- All right... Okay.
- We are. We're good.
His airways are clear
and there's no indication
of any residual damage
from the asthma attacks.
Awesome.
- I can go to soccer today?
- Rest the engines, bud.
Next week, okay?
I didn't mean to put pressure on you
last night.
I just...
I think you're a good guy. And...
you told me the truth.
I really appreciate that.
I just want this to work.
I... just came to...
check up on you...
But... wow.
She really loves you.
- She has dreams about me.
- Sex dreams?
I thought I was making progress.
We went over it yesterday.
But then Anita says that we've been
so close for so long,
she can't stand not expressing
what she feels anymore.
And that it may seem crazy to me,
but she wants me bad...
so damn bad.
- I'm quoting her.
- That's excellent, Sheldon.
Now you're mocking me.
No, she's saying to you
what she can't say to her coworker.
You know, you have to get her
to talk to him.
If she has feelings, and she
doesn't tell the other person,
it's a missed opportunity.
You know what, Violet?
- You're good.
- Clearly so are you.
I'm scared.
Dr. Barnes says the heart's taking.
You can do this, Janine.
You and the baby are gonna be fine.
It's not that.
It's Malcolm.
He's been there for me.
Everything I've ever needed,
every time I've needed anything.
He would do anything for me.
- Well, why does that scare you?
- I think...
I know he loves me.
But he's in love with me.
He's never done anything
or said anything, just...
Phillip is gone.
And I needed a heart,
and then phillip died.
Look, I don't want to think it.
I don't even want to believe it, but...
do you think malcolm killed him
for me?
What are you doing here?
I didn't feel like being
at the office, and,
you know, I heard about Phillip. I wanted
to see how Malcolm was, ans Janine.
Something happen?
Janine...
thinks that phillip's death...
that...
she thinks that Malcolm
may have killed him.
She says that Malcolm's
in love with her.
Well, yeah, I mean,
I could've told you that part.
- What, you didn't see it?
- I don't know. I gu...
- I mean, he's good to her, but...
- Well, he's also a nurse, so...
he'd know how much insulin to use.
I mean, he'd know what they'd look for,
what would look normal.
We're talking about Phillip's brother.
No, we're talking about watching someone
slip away, someone that you love.
William, I...
I am flattered.
I really am. But you're asking me
to orphan my baby,
and I can't.
Oceanside is not just a job.
These people are my family, so...
I saw that yesterday,
and while I admire it...
I have to think of my own family.
I love them,
which is why I live 3,000 miles away
from them...
So they don't interfere with my life.
Well, Sam's not like that.
We are...
I can tell him anything.
Does he know you're here?
There's no one else on my list,
Dr. Bennett.
I'll be back in two weeks
to make an official offer.
- Is everything all right?
- My husband posted bail.
His parting gift.
He's done with me.
I'm sorry.
Come to my office.
What?
It's Bobby.
He says he wants us
to go off together,
that he doesn't care about his parents,
school, anything.
All he cares about is us,
me.
The thought of it right now...
To escape everything?
- I wish I could.
- Well, you know that you can't.
I love him, Sam.
He's all I have.
- What's wrong with me?
- Nothing's wrong...
You can't help love. I get that.
But if you love Bobby,
you gotta let this go.
How do I do that?
How's the baby?
I just... checked their chart, and...
they're both doing fine.
It's hard watching her go
through all this pain,
losing Phillip,
maybe the baby.
That baby means everything to her.
Well, at least she has you.
- Is there something bothering you?
- Yes,
the timing of this,
Phillip dying in a way
that kept his heart pumping.
You think he killed himself for her?
You think I killed him?
I think there's a fine line
between miracle and convenience,
and I think about this pregnancy
and how I got to know Janine
and you
and not phillip.
- He pushed me to be there.
- And you let him.
Here was this wonderful,
sweet woman
feeling alone in her marriage.
And there's Phillip,
not deserving what he had,
not appreciating what he had.
But he had it. He
had her.
So I wanted
something I couldn't have.
Don't tell me
you've never felt that way.
I loved my brother.
But he wasn't
good enough for her.
But if he's dead...
At least she's alive.
Hey, you all right?
You know, Malcolm...
might have killed his brother
for someone that he loves.
And me?
I can't even find her, Pete.
Betsey.
All I know is St. Louis.
You know, Heather is working
for a company in St. Louis.
But I don't know who Betsey's with
or where she's living or
what she thinks about me.
And...
I mean, as far as she knows,
her father's gone.
That's horrible, Dell.
But Heather was in a good place
when she left,
and she loves Betsey.
But she's my child.
You'll know. When... Violet's baby
is born, you'll know, and you...
I'd bet you'd do anything.
I mean, what kind of a man am I
that I just sit here and watch?
Just because you haven't found her yet
doesn't mean you won't.
What's going on?
I want to believe it
won't be a problem,
that I can be there for you and Ben
and the baby.
Yeah, the baby has to come first.
I get that.
I can make that work.
I need to be there
for both of them...
For the baby
and for Violet.
I guess it's better you know now
before anyone gets hurts.
I'd like to keep treating Ben.
I don't want this to affect him.
I don't know, Pete.
You are testing phillip's blood?
Why? I mean, the M.E.'s doing that.
I think he did it.
Malcolm.
I think he murdered his brother,
and I need evidence. I need proof.
We just pulled off the unthinkable.
I mean, two lives were almost gone,
and then a heart dropped in our laps,
and now they're gonna live.
It's a miracle.
You and I did it.
Can't we just
focus on that?
I can't.
Phillip's dead. And Malcolm
might get to be with Janine.
Why's he got to be a bad guy?
I mean, maybe he's just a guy who
didn't get along with his brother.
You told me he was a good guy.
Good people don't murder their brothers
and then get to sleep with their wives.
Can't they just be
two people in love?
- I mean, why try and tear 'em apart?
- Okay, Noah,
there are lines and rules
and things that you can't do.
They shouldn't be together.
It's wrong.
Autopsy results came back.
M.E. ruled it an accidental
insulin overdose.
Guess it all worked out.
- I still think he did it.
- There isn't any proof.
You kissed me back.
You're angry at me.
You say that I'm at fault.
But it isn't just that I kissed you.
It's that you kissed me back.
That's why you're angry.
Thank you for letting me talk to him.
What's going on?
Bobby, honey, listen to me...
as soon as they leave.
- They can't, Bobby.
- Don't let them tell you that.
Don't let them make you feel
this is wrong.
I'm twice your age.
Age doesn't matter, Donna.
I love you.
You're 17.
And I was in a really bad place,
and I needed you, but...
I don't love you.
You're lying.
They're making you say this.
Bobby, you have your whole life
ahead of you.
And no one is saying that
this isn't real, what you feel...
we both feel.
You know it.
I'm sorry.
Bobby, I know that you love her.
But sometimes the best thing to do
when you love someone
and it's not right
is to just let go
and move on.
I had no idea you were in town.
Just a bit of business.
I wanted to
check in and see
how my practice was doing.
There were some bumps, but
I'm feeling good about
where things are heading.
Patient bookings are strong.
Good, good.
I'm glad to hear it.
That's...
all you wanted?
I'll be back in a couple of weeks.
You can
bring me up to speed
on everything then.
You were right.
I wasn't being honest,
and...
I think maybe I should be.
You know what I think?
I think that... what we're doing...
is too hard.
We're divorced,
but I still care about you.
And hearing out
everybody you're dating
and what you're doing, it's just...
It's not good,
for either of us.
You said you could handle it.
I mean, I thought we were friends.
I know, I did, and we are, but I...
When your dating pool
is everybody that I know...
Archer, Bryce,
Duncan...
there's a limit, Nai.
And maybe I said I could handle it,
but I can't
and... I shouldn't have to.
- So what are you saying?
- We can't be friends anymore.
I need some distance,
to let go, to...
to move on.
You want distance.
I need it.
Don't you?
Sheldon. What happened?
Anita thought I was gonna confess
my love.
When I insisted her feelings
were misplaced, she...
she beat me with the roses.
It was great.
- It was great?
- I forced her, I pushed her,
to a breakthrough, Violet.
And... when she saw what she
did to me, she broke down.
She realized she spent so much money
on gifts for the wrong person.
She called her coworker
from the office, and th...
they're having dinner.
You should feel so proud, Sheldon.
You know, you...
gotta put something on that.
But that's not the best part.
The best part is I
had a breakthrough of my own.
And I realized that
when someone has feelings
and doesn't let the other person know,
that's a...
that's a missed opportunity.
But isn't that what I said before?
Yes, and I convinced Anita,
but then
I realized that it...
it applied to me.
I'm in love with you, Violet,
from the first time we rode
on that elevator.
I don't care
whose child you're carrying.
I can talk to you about anything.
I want to talk to you
about everything.
And... when I'm not with you...
I'm empty.
Will you marry me?
Mc Dreamy Team
pour Forom.com