Don't scare the erection.
It's up, Violet. Full mast.
I thought you just wanted
to be friends.
I did, but a week of friendship...
it looks like I'm over my issue,so...
is... this okay?
This is embarrassing.
I shouldn't have come.
hold it!
What's your problem?
You look like someone died.
Dying.
- Big Daddy.
- Big Daddy?
Well, that is a screen name.
When you get back on the horse,
you really get back on the horse?
What's killing him, the...
the sex or the cold-fish attitude?
Big Daddy's my father.
Kevin's back at my place.
That's good.
I don't know. It's just weird.
It's all...
negotiation and awkwardness,
but it's fine, it's fine.
Sam has a girlfriend.
Maya hung out last night
with her at Sam's.
- That's not good.
- No, it's good.
It's good.
Why do you two look like that?
- We're good.
- What?
- Your girlfriend is nice.
- You have a girlfriend? Well, that's...
- Good.
- It's good.
- It's really good.
Who calls their father "Big Daddy"?
I mean, that's like...
it's like "cat on a hot tin roof".
It's like...
Charlotte King does.
She actually calls her father
"Big Daddy"?
And, you know, he's dying, and,
I made a
jerk of myself in front of Charlotte
because I was laughing.
- Nice move.
- Should I do something?
Walk away, Cooper.
Big Daddy is not your problem.
you have another kid
that we don't know about?
Funny.
This is Julian.
It's the C.F. family, Sam.
Champ, come here.
It is just wrong...
a single father, two kids, and
and all of them havecystic fibrosis.
And... Julian's father
doesn't sound so good.
Hey, you two.
Is it photography day?
I got Gracie a camera for her birthday.
She's... been taking pictures
of everything.
I'm maKing a scrapbook.
It's really great.
When I don't feel good,
it gives me something to do.
Well, let's see if we can make you
feel better. Do you want to be first?
I'll keep your dad entertained
with some percussion therapy.
- Where you beat me healthy?
- Or we can let Addison
do the bronchoscopy lavage.
All right, we'll get your labs done,
get you out of hereas soon as we can.
- You gonna be okay on your own, kiddo?
- Dad, I'm 9.
All right, any dizziness
or slurred speech?
Seth. Will you please tell my son
that I'm fine?
You still have weakness
on your right side
and a persistent visual field defect.
- I'm concerned.
- Tell her she needs to move.
- I'm not moving to Florida.
- I can take care of you there.
I can take care of myself here, right?
Well, you're still at risk
for another stroke.
- You should be with someone.
- Are you ganging up on me?
Since dad died,
you barely want to talk on the phone.
- That's not true.
- It is.
- It's not true.
He thinks I'm depressed.
I'm not.
- I have friends. I'm not alone.
- They're not family.
- You should be with family.
- This is a Big decision.
Deciding to move, up root your life...
it's huge.
But losing a spouse is huge, too.
Do me a favor, Cynthia
speak with our therapist?
It would make me feel
a lot more comfortable.
I thought I was okay with it,
but I'm not sure if I am okay with it.
I'm sleeping with two men.
Do I get a lecture now?
Yes, you do.
This is good.
- This is progress.
- Really?
- That's my lecture?
- It's fun, it's exciting, it's...
congratulations, man.
So you're okay with it?
Because the weird thing is,
I'm okay with it, except for the part
of me that thinks I shouldn't be, but I
- I think I am.
- Sex is good.
Relationships are bad.
Relationships are what cause people
to be cold and lying and deceitful.
I mean, you know.
You're a therapist.
Professionally, I would dispute that
and suggest that you need
to see your own therapist.
But personally?
Yes.
As a red-blooded american,
sex is your birthright.
Go forth, enjoy...
guilt-free.
I will.
I will exercise my right.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- The C.F. results are back.
How bad?
If this... is... if this is serious,
if I'm gonna die, please just
- tell me now.
- Daron, your tests came back fine.
It's... it's Gracie.
She tested positive
for burkholderia cepacia.
- It's a bacteria that gets in...
- yeah, I know what it is.
I'm sorry.
It's gotta be some kind of a mistake.
I mean, she looks fine. Look at her.
You're not gonna tell me that her lung
function's gonna start going down hill.
From her test results,
it appears that it already has.
You know how contagious this bacteria
can be for C.F. patients.
It's a miracle that
you and Julian haven't caught it.
What we need to do now
is get Gracie to the hospital,
get her into isolation
while we figure out what to do.
Okay. All right.
- I'll... take her there now.
- No, Daron, you can't take her.
You can't touch her,
you can't be with her or you'll die.
Private Practice S02E12
Homeward Bound
I'm not being stubborn.
I don't want to move.
Moving to a new city
at any age is stressful.
But just for a minute,
let's look at the other side.
Could this move be good for you?
I can't move.
And I can't talk to him about
why I can't move. And...
he's not going to take no
for an answer.
and now...
now he has Sam on his side.
Well, you can talk to me.
If Seth finds out the truth,
he's going to hate me.
Cynthia, anything you tell me
stays with me.
Let me help you.
Talk to me.
You can't even...
you can't even tell Sam.
If I can't come near you,
how are you gonna take care of me?
Well, we'll fiomre sething out, honey.
Okay? I promise.
But for right now, you're gonna have to go
to the hospital with Dr. Freedman, okay?
She needs me.
You can't put yourself at risk,
or Julian.
If either of you gets exposed,
this will kill you.
So I just leave her alone?
Isn't there a family member
you could call,
someone who could help you,
who could be with Gracie
I got a sister in Nashville,
but she doesn't really know Gracie.
Look, Gracie needs me.
Okay? I need her.
She's already lost her mother, you know?
I'm... all she has.
Look, I could wear a mask, right?
We, you know, we could take precautions.
Daron, if you live together,
you will get this,
and there is no way we can treat it.
Well, I need to be there
for both of them.
You know, they both need me.
how am I supposed to choose?
- I'll be back.
- Okay, take care.
Hey, how's... how's Gracie
You know, not good. She's trying to be
brave, but she doesn't like the hospital...
And I don't think
that she really understands
that not seeing her dad or her brother,
not living with them, that's permanent.
What were you talking
to Charlotte about?
She asked me to do her neonatal rounds
while she goes to Alabama to see her dad.
What, like you owe her a favor
after what she did to us?
Cooper, her father is dying.
I'm sorry about your dad.
- If there's anything you need...
- I'm fine.
I see death every day on the job.
It's a part of life,
and I'll deal with it.
I'm late for my flight.
Cynthia is fully capable
of making decisions about her own care.
And you're not at all concerned that
a 70-year-old woman
still recovering from a stroke is putting
herself further at risk by living alone?
Sam, you asked me to evaluete her.
So she's not depressed,
she is not clinging irrationally
to her independence.
She has legitimate reasons
for what she's doing.
- Which are?
- Privileged.
I think it's confusing to Maya,
meeting a woman
that you've just started to date.
- What?
- I think meeting a new girlfriend
could be... scary for her.
Do you have a problem with Sonya?
You date who ever you want. Just...
think about how this affects Maya.
That was almost the high light
of my day.
Not in the mood.
Cute kid.
What? I can't feel for a patient?
Try me.
9 year old with cystic fibrosis patient.
Rare bacterial infection in her lungs.
Father can't be with her anymore
because he has C.F., too,
same thing with her 2-year-old brother,
because if ither of them get infected
with the bacteria, they'll die. So,
father has to choose...
let his girl die alone or
stay with her and leave a 2 year old
with C.F. behind.
Burkholderia cepacia?
What?
I had cancer patients manifest the same
bacterial complications
as those with B. cepacia.
I've had success eradicating
the infection.
Okay, no one in the world has found
a cure for cepacia syndrome,
but you're gonna pitch me one?
I know cancer's a lot different
than cystic fibrosis,
and the bacteriais more drug resistant.
I just...
it's a tragic story.
- Worth a shot.
- Why would you help me?
I'm a doctor.
So...
I've spoken to your mother,
Seth, and...
she is not ready to move.
Seth, please, you won't listen to me.
- Listen to her.
- She understands your concerns.
She has agreed to come in
for weekly checkups with Sam
and counseling with me and to put
a medic alert system in her house.
And if her condition worsens,
then we can always revisit this.
I promised...
I promised dad...
I would take care of you.
Most of my friends, the idea
of a parent moving in is terrifying.
We want you.
It's not like I want
to put you in a home.
- Stop pushing me.
- Then help me understand.
You hate the city. You hate the traffic,
you hate the crime...
Talk to me.
- Easy, Seth.
- I think I need a...
Get an ambulance, please.
Is she having another stroke?
It was a transientis chemic attack...
press...
- a warning sign for a stroke.
- It happened because I got upset.
That's all.
I am fine.
- You're not a doctor.
- Your doctors are saying
you're not fine.
- Hey, I came as soon as I could.
- I'm fine. Everyone is making a fuss.
You're not fine.
Hi, Annette.
Thank you for coming. Listen,
can you just wait outside?
We're discussing things
with the doctors.
She can stay.
I want someone on my side.
It's not about sides.
I'm sorry. I'm... I can'T...
I'm moving you out.
I... I'll get a lawyer if I have to.
Talk to him.
Talk to your son.
He'll understand.
Violet, what's... going on?
She's right.
It's gotta be better than this.
I'm... I'm not alone.
I have someone here...
who... who loves me and who wants
to take care of me. And...
I was afraid to tell you because...
I love you, too, and I...
- I'm afraid you won't understand.
- Understand what?
I have someone.
Your mother's in love.
She has someone here
that she doesn't want to leave,
and she was afraid to tell you.
You've gone along I get that since dad's
been gone, it'been confusing, and...
and you need to have somebody here
with you. This is not who you are.
Seth, this isn't a reaction
to your father dying.
I'm not talking to you.
This is just some...
grief-stricken, crazy reaction.
We've been together for years.
When you were with dad?
- I am so sorry.
- You cheated on dad with her?
You wanna catch a movie after?
Just... get away from it all?
I can't. C.F. research to do.
Begins the day, ends the day.
I've got a little girl
who's about to die, Kevin.
It's hard to think about going out
and relaxing.
Well, you could a called.
You... could a said don't come over.
- You wanted me to cancel?
- You're giving me attitude.
I'm here.
There are other things
I could be doing.
I get a lot of invitations...
my friends, women...
So what, you want to date other women?
Maybe I do, but I don't.
I'm not.
Because this is so much fun.
What hapened to us?
I mean...
there was a time when you'd eat noodles
off my naked body. What...
what happened to us?
Look, I'm sorry.
I thought...
I... usually think that
honesty is for the best.
Well, I knew at 15.
But... back then...
that was not what you did.
You...
found a guy, got married, had kids.
And I loved him.
I did.
And then I met Annette.
You know, our kids were the same age,
and she was...
I couldn't stop myself.
Well, you were honest with yourself.
That's...
that's sometimes the hardest piece.
He's got to understand, right?
I mean...
- once he gets over the shock?
- He loves you.
He... wanted to do
what was best for you.
He'll come around.
Electrons that detach
and move around are called...
- Atoms?
- Free electrons.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Ten's he last time you gave me answers
without torturing me first?
I just know you...
didn't have a chance
to study last night.
What do you want to know about her?
Sonya?
I wasn't...
- How was last night?
- It was fun.
It wasn't... uncomfortable?
Because, you know, you do not have
to hang out with your dad
and his new girlfriendif you don't want to.
I like her mom,
and dad really likes her.
You'd like her, too,
if you got to know her.
Don't worry about me.
Dad's just having fun.
You should have fun, too.
You need to get a life.
I can't stop thinking about you.
She loved Sonya.
And why shouldn't she? She's smart,
she is pretty, and she is fun. I mean, she ...
she brings over movies and popcorn,
and I, I just... I do homework.
Nai, you're her mom.
You're supposed to do homework.
And Sonya is being fun because
she's trying to make a good impression.
That's what happens
when things are new.
You go out of your way to be nice.
Look at me and Kevin,you know?
Not so new, not so nice anymore.
That sounds like marriage.
You gonna end it?
Hey... I've been through all
of Wyatt's research.
It's pretty convincing.
He had an idea... to help.
Let's go find Pete and Coop.
So... I could get her back?
It's a long shot,
but we'd like to try.
It's not gonna hurt? I mean,
I don't want anything to hurt her.
Her lungs are already full,
so we have to clear them.
So it's the same procedure.
We just take a sample of the bacteria.
We know that it worked on cancer.
We are hoping... really hoping...
it can help Gracie.
You know, she loves horses.
Her whole room is horses.
You know, I thought if she had these here
in her room, that she'd feel more...
I don't know. I'll... go call her.
I'll tell her maybe.
Delivery for Ms. Gracie Rousakis.
He's worried about me.
I don't like it when he worries.
Well, you know, he's your dad.
It's his job to worry.
Tell him I'm fine.
Make him stop worrying about me.
Since mom died, he's done everything.
And when he starts worrying,
he starts coughing,and then...
You need to tell him I'm fine.
It's okay if you miss him.
I want my dad.
- We got your page.
- You've got to give her something.
Seth hasn't come back or called.
- She can't stop crying.
- We'll prescribe some lorazepam.
What you need to do is call Seth
and get him back. Tell him...
tell him she'll go with him to Florida.
I love you more than anything,
but you need your son
and you need your grand children
more than you need me.
Please. Talk to him.
Tell him she'll go.
Just get him back here.
I just want you to know
that your dad's outside waiting.
He wanted to let you know that
he's here.
What about Dr. Cooper?
He's gone for the day,
but you don't have to worry.
I am gonna take good care of you.
Once you're asleep, I'm gonna use this
to clean out your lungs.
You'll feel much better.
See? Who's that?
Then we're gonna give dell some of
what we took out
to give to Dr. Montgomery and
Dr. Lockhart to test the antibiotics on.
I know it's scary, but when you wake up,
it'll all be over.
I just...
I hope it works.
Now we just need one of these
to stay clear,
and then we'll know
that the bacteria is sensitive
to that combination of antibiotics.
By morning we should know,
one way or the other.
- Want to grab a bite?
- Actually, I am starved,
but I am supposed to...
meet someone.
- The cop.
- Yes, the cop.
So you really think a hot date
and fine dining is better than a guy
you can barely stand
and cafeteria mac and cheese?
I do love... the mac and cheese.
From a psychophysiolical stand point,
- this is remarkable.
- What is?
- You.
What you do to me. All day
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
And ever since you called...
I remember this tasting a lot better.
I don't know.
It takes me back.
To residency, you know,
when life was simple.
See, I have a hard time picturing
you as an intern, taking crap
- from your attending.
- By year two, they all hated me.
It took them that long?
sorry.
It's just... yeah,
they really hated me.
so'd my wife.
- You're married?
- Was.
The divorce took 2 years, 4 lawyers,
hundreds of thousands of dollars.
We... discussed assets, property,
money, the dog.
But not once...
in all that time
did anyone ever ask me about love.
I'm still bitter...
about the dog.
I get what bitter does.
You have all that love, and then...
- where does it go?
- You, too?
Member of the club.
So I'm gonna ask this again, but
this time, pretend you think I'm human.
You want to maybe have dinner with me
sometime?
- A date?
- I...
don't think that's a good idea.
Is it 'cause it's me or
because of the cop?
Think about it.
I am not here.
This is not jealousy.
This is concern for my daughter.
Remember when Maya told you...
remember when Maya told you to get a life?
I have a life.
I have a... great life.
I'm just standing here on my patio
in the dark spying on your ex,
his girlfriend and your daughter.
I'm being replaced.
Sonya is my replacement.
That's Maya's new mommy.
I am freaking... oh,god.
Ignore me. Ignore me.
I'm just freaking.
Thank you.
Why aren't... you out with Kevin?
It's not like we're married.
I don't have to be with him every night.
I don't have to call or check in,
and if I want to talkto another man,
it's not like we have promise rings
or anything.
Who is it, this other man?
Wyatt asked me out on a date.
He's...
different than I thought.
Okay, well...
can I just say that... you're
in a relationship, so, you know...
- knees together.
- No,I am not a cheater.
Okay, I've done that.
I'm not gonna do that again.
I don't know. But I do want to say
yes to the date.
I just... I don't know. Should I?
I shouldn't. Should I?
We are so screwed up.
This is a nice place.
Crazy humid.
Lung cancer.
Doctors gave him six months
two years ago.
He went into respiratory failure
last week.
How you holdin' up?
Let's see...
Duke and Landry are downing bourbon,
mom has taken to her room with the vapors,
and not a one of 'em wants any part
of making a decision about Big Daddy.
The vapors?
You have a medical degree
from Johns Hopkins.
You've diagnosed your mother
with the vapors.
She's a drug addict.
But here in Dixie,
we're more polite about it.
- What?
- Why are you her, Cooper,
in the middle of my southern
gothic tragedy?
I came for you.
Landry was supposed to pull the plug
this morning, couldn't do it.
Duke can't even come in the room.
- So it's just you.
- Just me.
He's not even there anymore.
It's just...
the ethical, moral,
medically correct thing to do.
Pull the plug and...
it's done.
- Are you okay?
- No, not really.
So I've been having sex,
lots and lots and lots of sex.
- Yes, with Pete.
- And with Sheldon, many times.
Many, many...
many times.
and I'm in pain.
- And I can't stop peeing.
- You need Addison.
You've got honey moon cystitis
from too much sex.
So I will prescribe you an antibiotic
and something for the pain.
Violet Turner, I am your friend,
and I know you.
Sleeping with Sheldon and Pete
is not you.
Come on.
When Cooper does it, he gets a slap
on the back and an attaboy,
but when I do it...
when a woman...
takes control of her sexuality,
she's a whore.
You are just not that person.
Something is going on here.
I mean...
I don't know, you're avoiding something
or in denial. Something psychological.
I don't know. You're the therapist.
You know.
And you know this is not good.
Wouldn't it be better just to figure out
which one you want to be with?
How can I choose?
I mean, Pete is...
Pete's all heat.
I just see him, and I melt.
- And Sheldon is comfort.
- Like mac and cheese.
What?
Do you think this is okay,
what she's doing?
I think that it's hard
to figure out who the right person is.
Thank you.
Yeah, I mean, Kevin's great, but,
you know, I mean, is...
is he the one or is it someone else?
I want to be okay with this
Sonya thing. I do, I do.
But I don't think I care that Sam
is dating, but do I care?
Am I in denial?
No, this is about Maya, right?
I'm not crazy. This is about Maya.
I'm not crazy.
Does this really look like
the time for therapy?
- Thanks for coming in.
- I just came to pick up my laptop.
- I left it yesterday when I ran out.
- Your mother needs you.
She is willing to move all the way
to Florida if that's what you want.
Think about it, Seth.
Think about what's best for her.
The only thing I've been able to think
about this how stupid I was
not to have fired this out.
She wanted to tell you. She was just
afraid that you wouldn't accept her.
You know, it's not about accepting her.
You think I can't accept that she's gay?
I've known Annette my whole life.
Now it's like I'm...
replaying every moment,
every christmas, every thanksgiving.
You know, I was in the backyard
playing football and they were...
- fooling around.
- You don't know that.
Do you think I want to think about it?
And my dad?
She was everything to him.
She be trayed him.
She be trayed us.
You're a father.
You've gotta know
how difficult it is to be a parent.
You love your kids, so you want to do
everything you can to protect them.
So you try to figure out
what's right to tell them and
what's right to keep from them. And
sometimes you don't get it right, but...
you know, you do your best
because you love them.
You think it would've been better if
your mother had left your father
when you were a kid?
She was just trying
to keep the family together,
trying to give you the mother
that you wanted.
I don't know her.
I feel no connection to that woman
- because I don't know her at all.
- She is your mother.
She would give up everything for you.
Don't you think she has given up enough?
I'm almost afraid to come in here.
We just need one dish
without bacterial growth.
You make it sound so simple.
So that's what it looks like
inside of her lungs.
It was a long shot.
You had to try.
We had to try.
- I don't think we should have dinner.
- Why?
Why, because of me or
because the miracle didn't work?
I don't know.
Sam just left for St. Ambrose
if you're looking for him.
Thank you.
I guess patient trumps lunch.
Look ... we didn't really get a chance
to talk the other night, and...
- I just wanted to...
- No, look, you don't have to.
It's me who should say something.
I know it must have been weird, seeing me
hanging out with your daughter.
I remember what it was like
when my mom dated.
It's... fine.
Well, you know, I just want you
to know that...
wherever this is heading
with Sam, I want to be
really careful about Maya's feelings.
I got burned a few times, so...
I get it.
Well, thank you.
That's... very...
thank you.
You're very nice.
Well, so are you.
Big Daddy always said cancer was just
his chickens coming home to roost
'cause he didn't believe in tears.
If he ever cried,
he did it in private.
Cancer was just his chickens...
payback for being a son of a bitch.
And he was
a son of a bitch
to everybody...
everybody but me.
He loved me being a doctor.
He loved that I didn't just...
marry some boy and
have a bunch of babies.
He would've killed me for marrying
a son of a bitch of my own.
'Cause he knew...
what that would've been like for me.
But if I'd have stayed...
married some boy and had babies,
I would've been here.
When he got sick, I would've been here
to take care of him.
So...
these aren't his chickens.
These are my chickens, 'cause now
I'm the doctor in the family,
and I know what has to be done.
I can do this.
Shut up.
I can do this,damn it.
I can...
That's that.
It's okay to cry.
it's not.
- Daron, I'm sorry.
- Nothing?
Well, we knew it was a long shot,
but I'm sorry.
I can't even go in there to tell her.
I'll do it.
I can't.
I want my dad.
Pete's gonna handle this.
He'll take care of her.
I can't... I can't do it.
here.
Here are the keys to my house.
All Julian's clothes...
and his toys are in his room, okay?
Just...
just make sure that...
he knows why I did this...
- Don't d...
- and that they take care of him.
- No, Daron...
- You can't do this.
I will not let my daughter
go through that alone.
- But, Daron, if you go in there...
- I love my son, okay?
But I love my daughter.
- He's not coming.
- I can try to talk to him again.
- Maybe he just needs more time.
- It's my fault.
I tried to keep it separate...
who I was, who I loved.
You are who you are, and you shouldn't
have to hide that from anybody.
I love you.
I made it all the way out
to the airport,
but I couldn't get out of the car.
I just...
sat there for an hour
in the rental car return l'm...
I'm still trying to understand this.
I know you took care of us.
Dad was happy.
I was happy.
I guess it's your turn to be happy.
You should...
stay here with Annette.
I'll...
I'll... I'll visit.
Maybe sometime, we'll visit.
I'd like that.
Daron gave up on his son.
Just...
walked away from him.
Well, it was an impossible choice
to make. It's hard to fault him.
The reality of Gracie dying
was right in front of him.
The idea of Julian having to bury him
or not be with him,
it's just too abstract.
I just wanted to...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt a conference.
I just
wanted to know if you wanted
to come over later.
You're going over to his house?
I'm sorry. Is there a...
Okay, look...
Pete, Sheldon, I am...
I'm sleeping with both of you.
I thought it was okay,
but it's not.
I realize that...
you... you just can't do that.
I can't do that.
And...
and I'm sorry.
Who are you?
He's right.
I'm a mess.
We're all a mess.
Don't you know that by now?
All I know is,
don't mind finding out...
who you are.
- I was... just coming to see you.
- Yeah?
I just wanted to say that...
I feel I have a responsibility
to our daughter...
for her to know who I am,
good or bad...
but even if that means
telling her who I'm dating.
I never want her to not know
who I am.
I'm gonna say this,
and I know how it sounds.
Maya likes her better than me.
She's your daughter, Nai.
You are her mother.
She doesn't like Sonya better.
Sonya's just new.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
Transcript : Ydy
The Mc Dreamy Team
pour www.forom.com