what are you people doing in my house?
I told you. It's a surprise.
it's a surprise for Sam.
You know about this?
Sadly,I do.
If it's a surprise for sam,then
why aren't you at Sam's house?
Put that down.
'Cause that would totally
ruin the surprise,wouldn't it?
Wait,what are you doing?
Cooper thinks sam's in a rut.
what-- well,I am not in a
rut,okay? And,in fact,I have plans.
You have plans? With who?
With Naomi.
- You invited Naomi here?
- Hey...
no,see,actually,no,that's no good.
Well,it's good for me.
It's good for Naomi. Naomi's my friend.
You, people,I barely know.
The thing is, Naomi kind
of steps on the surprise.
What kind of surprise is this?
one named Ginger.
- What?
I'm outta here.
Oh,she's about to ring the doorbell.
Five minutes.
Ah,okay.
Now we're getting somewhere.
They can't stop us,buddy. Right?
Sam?
Cooper,how do you even
know how to find a stripper?
Ginger is not a stripper.
She's an entertainer.
What does that even mean?
I'm still trying to figure it out.
Sam is not like you, Cooper.
- He's not interested in-
- I think Sam is.
Sam and a stripper,who knew?
Hey,it's just getting good. Could you...
a stripper?
Oh,you like that?
You have something.
Thanks. You're sweet,too.
- No,you got something right here.
- Huh?
Let me just get a closer look.
Uh,yeah.
hey,man.
What were yothinking?
It's a long,sad story.
Hey,did she do the thing where
she,um-- could be pneumonia,
and I'm gonna set
them up with an x-ray.
You're not fooling anybody, Cooper.
Who's up first?
Uh,Dave Walker called this morning,uh,
complaining of headache and nausea.
I heard his wife left him.
Yeah,and he's drinking again.
Got his son and his
mother living with him.
So I'm gonna go check him out.
- You do house calls,too?
- We.
We all do house calls.
- What?
- Nothing.
I got the O'Briens bringing
their baby in again.
9-month-old girl,she's
been sick since birth.
O'Brien--is that
the dad who's--
yeah,he's totally
disconnected from this baby.
It drives me crazy.
I tried to get him in to see you. No go.
Well,let me know if I can
be of any help on the case.
You want to help me?
What?
Anything else?
- Uh,yeah,I have two cases
next week- - nobody?Super.
Pete,do you think that,uh,acupuncture
could help with a patient that's,
uh,presenting with-- just--could you tell
me,did she do the triple-jointed thing?
All right,and I'll be leaving.
Does it even occur to you
to think of Naomi's feelings?
so wait,do they know?
Does Naomi know?
Back to the triple-jointed thing.
It--it--it looks like it hurts,but
in the most awesomest way.
This--this--
look,did she do this?
Amber Johnson.
Hey. Are you mad at me?
Because it kind of seemed like
you were mad at me in the meeting.
I'm just looking out for Naomi.
Hi, Amber. see you next week,Thomas.
Addison is mad at me because
Cooper hired a stripper.
I'm ignoring the stripper.
Today is a day for ignoring things.
I am all business today.
Who's my next patient?
This guy wants to talk to you.
Sign,please.
Oh,no.
That's a nice bike.
No? Okay.
Looks like Emily's gained
some weight. That's good.
She been sleeping?
Better,don't you think?
No,I don't,actually.
You know,we said it was gonna be a long haul
when she was born with these symptoms. So...
I just feel like,when is she
gonna catch a break,you know?
Well... here you go.
Come here,Emily. Look at that guy.
Who's that guy?
You know,just to be safe,I am
gonna run a couple more blood tests.
Oh,she hates needles.
If it was optional,I wouldn't
do it,but it's not,so...
okay?
Did you know you have an office here?
Here,it's--it's
right next door.
I am asking because I am
curious,not because I care.
What's her name?
Who's name?
The girl. The girl, Sam.
Ginger.
Her name is Ginger?
Hey,I did not name her.
I didn't hold her up to the moon
and do the whole kunta kinte thing.
This isn't "roots".
Oh,you funny-- you funny man.
Her name is Ginger.
Did you sleep with Ginger?
And you're asking
because you're curious?
- Yeah.
- YeS.
- Samuel!
- No,I didn'T.
I just wanted to see what
"curiosity" looked like.
It's an awful lot like jealousy.
I am not jealous.
Oh,yes,you are.
If I want to see a stripper,I'm
gonna see a stripper.
Shoot.
I'm grown.
Tryin' to tell me... come on, Dave.
I know you didn't go to work.
Dave probably gets to see strippers.
Probably got one in there right now.
I know you didn't make me
come out here for nothin',dave.
Come on.
Dave!
Dave,open the door.
Ms.Walk,open up the door.
all right.
- how long has he been
like this? - I-I don't know.
I just came downstairs
and he was--I-I don't know.
All righT. Ms.Walker,how
long's he been like this?
Grandma?
Yes,this is dr.Sam Bennett.
I need an ambulance immediately.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚ ÷• øµ∞∏‚
Dave,what happened in there?
Oh,I don't know. I...
had breakfast,getting ready for work,next
thing I know,I'm hugging the toilet.
What's wrong with him?
Well,once we get to the
hospital,we'll figure that out.
But he's coming back?
Of course I am, Stevie.
Stevie,I don't want you
to be here by yourself.
I'm okay. My--my
grandmother's here.
Yeah.
Fellas,would you mind,uh,taking the
boy and his grandmother with you?
I'm worried about leaving
her in charge. All right.
Do you want to talk about Sam.
- well,not Sam-
- I mean,clearly not-
- Will you say it? say it.
- It's not--
Sam's stripper.
Sam's stripper. Say it.
So what?
So? And Sam's single.
I'm single...
so single,and--and
single people move on.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I've been looking at
this in my office all day.
You bought a bike?
Yeah,it's custom built,it's from italy,and
Allan is never getting his hands on it,ever.
I don't care if it costs $6,000.
You bought allan a $6,000 bike?
I-I ordered it last year.
It just arrived today...
on his birthday.
Brutal.
Why don't you sell it?
yeah. Yeah,maybe I will.
Or give it
away.Just--
great. Exactly.
I'm gonna give it away.
Hey. Hey.
You will not give Allan that bike.
I won't?
Will you be strong?
Yeah.
Strong.
I-I told my teacher there's
probably no way you could do it,but--
do what?
Speak at my midwifery class.
I told my teacher about Naomi,and--and
she called you "a primal life giver.
-I think I have something that night,so-
- come on.
Do it.
Might give you a boost.
I don'T... I don't need boosting.
I'm fine.
I'll do it.
I love talking to midwiffs.
yeah,actually I think-- I thk
we're-- we're good on O.B.S but--
oh,I'm actually a double board
certified uh,neonatal surgeon.
One of the best... in the world...
with a specialty
in genetics-- D.N.A.
Uh,well,yeah,maybe,you
know,if,um,if someone drops out.
You can't get more primal
and life giving than D.N.A
Dell?
Excuse me.
Uh,do you still have
time for that consult?
- The little girl?
- Yeah.
Um,please tell I'm reading that wrong.
Cooper asked for a second opinion,but
the genetic tests we ran confirm that
Emily has a serious presentation of
something called pelizaeus-merzbacher disease.
How do we cure it?
Well,there's medication to treat
the symptoms,but there is no cure.
So she'S...
not going to get better?
Ever?
The drugs can give her
five years,maybe more.
What? Five year--five?
I'm sorry.
I know this is difficult to hear.
And we will do everything that we can.
Wait,you said that this was genetic.
So one of us made her sick?
No,you can't think of it like that.
Because my sister,she's
trying to get pregnant.
I mean,could she have this,too?
We'll have to run some blood tests.
We'll see which
mutation you're carrying.
It's important not only for
your sister,but also for you,
if and when you should decide
you want other children.
No. Emily-- Emily is all we need.
Excuse me. I'm looking
for a dave walker.
He came in with vomiting
and severe dehydration.
He was released 15 minutes ago.
On whose orders?
You don't release my
patient without calling me.
Don't lecture me on medical etiquette.
The vitals were normal,we needed
the bays,and he wanted to leave.
Probably just had some 24-hour bug.
Well,it didn't look like a bug.
He was unconscious when I found him.
He saiit was something he ate,but he
tested negative for E.Coli,salmonella--
that still leaves about a hundred other
possibilities,none of which require hospital stays.
He was fine, Sam.
Besides,grandma said
she could handle it.
The same grandma who
couldn't call 9-1-1?
That's why you don't release
my patients without calling me.
Any word back about the little girl?
Yeah,but the test results
don't make any sense.
Sometimes they can be
hard to read. Let me see.
- This does not...
- no,no.
You see the...
this doesn't make any sense.
Which mutation did the
parents pass on to Emily?
None.
Well,how is that possible?
Because they're not her parents.
Emily is ours. She's my baby.
Uh, there's the chance
that this was human error--
the hospital nursery wristbands
fell off, got mixed up.
There is also the possibility that
someone may have done this on purpose.
Are--are you accusing us?
I mean, you think that we wanted this?
Right now, all you have to
do is take care of Emily,
and we'll find out what happened.
I'm telling you, there is
something wrong with this guy.
We tell him his daughter's
dying, he's cold as ice.
We tell him he's not the father,
he gets defensive right off the bat.
People react to terrible
news in different ways.
It's his child. Show some emotion.
Where did Beth give birth?
St. Ambrose.
Oh, perfect.
- Charlotte King's hospital.
- I'm going over there.
No, you--you need to stay here
and just calm down. We'll go.
Fine.
where are those nursery records?
There was no stolen baby reported-- not
in this hospital,not while I was chief.
Well,then two sets of parents
went home with the wrong babies.
I swear,do you all take some kind of
perverse pleasure in ruining my life?
Yeah,there are switched babies
out there,but this is about us.
This hospital has the
best nurses in the city.
Neonate spent a fortune on security.
Did st.Ambrose institute nap
time,or do I still have a staff?
Then why don't you show us the
records for the other babies
that were in the nursery the
time that Emily was there?
Will someone just br-- thank you.
There was only one other african-american
girl in the nursery at that time.
Who is it?
This hospital spent 124
years building its reputation.
I am not gonna ruin that
by chatting with you.
Can you just give us the name?
Not until I talk to our attorneys.
Blood pressure 125 over 84.
- That's normal.
- Yeah.
- I feel a lot better.
- Okay.
Maybe a little shaky.
What--what do you think it was?
Still not sure.
Just to be safe,why don't you
clean the kitchen top to bottom?
It's not the food that got him sick.
Ma,please.
Oh, Stevie. Close the door,honey.
I'll leave it open. Then the next time dad passes
out,no one's got to break a window to get in.
Hey, Stevie.
Is he okay?
Oh,he's just bullheaded,like his dad.
what are you gonna do?
And your mom?
We're doing real good,doc.
Things are good.
so what am I missing?
Well,in 90% of these cases,it comes
down to history and environment.
Oh,well,the environment's all messed up.
The dad's drinking,grandma's got way more
than she can handle,the kid's acting out.
That sounds a lot more
serious than a 24-hour flu.
see,that's why I'm worried.
They've got enough to deal with as is.
And if david's got something really
serious,I'm not sure how they hold it together.
- Hey,coop.
- Hey...
Ginger.
I didn't recognize you in...
I didn't recognize you.
Tell me that is not the
girl from last night.
Cooper's bringing 'em to work now?
Oh,my god. That's it.
He has just crossed the line.
Sam just hugged a stripper.
God,at least with Cooper,you
know what you have.
Okay,now let's all calm down.
Sam is not a dog. He never was.
Now there could be a totally
innocent explanation for this.
What--what--what,for
stripper hugging?
Give me one. Give me one.
Well...
like she's here to see the real dog.
Oh,would--would
you look at him?
He's all... "I'm a
doctor.My touch heals.
can I talk to you?
- I spoke to our attorneys.
- And?
Some days I really hate
the hippocratic oath.
Here.
Here's the file on the second
african-american baby in the hospital nursery.
You're just giving it
to us,just like that?
If you think I'm being
nice,read the name.
Oh,god.
What?
And my problem becomes your problem.
Melinda and Duncan Stinson.
You know them?
I got them pregnant.
what do you think of
your handiwork, Naomi?
oh,she is so cute.
And if you tell me I've got more
hormone's to take,I'm gonna scream.
Oh,no. No,no,no.
It's just,uh,we need to run
some blood tests on all of you.
What's going on?
so how are you holding up?
I'll be better when we
find out who did this?
All your nurses check out?
One moved a few days later,but
her record was impeccable.
Well,something happened in that nursery.
You don't know that.
That doesn't stop you from
tossing the blame my way.
I know that if one of my patients was in this much
pain,I would be busting my ass looking for answers.
Thank you.
I hadn't gotten my earful
of Oceanside arrogance today.
look at him.
How is that guy and the guy who
hired me a stripper the same person?
he's Cooper.
So this other couple...
their baby was born the same night?
That's right.
We're--we're running
blood tests on them now.
What if the other blood
tests come back positive?
This is the hard part.
according to California law...
you would...
say good-bye to Emily...
and you would welcome a
new child into your lives.
That's--that's ridiculous. Okay?
The blood tests are not
gonna come back positive
and I don't care what
our blood tests said-
- honey,honey-
- no.No.
I know Emily is my daughter,okay?
A mother can feel these things.
I don't love that other child.
I couldn't love another baby.
I love Emily.
Well,why don't we just wait for the
results of the blood test and go from there?
Emily's had a hard time,now she
has to adjust to a whole new family?
Well,the babies are young.
You know,adoptions take place
at this age all the time.
The kids are usually fine.
It's the parents I'm worried about.
They're the ones who grieve.
Greg O'Brien doesn't
seem to be grieving.
What is up with you and this case?
Your emotional attachment is huge.
You're one to lecture me about
unhealthy emotional attachments.
Okay,that was a nice deflection.
But unlike you,I am detaching.
You want to try it?
It's yours.
Light.
Why didn't Allan buy his own bike?
On our third anniversary,you
know,we took that trip to italy,
and he took me to the town where they made those
because even as a child he had--he'd wanted one.
So he saved up his money...
But then his dad split on his mom,
so he had to use his savings to
pay rent and to keep his mom afloat.
And he never got the bike.
What? What?
Take the bike. You love it.
Yeah,I loved it when I thought it
was a cool,sexy,"get me laid" bike,
not some sad, Allan-y
"cat's in the cradle" bike.
hey.
Is that stripper still in your office?
Entertainer not stripper,and yes.
And she's been in there all day? Why?
We're trying a few different techniques.
oh,yeah,I'm sure you are.
You know what?
Naomi does not need
ginger thrown in her face.
Naomi is a big girl. She can handle it.
She doesn't have to.
That's why I'm here.
Pete,is it supposed to feel tingly?
"Pete,is it supposed to
feel..." you know what?
Go.Go
do--
take care of your poor little
stripper girl and her "tingly".
Entertainer,and why
are you so angry at me?
- You--I-
- Cooper's the one that set this--
you know,I am trying to
take care of my friend.
And Cooper is bad,but you're worse.
And you know why? Because
you're slippery.Yeah.
You walk around pretending to be all
soulful,but you don't take the heat.
You just do whatever you
want to do and you evade.
Evade,evade,evade.
Do you need me to kiss you again?
No!
Okay.
You're back.
Nurses' schedules...
perinatal testing,personnel files.
What'd you find?
Not a damn thing.
I have been through every one
of these backwards and forwards.
You're so sure my hospital ruined these
people's lives,then help me prove it.
please! Someone hurry!
Help me!
Please!
Sam! Sam,front.
Hey! Hey! Help!
- Please,help me!
- Yeah,ma'am,it's all right.
- Sam!
- Stevie,what's going on?
Whatever my dad had...
I got it worse.
I got home., Grandma made dad and
me some sandwiches,then...pukeville.
Mrs.Walker,what did i tell
you about that kitchen?
Well,it was just a sandwich.
That could've killed him.
where is your father?
At--at
work.
I didn't want to bother him with this.
Mrs.Walker,I understand you
mean well for your family,
but something you are
doing is making them sick.
This is a family matter,doctor.
It doesn't concern you.
Hey, Dell,can you hand carry Stevie
Walker's blood to the lab for me?
Put a rush on it.
Have them screen for ingestible poisons.
Hey. I just got the test
back from the Stinsons.
The O'Brien baby is their babY.
And the Stinson baby
belongs to the O'Briens.
Yep.
How do you tell someone that their
baby was switched with another baby?
Damn it.
well,that was the hardest
thing I've ever done.
You did everything right.
And dad doesn't shed a tear.
How's it going with Naomi?
Well,you know,so far,so--
do you know what you
put my wife through,
what you put us through?
And now you tell us that this--this
other baby who we've never met is sick!
We did everything you asked us to do.
I know how hard you two
worked to get pregnant.
Let down after let down,the--the
miscarriages,the hormones...
you how many shots I
had to stick in her?
She could hardly move
she was so bruised.
I-I wish there was
something I could do.
Yeah,there is something you can do.
You can start by explaining how you--
how you can live with yourself--
taking our money and
promising us a healthy baby.
Duncan,I never promised you perfection.
I promised you a child.
My retirement,vacation pay--
our future!
we spent it all so we
could have our little girl!
Duncan,please.
I want my money back.
I want my damn money back!
your husband...
he has a right to be angry.
So do you.
I could just take Sarah and go.
We could just go away.
No one would find us.
Except you won't.
Because Emily is your daughter.
And she is sick.
And a mother never
leaves her child behind.
Not a strong mother.
No. No.
This isn't happening.
I'm not gonna do it.
come on,baby.
Hey.
Stevie Walker's lab results.
Coprine?
From the mushroom?
Ink cap mushrooms contain coprine.
It's like a natural form of antabuse.
When you ingest the mushroom,then
if you drink alcohol you get really--
really,really sick.
So someone's poisoning Stevie?
any luck?
Well,I think we know
when the switch happened.
We have baby Emily's hospital record
and baby Sarah's hospital records,
and then on day two,they switched.
Emily becomes Sarah
and Sarah becomes Emily?
What about this nurse,left town?
No,she was in the E.R. Of my hospital,
laid out with the flu hooked
up to an I.V.All night.
So we're back to square one?
My patient is being poisoned
by his own dear,sweet mother.
She's dosing him with ink cap mushrooms.
Which means he's drinking--
boom,on the floor.
- Baby switch.
- Poisoning?
For real?
Baby--
hi. You are not a
member of this practice.
So you have to go ahead and unhear that.
I thought I had a problem.
Yeah,well,maybe we can help you with
yours since we're not getting anywhere.
I-I don't know.
I-I gotta stop the mother
from hurting her son.
Now she's also poisoning her grandson.
But I can't send her to jail,can I?
How could a parent do that to a child?
Let me see the visitor's log again.
Yeah.
The first two days,one
person was there constantly.
A parent...
did that to a child.
What you're doing is a crime.
You can't go around poisoning people.
No,I only meant it for David.
I didn't know Stevie was drinking.
So it's okay to poison your own son?
Well,every time he takes
a drink,he pays for it.
That's how you teach my David a lesson.
You have to stop doing this,now.
No.
My family,we're weak
when it comes to this.
David's not weak.
He's an alcoholic.
And some old world remedy will not
guarantee that he'll stop drinking.
Now I'm a doctor,and
I'm telling you--
what? You...
you're like all the other doctors.
Oh,you make him go to a 12-step group,
but do you make him stop drinking?
No. So I did.
Please.
You can't tell David.
This will work.
As David's doctor,I can't let it happen.
I'm sorry.
Then you might as well have me arrested.
Because I don't know how long I've got,
and my family means everything.
If I don't protect them,who will?
from birth your baby-- your biological baby--
well,it was difficult.
She had a neurological problem.
She did?
Your c-section caused
severe post-labor pain,
so you were sedated for
most of the first two days.
You wouldn't have been
aware of how serious it was.
But you were,Mr. Stinson.
You were in the nursery 24/7.
And then when your daughter was 2 days
old,she seized while you were holding her.
What are you saying?
What-- what are you saying? I--
She's saying that the next time you were in the
nursery alone is when those babies were switched.
you were the only one there.
It would've been easy enough to switch
off your baby's security bracelet
because she was so small.
No,I'm not gonna stand for this.
If I were that
baby's father--
Mr. Stinson,people's lives have been
altered-- your child's life.
You were supposed to take care of
her,and instead you switched her
because she was sick.
Mr. Stinson,I-I think this is your
opportunity to explain to us--
no,no,no,you explain.
You explain!
3 years and--and $250,000 and
all my wife's hopes and dreams...
oh,my god.
Melinda,th-this other family,they
can have more kids,healthy kids.
You see?
Duncan...
wait,this isn't--
I'm not a--
Melinda,honey...
How could you give my
baby to somebody else?
How could you?
What switch is in your brain and makes
it okay for you to steal a child?
Adults are there to protect children.
We're supposed to keep them from harm.
You're angry at yourself.
What?
I'm talking about Duncan
Stinson,what he did.
I'm angry about that.
Right. Before that,it was greg O'Brien.
But it's really about you.
Don't...
do the shrink thing, Violet.
You can't blame yourself for not
being able to make her better, Cooper.
She's just a baby.
Dave,we're here because you
have a problem with alcohol.
A problem?
no.
- Maybe I have a glass of wine or a beer--
- Dave.
Once,twice a week,maybe I
drink more than I should.
We need to get you into
a treatment program.
why?
Because I like beer?
Come on.
I don't need treatment.
Dave.
Sorry.
All right,well,you should know that I
figured out why you've been getting sick.
Uh,you've developed an
allergy...to alcohol.
what? That's not possible.
Well,it's rare.
Yeah,it's--it's
really rare.
And it probably runs in the family.
So,I mean,you've seen what
happens when you drink.
That's gonna happen every single time.
So I...
I have to stop drinking?
Yeah,you do.
That's my diagnosis.
Now if you continue to get sick,
then I'm going to have to consider
that it's something much more serious.
Gloria,you're gonna help Dave make
sure that never happens,not even once?
Oh,yes,yes.
He--well,he--
he's learned his lesson.
come in.
Would you like to sit down?
I think it might be helpful for
us to talk about what happened.
Your husband...
is not my husband anymore.
that other little girl...
your daughter.
She's so sick that she could die?
Yes.
Before she's 5 years old?
Melinda...
this is Emily.
This is mama.
This is Emily.
I don't,um...this is a mistake.
I can't-- I-I thought it would feel like--
listen,listen,listen,
it is natural that you would
feel like a stranger at first.
It'll get better.
She's,uh,she's so small.
The condition she has,it's
caused a failure to thrive.
She's so beautiful.
I know.
I sing her to sleep.
Sarah likes...
it's gonna sound stupid,but,uh,I
sing madonna songs to her
'cause they're the only
ones I know all the words to.
But they work.
She goes to sleep so easy.
Emily screams...
every two hours.
But if I...
put her on my chest,the
sound of my heartbeat...
your heartbeat...
it calms her.
Sarah is beautiful,too.
- look at her
- no,I can'T.
I...I can'T.
you have to.
She's yours.
A mother never leaves her child behind.
Hi.
Hi,Sarah.
I thought...
I couldn't watch her die.
And now I can'T...
let her go.
I'll get you a tissue.
I'm fine.
It's okay. It'S...
it's been a big day.
Montgomery...
I'm chief to over 200 physicians.
you call this a big day?
This place is making you soft.
god...
I am a wreck.
Long day.
We just sent a man to jail for trying
to get rid of his own kid,but...
your day sounds really hard.
I didn't know.
No,of course not.
You spent the entire day dealing with the
perils of aromatherapy and,uh,your stripper.
I know you don't believe
me,but I like my women real...
real skin...
real breasts...
real lines arountheir eyes that mean
they've really lived and had pain.
You show me that woman...
and I'm interested.
And...not in a slippery way.
And, Addison...
I think it's great that
you try to care of Naomi.
But...
who takes care of you?
No Ginger.
She can't be her. Ginger cannot be her.
Okay...you're gonna have to translate from
freaked-out language to normal-people language.
The first woman you date
after me has to be...
she has to--look,she cannot be some
stripper with clear platform shoes and--
and a suspicious skin condition.
Naomi,eventually I'm
going to start dating.
I know that.
And when that happens,you do not
get to have a say in who I date.
I know that.
So...
so fine,date.
But it can't be Ginger.
And we're back to crazy.
Hey,you know what? I'm a catch.
I-I do "the new york times'" crossword
puzzle in pen,I eat vegetables,
I have a very good sense of humor,and I
don't do pilates 'cause I think it's fun.
I mean,have you seen me?
If you date Ginger after you're with
me,if she is what you are choosing,
if--if your big dream is
rashy-skinned strippers,then what...
- what were you--
- what was I doing with you?
Yeah,you know what?
Forget it.
The next girl I date will be amazing.
She will be beautiful,she will be
intelligent,and she will be rash free.
She'll be better than me?
She will be way better than you.
Okay?
Okay.
That's sweet. Thank you.
Vye,open up.
I think I might need
to borrow some tools.
The--the frame's
still in one piece.
The wheels came off and the chain,
but I-I think I might need
a-a blowtorch or a hacksaw.
Do you have a hacksaw?
Is this helping?
Yeah. Yeah,actually.
It's very therapeutic.
Oh,damn it. I am so full of crap.
I went over to Allan's with the bike.
But he'd already gotten one...from Cami.
Yes,he told her the bike story.
It took him two years to
tell me the bike story.
They've been together,what,a day?
And he told her the bike story.
- I'm an idiot.
- No,you're not.
No,I am. I am. I am.
He's married. It's over.
I am an idiot.
Violet,you are not.
You're just--you're,uh,you're
just honest.
That's your fatal flaw.
It's my favorite thing about you.
All right.
Come here.
You want to help me run
the bike over with my car?
Absolutely.
look at him,st sitting up
there with that dumb little dog.
Well,if you want,we could...
I mean,you want to go and say hi or...
or you could just look a little longer.
Yeah,the last one.
Okay.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-ﬂ«»‚»‚ ÷• øµ∞∏‚
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Private Practice
Season 01 Episode 02