 Hey.
What?
You kissed me,and then you walked away.
Messes with your head,huh?
So it was a revenge kiss.
No,no,not intentionally,but then,uh,watching
you get all swirly since then?
It is kind of gratifying.
I think we should stop kissing.
I mean,come on.
What are we,12?
No,we definitely are not.
Which is why.
I. do not want to be just another
notch in your acupuncture table.
I want more.
What do you say we just see how it goes.
tonight?
I can work with at.
we.
-were just talking about a case.
-Uh,she needed a consult on the.
locked in the,uh,dell vault,all right?
Your patients are here.
we're in the dell vault.
Locked in the dell vault.
who keeps sticking bananas
in the refrigerator?
I,um,that. that would be me.
Bananas need the climate of the tropical equator.
You never stick bananas in the refrigerator.
Susan mccullough is on her way in.
Hey,how'd she sound?
I believe her exact words were,"you
guys better not screw this up.
" Blocking the toaster. Hello.
Wow,okay. That toast
needs to happen right now.
Somebody really needs to get.
-don't say it.
-I wasn't.
I wasn't going to say "laid.
" so we're inducing susan today,right?
Yes. It is very important to her
that we follow her labor plan.
That means pete's stress-reduction
techniques,the birthing tub.
Honestly,not a big fan of the tub.
There are fluids in there.
blood,uterine
tissue,sometimes fecal matter.
Okay,you made me think about it.
Well,you know,I mean they're just big
and wet and difficult to work with.
I mean,the's a reason they don't
use those things in hospitals.
She's my patient,and we're
gonna do it the way she wants.
Well,I'm not really comfortable
being a,uh,birth coach.
That's not what I do.
Really? Because.
addison,susan was widowed
few months into her pregnancy.
Her husband jason was a
cop. He was killed on duty.
Oh,that's.
she's had panic attacks,and that
would be a problem during a birth.
She doesn't have any other
family,so she's on her own here.
I promised her we'd take care of her.
Okay.
Okay,I'llave dell go ahead
and prepare the bathtub.
yeah.
Hey,Dr. Bennett. It's sara hill.
Hey,sara. How you doing?
Is there any chance you
could do a house call now?
I kind of hurt my leg.
I'm afraid it might
get worse,a lot worse.
Okay,I guess I can run over
there and check you out.
The address is 5600
alverson. And can you hurry?
So you moved away from the marina,huh?
alverson. hello?
Okay,uh,I'm gonna need the lights dimmed,and
we can put the birthing ball right here.
Where's the music I
asked for? I need the cd.
Oh,I have it. Why don't you just relax?
We'll get everything taken care of.
Oh,I know. We've got a
plan,and we're following it.
But as we discussed,not
everything is under our control.
Babies often have plans of their own.
I'm prepared for that,too. I
wrote down all the contingencies.
Dr. Montgomery,it's baby day.
Hi,susan. Uh,as soon as pete does his
relaxation therapy,then I will be back to.
to administer the pitocin after
you remove the prostaglandin insert.
That's exactly right.
Okay. So let's do this.
Cooper!
Hey,malcolm,you got a game today?
I caught a fly in the toilet!
You did? No way.
Really? good work.
Patrick,can you keep them kind of.
doc,spider web,3:00.
-How you holdin' up?
-Hangin' in.
Uh,her due date is right around the
corner,and it's time to stop by for a checkup.
You're having a girl.
It's about time. I'm so excited.
Danny,give mal back his mit.
I'll show you back.
All right,team. Let's go. Come on.
Okay,the baby's heartbeat looks good.
Good.
This is my fourth baby,so i
should know the drill by now.
Come on,mom,hurry up.
I gotta go to the game.
Todd,todd,todd,honey,not in here.
Just a minute,and then we'll go.
Ya ashley,you may be here
longer than you think.
You're in labor.
You're having this baby now.
you leaving?
Yeah,sara hill wants me to
drop by her place,a leg injury.
Uh,what about your
patients on the books?
I moved some things
around. I like getting air.
I know going off schedule is
something that's hard for you to grasp.
I can grasp it just fine,thank you.
-Oh,really?
-Really.
Go. Enjoy.
-Where's he going?
-House call.
Whatever.
Hey,you need to do something about pete.
Does he know what he's
doing with addison?
What is he doing with addison?
Oh,no. Did they?
It's imminent.
So none of my business.
All right. It's none
of my business either.
Except pete already proved
he shouldn't date at work.
M-maybe addison decided
to enjoy herself.
Men do it all the time.
Right,that's. that's fine.
It's empowering for women,actually.
casu sex. It can be,as long
as the boundaries are clear.
And I'm very,very good
with boundaries,aren't I?
Not really,no.
But you're looking right through me,so I'm
guessing you're not hearing a word I'm saying. So.
5600 alverson.
This can't be right.
Sara.
ClOSED CERRADO
It's him.
Thanks for coming.
Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
Uh,are you okay? Your leg.
I-I didn't call you here for
me. I-I called you here for him.
sara,what's going on?
it's my leg.
What happened to you?
She shot me.
She. you shot him?
Not her,me.
I shot him.
Okay.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-Âí¿ËË¹
Private
Practice  Season 1 Episode 7
fix him. You're a doctor,right?
She said you were a
doctor. You gotta fix him.
Is,uh,is everybody else okay?
Everyone else is fine! Except for her.
She's crazy! She shot me.
It was an accident. I'm
sorry. I said I was sorry.
Okay,everybody,let's be calm.
-Sara?
-She wanted a doctor.
You're the only one I know that
makes house calls,so I called you.
After you called the police?
She didn't want the police.
Of course not,because she's crazy!
hi,I'm,uh,officer kevin nelson. I'm
here for susan mccullough's delivery.
Is she expecting you?
No,I'm just here,uh,to support susan.
She said she didn't want anybody,but I wanted to
come down in case,uh,uh,uh,she changed her mind.
-I'll let her know.
-Thank you.
You waiting to see a doctor?
No,I'm just here to support a
friend. I'm a police officer.
Kevin nelson. Officer kevin neon.
Addison montgomery.
Doctor. addison montgomery.
Nice to meet you,doctor.
Okay.
uh,ms. Mccullough,there's an
officer kevin nelson hereor you.
Are you serious?
he was jason's parer.
Well,that's nice of him to
come check on you,isn't it?
It is,but.
he's gonna get emotional,turn
this into a memorial for jason.
I don't want that. Jason
wouldn't have wanted that.
This should be about the baby.
Can you just tell him I'm fine?
He can go back to work.
you okay?
yeah. I just.
feel a little anxious.
He shouldn't be here.
I didn't want to think about it.
God.
Remember the visualizations we
worked on? Focus on those images.
Okay?
We're following the plan.
Everything's right on schedule.
I'm fine.
I'm totally fine.
When you have sex.
I mean,when there's no romantic
entanglement,which is never.
yes,thank you.
I just wanted an apple,but now get to talk
about the fact that I'm an emotional dwarf?
No,that's not what I'm talking about.
Is it about that I said that you needed
to get laid,which i didn't say. verbally?
No,listen,listen,I've been.
I've been thinking about this.
When you do it,it's just
no-nonsense,uncomplicated sex,right?
Just simple,stress-reducing fun.
That's the idea.
What,are you asking me
to have sex with you?
Yeah. Why not?
You and me. friends
with benefits,tonight.
I mean,you're right,you're right.
I am. I'm stressed out,and I just.
I just need some. touch.
and you're perfect because unemotional
sex is the only kind you have.
And.
What time should I come over?
-Really?
-Really.
Oh,hey,cooper,can you take
sam's 11:30? I gotta help with.
I'm getting laid tonight.
Congratulations. What's her screen name?
No.
Me and violet.
What?
Friends with benefits. her idea.
No strings,no expectations,no downside.
You really think that's smart?
Glass house,stone thrower.
You remember the last time you
dated a doctor in this practice?
-Oh,that was fun for everybody.
-Oh,I don't. that was one.
and now you and addison
have this whole weird thing.
I can make it work with addison.
Based on what? "Oh,addison,you
moved down here 'cause I kissed you.
" "Oh,pete,you fake
doctor. Your touch heals.
" You've been friends
with violet for years.
U really think things are gonna be
the same after you've seen her naked?
No,I think things are gonna be better
because I will have seen her naked.
I'm getting laid
ashley,this is Dr. Bennett.
Things are a little busy here today,so
she's gonna be monitoring your case.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Maybe mommy would like some time alone?
Uh,hi. We can have someone watch your kids
if you want to stay here with your wife.
Oh,no,I get queasy during these things.
Trust me,he'll be
more trouble than good.
Can you take the boys to the lobby?
What am I supposed to do with 'em?
Well,I don't know,honey.
Just occupy 'em.
-Come on,guys.
-Bye,sweeties.
Uh,naomi,addison,we have a situation.
I-I told them that susan said
no,but,uh,then a bunch more of 'em showed up.
uh,what's going on?
I know susan doesn't
want anybody in there,
but she's part of our family,and we're
not gonna leave one of our own alone.
Guys coming off shift,uh,they want
to they want to be here for her.
Now I'm not comfortable with
this whole birthing myself,
but keith here,he's got two kids,another
one on the way,so he's good to go in.
I.
I don't think susan is
going to change her mind.
But susan. she's. she's just a kid.
Yeah,but she. she needs
to do this her own way.
All right. Well,uh,we'll wait here.
We're staying.
How do you feel?
How do you think I feel?
I feel like I got shot.
we're closed.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about that.
It's,uh,it's been awhile since I've
had to deal with a-a bullet wound.
He's more of a mind-body doctor.
Dr. Feelgood?
Uh,yeah. Hi. Hello.
Mind-body? Uh.
I need a doctor.
Do you even know what you're doing?
Yeah,I know exactly what I'm doing.
All right,it's a good
color. I feel a strong pulse.
I need a doctor!
I am a doctor.
All right,it looks like the
bullet missed the artery.
Probably just nicked
the muscle. He's lucky.
I need a doctor for me.
My water just broke.
What's taking so long?
Okay,okay. All right,just take this,put
it there,and apply pressure,okay?
Wait,wait,you're helping her?
Will you shut up? It's a flesh wound.
You're gonna be fine.
Okay,ma'am,you're in labor.
All right,we really should
try to get you to a hospital.
-No.
-ok ok
Well,then let me
just call 9-1-1.
No,no
cops,no 9-1-1.
You're delivering this
baby,and you're doing it now!
Okay.
Okay,if you don't mind,I'm
just gonna make one quick call.
I said no cops.
Don't try anything. I said no cops!
I just want to call a colleague so that
I can give you the help that you need.
Please.
You dial,and you hande the phone,okay?
Okay,I'm dialing. See?
all right.
Don't try and take the
gun. That's how I got shot.
-Okay.
Hey,naomi,it's sam.
Uh,I need your help.
I'm about to,uh,deliver a baby.
I thought you were on a house call.
I am. Well,I was.
But then I ran into a really
nice lady,and she is in labor.
Uh,h-hold on,sam.
Hey,dell,I need you to monitor
ashley minnehan's contractions,
and you tell me the second
she's dilated to 4 centimeters.
Really? A-a birth?
You. you bring me in as
soon as she's ready to go.
Okay? Thanks,yeah.
Understand?
All right,now,sam,wait,where are you?
Okay,I really don't have the time to talk
right now,so if we could just get to it?
O-okay,fine. Um,is she fully dilated?
Uh,just a minute.
I'm here to monitor your contractions.
All right.
Uh,any questions or concerns?
Anything I can do to help?
Oh,no,no. I've. I've
done three of these.
I just say a little prayer and go,and you just sit
there and catch the baby like it's a football,okay?
can I just say,it's a good thing that
pete is getting me now,because I am hot.
I am on fuego.
This place is crawling with cops.
And that cute one over
there,he's totally.
what?
Sam just called. He's delivering a baby.
He is? What's with all the births today?
It's like babypaloozA.
God,how does he get
himself into these things?
I-I should just mind my own
business,right? About sam?
Yeah,about sam,and about
you on fuego and pete.
You all. you all just.
leap.
And you are a thinker.
So.
what do you think.
about me and pete?
Come on,nai.
you're my friend.
Okay. Fine.
You said you want
change and you pick pete?
What,a cute doctor boy with
nice eyes? That's not change.
That's your M.O. You're just.
you're rushing into something new.
I'm not. I'M.
making a decision,uh,to take a
chance on something that feels right.
Because you're afraid to be alone.
So what if I am? Surprise,naomi.
I'm susceptible to the human condition.
I mean,look,there are other men.
I mean,there are men in uniform that
I can not be alone with right now.
I did not pick pete because
I'm desperate and lonely.
Pete is my choice.
You asked.
Are you okay?
The baby's coming now.
What? No,um.
are you sure?
It's coming.
U have to catch the baby.
Okay.
No,no,I-I can't do this.
I have to call naomi.
Now would be a good time!
naomi!
Susan,your contractions
are five minutes apart. So.
it won't be too much longer.
I'm ready.
You really are,susan. You
are totally prepared for this.
Oh,god.
Today. My son's birthday is today.
what are you doing?
Timing your contractions.
You been having pain long?
Yeah,since I got up this morning.
What were you thinking?
I was thinking that I need to rob a convenience store because I have
no money for diapers or food or to put a roof over my baby's head!
-Okay,ma'am.
-that's not a reason.
Normal people don't
hold up stores,kelly.
Kelly?
So you two didn't just
meet today,did you?
That's my baby you're delivering.
okay,okay,okay.
dell.
it just. it just happened.
I-I-I
swear.
It was the fastest
delivery I've ever seen.
Okay,it's all right. All right,dell.
Okay,first what we're gonna do is
we're gonna cut the umbilical cord.
Yeah. All right,see?
Right here. You see?
-About a half an inch.
-You got it?
There we go. Yeah.
Keep the baby low for me.
There you go. All right.
there you go.
-How is she?
-oh,she's great.
She's great. She's,um,oh!
She's. she's a boy.
congratulations. It's a. it's a boy.
No!
You shove that boy back up
there and pull out a girl!
 one girl.
Is that too much to ask?
Well,uh,your. your ultrasound
was quite a while ago
,and,uh,misinterpretations can
happen that early on in the pregnancy.
I bought a little pink dress with some
little pink shoes for a little pink girl.
And I'm not leaving
until I get some pinkness!
all right,kelly,I need you
to take slow,deep breaths.
Babies take money,damon.
What,you think I wasn't gonna
turn you into the police?
What,you think I was just gonna let you rob
the place where I work and not turn you in?
You owe me.
you're crazy!
I'm not crazy. I'm hormonal.
Tell him I'm hormonal.
Uh,I think that maybe there's
a new word for what you are.
I couldn't raise this baby on my own.
You wouldn't give me any money,so
I had to come and take it.
You left me with nothing.
Why do you think I took
this job in the first place?
I told you,I'm gonna
take care of this baby.
But you left me.
Yes. I left you.
But I won't leave our baby. Let me help.
I have.
I have to just say,it sounds
like damon's an okay guy.
So,you know,maybe you should let.
stay back! Stay back!
Okay,everybody,stoP.
just stop.
We are going to listen
to the lady with the gun.
I can't take it.
Does everybody understand?
keep taking those
long,slow,deep breaths,okay?
there we go.
Ashley minnehan will not bond with
this baby. She won't even look at him.
She was expecting a girl.
She's hormonal,so she's at
risk for postpartum depression.
-Can you talk to her?
-Sure.
Let me just make sure
susan's ready for me to go.
Okay.
-My place,8:00.
-Done.
I can't raise four boys on my own.
Well,have you,uh. you have your husband.
He can help.
Oh,yeah,sure. Yesterday he taught the
boys how to burp the national anthem.
Not the right kind of help.
I'm the only one who puts batteries in the smoke alarm,the
one who puts the cover on the swimming pool at night.
Have you tried talking to patrick?
Oh,he says I'm just being silly
because nothing bad ever happens.
But that's only because I make
sure nothing bad ever happens.
Ashley. you are a great mom.
the boys likhim better than
me because he plays with them.
I just wanted one girl
so she could be mine.
And then I wouldn't care so much
about having to do it all myself.
Well,maybe you have
another boy for a reason.
Maybe it's because you're a great mom,and
you're going to raise your boys to be good men.
And the world needs good men.
I want a girl.
I've been kind of a pain in the ass.
No,you haven'T.
Yes,I have. all my rules.
but things work out better when I
stay focused,don't let my mind wander.
You have nothing to apologize for.
you can't really. I mean.
there's no plan for
doing this alone,is there?
Look,there's a roomful of jason's
friends from the force here for you.
You could bring someone in.
They don't get how lonely
it is since he died.
Probably not.
I lost my wife a while ago.
I'm sorry.
It gets better.
Does it really get better?
Or do you just bury it deeper?
I don't know.
Maybe it depends on how you left things.
They were good.
He was so excited about this baby.
Hold on to that.
Oh,here comes another one.
Stand up?
Okay.
-You're doing good.
-Breathe.
that's it.
That's it. That's good.
Just like that,kelly.
Oh,god.
Uh,you may be fully
dilated. Here you go.
Is the baby okay?
Please make it stop.
Make it stop,Dr. Phil.
Well,not. it's not phil.
It's feel,like "feel good.
" Okay,never mind.
I want an epidural. Oh,please.
Epi. yeah,well,we're in
a convenience store so.
oh,god.
She's in pain. Do something.
all right,all right. Kelly,listen to me.
your mind is a very
powerful healing tool.
So if you can relax your mind,you'll
be able to relax your body.
All right? You understand what I'm
saying? So try to relax your mind.
I just wanted a home to raise my baby in,and now I've
ruined everything,and you're telling me to relax my mind!
Okay,good.
You're ready to start pushing.
Nice and easy.
I dropped it.
I dropped the list.
Well,it's all right. We know what to do.
No,I. you know,I should've laminated
it. Why didn't I think of that?
We don't need it,susan.
I need it. I need to get
outta here. I need it.
Whoa,whoa,susan,stay where you are.
Just grab on to the
handles if you need support.
Try to relax. Relax.
No,I can'T.
-I can't push.
-Yes,you can.
Susan,the baby's coming.
No,something's wrong. I can feel it.
Nothing is wrong,susan.
You're doing great.
Where the hell is jason?
-You're in control.
-No!
Just stay with it.
He's supposed to be here! He's.
where is he?
okay,susan.
Susan,this little baby is
ready to come right now.
We are ready,just like you planned.
No,no. He's.
Oh,my god.
-Try to breathe.
-My jason.
my.
oh,he's dead.
Oh,he's dead!
He's dead.
He's really dead.
Okay,susan,susan,when you hyperventilate,you
lower the baby's heart rate.
All right,if we don't start pushing right
now,there's a chance you will lose the baby.
Do you understand?
I can'T. I can'T.
I didn't want to be alone.
Oh,this wasn't my choice.
No! I chose jason!
I didn't want this.
Susan,honey,listen to me.
You're not alone.
Okay? I am right here with you.
Okay?
Now.
you're not alone,and we're gonna push.
Keep breathing.
Push.
good girl. Good,good.
Good. Good.
You're dng great.
Now let's bring your son out here,okay?
All right. Ready.
oh,god.
Please,please,please,please,please.
Oh,god.
-I can help.
-You stay back.
You want to kill me,then kill me.
No,no,no,no,no,no.
We don't have to go there.
I'm not gonna leave our baby.
Hey,hey,hey,man. S-sit down,sit down.
Kelly.
I got news for you.
You tried to rob a
convenience store today.
When this is all done,you're
gonna have to answer to the cops.
And they're probably gonna try
and take your baby away from you.
But I think that,uh,that
maybe you're lucky because.
your baby's father,he really
wants to take care of your child.
No,he left me.
Okay,if you want what's best for
your baby,you gotta put down that gun.
I can'T. You'll call the cops.
I'm not gonna call the cops.
You're gonna have to trust me.
Can you trust me?
All right,then put down the gun.
okay,now,uh,let's get this baby out.
-You didn't call the cops.
-Nope.
I didn't call the cops.
All right.
time to see my new boy?
How awesome is that?
Another little dude.
He's. he's with the nurse
right now,getting cleaned up.
Is something wrong?
You need to grow up.
I'm sorry?
-You don't.
-patrick,he,uh,he's right.
Um,you need to help
out around the house.
I help. I hang with the boys.
Upside down,out windows.
that's not any help.
Honey.
Ashley really needs you to not
play so much,do more parenting.
You know what? You need to grow up,too.
Me?
What did I do?
You knew going in that the odds
of having a girl were 50-50.
You decided to populate,and
that boy is yours.
You get what you get,and
you don't get upset.
Or,if you'd like,I can introduce you to one of the
many families I treat who can't even have a child.
All right?
All right.
I'm sorry.
Are you two ready to see that
beautiful baby boy I delivered?
We're ready.
That's good. That's real good,kelly.
That'S.
what? What is it?
Uh,okay. You just hang tight,kelly.
Hang tight. You're doing real good.
yeah,naomi. There's a problem.
The head is out,but the
baby's not delivering.
That's shoulder dystocia.
Sam,you're gonna have to release that
shoulder quickly,or she's gonna lose the baby.
You're gonna need forceps,you're gonna
need anesthetic,and you need to make sure.
no,no,no. I don't have any
equipment,o anesthetics.
I don't. I don't. I don't have anything.
Sam,where are you?
Please don't ask questions. Ju
tell me how to fix this,fast.
Okay,okay,sam.
You need to reach in and you need to
rotate the baby's shoulder counterclockwise.
Right now she's probably.
okay,that's all I got
time for. I gotta go.
okay,listen,listen,listen to me.
I'm gonna have to
rotate this baby myself.
You're gonna what?
All right,now we have to do this now.
I'm gonna count to three,and
then I'm gonna reach in.
All right,now this is gonna hurt.
-No,no,no,I can'T.
-Get behind her. Hold up her legs.
-No,I can'T. I can'T.
-Yes,you can. Yes,you can.
Stay with me.
All right?
You got this. Come on.
Okay,okay. All right,here
we go. You ready?
Okay,come on.
almost there,susan. Almost there.
We're right here.
You're so close. Come on.
okay,okay. I almost got it.
Oh,my god. Oh,my god!
Okay,here we go. Here we go. I got it.
Alright. Now the baby's in position.
All right,go on and push now.
God,it hurts. It hurts.
You can do it. Take my hand.
Come on. Here we go. We can do this.
Here we go,here we go.
one more big push,susan.
Push,push. Come on.
This is final stretch.
It's the last one. Come on. Come on.
One more big push,and
you'll have a new son.
Come on. Please.
Don't give up on me now,kelly.
Push.
Push. Push it out now.
-Okay,okay,okay.
-Ready?
Meet the newest addition to station 422.
jason mccullough jr.
8 pounds,10 ounces.
is she okay?
Yeah,she looks good.
Congratulations.
get the head,man.
okay. Um.
I gotta make this call.
To the cops?
Yeah,to the cops.
They're gonna come and. and get you and.
okay.
Did officer nelson see him,the guys?
Yeah,they saw him.
Good,good.
You did great.
Thank you.
for everything.
His face is all squished.
Squished face!
Hey,get off your mom.
Give her a break,now.
so.
what time tonight?
Well,my place,8.
Great. It's a date at 8.
It's not a date,Dr. Seuss.
it's sex.
your help with susan,it.
it means a lot to me.
Well,to all of us.
Oh,I'm. I'm glad to help.
Well,thank you,Dr. Montgomery.
Addison.
Addison,I was wondering if you would be
interested in having a drink with me tonight.
I,uh.
that's,um.
very nice of you.
I,uh,already have plans.
maybe another time.
But,uh,thank you again.
Thank you.
I'm gonna take my clothes off now.
I love that family. Don't you?
Take your clothes off,cooper.
I want a big family like that.
whole bunch of kids,little
rug rats,you know?
I want to be a dad. I want.
-I want to be a.
-I'm trying to have sex here.
I don't really want to talk
about kids or big families.
Sorry.
Oh,you're.
You're naked.
Yeah,it makes the sex easier.
It's just. I've never seen you naked.
In the office,you always
have your clothes on.
Well,yeah. I-I try
to be a professional.
Rip off the band-aid,coop. I did.
Yeah,I can'T.
Y-you have to. You've
already seen me naked.
I know,and you're.
beautiful.
I'm sorry. I th-thought I could,but.
you can't reject me.
You have low standards.
You have no standards.
-It's different,violet.
-No,it's not different.
I-I am offering you
uncomplicated,unemotional sex.
No! I. you're not some
random girl from the internet.
With you,it doesn't mean
nothing. It never will.
all right. Get out.
oh,damn it.
hi.
Okay. Hi,uh,cooper.
Uh,I came to talk to
sam. He wasn't home.
I just thought. I saw you through
the window,that you were alone.
,It's. it's fine. Come in.
Pete said you had a date.
Yeah,we do. We did.
an hour ago,we did.
oh,damn it.
He stood me up.
He actually.
stood me up.
If it helps,I was
colossally stupid today.
I mean colossally. with violet.
Friends with benefits. she wanted us to.
you know,uh,together.
-And?
-I couldn'T.
No benefits.
I just. couldn't mess with it.
Stupid.
I think I win that award today.
No,I am the most stupidest.
Stupider.
Or more stupid.
Stupidiest.
Let's call it a tie.
Would you like to order some
pizza and get really fat with me?
Yes,please.
cooper,not now.
I can'T.
pete.
Sorry it's so late.
What's wrong?
When she died,anna
and i had been trying.
to have a baby?
Yeah.
You're here late.
Oh,my god. Sam,are you
all right? What happened?
Uh,she had a healthy
baby girl,thanks to you.
I don't understand. How do you.
how do you get those
bruises delivering a baby?
Oh,yeah. The mom.
she hit me.
She hit you?
-With her gun.
-With her what?
It was sort of a. like
a hostage situation.
I didn't mention that to you on the phon
no,sam,no.You did not mention
that to me on the phone.
I,uh,didn't want you to worry.
God,sam,you could've been hurt.
You.
-you could've.
-I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
Everything is not fine,sam.
Everything is very,very not fine.
You got beaten up by a pregnant lady.
this is what happens when you
do things without thinking.
-I. naomi,I.
-I am sick of it.
I am so sick and tired of being the
only person in this practice who thinks.
who thinks and thinks and.
Private
Practice  Season 1 Episode 7
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync:YTET-Âí¿ËË¹
Proudly Presents