Surfing?
You're into surfing now?
You should see her room.
She's got surf posters everywhere.
As soon as my heart is better,
I'm gonna have a birthday party
on the beach,
and I'm gonna learn how to surf.
I've been watching them from my
window, and it's totally cool.
That sounds totally awesome.
So how's our patient doing?
This is Dr. Barnes.
Dr. Barnes is gonna remove
the tumor from your heart.
What happened to the other guy?
This guy's much better
than the other guy.
Dr. Barnes is the best heart guy in L.A.
This is gonna be your last surgery.
That's how good he is. And so I snagged
him for you because I'm on your side.
It is a 6-hour procedure, so we should
probably get going. Right?
- You'll be here when I come out?
- I'll be here.
Don't look so scared.
It's gonna be fine.
- Finishing or starting?
- Finishing. You?
Starting.
I've got myocardial resection on a kid.
I hate working on kids.
I feel like I'm holding my breath
the entire time.
I know what you mean.
I work on babies sometimes.
So you... come here often?
Was... that actually sounded
like a... was that a pickup line?
That... I apologize.
Besides, I would...
I would give a better
pickup line than that.
I'm... not into this.
The bug needs stimulation.
I'm the pediatrician.
This is my area.
Hello, little one.
- I'm stimulating the bug.
- We've made a decision.
- Together?
- Paternity test, now.
One of us gets out of your hair,
the other one has a right to know.
- Look...
- You know what?
You moved in, you pushed us out,
you've claimed your territory,
but one thing is clear...
This kid you're talking to is not
your kid. So stay out of it.
The answer is right there
for us to know.
We know that you don't want
to face it, but we do.
I've gotta go.
I have no defining exit line, so...
They told me it was a carjacking.
They told you?
You don't remember?
I remember leaving soccer practice.
I'd parked across campus
in student parking.
I got to my car.
There were people around.
I pulled out my keys,
and I heard a noise behind me,
and...
That's all I remember.
Woke up in the ambulance.
I loved that car.
I love school.
This guy came into my world and...
I'm pissed.
I'd like you to see
our psychiatrist Dr. Turner.
- 'Cause other than pissed, I'm okay.
- Just...
do me the favor
so you stay that way.
You know what'll make me okay?
When they catch this guy.
Private Practice S02E18
Finishing
Are you snooping?
This is public space.
I'm just standing here.
Snooping.
Do you want to know
what's going on or not?
Of course I do.
Possible baby daddies
demanded paternity test.
Said my name during sex with her.
Wait a minute.
How do you know all this,
just by watching?
What, do you read lips now?
Sam told me the whole name thing.
What?
We are friends. He tells me stuff.
We're just friends.
And violet was yelling so loud,
it just...
Oh, god.
He called out your name.
I'm the only person that the man
has had sex with in the last 15 years.
It was just habit. That's all.
We're just friends.
I wish someone would call out another
woman's name in bed with me.
I'd even take not knowing
who the father of my baby was.
Either way, it would mean that I'd had
a man on top of me in recent history.
- You know what? That's really sad.
- I know.
I thought somebody
was trying to pick me up...
And I felt my knees
open just a little bit.
I don't want to spoil the fun,
but I've got Betsey
with me today, and
"say my name" and "who's your daddy"
are getting a little loud,
and I don't want to have to explain what
a paternity test is to my 6 year old.
I'm not telling 'em to shut up.
No, me neither.
I will have a paternity test when
I want to have a paternity test.
You can't do one for
a few weeks anyway.
Who do they think they are,
telling me what to do? It's my body.
- It's my uterus.
- You can't do one for
- a few weeks anyway.
- I mean, yes, I was...
A little bit irresponsible,
having unprotected sex with two men,
but does that give them
the right to dictate...
You can't do a C.V.S.
paternity test for a few weeks.
The point is mute.
Moot.
- The point is moot.
- Is it "moot"?
- I'm pretty sure it's "mute."
- It's moot. The point is moot.
I can't have a paternity
test for weeks.
I didn't come here to...
I need you to see a patient.
Is the point moot
or is the point mute?
Annie's out of surgery.
Where's the patient?
You were in bed with me, and
you called out another woman's name.
I know, and... it was wrong,
but I was not thinking about her.
It just slipped out.
I promise.
- What... please, what are you...
- I have to go to work.
And you've explained yourself
as best you could, I guess.
Have a good day, Sonya. See? There.
Sonya. See? I s... I know it.
It's a beautiful name.
Sonya...
You're just in the doghouse,
you know?
You're just gonna have to suffer,
just for a little bit.
Maybe I should make her dinner tonight,
you know, go all out...
Candlelight, flowers, the works.
You need to take her out. Take her out
somewhere nice, somewhere romantic.
The Blue Sea in Malibu.
The Blue Sea,
the place we used to go?
The place with the great mimosas
that you drank way too many of.
The Blue Sea.
That sounds perfect.
The memory loss is not unusual,
and it's not
necessarily a bad thing.
- You're protecting yourself.
- I don't want to protect myself.
- I want to remember.
- The memory may come out naturally,
- when you're ready to deal with it.
- I'm ready to deal with it.
I want to help the police find this guy,
and I can't unless I remember.
I don't want to be a victim.
I want to find this guy
and rip his throat out.
Close your eyes.
So I want you to think about
something you like.
Griffith Park.
- I like riding horses.
- Good.
So I want you to
see it in your mind,
like you're sitting in a movie
theater watching it on a screen.
Describe what you see.
The horse is chestnut
with a white streak
down the side of his neck.
We're riding off the trail,
up a hill,
then we cut through some trees,
cantering.
Good.
So you're relaxed,
and you're feeling that,
only the picture on
the screen is going to change.
Focus on the screen.
You see your car, you see yourself.
Now don't bring
everything into focus,
and you can look away
anytime you need to. But...
do you see anything
about the attacker?
His arm...
his hand.
He was white.
The guy was white.
I can remember this, can't i?
- You can help me remember?
- I'll try.
It always starts with the cramping.
My husband and I can't
go through this again.
I didn't even tell him
this time because...
We just can't take losing another...
Miscarrying once is hard enough.
But twice must be...
We're not even telling friends
and family about the baby this time.
I think I know why you're cramping.
The placenta is implanting
low on the uterine wall,
and that can cause bleeding
as the pregnancy progresses.
- Is that dangerous?
- It can be
unless we can do something about it,
and in this case, you can.
Sure. What?
Anything.
- No sex.
- No sex is the treatment?
No sex.
We'll just spend our evenings reading...
and talking and not having sex.
If it makes you feel any better,
I'm not having any sex either.
Your tumor was bigger
than we expected.
We weren't able to remove all of it.
But Dr. Barnes thinks that more chemo
will shrink this tumor,
and in another month,
he can take it out completely.
That's what you said last time...
And the time before that.
And then this was supposed to help.
But none of it helps.
Just more hospitals...
More medication,
staying inside all the time.
- I don't want anymore.
- Don't talk like that.
It'll be okay. You'll see.
No, it won't.
I don't want anymore surgery.
You promised you were on my side.
Tell them no more surgery.
- Finishing or starting?
- Finishing. You?
- Starting.
- Our timing.
My pickup lines
are usually just honesty.
I don't have any lines.
For instance?
- Honesty?
- Honesty.
You are breathtakingly beautiful.
That's what I'd say,
you know, if I were trying
to pick you up.
How was that?
That was good.
You missed the window.
For the C.V.S. test.
- The risks of puncturing the placenta...
- Minimal.
But it's... there.
- You, too?
- She missed the window.
Paternity, C.V.S.
Window, it's... gone.
So amnio?
You're far enough along for an amnio.
There are risks to...
I'll consider it.
And... while you're at it, will you
consider backing off with Jill?
She's in my office,
and her body is a mess.
- Her muscle pain is unreal.
- She's injured.
She was injured before the attack.
You were treating her.
For a rotator cuff tear.
She was getting better.
Her treatment was nearly done.
Since the attack...
Her injuries are not muscular.
Pulling up those memories,
- that's what's eating at her.
- If i can walk her through the attack,
then I can desensitize her
to the memory.
But then you run the risk
of retraumatizing her,
which her body tells me
is what's happening.
You should be careful.
With a trauma,
if she's internalizing...
I've seen people get really sick.
So now you're ganging up on me
about everything?
I'm doing what's best for Jill.
Are there bumps along the way?
But in the end,
it's best that she knows now.
She wants to get this guy
who did this to her.
So if she remembers, she can put
him away and have her life back.
That's interesting.
Sometimes you think it's better
to know. And others...
Denial works for you.
- What is it?
- The man who attacked me,
they think they found him.
They want me to come in for a lineup.
Your face is all scowly.
Scowly?
You didn't light up
as soon as you saw me.
This is me, lit.
What... What's wrong?
I mean, you've been kind of...
We've been in a better place?
We started fresh?
I slept with Archer, and you
forgave me. Better place, fresh start.
But?
But nothing. Everything's fine.
We're in a good place, really.
- You're looking...
- Don't tell me I look good.
Because I don't.
Here's some good news.
I just looked over your labs, and
the chemo is doing
what it's supposed to.
It's getting you ready for the surgery.
The chemo is making me sick
I've tried to tell my parents
I don't want this surgery,
- but they won't listen to me.
- I know this is hard,
- but you gotta try to hang in there.
- Hang in for what?
I know what dr. Barnes
wants to do for me.
The surgery stinks. Only 20%
of the people who have it
- live for more than six months.
- And that can be you.
I know I'm sick,
and my heart is really bad,
and if I do nothing, I'm gonna die.
But this surgery?
Chances are it's not gonna work.
And if I was off this medication, I
could really feel good for a little bit.
I could play with my friends again.
If I had this out of my arm...
I could go in the ocean.
I could be normal for a little bit.
I'd rather have one good day
than be sick for the rest of my life.
- The bleeding started this morning?
- In the shower.
I've been doing everything
you told me... no sex,
taking it easy.
I even cut back my hours at work.
- This shouldn't be happening.
- The placenta previa hasn't improved.
So I'm just gonna keep
losing babies...
One after another after another?
Look at me.
You are stressed. And if you're
stressed, then the baby's stressed.
You are not going to lose this baby.
It just means that we need
to be more aggressive.
I'm gonna put you on total bed rest
for the remainder of your pregnancy,
and then I'm gonna watch you
very carefully.
I want an amnio.
If I'm gonna lay on my back
for 5 months, I need to know
this baby's gonna be okay,
you know, that there aren't any
- genetic defects.
- An amnio is usually done at 17 weeks.
We need to wait another month.
- What if...
- No what-ifs.
We're gonna wait.
We're gonna do the amnio
at the right time.
I'm at the doctor's office.
She's putting me on bed rest.
She's not letting me into the bed.
There's no sex.
And you need sex.
I'm grown.
Dinners are cool, restaurants are cool,
but she has me sleeping on the floor.
Come on, Sam. Be smart.
You gotta change the scenery.
You gotta make her forget
what happened. You gotta...
take her away to...
I don't know, take her to...
the grand spa in Palm Springs.
I remember we had
a really good time there.
That first weekend after Maya,
ust the two of us.
We certainly forgot about everything.
That was great.
That was fun.
- I have Maya this weekend, though.
- I will take Maya. You go.
Go have fun. Go?
Whisk her away. Go.
Whisk.
We don't know what to do.
She's miserable and sick,
and she doesn't want this.
And she makes sense,
but she's only 12.
She still loves stuffed animals.
She giggles when
she has to talk to boys.
Anytime there's thunder,
she comes to sleep between us.
I don't want to lose her, but
I can't stand forcing her to do
something that she doesn't want to do.
You really think you can help her?
I know it's hard, watching her.
But I think if I operate,
- there's a chance she'll make it.
- A chance.
You don't think
she should have the surgery?
I don't wanna...
- This is your decision.
- I'm asking you. Please.
I think even in the best-case scenario,
it's months in a hospital,
constant drug therapies
and interventions,
and this is not about a cure.
However,
considering the alternative...
Wait a minute.
Go on, Dr. Cooper.
I want to know what you think.
I think Annie has considered
the alternative.
And even though it
terrifies us, for her,
the alternative means having
a life, a real life
like other kids, even if
it's just for a little while.
You know, playing outside
and maybe going surfing and...
Instead of spending her life...
In that little room
we have down the hall.
It means celebrating her birthday
somewhere other than here.
In the future, we will be able
to treat people with Annie's condition
much more effectively.
She doesn't have the perspective
to understand that
because she's still a kid.
You can't put a decision like this
in her hands.
If the surgery works,
what will her quality of life be?
It's hard to know.
She'll be limited in her activities.
You'll need to keep her home mostly.
But with medications, we can sustain
her heart. She'll be alive.
For how long?
I want to take her home.
Wait. You're the one
from the scrub room.
I didn't realize 'cause of the hair.
I had this image of it in my head,
you know, under the cap, and...
You didn't recognize me.
But red.
Red is good.
Red becomes you.
Thank you.
Look, I'm sorry.
I am...
I am having a day.
I got some bad news,
and then I've got this patient...
Another doctor has convinced
her parents to let her die,
which I think... I know...
Is the wrong decision.
Anyway, it's a...
a day.
You ever do that? You ever
- worry over a patient?
- Absolutely. I'm
worrying over this pregnant woman
right now.
Charlotte King
Is that your name?
No, she's...
- the chief of staff here.
- Right. I knew that.
You should talk to her.
If you believe your patient should live,
then you should fight for it.
And Charlotte... I mean,
she's Charlotte, but she...
- She'll help you fight.
- Thank you.
No problem.
I should...
go...
- See Charlotte.
- Right, of course.
If you see the man who assaulted you,
please identify him by stating
aloud his reference number.
Take as much time as you need.
5.
You've indicated suspect number 5.
Are you sure that's the man
who attacked you?
I'm sure. 5.
All right, miss Avery.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You did it.
The face...
- Seeing it again, it's...
- It's okay.
- He can't hurt you anymore.
- I thought it would be good.
I thought it would help me remember
what he did to me. But it...
It's just...
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I can't believe it's coming out.
I'm gonna get to go in the water
for the first time ever, ever.
Can I see you for a sec?
- What's going on?
- Just give us a sec.
- Catheter is not coming out today.
- What?
Dr. Barnes approached me.
He feels he can save Annie's life
and that you're letting a minor make
a decision about refusing treatment.
The family and I concur on this.
What are you doing?
He has a valid claim.
- He's going for a court order.
- Why are you talking to me like that?
- Like what?
- Like I'm some stranger.
I could've let him sandbag you.
I didn't. I'm giving you a heads-up.
Still like a stranger,
and you know me.
You know I wouldn't be doing this
for her if I didn't think it was right.
Come on.
- I'm just doing my job.
- That doesn't make it right.
There was definitely flirting.
With the surgeon?
Cute surgeon.
- Cute surgeon.
- It felt...
to feel like me again.
Can I steal some of those
colored paper clips?
On your desk?
For an art project
that Betsey's doing?
She's in a trance.
Resort porn.
Look at this.
You can watch whales breach,
just right from your palapa.
When are you going?
This isn't for me.
This is for Sam
and... Sonya.
You're... planning a trip for your
ex-husband and his new girlfriend.
You realize how weird that sounds?
Of course I do.
It's ju... look at this place.
Somebody should be enjoying it.
Without the surgery, Annie dies.
Without the surgery,
Annie has a life,
at least for a little while.
There are a number
of precedents that deal
with the denial of medical
treatment to children,
but they primarily involve the
religious convictions of the parents.
This isn't a religious thing, judge.
It's about giving our little girl
what she really wants.
Look, this is as painful a decision
as anyone can face.
I understand why the Bishops
don't want to make it.
But by giving in to
what their child wants...
And she is a child.
They are abdicating
their parental responsibilities.
Do I get a say here?
I'm sorry, but you don't.
But it's my life.
But legally,
your parents are responsible
for making decisions
about your medical care.
And you should know that state law
prohibits you from acting
in any way that endangers
Annie's health.
You're going to force them
to make Annie undergo the surgery?
That catheter stays in,
and the surgery is scheduled
for the first available date.
That's not fair.
That's not fair!
I haven't seen you in a while.
I lightened my surgical schedule.
I had some personal stuff.
- Finishing or starting?
- Starting. You?
Me, too.
I missed you.
I shouldn't say that.
But I did...
miss you.
Why...
- Shouldn't you say that?
- I just...
I don't know.
I should go...
back in there before
the baby comes out without me and...
I get sued.
Still nothing.
Only his face.
I can't remember anything else.
How am I supposed
to testify against him
if I can't remember anything
about what happened?
The trial is a month away.
You have time.
- You'll remember.
- And then what?
I can see what he did to me
again and again?
Because right now, all I see is
his face, and I see it everywhere...
At the store, on the boy who packs
my groceries, at the gym,
every guy in the corridor.
Every time I go anywhere,
I see him.
And at night,
- in my dreams...
- We can stop.
We can work on helping you cope
with where you are today.
I want to put him away.
I need this fear
to go away.
I'm gonna insert the needle now.
- You might feel a slight pinch.
- Wait... before you do it,
I just need for you to talk to me
about anything,
just to get my mind off this.
Let's see.
We can talk about...
You know, you said
you weren't having sex.
Why not?
You're beautiful, successful...
I'm kind of in between guys
right now.
- Anybody you got your eye on?
- There is...
- This one guy.
- Cute?
- Very.
- Details.
I'm on bed rest and being denied sex.
I need some details.
He's a good guy.
I don't know him that well or anything,
but you can just tell, you know?
He's a good guy,
and I need a good guy.
- Any dates?
- I don't know...
He's...
It's like he wants
to ask me out, but
I don't know. It's like there's
something holding him back or...
Go after him.
Get yours.
And then tell me all about it.
If something happens,
you will be the first to know.
I hear the waves are 2 to 4 feet,
great shape.
One of the guys in the office surfs.
Said it was great out there today.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Can't see it from here.
I know.
I'm sorry.
When I thought that one day,
I could be out there doing it myself,
it was fun to think about.
But now...
- Come on, Annie.
- We both know the truth.
I'm gonna die in this hospital.
You sign off on the junction
Now you're telling me you just want me
to let her die?
I was doing my job.
I was following the law.
- But?
- Maybe Cooper's right.
Keeping her alive isn't the same
as saving her life.
I am sorry Annie can't go to school
or go surfing,
but is the chance to do that
for a month or two,
is that worth giving up the chance
at living past 13?
She's got nothing left in her,
not even the will to fight you.
So maybe you should ask yourself,
who are you doing this for?
She still hasn't done the amnio.
Maybe you should just do that
charm thing you people do.
You're charming.
I'm thinking about it.
In psychological circles,
we call that a stall.
Jill had a very tough session today.
I was wondering if you could
do something to help her relax.
Don't touch me!
It's me. It's Pete.
Focus on me. Look at me.
It's Pete.
Take a deep breath.
You're here. You're okay.
She's resting.
Thanks.
You have to stop.
- She's traumatized.
- By the attack.
She... is afraid that if she doesn't
finish what she started,
then this thing will keep haunting her.
So I'm... gonna support her in that.
Jill is a wreck.
- She's falling apart.
- She was happy.
She had a life.
He came in and...
took a piece of it away...
Her contentment, her security.
And until she sees this guy
locked up and paying for what he did,
she's not gonna move past it.
I hope you're right.
You're here late.
You know, babies don't tell time.
Besides, you're... here, too.
Do you think we push?
As... doctors,
do you think we push too hard?
I don't know.
I mean...
I have this patient now.
She's pregnant and just...
Just trying to get her through
it so she can have a healthy baby,
I push,
you know, for patients like her,
because she needs me to.
What about when they
don't need you to?
Are you okay?
I think i've been pushing too hard.
I don't know.
Just sit here with me?
Do you realize that we don't even know
each other's names?
You're right.
I'm Addison Montgomery.
I have to...
I have to go.
I have a patient.
Nice to meet you.
Betsey's sick.
Her school just called.
Do you mind if i duck out for, like,
an hour? Heather can't get her.
- That's fine. Go ahead.
- What are you doing?
Doesn't this trip look perfect?
For who?
You do see what you're doing?
- I am helping.
- You're avoiding.
Archer broke your heart.
And now you're throwing yourself
into Sam's life
so you don't have to pick up
and start yours.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but when was the last time
you went on a date?
- Come on.
- Maybe if you...
spent all this time and effort you're
spending on Sam and Sonya on yourself...
It might be more rewarding.
You here to force another
procedure on her or...
I won't push the surgery anymore.
If she doesn't want it,
I won't push.
- What about the judge?
- I told him I reevaluated my position.
I just wanted to help her.
So once it's out?
It's not easy to get back in.
If Annie were to have a problem?
We might not be able to get
medication into her fast enough.
You do understand?
This is it.
You sure?
I'm sure.
It's all right, mom.
I promise, it's all right.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You'll see.
- I'm gonna see the ocean.
- You're gonna see the ocean.
Good news.
Amnio was normal.
There are no genetic abnormalities.
The baby is perfectly healthy.
I can't wait to tell my husband.
He should be here any minute.
There he is.
This is the wonderful doctor
I've been telling you so much about...
- Nice to meet you.
You're gonna do fine.
I don't know if I can do this.
I know that you're scared,
but I also know that this is something
that you want to do.
What if I can't?
Look at him.
Tell me what he did to you.
I heard his voice...
Telling me not to turn around and...
Keep breathing,
just like we worked on.
He had a gun.
He grabbed me...
And the next thing I knew,
I felt a blow across my face.
And then he hit me with the gun over
and over
and over, until my head slammed
into the pavement.
That's right.
That's what he did to you.
- Now why are you here?
- That man robbed me.
He didn't just steal my car
and my money.
He stole my sense of security.
He stole my ability
to sleep at night.
He stole my sense of self-control.
So I came here today...
To get them back.
I'd say you're ready.
You should've seen the smile
on her face when she got on that board.
It's her birthday,
and it just keeps
creeping up on me...
That it'll be her last.
It's a good one.
It's... what she wanted.
She's living.
...going over, and I was freaking out.
I was so scared.
And I was, like,
just hold on to the board...
I should've trusted you to know
what Jill could handle,
to know that she'd remember
when she was ready.
You wanted to see me?
- Both of you.
- Wait... Did...
Did you...
I didn't.
Right now, in my mind,
the baby is...
is the bug.
And...
I've gotten used to the bug.
I'm actually...
Liking the bug.
And I'm afraid if I start
seeing it with a
Pete head or a
Sheldon head or...
I know myself, and I know that
I'm not ready to do this.
- What about us?
- If you want to know anything, ask.
If you want to be included, come...
both of you.
Or neither of you.
I understand if you want
to walk away, and I'm sorry.
But I know that this is
the best way to do it.
For you.
You're alone here.
You have...
and the baby.
But you're all alone.
And you don't have to be.
Cat got your tongue?
I do not understand you.
What?
I just bumped into him.
You went to Noah behind my back.
Why didn't you tell me you helped
him change his mind?
You did a good thing, a thing
that makes me love you even more.
I don't need you
to love me even more!
I slept with Archer,
and you forgive me.
You are good.
You are the good one.
You do good things.
You and...
It makes me sick.
You lovin' me, it makes me
literally sick to my stomach.
I slept with somebody else.
I screwed Archer's brains out,
and you forgive it?
Who does that?
So, see, you're the good one,
and I'm the bad one,
and I don't want credit for saving
a little girl's life. I don't want it.
- You need to forgive yourself.
- Damn it, stop loving me.
- Just stop loving me!
I will not stop loving you.
I'm sorry.
Look at this. Sonya and I got to make
our own private label.
- Now that's what I call a vacation.
- Thanks.
So what do you think
I should do next with sonya?
What's the... what's the plan?
You... know, there is no plan.
Travel agency's closed.
I'm finished.
What? You were helping me out.
It was fun.
That's the problem.
You shouldn't be having fun with me.
You should be having fun with her.
I should be having some fun
of my own.
Annie's 13.
Good job.
The jury found him guilty.
Very good job.
Will you talk to the bug?
I thought you hated that.
Just talk to the bug.
This is your uncle Cooper speaking.
And I look forward to seeing you
in a couple of months.
Ready to go?
I got us a 7:30 reservation...
What's wrong?
You don't call out your
ex-wife's name out of habit,
not if it's working...
Not if it's right.
Do you...
Do you want to be with her?
What she and I had...
a best friend...
and you and I...
- We're never gonna get there.
- I'm sorry.
Me, too.
- This is a mistake.
- Just... be here.
But still, it is a mistake.
I'll be over here.
- I wasn't going to come.
- But you did.
Thank you.
What do you want?
I just... wanted to say...
I just wanted to tell you
that the first time we talked,
I was just a flattered married guy.
Then the second time,
I was... playing with fire.
And then...
I got attached.
I got attached in a way
I didn't expect.
- I didn't mean to, I didn't plan...
- I have been where you are...
One step away from doing something
really stupid.
I've done...
Don't take the step.
What if I want to take the step?
What if the step is...
all I can think about?
- She's my patient.
- You think I don't know that?
Finishing or starting?
Finishing.
The Mc Dreamy Team
pour www.forom.com