Are you gonna be home late tonight?
Uh, well, I have a baby to deliver
If she doesn't want? I want you.
Tell you what. You get in the bed and when
I get home, I'll tuck you in. I promise.
I love you.
- You came.
- I've been summoned.
- Future under 14D.
- No.
- Addison.
- If you wanna tell me something, tell me why she is coming.
You can ask her yourself.
- Where are you going?
- Just wanted to make sure you'd showe up. Now that you're here...
What? Captain. You can't
just... Bizzy is you...
- What is going on?
- Ask your mother.
- You cut your hair.
- Yes, I... wanted, uh, something different.
So, uh, captain was here but
he left us to chat, is he?
It was a dreadful flight.
- Dreadful staff. Dreadful food. I'm gonna make a complaint to Wills.
- Right.
I cannot believe you moved
to this place. But here I am.
Yes, about that. I was surprised
that you actually came to visit.
Addison... don't push. You know short hair isn't
for everyone. Some people look older with them.
Absolutely gorgeous.
I think we'll win first
place this year at New Haven.
The Silvermans' tulips were...
you could cut the tension with a knife,
but they're smiling, they're drinking,
they're chatting about flowers.
Hmm. Trust me, they are
not chatting about flowers.
They are speaking wasp.
We learn it at an early age.
- What are they saying?
- See? Now that's the thing.
Usually I know,
but this time, I have no idea.
Maybe I'm crazy. I mean,
maybe everything is fine,
which would be creepy
because nothing is ever fine.
- Oh, here she comes.
- Ah, Mrs. Montgomery.
Now, Samuel, how many
times have I told you
to call me Bizzy?
Yes, Mrs. Montgom... Bizzy. Ma'am.
What is that?
Milo. I've deced to give
up men and get a cat.
Don't say that. That's so sad.
People will believe you.
And you'll have to
lock it up or something.
Well, if your father and I
are gonna be staying here...
- Stay here?
- Let me just get that for you.
So, Bizzy, uh, what
brings you here to L.A.?
Excuse me.
Yes.
- Sam?
- It's Dell.
Dell, what happened?
I... I don't know. The
house, it just exploded.
- It had to have been a gas leak. I don't know.
- It's okay.
24-year-old female,
extensive second-
and third-degree burns,
possible inhalion injury.
BP's 100 over 60. Pulse 130.
Let's go.
On my count. Ready? One, two, three.
I need high-flow 0-2.
I'm gonna need a blood gas
- and a carboxyhemoglobin.
- We're on it, Cooper.
I... I tried to get 'em both
out, but... but the flames...
I could hear heather screaming,
but I couldn't see anything,
So I got Betsey. By the
time I got to Heather, she...
I... I could... I... I couldn't get them both.
- Dell, you did all the right things.
- Let's get a liter of lactated ringers.
- Hey, do you mind?
You're interfering with our protocol.
Okay, guys. You have
to let my team work.
- They do this every day.
- It's not Dell every day.
- I know that. Now step back, both of you.
- I... I need to be with both of them.
- What do I...
- Pete, go with Heather.
You go with your
daughter. Okay, let's move.
I'll get you an update as
soon as I can, Dell. Let's go.
Please don't let her die.
Get out of the way now.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Okay, Heather.
- No! Betsey! Where's Betsey?!
- Heather, you're...
You need to keep the mask on.
- No!
- Heather, you need to keep the mask on.
- Where's Betsey?!
- Betsey is alive. She's unconscious.
She's in the E.R.
Cooper is working on her.
Dell is with her. Now you
need to keep the mask on.
She's got second-and
third-degree burns
over 60% of her body.
- Her lungs have sustained severe inhalation injuries.
- We should have an ecmo unit standing by.
- I've already ordered it.
- Let's give her morphine.
- Do you know her well?
- I used to work with her husband.
- What's the prognosis?
- In my experience,
30% chance of survival.
Dell, I'm so sorry.
- Is there anything... anything we can do?
- I... I'm supposed to deliver the Higgins baby.
- They're gonna be waiting for me.
- I... I already took care of it.
- The on-call doctor is gonna
deliver. It's fine. - Okay.
Did I give my insurance card?
They're gonna... they're gonna need...
Dell, I'll... I'll make sure they
have all the information, okay?
Hey.
Hey, Dell, I took a look
at Betsey's C.T. scan.
She has a moderate brain contusion
and she also has carbon
monoxide poisoning.
Now most people wake up in a few hours,
but because she's so small,
it's gonna take a little longer.
- Heather... how is she?
- I don't have an update on Heather from Pete yet.
But they know what caused the explosion.
- Okay.
- Maybe we should go outside.
- Just say it.
- Um...
Heather was cooking meth.
They think it was ether.
Dell, we've got Heather stabilized.
She's asking for you. I know
you don't want to leave Betsey,
but it...
Heather.
Don't try to speak.
Can you hear me?
Can you understand me?
Good.
I hope you die, bitch.
You almost killed my daughter.
I hope you die a miserable...
painful, agonizing death.
You're almost there,
Heather. Almost there.
After this, we're gonna
test your lung function.
Help us decide our next move, okay?
He hates me. He wants me
to die. Just let me die.
Heather, listen to
me. You can't give up.
Dell doesn't want you to die.
He's upset and he's
worried about Betsey.
But you gotta fight,
okay? You gotta fight.
Give me more drugs.
Please. Just make it stop!
Okay, Heather.
- He said that?
- He's upset.
It's his way of dealing
with a tragic situation.
To tell somebody
who's fighting for their
life you want them to die?
I don't care what she did.
That's crossing a line.
He couldn't have meant it.
Do you guys think he knew that
heather was doing drugs again?
I got you all coffee.
I'm gonna go check on Heather.
I didn't know about the drugs.
I wouldn't have put Betsey in
danger like that if I knew...
since you were all wondering.
Dell, no o... no one thought...
It's cold in here. She hates the cold.
You know, she's always asking
for more blankets at night.
- She needs another blanket.
- Okay, you know what, Dell?
Why don't... we're gonna
go and talk to a nurse
and see if we can get some more, okay?
God, can you believe all this?
I know.
I feel terrible.
I... I feel like I really
should've pushed him harder.
I should've made him really think
about letting heather
back into their lives.
Nai, there's nothing you
could've done differently,
- Nothing anyone could've done differently.
- Well, maybe you're right. I don't know.
Hey, wait. Let... let... let's
just have a 1-minute mental break.
Sure. Maya?
Same... hating me and
loving Pink or Rink or Dink.
- Whatever his name is.
- Bizzy?
The same... cocktails, cold smiles...
You know, maternal.
Something's going on, but...
Bizzy.
Yes.
I will pick up some
more on the way home.
- Bye.
- Crisis?
- More gin.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Me, too.
Addie.
Susan? What...
- Oh, what are you doing here?
- Hi.
Oh, my God. You look great. You look...
- How long has it been? You look exactly the same.
- Oh, about eight years, and I look a mess.
You have your mother's skin.
Oh. So how is it?
She's driving me crazy.
He is driving me crazy. I don't
know how you work for them.
Remember to breathe and many cocktails.
What are you doing here?
- You know Bizzy's rule... wherever she goes, I go.
- Susan, why is she here?
- I have no idea.
- She didn't tell you? You really don't know?
Let's go face the dragon?
Breathe. Many cocktails.
Hey.
Look who I found.
Susan.
I brought the documents for
the Houston charity ball.
Hello, captain.
Who wants... a drink?
Excuse me.
You're turning down drinks?
Good night, Addison.
- Did something happen with Dell?
- No, no.
Susan... she runs the family
office. Do you remember her?
I like her. I mean, she's
close in age to me, you know,
and she would do things for me.
She would deal with my mother for me.
A... a... anyway, she's been
working for us for 20 years.
She's like one of the family.
She shows up here and...
And what is it?
I think the captain's sleeping with her.
I think that's why he sent for Bizzy,
because anywhere Bizzy
goes, Susan goes, too.
He invited his wife out
so that she would bring his mistress?
That's my father. And
my mother trusts her.
I mean, she lives on the estate.
You know, and now he does this? Ugh.
I mean, right under Bizzy's nose.
And now they're here in my
house. Uh, I need a drink.
- No, no, no, you don't.
- Oh, I do.
What you need to... you need
to tell those people to leave
instead of putting up with their lies.
Just kick 'em out before
your liver drowns in gin.
Sam, I can't tell the
captain and Bizzy to leave.
They're the captain...and Bizzy.
You are Addison Adrianne
Forbes Montgomery.
You have more names
than anybody else I know.
Tell them to leave.
I can do it.
- I could... tell them to leave.
- Tell them to leave.
Tell 'em to leave.
Good girl.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Don't worry.
I love you.
Susan?
Oh, captain. Bizzy's
right down the hall.
Captain...
Addison?
How'd it go?
What was Bizzy's face like...
What happened?
I can't... I... I can't.
I just... I... I...
Do you mind if I spend the night here?
I... I promise I'll, um, I'll
stay on my side of the bed.
Yeah, sure.
Morning.
You're short.
I mean, usually you're in heels,
very high heels.
I hope you don't take
that as a criticism.
It's a, nice change.
You okay?
14 down. I'm stumped on 14 down.
- I'm sorry.
- I was working a crossword puzzle yesterday,
and I couldn't figure out
14 down... "future hunters."
- Future hunters is a clue?
- Yes. Do you know the answer?
- I don't...
- "Future hunters." I know I know the answer to that.
It's just not coming to me right now.
If I could just figure out the answer...
and I... I know how I sound. I know.
I know that if I look
at you, you'll like...
think I'm some sort of
crazy woman or something.
I... but trust me, you want me
to be thinking about 14 down.
If I don't think about 14
down, then I'm just gonna have
a nervous breakdown in this elevator,
and I can't do that right now. I can't.
Why don't I ride up with
you the rest of the way?
You want to come to my office?
Do you believe that people are owed?
I sometimes believe that
you're owed, you know?
And I think Betsey's owed one.
She's just had such a tough life...
you know, teenage parents
and a mom on drugs.
And I'll never know what
this has done to her.
But I figured she's owed, right?
She's had it so bad, that
this can't be her end,
'cause then what was her life for...
Just suffering?
That would be cruel.
That would be just beyond cruel.
Dell.
Betsey, hey. Betsey.
- Uh, get it out, Naomi. Just get it out.
- Just relax.
I'm gonna count to three, and
then I want you to blow out.
One, two, three.
It's okay.
there you go. Good girl.
- Okay, good job, kiddo. You're okay.
- I'm gonna go get Cooper.
Okay, okay. Hey, hey, it's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Where's mommy?
Where's Betsey?
Heather, your potassium is
too high from tissue damage.
It's affecting your heart
rhythm. You need oxigen.
- Okay. What do we got? -
She's having runs of v-tach.
Lido 75 I.V. Push. I need that calcium.
V-fib. Charge  200. Everybody off.
Clear.
Is she dead?
No.
Heather crashed. We
got her heart started,
but she's dying, and she knows it.
Dell, I know you're angry,
but Heather is going to die.
You can choose not to see her,
- but she wants to see her daughter.
- No.
- Dell, it's her mother.
- No, a mother is someone who... who loves her,
who wouldn't have done this to her,
someone she's supposed to
have good memories about.
She should not have memories
of her mother burnt to a crisp
because she didn't give enough
of a damn about her daughter
or me or anyone else to stay off drugs.
No, Pete. I'm not gonna
let my daughter's last view
of her mother be this. Just no.
I hate him so much.
You hate your father for...
For breaking her heart...
For forcing her to do this.
He cheated on her for
40 years. She had no one.
She had no one to talk
to, no one to comfort her.
- Of course she turned to Susan.
- Is it possible that this relationship with Susan
is your mother's choice?
I know what it's like, okay...
to be rejected,
to have your heart broken,
to... be lonely.
Is that how you feel now?
Okay, we're not talking about
me. We're talking about her.
Actually, we're not talking about her.
We're talking about your
father, which is interesting.
You had this traumatic experience
- involving your mother...
- It wasn't traumatic.
- Okay.
- You suck as a therapist.
Okay.
Why am I here?
I don't know why I'm
here. Why am I here?
Uh, maybe because I'm a stranger.
You can talk to me,
tell me... your feelings.
I'm neutral. I'm Switzerland.
I'm just here to listen.
It wasn't traumatic.
Addison, I'm here to help you...
and to talk and to let you talk,
but I'm not sure you're focusing
on the right things here.
And I'm sure that I am.
Then why didn't you get off the elevator
when you saw your mother?
You might be right about
your mother and your father.
And far be it from me
to question what should make you angry.
But... you haven't talked
to either one of them.
And your point is?
Well, maybe you need
to get off the elevator.
Are you sure it's okay
for her to have ice cream?
Yeah. Wouldn't hurt for
you to get some food, too.
I just want to start over.
I just want to get as far away from this day as
possible. Get her home, not that we have a home.
Come stay with me. My home is yours.
- You know that. As long as you need.
- You guys, good news.
Betsey's neurological
exam is completely normal.
She shows no evidence of
any kind of ongoing problems.
7 year olds are resilient as hell.
So I would like to keep her
another day to monitor her,
just as a precaution, but she's
officially out of the woods.
That is great, which means you can eat.
So I'm gonna go to the cafeteria,
I'm gonna get you some food,
- and no arguments.
- Okay. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Uh, w... where's my daughter?
She's with Dr. Wilder.
Betsey, I want you to be prepared.
Your mom is all bandaged
up to keep her wounds clean.
So don't be scared, okay?
You ready?
Betsey.
Dell.
Betsey?
Daddy!
- Betsey.
- Daddy!
Bring her back.
Oh, Mrs. Montgomery.
What are you doing here?
- I'm waiting for Addison.
- Addison is not here this morning.
She actually, uh, went to... she's here.
She knows I'm here.
Have you talked with her?
Not yet.
Have you?
I have not talked with her.
Hey, Sam. I'm... I'm sorry to interrupt.
- I'm gonna go back to the hospital now.
- Violet,this is Addison mother
Mrs. Montgomery.
Hello.
I'm sorry. I have to go now.
And what do you do here at my
daughter's practice, Violet?
I... I... I'm a psychiatrist.
- Interesting.
- Yeah.
Have you met my husband... the captain?
Um... I...
Yeah, uh, once or twice.
Did you meet him once or
did you meet him twice?
Twice.
Yes, I believe twice.
I was hoping we could
do some shopping today
And then have lunch.
What are you doing? What's going on?
Okay, that was a mistake.
Mother, I'm just...
I'm so sorry
About what happened,
about what he did to you.
- Who did what to me?
- Look, I know, I know. We don't talk.
We chat about, uh, flowers
and pretend that he's
not... cheating on you.
But let's not do that
anymore. Let's face it.
I'll face it with you.
You've gotta be lonely
and... and alone and...
Addison, this is not your concern.
It's not my... you're my mother.
Exactly.
Let's not discuss these things.
No, we have to.
You're wrong... about your father.
I'm wrong. Bizzy, don't...
He drove you to kiss another woman.
Susan... has been with me for 20 years.
Yes, I know.
She's worked with us for
ages, which is why it's...
Susan has been with me for 20 years.
So, uh...
shopping and then lunch?
Mother...
Sit down.
There was one girl in boarding school
when I was 14.
And then there was the one
in Switzerland on holiday
when I was 17, but those don't count.
It was cold, and we were girls.
But...
then I met Susan.
And the captain?
- What about him?
- Does he know?
We don't discuss it,
but, yes, he knows.
I think he's always known.
Did you ever love him?
Oh, my... Bizzy, why did you marry him?
We're from Connecticut.
My father is a Bradford Forbes.
Okay, so... let me get this straight.
You were the cheating whore, not dad?
I'm gonna go.
If you're gonna talk like that, I'll go.
You have no idea how difficult it was.
Oh, come on, Bizzy. How
hard could it have been?
I mean, nothing was expected of you.
All you had to was order
the housekeeper around,
run your charities
and screw your husband
every Wednesday night.
How complicated is that?
You have no idea.
You don't know me.
You don't know me. You
don't know anything.
You don't know one
single thing about me.
I could have done things.
I could have... been things.
But I'm a Forbes.
So I got married because that
was what I was supposed to do.
And I chose your father because he asked
and he was nice
and he seemed like he
wouldn't suffocate me.
And by the time I realized
my mistake, I had children.
So I made a life.
I did what I could wi what I had.
And I may not have been
in love with your father,
but I loved him.
I do love him.
And I loved you and your brother.
And so instead of
doing what I wanted to,
which was run or slit my wrists,
I threw birthday parties and I smiled
and I kept my mouth shut.
And I raised you and your brother,
and you both turned out brilliantly.
Susan was for me.
Susan was the one thing that was for me.
My children took everything else.
And I'm sorry, but
until you have a child,
you have no idea what
it's like to be a mother.
You have no idea
the sacrifices a woman
makes when she has children.
So don't you dare judge me.
What the hell were you thinking?
- Naomi had to call me to calm Dell down.
- He can decide whatever he wants for himself,
- but that little girl wants her mother.
- That is not yours to say. You made it worse and...
Don't you dare lecture me
about making things worse.
- You don't get to lecture me.
- Dell... stop!
Dell!
- You want to hit me? Fine.
- Get off!
But there's a woman
in there who you loved,
the mother of your child, her child,
who desperately wants to see her.
Yeah, you're pissed. You
have a right to be pissed.
But if you don't make
peace with this, Dell,
if you don't make peace with it now,
you're never gonna get another chance,
- and it will eat at you.
- Get off!
- Dell, let Betsey see her mother before she dies.
- Stay away from me!
Just stay the hell away from my family!
- You want to tell me this isn't personal?
- You know,
maybe you can condone keeping
a child away from their mother,
maybe that makes sense
to you. Not to me.
Heather made a mistake,
but if that child doesn't
get to say goodbye,
you tell me what it does to that kid.
Drink before you speak.
She's very upset.
Is she? I'm sorry. That's so sad.
Drink some more.
Just give me one good reason
why my entire childhood was
a lie... one good reason.
We were trying to
protect you and Archer.
Really? Because I'm a
cheater, Archer's a cheater.
We're all these awesome cheaters.
So, you know, that's a bunch
of crap... protecting us.
I want a good reason.
She's the love of my life.
We've been married for 40 years...
40 years.
My entire adult life,
she has been at my side.
I love her. She's my best friend.
She's my... everything.
It's not her fault, you
know? She didn't know.
We didn't know.
And when we did...
She's the love of my
life. It's complicated.
Love is complicated.
Being a lesbian is not a choice.
She's not going to change her mind.
Hell, she's practically screwing
Susan right under your nose.
The mouth on you...
you know... she sleeps with one woman.
I sleep with all the rest. So what?!
And that's good enough for you?
My entire life,
I thought she was this
poor, pathetic woman.
I thought it was my
job to cover for you.
And it made me hate you.
I mean, don't you understand?
I hated the wrong parent.
I... my cheating? I
thought I got it from you.
But now I know that you're
the poor, pathetic one,
because you love her, and
she loves someone else.
But you stay.
This is like some pathetic,
sad, afterschool special,
which is just awful, because now,
now I hate you both.
Eaglets.
What?
14 down. "future hunters."
It's eaglets.
Thought I heard you come in.
Betsey woke up.
Got the call.
- That's great news.
- Yeah, and then Pete took Betsey to see her mom,
and Dell punched Pete.
We're one big happy family.
- Everything's bad now, I know...
- Stop talking.
- But you have to give me another chance.
- I said stop talking!
Just... I'm tired of talking
and I'm tired of thinking.
Could you just stop talking?
You gonna tell me what happened?
Addison.
Hey.
Talk to me.
Tell me... tell me...
- Wait, wait. Wait.
- Not like this.
Not like this.
Please.
Addison, no, no.
Sam...
No, no. No.
I'm sorry.
Shh.
Don't be sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You people need to leave.
Leave this house. Leave
this city. Go home.
- Samuel, you have no right to interfere in this.
- It... it... it's okay.
No, it is not okay.
Addison is over at my house right now,
and I don't know what
happened, but you people did it.
Sam. I don't think I've
seen you since you...
You were an awkward med student.
All due respect, this isn't about you.
No, it's about them.
It's their family.
I'm sure you care about
Addison, but so do I, so do they.
They're not just gonna run out
because Addison is... is upset.
And I will not let... this destroy them.
Well, she's my family, too.
And I think I know her better right now.
So I'm not asking. I'm
telling you, you need to leave.
Now if Addison wants
to make things right,
then that's up to her.
- But you are not going to push her.
- Sam...
Look...
If you care about Addison,
and I believe that you do,
leave.
Come back to bed, Coop.
I gotta get back to the hospital.
You shouldn't be embarrassed.
Things have been
really stressful lately.
Dell's family...
Oh, is it time for the sexology advice?
"Impotence happens to all
men. It's usually just stress.
- Maybe we can cuddle instead."
- Cooper...
You neglected to tell me
that you were married before.
- That's the problem.
- Cooper...
Oh, shut up, okay?
Shut up.
I hate you!
She's just upset right now.
Well, I'm upset, too,
okay? She hates me.
I'm... I'm not the one who
almost killed her, you know.
I'm tired, Violet. I'm exhausted.
- I'm just trying to protect her.
- And you are protecting her. I know that.
You're protecting her from
seeing something horrible.
But maybe you're protecting
her from the wrong things, Dell.
I mean, my life is a
mess. You know that.
And... and you're...
you're probably right.
I don't always make the best choices.
But, um, you know, I've
always made them with, uh...
with Lucas...
with Lucas in mind, to protect him.
And, you know, maybe
I'm right, but maybe...
I... I just know that if Heather
could, she would take away
all the hurt that she
has caused you and Betsey,
Every last bit of it, Dell.
I found a pipe last night...
Last night... and I
confronted her about it.
And she said it wasn't hers,
that she had a friend over.
You know, and I knew she was lying.
I mean, I knew she was lying.
But I wanted and I needed
to believe that she wasn't using again,
that she wouldn't do
that to me or to Betsey,
that she loved us enough to stay clean.
So I walked out of the
house, and I left my daughter.
I left Betsey.
And she must have been so
scared when it happened.
I did that to her... me. So
I can't let it happen again.
Hey...
Dell
Heather is going to die.
So you might want to allow
her a little bit of mercy.
Just for one moment.
Dell.
Dell, you came.
Heather, Dell is not here.
That's the morphine talking.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
And I'm... sorry for
hurting our little girl.
Tell her...
tell her that I love her so much.
Tell her that mommy made a mistake.
I love her so much.
Will you tell her, Dell?
I'll tell her.
I wanted to be a good mom.
I wanted to.
I forgive you.
It's okay.
I love you and I forgive you.
And our baby's gonna
be okay. So don't worry.
You just go ahead and go.
You can go ahead and go.
Just go.
just go.
Heather.
I'm sorry.
Addison.
We're leaving, all of us.
Bizzy never meant to hurt you.
I tried to get her to
leave. I was the selfish one.
I wanted more.
But she wouldn't leave her children.
That should count for something.
Heather died.
So I'm going to the hospital.
Wait, Addison.
I'm coming with you.
Dell, I'm... I'm sorry.
I have to...
Go in there and tell
her that Heather's...
Betsey's gonna want to know everything.
She's gonna ask me questions
about everything that happened.
What do I say?
You tell her the truth.
As painful and horrible as
it is, you tell her the truth.
Hey.
Mommy didn't make it.
Is she...
Yeah.
No!
Come here. Come here. It's okay.
I kept something from
you that I shouldn't have.
I lied.
And I lied because I didn't
want you looking at me
the way you're looking at me now...
the way you're not looking at me.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep saying it until it's enough,
until you forgive me.
Okay?
Heather's dead.
Did you call wilson to complain
about the service on your flight out?
No.
I'll call. I can call, make some noise.
They won't wanna lose your business.
That would be nice.
Thank you.
Sync by ReHelen- corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com