Should we...
talk about this?
no.
no talking.
my life has too much talking.
how does kevin leave one sockehind?
i mean, don't you think
he'd notice that one bare foot
when he went to put his shoes on?
call him.
he walked out.
you miss him.
call him.
do you want to go get a drink tonight?
i'll figure it out better then i'm drunk.
i... can't. i-i have to work.
work?
wyatt work? pacific wellcare work?
working for the enemy?
oncofertility is new,
and it's interesting.
you think wyatt's interesting.
well... he is.
he's arrogant.
yeah, but he's smart
and incredibly handsome.
you're not really...
oh, okay, you know what? never mind.
- i am--none of my business.
- exactly.
if you want to sell your soul,
i'll still be your friend.
when i used to go in for chemo,
to help me get through it,
i'd concentrate on exactly
what was going to happen.
and when you implanted
the ovarian tissue,
i tried to imagine
the blood starting to flow
and my ovaries starting to work again--
claudia, this is not your fault.
the tissue is very fragile,
and your body has been through
much more than any body should.
i just thought if i
was positive, it would work.
i picked out the crib and i
painted the nursery yellow.
we tried, claudia.
there just wasn't enough
blood supply in your abdomen
for the ovarian tissue to survive.
and there's nothing else?
i'm not gonna be able to have a baby?
wait, well, we only implanted
half of the ovarian tissue
that you took out, right?
right, but we just saw,
the procedure doesn't work.
no, my procedure doesn't work,
but if we were to implant
the ovarian tissue deeper,
more proximate, to--to a more
vigorous blood supply, then--
- next to the uterus?
- yeah.
well, what you're saying
is theoretically possible,
but the surgery is far too complicated.
- i don't know anyone that can--
- i do.
and this person could help me?
i don't know. i'll have to ask her.
oh, sorry. betsey.
pacific wellcare ruins
another day... and a shirt.
heather was supposed to
pick her up first thing.
that's okay. i got
another shirt in the office.
honey, maybe not such a
good idea to be throwing balls around
- in the office, okay?
- it wasn't her fault.
- it was mine.
- what wasn't your fault, champ?
oh, dr. freedman.
arlene. hi. oh, my god.
is this michael?
dude, you're a giant.
will, you remember me?
hi, jeffrey.
that's a pretty cool plane.
hey, let's go back. come on.
so where you been?
it's been, uh...
- two years.
- yeah.
i moved the boys to switzerland...
- oh.
- for jeffrey.
i found this great
experimental program there
- for autistic children...
- mm-hmm.
nontraditional therapy, megavitamins,
- diet modification...
- mm-hmm.
along with art, music therapy.
and how's it been going?
better, i think.
his temper's under control a little more.
um, he's obsessed with airplanes.
- sometimes he'll even talk to you...
- wow.
as long as it's about planes.
planes are good.
talking about planes...
even better.
and how's his health otherwise?
oh, jeffrey's fine.
no, i-it's michael, actually.
- oh.
- he caught a cold on the plane.
it's probably just some bug,
- but, you know...
- all right.
- i wanted to be safe.
- up for you.
so how'd you like switzerland, michael?
they had a cable car,
and there's this one place where
you could take a chocolate tour,
and my best friend has
sheeps and cows at his house.
what? sheeps and cows at his house?
i made butter.
you did? you made butter?
really? wow.
hmm. 102. does your throat hurt, michael?
- nope.
- okay.
open up for me, big and wide.
tilt your head back. ahh.
dr. freedman?
what is it?
what's wrong?
i need to ask you something,
and i know what you're gonna say,
so i don't want you to say anything,
at least, not until you hear me out.
it's about wyatt. i need a favor.
no. i'm not helping you get a date.
huh. no. not for him, for my patient.
- his patient.
- who i'm trying to help.
but i can't, and you can.
- we have to close the doors.
- see,
even cooper realizes pacific wellcare
is putting us out of business.
no, we have to close the doors.
my patient has the measles
and was in reception
for half an hour running around.
everyone that was out--
all our patients this morning
have been exposed.
measles? my pregnant patient...
- and the elderly.
- all at risk.
- we have to close the doors.
www.1000fr.com presents
capture:frm@evelyn~zx
sync:frs@°º
private.practice
season2 episode11
i'm sorry for the inconvenience,
but the virus stays airborne
for up to four hours.
we need to make sure everyone
who was exposed
has been immunized.
uh, excuse me?
can i get the shot now?
i have a lunch at 12:30.
oh, i'm sorry. it contains a live virus.
it's not safe to take when you're pregnant.
but if your blood comes back
and your antibodies are low,
then we can treat it with immunoglobulin.
and if that doesn't work?
doesn't measles lead to birth defects?
let's not get ahead of ourselves, okay?
uh, we need to notify
l.a. county health.
they're gonna want to do
a complete survey.
and they're always awful.
as if we didn't have
enough to do this morning...
okay, i have a light day.
you have to deal with this.
i'll speak to the health department.
i'm, uh, i'm in the mood for a fight.
- will's fine.
- so far,
but he hasn't been vaccinated,
and he's at risk to get this.
it's the measles. i-i--
when my parents were growing up,
everyone got it.
and hundreds of people
died from it every year.
- the vaccine changed--
- don't even think of suggesting--
there's no proven link
between vaccinations and autism.
it's not just me. i have
talked to dozens of parents.
you vaccinated jeffrey,
and it was like a light
went out inside him,
and he's living in some parallel world.
- arlene--
- you don't live with him.
so don't ask me to risk will, too.
hey.
hey, i can't get ahold of betsey's mom.
i don't know if she's been immunized.
- most kids have been.
- you don't know her mother, okay?
she forgot to pick her up.
you think she remembered doctor visits?
sh-should i just give her
the shot to be sure?
i mean, she played with that kid
for, like, a half-hour.
you have 24 hours...?
so wait for the mom and ask,
spare her the needle if you can.
grab a chart. we're checking every patient
who was in here this morning
for immunization.
how many of these are
we looking at, cooper?
- how many what?
- these littleime bombs--
kids coming in without their vaccinations.
the vast majority...
whether or not to vaccinate should
not even be open for debate.
well, it isn't, but i agree with
the academy of american pediatrics
that we shouldn't abandon patients
who choose not to vaccinate.
cooper's right.
you can't kick a kid out just because
the parents believe in a
conspiracy theory about vaccines.
the c.d.c. is clear--
vaccines do not cause autism,
they save lives.
that's the end of story.
hey, i was just in the pediatric
waiting area with betsey.
uh, this is michael's mom's,
and she left it in the lobby.
so if she was down
at pacific wellcare...
then her kids were, too.
someone's going to tell ...?
uh, hi. i need to speak to dr. king.
it's important.
you're dr. freedman, right?
- yeah.
- i'm sheldon. sheldon wallace.
- violet's friend.
- right, yeah.
well, i hope so.
i... i'd like that.
she's, uh... how is she... violet?
- exposed to the measles.
- exposed to the measles?
a kid in our practice
has the measles,
which is why i'm here.
this concerns me how?
well, you have this wonderful coffee bar
that you advertise so prominently,
and a lot of our patients
wander by on their way upstairs.
it is good coffee.
you've exposed my entire
practice to the measles?
claudia jenkins needs a surgeon,
a surgeon with a background in
both gynecology and fertility,
someone who can implant the ovarian tissue
close enough to the uterine blood supply
to allow her to produce her own eggs.
naomi was right. you want a miracle.
no, i want you--
just as a surgeon.
you'd perform the procedure
at st. ambrose-- neutral territory.
you bill all you want.
naomi and i do the follow-up.
you just go in and cut
and implant, and you're done.
claudia gets a baby. you're not
tainted by working with me.
take a look.
tell me that this surgery
wouldn't be amazing.
you don't get me at all.
you think all i want to do is cut?
if i do a surgery,i do the follow-up.
i make sure it takes,
i see the pregnancy the whole way through.
now you may just look
at procedures and outcomes.
but my patients get me
for the whole process.
well, that would be even better.
read the file, dr. montgomery...
before you say no.
are you still having sex
with the same guy?
with the same guy.
finally gonna fess up
and tell me with who?
i told you whom it was,
and you didn't believe me.
who it was,and you told me pete,
which is obfuscation.
- lying, really.
- it's pete, cooper.
i'm having sex with pete.
you need me to prove it to you?
lift your shirt.
- excuse me?
- i need you to lift up your shirt.
- trust me. i'm a doctor.
- you're a pediatrician.
that's like half a doctor.
lift.
this isn't one of your weird...
there's a tattoo.
you're sleeping with violet?
do you have to sleep with everybody?
i don't sleep with everybody a--
you sleep with people and
then they leave the practice.
do you want violet
to leave the practice?
i'm not gonna leave.
- you told him?
- it's just sex.
oh, no. you're not capable
of just having sex.
you are a relationship junkie.
and pete is the anti-relationship.
pete is the ruiner of relationships.
- pete is--
- right here.
and you know it's true.
isn't that, like, the proverbial
pot calling the kettle--
cooper, cooper, cooper, i'm fine.
we're fine.
there's nothing to worry about.
claudia jenkins could have a baby.
thank you, addison.
there's one condition.
- yes.
- this is a one-time thing.
we help claudia, and then you
are done working with wyatt.
- you're...you're blackmailing me.
- no, no, it's not blackmail.
it's ...?
i'm doing this for your own good, nai.
what, so--so that i don't become
corrupted and evil like him,
so i don't extort promises
from my friends?
do you want me to do the surgery?
i guess i have no choice.
okay, so that's it.
everybody's been immunized.
everybody that was here
has been contacted.
you can rele all these
immunization records--
oh, no, he can't.
sonya nichols. county health department.
i'm gonna need those.
oh, uh, sam bennett. i, uh,
i called you.
uh, are--are those all
the immunization records?
uh, yeah. yeah, this is everything.
i want the vaccination records
of all the patients in your practice,
and then after i interview all personnel
and review their employment certificates,
i'll need to inspect your
isolation facilities.
well, we don't have, uh,
isolation facilities per se,
uh, but--well, wait. we, uh,
we provide for rooms.
- we ...we just--
- are not up to current guidelines?
or are you aware of the recent
changes in those standards?
uh,
this isn't gonna be very much fun, is it?
you want to show me around?
yeah. all right, this way.
his--his fever, it was 104
by the time i got home.
i-i couldn't get it down.
how you feeling, michael?
i'm really cold,
and my stomach hurts.
- he vomited twice.
- his lungs are congested.
oh, okay. okay, we got you.
it's okay.
we're gonna get you some fluids,
and we'll bring that fever down,
and you'll feel better.
i need a nasal cannula at
2 liters, chest x-rays and ...
cultures times two.
i don't understand.
why is he so sick?
arlene, measles is serious.
it can lead to pneumonia, encephalitis--
all sorts of other complications.
...?
michael's resting now.
his fever's down.
but he's still having trouble breathing.
my husband is-- is still in switzerland.
you don't think he... needs to fly back?
if it was my son, i'd come.
arlene, we need to talk about will.
i-i--no. i told you no.
no vaccinations.
i don't think you can risk putting will
through what michael's going through.
i can't risk putting will through
what jeffrey's gone through.
i lost one child to autism.
i can't lose another.
- arlene, you won't--
- don't you think ...
seeing michael in there like that...
i would do anything for my kids.
i can't.
look at him.
don't you remember
when he was 2, that smile?
he'd light up the room.
and then you vaccinated him,
and that kid vanished.
those vaccines took him away.
i don't care what you know.
i know what i know.
i know what i lost.
i can't risk it again.
i can't believe this
health department lady
is making us jump through all these hoops.
she's horrible.
how's michael?
uh, not good, and arlene still
won't let me vaccinate will.
- you should call family services.
- you serious?
yes, it's child abuse.
she's knowingly putting her son
at risk for getting really sick.
- it's irresponsible.
- it's a parent's decision.
yeah, well, if i find out that
heather didn't vaccinate betsey,
i'll report her.
can i see you a moment, dr. bennett?
perfect.
that can't be good.
sam's right. i gotta call.
calling d.c.f.s.
while her other child
is still in the hospital
would just be cruel.
cruel? putting ant other child
in dangerous is cruel.
exposing a city to measles is cruel.
violet's right. you can't fault the
mother because she chose not to--
oh, yeah, of course
you're agree with violet,
you're sleeping with her.
i agree with her because she's right,
and i'm sleeping with her because it's
part of the fun of being an adult.
we can do whatever we want
with whomever we want,
however much we want.
so if everyone would just relax
and let us be adults about this...
we need to go over protocol.
um, how did you dispose of the
contaminated exam items
used on the sick boy?
tongue depressors, gloves,
thermometer cover?
uh, we use a, uh,
a medical waste company.
needlesticks--did you follow
c.d.c. approved guidelines?
i-i-i assume so.
i-i can check, but--
and what kind of
ventilation system do you have?
'cause you'd be amazed
how many practices
don't have a laminar flow room.
right. yes. laminar flow is good.
you don't know what that is, do you?
dr. nichols, look, i've spent hours,
uh, jumping through hoops for you--
you shouldn't have to jump through hoops.
it should all be standard.
it should all be covered
in your procedures and policy manual,
which it's required by law you have.
so i can see it?
you want to see our p-procedures
and policy manual?
yes.
okay. look, we just rented out a floor
and moved all oufiles.
so it may take a while.
okay, well, you have till
tomorrow to find it.
violet has got to know
that this is not good for her
or the practice.
says the person who
slept with my brother.
oh, now that was--
- oh, different?
- oh, yeah,
- totally and completely different...
- uh-huh.
- in every way.
- what?
- are you okay with it?
- yeah, she seems happy.
pete... seems happy, you know, i...
- hi.
can i help you?
yeah, i'm looking for dell parker.
uh, you are?
i'm heather. i'm betsey's mom.
oh. uh, yeah. his office
is at the end of the hall.
- it's the last one.
- thank you.
uh-huh.
that's heather? she's so...
she's not at all what i expected.
why did you do that?
- violet--
- i told you to tell you,
not to tell everyone.
- i have to go to the bathroom.
- what's your issue? you--
you don't want me to be happy?
of course i want you to be happy.
- i have to go to the bathroom.
- are you jealous of pete,
- is that it?
- no. no.
okay, maybe a little.
look, you have what
charlotte and i had--
the "just sex" part--
before it got all messed up
with emotions and feelings and betrayal,
which is where the "just sex"
train ultimately leads.
i don't want you to get hurt.
look, this is not
"romeo and juliet," coop.
there's not some tragedy looming.
we--we had an itch and we scratched...
and scratched... and scratched.
okay.
that's all it is.
it's just that last time... allan--
i know what i'm doing, coop.
i do.
i'm sorry i told...
everyone.
can i pee now?
yeah. yeah.
okay.
- mommy!
- hi!
i had a job interview,
and they really liked me,
so they made me take
all these different tests.
it took forever. i'm sorry.
babe... why don't you
go finish that puzzle, okay?
mommy needs to talk to daddy.
you couldn't call?
you leave your daughter alone
all day and you don't call?
- i forgot my phone.
- are you using?
no. no.
look, i know you're mad,
but i knew she was safe
with you, okay?
i-i couldn't leave to make a call.
i did not want to blow this interview.
well, she's not safe, okay?
she was exposed to the measles today,
and i-i don't even know
if s's vaccinated because,
you know, i'm not around enough,
and you...
is she vaccinated?
um...
you don't know, do you?
no.
i thought that was you.
not going home?
ugh. it's been a hell of a day.
yeah, but a cup of
non-fourth-floor coffee,
the fresh air, the ocean--
it all goes away.
look at you, all calm and buddhist.
so you and violet?
it's no big deal.
it's not a relationship.
well...
if you're happy...
things not going well
with you and kevin?
kevin and i are...
different,
and i still haven't
figured out
if that's a good thing
or a bad thing.
you want my advice?
- please.
- ignore all advice.
cooper is all over violet about
how i'm gonna destroy her life.
i just think people should be left
to decide things for themselves.
and what do you think?
- about you and kevin?
- about you and violet.
oh.
w-well, i...
the conversation is easy,
the sex is...
good.
we laugh a lot.
i mean, it's no big deal.
we're just similar and
we want the same thing,
so it's working out.
what?
you've got all that,
and it's nbig deal?
isn't that what
a relationship is?
oh, violet.
good morning.
hello, sheldon.
it's good to see you.
i've missed seeing you.
elevator rides are always
more pleasant with you.
hold the elevator.
glad to see i'm
not the only one.
so you look...
did you do something
different? y-you look great.
she did something different.
well, whatever it is,
just keep doing it.
there's a little bleeder
on the distal uterus.
got it.
hey, do you think
i missed the boat with pete?
ugh. you didn't miss e pete
boat.you dodged hurricane pete.
you really think it's
gonna end that badly?
are we talking about
the same pete?
sorry i'm late.
lots of patients to save.
well, why don't you go
save some more and let us work?
work, or discuss
dating colleagues?
which truthfully, i
concur is a bad idea.
however, since this is
our last case together, monty,
it won't be a problem for us.
she's involved with
a cop who has a gun.
yeah, so you better
watch out.
a cop? are you
really dating a cop?
i am not intimidated
by a man with a gun.
are you?
intimidad? hardly.
no, i was thinking
of their propensity
for depression and
divorce and alcoholism.
yeah, as opposed
to doctors,
who have a stable,
stress-free life.
true, true, but i could see
how a cop fulfills
some kind of base fantasy
for a woman like you.
wow. did you miss the
sexual harassment seminar?
well, i meant it
as a compliment.
i mean, she's a rich,
classy woman.
he's your version
of the pool boy.
okay, enough.
you are here to watch.
you know what i got here?
i'm not in the mood, charlotte.
public health notifications,
isolation requirements,
incident reports,
c.d.c. surveys.
we all have jobs to do.
i have jobs i'm not able to do
because i'm dealing with
the mess you made.
and i have a mom who feels like
she lost one son to autism
and may be losing
another one to the measles,
and she's got another one
sitting out here exposed,
and maybe i'm just not
persuasive enough,
but he's vulnerable,
and she's not gonna let me
do anything about it.
so i'm really sorry if i
piled on some paperwork for you,
but i don't need crap
from you right now.
he can't breathe.
full custody?
you want full custody?
i'm trying
to keep betsey safe.
now? now that i've changed?
now that i'm finally
getting it together?
you left her here all day.
but i got the job, dell.
okay, but...
how long until
you blow it off
because, you know,
you hate it
or you're bored or
you start using again?
i got the job,
and then i got home
and i got this letter.
and you know
what i wanted to do,
but i didn't.
i freaked, but then i looked
at betsey, and i didn't use.
i came here to talk to you
about what's best for her.
i'm glad
u didn't get high.
but it doesn't change things.
all you see is that girl
from the valley
that you
used to get high with.
i stopped.
well, you might have been
stronger than me then,
but don't forget
who got me started, okay?
because i wasn't
always like this.
just don't make me spend
every last dime that i have
trying to fight you.
it's gonna push me
back over the edge.
every bit of tissue
around her ovaries is friable.
i can't place a stitch
without her starting to bleed.
how much chemo did you give her?
i did what i had to
to save her life.
no, there's too much blood.
i've gotta clear the field.
- damn it.
- you need to implant the tissue now.
everything i touch bleeds.
we can't do this.
you have time and to
complete the implant.
back off, wyatt.
i can't see the target
through the blood...
and her pressure's dropping.
if you don't
get this done now,
she loses any chance
of ever having a baby.
if i don't stop and we don
have to worry about a baby.
addison.
all right. we're done.
wyatt, shut your mouth
while i save her life.
it won't pass.
his throat's too swollen.
get the ber-optic scope now.
we gotta ventilate him.
heart rate is dropping.
sats are bottoming out.
where's the damn scope?
it's coming, cooper.
open up a surgical tray.
i'm gonna crike him.
hold this.
what--what--what is that?
what--what are you gonna do?
just wait, cooper.
the scope's coming.
his heart's 40.
i'm doing this. betadine.
wait. wait!
slowly. easy does it.
almost there. almost there.
i got it.
sounds good.
he's gonna be okay?
set the vent at an f102
of 100, rate of 24.
i need a minute.
hey, i'll watch 'em
for a minute.
hey.
come here.
come here for a second.
get the hell
away from my son.
mommy!
- you have to stop.
- your son is dying in there.
get the hell away from me.
- mrs. perkins, please.
- no!
well.
are u okay?
the vaccine is safe.
you don't know.
it is.
look at him
and tell me it is.
vaccines are the
standard of care.
dr. freedman did something
that was medically necessary.
he assaulted my son.
and i am going to sue
this hospital, so help me,
if something happens to him.
i did what i felt i had to.
it wasn't yours to do.
it wasn't yos to do.
code blue, p.i.c.u.
i went under thinking about
the crib in the yellow room.
i wish we could've done more.
i know i should just be
grateful for being alive.
we all wanted to help you.
and i'm not giving up,
claudia.
i'll be back later, okay?
nai, would you go over post-op
instructions wh claudia?
i'll be right back.
what was that about?
that was about
my embarrassment
for picking the wrong
person for the job.
you're blaming this on me?
the chemo ravaged
her entire body.
there weren't 2 square
centimeters of healthy tissue
that could've held a suture
let alone an implant.
you talk like
you searched exhaustively.
what are you talking about?
you didn't push.
i agreed to do a totally
experimental procedure that,
going in, we all knew
was a longshot,
and when i felt the risks
to the patient's life
outweighed the potential
for success,
i chose to save the patient.
you had time.
you could've controlled
the bleeding
and implanted the tissue,
but you hate me,
so you didn't want to be told
what to do, so you stopped.
you wanted to prove
that you knew better.
i'm no surgeon, but i
think there was time.
well, i'm sorry
if what happened in there
didn't produce the results
that you wanted for some study,
but i made the right call.
you really believe that?
- dr. bennett.
- i got it. i got it.
okay.
everything is in here.
all right? protocols for
workspace contamination,
follow-ups for patients
with positive labs,
blood draw procedures that
include responses to needlesticks.
okay.
wait, that's it?
you...
you're not gonna read it
and ask me about our policies
on work-related injuries or--
i'm sure you did
a very thorough job.
you knew that i wouldn't
be able to find it,
and you knew that i would kill
myself trying to come up with it.
well, by law, your office
needed to have that.
- now you do.
- you enjoy this, don't you,
the power?
coming in here,
pushing me around...
oh, i...
that's not true at all.
i've been nothing
but professional.
you've been a bully.
you just can't stand
real doctors, can you?
do you...
know what it's like
to have everyone hate you
before they even meet you,
to walk in the door
and have everyone assume
that you're awful?
i don't know what some
evil public servant
did to you in a past life,
but i'm here to do a job,
a job i think is important.
if there were
a serious outbreak here,
you'd want someone like me,
because i am a real doctor
who chose this job
to help people.
all right, well, maybe
i was wrong, but...
for the past two days,
you haven't even
looked me in the eye
or even acknowledged
that i'm a human being.
what is your problem?
for two days, i've been thinking
your lips would taste like chocolate,
and i couldn't look at them.
i'm--i'm--i'really sorry
that i misjudged you.
do you believe that
people can change?
ugh! look, if one more person
butts in and tries to tell me
what pete is and
what we should be doing--
wow.
uh, i was talking
about heather.
oh. okay.
so you and heather...
okay, well, heather says that
she's not the person
she used to be,
and...
that by taking
custody of betsey,
i'm punishing her
for her past.
are you?
i just don't know
if i can believe it,
that she's different now.
well, you have to
protect your daughter.
right.
but if you're asking me
if i think people can change,
if i didn't believe that,
i couldn't do what i do.
when you look at
betsey and heather,
and yotake away
what you want,
what's best
for your daughter?
what?
i don't think
it's ridiculous...
the idea that you and me--
that...
we could be more than sex.
pete--
don't think about
what cooper would say
or sam or naomi
or anybody.
just think about...
what you think.
why does it have to
be a crazy idea?
asystole. i can't
find a pulse.
resuming c.p.r.
another round of epi.
cooper, we've done everything.
it's been over a halhour.
where's the atropine?
come on!
it's time to call it.
i'm running the code.
i decide when we're done.
please...
don't stop.
time of death--3:37.
michael?
he just learned
to tie his shoes.
he can't be gone.
not like this.
oh, michael.
oh, michael. michael.
i thought...
it was gonna be...
like a cold.
i was trying
to protect him.
you did everything
you could.
what are you
doing in here?
i was thinking about
the two doctors
that came before addison...
about you...
and them leaving.
people can change,
violet.
isn't that
what you told dell?
yes, you can change.
i-i don't know if i can change
what i know about you...
how i look at you.
what about what you feel?
well, i can't
separate that out.
what i feel is aombination
of all those things,
and i can't help it.
look what happened
between you and meg.
i screwed that up, but it was
wrong before i screwed it up.
i like what we have, pete.
i mean, i...
i love what we have.
but i don't...
want it to be more.
wouldn't that be
a good thing--
what we have,
but...
more?
i don't know.
what are you doing here?
come to get evidence?
there's no needles,
dell, no booze.
- hey, beautiful.
- hi, daddy.
i came to apologize.
look...
you were right, okay?
i-i should've called,
and i should've been more
responsible about the vaccines--
not about that.
for getting you started...
addicted.
i should have kept you away
from my friends back then.
i'm sorry, heather.
well,
i'm doing better now.
you know,
we're doing better.
i know. i can see.
but i need
more time with her,
something more permanent.
dell--
maybe we can...
work it out,
you and me, without court.
okay?
i just...
i need to know
she's safe.
apparently, i'm a misogynistic,
manipulative son of a bitch...
and ungrateful.
you agreed to do something
you didn't want to do,
and i should've
been more gracious.
you protecting my honor?
i don't like bullies.
maybe he was right.
oh, i hate him. i hate his
arrogance and his pushing and...
if claudia was my patient, maybe
i'd have done the same thing.
pushed to ma it work?
addison...
you saved her life.
look...
if you want to work
with wyatt again,
work with wyatt again.
don't not do it
because of what i say.
you comfortable with that?
i'm not comfortable
thinking that my advice
colors what you say
or, you know, what you do.
hate him for yourself.
or not.
want to get a drink?
i could use one.
no. i am going to
take my own advice
and decide something
for myself.
come on in.
um...
i wanted to finish
the conversation
from the elevator.
i, uh...
i meant what i
said, violet.
i like you.
and i'd like for us
to be friends.
and i'm not exactly sure
how one goes about doing that,
because i'd like to get
to know you better.
not go out on a date,
just go out, as friends
and without all that
pressure of sex
and dating and...
i just...
i think we'd
be good friends.
i think you're right.
hey, kevin.
it's me.
yeah, i, um...
i miss you.
welcome to www.1000fr.com