Hey, I'm Chuck.
Here's a couple of things
you might need to know
or maybe you just forgot.
I had a fiancée.
Now, she thinks I'm dead.
Alex.
You got a daughter, Casey.
Do you think Ellie's happy
in your marriage? Of course.
Why? Did she say something?
This is about your
father, Ellie.
There are some
very bad people
looking for him,
including a man named
John Casey.
I knew it! You downloaded
the Intersect 2.0.
The Intersect...
it can have a negative affect
on the brain.
Your dreams are
all proof of stress
likely leading to serious
mental deterioration.
So, what did you want
to tell me?
Is it about the doctor?
He said that... I'm fine.
Wait a minute,
you dreamt Shaw was alive?
Chuck, you saw him die.
I call it the Governor.
It governs my neural network
and helps control the
power of the Intersect.
Could something like that
work for the 2.0?
It will. I'm going
to make you one.
So, how's everything, uh,
how's everything coming?
Same as the last
time you asked me.
Can I get you anything,
like a, like a juice?
Or coffee?
Maybe a breakfast sandwich?
I'm fine, Charles.
Just relax.
"Relax." That's good.
That's... that's good.
Dad, is this really
going to work?
This whole,
this whole Governor thingy?
I'm still alive, aren't I?
Look, based on
the schematics
of my own Governor,
I'm going to create
a new one that'll
help control
the Intersect 2.0 before...
Before what?
Before I go nuts?
Because that's exactly
what the Ring wants.
Son, your brain is working fine
so far, right?
Who wouldn't be
paranoid in your shoes?
Your cover's blown,
your secret base discovered,
your dead partner
and girlfriend's ex-lover
was a double agent.
Way to talk me down, Dad.
What I, what I'm trying
to say is...
Your courage makes me
very proud.
But there's some battles
you have to walk away from.
What are you saying- run?
Turn my back
on everyone that I care about?
There may come a time when
if you want to protect them...
...you have to go.
Go where?
Vacation.
Dad was just saying
that he thinks
I might need to get out
of here and take a little break.
Well, he's right. You've
been a little nervous lately.
So, is this what you two
have been working on?
Yeah.
Little family heirloom
Dad's just
sprucing up for me.
Well, I'm su
he doesn't need you
looking over his shoulder.
You could use some fresh air.
She's right, Charles.
Smell the roses.
I'd really rather not, Dad.
Seasonal allergies-
you know, runs in the family.
Listen to the man.
He knows what's
best for you.
Need any help?
Dude? You don't look
so hot, buddy.
I mean, compared to your
normal level of hotness.
Lost a little sizzle.
I'm looking for my wife, Morgan.
She didn't come
home last night.
You don't say?
I do say.
Why would I know where Ellie is?
Why'd you think there was
something wrong
with our marriage?
No reason.
You know, I just kind of...
Don't B.S. me, little man.
If something is
up with Ellie,
I want to know about it now.
Oh, boy.
She's having an affair.
She's cheating
on you, bro.
What? That's impossible.
Casey intercepted an illicit
phone message, and
he played it for me.
What? Ellie would never...
Devon...
Whoa.
I'm sorry.
You just called me "Devon."
Yeah, well, this is
no time for frivolity.
I really need to see you.
Devon thinks that I'm
at the hospital.
It's just, it's getting
harder and harder to lie.
I know.
How could she do this to us?
I need to call my wife.
Yeah.
I gotta get in on
some of this Ellie action.
That is why I choose
not to get married.
That's why I ward them off.
Hey, I need to
call my husband.
It's weird,
I'm not getting a signal.
It's blocked.
We can't have enemy operatives
like John Casey
tracking you here.
He's on the loose?
I thought... He had
fled by the time our team
got to your apartment.
I have to call Chuck.
I have to protect him.
Ellie...
We're in the process of
bringing your brother in.
You're safe here,
and John Casey knows better
than to show his face
anytime soon.
One apple pie
and one cup of coffee.
Black and bitter.
Actually, I didn't order yet.
I know. I ordered
for you. It's easy.
You always get
the same thing.
And you always sit in the
same seat facing the door.
Creature of habit.
What can I say?
What happened to your face?
Hmm?
Kitchen accident.
It's nothing.
Hey, how'd that, uh,
criminal psych final
of yours go? Good.
Piece of cake. I'm all set
to graduate next week.
Oh. It's like your days
of slinging pie are numbered.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure
the next girl
gets your order right.
You won't even miss me, John.
Thanks, Alex.
All of these people, any of
whom could be Ring agents.
Oh, come on. You've got to
switch off your spy mode.
You're going to drive
yourself crazy.
Yeah, well, I've been down
that road before, haven't I?
Well, the CIA shrink said
that you have nothing to
worry about, remember? Right.
Other than the Ring
trying to kill my father
or me imaging that Shaw
is still out there and trying
to kill me.
Look, your father is safe.
And not only that, but
he is here with you,
which is great.
And Shaw?
Shaw is dead.
Look, I know what
you went through,
but you really have to
start putting it behind you.
What if I can't?
Mmm, then there is always
blueberries.
How is this possibly
suppose to make...?
Oh, my God, these are
amazing blueberries.
Mm-hmm. Wait till you
try them with cream.
Mm, be right back.
What?
Beautiful day, isn't it?
Well, you have
a good one.
Thank you.
Oh, God...
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
Sa...
* *
Excuse me.
I must be losing my mind.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
You're sure this isn't just another
one of your Intersect dreams?
Yes, as a matter
of fact, I am sure.
Okay, Shaw is alive.
It was like he
was taunting me.
We have to call Beckman.
I already tried.
Her assistant said
that she's "indisposed."
"Indisposed"?
What is that suppose to mean?
Th-The guy that I killed
is back from the dead.
A guy who, keep in mind,
is a Ring operative,
who knows our covers, where
we live, where Castle is.
What station did you see him in?
North Hollywood. Why?
The time?
Maybe half an hour ago.
North or southbound?
South.
Any of this look familiar?
Are you kidding?
It's Bartowski running
around like a chicken
with its head cut off.
Slow it down.
Punch in.
Right there, Dad.
Oh, my God. Daniel.
Uh, do we know what
station he got off at?
One sec. Let me run the
facial recognition software.
Hollywood and Western.
Bingo.
Where did he exit?
There he is.
What the hell is he doing?
We need to follow Shaw
and take him down.
Yeah, that's one way
of looking at it.
The other option is, they're
leading you into a trap.
It's not like
we're going in empty-handed.
You know how I feel
about this, Charles.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do,
but I don't have a choice.
That's exactly what
the Ring wants you to think.
There's always
a choice.
What choice would that be, Dad?
To run away?
I'm not you, okay?
I'm not going to spend
the rest of my life in hiding.
I can't leave the
ones I love behind.
Let's go.
* *
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What are you...?
...doing here, man?
My life is over.
My wife has given herself
to another man.
Hey, your wife has
given you a pass.
You're now free
to go out and mount
whomever you want wish to.
If he's been doing
more mounting, he wouldn't
be in this situation.
You think that my wife
is unfaithful to me
because I'm not satisfying her?
Son, while you're
wasting your time
at the gym or the hospital,
your wife is at home alone,
unoccupied.
So, she hired herself
a pinch hitter.
Still can't believe
that your missus is taking on
new customers.
It's my dream come true.
Ellie is exactly like Chuck,
but with lady parts.
Okay. I'm going to go now.
Whoa, whoa. Come on.
That's the spirit, son.
Show the old lady
you know how to swing that bat.
Nice work, guys- awesome.
What?
No, not you, Awesome.
That's awesome.
General, I want to thank you
in advance for your testimony.
Now, it's my understanding
that, uh, you've been in charge
of the Intersect project
ever since it accidentally
was put into a civilian-
a one Charles Bartowski.
Is that correct?
Yes, sir. That is correct.
Is it also correct that
the project has fallen
well short of its
original expectations?
Yes, sir. Also correct.
But if I may add,
Agents Bartowski,
Walker and Colonel Casey
have proven
to be an excellent
albeit unorthodox team.
Your mission is to
grab Shaw or kill him,
whichever's quicker.
Hey, open sesame.
Okay, we'll split up.
Each take a floor.
Okay.
General Meriwether,
Members of the Tribunal,
you must understand,
Agent Bartowski has in many ways
exceeded expectations.
I am not denying that the road
has been long and rocky.
but after three years,
Charles Bartowski is poised
to become the weapon we have
always dreamed of.
Justin, what's going on?
We've been breached.
It's Casey, isn't it?
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you, Ellie.
We can handle
John Casey.
You're supposed to be upstairs.
Searched the whole floor.
Nobody here.
There's something wrong
with this place.
Hey, look. It's a government-
grade biometric scanner.
You'll never get through that.
Come on.
Let's go!
Casey, this is not a Ring base.
It's one of ours.
We've got to go find Chuck.
Justin...
Justin?
Chuck?
Ellie? Ellie, what are you
doing here?
What are you doing here?!
You just punched
a person. Chuck,
I thought you quit
kung fu in the third grade.
I... Look, I'll explain later.
Right now we have
to get out of here.
Come on. No, Chuck,
you don't understand.
You've been brought here
for your protection.
Justin is my CIA handler.
CIA handler?
You don't understand, okay?
This guy is not CIA. Everyone
Security! in this building
works for an evil organization.
Chuck, wait!
In conclusion, General,
I would stake my reputation
on the success
of Agent Bartowski.
As you were saying,
General Beckman?
What the hell are you doing,
Bartowski?!
Chuck, what the
hell is going on?
Apparently, I have no idea.
Where's my sister?
She's being escorted back
to her residence.
What was she doing her
You are dismissed.
General, what the hell
is going on?
I don't know how else
to explain it, Chuck,
but all our ass...
careers are on the line.
The committee is here
to determine if the Intersect
project is a liability.
Liability? Let me talk to them.
Shaw is somewhere
in this building.
We saw him.
If there is one thing
you can do to protect
the Intersect project,
it's keep your mouth shut.
Agents Walker, Casey
and Bartowski,
it's been brought to this
committee's attention
the Intersect is unstable,
expensive,
and most of all, dangerous.
That's outrageous.
Sit down, Chuck!
I'm sorry, General.
General, this is crazy.
Provide one shred of evidence.
Who said this?
I did.
Hello, Chuck.
Sarah.
Shaw?
Ladies and gentleman,
this man that stands before you
is a Ring operative.
He kidnapped me and he drugged
me and he tried to kill me!
All of that is
completely true,
except for the
killing part.
In fact, I was sanctioned
by this committee.
Why was I not apprised
of this,
General Meriwether?
Continue, Agent Shaw.
I was acting as a double agent,
working within the Ring.
That is, until Chuck shot me.
He's lying! Do not listen
to a word that he says!
I came here today
to make one thing
perfectly clear.
Charles Bartowski
is an American hero.
He didn't ask for the Intersect.
And it's not Chuck's fault
that his brain is deteriorating.
Excuse me,
Agent Bartowski was given
a full psychological exam,
and he was
cleared for all field work.
Sarah...
Do you want to tell her
the truth or should I?
What is he talking
about, Chuck?
Dr. Dreyfus's report.
"The subject's mental decline
"is both inevitable
"and irreversible.
"Agent Bartowski's mind
will soon succumb to paranoia,
dementia, psychosis,
possibly worse."
I can understand why
your boyfriend didn't want
to worry you.
Sarah, I was gonna tell you.
It's my recommendation
that the Intersect project
be aborted.
Before any decisions are made,
this committee
needs to review the Intersect's
successful missions.
Hugo Panzer: taken out
by Bartowski's team
with a combination of a fencing
foil, nunchuks and turbulence.
Alexis White died while trying
to elude capture from...
Guys, Casey, Sarah...
Zip it, Bartowski.
Figure a way out later.
No, he's, he's,
he's an Intersect!
Daniel Shaw is
an Intersect!
Sit down, Agent Bartowski!
It's okay, General.
I'm glad
you're seeing this.
See? He's not in control.
I'm in complete control.
I realize that what
I'm about to do right now
might come across as being
some kind of insane gesture
or maybe a completely
insane gesture,
but because I am
in fact saying,
and I am certain that
Daniel Shaw is an Intersect,
I'm just gonna have
to prove it to you.
Chuck, no!
You're supposed to catch it!
Guards, remove Mr. Bartowski!
No! He's an Intersect!
Sarah, I'm sorry.
These proceedings are adjourned
until further notice.
We gotta get out
of here.
We walked
into a trap.
What about Chuck?
Nothing we can do for him.
Not after that stunt. We
have to call Washington
and tell them what
is really going on.
Most of Washington
was in that room.
Shaw and the Ring have
taken over the CIA.
He's got the whole chain of
command eating out of his hand.
God only knows how many
Ring agents are on the inside.
It's only a matter of time
before they burn us, too.
So, what? You're just gonna run?
It's not just us
they're gonna come after.
They're gonna come after
the people we care about.
You coming?
No.
Everything I care about
is inside this building.
Good luck, Agent Walker...
Sarah.
Ellie.
Devon, I need to talk to you.
Where have you been all night?
Okay, honey,
I- I need you to listen
to me really carefully;
I have been keeping
a secret from you,
and I feel horrible about it.
No. Stop, okay?
I just, I don't
think I can hear
the words right now.
It's my fault.
I haven't been stepping up
to the plate.
Devon, I need you to be strong.
I can be stronger.
I can superset.
I will double my workouts...
Devon, stop it!
Chuck is in trouble
with the CIA!
What?
Chuck,
our Chuck
punched a CIA agent
in the face today, and they
are holding him right now.
You mean, you haven't
been cheating on me?
What? Devon, what
are you talking about?
No. Listen to me.
I think
he's gonna need a lawyer.
No, no, Chuck has been
with the CIA for years.
I'm so glad
you finally know.
What a relief
it is to talk...
You don't know.
Oh, no, I just told you.
You are gonna tell me
everything you know right now.
Order's up.
Alex...
You come here for the pie,
too, Agent Casey?
I think it's
the best in town.
Hey, guy.
And you brought
a friend.
Table for two, please.
Right this way.
Sergeant Mosley, you're needed
in the conference room ASAP.
That means run.
Follow you where, Dad?
Chuck!
Here you go.
Thank you
very much.
You're welcome. Enjoy.
Pretty girl.
So much to live for.
Be a shame if she didn't.
Not hungry?
Why don't you put your hands
on the table, John?
Good.
Mmm.
Too much nutmeg.
You're a smart guy, John.
I'm sure you figured it out
by now.
You're coming with me.
I gotta say, John,
I never figured you for a dad.
Well, I'm not a very good one.
What are you doing?!
I'm saving your life.
Put me down!
Hey! Ow!
Chuck, wait!
Where are you going?
Sarah, I have to leave.
My-my-my dad is coming.
Oh, you can't.
You have to stay and fight.
If you run, they'll
put a burn notice
on you,
and you'll be running forever.
We have to move
right now!
You can't do this.
If you run, there's a
bull's-eye on your back.
They will never ever
stop looking for you.
If you stay, everyone you love
will be in danger.
You have to choose who you
want to protect: you or her.
Dad, please don't leave...
Right now, Charles!
You have to run
to protect her!
I'm sorry, Sarah.
I'm sorry,
but if I have to choose,
I will always choose
to protect you.
Sorry, Alex, but this is
for your own safety.
You have to believe
I would never hurt you.
No, just forcibly kidnap me.
Here...
take it.
This is a key
to my locker
at the Burbank Buy More.
Everything inside is yours now.
Look, Mr. Casey,
if you want me to hear you,
I'd step out of the car and talk
so that I don't feel like
my life is in jeopardy.
Please?
Okay.
Alex, wait! Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait! No, no, no, no...
Wait! Come on!
I got an A
in my self-defense class!
Alex...
Alex, I'm your father.
That's impossible!
My father's dead.
He was a war hero.
He died before
I was even born.
No, I didn't.
Stop it.
You were named
after your dad, Alex.
You're named after me.
My real name's Alex Coburn.
Please, you have to trust me.
You have to get
to your mom and disappear.
Go, Alex.
Run!
CIA! John Casey, put your hands
on top of your head!
That whole Generalissimo thing?
I was undercover on a mission.
That's it.
That's all I know, babe.
Oh, and you can
blame the CIA
for my bachelor party.
Stripper?
She was an agent.
Told you I didn't cheat.
Faithful.
I can't believe that my brother
and Sarah are spies.
How is my dad
involved in all this?
I, uh, have pockets
of missing knowledge.
I didn't want to know
'cause I didn't want to have
to lie to you, babe.
Devon, an actual legitimate
answer exists
as to why my father has
been missing my entire life,
and you didn't think
to ask that question?
Correct.
You need to find me somebody
who knows
a lot more than you do
right now.
Morgan Grimes,
the boy that took
my pillow as his date
to Junior Prom
knows more about my family
being spies than I do.
Here.
It's valerian
root tea,
and it'll give your brain
a lovely, soothing bath.
I don't want a soothing brain
bath, Morgan. I want answers.
Startling revelation,
yeah, I know.
Well, Chuck has been with the
Company for quite a while now.
Suffice to say all
is in hand, so...
No, Morgan, all is
not in hand, okay?
The bad guys have my brother.
Hold on a second.
Nobody said anything
about bad guys.
What bad guys? The Ring? What?
The Ring; a nefarious
criminal organization
hell-bent on world
domination. All I know is that
Justin told me that John Casey
is a double agent.
And he's here trying
to gather information
about my dad, but if
Chuck is an agent, too,
then-then maybe
Casey lied to him
and turned him somehow?
Our Eagle Scout Chuck
turned to the dark side?
No, not gonna happen.
And any suggestions
that Colonel Jonathan Casey's
character's in question,
well, I would stake my entire...
albeit.. okay,
thin reputation
on the fact that he is
Uncle Sam's
most faithful servant.
Fine. Then one of you
geniuses explain to me
why the CIA is holding my
brother against his will.
I don't know,
but I will find out.
You wanted
to see me...
sir?
I'd be remiss if I didn't
tell you you looked
great, Walker.
Love suits you, I guess.
Shut up, Shaw.
This is crap and you know it.
Only two people know what
happened that day in Paris.
It's your word against mine.
Chuck saw what happened.
We all know that you tried
to kill me.
But Chuck has become
an unreliable witness.
His mind has
been compromised
by the Intersect.
And now that he's escaped,
he seems so guilty.
I'm sorry that you had to learn
about his mental deterioration
in such a public forum.
Sad that he
never told you
in a more
intimate setting...
Sam.
You're gonna put
your hands up
and you're gonna walk
out that door
and you're gonna tell
the generals
exactly what happened in Paris.
So move it.
I knew you'd bite.
Drop it, Agent Walker!
Arrest her.
She's gone rogue.
It's a shame.
I remember when nothing
affected you.
Now you're as emotional
as your boyfriend.
Sarah and Casey will know
how to help Chuck, okay?
You just go check the
dojo. There's a dojo?
General Beckman?
Where's Bartowski?
I'd hoped to find him in Castle.
I think there's been some
sort of mix-up. Chuck is being
held by the CIA. Maybe you could
actually help clear this up.
This is great. General
Beckman, open the door.
General, what's happening?
Open the door right now!
They're shutting down
the entire Intersect project,
including myself.
They apprehended Colonel Casey.
Agent Walker is in
custody. Bartowski
escaped this facility;
he is a wanted man.
I need you
to find him.
As much as it pains me
to admit,
you are our only hope!
You are our only hope!
Get your hands off me!
Dude, did she mean
you or me?
* *
Finished it.
Your Governor.
* *
It will activate
immediately.
Better?
Yeah. Yeah. Thanks.
Cell? That's not off
the grid, Charles.
Dad, it's, it's Morgan.
I never got a chance
to say good-bye to him.
Hey, buddy,
listen, I gotta go away.
I gotta go on a trip
with my dad,
and, and I could be gone
for a really long time.
Yeah, well, stop.
Sarah's in CIA custody.
Casey has been taken.
I think they got Beckman, too.
What? When did this
happen? Hey, Dad! No!
Dad! Dad, we have
to go back.
Shaw has got Sarah!
And that's no accident!
He doesn't want her;
he's trying to trap you.
He's after this.
I'm your father;
you cannot ask me.
Please do not ask me to put
my own son in jeopardy.
I can't just walk away, Dad!
Why did you come back this time?
You came back
because you wanted
to protect Ellie
and me.
Because you knew no matter
how far you ran,
you could never live with
yourself if something happened
to somebody that you loved.
* *
If we do this...
we gotta be smart.
Not think emotional!
We can do this.
We're Bartowskis.
Ellie.
Chuck, I thought
that the CIA still had you.
I wish I had time to explain.
You know what, Chuck?
It takes just as long to say
that as to tell me
what the hell is going on.
We need your help.
Who's we, Chuck? The government?
The answer is no.
No, we need your help.
Dad? I thought that you left.
El, I know
you got a lot
of questions,
but right now
you have the answers
that we need.
This is it.
This is where
I would meet Justin.
This is our
rendezvous point.
There's got
to be more to it, okay?
Shaw has to have
another location.
This can't be
a dead end.
What are you two
whispering about?
No more secrets.
May-maybe you're forgetting
something.
Walk us through
what would happen
when you met Justin.
I don't know, Dad,
this is it.
I would, I would sit here
on this bench and we would talk.
And then he'd
get up, he'd leave.
He'd go over there.
Through that door.
The subway again.
Hey, we need you
to stay here, okay?
You just stay
right here on this bench.
If we're not back
in 20 minutes, run.
Dad, I need
to hear you say it.
I need to know that there's
a reason that you left us.
It's a long story.
I want to tell you everything,
but I gotta,
I gotta take care
of this first, okay?
This is the last time
I'm gonna walk
away from you.
I promise.
I love you, baby.
You're not gonna
get away with this, Shaw.
Yes, I will.
Love-soaked Bartowski
will try to come save you,
and this time
I'll be ready
for him and
his father.
Mu-ha-ha.
Over here. Over here.
Dad...
This control panel
was manufactured
by McTiernan Industries.
It's a Ring subsidiary.
Fake wall.
Aces, Charles.
All right.
Shaw, Bartowski's
infiltrated the base.
Of course he did.
Why won't your boyfriend
ever think
with an organ besides his heart?
No, sir, not this one.
Bartowski and his father
found the other base,
the Ring base.
Triggered
the silent alarm.
Damn it.
Hmm. Don't know
when it happened,
but our boy
became a man.
Bartowski's a spy.
Picked a good
one, Walker...
finally.
Oh, my God.
Dad, this is what I've
been having dreams about.
Dr. Kowambe's medical
experiments;
cellular regeneration.
It's identical. They did it.
I can't believe
the Ring built one.
They must have saved
Shaw's life, and then...
and then turned him
into an Intersect.
I was right.
Dad, the lab is all
the proof that we need.
It'll vindicate my team,
Shaw will be exposed.
Exposed? Exposed as what,
uh, the Intersect?
I see you got a fancy
new watch there, Chuck.
Do you mind
if I try it on?
Why don't you come over
here and take it from me?
Actually, I think I'll have
my friend grab it for me.
I don't need a watch
to beat you, Shaw.
Come on.
Aren't you a little curious?
I know I am.
Don't you want
to know how your Intersect
stacks up against mine?
You're right, Chuck.
The fight will be incredible.
We're totally equal now.
Nothing separates us.
Though... there's one thing
that is different.
You can't function
when your emotions have
been compromised.
Don't worry about that.
I've never been more calm.
Really? How you feeling now?
* *
Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad!
Dad, hey, hey, hey,
hang on! Hang on!
Hang on! Stay with
me! Stay with me!
You're gonna be okay,
okay? I promise.
You're special, son.
Always remember...
you're special.
Check out the fresh fish.
Wait here.
Hello, miss.
Hi.
I was wondering
if I could
service you in some way.
Yes, I guess. Um...
could you tell me where I could
find John Casey's locker?
What exactly is your
relationship to Mr. Casey?
If I may be so bold.
He's my... friend,
and he asked me
to get something
out of his locker.
He gave me his key.
That doesn't look like
one of our keys. Shh!
Maybe you're talking about
a different John Casey.
Ours doesn't really have
any friends.
Thank you, guys.
I'll take it from here.
Morgan Grimes,
assistant manager.
Hi. Alex.
Alex, take a walk with me?
Did you say that belongs
to John Casey?
Yes. Um, he does
work here, right?
Of course he does.
Yeah, yeah.
Who do you work for?
It's okay;
you can tell me.
I'm on the inside.
Um, the Pie Shack
in Silverlake.
Yeah, okay.
Come on.
Lady, please, I have
a very high level
of clearance, okay?
Listen, I can't let you walk
back there, have access
to John Casey's locker
without knowing what's going on.
I'm sorry. My hands are tied.
I don't know what's going on.
All I know is that
this customer John
kidnaps me, and then he tells me
that he's my father,
and now there's
men chasing us.
And I'm sorry. I know
that I don't
really know you.
I'm just a little
confused right now.
No, no, that's okay. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you upset.
Look, miss,
I promise you this:
if John Casey said he's your
father, then it's the truth.
I trust that man with my life.
You have nothing
to be afraid of.
Not if he's your father.
And in fact, this store's
as safe as anywhere,
provided you stay away
from those two.
Yeah?
Let's go see
what's in that locker, all
right? Are you okay? Yeah?
This isn't a Buy More key,
so I'll have to use mine.
Assistant manager.
That's why
I have this.
So you know.
Okay. Avid reader.
Oh, my. Whoa!
How long it's been
in there. Yeah.
Oh, check it out.
That's gonna work.
Oh, actually, you might
want to stand back.
This could explode.
Ooh... okay.
He said this is for you?
Yeah. What is it?
He must have been saving
for, like, ever.
We don't pay that much here.
Morgan, Ellie called.
We need to talk.
Yeah, shoot, buddy.
Whatever you got to say,
you can say
in front of her.
She's one of us.
Not this.
Try not to spend it
all in one place.
Chuck, what happened?
Are you okay?
Where's your dad?
I'm sorry, guys.
Shaw has won.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry, buddy,
we'll get Shaw.
No, we won't.
Love the new defeatist
attitude, Chuck.
Suits you.
We'll be leaving
momentarily
for the CIA
detention facility.
These people won't be seeing
the light of day for some time.
Enjoy this ride together...
bond.
share all the war stories...
because as soon
as the truck stops,
so do your lives.
We'll figure something out.
It's over.
There is no one left to save us.
I'm following them now.
Are you ready?
We're ready.
I'm warning you, Ellie,
if we do this,
there is no turning back-
our lives are changed forever.
I'm asking one final time.
Are you sure
this is what you want?
Yes.
Let's do this.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com