TOP SECRET LOCATION, 1994
I yield, sensei.
You are unfocused, again.
- I yield.
- Too slow.
Again!
Your center is filled
with conflict, John.
Until you find your calm center,
you will never beat me.
You can't beat
a winning smile, John.
Not in retail sales.
You need to show your customers
those pearly whites.
Well, soon-to-be pearly whites.
You need to bleach them.
Just show them you
got a pulse, Casey.
Give 'em a "Hey, how ya doin?"
Or a "Put 'em there, partner. "
Or "You bet!"
Walk on back to the back...
You bet.
Thanks for the
tips, Emmett.
Yup. John Casey
scares me.
Well, that's what happens
when you bottle up
your feelings like that.
You wake up one day and
you're a seething mass of pain.
Right. Hey, what's going
on with you and Jill?
Ah, yeah.
My, my pain.
Let's talk about that.
- Where is she?
- Big house.
Bought a big house.
Bought a real big house
up the river.
Oh, that sounds
really pretty.
You guys are, uh,
"done" done, right?
Yeah, I mean, I just figured
out hanging out with Jill
- was more about closing a door than opening one.
- I get it. I get it.
Listen, the old flame can burn,
right? But I bet you, it made
you even more sure who
the right girl is for you.
Ah, speak of the smoking
hot angel.
- I'll get out of here.
- Yeah.
Hey, Sarah.
Chuck, does
the Global Launch Agency
mean anything to you?
GLA? Sure, they've
sent probes
to every planet
except Pluto.
Although, Pluto's not officially
a planet anymore,
which really bums me out.
That's true.
Space camp is where
all the cool kids go.
GLA also conducts
top secret research
for the NSA.
Most of our surveillance
and weapons tracking technology is developed there.
We picked up intel that
someone might try to penetrate
one of the lab's
secure facilities.
I want you and the Intersect
to surveil the facility.
See if there's anyone inside
who you flash on.
Another mission already?
Is there a problem,
Mr. Bartowski?
No, no.
No, I was just, you know,
I was kind of hoping
for some downtime.
We'll take it from here, ma'am.
Aw, you need a little break,
Bartowski?
Yeah, that'd be nice.
I mean, finding out
Jill was Fulcrum
was a bit of a shock
to the system, you know?
I guess I wouldn't mind
some time
to sort out my feelings.
Sure thing, Chuck.
I'll just call all the criminals and rogue spies
and let
them know to hold on a sec,
'cause Chuck Bartowski
needs some time to sort out his lady feelings.
Ease up, Casey.
Look, Chuck, we know how hard
this has been for you,
but maybe a new mission is
exactly what you need right now.
Great, new mission
in the surveillance van.
Very exciting.
You're on an open mic, Chuck.
Am I? That's, that's
good to know.
Thanks for telling me that.
Uh, I have all the entrances
and exits covered.
It looks pretty quiet.
You're not seeing anything?
Nothing. No flashes, nothing.
I'm all clear here.
All clear.
Security's tight.
Close the west lab door, Chuck!
I'm in! I'm in! I'm in, it's
just going to take a second.
Do it! Do it!
Almost got it. Almost got it.
Almost there.
Now, Chuck. Close it.
Lock it down!
You know, I don't know
one person
who responds positively
- to being yelled at!
- He's getting away, Chuck.
Door closed.
Got it. There. See?
You idiot!
You said you knew
how to work this system.
Ooh, hang in there.
Come on, Chuck!
Almost got it.
Got it.
No problem.
Ye of little faith.
Sensei?
GO!
NSA TACTICAL INSTRUCTOR
TY BENNETT
Oh, no.
Hey, did you get
a good look at him?
Didn't have to.
I know him.
What?
Guys! Hey! I just
flashed on that dude.
And it is crazy,
it's actually
kind of a small world,
funny story.
Save it.
His name's Ty Bennett.
He was my sensei.
Taught me everything I know.
You okay?
Hmm.
BUY MORE
Feeling better now.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
- =http:/www. ragbear. com=-
CHUCK 209
- =破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译: 校对: 时间轴:我爱狮心小s
Chuck! Chuck! You've got to
help me! This is an emergency!
- Chuck!
- What? What? What?
- Ellie! Ellie! Ellie! Are you okay!?
- No! No!
Devon's parents decided to take the red-eye in
from Connecticut to surprise us!
You scared the heck out of me.
I thought this
was life or death.
It is! These are
two perfect parents that raised
three perfect boys
in a perfect house,
- and this place is a pigsty.
- Don't worry.
We have time to clean up.
If they flew all night,
they're going to want
to sleep all morning.
Are you kidding me? The
awesome apple doesn't fall
far from the awesome tree.
I'm just going to...
I'll be right there.
Awesome!
There's the man!
Wow! Welcome! Hi.
You guys are very muscular.
And... and awake!
Chuck, this is
Devon's mom and dad.
Drs. Woodcomb,
so nice to finally meet you.
Oh, no handshakes
in this family.
- You just call me Honey.
- Okay, Honey.
- I'm Woody.
- Hey, Woody.
Yeah. My father
always said,
"A terrible nickname
builds character. "
Of course, Devon wasn't into nicknames.
I just can't
wait to start planning your dream wedding.
Wow! It looks
like you already have.
Oh, and, Chuck,
the caterer is
bringing over
a sample menu tonight for Devon and Ellie
to decide what they like. We hope you
and your... girlfriend
can join us.
Yes! Of course!
Of course!
- Sarah loves food.
- That she does!
So, yeah,
we'll be there!
Good. Good.
So nice of you guys
to help us plan
the wedding. Right, Ell?
Oh, absolutely!
Your mom's already been busy with
all these lists of guests, locations,
color palettes...
She's been
so excited
ever since Devon
asked you to marry him.
I can't tell you
how happy we are
to welcome you
into our family.
And now, you're stuck
with us, too, Chuck.
You're very strong,
and have fists.
Thank you, Dr. Woodcomb.
"Woody. "
Okay.
Dad, let's go do our abs.
- Ooh, yeah.
- You guys do abs.
I'm... I'm just going to go...
kill myself.
Ty Bennett: karate master,
kung fu expert,
master strategist.
A former instructor at our
training facility. And, today,
one of our most wanted
rogue agents.
Dude, your sensei is a badass!
He's not my sensei.
He's a traitor.
Wow. I've heard of Bennett,
but I've never met anyone
who actually trained with him.
I can't talk about it.
It's classified.
We're opening Bennett's file
for this assignment.
Any personal knowledge you have
could be vital to the success of this mission.
Come on, Casey.
Share with us.
In hell.
General, if I may, why wasn't
I told that Bennett went rogue?
Ty Bennett has been recruiting
his former students.
He's actually turning agents?
With the team he's assembled,
Bennett has been extremely
effective at stealing weapons
and reselling them
on the global black market.
What did he steal from GLA?
An advanced
inertial guidance system.
Well, that's not a weapon.
Well, fit sure looks like one when
it's put in a missile, moron.
You know,
when you call me moron,
that hurts me on the inside.
Bennett got away because
you couldn't open a door.
You're lucky your feelings aren't the only
thing that got hurt.
Technically,
I only have to sit in the van and flash.
Hey.
Guys.
Gentlemen, we have intel pinpointing the location
where Bennett plans
to transfer the GLA technology
to his buyer.
It's a construction site
in Simi Valley.
I want you to stop the deal
and recover the guidance system.
We're on it.
You know, I wonder if it's safe
for Chuck to go on this mission.
Too many unforeseeable
variables.
In situations like this, he
has proven himself a liability.
I think you're right, Casey.
Chuck, you will
be sitting this one out.
What? Wait a minute.
You might... you might need me
to flash on something.
Oh, this country
has gotten
by for 200 years
without an Intersect.
I'm sure we'll
be just fine.
What? Did I hurt your feelings?
I've tried to spare
your feelings,
but the gloves
are coming off, people.
I've decided to reinstitute a
time-honored Buy More tradition.
Commando Wednesdays.
That tradition
never stopped.
From this day on,
this branch will hold-
wait for it-
an Employee of the Month
contest.
Oh! Isn't that exciting?
I can barely contain myself,
sir.
I assume you're all aware of our
customer
comment cards.
Each month, we will
tally your score and select a winner.
He or she
or whomever
will not only get
an 8 X 10 glossy photo
right beside Moses Finkelstein,
EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH YOUR NAME HERE
the CEO and founder of Buy More,
but there will be
a bonus prize!
May the best employee win.
Okay, so how are feeling
about this
about this whole
Employee-of-the-Month thing?
Um, you know what?
Whatever, Morgan.
I don't, I don't really care.
We don't care. Roger that.
Hey.
I thought you guys
would already be gone.
Admit it.
You need me, don't ya?
I came to make sure
you're okay.
Well, isn't that what all the surveillance
cameras are for?
Listen, I don't agree
with Casey
that you would be a liability
on this mission.
He was out of line.
Don't worry. I get it.
He thinks I let my feelings
for Jill
get in the way
of the mission.
But he's wrong.
I would never do that...
...again.
Listen, Chuck,
this isn't about you,
it's Casey.
Casey trained with Bennett
for a long time,
and when you have a mentor
like that,
a real trust develops
between you,
and Casey feels betrayed.
I know it's hard,
but maybe you could
cut him some slack.
Yeah, I guess I know
how that feels.
THROUGH THESE HALLS WALK THE SMARTEST
EMPLOYEES IN THE WORLD SALES TEAM
All right, just to be absolutely
clear, our position on
Employee of the Month
is that we don't care,
Are you guys with me?
Yep, not caring.
Not a rat's ass.
Not a fat
and/or hairy one.
Wait. Why don't we care again?
Because Employee of
the Month is a scam.
And working hard
is for suckers.
Think about it.
You work hard,
sales go up.
Sales go up,
shareholders get rich.
Shareholders get rich,
and we get what exactly?
He said something about a prize.
Your face on a wall
next to Moses Finkelstein?
No, thank you, no.
You know what?
Keep your stupid stooge prize.
So we get nothing?
Emmett's gonna get
all the credit.
He may even get a promotion.
And then guess what?
One day, he's gonna be the boss.
So then what?
Then Emmett turns the Buy More
into a nightmare of pain
and suffering?
There is a solution.
Tell it,
tell it.
We have our own contest,
a side bet.
We see who can get
the lowest score
on their comment cards.
We beat Emmett at his own game.
Pure genius.
From now on,
the customers can go
service themselves.
In the retail sense,
Jeffrey.
Don't get any ideas.
Bennett will never show.
Why?
He's too smart
for this.
You get a read on the plates?
Look, Casey, just call Chuck.
Maybe he'll flash on it
and we'll know
who we're dealing with.
I think I'll take my
chances without him.
Oh, all right.
Fine.
Hello?
Hey, we just sent you an image
of a van.
Take a look at the plates,
see if you flash on it.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, of course.
Absolutely.
Whatever I can do to help.
You know, I don't have it yet.
It's probably
a high-resolution photo.
And my 3G connection gets
interference in here sometimes.
Spare me the Nerd Herd crap.
Get on it.
If there's intel,
we need it now!
Hey, I thought you said
the U.S. government got by
just fine for 200 years
without the Intersect?
Listen, you insignificant
little puke...
You're on a mission.
Maybe surrounded
by Bennett's men.
Pick up, pick up, pick up,
pick up.
Did you hang up on me?
No, that's crazy talk.
I would never do that.
It's a bad connection
that I had with the...
Hold on. Let me just look
at the picture real quick.
I got nothing. Sorry, no flash.
Thanks for wasting my time.
Hello?
Hey, that's the buyer.
We're out of time.
Looks like we do this
the old-fashioned way.
- Okay? Go.
- Yeah.
Get out of the car!
Out of the car!
Take the car, man,
and I won't call the cops.
Hands on the car!
Put 'em on the car!
Who the hell are you?
I'm a driver. I'm here to pick
up a passenger
and give them that.
Bennett. Run! Go! Go!
Excuse me.
Can you tell me where
I can find John Casey?
I have something
that belongs to him.
...Casey,
you say? John Casey?
You know, I'm gonna go
to the back
and-and-and check
on that for you.
So let me just... do that...
quick.
Pick up the phone, John.
Pick up the phone, Casey!
This is Casey.
Code Red! Code Red!
Redder than red!
It is the reddest!
It is the reddest of all hues!
We are Defcon One, or Five
or whichever means "Hurry,"
right now!
Bennett is at the Buy More!
Oh, no.
I'm looking for John Casey.
Can you tell me where
to find him?
What do I look like,
an information desk?
Excuse me?
Yes, fine, you're excused.
Oh, and don't forget to fill out a customer comment card
on your way out.
Wise man always
treats a stranger with respect,
for he could be gazing
on the face of an enemy.
Hi. Sorry, sorry.
I just checked into
it, sir,
and John Casey
is unfortunately not
working today, and I don't know
when he's gonna be back in,
but you could try back
next week.
Uh, maybe, maybe Tuesday-ish.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That guy was awesome!
Dude, did you see
what he did to this can?
He did this
with his bare hands.
Crush, like that.
Could you imagine what he could do to a guy's face?
Not feeling very
chatty right now.
Hold on, Casey, don't hang up.
I'm looking right at
your sensei.
Bennett's at the Buy More?
What? How is that possible?
Was. Was at the Buy More.
Now he's in the Large Mart
parking garage. I'm tailing him.
No, stop, imbecile!
You're no match for him.
Don't be an idiot!
Look, you're only reacting
like this
because your own feelings were
hurt, okay?
Please don't lash out at me.
Where did he go?
Oh, God!
Chuck?
Chuck?!
Bennett's got him.
He's probably dead by now.
Shut up and drive!
I'm a little tall for something
like this.
Is there another seating option,
perhaps?
Ell, are you sure
you're okay registering
for a wedding here
at the Buy More?
Whatever your parents want.
You think you may not need
a vacuum sealer,
but suddenly the Chief of
Surgery is coming over
with her husband
for salmon kabobs,
and voila, Saturday's party
turns into Sunday's picnic.
Why not? Can't hurt?
Ooh, camcorder.
Ah, first for the honeymoon,
then the grandkids.
Dad!
Crossing the line.
Before you say
anything,
I know they're coming on strong,
but they're just really excited.
They know your parents
aren't around.
That's fine. I know that they're
just trying to help.
And you know, they're,
they're awesome.
Hey, Lester,
you seen Chuck?
Maybe.
So, is he around?
Don't know. Could be.
Can you find him for me?
Yeah, sure, I could,
but, uh, wouldn't that be more
fulfilling for you
if you did it yourself?
Look, I'm so sorry.
It's a stupid store contest.
I can help you,
but do me a solid
and do not mention it
on this card.
Yes? Thank you, buddy.
LOCKED
The signal from
the watch
is getting stronger.
Chuck's close.
Casey, what are you doing?
The vic can take the hit.
Oh, no, not good, not good.
Wait. I've got Chuck.
It says the signal is...
the signal is right
in front of us.
No, Casey, stop, stop!
Chuck's in the car!
You're gonna kill Chuck!
Oh, fast. And he's driving very,
very fast.
Casey!
It's actually more spacious
in here than you might think.
Hey!
Freeze!
John, it's good to see you.
Keep your hands on your head.
You survived my trap.
Very good.
Get on your knees.
I followed your career, John.
You survived torture
at the hands of Baath separatists.
You did two years undercover
in Afghanistan.
Could you have done
any of that without me?
No.
Of course not.
My training saved you.
I came here
to ask you something.
Be my student again.
Take your training
to the next level.
That's it?
That's all you got?
That's how
you're turning the others?
Save your breath.
I'm no traitor.
Obviously,
I made a mistake.
You aren't good enough
for my team.
Hey!
So Bennett got away.
Again.
If you don't mind me asking,
where was the Intersect
during all of this?
Well, technically
I was in Bennett's trunk,
so I didn't see anything
that happened,
but it sounded
very exciting.
Wait. So, Major,
while you were playing
your game of chicken,
Chuck was in Bennett's trunk?
As soon as we
ascertained
the Intersect's location,
Major Casey disengaged.
Sounds like Bennett has decided
to make this personal, Casey,
and so have you.
- I'm pulling you off the case.
- With all due respect...
This is why I didn't tell you
about Bennett.
I knew you would turn it
into a vendetta.
I'm bringing in another team to clean up your mess.
But I know Bennett.
I know how he operates.
You're forgetting
your primary objective is protecting the Intersect.
You will remain in Castle until the mission is completed.
Consider it
a cooling-off period.
You little...
I didn't know this was
going to happen.
I didn't know... tell him I didn't
know this was going to happen!
If my primary objective
wasn't to protect you... I KILL YOU.
I can't believe it.
Beckman was out of line pulling
me off this mission.
I agree with her.
You're too emotionally involved.
This from the agent that can't keep her
chocolate out of Bartowski's peanut butter.
Whatever my feelings
may be for Chuck,
I never knowingly endangered the asset.
You let your anger
toward Bennett cloud
your judgment.
You finally admit that you do
have feelings for the nerd.
No, all I will admit to
is having feelings.
20 years in the business
has taught me one sure thing-
that people...
people let you down in the end.
Well, it's nice to know
where we stand.
Did you talk to Casey?
Is he mad?
I feel horrible.
Casey is always mad.
That's his baseline.
I never should have said
all that stuff in front of the general.
No, your assessment
was accurate.
I mean, the facts
are the facts.
True, but the guy's
going through a lot.
If I were really a friend,
I would look past
what he's saying and remember
how he's feeling.
I mean, I should know
better than anybody
what he's going through
right now.
Chuck, you're so sweet.
But, you know, an apology
is not going to work,
because Casey is combat ready
at all times.
Which means his feelings
are liabilities.
Well, aren't you supposed
to be combat ready at all times?
I'll meet you at your
sister's wedding tasting after your Buy More shift.
And please,
don't go downstairs.
Leave Casey alone.
If it isn't
Tweedledee, Tweedledum
and... Tweedledumber.
Oh, congratulations
goes out to you.
What do we win,
a prize or something?
Well, of all the incompetent
employees in this backwater branch,
you three have
distinguished yourselves-
with the lowest
customer evaluation scores in recorded history.
Really?
- What... how low exactly?
- Are we talking like
truly abysmal, or...?
Combined your highest score
was a one.
- Dare to dream, baby.
- All right.
Well, since none of you
seem to be taking
this Employee of the Month
contest very seriously,
I must abandon the carrot,
and use my stick.
You sure that's legal?
From now on, the employee
with the lowest scores
will close up
every Saturday night
- for an entire month.
- All right, stop.
You can't do this
to us, okay?
I'm sorry, I can't?
- Saturday's are sacred.
- I can't work on Shabbat.
Yeah. It's date night.
Laundry night?
- It's two-for-one night.
- You're wasting time.
You have one night
to raise your scores.
You better get crackin'.
This is my employee
discount card.
It's good for 20% off
anything in the store. Go nuts.
Just put in a good word
for me on your way out.
No, mind?
Why would I mind?
Just let me get this puppy
loaded up for you
and then I'll come right back
for sub...
Four stars?!
I just kissed your ass
for four lousy stars?!
What do you people
want from me!
Just spit in my
face next time!
Hey, Jeff.
How's it going, man?
You all right?
I think I'm getting the hang
of this customer service stuff.
ENTER
Yeah...
ACCESS DENIED
Casey, hey.
Hey, how you doing?
Get down here.
Um, look, I'm glad you called,
because I was actually going
- to call you to say sorry... - I don't care
if it's your time of the month, Bartowski.
Get down here please.
I don't...
I don't think I can.
Sarah said not to.
Listen, buddy...
I started training
under Ty Bennett
when I was 23 years old.
I was an idiot back then.
I wasn't good enough
to qualify for his program,
but he took me on anyway.
You know, so, he taught me
everything I know-
self-discipline,
duty.
I don't know
what to think here, pal.
I'm feeling kind of exposed.
I feel like my whole foundation
has been undermined here.
He was like, a...
I can't talk about this
over the phone.
No, no, I'm glad you're finally
opening up to me.
Be right there.
Thanks, buddy.
Hey...
Hey, buddy, I'm sorry, I got
here as fast as I could.
And I wanted
to tell you seriously
what I was saying
on the phone earlier-
I am sorry, man.
I know, your sensei from the
past... it's very personal...
- Yeah.
- Hey! Hey!
Let go.
What are you doing?
Oh, oh, gentle.
Now, Intersect, flash.
This is the surveillance
footage from the crash.
Casey, it doesn't work
like that, okay?
I can't just flash on cue...
Okay, okay,
1919 Mulholland Drive.
It's a martial arts dojo,
but also a cover for
Bennett's illegal activity.
Good work, Intersect.
You know, I think
you should reconsider
this whole cooling-off period.
I think General Beckman was
onto something when she said you
- should stay down here...
- Come on, I need that eyeball.
Casey, what has
gotten into you?!
What is going on? This is
totally uncharacteristic...
I've never seen you
disobey an order.
What are you, nuts,
crazy, out of your mind?
Okay, that's it-
I'm calling Sarah.
You know what, Chuck?
I think I might owe
you an apology now.
That's very nice of you.
Huh? What's it for?
The lying, the name-calling,
the emotional manipulation?
Nope. For this.
Wait, no, no.
No, Casey, no, no, no, wait,
wait wait. You don't understand.
I have dinner with Ellie tonight and we're tasting food
for her wedding.
I can't miss it.
You know, when I was
Bennett's student,
I struggled with my calm.
He said I held too much anger
and that made me weak.
Sometimes when I see
your face, Bartowski,
my calm center just wants to...
You tell anyone where I'm going,
and this is yours.
What? Hey!
Use the Force.
Use the Force, Chuck.
So, you're sure it's all right
to start without Chuck?
- Yeah, he has a tendency to run late.
- Yeah, it's like the kid's
in his own world
half the time.
Must drive you crazy, Sarah.
Oh, I'm pretty
used to it, actually.
And Chuck always
has a good excuse.
So we are all
in agreement then?
Yes to the trout,
no to the beef au jus.
And what was
your favorite cake, Ellie?
- Um...
- Oh, it doesn't matter.
- Let's agree on the red velvet.
- Big fan.
And I love sorbet
between courses.
Great idea, Woody.
So, are you going
to wear your hair up?
Wait a second...
I just had
a brilliant idea.
White ties.
Woody looks so handsome
in a white tie.
- That's not too formal is it?
- I don't know.
And I know you're not
in contact with your dad,
so I would be honored, really,
to walk you down the aisle on your wedding day.
You know, guys, maybe we should
just table the wedding talk.
Um, no.
I have something
I'd like to say, actually.
Um, I said yes to the big
wedding and I said yes
to the burgundy organza
bridesmaid dresses,
and I just can't
say yes anymore.
And I'm sorry, I know that
you're trying to help,
but the answer is no.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
Babe...
Sorry.
Sweetie...
sweetheart...
Sweetheart?
Well, Sarah...
so you're in the yogurt game?
Yeah.
Yeah, yogurt.
Come on, baby.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
- Woody...
- Huh?
I think we should go for a walk
and give the kids some time to themselves.
Oh, it's Ellie's phone.
Oh, it's Chuck.
Should I answer it?
Oh, I'll take it.
Thank you.
Hey, Chuck, where are you?
Sarah, Sarah, thank God.
Listen, um...
Casey threatened my life,
- so technically I can't tell you...
- What?
Well, you could guess though.
Yeah, you could guess.
Chuck,
I don't have time for games.
Just guess!
I'll tell you if you're
hot or cold.
And FYI,
this place is very cold.
It's... it's practically frozen.
You're at Orange Orange.
Bingo! Yes, you're amazing!
Let me guess- you went down
into the Castle and Casey
used you to get out and
then he locked you
in the Orange Orange and now
he's going after Bennett.
Wow. That's very impressive.
How did you...?
Okay. Where did he go?
You didn't hear this from me.
1919 Mulholland Drive.
Can you get out?
No. No. Not until
you get down here
and get the key to get me
out of these handcuffs.
Good. Then stay there.
What? No, no, no! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait, Sarah! No, no! Wait!
Those seven years of MacGyver
finally paid off.
You shouldn't be here.
You want to stop me,
you're going to have to kill me.
Well, I'm your partner,
and I'm not letting
you go in alone.
Okay.
Come on.
Um... computer emergency?
I was waiting in the car.
I swear.
Hello, John.
And friends.
This is unfortunate.
No matter where you run, where you hide,
I'm going
to be there,
waiting.
Please be careful.
Always so proud,
so righteous, John.
But I have business to attend to.
I can't have you interfering.
I thought you
were a man of honor.
If I'm not good enough
to make your team,
surely you could defeat me without the gun.
Withhonor.
You're right.
My students,
this is a special lesson:
How to kill a man with honor.
It will happen
very quickly.
Eye of the tiger, buddy.
Shut up, Chuck.
Sorry.
We're in trouble, aren't we?
Use the snake on him.
Get around him.
Come on!
Casey, hit him!
He's outmatched.
You lost your calm, John.
Your center
is filled with conflict.
That's it.
Casey... Casey!
Casey, you gotta get up.
- You gotta get up.
- Run for it, Chuck. Go.
It's too bad,
really.
I was hoping my
men would see
better skills
from a former student of mine.
Look. Look, I get how you're
feeling, man. I totally
get how you're feeling.
You're feeling betrayed
by someone that
you really care about.
You're damaging my calm, Chuck.
You've spent so much of your life-
pushing people away.
Lashing out with purple words
and... and punches.
But I know why you do it.
You do it because you're scared.
What?
Scared. Scared to be known.
Scared that, if we see
who you really are,
we'd actually care about you.
You shut up!
Yeah. Shut up, Chuck.
You're making him mad.
Underneath that extremely
terrifying exterior lies a man
who deeply, deeply feels.
You care. You care about us.
You care about me.
Admit it. You feel all
warm and mushy about me.
Go ahead. Say it.
You love me, John Casey.
I'm going to kill you!
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on.
No. Not me.
Him.
Nice work, sensei.
Yeah. Well,
the thing is, Casey doesn't
really have a calm center.
It's more of an angry center.
There he is.
There's your sensei.
Take a good
look at him.
Who's next?
Hands on your heads!
You called Beckman.
What? It's not my fault.
She guessed.
And now it's time
to announce this month's
Employee of the Month.
And, for what
it's worth, you all tried your... best.
The employee with
the highest level
of customer service is...
Skip Johnson!
It's not my fault.
I tried to be a jerk.
Oh, congratulations!
Clearly, there is no prize that I could
give you
that would compare to the satisfaction
of having
your name and photo immortalized
on a Buy More plaque.
What did I tell ya?
So lame.
However,
please accept
this one-time only bonus gift.
A 65-inch flat screen TV.
Well, thanks for saving my life
today, Chuck.
Anytime, Casey.
Yeah.
You know what?
You're my friend.
Yeah. You know what?
You're my friend, too.
Well, that's really kind
of you, Casey.
Have a good night.
Thank you.
You said something, didn't you?
You said something.
You said something!
I heard that. I heard that.
Hey.
Sorry I missed
tonight.
I got stuck at work.
It's okay.
Sarah told me.
Uh... Where are
Awesome's parents?
He's, um... he's taking
them to the airport.
I really am sorry about
missing the dinner, Ell.
I mean, I know
it's important for you
to let your future in-laws
meet your family and...
You know, I, um...
I've never been
one of those girls
that dreamed about what
their wedding day would be like.
What I would wear.
Even the person
that I would marry.
It was all kind
of, uh... kind of hazy.
Except... except
one thing was clear-
That Dad would walk me
down the aisle.
Hey, Ellie.
I know it's not
going to happen.
It's just... it's just really
hard to let go of that.
ALWAYS THINKING OF YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DAD.
The number you have reached
is not in service.
What is it?
Dad's going to walk
you down the aisle.
You can't say that, Chuck.
I know that you
want that for me,
but we haven't heard from him
in a really long time.
Yeah. Well,
I'm going to find him.
I'm a smart guy.
I can do that.
And, when he hears
about the wedding,
he'll be here for you.
Come on. You really
think he's going to make it?
I guarantee it.
破烂熊字幕组 -
=http:/www. ragbear. com=- 欢迎加入