Chuck! Get back here!
Mom is going to be so mad!
Dad, help!
I'm working, Charles!
Uh...
she's gonna
hurt me.
What's going on out here?
I'm trying to work.
Chuck broke Mom's
favorite necklace.
Is that true, Charles?
I didn't mean to.
Ha!
He admitted it.
Uh, uh. No.
Let me...
Let-Let me see.
Um...
There's nothing broken
in-in this whole world
that the two of you can't fix
if you work
together.
Here.
Charles, go into
your sister's room
and get some of
her art supplies.
Go on.
Ellie, you're gonna help him.
I know it's hard, El,
but your-your brother...
does have a knack for getting
into trouble.
But you...
You're gonna have
to protect Chuck.
Be there for him
no matter what
'cause you're
his big sister.
Can you do that for me?
Devon, I lost them.
I lost the truck!
Call me as soon
as you can see them, okay?
Chuck, where are you?
Chuck, I know
how much you're hurting,
but you have to know
that there is nothing
that you could
have done, okay?
It's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
I'm the one who downloaded
the Intersect 2.0.
I'm the one
who chose to be a spy,
and it's him who paid the price.
So who's gonna get us out
of this one?
Who even knows we're here?
Okay, babe.
We found him.
Devon, these people killed
my father.
They're gonna do the same thing
to Chuck.
You have to stop them, okay?
I know. I know.
We're on it.
What are we gonna do?
We don't have a plan.
No plan?
Never stopped me before.
Everybody good? Comfy?
Uncuff yourselves.
It should look like
you were trying to escape
when I kill you.
Gee, Morgan,
I think that when one is facing
a group of murderers,
one should have a plan.
Okay, I agree with you
in principle, but we're
here now, all right?
What would you like me to do,
open up the glove box?
Pull up the spy manual?
Maybe just...?
This is Casey's car.
Glove box.
Whoa.
Get to it.
Don't look at me.
I'm a doctor.
I can't use this.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Easy, will you?
I'm a lapsed
vegetarian. I...
Here...
Here's a button.
Whoa.
What did you just do?
I hit... I hit a button...
Yeah, well, un... unhit it.
What's wrong with you? Hey! Hey!
You just push any button
you see? You're like...
How many missions
have you been on?
have you been...?
Chuck?
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
Everyone okay?
We're here to save you.
Hey, you used my missile.
Pretty cool, huh?
Yell at me later.
Let's go.
Chuck. Come on.
Get in the car.
Come on.
Let's go! Let's go!
Move it! Move it!
You're gonna have
to protect Chuck.
Be there for him
no matter what,
'cause you're
his big sister.
Can you do that for me?
Yeah.
Okay, Dad, I promise.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
Look, by now, Shaw's alerted
the Ring of our escape.
They'll be looking
for us.
What do we do now?
If there's one thing
I learned from my dad,
it's that we have to be smart.
We have to do what he would
have done. We need to disappear.
Yeah. Give up
our old lives.
Drop off
the grid.
Okay, so we're in agreement
then. That's the plan.
Wait. I'm sorry.
That's the plan?
We give up our lives?
Babe, it's the best
for all of us.
Devon, what are you
talking about?
This is not us.
We don't live
off grids, okay?
We are regular people.
We live on planet Earth,
and my father was murdered
today.
Our father, Chuck.
I'm calling the police.
It's what regular people do.
No. Hey, no calls.
They'll track 'em.
This is insane.
I'm going.
Sis, wait!
Get out of the car, Chuck!
Can we talk about this
for a second?
What's happening?
Is my husband safe
with you?
Um... yeah. Why?
Because Chuck
and I need to talk.
Hmm. Two Bartowskis.
Double the fun.
Hello, egg white omelet
on English muffin
with my favorite
banana peppers to boot.
160 calories of deliciousness.
I do know how
to build a better breakfast.
Mmm!
Talk to me, Moses.
Anyone seen Morgan?
Chuck around?
Tell me John's in the john.
Can we help you, sir?
I need my assistant managers
and Chuck.
Hey, what we lack profoundly
and proudly
in on-the-job competence,
we more than make up for
with listening skills.
Actually, I'm deaf
in my left ear,
except for a faint ringing.
Psst.
It's big news, boys.
The store's numbers are down.
Mm. My main man Moses,
founder of the Buy More
himself, called.
Said if we don't see
a spike in numbers
and fast, they're gonna
close the store.
What?! Factoring Jeffrey out
of the conversation
for a minute,
may I propose something
that I rarely do
in life myself?
Tell... the... truth.
What you talking about, Lester?
Well, if in fact, we are
going out of business,
why not just tell that to
our most loyal customers?
You mean have
a going out of business sale.
Slash the prices.
Sell everything
to juice the books.
That's crazy!
Crazy...
good?
There may be a brain
under that mop after all.
Hello.
The phone did not
ring, Jeffrey.
Stupid left ear.
I don't understand how
you can know all this,
how you can have
all these secrets...
...and I'm the last
person to know.
I thought that I knew you
better than anyone.
Not telling you was the best way
to keep you safe.
Believe me, there's no one
I wanted to tell more.
I mean, you raised me, you know?
Do you remember
when I broke Mom's necklace,
and she left a couple days
later, and I thought,
that's-that's why
she disappeared?
That it was my fault?
I hated her for leaving.
For making you feel that way.
And the way you were with Dad.
No 12-year-old should
ever have to worry
about handling
the family's bank account.
I can't believe
that he's gone.
Our crazy dad.
He wasn't crazy.
Our dad was a hero.
He was a great man
who did amazing things.
He was not perfect-
not as a dad, no-
but he was great.
That's the secret
I most wanted you to know.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna go after 'em,
and we're gonna get 'em.
We're gonna take 'em down-
the Ring and Shaw-
for what they did to Dad.
They are not gonna
get away with this.
Okay.
And then you're done.
What?
As a spy, this-this life,
this job.
Chuck, I made a promise
to protect you,
and I can't do it,
not from this.
So you finish it,
and then you're done.
Ellie, I can't...
We are all that we
have left, Chuck.
And I'm not gonna lose you, too.
Okay.
I'll get Shaw and I quit.
I promise.
All right,
so Devon's in the car.
Sarah's making sure
it's not bugged.
You remember the plan, right?
You leave the city-
don't tell me where-
I don't want to know.
Use only cash
and pay phones,
and I will call you
when it's safe.
You got that?
I got it, okay.
Uh, what
about Morgan?
Should I take
him with me?
Funny thing about Morgan-
he's, he's actually
a part of my spy team.
He's helping
Casey's daughter go off-grid.
Casey has a daughter?
I know it's a lot
to process,
but there's not enough time
right now.
You have to go.
Stay safe.
Don't forget about your promise.
I won't.
Time to take down the Ring.
Perimeter is set.
What are you doing?
Well, when Shaw grabbed me,
I noticed
that the holding cells
were equipped
for remote interrogation,
so if I can crack
into their system, I can...
Wait... There,
there, right there,
there she is.
It's Beckman.
I'm going to open a channel.
General.
General!
Who's there?
Is that you, Shaw?
No, General, this is Chuck.
Chuck, thank God.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
We're gonna take down Shaw
and the Ring,
but we honestly have no idea
how to do it.
Listen fast.
I came to Los Angeles
for the Joint Security Summit.
It's a public conference
of security experts,
but it's really
a secret meeting of spies.
Shaw's plan was to discredit me
and take my place
at the conference.
Coup d'état. The Ring is
taking over the CIA and the NSA.
So if we had a plan,
that plan would be...
The conference is happening
tonight at the Grand Ambassador.
Wait, General, wait.
Damn it.
Chuck, Chuck,
the five elders will be there.
Hey, a-are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, sorry, yeah,
just a, a lot of data.
Listen, who are the elders?
They sound scary,
like World of Warcraft scary.
The elders, Morgan,
are the leaders of the Ring.
Makes sense.
Ring operatives were hidden
in all the major agencies.
All right, that's it:
we break into the convention;
we expose Shaw;
and we capture the elders.
Conference will be surrounded
by an army
of security agents
and filled
with spies.
Suicide mission.
The only ones
who could pull it off
would have to be
the best spies in the world.
Chuck, you're embarrassing me.
We can do it.
Yeah, well, we'd better.
It's Shaw.
We don't have a choice.
Yeah, let's go get some payback.
Payback-
that's what I was gonna say.
Definitely
get-some-payback time.
Okay, Chuck,
we're going in undercover
as members
of the Russian delegation.
This means we need disguises.
Think you can handle that?
Sarah, I was Perchik
in Fiddler.
It's true. He was great.
Thanks, buddy.
It's him- Shaw.
Excuse me.
And once
we I.D. Shaw,
Casey, you, and Morgan
will take over.
Okay, we're in the server room.
Why'd I get Morgan for this job?
Hey, hey,
I'm right here, please.
Just call me after
you've cracked
into the conference's
database.
Okay, this is great.
That's the conduit right there,
so I just need a hand
getting up there.
Boost.
You ready?
I was born rea...
well, no, actually,
no, I wasn't born ready,
but I am ready now.
Now, remember, Chuck,
in order for this plan to work,
you'll need
to fully convince Shaw.
Make eye contact,
shake his hand,
and act
as if you were strangers.
Excuse me.
Uh, I don't believe
we've met.
Daniel Shaw.
Ah, yes.
Yuri Sheshenko.
It is
a great pleasure
to meet you,
Mr. Shaw.
Well, thank you.
Now, if you'll
excuse me...
Do svidaniya.
Good job.
Yeah, well, you can thank my
very convincing facial hair.
Come on.
Okay, good, good, Chuck.
Number 752.
Hear that? 752.
One second, hold on.
Okay.
Let me get this thing off.
Hold on one second.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, little help.
What is this?
Why do you have
my daughter's phone number?
Hmm.
Hi, Chuck.
Shaw says your accent
could use a little work.
Justin, right?
You're the one
who manipulated my sister.
That's right.
Yeah, well, I think this is
going to hurt a little bit.
Chuck? Chuck?
Are you okay?
Sarah.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to tell you.
Can you please just tell me
what's really going on?
The Intersect-
the flashes are getting worse.
Okay, we have to
abort the mission.
Shaw is not worth this.
No, if I get
the Governor
back from Shaw,
then I'll be fine,
but the plan is
only gonna work
if you help Morgan and Casey.
I can't leave you like this.
I'm okay, really.
You have to go.
We have to stop him.
You're not going
to believe it.
There's a line around the store
of stay-at-home moms
ready for the sale tomorrow.
Yes.
Um, Big Mike,
we, uh- Jefferson and myself
were hoping to...
screen this tomorrow.
You know, since you're
our manager and all,
we thought it'd be a good idea.
What is it?
Our music video.
We spent two weekends on it.
Two weekends.
Great idea.
But let's do it late in the day.
Wouldn't want to scare anyone
away too early.
The CIA believes
that international terrorism
is a growth industry.
The demand for the security
we offer is even greater
than it was a year ago, which
brings me to my next point.
Excuse me.
Did you know the Nerd Herd
offers a wide variety
of helpful hints for making your
business presentations better?
Chuck, where are you?
I'm in room 752,
which I believe is your room.
Also, we are well aware that
your bosses- the Ring elders-
are in the audience right now...
...and they have got
to be asking themselves,
"Who is Daniel talking to?"
Ladies and gentlemen,
please remain seated.
The presentation
will begin again shortly.
Casey, Morgan,
Shaw's left the stage.
Tell me everything.
Why do you have
my daughter's phone number?
Hold on a second.
Alex gave that to me
on her own free will.
But as friends.
Friends?
Yeah.
Or something more?
Your heart's racing; pupils
dilated; skin's flushed.
You like her.
Or you're choking me.
Hey.
Sarah.
Oh, just in time.
What for?
Come on. Let's go.
Here.
It's not a toy,
Morgan.
Ready?
Yeah.
This discussion
is not over.
Muzzle down.
Yeah, muzzle down.
No gun.
Very brave, Chuck.
So what's happening?
You're under arrest.
No, what are
you doing here?
What's your plan?
I'm sorry.
Are you asking me
to make
the classic villain mistake
of explaining
my dastardly plot to you?
You know what?
I'd love to.
I confess
we had no idea who the elders
were or how to I.D. them,
so we let you do that for us
when you warned them
to leave the theater,
so on behalf
of the NSA,
the CIA, and of course
your local Buy More,
I'd just like to say
thanks a lot.
Hey.
Going somewhere?
Reach for the
sky, dirtbags.
Oh, you people are the disease
and I'm the cure.
Back off there, Cobra.
I didn't give you any bullets.
Are you kidding me?
I knew this thing
felt too light.
Chuck, we've got 'em.
I'm on my way up to you.
Do not give Shaw an inch.
Done.
Ring captured.
It's another check
on my to-do list.
Do you see what you did wrong?
You and your team
are fugitives.
On whose authority
would anyone arrest me?
What about my father?
Yes, I killed your father.
Yes, I work
for the Ring.
I'm going to take down
the CIA, Chuck,
and still I'm going to walk
out of here a hero.
How does that make you feel?
You know, your Nerd Herd
associate can also help you
with videoconferencing.
Smile, Daniel.
You're on TV.
What do I say
to that?
Mwah-ha-ha.
Now...
Give me the Governor.
Don't make me take it from you.
I'd like to see you try.
I knew you didn't
have it in you.
So clever, so smart.
There's no way out
of this one.
Shaw!
Drop him!
Chuck?
Hey.
Help me.
Going out of business?
What the...
...hell is going on here?
I've only been gone
for two days.
These numbers
are amazing.
Boys... you know
what time it is.
Please.
Say "Jeffster time."
Say it. Say it.
What the hell
is going on here?
Who authorized this sale?
This store is supposed
to be closed.
These people are
stealing from us.
You guys, you guys,
this is not good.
Old man Moses couldn't
protect us anymore.
They up and closed
the store.
All of this merchandise
was supposed to be shipped
to Beverly Hills.
Where is Mike?!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hey.
Where is everyone?
Casey's gone to get Ellie
and Awesome,
and Morgan's checking in
to the Buy More.
I promised her I'd leave.
That I wouldn't be
a spy anymore.
What?
Ellie.
She's going to be so mad at me
if I die.
Hey, we're going to get
that Governor, okay?
I'm going to find Shaw
and I'm going to get it back,
no matter where he is.
Hello?
This isn't about you.
Shaw.
I'm in the store.
I've wired it with explosives.
It'll take ten minutes for
the CIA backup team to arrive.
I only need seconds.
I want you to send me Chuck.
Now.
Okay.
We're on our way.
Help!
Help me! Anybody?
Come on.
Come... oh, no.
What the hell's going on,
Morgan?
Walker just pulled
the silent alarm.
Yeah, it's-it's Shaw, okay.
He's here and he planted
bombs all over the store
and he's going to blow
the whole place up.
Where's Chuck?
You got to get everyone
out of the store.
You anywhere near a fire alarm?
Yes. It's outside the cage.
But I'm-I'm-I'm tied up
inside the cage.
My hands are cuffed to a chair.
You got to break your thumbs,
Morgan.
I'm sorry.
Can you say that again?
Your thumbs.
To get free,
you got to break 'em.
Now! Do it!
Break your thumbs.
Yes, sir.
You don't want to kill
all these people.
You're right.
I don't want to kill
all these people.
However, I would like
to kill Chuck.
And I wouldn't mind
killing you, too.
Hey, have you seen Big Mike?
We're going to need a diversion
to get out of here.
What are you thinking?
Pineapple.
Go, go, go.
Well done, Jeff.
Let's go.
Shaw, stop it!
You don't understand.
Where is he?
He's not coming.
He can't.
A gunfight?
Is that what you really want?
Do you have one good flash left?
Saved the best for last.
* *
I'm waiting, Chuck.
Please, stop it, Shaw!
Chuck?
Chuck, please.
Chuck, please wake up.
Hey, Dad...
Charles, I'll be back
in a second.
Chuck?
Chuck, you all right?
Are you all right?
Did you...?
Was a complete transfer.
Empty files.
The whole system went
into you. You...
processed an incredible
amount of data.
But you're okay.
What does that mean?
Hang on. Stay with me.
Stay with me.
You're going to be okay.
You're special, son.
It means you're special.
You're special.
You're special, son.
It means you're special.
Please, Chuck,
come on.
Shaw, stop it!
Chuck?
Chuck.
Sorry.
Just had to reboot.
You have to do it.
You have to kill me.
No, thanks.
I've already done that
once before.
That's what makes you weak.
No. That's what makes you great.
Your dad wanted you
to have this.
This is not good.
I am definitely going
to be fired tomorrow.
Big Mike, sir,
what if I told you
there was another way?
A way we could
save our jobs,
be heroes...?
Do tell, Barnes.
Do tell.
We burn the Buy More.
Burn it down to the ground.
Burn down what?!
It would be my honor
to do that for you.
That's it.
I have had it with you two!
You have brought me nothing
but pain and misery.
You answering phones
that ain't ringing.
And you- your singing voice
is a vocal felony.
With that, good night,
good riddance,
and good-bye!
So none of these firemen
are real, huh?
CIA cleaners looking
for Shaw's detonator.
By the way,
good work today.
Takes something special
to break your thumbs.
Come on. It's nothing.
They're just thumbs.
What any good partner
would do. Yeah.
Will you tell Beckman of
my exploits? It depends.
Why do you have my
daughter's phone number?
Oh.
Aah. Aah. Aah.
Sarah, I told Ellie that I'd
quit after we stop the Ring,
and I meant it.
I can't lie to her.
You think you could
love a regular guy?
Well, I fell in love
with a regular guy.
Hey!
Found the detonator.
Found the
detonator, Colonel.
Am I on some hero
streak or what?
Man, when you're hot, you're
hot. Careful with that, Grimes.
Now will you tell Beckman
of my exploits?
Okay? How I broke
my thumbs and how
I found the detonator.
He's gonna drop it.
And how I...
dropped it.
I can't believe
I just did that.
Bombs are armed, everybody!
Run!
I'm-I'm so sorry, everybody.
I'm so sorry.
It was an accident.
Everybody, get back! Get back!
Get back!
Hit the deck!
Did we do that?
I don't know.
Start the van.
All clear!
Everyone please exit
the area in a calm
and orderly fashion.
Sweet lord, they did it.
They actually did it.
Those crazy nerds
blew up the freakin' Buy More.
In our top story
tonight, it's been 24 hours
since the Burbank Buy More
burned to the ground,
and the police have had no luck
in apprehending
the two lead suspects.
These two men are on the run
and considered
extremely dangerous.
If you encounter
these fugitives,
please call your
local authorities immediately.
And in other...
Thanks, buddy.
Of course.
Um...
We didn't always think
he was the greatest family man,
but we know
that there was nothing more
important to him than family.
To a great man,
Stephen J. Bartowski.
To Dad.
Mm.
Hi.
I hope I didn't miss dinner.
No. No. come in,
please. Welcome to
La Casa de Bartowski.
Uh, Alex,
this is my sister Ellie.
Hi.
And that's Devon,
her-her husband
back there.
Just so glad you came.
Me, too.
Oh.
Okay.
Well,
he's not much
of a hugger,
but baby steps, right?
I'm glad to see you,
Alex. I, too,
am glad that you
came... Step aside.
Before I break the rest
of your fingers. Hmm?
Or you blow up
the apartment.
Oh, that's low, Casey.
Okay? It was an accident.
Chuck it was
an accident.
I couldn't grip anything.
I know. I know it was...
I know it was
an accident, buddy.
So... Chuck... are
you done for real?
Uh, I told Beckman
that I'm out.
I mean, after all, I did
get her her job back, and
simultaneously saved
multiple branches
of the United States government,
so she accepted.
I'm a civilian
just like you.
Really?
You were right, sis.
There's nothing more important
than family.
Love you.
I love you, too.
Oh, boy.
Hello, Chuck.
If you're seeing this,
that means I wasn't able to stop
this message from sending.
which also means I'm dead.
I want to say about that, um,
I- I'm sorry and-and...
Well, I hope you and your sister
know how much I love you.
Loved you.
Now I need you
to do something for me,
Charles.
Something secret.
You better get a pen.
I never wanted you
to be a spy.
I knew how dangerous
this world is,
what it does
to the people in it.
Boy, do I know that.
That's why I kept something
from you,
something about me,
about Orion.
Charles, I'll be back
in a second.
Hey, Dad.
I've been a spy
for the last 20 years,
working for myself,
doing things
governments are afraid to do.
Maybe being a spy is...
is in our blood,
and... maybe
I should have told you...
all of this long ago,
but
Chuck,
your story-
it's only just beginning.
It's time you know the truth
about my work
and about the people
who tried to destroy me
because if I'm gone,
then you're not safe
from them anymore,
and neither is Ellie.
These people-
they-they are...
They are ruthless
and cunning and...
Chuck, it's-it's time
you learned
about your family.
Because...
I did it all for her.
Yes.
MAN
We're going to have to move you.
Now.
Mom?
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com