Hey, i'm chuck. Here are a few things
that you might need to know.
Jill, hey. I can help you.
Come on.
You're under arrest, Jill.
And i'm breaking up with you.
Dad's gone. I thougt i needed him
to walk me down the aisle,
I thought that he would be different
from that guy who walked out on us.
Don't worry, Charles.
I'm not who you think i am.
You're Orion.
I'll give Fulcrum their Intersect.
But my son walks away from here.
Take care of yourself.
As soon as my dad finished
the new intersect,
I'm worthless to you.
And Fulcrum wins.
The only thing that matters now
is getting my father back.
Fro-yo?
It's time to try our latest flavor,
Obama Guava.
I didn't make up the name.
-Uh, no, thanks.
No that i'm not thrilled that the CIA
has found a new yogurt recipe, i was just...
I don't know, kinda hoping the CIA
would find my father first.
The government is doing anything
they can to find him.
How would i know i can trust them?
The government wants to keep
the intersect in my head.
My father is the only person
who can get it out. It's not rocket science.
Okay, i know that you don't trust them
but do you trust me?
Yeah.
Good. Then i promise you
we're gonna find him.
Well, hurry, please.
What's the matter, Chuck?
You're dad's back in town, right?
You're dating the hottest slice of a BBQ pizza.
And you are best friends with me.
Which means,
two out of three ins of bad, right?
Come on. You're king of the world, dude.
Bartowski, get it together.
Yeah. King of the world.
Emmet got an announcement.
So listen up.
Aye aye, captain.
All right, now, sometimes
over the next 24 hours,
a Buy-More corporate evaluator
will be here to evaluate yours truly.
Now, normally in this situation,
i would expect to certain...
tribe* to use this oppurtunity
to make me look bad.
Laugh it up, cretins.
The tech jobs are being shipped
to India faster than you can say,
"Would you like fries and a soft drink with that?"
-I can't work fast food, Emmet.
I keep kosher.
-Count me in on the trip to India.
I've always dreamt seeing
Lester in his native enviroment.
What?
-You test me,
and you'll be flipping burgers in
Encino for the rest of your miserable life.
Now, let's show corporate
that we are *lean, mean, Buy-More machine.
So comb your hair.
-Jealous.
Lower that *whore skirt.
-Excuse me?
And for god's sakes, Barnes...
I am tired of seeing your but crack.
Pull 'em up!
Well, that went well.
Hey. Updates from Beckman.
Yeah? Is it information about
where my father is?
We're about to find out.
Come on.
I mean, people, do you have any idea
what working with fried food
will do to my complexion?
Can't leave the Buy-More.
I won't survive in the real world.
I'm institutionalized.
Morgan, we are the brains
of this operation.
So let's you and i
come up with something.
Why don'y you start us off?
-What? As i see it,
Emmet's threat was a ruse
to get us to work hard,
So he would look good
in front of corporate. Think about this.
Emmet's asked us to behave becuase
he knows we would do the exact opposite.
We misbehave. But Emmet, he's no fool...
So he would know that we
would know that he knows this.
So obviously, we need to behave.
Okay, so we behave.
Pay attention. It's the exact opposite.
Emmett would also know that we'd
know that he knows we know,
because he knows that we know that what he knows
is that we know he wants us to behave.
Right! Yes!
Yes. I don't know how we do it,
but we are geniuses, my friend.
Thank you.
-So, what are we doing again?
God, I love technology.
What we are doing again
is we're going to let Rome burn.
We've used every resource
to find him with no luck.
I'm sorry, Chuck.
FULCRUM's kept a tight lid on
your father's whereabouts.
That's your update?
Well, I'm sorry, but that's a non-update.
And you know what? It's not good enough.
Watch it, Bartowski. It's a U.S.
general you're talking to.
I've spent the last year of my life
being tortured, dangled off of skyscrapers,
bathed in sewage.
Stop me if I've forgotten
any other glamorous perks of this job.
I've continually done everything
that you guys have asked me to do,
but once my dad gets kidnapped,
all you can say is sorry?
Chuck, I understand your disappointment
Do you? Then why haven't we found him yet?
We've captured FULCRUM agents before.
Can't we talk to them?
Yeah, we tried that, but since the new
administration discontinued water-boarding,
FULCRUM agents don't talk.
And even if we did, we have no reason to trust them.
I'm willing to do whatever it takes
by any means necessary.
So what if I could get a FULCRUM agent to talk?
You're 100% sure you want
to go through with this?
More like 45,
maybe... maybe 30.
But I guess I don't really
have any other choice now, do I?
Hi, Chuck.
Hello, Jill.
- Chuck -
- Season 2 Ep 20 -
Fixed to perfection by:
Mithrandir
All the thanks to italiansubs!
So, how's the food?
Standard prison issue, or are they doing
anything fancy with the sauces?
What are you doing here, Chuck?
FULCRUM has kidnapped my father.
They're using him to rebuild their Intersect,
and when he's done...
Look, I don't even want to think about what's
gonna happen when that happens.
Let me guess.
You want my help?
Forget it.
-I get that you're mad at me,
but it's not my fault you're in here.
You betrayed your country.
Yho betrayed me.
I thought you cared about me,
but now, all I'm asking is formy family back, please.
I might be able to help.
But I want a deal.
Do not make a deal. Do not make a deal!
I'm-I'm not... I'm not really authorized
to make any kind of deal.
But in this case, I think
I can make an exception.
Do I work here?
No, no. I just wear this
ridiculous outfit
so that people like you will ask me if I do.
Emmett asked me to give this to you.
Mighty fine cart work.
Emmett?
Hello?
Got this... Got this note.
Milbarge.
-Grimes.
Let me cut to the chase. I despise you.
But these losers listen to you for some reason,
so I need you.
-Talk to me.
I was brought here to make this store efficient.
If corporate sees that, they will have no recourse but to do the
efficient thing and promote me out of this hellhole.
Get your little merry band of misfits
to behave,
and I'll be out of your dirty beard forever.
How do I know that I can... trust you?
-You don't,
but I want out, and you want me out,
so let's...
...make a deal.
I can't believe we made this deal.
If you run or double-cross us,
your deal is void. Plus, as an added bonus,
she'll shoot you.
Chuck's dad- where is he?
-I don't know exactly,
but I do know someone who might know
where they're holding him.
Who?
-My Uncle Bernie.
That better not be a joke,
'cause I don't have a sense of humor.
Yeah, I don't remember you ever mentioning
an Uncle Bernie to mewhen we were dating.
He's not a real uncle.
He's a friend of the family.
He's the one who first recruited me into FULCRUM.
-And how do we know we can trust him?
He's my dad's best friend.
If there's one person I can trust, it's him.
Where's Bernie? We'll flush him out,
torture the location out of him.
He's guarded almost 24 hours a day.
-What does almost mean?
Yeah, when is Bernie away from his bodyguards?
-Usually only for family functions.
Are there any coming up?
Birthdays, confirmations, quiceaneras?
Well, then, I guess we're going to have to
create one on our own.
I'm engaged.
-It's Tacori. It's beautiful.
Oh, well, thanks, Judy.
-No, call me Mom.
Most girls only get four C's with a ring,
but, uh, my Jill- she got five.
Cut, color, clarity, carat, and Chuck.
Isn't this gorgeous?
That ring cost the taxpayers
a fortune, Bartowski.
Don't lose it.
Here they are.
Mr. and Mrs.Bartowski.
So, Jill, this is such a wonderful surprise.
We thought she was living in Helsinki. We...
We didn't know when we'd see her again.
Well, Chuck popped the question,
and I wanted to share it with everybody.
Well, Wally,
I think this calls for a toast.
No, no, no, Dad. You don't... You don't have to do that.
-Listen, I have waited
all my life for my little girl to get married-
you bet I do.
I remember when you first met at Stanford,
the way you'd look at each other...
Just like your mom and I did.
And I know you've had your problems, but
deep inside,
you knew you were right for each other.
And you never let anything get in the way of that.
To Jill and Chuck.
To Jill and Chuck!
Congratulations, Bartowski.
You're now qualified for conjugal visits.
There's a car approaching.
This could be him.
Bartowski, this guy's a madman.
His codename's "The Carnivore."
Seems he's got a real appetite for blood.
Great.
Hey, Bernie, how are you?!
-Great, Wally.
So, what is this big surprise
you couldn't tell me over the phone?
Jill's engaged!
Jill's here? Where?
You are so adorable, Chuck.
You two are gonna have the most beautiful babies.
I want a girl and a boy.
Fulcrum smuggling Drops
Out of towner downs 96 Ouncer
I'm sorry, Chuck, is all this talk of children
scaring you?
No, no, no, I love kids, really, yeah.
JILL!
I thought you moved to Helsinki.
-You're not the only one, Bernie.
You really need to come home more often.
Yeah, I-I barely get to see her myself.
She works so much, she might as well be in prison.
so you're the lucky guy, huh?
It's Chuck, nice to meet you, Bernie.
No, no, no. You call me Uncle Bernie.
We're family now.
We were just telling them that the key
to a good marriage is trust.
Your spouse must be the only
person you always rely on,
who'll never betray you.
you mind if I, uh, borrow the happy couple?
I got a few words of wisdom myself.
-Okay.
Good luck!
Bernie didn't like Jill's last boyfriend and...
that's the last we saw of him.
Is that so?
What are you doing here, Jill?
I thought you were in jail.
I made a deal with the CIA.
-What? What kind of a deal?
Look, Bernie, all you have to do is
tell us where FULCRUM is hiding my father
and we can offer you witness protection, too.
Oh, you stupid little... Are you wired?
-No, we're not.
Are you wired?!
-Yes, yes, we are.
They're gone.
-Let's go.
No, we can't just blast in and
blow Chuck's cover.
Oh, my. Look how happy my baby is.
I'm sorry to interrupt, I just wanted to tell you
that dinner's almost ready, okay?
Thanks, Judy.
-Don't torture them too much, Bernie.
Jill!
Oh, no, no!
Come on, come on, come on!
Hi.
And you are?
-I'm Chuck's cousin, Sarah.
And this is my boyfriend, John.
Talk about beauty and the beast, huh?
You must be loaded!
Just a little friendly ribbing.
We're family now!
Yeah, family.
This is my lovely wife, Judy.
Hello.
Pleased to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
Yeah, so, where's the lucky couple, hmm?
They're having a sit down with, uh,
Uncle Bernie. And if I know him,
Chuck is dead meat by now.
Casey, Sarah, third floor!
We're in trouble! I don't know
if he wants to kill me or eat me!
Is the bathroom upstairs, I hope?
I have to... we had a very long drive.
Where are we going?
-The attic.
The only way out is up.
hey, Casey and Sarah, we're in the attic, we
need some help, A lot of help!
Window!
Jill!
Bernie, please don't do this.
You can't shoot us
because the whole family will hear it.
You're right; I can't.
But I can beat you to death.
I was really hoping for a third option
that did not include death.
Chuck, are you okay?
Yeah.
Congratulations, Bartowski.
It's your first confirmed kill.
Kill? No! No, no, no, no.
I didn't kill anybody, okay?
He just died; it was an accident.
Well, maybe he had a heart attack.
What do you call your move, anyway?
What move?
The girlie pose I saw you in.
What do you call that?
The Morgan.
-The Morgan?
He invented it in high school
when girls were beating him up.
You kind of duck a little bit, protect the
important... You know, your face and your...
What are we gonna do?!
We were telling him about our wedding plans,
and he just kept knocking back scotches
until
the next thing we knew he was dead drunk.
Uh, call me, Bernie!
-Yeah, get some rest!
Okay.
Yeah, we should get him home.
-Okay.
I love you. Take care of yourself.
Good-bye, everyone!
-Coungratulations!
See ya!
-Thanks!
We'll take care of Bernie.
Way to go, killer. You just offed the only person
who knows where your dad is
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
Wow, Morgan.
They look great.
I may look good, but I feel like an idiot.
Anybody sees or hears about this,
my rep is ruined.
Can you relax? Relax and trust me, please.
This is the only way
we're gonna get Emmett out of our hair.
No pain, no gain, remember?
As you can see, we're running
smoother than a Swiss watch.
You'll find no finer example of Buy More
employees in the land.
Mr. Patel here is one of our certified
computer technicians.
Very pleased to meet you, sir.
-And may I just say,
I would do pretty much
anything for this man. He is...
...somewhat of a hero around here.
A constant brownnoser.
Well, he was born brown.
May I go a step further and say that,
uh, to me, Emmett is the straw
that gently stirs the Buy More drink.
I can't tell you how many times I
defiled myself at work.
Emmett cured me of that.
Now I only violate  myself at home
or in the car.
But never in the Nerd Herder.
He has made such progress under Mr. Milbarge's...
...tutelage. We're all so proud.
I'm your captain.
-Yes, captain, my captain.
Let me show you around.
You better be right about this, Morgan.
Yes, General, I understand.
Sarah, what's happening?
-We're moving Jill back to prison.
What? No, we can't..
We can't send her back.
We haven't found my father yet.
She still might know somethingand we had a deal.
Chuck, I'm sorry but the mission was a bust
and Jill only put us into more danger.
That wasn't her fault! It was Bernie! He
manipulated and betrayed her!
You know Jill.
She's a FULCRUM agent.
Exactly! That's exactly why we need her.
She knows FULCRUM; their procedures and secrets.
Look, I know she tried to kill you
and I'm sorry about that,
but she is the best chance I have
at rescuing my father.
He's out there somewhere and God only knows
what's happening to him.
Chuck, you have to realize that there are some
people that you just cannot trust.
Sarah...
I already know that.
I don't trust anyone.
Except for you.
And right now I need you to trust me.
Jill is the only way I'm gonna get my dad back.
Chuck, the answer is no.
Hey, buddy.
Chuck, where you been, man?
I've been calling you all day.
I'm sorry, buddy, I've just been a
little a little busy, that's all.
All right, well, listen,
we have a situation here at the Buy More
and I could really use your help.
I'm on an install.
I- I can't help you right now.
Okay, well, just bear with me for one second here, okay?
What do you do when the person
that you think you can trust the least
can actually get you the thing you want the most?
You know what, Morgan?
Sometimes you just need to trust a person.
Do whatever it takes.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Roger that.
Thanks, buddy.
I'm sorry.
They're sending you back to prison.
Well, it's not your fault.
At least I got to see my family one last time.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you, Chuck.
It's okay.
I'm sorry about your Uncle Bernie.
I had no idea The Morgan was so lethal.
I'm glad you haven't lost your sense of humor.
They changed me.
Promise me that you won't let them change you.
I'll do my best.
I liked wearing this.
Even if it was just for a few hours.
They were never gonna let me go,
even if we found your dad, were they?
NSA, FULCRUM, CIA- they're all the same.
They all lie.
They're not gonna let you go either, Chuck.
Watch your back.
Skip, I can tell you got a bright future
ahead of you. It's a pleasure meeting you.
Well? When are you out of here?
We've done everything that you asked.
Not everything.
The hoi polloi have bowed to me,
but now the king
must kiss my ring.
Oh, come on.
Man, why don't you just have
Mr. Mercer speak to Big Mike directly?
Because Big Mike needs me.
He'll never say kind words about me,
because if I were to leave, he has to work,
and then he has to start expending
all of his energy on the store.
Rather than expending it on your mother.
Okay, okay, hold on a second.
-Yes?
What-what, uh...
what do you want me to do?
Use this, and get him to say nice words about me.
When Mr. Mercer hears Michael rave,
he will finally release me from Satan's pit,
and it will be your paradise.
Here's the thing. Big Mike's never going to
speak to me about another employee, okay.
The man's like a wall of stone when it comes to
breaching Buy More policy.
Please. Every man has a weakness to exploit.
Mine is Renaissance fairs.
Just soften him up a little bit. Grease his wheels.
-Grease him?
What is that Michael just cannot get enough of?
What can I do for you, son?
Well I had an extra chicken teriyaki footlong
I thought someone would be
interested in?
-Do tell.
Five-dollar footlong.
Oh, boy.
Chicken teriyaki. Yep.
A taste of the Orient in Burbank.
The flavors melt together in perfect harmony.
Just like me and your mama.
Can I ask you a question?
What do you think of Emmett?
I really don't think I should talk about
other employees in front of you, Morgan.
Well, don't-don't think of me as an employee...
Dad.
You think of me as
family.
You're right.
If you can't trust family...
who can you trust?
I guess this is good-bye, huh?
Yeah.
Well, thanks for trying.
Ugh. Disgusting.
Oh, God.
If it's FULCRUM, this could be my last
chance to find out where they put my dad.
Don't answer that, Bartowski.
Bernie. Talk to me.
We're moving Orion. Bill wants all agents
back to base.
They're moving my dad,
and they want all the agents back at the base.
Okay, keep him on the line.
We're going to trace his call.
Yeah, yeah, I'll, uh,
I'll be back at the base
pronto, but first there's a couple
of things I'd like to discuss.
Discuss? Discuss what?
You know, you know, stuff.
Stuff to discuss.
particularly my salary.
Your salary?
I've been burning the midnight oil,
and if you ask me, my work speaks for itself.
Bernie, what the hell are you talking about?
Also,
there are other pertinent things
that we could talk about.
Including, but not limited to...
the dental plan and vacation days.
And I could use a gym membership.
Have you looked at me?
Excellent. Good. We'll talk about it at the base. Bye.
Dental plan? Moron.
Okay, it looks like the call came
from 1600 Destefano Court.
It's an office building somewhere off Mulholland.
I- I know that building.
It's the headquarters for the
Strength Leadership Corporation.
They run CEO and management training seminars,
but really that's just a front
for a FULCRUM recruiting facility.
Why-why would they take my dad there?
Because they have holding cells
for prisoners on the eighth floor.
We better hustle. Let'go.
-Take me with you. I've been there before.
I know my way around the building
and the security system.
Guys, we need her.
Chuck, you can't trust anyone.
I know it looks look like a boring office
building, but it's run by FULCRUM.
Casey, she's right, these are not pencil pushers.
These are FULCRUM assassins.
Relax, killer. The going gets rough,
you can always deploy The Morgan.
Chuck, we've tapped into the security feed.
I'm watching your every move.
You're going to be safe.
When you get to the desk,
tell him you're here for Auditing.
What, is that like accounting?
No, it's like testing.
Can I help you, gentlemen?
-Yes, we're here for Auditing.
Second floor. Up the stairs.
Okay, now, go past the testing
center down the hallway to the elevator.
The holding cells are on the eighth floor.
Okay, make a right
and go down the hallway.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Uh, we're, uh...
we're here for the Auditing.
Who set the meeting?
Tell him Mr. Dornhoffer.
-Mr. Dornhoffer.
You're on the wrong floor.
Oh, we were told eight.
-Eight.
No? Okay.
Sorry about that.
But it's a... it's a common mistake I'm sure.
Chuck, just do what he says.
I'll find another way
to get to your dad.
You two are late.
Sorry.
Before the test, we have a brief video
for you to watch.
Welcome to FULCRUM.
Solving tomorrow's problems...today.
We live in a dangerous world.
And you want to do something about it.
Do you have what it takes?
We're about to find out.
Good luck on the test, comrades.
You may begin.
What do we do now?
You have to take the test, Chuck.
You don't want to raise their suspicions.
To begin test press Start
I hate these tests.
I'm not gonna cheat.
You're kidding, right?
-No, I'm not kidding.
Found them on the eighth floor, Mr. Bergey.
Said they were lost, were here for Auditing.
Well, let's find out who they really are.
System - Facial Recognition...
Analyzing.
Subject: John Casey
Affiliation: NSA
Subject: Charles Bartowski
Affiiation: Unknown, Son of Stephen
Here to rescue your father, Charles?
I must say, Emmett, I'm impressed.
The store's running smoothly.
The employees, for some strange reason,
respect you.
Now if I could only find Big Mike.
Oh, he took the day off.
What? Why would
Michael take the day off?
You're looking at him. Please.
Listen.
Emmett's a good worker. Thanks to Emmett,
I can fish three times a week
and the store never misses a beat.
In fact, I'm-I'm gonna take the rest of the day off,
do a little fishing this afternoon.
-Okay.
I came down here to evaluate
Big Mike and he's off fishing?
Well, Emmett,
you've been gunning for Mike's job all year.
It's yours.
Good luck...
...store manager.
-Thank you.
Test Complete
Congratulations.
Your test score was very impressive.
Bill Bergey, our seminar leader,
would like to meet you.
Bill Bergey's head of recruiting.
He'll know where Chuck's dad is.
How did I do?
-I'm sorry, sir. You failed.
In fact, I'm afraid you had one of the
lowest scores we've ever had.
Come with me, Mr. Carmichael.
you know, what-what my friend lacks in the
intellect department, he does make up for in brawn.
Certainly, you must have some kind of a job
moving boxes or heavy equipment?
Come with me, Mr. Carmichael.
-Okay.
Casey, stand down.
Just let Chuck go.
We can track him using his watch.
May I help sir?
This way.
This way, Agent Casey.
Talk to me, Walker. I'm all clear.
-Okay, Chuck's on the 15th floor.
He's heading to the far west side
of the building. It's a secure area.
You're going to need a way in.
hello, welcome. I'm Bill Bergey.
-Charles Carmichael.
Nice to meet you. Please sit down.
-Thank you.
So...
I know who you really are, Charles.
That your father is Orion.
Orion?
Uh, I'm not really tracking.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm-I'm just here for the... for the seminar.
Leadership first, right?
well, then you're out of luck.
The seminar is full.
Are you wearing a wire?
-That's preposterous.
-Yes, yes, I am.
Chuck?
Okay, Casey, they've got him. I'm going in.
-You have to take me with you.
And how do I know I can trust you?
-You don't. But you need my help,
and we're the only chance Chuck's got.
You made a big mistake coming here to rescue him.
Intruder alert, 15th floor.
-Sir, we have a break in.
Security breech.
Watch him.
He tries to escape, shoot him.
Guys, look, honestly, I'm not going
to try and escape. Scout's honor.
CIA intrusion- get everyone out.
We're out of here.
Looks like I passed that test.
-Where's Sarah?
She came to rescue you,
got pinned down by some FULCRUM agents.
Okay... let's go get my dad.
-Your test-taking skills
won't do any good out there. Get on the
computer. Find out which room he's in.
Please exit in orderly fasion
Jill, which office is Chuck in?
Jill?
Casey, Jill escaped.
Let's go, let's go.
Destroy the hard drives!
Go to cell 11- move Orion to Black Rock.
No time to waste- Orion's too valuable.
We'll talk again at Black Rock.
Get away from that computer, now!
I just want my father back.
-Good news, bad news, Charles.
The good news is that your father
is too valuable for us to kill.
The bad news?
You're not.
Now, step away from the...
What is it with that move?
Help. -Oh, God.
-Help me.
Help! Please, please, somebody, I need help!
Pull me up!
-I'm trying! I'm trying!
Look, please, please, tell me where my father is.
-Or what, you'll drop me?
I'd never drop you- that's a horrible thing
to do to somebody.
Really?
-Yeah,
it's a 15-story fall. It's an awful way to die.
Pull me up, I'll talk.
-Hold on.
Hold on, Chuck, I got you.
No, he's slipping. Hurry, he's slipping.
Hold on.
Oh, God... oh, God.
Thank you.
Look, we have to get to my dad now.
-Eighth floor- let's go.
That's for flunking me.
Miss me?
-Yeah, immensely. Jill's gone.
What happened?
Well, he attacked me.
I did The Morgan, and he flew out the window.
Two kills in two days, Chuck.
that Morgan move is real killer.
Dad!
We're too late.
I'm never going to find him, am I?
Wait, I overhead them say that
they were moving your father to a place
I never heard of, a place called Black Rock.
Oh, my God.
I know where they're taking him.
Black Rock is a code name for Protocol 7,
a secret FULCRUM base in Barstow.
How do you know that, Chuck?
You don't want to know.
Chuck, can you hear me?
I'm on the eighth floor.
They've already evacuated my dad.
Okay, hold tight. We're on our way.
-Okay, come on.
What are you doing?
-Don't move.
Look, Jill, there was no deal.
I lied to you because, at the time, I was willing
to do whatever it took to find my father,
but not anymore.
You held up your side of the bargain,
and I'm going to hold up mine.
I told you I wouldn't let them change me, and I won't.
Thank you, Chuck.
Look, you should go before they get here.
-Okay.
But, Jill,
look, you're going to be all alone out there.
No friends, no money, nothing.
This is worth a lot.
Casey's probably going to kill me.
I always dreamt of giving you a ring, Jill...
just not like this.
You're sure you can trust them, right?
Go.
Welcome back to gen pop, Michael.
Good luck.
I know it was you, Morgan.
You broke my heart.
I don't want anything to happen to him
as long as his mom and I are dating.
How could you let
Jill Roberts get away?
I'm sorry, General, I took her inside the
building because I didn't have a choice.
So, not only do we have no idea where
Steve Bartowski is,
we have a FULCRUM agent
who knows all of our secrets running free.
Where is Chuck now?
He's on his way to the Buy More.
Permission to drop the twerp into
a deep dark hole, General.
Granted.
Huh?
-It's over
the Human Intersect project
has become too hard to control.
I can't afford to wonder anymore if
this team or Chuck Bartowski
is a liability.
What are you saying, General?
I'm Shutting down this project.
Chuck's going into lockdown.
He'll be taken to Washington
and put into a secured facility
once and for all.
Operation "Moron" is over?
You are making a mistake, General.
I have made my decision, agent Walker.
Chuck isn't gonna go down
without a fight.
That's why there won't be one.
What do you mean?
Chuck trusts you, Sarah.
He believes you would
never betray him. Use that.
Go to Chuck.
Tell him that we intercepted his
father while being transported,
And he's back at Castle.
Trusted the wrong person, Chuck.
Agent Casey will be waiting here.
He will trank Chuck.
Then he will wait for the
extraction team to arrive for his transfer.
That is all.
How can you just stand there
and say nothing?
Beckman's right, safest place
for Chuck is underground.
What do you think is gonna
happen when FULCRUM finds Jill anyway?
We have good news.
-Can it wait? Computer emergency.
It's about your father.
We found him.
What? How? Where is he?
One of our recon teams intercepted
his trasport as FULCRUM was moving him.
He's back at the castle.
He's safe, Chuck.
It's all over.
I owe you an apology.
Why?
I was beginning to think that i couldn't
trust you anymore, Sarah.
That maybe Jill was right, that the CIA
was never gonna let me go,
That they would always put their
best interest ahead of mine.
But not you.
You've always looked out for me,
Thank you.
Take off your watch.
Why?
-Because it's all a lie.
Your dad is still out there, Beckman
sent me to get you to bring you back to the castle.
They're gonna take you underground.
We have to run.
You're disobeying orders for me?
You're commiting treason, Sarah.
You could go to jail.
I Know.
- Chuck -
- Season 2 Ep 20 -
Fixed to perfection by:
Mithrandir
All the thanks to italiansubs!
www.tvsubtitles.net