Here's a couple of things that you might
need to know or maybe you just forgot.
Hannah, there are things in my
life that you can't understand.
So I have to end this.
Chuck, I think we need to talk.
Not a good time.
Are you suggesting Chuck
is caught in a big,
giant web of conspiracy
and deception?
I'm gonna have to lie
to your sister,
and I can't do that
anymore.
From now on, if Ellie
asks you something,
just say "I don't know."
You two got it bad
for this blond.
It's about keeping his emotions
in check so that the Intersect
can work.
Flash.
Come on.
You know what, Casey?
You're right.
I don't work. My emotions
just mess everything up.
* *
Hey, guys, I got your call.
What's, uh...
What's going on?
You're the Intersect.
You tell us.
We've intercepted intel
that the Ring
is planning to turn and use
a CIA agent against us.
The problem is, we don't
know who, when or where.
Did you flash?
Uh, yeah. Not, uh, not flashing.
You haven't flashed
in a week, Chuck.
Ever since Rafe tried
to kill Sarah and me.
That's a problem.
Problem?
Really? Problem?
Kind of a strong word,
don't you think? Just 'cause
a guy had a couple off nights.
Off nights get agents killed.
You need to
figure this out, because the
Intersect's not working.
And I can't risk putting you
out in the field.
Okay, so, what exactly
are you saying?
I'm saying that until
you start flashing again,
you're no longer a spy.
No. No.
No, you can't...
you can't do that.
Being a spy is all
that I have.
I gave up everything for this.
Well, maybe some time off
will do you good, Chuck.
It'll help you
function again.
I don't need- I don't
need time off, okay?
Maybe I'm not flashing
because I have all these
emotions bottled up in me.
You ever thought about that?
I mean, I just broke up
with Hannah,
I can't talk to my best friend
or my sister
about anything in my life.
I'm not a machine.
Okay, I am a machine,
but I'm also a person.
Well, you can always talk to us.
Yeah, uh, no thanks.
I don't think that's going
to work for me.
Find something
that does work.
Because until you do,
you're benched.
* *
Mmm, this getaway was
the perfect idea, honey.
It's just what we needed.
You said it, babe.
I can't tell you how awesome
it feels to be alone,
just the two of us.
Mmm.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'll be just a sec.
Hey, Chuck.
Awesome, hey. Thank God
you picked up.
Everything okay, Chuck?
No, no, not really.
I broke up with Hannah,
and-and Sarah's falling
for another guy.
Not only is my personal life
a mess,
but my spy life, too...
Chuck, I went on vacation to get
away from your spy life.
Okay? And to fix things
with Ellie.
No, no. Devon, Devon, Devon.
Devon, Devon, I don't have
anyone else to talk to.
I'm sorry, bro.
But remember what you said about
discussing your spy life:
I don't know.
I say he can get
it in there,
but I agree with you,
it seems impossible.
So, put your
wagers in.
Put your wager- you are
going to win this, children!
What do you got
in your pockets?
MORGAN
Charles Irving Bartowski,
please report to the assistant
manager's office
for disciplinary action.
Right? Ah.
Oh!
Oh, my!
This is a shocker!
He got it in.
I'm saying, do not wager
against the brown beauty
and the snake.
He can unhinge his jaw
and he sheds skin.
Have a seat, please.
You need anything?
You okay?
Uh, no, I'm-I'm-I'm good.
I mean, you know, maybe a little
more leg room would be nice.
This conversation
is never
an easy one to have
with an employee, Chuck.
And what conversation
would that be, exactly?
We've known each other
most of our lives.
Hmm.
We, uh, we went
through puberty together.
We went through the awkward
stage after puberty,
the awkward high school years,
your awkward college years,
and now, our current
awkward Buy More years.
Which is why
this moment for
me is so very...
Awkward?
Yeah.
Morgan, what exactly is
going on?
Something is.
Something is going on
in your life.
You dumped Hannah.
She quit the Buy More.
She was a valued member
of the store.
And I just feel that
a true best friend
would share that
with his true best friend.
You really want
to know the truth?
I do.
Lay it on me like a slice of
cheese on a tuna melt.
I am ready.
Okay, here goes.
I...
Okay. Got it.
You don't have to say any more. Say wha
-?
I didn't say anything.
Mor- do you need help?
I'm fine. No.
I cannot believe
I'm saying this, but...
you're fired.
Wha- what?
You're firing me
from the Buy More?
Buy More? No,
are you kidding me?
You're the best
Nerd Herder we have.
I need you here.
I'm firing you
as my best friend.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
Hey! You guys, uh-
you guys leaving
on the mission?
You sure you don't
want me to join?
We'd love you to, Chuck,
but the Intersect
is not working.
The agent that
the Ring plans
to turn is staying
at this hotel.
We have no record
of any spy being there,
so whoever it is
is deep undercover.
Yeah, I'm-I'm-I'm sorry.
I'm still not flashing.
We've got to go.
Guys,
the team's a man short
without me.
Not today. I'm taking
your place on this mission.
The Ring knows that
you're still alive, Shaw.
It's too dangerous for you
to be in the field.
And I can't leave this team
shorthanded.
Besides, if the Ring wants a
fight, I'll give them a fight.
Now... when we get back
I expect this place
to be exactly
as I left it.
You two newlyweds ready?
Yeah, let's go.
What's with the-the... rings?
What...?
Hey, Casey. What am
I supposed to do
while you're gone?
Don't you have a day job?
Hey, what's going on, guys?
Shh!
Charles, please!
It's a spy mission. You are
not qualified. Get away.
I...
49...
57, 43.
40.
El Segundo School
of Finance,
we take care of business!
What's going on
here, Big Mike?
Someone's thinking
of buying the store.
We're closing today
so some building
inspectors and technicians can
come down and kick the tires.
Sweet. We get the day off.
Jeffrey, let's get
pershnickered.
No.
They want to interview everyone.
Reevaluate the entire staff.
Gonna fire everyone
who's not essential.
So, I can get started over here.
We're in big trouble, boys.
Here are your keys.
Enjoy your stay here
at the Malibu Vista Hotel.
Might I add that the two of you
are a very beautiful couple.
Oh. Thank you.
You two lovebirds have fun
while I'm cooped up
in the van again.
Have a margarita for me.
There's a Ring agent
somewhere in this hotel.
We need to find him.
I tapped into the phone's
mainframe.
If the Ring calls out again,
we can trace it
back to the room
it originated from.
Sarah and I have set up
the surveillance equipment.
We'll begin searching
for possible targets.
Listen up, team.
These suits are sharks.
They'll try to divide us in our
interviews, find our weaknesses,
look for any excuse they
can to fire our asses.
Yeah, yeah.
Listen, despite our differences,
all we have is each other.
So let's, uh, let's stick
together here, all right?
This is a blood oath
right here.
One for all, and all for one.
All right.
Lester Patel?
Yeah, I've found it!
Found it! Contact lens.
All crisis averted.
I love you guys.
Come on down.
All right.
Oh, my God.
We're doomed.
Have a seat, yeah.
Okay, so...
before I spill this
place's dirty secrets,
I want to know
that I'm protected.
I want diplomatic immunity.
I- I don't think it's appropriate
in this situation.
Bah, bah, bah, bah bah, bah,
bah. You want the dirt?
I want immunity.
Okay.
Immunity granted.
Thank you, my brother.
Well...
it's an interesting
group of employees
you put together here.
Oh, they scare me, too.
But I got Bartowski, don't I?
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
A man
with a Stanford degree
is working here.
You see, gentlemen, I'm
not just a manager;
I'm a people person.
Talent follows me.
Morgan Grimes, assistant
manager, how are you, sir?
Morgan, hey, buddy,
I need to talk to you.
Clearly you don't, Chuck,
or I wouldn't have fired you
as my best friend.
Can I please just have a minute?
Not now, Chuck, all right?
I'm freaking out about
this interview, man.
Look. Hey, buddy?
You're going to be fine.
Besides, it's only the Buy More.
You can always get another job.
It's not the end of
the world. Really?
See, it may not be the end
of the world to you,
but I don't have
a Stanford degree, Chuck.
I can't do anything else
but the Buy More.
This job is all I have.
I...
Chuck Bartowski? You're up.
That's an impressive
résumé.
So what's a Stanford grad doing
working at a Buy More?
Uh, you know, let's just say
the-the Buy More offers
more opportunities than
initially meets the eye.
Really?
For instance?
For instance, I get to work
with my best friend every day.
Your best friend?
Yeah.
Yeah, Morgan Grimes.
The, uh, the assistant manager.
Based on your
track record,
you're the cream
of this Buy More crop.
Why aren't you the
assistant manager?
Because the right guy
has already got the job.
I- I know that you guys
are maybe gonna be
making some changes around here,
so I just want you to
know that while I might
look good on paper, I'm
not the cream of the crop.
Morgan Grimes is.
Okay, the Ring just made
a call from the hotel.
I'll connect you in
while I trace it back.
The target is by the pool.
Six foot two, well built.
He's wearing a blue
and white bathing suit.
You got that, Walker?
Yeah, I got it.
Did you find the target?
Yeah, we found him.
Cheers.
Oh, it's so nice.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you, too.
Yeah, good egg.
Yeah.
Really good egg, yeah.
Really good egg.
Well, ha-have
a good day.
Hey, you too.
Take care.
Get the others in here.
So, you really think this
Bartowski guy is
Agent Carmichael?
Oh, it's Carmichael,
all right.
Looks like Shaw left him
behind to man the fort.
Should we abort the mission?
No, with Shaw not here,
it's our best chance to
infiltrate and recover
everything he has on us.
Have you found the entrance
into Shaw's base yet?
No.
We don't have much time.
We have to find it fast.
Do you want us
to take out Bartowski?
Not yet.
Let's keep interviewing
employees and make sure
Shaw didn't leave any
other surprises behind.
Chuck said Grimes
is his best friend.
We can use both of them
to our advantage.
What do you want me
to do about the others?
I think we need to
be conservative here.
Getting away is the best thing
we could've done, babe.
I know I haven't been
the same guy lately,
but since we got here,
I gotta tell you,
I feel awesome again.
Me, too.
To us.
No stress, no work,
no problemas.
The call came from Room 4305.
I'll head there now
and search it.
We'll go down to the pool,
get Devon and Ellie
out of harm's way.
Come on, flash!
Hmm.
Uh... no.
Oh, I know, I know this.
I know this.
Uh, uh, The Condor?
Uh, The Jackal?
Chan Min Chi.
Damn it, I thought
I had that one.
This better be good.
Hey, yeah, hey, just, just
checking in on the mission.
Seeing if you guys
needed anything.
Why, are you flashing now?
No, I'm not. But I thought,
you know, maybe if you throw me
the rock, I'll pop on something.
I don't have time
for this, Bartowski.
Only as good as your
last flash, huh?
Mmm, two more Piña Coladas
coming right up.
Looks good.
How's the water?
What are you two doing here?
You're not supposed
to be here.
I just reclaimed my
awesomeness. We got a tip that
the Ring was trying
to turn an agent
staying at this hotel.
You.
Me?
But I'm not an agent.
Chuck told me that
I was in the clear.
Are Ellie and I in danger?
I don't know.
I can't believe they're
selling the Buy More.
Oh, man, I think they're really
serious about buying this place.
'Cause they have been going
through it with a fine tooth comb.
Even checking lockers.
NEIL It was really
great talking to you.
Jeffrey Barnes?
You gotta help me, Morgan.
I got contraband in my locker.
What kind of contraband?
Just a little something I use
to take the edge off
on a stressful day.
If they find it,
Ill be fired for sure.
Mr. Barnes...
Morgan, please.
Okay.
Okay, all right, dude.
I'm at the Ring
agent's room.
I'm going in.
Be careful.
I'm always careful.
The target is by the pool.
Six foot two, well built.
He's wearing a blue
and white bathing suit.
Our operatives are in position.
Ugh, it's a set-up.
I gotta get Ellie out of here.
I got to get both of us
out of here right now.
Keep it together, Devon.
We'll figure this out.
What? What was that?
I'm so sorry, false alarm.
Wait, you crashed
my weekend getaway
to tell me I'm in danger
and now you tell me what,
we're safe?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Please try and enjoy
the rest of your vacation.
We gotta get
away from this.
Oh, my God.
Let's see if we can find
anything in the break room.
Found something.
There's a tunnel
behind these lockers.
Fingerprint scanner.
This must be it.
Go get Del and Neil.
Tell them we found
the CIA base.
Good work.
Tell the others
we found Shaw's base.
Oh, my God.
This is not right, no!
You understand me?
Hey.
What's going on?
My spy work paid
off, obviously.
I mic'd Big Mike's office.
All I got was a few seconds,
but come in, listen.
Chuck said Grimes
is his best friend.
We can use both of them
to our advantage.
What do you want me
to do about the others?
I think we need to be
conservative here,
terminate the rest.
They're gonna fire
the entire store,
except you and Morgan.
I just got this job back.
Where is Morgan?
Clever, putting a CIA base
under an electronics store.
Every piece of
intelligence Shaw has
on the Ring is in here.
We'll be putting a dagger
through the heart of
the CIA's operation
by taking it out.
All right, Neil, you're on.
Cut off any and all
communications coming
in and out of the store.
Break into the mainframe,
find and destroy
everything they have on us.
Then blow this base sky high.
Be a pleasure.
The phone works remotely.
It was a set-up;
they've lured us here.
Why would they
lure us here?
It's not where
they lured us to,
it's where they
lured us from.
The Ring knows I'm alive,
which means they know
I'll have a base
of operations somewhere.
They sent us here
so I'd abandon my base.
That way they
can go and recover
all the intelligence
we have on them.
They weren't after Devon.
They're after Castle.
Chuck's in there,
and he's not flashing.
He's a sitting duck.
Go!
Hey, Morgan, we need to talk.
Chuck, we gotta talk, listen.
Me first okay, trust me,
whatever you're gonna say
is nothing compared
to what I got.
Hmm?
Okay.
Fine, yeah, please, shoot.
Okay, uh...
Dude, there's a secret
underground CIA base
under our Buy More.
I... Hey, listen,
I know it sounds crazy,
but you have to
believe me here, okay?
These people who are
claiming to buy the store,
they're bad guys, okay?
And they call
themselves the Ring.
Which I know is like,
ooh, not that scary...
But trust me, these guys
are not to be messed with.
How do you, how do you, how
do you know all this, Morgan?
Okay, I was hiding.
I was hiding in there,
and I saw them enter the base
through an entrance
behind our lockers.
So, I followed them.
I heard and saw everything.
Hey, whoa, whoa, dude, listen, I
know this is a lot for you to handle,
but you gotta stay with me,
you gotta pull together.
'Cause we are now in
real danger here, okay?
Buddy?
Don't freak out.
Chuck's not answering
his cell.
Buy More land line's down.
I can't get through either.
I think we should
call the police.
That's a great idea.
That is a great idea, man.
Wow, wow, yeah, yeah.
What...
Wha... Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
I don't, I don't,
I don't have a signal.
Right, right.
Bad guys probably cut off all
communication to the store.
It makes sense.
You know what?
By the time the cops got here
it'd be too late, anyway.
We need to handle this now.
No, no, no, no, Morgan.
We don't need to do anything,
except get everyone
out of the store.
Charles Irving Bartowski,
listen to yourself!
These men are trying to blow up
a CIA base under our store.
Okay, we are Buy More's-
America's last
line of defense.
And we are going
to take the fight to them.
Morgan, listen to yourself
right now.
This is not a video game.
This is real life.
People get hurt.
There is no restart
from last checkpoint.
I understand
that you're scared, okay?
And that not everybody
has the stomach to be a hero.
So I'll just go see if Jeff
and Lester want to help,
and, well...
Okay, look, fine,
fine, fine.
I will help you
on one condition.
We get everyone else out of
the store first, and what
you've told me remains a
secret between the two of us.
Yes, yes.
You know what?
No need to put
everyone else at risk.
We will handle this, okay?
And this secret is locked down.
What's going on?
We're locking down
the store, Charles.
We're refusing to leave until
they give us our jobs back.
No, gu-guys, that is a very...
Please, don't-
don't do that.
Don't put that there.
Don't, do... Stop! Stop!
Stop putting things down.
Look, locking down the store is
a very, very, very bad idea.
You two want to turn tail
and run, fine.
I'm staying here and fighting
for my job.
Mike, gentlemen, assorted
ladies, taking over the Buy More
is not only illegal, but it's
very dangerous, trust me.
The only thing dangerous
is if they try to fire us.
They're going to have to
do it over dead bodies.
These corporate fat cats
think they can take
whatever they want.
They can take
our dignity,
they can take all the hot women,
but they will not take our jobs!
And they will never take
our store!
Buy More!
Sarah, Shaw, Casey,
can you hear me?
You have to... your frequency.
* *
Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
What's going on?
Oh, thank God.
Thank God.
Listen, listen, listen.
The Ring is inside Castle, guys.
They came in posing as buyers
trying to purchase the store.
We're on our way back.
Sit tight.
This is for you. Mace.
I know it's not much,
but it'll have to do.
Emmett kept a stockpile in case the
Russians attacked Red Dawn style.
This is for you also. Walkie-talkie.
Don't drop it. It's expensive.
You ready to do this? Let's do
this. No, no, no, no, no, Morgan.
Listen, on second thought, I-I-I
don't think we should do this.
No, maybe you're right.
Let's get out of here.
Right? Maybe get a little
burger or something...
Are you kidding me, Chuck?!
Men are trying to blow up
a CIA base here, okay?
Time is running out.
Time to step up.
No, no.
Morgan, you don't want
to do this, okay?
Trust me, you don't understand.
You don't understand, Chuck. I've
been a loser my whole entire life
and I'm done with that, okay?
Time for me to be a hero.
But-but what is a hero, really,
you know?
You're all alone,
Agent Carmichael.
I've locked down the base.
Sir, who's Agent Carmichael?
Okay? You're crazy.
This guy is crazy, Chuck.
Thinks you're a spy.
Yeah, yeah, th-that's
ridiculous, thinking I'm a spy.
Ridiculous, sir.
Okay, listen to me, we
work at the Buy More, all right?
And if you just- if you
let us go, I promise
we're not going to tell anyone
what you're doing here.
Tell him, Chuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, n-not a word.
Zipping it. Locking it down.
Locked, it's already locked down.
That is a really
sharp looking razor.
We've searched the
base's main frame.
Shaw's files aren't there.
We know that he's
hiding them here.
Tell us where they are,
Agent Carmichael.
Trust me-
the alternative
is extremely unpleasant.
You know, I don't think there's
any need for torture right now,
because even if I was a spy,
which I'm not-
I'm not saying that I am a spy-
but even if I was a spy,
my training would have taught me
to withstand said torture.
So I don't really think it's
going to have any kind
of effect at this particular
juncture, right?
That's why I'm going
to torture him.
You made the mistake
of telling us
the bearded fella's
your best friend.
For the last time-
where are the files,
Agent Carmichael?
Guys, guys, please, please,
please just listen to me.
This is ridiculous, okay?
I have known this man my
entire life, all right?
Chuck Bartowski has been
my best friend- my brother-
since we were six.
Chuck Bartowski is not a spy.
Chuck?
Chuck! Chuck!
Chuck, please!
Tell him something! Tell
him the truth! Chuck!
I'm really scared here!
Chuck!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, stop, stop! Chuck!
Stop, stop.
Morgan, the-the truth is...
The truth is... I am a member
of a joint NSA-CIA
black ops team
that is stationed
here in Burbank.
I have a level six clearance,
and my code name
is Charles Carmichael.
I'm a spy, buddy.
Sarah, anything?
We're locked out. They overwrote
our security access.
I'm locked out here.
Casey's checking
the Buy More.
Cease fire, cease fire.
Hold your- hold your fire.
Unlock the door.
What the hell is going on
in here?
The store's being bought.
They're canning everybody
except Bartowski and Grimes.
We're staging a revolution
to take down the Man.
I want in.
How do we know that we can
trust you, son?
That you're not some kind of spy
for the Man?
Because the only thing
I hate more
than hippie neo-liberal fascists
and anarchists...
are the hypocrite
fat-cat suits
they eventually grow up
to become.
Yep, that works for me.
Good-good-good point.
Nice to chat.
Welcome aboard, my brother.
You're a spy?
You remember what
I just said
about freaking out? I think
you're doing that right now,
and-and-and you shouldn't
do that.
You're a spy?
Stay with me, buddy, okay?
You two can kiss
and make up later.
Where are Shaw's files?
Now, Chuck!
We've got visitors.
Colonel Casey and Agent Walker
decided to join
the party.
Casey and Sarah
are spies, too?
You have a lot of
catching up to do.
Excuse me while I take care
of your friends.
We'll save the torture
for later.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't- I can't believe it.
All this time,
you kept this
a secret?
From me?
I'm so sorry, Morgan.
You have no idea how badly
I've wanted to tell you.
All this lying about
where I've been.
You know, making plans
and breaking them.
And-And all the time,
all I've wanted to do
is tell you all about it, but...
but I had to protect
you, too, you know?
Please understand that.
Wow...
Wow!
I don't...
My best friend is a spy?!
This is unbelievable!
This is the best news
I've ever heard!
Holy smokes, it makes
perfect sense, too.
Why we stopped
hanging out and talking.
I thought I lost you, buddy.
I thought I lost you.
But you were out
saving the world?
Chuck, you are officially
rehired as my best friend.
Great. That's
good news. Thanks.
Oh, I have so many questions.
I mean, wh-wh-where do I start?
Uh, how did this happen?
Did they recruit you
at the Buy More? Stanford?
Chuck? Yeah, I'm pretty sure
we're going to die here, Chuck,
so no time for secrets.
You know what,
you're right, buddy.
You're right. And-And...
and quite frankly,
you deserve to know.
So here goes- you ready?
Yeah. Yeah, man.
Okay.
This all started about
two and a half years ago
when I got an e-mail
from Bryce Larkin...
* Some folks are born
made to wave the flag *
* Ooh, the red,
white and blue *
* And when the band plays
"Hail to the Chief" *
* Ooh, they point
their cannon at you, Lord *
* It ain't me, it ain't me *
* I ain't no senator's son,
son *
* It ain't me, it ain't me *
* I ain't no fortunate one, no *
What the hell is that noise?
The Buy More employees
have staged a revolution.
So that's the sound
of liberty? Mm-hmm.
* But when the taxman
comes to the door *
* Lord, the house looks
like a rummage sale... *
Good news, bad news.
The good news- we found what
we were looking for.
I've uploaded it
to headquarters.
The bad news, Colonel Casey's
arrived at the Buy More.
Could be a problem.
Not if he's dead. Kill him.
* Whoo *
* It ain't me, it ain't me *
* I ain't no fortunate one,
no, no, no *
* It ain't me, it ain't me *
* I ain't no fortunate son. *
Peace out, man.
Hey, brother Casey,
make love not war.
You want a hit?
Hey, man,
that's not cool.
Fight the power.
Yeah. Peace out.
Crap!
Castle has a self-destruct
program built into it
in case of catastrophic
events like this.
I'm calling Langley
to activate it now.
You can't destroy the Castle.
Chuck is down there.
So is every piece
of intelligence we have.
Not just on the Ring-
everything.
Please, just give Chuck
five more minutes, okay?
For me.
I'm sorry, Sarah, but you
can't think of Chuck.
You have to think
like a spy.
I am thinking like a spy.
Chuck is a member of my team,
and he has served
this country well,
and for all that he has done,
the least we can do is just give
him five more minutes.
So, that's it.
That's how it happened.
So, now I got this thing
in my brain-
the Intersect,
like I told you-
you know, and...
and it's not working.
Anything else you want
to know before we die?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Just one more.
Um, so if Sarah
is your handler,
does that make her your beard?
In other words, like,
is your whole
relationship a fake?
'Cause, oh, buddy, that's...
that's just awful.
Why? Because we never had sex?
No, I just feel like,
you know, having to be...
you never had sex
with that girl?
That's not... no, no.
It's... it's awful that you had
to pretend to be
in a relationship
with somebody
that you clearly love.
Sarah and I are over, you know.
No, you're not.
You're a good liar, Chuck,
but you're not that good.
All right, you lied to me
for three years,
but I always knew
you loved
that girl.
I mean,
I saw the way you looked at her.
We all did.
It's okay.
You don't have
to deny it.
Tell me you don't
love Sarah.
You know what,
you're right, buddy.
I do love Sarah.
I kept telling myself
that I didn't.
That I wouldn't,
I couldn't, but I do.
Morgan, you have no idea
how badly I needed
to get all this off my chest.
Thank you.
Get rid of them.
Kill them.
Dump the bodies.
Thank me later, buddy.
We're about
to die.
No, you're not.
Hey!
Chuck, sword!
Thanks, buddy.
Mine's bigger than yours.
That was incredible.
You were incredible.
You were like
Bruce Lee, Van Damme, Seagal
all rolled up into one.
That's my best friend!
Yeah, he's out. He's out.
I couldn't get in.
We're locked out.
Time's up.
MAN
This is Langley Control.
Bag 'em and tag 'em, Sarah.
Excuse me.
Agent Walker.
We'll just have to put Grimes
in witness protection.
Move him out of Burbank tonight
after dark.
What? Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Hang... hang on a second.
Morgan is not
going anywhere, okay?
Chuck, he knows your secret.
Yeah, well,
so do a lot of people.
Awesome knows, and we didn't
put him underground.
Yeah, because
Awesome's awesome.
Grimes is a moron.
It's just too dangerous.
We have no reason to believe
that we can trust
him. Yes, we do.
We have 22 reasons
why we can trust him.
That's the number of years
that Morgan
has been my best friend.
And, yes, he has his faults-
granted-
but one thing he is is loyal,
and he will never betray me
or my secret.
He's right.
Thank you.
Look, I'm flashing.
I'm a spy again because
I have my best friend back.
You need the Intersect,
and I need him,
so Morgan Grimes is staying
exactly where he belongs,
which is the Burbank Buy More.
Hey. Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Sorry about the wait.
No, no problem, no prob...
Casey.
Always walking around
so angry.
I should've known
you had a big secret.
God help us.
So, yeah, everything's okay.
That's great.
Yes! I love to hear it.
Okay, so am I, uh, like,
officially part
of the team or...
Let's um...
let-let's walk
before we run, huh, buddy?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Definitely. And maybe
crawl before that.
Yeah, yeah. You know what,
we should celebrate.
Okay, little old-school
game night-
Duck Hunt, Subway
meatball marinaras
with extra jalapeños.
That's how
you like it.
And, uh, just
the two of us.
Yeah, just the two of us.
Buy More.
Yes, hello.
This is Craig Rogers
from Buy More corporate.
I heard what happened
down there today.
Interesting display
you put on there.
You-You calling to fire us
or arrest us?
Neither.
I'm calling to hire you.
Huh?
Yesterday, I was planning
on selling this store.
But I spoke
to the potential buyers,
and from what I've heard,
your store showed
the most incredible display
of store loyalty I've ever seen.
The store is no longer for sale.
* *
Victory!
No, I'm not
kidding you.
When was the last time you
beat me at Duck Hunt?
I am the old-school
master. I...
What are you...? I want you to tell me
- when was the last time
that you beat me at Duck Hunt?
That's... that's incredible.
Uh, hey, keep
these, uh,
meatball subs warm for me,
would you, buddy?
I'll be right in.
Um, I talked to Shaw,
and I heard what happened.
The Ring used me as a decoy.
You said I was safe, bro.
And you are.
You... you will be, okay?
We are doing everything
that we can to make sure
that you and Ellie are
protected and safe.
Okay?
Okay.
* *
Are you okay?
You've been
a nervous wreck
ever since this morning.
Babe, we need
to get away.
We just got away.
I'm talking about
really getting away.
You know, just
you and me.
Okay. Where do you want to go?
Cabo?
Further.
Hawaii?
No, no. Further.
I'm talking about...
Africa.
Africa?
We can join Doctors
Without Borders.
Doctors Without Borders?
Honey, you didn't want
to go to France.
This is different, hon.
I am talking
about you and me
traveling the world.
What do you say?
I don't know what to say.
Say yes.
This is crazy. We can't
just up and leave.
What about Chuck?
I'm the only family
that he has.
But this isn't about Chuck.
No, this is about you and me.
Our family.
Come on, babe.
So, now that the Ring
knows about the Castle,
does that mean we have to
shut down the operation?
The Ring shut down
all communications.
They never had a chance
to let their superiors know
about their discovery.
That'll buy us
the time we need
to put together
a full offensive,
take them down
once and for all.
So then, what's wrong?
The Ring had me dead to
rights today in Malibu.
So why didn't they kill me?
So, Sarah and Casey-
they're really spies, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
They're great.
I trust them
with my life.
Are you kidding me?
That is ridiculous, dude.
Look at that shooting.
Are...
You did your flash thingy on it.
You flashed on Duck Hunt.
Hello?
MAN
Hello, Colonel Casey.
It's been a while.
www.addic7ed.com