Hi, i'm Chuck, here's a few things
you might need to know. Who is that?
Super-hot blonde, heart of ice,
yeah, it's Chuck's ex, Sarah.
What's their deal?
Turns out I haven't been
completely honest.
The truth is, I was
hitting on you.
It was completely
unprofessional,
and I apologize.
Oh, my God.
Chuck has a secret girlfriend.
I can't believe that Chuck
is sneaking around
my back like this,
living this other life
that he doesn't think
I know anything about.
I guess he'll tell you about
Hannah when he's ready, hon.
Hannah- you've said it a
hundred times before so casual.
Hannah. Chuck had asked
me to keep it a secret.
You know, maybe it's me.
Maybe he thinks, like,
I'll judge him
or something.
I mean, he told me about the
first girl he had a crush on-
Mrs. Seaver.
Who?
The mom from Growing Pains.
And-and you,
you used to tell me
everything, too,
and now you and my brother
are as thick as thieves.
Is there something you're
keeping from me, too?
Any secrets?
No, nothing, not a thing.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
Your pulse is racing.
I'm exercising.
Honey, go to Chuck.
Tell him how feel. Be honest.
That's good advice, honey.
I love you.
Chuck?
Chuck, listen, uh,
I get it.
You know, I'm not the one
that you...
share everything with anymore.
I just- I just miss
being that person.
Everybody knew about this
new girl that you're dating
before I did.
I just wanted to let you know
that I'm a really good
secret keeper.
And if you don't want Sarah
to know about the new girl...
I won't tell Sarah if you don't.
Um, I'm Hannah.
Oh, my God, this is
so embarrassing. No.
Ellie... uh... my sister.
I've been meaning
to introduce you to...
...Hannah. Hannah-
who apparently you've already
just met right now. Mm-hmm.
Hannah is...
a girl.
She's a girl...
and a friend.
A very close friend.
Technically as close as two
people can kind of... Okay.
Doughnut?
No, thanks.
Um, I need to go and get dressed
so I can go to work.
It was, uh... it was really
great to meet you, Ellie.
Likewise.
Okay. Bye. Bye.
I am- I am so sorry.
I just... I don't know,
I felt like I was
out of the loop,
and you used to tell
me everything, and...
I know. I'm sorry. You
shouldn't be sorry, I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you.
I've just been really
wrapped up at work, and...
But I have an idea.
I'm going to make dinner
for the four of us tonight.
And guess what, it's
going to be your favorite.
Oh, yeah.
My famous chicken pepperoni.
Huh? Oh, I got to
tell you the truth.
I love...,
your chicken pepperoni.
Yes, I know this.
Really, I'm just-
I'm so glad that you're
moving on from Sarah.
I thought
you didn't want dessert.
I don't.
I want yours.
See, my dessert is contained
within your dessert.
Listen, Shaw...
I like that.
Keep it a last-name
basis. Impersonal.
Very sexy, Walker.
I don't think we should see each
other in a non-work capacity.
Oh, is that what this is?
Look, I-it's just,
it's becoming
a pattern for me to get involved
with the guys that I work with,
and I really need to put a stop
to that before it starts.
So, this is a
preemptive breakup?
I need to stop mixing
my personal life
with my professional life.
I'd be a liar if I didn't say
I was disappointed,
but I get it.
The vehicle in question
has arrived.
Roger that.
The man is on the move.
I have the target in sight.
Did you wear cologne
in my car?
Nobody wants to smell you.
The next time you wear
cologne in my car,
I will end you.
Night-night.
Rafe Gruber is a martial arts
expert, a sharpshooter.
He is one of five people
who can hit a target
from half a mile away.
I mean, the man
is a chameleon.
It is a miracle we even
got a hit on his location.
Very few people have
seen his face.
Big deal, not impressed.
Well, The Ring is.
They wired a million dollars
into his account.
Enemy of my enemy is
my friend, kind of thing.
We need to know who
The Ring wants dead.
There's nothing this clown
can do that I can't do.
I'm perfect for this mission.
Still, we're going
with Bartowski on this one.
He'll assume Rafe's identity
in order to learn
the Ring's target.
The Intersect is performing.
He can do this. He's ready.
Right, Walker?
Chuck wants to be a spy.
Hello, team Bartowski.
Tempt anyone with
a tasty treat, huh?
What's with him?
Stallion had a date last night;
must have gotten lucky.
So, what is going on?
Who's this guy?
That is Rafe Gruber.
Wow, old Rafie boy's not such
a good guy now, is he?
What are we doing with him?
Not we, Chuck. You.
You're about
to assume an alias.
You're going to become
the world's most
dangerous assassin.
Becoming an alias, Chuck,
is unlike anything you've had
in your spy training before.
Under the most
stressful conditions,
you have to react only
like Rafe, not Chuck.
Guys, please.
I think I know a thing
or two about acting, all right?
I happened to play Perchik
in my high school's production
of Fiddler on the Roof.
And I was really quite good.
Ow! Ow!
What'd you do that for?!
I'm proving a point.
Everything you think
and feel, Chuck,
even your innate
reflexes have to change.
The kind of people that
Gruber associates with
will kill first,
ask questions later.
Yeah, okay fine, I get it.
What's the plan?
Well, Casey is going to elicit
the details from Gruber,
whom he's meeting,
where and when.
Then you'll go in
as Gruber, take his place.
Well, good luck there.
It's gonna be tough getting
information like that
out of a top
assassin like Rafe.
Nah, I can be
very persuasive.
Hey, let me talk to him for
a second. Step off, Bartowski.
I got a job to do.
Yeah, well, hey, so do I, okay?
I've got to learn
about Rafe
so I can get into
character for my mission.
For example:
Assassin is not normally
a booth one finds at Career Day.
How'd you initially get
interested in this line of work?
Why would I tell you anything?
I can think of
one burning reason why.
Okay. How about this one: What
was your most difficult hit?
I'll take the torture over this
man's questions. Roger that.
I'll take the torture
over this man's questions.
Hey, it's just a phone.
Gruber here.
Of course I'm ready.
Who do you think
you're dealing with?
Yeah, yeah, I know
where that is.
Across the street from
the cupcake place.
Because I like
cupcakes, that's why.
Who doesn't like
a good cupcake?
I'll be there.
Not bad, Bartowski.
Who the hell is Bartowski?
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
Look at that guy.
Chuck's the greatest lady
killer Burbank has ever seen.
He's a real "chuck" magnet.
Please with the puns.
Terrible timing for my
number one employee Morgan
to be away at
a leadership seminar.
Due to a clerical oversight,
we received
triple the number of Crock-Pots
I may have intended.
I'm excited about
dinner tonight.
Oh, yeah, yeah, me, too.
What's that guy's secret
with women?
What, has he got some kind
of deal with the devil?
I've narrowed it down.
Either mind controlling LSD
or sorcery.
El Segundo School of Finance
has taught me
when you try to sell a house,
bake some cookies.
Make the place
smell familiar.
We're gonna do
the same thing here.
Except with gumbo.
Folks smell something
cooking in that Crock-Pot,
make them want to buy
the fool thing.
Need a volunteer.
You look like
you've peeled a few spuds
in your day, Casey.
And I would have picked you
if these two dipsticks
hadn't been faking sick
to get out of
chopping and dicing.
Wash your filthy hands, boys.
Hey, um, I'm cooking
dinner tonight
for my family, Hannah,
and my special chicken
pepperoni recipe
takes a little time to prep,
so I don't know how long
the mission is,
but I need a hard
out by 5:00. Mm.
I can give you a hard out
with these five.
Get your priorities
straight.
You okay in here?
Yeah, yeah. I'll
be out in a sec.
I see how that guy
looks at you.
I bet he has no clue what to do
to a beautiful
woman like you.
But I do.
I will take such good care
of you, sweetheart.
All set.
Quick thing I gotta do first.
Okay, ready when you are.
Hi.
I miss those lips.
What, these old things?
I'm gonna be thinking
about last night
when I'm on my install.
What are you doing today?
Yeah, same thing, install.
Big, huge, complicated.
Probably faking my way
through most of it.
But hey, how about I come
and pick you up before dinner?
That's great.
Definitely a deal
with the devil.
I am so lonely.
Come on.
I can pass for a cold-blooded
killer, right?
What happened to Rafe?
What?
Imbecile can't go in alone.
Hey, where
am I going?
Chuck, Rafe wasn't going
to meet with your usual spies.
These guys are a little more
old-fashioned.
Heard a story this cugine
whacked this guy
during his spaghetti dinner.
The coroner couldn't tell
between the marinara
and the mess.
Hey, boss,
someone to see you.
Well, well, well,
Rafe Gruber.
Your reputation precedes you.
This is my coworker.
You may call
him John.
How ya doin'?
John doesn't talk much.
I know you from somewhere?
Doubt it.
When we had previous dealings
with our mutual friends,
you had more trepidation
about letting us I.D. you.
Not many people have seen
my face and lived.
Consider it an honor.
Look, I'm not much
for foreplay,
so forgive me
if I'm a little rude.
Who's my target?
No one thinks
this guy looks familiar?
You got cousins in Philly?
No.
I'm a huge fan
of your work.
Can I ask you
something?
What was your toughest hit?
You want to know
my toughest hit?
Look, I was just asking.
Yeah, take it
easy, boss.
You shut your mouth!
You think it's okay to ask
a guy you just met
something personal like that?
I really didn't mean
no disrespect, I swear.
Your toughest assignment's
always your next one.
You forget that, then you die.
You okay, Walker?
Yeah, yeah, it's
just this alias thing.
It must be a lot
for Chuck.
He's not a very
good liar.
Listen to him.
He's completely living the lie.
I know, but he's not like
you and me.
We're both used to living
somebody else's life.
That's the job.
Yeah, but where does
the job end?
I can barely remember
who I am anymore.
CHUCK I'm a busy guy,
so what's the name?
Who do our mutual friends
want me to kill?
The guy's name is...
I remember now!
You look like this
hotshot sniper
I served with a while back.
Name Alex Coburn,
ring a bell?
What are you trying to say?
Simple. This guy isn't
who he says he is.
Maybe he's some kind of fed.
Damn it!
Casey's been made.
We need to get them
out of there.
How are we supposed
to do that
without getting
everybody else killed?
We need that name, Walker.
We need to know who
the Ring wants dead.
Are you implying that this guy,
my guy, is a cop?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
So what does that say about you?
If he's a cop...
I'll kill him myself.
Do him, Rafe!
What are you
waiting for?
Quit stalling.
Keep stalling, Chuck.
We need more time.
We're waiting for backup.
Time's running out.
Kill him.
I'm not a murderer.
I'm an assassin!
What's the damn difference?
What's the damn
difference?
I don't kill because I like it.
I kill because it's a means
to something.
In this case,
information.
Information that I wouldn't get
from a dead guy
per your suggestion!
Now you're gonna tell me,
who's your informant?
Who's the leak?
Why would I tell you anything?
Sell it.
Wait!
I got something
special for occasions
such as these.
Is this stuff sterile?
I take pride
in my work, all right?
I want to kill him, not some
secondary infection.
No.
Tell me what you know!
Move!
Move, move, move!
Everyone, move it! Move it!
Oh, my God, Sarah!
Sarah, I'm
freaking out right now!
I've never been so happy
to see you in my life!
Stop it!
You're not you,
you're Rafe.
You have to be him
in this situation.
Think what he would do.
Live the lie.
Come on, move!
We gotta split up!
We'll contact you later
with your assignment!
Rafe,
You're incredible!
Yeah, whatever. It's my job.
Good work, team.
Wow, Bartowski really sold it.
For a second, I hardly
even recognized him.
Guys, I told you
I needed a hard-out at 5:00!
How am I gonna get
everything done?
I gotta cook dinner,
my apartment's a pigsty,
gotta pick up Hannah,
take a shower...
Where is everybody?
Walker and Shaw knew
you were in over your head.
They went back to your place
to fix dinner
for your date.
They did, huh?
Weird, huh?
Walker helping you get laid.
Um, hey, Casey, I'm...
I'm sorry about your tooth.
That's all right. At least
you got one with a cavity.
Saved me a trip
to the dentist.
You did good work, Chuck.
Proud of you.
You think you can be me?
You shut your mouth.
Where are you
taking Rafe?
Interrogation.
Just wish
I could do it
myself.
You think you can be me?!
Uh, Case,
back there on
the mission,
I flashed on
the name "Alex Coburn."
Who is that?
You mind your damn business.
Oh, hey!
Hi!
Let's go eat.
I'm not gonna lie
to you, boys,
Bartowski is killing it
with the ladies.
I know.
First there was
that hot girl from Stanford.
Jill.
Yeah.
Then the brunette with
the overpriced deli.
Lou. She was a fine, miniature
piece of woman.
And now Hannah.
I'd like to moisturize her feet
with my saliva.
Don't you get it?
None of them matter.
Chuck may try
to replace her,
but when he's with
Sarah, the light
in his eyes
shines brightly.
Damn onions!
Oh, knife.
I want expectations
to be managed here.
I'm not Chef Boyardee.
Just looking forward
to hanging out with your sister.
I like this one,
Chuck.
Oh, my God, Chuck,
this looks amazing.
And smells amazing, too.
Dude, I thought
you worked all day.
How'd you find time
to do this?
Um, you know,
it's a, it's a juggling act.
No biggie.
I just threw it together.
Uh, Devon, you want to help me
with the wine?
Smells delish.
My taste buds are fist bumping
each other, bro.
Red okay?
Listen, I didn't
do any of this, okay?
I didn't buy the cheese.
I didn't
make the dinner.
Thank God,
I can tell you the truth.
Stop. Stop.
If you keep talking,
I'm going to have
to lie to your sister,
and I can't do that anymore.
I'm not cut out
for this, Chuck.
I'm not like you.
I'm sorry. I get it.
Look, from now on,
if Ellie asks you something,
just say, "I don't know."
That's not a lie.
I lied.
I'm a liar.
I've been telling you for
years that I love this dish.
And it's been horrible.
And now, I can tell you,
honestly, that this is
fantastic.
Well, yeah. I think you're just,
you're just being polite.
It's not really my best.
No, it is, actually.
The others were
quite horrible.
Devon, can you believe
that Chuck made this?
I don't know.
Isn't this
chicken moist?
Chuck's chicken?
This chicken?
Chuck's chicken.
Um...
Hannah, don't you think
Chuck's chicken is moist?
Actually, I, um...
I'd like to make a toast.
Um, you know how, in life,
there's always something
that just doesn't line up?
Like, um, either you're
working at the wrong job
or dating the wrong guy,
or you're eating
some really bad meal?
Uh, but
right at this second,
I feel like I'm exactly
where I'm supposed to be.
And I want to
thank all of you
for making me
feel that way.
Hope dessert
doesn't suck.
Um, cheers.
Cheers.
I managed to sneak
us out some chicken.
I don't want to brag,
but it turned out pretty good.
Oh, uh, no, thanks.
I'm not hungry.
I'm clocking out. Have
you got this covered?
Uh, yeah.
This is cool.
Is this new?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Little perk of the job.
You know, just testing it out.
Work thing.
Listen, I, um, I
know this is fast,
but my parents
are coming in
from Santa Barbara
tonight for dinner.
Oh. Yeah, and I wasn't
going to ask you to come,
but since I got to hang
out with your family,
I'd love it if
you met mine.
Yeah, yeah.
I would love to meet them.
Bartowski, I need your
professional opinion.
Your latest
little lady said
that you're some kind
of cooking expert.
I need your
palette's advice.
Uh, actually, you know,
my recipe last night
didn't really
come together.
That's not what she said.
She said she
couldn't wait
to gobble up every bite.
Mouth as pretty
as Hannah's,
she can taste
the difference.
That's the mouth
of a professional.
Hello?
Burbank Buy More.
The-the flavor profile's
not quite right.
I think it could use a little
Worcestershire sauce, maybe.
And, oh, oh, wait.
Is that frozen okra?
Good taste in women,
bad taste in food.
Jeffrey, if you double-dip,
we all may die.
Who was that?
What did they want?
Um, it was a wrong number.
They were asking
for some guy named Rafe.
That's odd.
What did you tell him?
Um, I told them that this
was a Buy More phone.
Uh, but the guy? Just,
he wouldn't listen,
and he kept saying that he would
be here, in like, two minutes.
Oh, here.
What do you think you're
doing with that watch?
I can explain.
There is no
explanation.
Give me this watch.
For a bad ass killer to own
such a piece of crap watch?
Crazy!
So, we bought you
a little present,
though "bought"
is a very loose term.
Look at that.
Gold. Wow.
It's very understated.
What are you doing here
at Buy More, anyway?
What, are you getting some
speaker wire to, uh...
What do I look like,
a workaholic?
A man's got to have
hobbies other than murder.
I was here browsing music.
Hey, you saved us
from getting pinched
yesterday, huh?
What a guy.
Ooh, I could hit you.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
Never seen
anything close
to what you
pulled off, Rafe.
The trick is
making it look easy.
You did us a favor, and in
turn, we did you a favor.
We tracked down
the location
of the guy you're
supposed to kill.
Good news, huh?
Good news?
That is very good news.
Yeah. Enough of that.
Oh, I'm sorry if
this is a bad time.
No. Hey, Walker.
Come on in.
Listen, Shaw, I just
wanted to say, um...
What?
Well, I-I came by to, um...
I'm sorry. Can you please
put some clothes on?
Oh. Yeah.
I wanted to apologize
for my behavior last night.
No apology necessary.
Okay.
Um...
Well...
You still, um...
You okay with
this whole Chuck/Hannah thing?
Thank you for asking.
But that's not really the change
that I'm having trouble with.
So, who's the mark?
Who am I taking out?
He's in the hotel room
right over there.
Got a girl with him.
A real hot piece of tail.
I think they're going to plow.
Perfect distraction.
How am I supposed
to see him?
With this.
Naturally.
We hear you're one of five guys
that can make this shot.
It's over
half a mile away.
Well, apparently, my
reputation precedes me.
Again.
Oh, my God.
What?
SARAH
It's just really difficult
to see Chuck
become a different person.
That's the
mission, Walker.
No, it's not the
mission. It's...
Everything.
Take the shot.
It's how he pulled out
Casey's tooth,
and how he burnt that asset
a couple of weeks ago,
and the way he
lies to Hannah.
I mean,
it's so easy for him.
Chuck's changing.
He's becoming a spy.
I know. I know.
But lives are being
affected here.
Sounds like he's not
the only one who's changing.
It's like I'm watching
Chuck disappear,
and the further
he gets from who he is,
the...
Cap him.
It's okay. Talk to me, Sarah.
Come on.
Well, the more I want
to remember who I am-
who I was before
all of this-
Well, if this is
you, I like you.
I want more.
I've been on this assignment
for almost three years,
and I've never told
anybody my real name.
Not even Chuck?
No.
Not even Chuck.
So, what is it?
What's happening?
What's going on?
Shut up! Shut up!
Feels so weird
to say it out loud.
Yeah, it's just, you
never seemed like a Sarah.
It's 'cause I'm not.
What is it, Rafe?
I'm Sam.
Hmm.
My real name is Sam.
Sam?
Well...
I'm going to kiss
you now, Sam.
Sam?!
Sam?
Who's Sam?
The guy you're supposed
to whack is Daniel Shaw.
The organization that
had us contract you
thought this
Shaw guy was dead.
Turns out,
he's just not dead yet.
This is the right guy
all right.
So, who the hell is Sam?
Sam...
Sam's the girl.
My girl.
Sort of.
Me and Sam are on
again, off again.
Driving everyone in my
life a little crazy.
I hate those "Will they
or won't they?" things.
Just do it already!
If you and this girl
love each other so much,
what's keeping you apart?
It's complicated.
Sort of came down to a question
of work.
What are you gonna do?
You got your priorities
straight.
Right?
And plus, she's the one who's
always pushing me to be better
at my job in the first place.
Women- screwed
if you do,
not screwed
if you don't.
Wait a second.
The guy you're supposed to whack
is banging your girl?
It sure seems that
way, doesn't it? Huh.
Jeez, this unlucky guy is
about to get double dead.
SHAW
Do we have a situation?
I tried contacting the agents
transporting Gruber,
but they're not responding.
They checked in yet?
No.
Damn it!
Get me Bartowski's last-known
location.
What are you waiting on, Rafe?
There.
That's better.
What's your problem, man?
Ice him!
I can't do it.
A bullet's too good
for this guy.
Yeah, you gotta look
this jerk in the eye
before you cap him.
Yeah, yeah, my thoughts exactly.
I'm going over there.
You two stay put.
Don't worry, Rafe.
We got your back.
Anything weird goes down,
I'll take out the whole room.
I ain't a marksman
like you are,
but I make sure
they're all dead.
Yeah, that's...
real good.
Open the door!
I know you're in there!
I will kick this door down!
What's going on?
Shut your mouth!
I'll deal with you later.
What's your problem?
My problem is that
nobody messes with Rafe Gruber.
They're watching us.
I'd like you to remove those.
No, no, no. These are the hands
that are gonna
kill you, Shaw.
What are you doing?!
You stole my girl.
I'm going to end you
for taking Sam!
You had your chance
and you blew it.
Who the hell are you?
Ah, Shaw, wait!
Shaw, enough!
Would you stop already?
I'm trying to sell myself
as Rafe!
They're across the street
with a sniper rifle.
They're gonna kill all of us!
No, I'm gonna kill all of you.
Come on. Flash.
Flash!
Come on! Flash!
Wake up, pretty.
Come on.
That's it.
Come here, yeah.
No, don't shoot!
Please don't!
You two got it bad
for this blond.
Can't say
I blame you.
I'm gonna make it easy
on both of you.
Take her out
of the equation.
No!
Five people in the world
can make this shot, huh?
Guess I'm one of them.
Hi.
Um...
you said that I could come to
you if I ever needed to talk.
Yeah. I'm so glad.
Please, start at the beginning.
I feel like I'm living
a lie, Ellie.
I used to be able
to compartmentalize
these things, but it's, like,
it's all the time now.
It never stops.
I feel like I'm not me anymore.
I think I know what
this is about.
You do?
Maybe things are moving too fast
with Hannah,
and even though you
really like her,
it feels dishonest because
the truth is
that you still have feelings
for Sarah.
Does that sound
about right?
See, this is... this is why
I don't come talk to you, Ellie,
'cause you're half a spy.
I'm sorry, Chuck,
maybe that's not it.
No. No, no, no.
What I mean by that is
that you're an excellent
half a spy.
Thanks.
Any time.
Hi!
Hi. I'm, uh,
I'm Chuck.
Can we talk
for a second?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
Are you okay, Chuck?
What's the matter?
You know how much
I like you, right?
What's wrong?
Hannah, there are things
in my life
that you can't understand,
and I can't explain them to you.
I've been dishonest,
and it's not fair to you.
So I have to end this...
...because you deserve to be
with someone
who you can know
completely and...
I, um, I thought
you were a nice guy.
No, I am a nice guy.
No, you're not a nice guy.
We had sex this morning,
and now you are dumping me.
No, it's not like that.
Then how is it?
Explain it to me!
Look, I have dated a lot
of liars before,
so I usually know how
to spot them,
but you- you're, like,
the best I've ever seen.
I hope that your lies
keep you warm at night.
So, now that the Ring
knows you're alive,
looks like you're gonna
be down here for a while,
so I bought you that.
It's a Crock-Pot.
They're practically
giving them away
at Buy More.
And just so you know,
the Castle is outside of Bamboo
Dragon's delivery radius.
Thank you... Sam.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com