Hey, I’m Chuck. here's a few things that you
might need to know or maybe you just forgot.
There's only one piece
left to clean up.
Perry. Chuck has to kill him.
You are giving him
his red test tonight?
You kidding me?
Kill him here, now?
I can't do that.
Then you won't become a spy.
You passed the test.
To them you killed Perry.
No one can know the truth
ever. Not even Sarah.
You're now officially an agent.
Included there's a plain ticket to
Washington, you'll leave tonight.
CHUCK:
First day. Don't be nervous.
Don't be nervous.
What floor? Five.
No, not five.
Oh, hey, uh, I'm so
sorry to bother you.
You wouldn't happen to know what
Floor General Beckman is on?
They told me at the front desk
and I-I just totally forgot.
You couldn't miss her.
She's real little,
lots of medals, red hair.
Nice, nice, friendly conversation.
That's good. I'm glad we did that.
No!
Sir?
Excuse me, sir.
This is a restricted floor.
I need a badge and a signature.
Sir, I can't let you examine a body
without an authorized NSA badge.
Would you do me a favor?
Just... one step.
There, perfect.
What do you think you're doing?!
It's done.
Package is intact.
NSA, General Beckman's office.
Please hold.
Thank you for waiting.
Here we are. Thank God.
Hello. Thank you for waiting.
How's it going?
NSA, General Beckman's office.
Please hold.
Super.
Thank you for waiting.
Hello. Thank you for waiting.
Yes, I'll put you right through.
Excuse me. Hi, my name's...
Have a seat, Agent Bartowski.
The General knows you're here.
NSA.
Right. Yeah, of course
she knows I'm here.
NSA, General Beckman's office.
Please hold.
Oh, God, these things are
incredibly uncomfortable.
Is there a particular place
that you like to put this?
'Cause I'm always having...
Oh, right, yes.
Sorry about...
Finger always on the slide,
and you know, totally empty so...
But I hear you. Safety first.
A pleasure as always, General.
The pleasure's all mine, Diane.
Mr. Bartowski.
Oh!
For God's sake,
put that gun away.
You're a spy now.
Well, that's, that's
actually what I wanted
to talk to you about, General.
Your first assignment
just arrived.
The CIA wants you
in Rome right away.
Uh, what?
Excuse me, right away?
Mm-hmm.
You will be posing
as a independently wealthy
young expatriate.
That way, your jet-setting lifestyle
and influential associates
won't draw attention.
Here is where you'll be staying.
Uh, wow.
Obviously, you will be afforded
all the accoutrements
that go with it:
cars, clothes, a yearly stipend.
Huh? What? Yearly?
Yearly stipend?
This is all moving very, very
fast, don't you think?
The NSA has spent three years
and countless millions of dollars
helping you reach
your potential.
There's nothing fast about it.
I get that. I do.
I do, General, and
I certainly don't
want to come across
as being ungrateful
for the, the villa
or the car or the stipend.
I'm just not sure
that I am really ready
to pack up and move
somewhere to live
this whole new life
when I'm just starting
to become comfortable
with the life I'm living...
right now, you know?
What exactly did you think
we were training you for,
Mr. Bartowski?
I don't... I don't really know
what to say, General.
I'm sorry.
Is not an option!
I understand that
the hand-wringing
and the second-guessing
are all part of your process.
Here's what I'm offering:
take the week off,
anywhere you want, on us.
But afterwards, I expect
you back in Washington and
ready to assemble your team.
Is that understood?
Hang on. Um, back up a second.
What do you mean by
"my" team?
You didn't think we were going
to send you to Rome alone?
You'll have your pick
of our top agents,
whoever you want.
So where will we be sending you,
Mr. Bartowski?
Bali? Bora Bora?
Burbank.
Bob Hope Airport, to be exact.
I see.
And will you be requiring
a companion ticket?
No, thanks.
She's still there.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
That's, uh, that's
fantastic news. Okay.
Thank you.
Enough of the suspense, babe.
One word, Devon: Africa.
Africa?
That was the hospital.
I didn't even have to ask.
Out of the blue, they just offered me
a sabbatical. I have a year off.
Do you know what that means?
Africa.
We can do Doctors without Borders,
follow our dreams,
whatever you want.
What about Chuck?
Chuck is moving on, you know?
I really believe that this time.
He said he was on a business trip
for Buy More in Washington.
Yeah, yeah, he did
Sound pretty pumped
when I talked to him.
Who knows where
he'll end up. Who knows?
Honey, there's nothing
keeping us here.
Africa.
I've never had to win
a girl back, buddy,
so I stopped by the store
on the way here.
I got Sarah a bunch of stuff.
What do you think? Am I overdoing it?
Hmm-mmm.
You think I'm overdoing it.
I'm overdoing it.
Well, the chocolates
are a nice touch, I guess,
to buy her back,
if that makes any sense.
I know, I know, you're right.
It just finally clicked
for me, you know?
Sarah is, is the most
important thing.
I mean, what's the point
of being a spy without her?
I've got to win her back,
and I've only got a small window
of opportunity to do it in
before I have to leave for Rome.
Hey. Did you just say
you're gonna go to Rome?
Yeah, my new assignment
starts there next week.
Then you are still leaving.
Thank God!
I just fed Ellie some story
about you working for
Buy More corporate.
She won't go to Africa
if you're still here.
Well, I'm not going anywhere
without Sarah.
Then let's get you two
kids back together.
Shouldn't be too
difficult, huh?
You seen the stallion
she's dating?
Casey, do you...?
Do, do you ever knock
or use a door?
Shaw's not some geek who likes
to talk about his feelings
all day long. He's a real spy.
Oh. Oh, really? Is that so?
Well, apparently, you haven't
heard because you no longer work
for the United States government,
but I'm heading up my own
undercover operation.
In Rome. And I get to
choose my own team.
Really? Anyone?
Including a civilian with
extensive military background?
Take a number, Casey.
Chuck, I speak fluent Italian.
Menu items mostly.
I'd be an invaluable asset.
Listen, guys, I got
to get Sarah back first.
Then we can start talking
about a team.
What are we waiting for, fellas?
Let's help the guy
get his girl back. Come on!
Yeah, so Ellie and I
can go to Africa.
And I can get out of Burbank.
I can finally go see Rome.
Maybe meet a nice Italian girl.
See the Vatican...
pay my respects to the Pope.
DEVON:
What are you waiting for,
lover boy?
Hey, um...
You're back.
I've been calling you
for, for a couple days now.
You know, there's a lot
we need to talk about.
I know. I'm sorry.
It's been a little...
Crazy. Yeah, I know.
Beckman flew me to D.C.
I got my badge.
It's official now.
I'm an agent.
Congratulations. You earned it.
You know the CIA--
they're sending me to Italy.
You wouldn't believe the villa
that they're putting me up in.
I'm supposed to be
some rich young playboy.
But who cares about that?
The point is, Sarah...
I want you to go with me.
Chuck, I can't.
No, Beckman said I get
to choose my own team,
cream of the crop. That's you.
I'm going to Washington, okay?
And I'm going with Shaw.
Wait a minute.
Wasn't this the plan?
There's nothing stopping us
from being together now.
I passed my spy test.
That's why I can't
be with you, okay?
You're not... you're not the same guy
that I fell for.
How? Why? Because I'm an agent now?
How am I not the same guy?
You killed somebody, Chuck.
I saw you kill the mole!
Sarah, I know what you think
you saw on the train tracks,
but it's not that simple.
It's more complicated than that.
and I need you to believe me.
I don't.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Congratulations on your promotion,
Special Agent Bartowski.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Yeah, it's, uh...
it's very exciting.
So what brings you
back to Burbank?
Um... I, uh,
you know, just, uh,
just-just tying up
a few loose ends.
Actually, Chuck was
just wondering
if I had any last-minute advice
on his new assignment in Rome.
Well, you shouldn't
have come to her.
You should have come to me.
I was stationed there
for two years.
Come on. I can tell you
everything you need to know.
Oh, great.
Hey.
How'd it go with Walker?
Because she thinks
I killed the mole,
she believes I'm no longer
the guy she fell in love with.
I have to tell her the truth.
What? That I killed him?
Not gonna happen.
Casey, you said it yourself.
The guy was a traitor.
Yeah, well, according
to Beckman, so am I.
I'm lucky she didn't
put a bullet in my head.
Get her back some other way.
Well, what the heck am I
supposed to tell Sarah?
Tell her whatever you want,
just not the truth.
You like being a full-fledged
spy, don't you?
You like that nice villa the CIA
picked out for you in Rome, hmm?
Then you killed the mole.
That's how it's got to be.
MORGAN:
Okay, okay.
How did it go? How did it go?
Crashed and burned.
Chuck, did you tell
her how you feel?
Forget it.
She's leaving with Shaw
in the morning.
CHUCK:
I'm sorry, guys. It's over.
I'm going to get some fresh air,
and figure out how I'm going
to tell Beckman I'm quitting.
There goes our chance to ever
get out of the Buy More.
Really? Is that what they
teach you in the Marine Corps?
Hmm?
Roll over and die?
This isn't exactly combat,
Morgan.
That's where you're wrong,
Casey.
Because love?
Love is a battlefield.
Huh.
Hey, fellas.
Need your help.
Actually, Chuck needs your help.
Went and lost his
old lady again, huh?
Yeah. How did
you know that?
We know everything.
The eyes and the ears
of the strip mall, my friend.
Chuck better move quick if he
wants to get his froyo ho back.
Another fella sniffing
around the orange.
Orange.
Guy knows how to fill out
a pair of slacks.
If you know what I'm saying.
No, I don't.
I didn't notice that.
You want us to put a tail
on blondie's new piece?
Find out his weaknesses,
see what skeletons
are in his closet?
Blood sample, urine?
Stool?
No.
No, not at... I just...
I just need to borrow something.
Whoa! Whoa!
What the crap is going on?
You guys scared the
bejeezus out of me.
We're here to help you
reacquire Agent Walker.
Guys, listen. You don't understand.
No, Chuck, you don't understand.
You're not the only one with
something at stake here, Chuck.
Yeah, we help you
get the girl back,
you help us get out of Burbank.
Think of it as a test run for Rome.
MORGAN:
What do you think, boss?
Hey, get dressed.
Reservation's in ten minutes.
Reservation for what? Come on.
CHUCK:
Guys. Is this Jeff's van?
CASEY:
Go, go, go!
(tires screeching)
Darn, he's on the move.
Guys, what are we doing here?
It's Shaw's date.
MORGAN:
Wow. That guy can fill out
a pair of slacks.
Sarah's with a stallion. Huh.
Don't listen to him, Chuck.
We have a plan.
You've got nothing
to worry about, man.
MAN:
Target is in position, sir.
Looks like a romantic dinner.
Sorry, Shaw.
1990 Chateau Latour.
Excellent choice.
SHAW:
Thank you.
Knowledge of fine wine.
Very classy.
He just ordered for both of them.
That's a power move, bro.
Yeah. Guy's a closer.
Guys, guys.
A little sensitivity would
really go a long way.
Just a smidgeon. A skosh. A dab.
We're talking about
the girl I love here.
I'm sorry.
What could you possibly
be sorry for?
This is amazing.
It's just...
I'm sorry that we haven't
done this sooner.
This is nice.
No, it's perfect.
Being here with you.
SHAW:
To a new life and a fresh start.
No Burbank, no baggage.
All right, this isn't good.
Why doesn't John here
just drag him out of there?
I'm afraid my days of legalized
body snatching are over, guys.
I'm a civilian now.
This one's on you, Bartowski.
All right, Chuck. Whatever you
do, do not go in there too hot.
You will scare her away.
Negative. Okay?
Chuck has to lay it all
on the line.
Shaw, he may be
handsome and worldly
and know his way around a menu,
but, man, he's stiff as a board.
Where's that Bartowski charm?
The pizzazz? You flash a smile,
you go in there and you...
Morgan, why don't you
let me handle it? Okay?
No offense, but I've had
my fair share of ladies.
'Cause you live in a bubble.
Okay? Take a look at yourself.
Go ahead.
It's a freakish bubble
of handsomeness.
Now, look at me.
No bubble. No bubble.
I got to be completely verbal.
Now, Chuck, I'm telling you,
you just go in and you
be fun and you be witty,
and you be the charming
guy she fell for.
Yeah?
Okay. Okay, fine.
But what about Shaw?
Just worry about the girl.
I'll take care of the stallion.
Sorry to disturb you, but,
Mr. Shaw, you have a phone call.
Target's on the move.
DEEP VOICE (on phone):
Agent Shaw.
I'm an operative of The Ring.
If you want to save everyone
in this restaurant,
you will listen
to my instructions very carefully.
(deep voice):
You will do everything that I say.
Where the hell do
you think you're going?
Exit the restaurant. Side door.
And head to the back alley.
We've lost visual on the target.
Bring up the phone dub.
DEEP VOICE (on speaker):
Stay cool and nobody will get hurt.
Who the hell is that?
Is this seat taken?
Chuck, what are you doing here?
I'm here for you.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to say that
you'll come with me to Rome.
Well, you know that I can't,
and you know why.
Look, Sarah, I don't want
to have to make a scene
in front of all these
very nice people, but I will
literally do anything
to change your mind.
Well, then tell me what really
happened at the train tracks.
SARAH: If you didn't kill
the mole, then who did?
Look, I don't want there
to be any secrets
or lies between us, ever again.
So, please, let me
just have this one.
And I promise I will
never lie to you.
There you will head
to a pay phone.
The southwest corner. Do it.
But do it slowly.
DEEP VOICE (over speakers):
Slowly.
Not one of ours.
Take him down.
We know exactly what
you look like, Shaw.
6'2", 220, black hair,
very attractive.
Next move, you're to wait
for a phone call.
Might not happen right away.
So be patient.
And then, when you...
Do you have any idea
who these people are?
What they're capable of?
Mm-mmm. Nope?
Listen.
I know that you think
I'm not that same guy
that you met the first
day at the Buy More.
And you know what? You're right.
Okay? You're right.
The guy that I was back
Then hated himself
for not knowing what he wanted
to do with the rest of his life
or who he wanted to
spend it with, but now?
Finally, now... I know.
I want to be a spy.
And I want to be with you.
MORGAN:
Hey, it's just a harmless prank.
Listen, you have to understand...
Who are they?
Is that a taser?
Sorry about this.
Oh, boy.
Sarah.
Man down.
I've been tased.
I can't feel my legs.
Bring a stretcher, a wheelbarrow.
Possible change of pants.
Casey, you got to do something.
He's gunning for Chuck.
I'm a civilian now. I can't.
Well, I can.
Daniel.
If you're going to
shoot me, just do it.
Put a bullet in my head.
Bullet?
The director wants to meet
with you face to face.
What are you saying?
Sarah, I'm saying... that I...
Next time, take out
the guy with the gun.
Jail? Seriously, you guys? Jail?
I mean, Morgan,
I would have expected
This from you.
Or even from Casey,
now that we have all been privy
to your public indecency problem.
But, Devon, I never
expected this from you.
No, babe. I am so sorry.
You know what?
Just save the apology. Okay?
I want answers.
I want the truth. I want you
guys to tell me everything.
The truth?
Yes.
The truth is...
We were, uh, helping Chuck.
Chuck is in D.C., Casey.
Well, he was. He's back
to win back Sarah, so...
Hold on for a minute.
You guys expect me to believe
that the three of you
got my husband beat up
and tossed in jail
to save my brother's love life?
Yes. Yes, we did.
We're as shocked as you are.
And, what's more,
Chuck came to you
Three for advice.
Before me.
Yeah. Yes, he did.
Why am I not surprised
this ended in jail?
Agent Shaw, we have
just received intel
that the Ring agent
who tried to capture you
is the same man who
removed a data drive
from inside the mole's body.
The data was inside him?
He was in the process of
digesting it when he was killed.
I'll spare you the gory details.
Lucky he was dead first.
We believe the stolen data drive
contains highly sensitive
case files.
Your new mission is to
bring back those files.
General, if I may,
it's not good enough.
Excuse me, Agent Shaw.
You have a better idea?
The Ring agent we encountered
did not want to kill me.
He wanted to take me
to the director.
If the Ring wants to
take me, let them.
You're volunteering
to be a double agent?
I'm volunteering
to be a bull's-eye.
I'll paint a target
on the Ring from within.
I can get close to the director
and track his location.
And then what?
It's your call, General,
but I'd suggest you
launch an air strike.
Shouldn't we stop and ask
what the Ring wants with you
in the first place?
And why they want you alive?
It doesn't matter.
We can decimate the
Ring's command structure
with a single mission.
I see the merits.
But you do recognize the danger?
General.
This is the moment
I've been waiting for...
we've been waiting for.
A singular opportunity.
Whatever the risk may be,
I say it's worth it.
Very good.
Make it work.
Are you trying to
get yourself killed?
You're asking if I'd trade my life
for the man who
killed my wife?
I would.
Well, what if I don't let you?
It's not your choice.
MAN:
Hello?
This is Daniel Shaw.
I believe you've
been looking for me.
I'm ready to come in.
It's done.
Ellie, hey.
Um, look, I can explain.
Chuck, listen to me. No. I know
Exactly what you're going to say.
And you're absolutely right.
It was completely immature of me
to get everyone involved like that.
Chuck, you're not listening.
Stupid? Maybe stupid's
the word you're looking for.
I get it. I went too far.
You didn't go far enough, Chuck.
Sarah is special. I know it.
You know it. If you love
her, if she's the one,
then you don't stop.
You don't quit.
You never go too far.
You are a Bartowski, Chuck.
Start acting like one.
Shaw, please. You're
moving too fast.
You're not thinking
this through.
Hey, we're spies, Walker.
Let's start acting like it.
But you don't have to do this.
There's got to be another way.
It's the only way to be sure.
I have to do this.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
SARAH:
What's that?
It's how you'll find me.
This will give Beckman the
coordinates for the air strike.
Wow.
You just...
You just swallowed
that thing whole, huh?
No-No water to wash it down.
Take care of her, Chuck.
Uh...
Where is he going?
Shaw is turning himself
In to the Ring.
He's leading us to them.
He's sacrificing himself, Chuck.
Oh.
I never should have let Morgan
lay his dirty little
hands on Loretta.
She's a sweet van, my friend.
That van's my retirement, dude.
And they took the van
and they left us.
That is a slap in the face.
It's insulting.
Do they have any idea how much
stalking experience I have?
If only they did, Jeffrey.
You're very prolific.
You're the-the
Picasso of creepiness.
It's true. And this
is my Blue period.
Good. There's the guy.
Blondie's new boyfriend.
We need to demonstrate our worth.
Show them that we can stalk
with the best of them.
What do you say, my friend?
Let's do the dizzle.
Shaw's going on a suicide mission?
I don't care what he says.
I am not letting him go in alone.
He's not going in alone.
Chuck, what are you doing?
Shaw needs help.
I know he does.
And that's why I'm going
In to bring him back.
But the air strike
is on its way.
You're both going to get killed.
Why are you helping him?
'Cause I know how much
you care about him.
Glad you could make it.
The director's expecting you.
Be cool.
You think he saw us?
Never.
Frisk him.
Stalkee is behind a gray van
with another male, possibly
for a sexual encounter.
Both men are physically fit.
Should be lively.
Jeffrey?
Don't make me afraid
to be alone with you.
In case you swallowed a tracker.
Rather err on the side of caution.
They're much quieter
when they're dead.
What do we have here?
Now we can go see the director.
This is the exact model
our federal government uses
when cleaning up hot zones.
Murder investigations.
So, does this model come
with any rebates?
Huh?
Morse code.
Got to run.
It's on the house.
Oh. Ugh.
Lester, I'm in the middle
of something right now.
I can't talk.
Oh, yeah. No, no, no, no.
No worries. No worries, buddy.
I, too, am a little bit busy.
Uh, stalking Sarah's new
stallion, as Jeffrey would say.
You got to be kidding me.
LESTER:
Hang up the phone.
I've been insulted enough.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no, no, no.
You guys are stalking
Sarah's new stallion?
Yes, on our off time,
to show you what amateurs
you're working with.
Well, can you see him right now?
No, we're tucked
behind a dumpster.
But it did look
like the Stallion
and some frat guys were heading
into a dingy warehouse
or something.
Dude is into some kinky stuff.
Okay. Listen, Lester.
I need you to tell me
where you are right now.
It looks like we're at the
corner of 2nd and Alvarado.
Hey!
Oh, thank you, Casey.
I haven't used Morse code
since basic training.
I use it all the time to talk
to my Marine buddies. What's up?
Okay, Shaw gave himself
up to the director,
and Chuck locked me in here
because he knew I would
try and rescue him
and Beckman's going
to bomb the location.
Shaw dies an American hero.
Not if I can help it.
Okay, good. He's
still on the move.
Thank you, Casey.
I'm sorry. I can't
let you stay in here.
Now, Casey.
Hey!
Where is he?
Nice to see you, too.
Suspects have entered
the building.
That is incredible.
You guys are, like, the most
amazing stalkers I've ever seen.
I will tell my grandchildren
about you.
Wait. Wanna borrow
some brass knuckles?
Nunchuks?
Uh, why would you even have...
No. While I appreciate that,
Jeff, very much, I-I-I
don't believe in violence.
So, should they give
You a beat-down,
you expect us to have your back?
No, thanks. Okay. See you later.
Oh.
Here we go.
Wow.
Tracker's gone subterranean.
Location is stabilized
and remains fixed.
Agent Shaw has arrived
and the B-2 has been deployed
with bunker-busters.
What do you want to do?
Drop the bombs.
And Agent Shaw?
He's a true American hero.
Welcome, Daniel.
I've been waiting to meet you
for a long time.
If you're going to kill
me, get it over with.
I don't want to kill you, Daniel.
I want to educate you.
What is this?
A gift.
The answer you've been seeking
for all these years.
MAN (echoing):
Max, who loves you...
WOMAN: (echoing):
Happy birthday.
Okay, my turn. Give me the camera.
Maybe it was a bad idea
to get you a video
for your birthday.
Come on. Now you're
Just wasting tape.
This is ridiculous.
Happy birthday.
How'd you get this?
We have lots of information on Eve.
Just watch, Daniel.
It's time you learned the truth
about your wife's murder.
Thought you might like to see
some surveillance footage
from that night.
No!
It must be so difficult for you.
You didn't think
I'd come here in person.
I'll be in touch.
MAN (over radio):
Three minutes to target.
Huh. No flash necessary.
Good tranqs.
Freeze!
Drop it.
MAN:
We got a lock on the tracker.
BECKMAN:
Congratulations, Agent Walker.
We destroyed a Ring compound,.
hopefully eliminating
some of their higher-ups,
and you managed to rescue
Agent Shaw.
Once again, you and
your team prevail.
I can't take any of
the credit, General.
It was all Chuck.
He saved Shaw by himself.
Duly noted.
Well, Agent Walker, it's been
a highly memorable
three years in Burbank.
I look forward
to working face-to-face
with you in Washington.
Have a safe flight.
How's Shaw doing?
He's still unconscious,
but the doctors say he'll
make a full recovery,
thanks to you.
Well, I mean, you
know he would have
done the same for me.
Look, I don't want
to pester you, Sarah,
or become some, some nuisance
that you can't avoid.
I've seen Morgan
go down that road
far too many times to count.
And since I've already
given the fancy
eloquent version
of this speech before,
right now I'm just gonna be
blunt and honest.
I love you.
One more time just because
it feels really nice
to say: I love you.
I feel like I've been bottling
this up forever. I love you.
Chuck, you don't have...
I'm sorry.
I'm getting out of hand, but...
Look, you were right in Prague.
You and I-- we're perfect
for each other,
and I want to spend the
rest of my life with you
away from everyone else
and away from this spy life.
Chuck, I've made a commitment,
and not just to Shaw.
Don't go.
Don't do it.
Leave with me instead.
Today at 2:00, Union Station,
we go to Mexico, and after that,
anywhere that you want.
I would, however, like to go
and see the Eiffel Tower
at some point
if that's at all possible.
Don't answer now.
Don't say a word.
I don't want to have
to convince you.
I just want you to show up.
I'm gonna kiss you now...
if that's okay.
I'm gonna go home to pack
both summer and winter wear.
I love you, Sarah Walker.
I always have.
WOMAN (over P.A.):
Dr. Morris, dial 183, please.
Dr. Morris.
This is Shaw.
You got a sec?
Uh, yeah, sure. Come on in.
Uh, can I get you
a drink or anything?
No, no, I can't stay.
I just wanted to come by
and tell you something
about Bartowski.
Well, if you came
to plead his case,
then that's really
not necessary.
No, he didn't send me.
He doesn't know I'm here.
I just wanted to tell you something
in case it changed anything.
He didn't kill the mole.
What?
I did.
He didn't have the stones
to pull the trigger.
The kid's not a killer.
Just not wired that way.
Unlike us.
Just thought you should know.
See you around.
Casey...
Yeah?
Thank you.
You have a nice life, Walker.
Hey, Washington will have to wait.
We have a trace on the director.
I have the details
in the car. Come on.
Well, I need to call Chuck.
There's no time. You
can do it from the car.
Chuck, we have
an urgent situation.
Our forensic team was able
to recover this video
from the wreckage
of the Ring's bunker.
The woman is Agent Eve Shaw,
Daniel Shaw's deceased wife.
Well, this is all very
touching, General,
but what does it have
to do with Sarah?
Keep watching.
The data drive the Ring
recovered from the mole's body,
we now believe it contained
footage of a red test
conducted on the night
of Agent Shaw's death.
That's Sarah.
Sarah killed his wife.
Did you know?
I assure you I had no knowledge
that Agent Walker
was responsible
for Eve Shaw's death.
If Shaw has seen this...
if the Ring played
him this video...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. General,
where is Sarah now?
We believe she's with Agent Shaw.
Do you have any idea where
Agent Shaw might have taken her?
I still don't have a signal.
Daniel, where are you taking us?
To settle an old score.
www.addic7ed.com