Hi. I'm Chuck.
Here's a few things
that you might need to know.
I just got fired from my job.
Meeting you, almost makes it worth it.
If you ever find yourself in
Burbank and is still without a job,
my assistant manager owes me
about a million and a half favors.
Here's the thing.
I like her.
I think there's something weird
going on between Chuck and Devon,
it's like they're keeping
this big secret from me.
Finally someone with
some common sense.
We have to figure
out what's going on.
Don't worry about it,
I've got my best men on it.
Perfect.
Casey, things are getting
a little hairy in here.
Please tell me the
Intersect isn't busy.
Busy?
For you? Never.
I want you to teach me, Chuck.
Oh, really? Do you?
Well, I assume that you're
referring to the ancient art
of Nerd Herding, but I must warn you,
the road to computer enlightenment
is a long and treacherous one.
Bring it on.
Speaking of,
how about you bring me
on your next install?
Whoa, easy there.
Before you can run,
you must first learn
to crawl, young grasshopper.
Okay. Well, maybe you would
prefer to go with Jeff, then.
Just the two of you,
cramped into that tiny,
hot Nerd Herd mobile.
Well played, newbie.
Next assignment,
you get to ride shotgun.
Nice.
Excuse me for just one second.
What's going on?
I'm in the middle of something here.
- It's Shaw. It's bad.
- Can't it wait?
No. Not unless you want him
to suffocate to death.
Suffocate to death?
What are you talking about?
'Sup, Hannah?
Hey, just wanted to let you know,
if you need anyone to show
you around the, uh, Buy More...
Who is that?
Super hot blonde, heart of ice?
Yeah, that's Chuck's ex, Sarah.
Oh. What's their deal?
Well, deal is Sarah dumped his ass
and, uh, broke his heart.
And now she can't resist
coming back here to stomp on it.
Look at my boy.
Ah, poor sap.
Everything all right, buddy?
Yeah, got to run.
Nerd Herd emergency.
Right now? I didn't get the call
and technically, all onsites
should run through
the assistant manager.
I gu... Wait, where are you going?
You heard the boss.
Nerd Herd emergency.
Ah, Carry on.
Wait a minute. I'm the boss.
Hey.
Took you long enough.
Yeah, good to see you, too.
You mind telling me what Shaw's doing
breaking into a museum vault?
Forget it. He's only got
five minutes of air left.
Fine. What am I doing?
Getting on the museum's server,
rebooting the system,
and opening the vault door
before Shaw gets snuffed.
They're never going to
let me on their server, Casey.
Well, I took the liberty of crashing it.
It was the only way to stop the alarm.
Unless you get on that server,
there's no way
to open the vault door.
Now get in there, Bartowski.
Oh, you're here.
Thank heavens someone called you.
Yeah, uh, what seems to be the problem?
I'm the curator of Classical Art.
I've never even touched one
of these machines in my life.
All I know is the museum went
into full lockdown mode.
It's designed to protect
the collections from fire,
but unless you fix it,
there's no way to control
the temperature or-or the humidity.
Some of these pieces
are extremely sensitive.
So am I, Chuck.
Chuck, we're in the
crawl space above the vault.
We're trying to get the door open.
It's four inches of solid steel.
We could try blowing the hatches.
We'll have to use C4.
No. Shaw's too close.
You're going to kill him.
It's up to you, Chuck.
You've got to get this door open.
Some of these artifacts
are over 3,000 years old.
To have survive that long
and then to be ruined
by some stupid computer system.
You know, if you don't mind,
I could really use
a little breathing room.
Hmm.
That's right. Step aside.
We are the professionals.
Hannah, what are you doing here?
Surprise. I saw your Nerd Herder
parked outside the museum.
And you said that I could ride shotgun.
So, what's the problem?
Get rid of her, Chuck.
Shaw's got less than a minute.
Look, I don't care which of you it is,
but please do something.
Have you ever restarted a server
from the backup database?
Oh, now you're just insulting me.
Show me what you got.
Run the context script off server one.
Validated. Next?
Just blow the hatch.
Blow the hatch.
What about the mask?
I'm dying.
Roger that.
Fire in the hole.
No, don't!
Don't, computer. Don't do...
I'm just talking to the computer.
'Cause sometimes,
I feel like it helps. Ha.
I need you to reboot
on the count of three.
One, two...
Oh, my God. We did it!
We did it! Hi!
We did it!
Not bad for your first mission.
Splendid work, absolutely top notch.
Really, I mean,
I can't thank you enough.
Well, you know, hey. Any time.
Oh, all right.
Um, how about tomorrow night?
What?
Well, it's the unveiling
of the Mask of Alexander.
Everyone in the art world's
going to be there,
and I'd like you to be also.
Not that I don't appreciate
the invitation...
Oh, no, no. I'm not inviting you.
I'm hiring you.
I want you there
to ensure that, well,
there's no more, uh,
what do you call them?
Bugs.
Take the job, Chuck.
You and your new partner
are going to help us steal
the Mask of Alexander.
So, what do you say, partner?
It's a date.
Magnificent. Isn't it?
Sync by Guga - Corrected by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com
What is that?
Double shot Americano.
No cream, no sugar.
The way you like it.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I noticed you like to chew them
when you get nervous.
Hey, gang.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's going on?
Thanks for joining us, gentlemen.
I'm sure you've all
guessed that the CIA
is not interested in stealing
the Mask of Alexander.
We believe that this artifact
and possibly others,
are being used to smuggle
items through Customs.
What sort of items?
Items of interest to the Ring.
This was three months ago
at the National Museum of Damascus.
A team broke in,
but didn't take anything.
You think the Ring broke in just
to hide something inside the mask?
That's pretty smart.
Traveling exhibitions
don't have to go through
normal screening.
All I know is that we
have to secure the mask
before the Ring does.
Chuck, you'll be in the
museum's control room
in case we have any other snags.
Casey, you'll handle surveillance.
Sarah, you and I will pose
as guests at the party.
We'll break in
and swap the mask, before the unveiling
with this reproduction.
Any questions?
Concerns?
You mean other than us bringing
a civilian on the mission?
I do have some new tranq darts
I'd like to try out.
No, no. I can handle Hannah.
Besides, she can cover for me
in my Nerd Herd duties
in case you guys need
to call in the big guns.
And that would... that would be me.
When I say "big guns", I'm referring
to the Intersect, to myself.
You know, if I need to flash.
Glad we had this talk.
- Morgan.
- Hey.
Chuck would freak if he knew
we were meeting like this.
Morgan, you told me
that Jeff and Lester would get
to the bottom of Chuck's secret.
I may have overstated
their abilities at bit.
What I can tell you
is that Chuck is hardly ever at work.
Always ducking in and out on, uh,
weird Nerd Herd calls.
Yeah. Like his
mysterious trip to Paris.
He's been acting weird ever since.
Right.
You want to know what I think?
- Not really.
- All right.
I think Chuck's protecting us.
Protect us from what?
I don't think he wants us to know
that he's gone to the dark place.
Oh, you don't mean...
Yeah. Junior year.
When Jill dumped him.
Sat in his room and played GoldenEye
for what, three months?
Who knew you could get bedsores
from playing video games?
This makes total sense.
This time, Sarah breaks Chuck's heart,
sends Chuck into an emotional tailspin.
Oh, let's not panic.
Let's not panic.
I'll... I'll see what I can find out,
you know?
How?
I'm the assistant manager
at the Buy More, okay?
I have my methods.
All right, Let's see here.
Phillips head screwdriver set?
Check.
Dummy artifact?
- Check.
- Harnesses?
- And needle-nose pliers.
- Check.
- Descender line.
Check.
Fantastic.
Well...
Lock and load.
You ready, Agent Walker?
Of course I'm ready.
It's just, this is our first mission
in the field, so...
I want to make sure that
we're both on the same page.
Hmm.
So, you ready for your
first mission, Hannah?
Mission?
Well, I'm just trying to say
that, you know, you never know
what's going to happen out there
outside the protection of the Buy More.
You and me, we're...
we're going behind enemy lines.
- Okay.
- You know, maybe we should talk
about how many dates we've been on.
You know, we are playing
a couple tonight, so...
What do you think?
Uh, one, two?
Five?
Does it really make a difference?
It informs our cover.
Our chemistry, body language.
For instance,
have we slept together yet?
You got to be kidding me.
No, it changes the whole dynamic.
Well, in that case, no,
we definitely have not slept together.
Good to know.
All right, well, uh,
make yourselves comfortable.
I trust I shan't be seeing
either of you two again this evening.
The vault is scheduled
to open at precisely 8:00.
The unveiling must go
off without a hitch.
No more bugs,
no more crashes, no more...
No problem.
Problems.
The mask is in this vault.
It opens at 8:00.
Doesn't give us much time
to make the swap.
I thought I made myself
clear about our cover.
Just because we haven't slept together
doesn't mean we have to act
like this is a middle school dance.
Over there, behind that door,
is a staircase that leads
up to the top of the vault.
Keep an eye out on the security cameras
up to your right
and straight ahead.
Are we good, Agent Walker?
Yes, we're fine.
Thank you.
Man, it really is impressive...
The size of Alexander's empire.
You know what I mean?
Can you keep a secret, Chuck?
Huh? Uh... uh...
Yeah, yeah, it's, uh, kind of my forte.
Do you want to know the real reason
that I took this job?
Um... Was it the snazzy outfits?
No, it was the barely livable wage.
You.
Uh... me... me? Really, me?
It's not like I haven't been
giving you signals.
I hope this isn't too forward.
No.
No, forward is good.
In that case...
What did I do?
What did I...
Is there something wrong?
You and your ex-girlfriend...
Yeah, what? Who? Sarah?
Yeah. Morgan said that
you guys were done.
100% done-zo. Why?
That is her, right?
Any idea what she's doing here?
Other than making you jealous
with that ridiculously good-looking
date of hers.
R...  ridiculously good...
Him? Him? Nah.
Yeah, if you're into the...
the strong, kind of Superman-y
type of a guy.
Um, I am going to be right back.
Chuck, what are you doing here?
The Ring agent who broke
into the museum
in Damascus, Vasillis,
is here, and when I say "here",
I mean in the same room, here.
Look over there.
We have to abort.
We don't have a choice.
Vasillis and I have a history.
Are you sure he remembers you?
You tend to remember the guy
who set your face on fire.
Uh, yeah, looks like
your friend isn't alone, either.
They're casing the place.
They're here to grab the mask.
We better move right now.
I'm not sending you in alone.
Hey, it's okay.
No problem. I'll go with her.
You don't know
what you're dealing with.
Get out of here, Shaw,
unless you want to blow the cover.
Chuck and I can handle the mask.
All right.
Casey and I will be in
the van if you need us.
Well, what do you say, partner?
Let's go.
Watch those security cameras.
We have to assume
the Ring has tapped
into those, as well.
Yeah, I'm, uh, one step ahead of you.
Sorry, Hannah.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What's that beeping noise?
Uh... And where's your partner?
Um, he's, uh...
Actually, I don't know.
Look, people have traveled
from all over the world
to be here tonight.
Now, I don't care what's going on,
just fix it.
You have five minutes
until the grand unveiling.
Now, go!
Okay, you're going to have to lower me
into the vault by hand.
Here.
So...
you and Shaw looked like you
were having fun at the party tonight.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm just saying...
you two make a cute couple.
Shaw and I are playing a cover.
Whatever.
But the guy's a...
Walker and Bartowski turn off
their mics for some reason?
No, I did.
Those two gab like little schoolgirls
when they're out in the field.
It's murder on the ears.
- That's ridiculous.
- Ridiculous?
He couldn't keep his
hands off of you all night.
And the way he brings you
coffee every morning?
Seriously?
You don't see the...
You got to be blind.
You're one to talk.
Well, what is that supposed to mean?
Oh, nothing. It's just that,
ever since Hannah showed
up at the Buy More,
she hasn't been able to
keep her hands off you.
Cut the girl a break.
You guys are cute together.
Hannah and I are colleagues.
Forgive me for trying
to be professional.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize professional meant
having her perfume
lathered all over you.
Come on. We got a mask to steal.
Sir, we're ready.
Vasillis sent his men into the vault.
They must have the code.
Walker, you've got company.
Bartowski, you copy?
Incoming.
My hands are kind of full here.
Hi there.
- Sarah.
-Chuck.
Hang on, Chuck. I got you.
Okay.
It's five past 8:00.
Why isn't the vault opening?
Keep your shirt on.
Almost there.
Yes!
Bartowski, I thought you
took care of the vault.
It's the girl, Hannah.
She must be using Bartowski's laptop.
We still tapped in remotely?
Go.
Opening the vault right now.
Thank you so much.
Oh...
No, no.
Why is this happening?
Oh...
Chuck.
I got it, I got it! Chuck.
She broke the connection.
Come on, man.
Go, go, go, go!
Clear! Clear!
We're clear.
Ta-da.
Hey. I'll meet you back at Castle.
Just give me a few minutes to pack up
and smooth things over with Hannah.
Bye.
Hey, Hannah.
Sorry about that.
Where the hell have you been?
How could you abandon me like that
on my first Nerd Herd assignment?
Forget it.
I know where you were.
You do?
Yes.
I saw you with your ex-girlfriend.
Why would you tell me
that things were over
between you when they're clearly not?
It's... it just...
it's not what you think.
Okay. Then, what is it?
Sarah and I have a very...
unique relationship.
Wow.
That sounds really special.
I... I cannot believe
that I made such an ass
- out of myself, kissing you like that.
- No, no!
You didn't make an ass out of yourself.
I'm... I'm the ass.
Yes, clearly.
I think we should just
keep things professional
between us from now on.
No, Hannah, let... let me
make it up to you.
Forget it.
Chuck, don't bother.
I'll see you at work.
That's, like, six knocks short.
I don't know the knock.
Can I come in?
Yes, yes, he's asleep.
He didn't get home till God knows when
after doing God knows what.
Wait, I thought he was at work.
Yeah, so did I till I got
a pissed off call from the museum.
Chuck bailed on a Nerd Herd
and left his partner behind.
Does that sound familiar?
That's great.
So now we're back at square one.
Not necessarily.
I had an epiphany last night.
- What's that?
- It's a sudden, intuitive realization.
- I looked it up.
- I know what an epiphany is, Morgan.
I'm asking what epiphany you had.
Ah, right, well, I think
that we might be going
about this all wrong.
Okay, let's just sit Chuck down
and have an intervention,
force him to be honest with us.
It's the only way to get
to the bottom of this.
Get to the bottom of what?
Nothing, probably my breakfast.
No, what? Good morning.
Hi, morning. Morning, Ellie.
Okay, well, we're going
to be late for work.
Oh, look at that.
- My goodness.
- You...
- We can't do this right now.
- What are you talking about?
You just said "intervention".
What is wrong with you?
You are a coward.
That's who stole my mask.
Pause it.
Who is she?
Oh, he's good.
A real Casanova, this one.
He used the blonde
to get into the vault
and seduced the computer girl
to access the security system.
It's time to see how coldhearted
our thief really is.
Tough night at the museum?
Curator called me
and gave me an earful.
Oh, really? What did he say?
You know, I don't really know.
I have a hard time making out
British accents, you know.
To me, it's just
"Oi, blighty this."
You know, it kind of just
reminds me of Mrs. Doubtfire,
which is an awesome flick.
So what did happen last night?
Well, you know, I...
I don't want to point any fingers...
Don't snitch...
code of the streets.
What are you talking about?
Well, your loyalty to Chuck.
You know, I get it.
You want to protect
your boss, but here's the thing.
I'm his boss is what I'm saying.
Actually, I don't want you
to think of me as your boss' boss.
I'd rather you think of me as a friend
ultimately, you know,
and a friend you can tell anything to.
And I do mean anything.
Excuse me.
Hello. Nerd Herd.
I'm calling from the museum.
Another doofus with an accent.
Can you believe this?
How may I help you?
We are still having problems
with our computer system.
Perhaps you can send the
girl you sent last night.
Uh, you must mean Hannah.
Right.
Hannah.
Absolutely, I think she'd be
happy to come back out,
and in fact, to make up for the hiccup,
it's on the house.
I can even send her supervisor along.
But I... cannot do that actually, um...
He is busy.
I'm sure she'll be able to
handle the problem herself.
She-she will indeed, absolutely.
- Okay.
- Thank you,
Morgan, you are a great friend.
That's very sweet of you...
and also very poignant because...
I believe that that's
a great place to start,
you know, and then
we can build from there.
Oh, God.
Good morning, Walker.
Okay, we need to talk.
- About last night?
- About everything.
About professional boundaries,
about you bringing me coffee
to work every morning and noticing
that I like to chew
on my swizzle sticks.
You're embarrassing us both.
We are just colleagues and that is
all we are ever going to be,
so please keep your coffee
and your cheesy come-ons to yourself.
Okay, you got that?
Good, now let's get back to work.
I feel like I should probably
apologize to Colonel Casey.
Hey, Shaw, thanks for the coffee.
Just the way I like it. Black and bitter.
Hello?
Nerd Herd.
Hi, someone called.
Yes, thank you for coming.
Where's the old curator?
He's tied up.
I'm the assistant curator.
This way.
We've been having problems
with the security system in the vault,
if you don't mind
having a look.
I really just fix computers.
You seem like a smart girl.
You'll figure it out.
Oh, you don't happen to have a phone?
No, I left it in the car.
Don't worry.
Hey.
Hey!
Nerd Herd. How can I help you?
You can bring me my mask.
Uh, I think you might have
the wrong number, sir.
Let me rephrase.
Either you bring me the mask or
I kill your girlfriend.
Morgan, have, uh, have you seen Hannah?
Yeah, she's out on a call.
Something at the museum.
Sir, first of all,
I... I don't have a girlfriend,
just for clarification's sake,
and second, like I mentioned earlier,
this is the Nerd Herd desk,
so unless you have
a computer-related...
I know who you are.
If you want to see the girl alive,
you'll come to the museum
and come alone.
She runs out of air in 30 minutes.
Bring me my mask.
Hey, buddy.
Uh, here we go.
- Chuck, I think we need to talk.
- Not a good time.
You know what?
I don't care anymore.
Listen, I'm your best friend, dude,
or at least I used to be,
and I deserve to know what...
No, I demand to know
what the hell is going
on with you lately.
Chuck...
You got to be kidding me.
Hmm, check the base.
- Chuck.
- Sarah...
Sarah, I need the mask now.
Vasillis knows we took it
and he wants it back.
He grabbed Hannah.
I'm coming down the tunnel.
That can't be good.
Uh, Chuck, don't come in here.
We think the mask is some kind of a...
No.
Oh, no.
Guys, guys, it's poison.
You think?
It's a designer weapon
developed for battlefield use,
but th... there's a counteragent
that can be taken up to
30 minutes after exposure.
Or what?
Look, don't worry.
I'm gonna get the
counteragent from Vasillis.
He wouldn't have shipped
the weapon without it.
It's got to be back at the...
Casey, gear up.
We're heading back to the museum.
- This is never gonna work.
- It'll work.
Here.
Okay... okay, fine.
So let's say we're able
to fool Vasillis
with another fake mask
and we save Hannah.
That still doesn't solve the problem
of how we convince him
to give us the counteragent.
What about Sarah and Shaw?
Do we have enough time
to save them, too?
Wait, wait, I got it, I got it.
We gas him.
That's a great plan,
except the chemical weapon's
already been deployed.
Yeah, but Vasillis doesn't know that.
I got some smoke grenades in the back.
Funny, I don't feel like I'm dying.
Chuck will come through for us.
In case he doesn't...
I wanted to clear the air between us.
It turns out I haven't been
completely honest about, uh, the coffee
and how I was acting at the museum.
Truth is I was hitting on you.
It was completely unprofessional
and I apologize.
I owe you an apology as well.
I overreacted.
The way you touched
my neck at the party...
I guess it was kind of nice.
Really?
Really.
Well, then,
I... I'm glad we had this talk.
Yeah, me, too.
The poison has been contained.
The room has been cleared.
We got to get you out of here.
Stop there.
Show me my mask.
Show me my Nerd Herder.
She's in the vault.
Oh, look at the time.
Air must be getting a little thin.
If he doesn't open the door,
I'm going to blow the vault.
I can't promise she'll be okay.
I did what you asked
and I brought the mask.
Now let her out.
If it were up to me, sure.
She would walk free.
But the people you've stolen from,
the Ring, they're not so forgiving.
Do what you want to me
but the girl had nothing
to do with this.
You're in no position to make demands.
You gave up any leverage
you might've had
when you walked in with the mask.
Not quite.
I think we all know
what's inside this mask.
So either you open that
door and let her out
or I release the gas.
I don't believe you.
Well, that's too bad.
You should've.
You've killed us all.
You idiot!
Well, there's a counteragent, right?
Where is it?
It's in a vase.
There's hundred of them.
Which one?
How am I supposed to know?
I wasn't going to steal it personally.
Oh, I see, and I'm the idiot?
Come on, Chuck.
One of these things
is not like the others.
Oh. Oh.
Time's up, Chuck.
No, Casey, wait!
I found the counteragent.
Meet me in the control room.
When do I get to blow something up?
Casey, here, here.
How time we got left?
Don't worry about that.
You get her out of the vault.
You don't have enough time, do you?
Focus, Bartowski.
Even if they are lost,
we still have a civilian in there.
Get her out of there!
Come on, come on.
Yes!
Sarah? Shaw? What the...?
Here's the counteragent.
I'll go release the curator.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, thank you.
Hannah? Hannah? Hannah?
- What happened?
- You, uh...
You passed out and I think, uh,
somehow you got trapped in the vault.
Oh, my God.
I could've died in here.
You saved my life, Chuck.
Well, I don't...
Oh, hey.
Hey, hey.
Look, I know I was acting really weird
- the other night...
- Forget it.
Nice work, everyone.
And you...
- I owe you one, Bartowski.
- Oh, come on.
Just 'cause I saved your life. Twice.
Don't mention it.
It wasn't just my life.
Yeah.
You also helped
secure a rogue chemical weapon.
Guys.
Look, I appreciate a ticker tape parade
just like the next guy,
but, come on, I got a great team.
And that brings us to our
next point of business.
Well, uh, Chuck,
you're not going to have us forever.
The Intersect was originally designed
so that agents could work autonomously.
We're your training wheels.
And your performance tells me
that it's about time for
us to come off.
Hope you're ready for your
big boy bike, Bartowski.
Huh.
Hey.
Uh, I just wanted to
make sure you were okay.
Yeah. I mean, I guess
I've gotten used to us being a team,
- you know.
- Well, we're not going anywhere yet.
But Shaw's right.
At some point I'm just going
to be standing in your way,
and not just professionally.
Right.
Are you sure you're okay
with the whole Hannah thing?
Oh, I should've have
given you a hard time.
She's great and...
How do you think
I feel about you and Shaw?
I mean, you two are perfect together.
It's disgusting.
Oh.
In... in... in a heartwarming
kind of way.
Look, all I know is the guy carried you
out of Castle on his back
while you were both dying.
So, if I have to see you
with someone else
it might as well be a hero, right?
What can I say?
I have a type.
I'll see you, Sarah.
Bye, Chuck.
Well done on the knock.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Is Chuck here?
Slinking around somewhere, yeah.
Uh, you ready to do this?
Time for an intervention.
What is Chuck doing here so late?
This is exactly the behavior
I was talking about, Ellie, okay.
Your brother...
He is into something weird here.
No, no...
- Cameras, cameras, cameras.
- Morgan, listen to me.
Whatever is going on behind that door,
we need to know about, okay?
This is for Chuck.
For Chuck.
- Yes.
- You go.
- Okay, I will.
Oh, my God!
Chuck has a secret girlfriend.
This means he's moving
on with his life,
and he's not wallowing in self-pity,
and playing video games.
This is such a relief.
Such a relief.
Man.
Okay, I'm going to head out.
You two coming?
Uh, no, I'm going to finish up in here.
Yeah, I'm... I'm pretty buried, too.
So...
Ah.
We both know how dangerous this is.
Relax, Sarah.
I'm the safest guy in the world.
Are you sure it was him?
I'd never mistake Daniel Shaw.
What are you going to do to him?
Same thing I'm going to do to you.
Sync by Guga - Corrected by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com