DJ Just got a call
from Heather Chandler,
who'd like
to dedicate this next song
to the James Buchanan
varsity football team.
Go, Cougars!
SAN DIEGO, CALIFORNIA. 1998.
IN CASE OF EMERGENCY
LOVE YOU, DADDY
You know, you don't have to
keep buying stuff for cover
BURBANK, CALIFORNIA. 2008
just 'cause you're
in here all the time.
BURBANK, CALIFORNIA. 2008
I actually needed
new iPod speakers.
I'm just saying it's
perfectly plausible
that you're in
here to discuss
dinner plans with
me, your boyfriend.
Okay, sweetie, what are you in
the mood for, Thai or Chinese?
Wait, really?
No, I'm still
digesting my Honey
Nut Cheerios.
Okay, I'm a
little unprepared
to discuss dinner
plans at this point.
Oh, unless we're...
unless we're not going
to be actually eating.
Will we be eating food
or are we just saying
we'll be eating food?
Not that it really
matters, it just...
it'll factor into
lunch, you know?
Can I get a straight
answer from you, Sarah?
I mean, you don't have
to be so secretive
or dodgy about pad
Thai noodles...
Bogey at your six.
Roger that- secure
the asset immediately.
Take him to the Orange Orange.
Hey, ow, ow,
okay, okay, okay.
You stay here.
Why, what's going on?
I couldn't shake
a suspicious tail,
so until we establish
the depth of the threat,
you're staying put- don't move.
Touch nothing.
Wait for me, got it?
Whatever.
Oh, wow.
I can't believe I'm this close
to an actual DU97.
Freon-cooled, reconfigurable
30-teraflop architecture
with modules for cryptanalysis
and video processing.
She's so beautiful.
I know you.
And I never
forget a face.
Buy More, courtyard.
AKWARD
Guess I just have one
of those familiar faces.
Jackpot.
That's not it-
I know you.
I tried my hand at acting
a while back.
It'll come to me.
I was on a national
television commercial.
I ate a messy cheeseburger.
Maybe that's it.
I know exactly who you are.
We went to high school together!
What?
Wait, wait, wait,
don't tell me your name.
I'll get it.
I never forget
a face.
You look so
different now.
Well, for the
better, I mean.
Oh, I'm sure you
have me confused
- with someone else...
- Jenny!
That's it: Jenny Burton!
Jenny Burton?
Heather Chandler.
Well, Heather Ratner now.
I married
Mark Ratner.
James Buchanan High,
class of '98.
Go, Cougars!
Heather, of course.
Um, how have you been?
Oh, my God, Mark,
look who it is.
It's Jenny Burton.
Who?
Jenny Burton from
high school.
You know, the one.
Oh, yeah, hi, Jenny.
Heading down for the reunion
this weekend?
Oh, no, I'm not much
of a reunion person.
Hey.
I told you to stay put.
I know, I just, you know...
the tummy is a-rumbling.
- Chuck.
- Yes, honey?
Is this your
boyfriend?
Wait, you know
these people, sweetie?
- NO.
-  I'm Heather- we all went to high school together.
Come on!
Of all the semi-tart
Asian influenced
frozen yogurt shops
in all the towns
in all the world,
you walked into hers?
I know, it's
crazy, right?
We live
in Westlake now
because its closer
to Mark's work,
but we go down
there all the time.
Do you? You go...
go down there, huh?
Weather's real nice
this time of year.
Do you need a to-go lid?
Well, come on now.
Weather's always great
in San Diego.
Yes, it is!
That's what I always say,
down there
in San Diego where you're from.
I'm Chuck, by the way,
but around here,
people just know me as...
as Jenny's Chuck.
Jenny and Chuck.
Chuck and Jenny.
Chuck, I'm Mark Ratner.
VOICE RECOGNITION: MATCH
VINTHROP-KELLER
AERONAUTICS
Brain freeze.
I think I had a little
too much yogurt.
Hey.
What are you guys doing
for dinner tonight?
You got any plans?
'Cause maybe
we could all
get together
and reminisce about old times.
Sounds great.
I mean, any friends of Jenny
are friends of mine.
Oh, I don't know, Chuck,
it might be pretty
boring for you
to take a trip
down memory lane with us.
Good God, no, not at all.
I can't think of anything
that I'd rather do
than spend an evening
learning all about...
my Jenny.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
CHUCK 204
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译: 校对:
时间轴:我爱狮心小s
Gather 'round, clock punchers.
Big announcement.
I'm not coming in
for a few days-
got a meeting.
Oh, some fat cats
over at corporate?
Nope.
With a bunch
of fat catfish
over in Lake Havasu.
And while I'm away,
Mr. Patel here
will be in charge.
Party hardy.
Or the opposite of that?
I want you to give Lester
the same respect you give me.
When you look
at him,
I want you
to see Big Mike
and not some
scrawny-ass Indian kid
with a Bay City
Rollers hairdo.
Thank you, sir.
That's it.
Back to the salt mine.
Dinner? Come on!
What the hell
were you thinking, Chuck?
What was I
supposed to do?
I flashed on the guy.
Those people
are from my past,
a past you have no business
poking around in.
Well, I'm sorry, I was
just trying to do my job.
I thought you'd be happy
I used a little initiative.
Uh, don't kill the messenger.
Not the kid's fault
you went to high school
with a treasonous scumbag.
Good morning, boys and girl.
First matter of
business: Mark Ratner.
He's an engineer
at Winthrop-Keller Aeronautics,
has clearance to
extremely sensitive plans
for future weapons
technology.
Picture the next generation
of F-22 Raptors.
Essentially, a superbomber.
This technology
has been leaked.
Chuck's instincts
were good.
Your mission is
to go to dinner
with the Ratners, see if Chuck
flashes off of anything.
General, I apologize,
but I'm afraid
I must recuse myself
from this mission.
My cover has been compromised.
Agent Walker,
you have preexisting social
history with the target.
Seems to me like you
have the perfect cover.
But it's not a cover,
ma'am, it's me.
Well, I hope you
enjoy Italian food.
Buon appetito.
With Big Mike gone,
I've come up
with a plan
to revolutionize
Buy More sales.
From now on, we're gonna work
with our customers
to create a mutually
agreed upon price.
Yeah, but how are we supposed
to do that? I mean...
As this is
a teaching hospital...
watch and learn,
my friends.
Watch and learn.
- Hey.
So, you're in the market
for a new TV.
- Yeah.
- You shopping for your mother?
What?
No, it's for me.
This one's a little
dainty, isn't it?
You want the complete
entertainment experience.
I would recommend
this one.
Uh, I can't
afford this one.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Don't get caught up in this.
This...
is just a suggestion.
How about you make me an offer?
Okay.
How about you shave 300 bucks
off that price?
- Sold.
- Really?
Hey there.
May I help you
with this washer and dryer?
Oh, afraid it's
not in my budget.
I'm only in the
market for a dryer.
Ma'am, that's like
buying one new shoe.
No, no, no, no,
make me an offer.
You happy with
that price?
Guess I'd be happier
if it was 100 bucks cheaper.
I live for your smile.
Let me take off $200.
Deal.
I'll sell you
that computer
for 400 bucks
off sticker price.
Hey, buddy, what's going on?
Lester's new sales policy.
We're giving away
the merchandise.
Throw in
a wireless mouse?
Throw in a wireless mouse
and a bonus computer.
That's gonna
end badly.
I know.
I know, Chuck.
That's part of the fun.
Sold.
You're early.
Technically, I'm right on time
for my pre-mission
debriefing.
What are you talking about?
Standard spy protocol.
You know, I need some stats
for my cover tonight.
- Chuck, I'm really...
- No need to apologize
if you didn't have time
for full dossier preparation.
I think we'll just go over a few
facts together if that's okay.
Fantastic. I'll go first.
Uh, tonight, I'll be playing the
role of Jenny's boyfriend Chuck.
He works at the Buy More,
not living up to his potential.
Sister is Ellie, doctor,
engaged to a doctor.
There, all up to speed
on Jenny's boyfriend.
Your turn.
I'm not doing this.
Okay, here's what we know
thus far.
Jenny Burton went to
James Buchanan
High School
in San Diego, California,
class of 1998.
Is it safe to assume
that "Jenny"
is a diminutive of "Jennifer?"
Back off, Chuck.
You have as much information as
is pertinent to this assignment.
Spell "Jenny" with
an "I" or would...
All Jenny's boyfriend
needs to know
is that Jenny hates
questions about her past.
You got that?
I'm good.
Yeah, I'm good.
How do you do that?
So, Mark,
uh... what line of work
are you in?
Uh, engineering.
Actually, what
I'm working on
is technically...
- top secret.
- And let's keep it that way,
'cause no one gives a rip.
So, how long have you two
lovebirds been together?
- Months.
- Years.
That add up to years.
You know, I don't even remember
my life before Chuck.
What's the matter with you?
You're sweating
like a pig.
It's kind of gross.
No. Oh, sorry.
I'm fine.
Would you excuse me
for a minute?
Sure.
So, Jenny, is your
job at the yogurt shop,
like, a career
or are you
keeping yourself
in Top Ramen
between acting gigs.
Oh, I-I've got
a few things going on.
I mean, Chuck,
if you had told me
in high school that Jenny Burton
wanted to grow up
to be a movie star,
I would've said,
"Dream,
little duckling, dream. "
And now here we are.
Your time is up,
Mr. Ratner.
Soup looks delicious, Chuck.
Mmm, it is.
Cilantro,
very controversial.
You either love
it or hate it.
Me, I love it.
So, Jenny, when's the last time
you were down in San Diego?
Mm, it's
been a while.
Mm, don't get to visit
your dad much?
Um, excuse me,
more wine, please.
Ah, yes.
It's a lovely pinot
noir, earthy, complex,
- with a hint of cherry blossoms.
- So, you know when you're kids
and there's
always that funhouse
that all the kids
hang out at.
Would you say that was
the case with Jenny's
- house-condo-apartment?
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
God, I'm-I'm
such a spaz.
Now, there's the Jenny we know.
Excuse me.
Beg your pardon.
Not the first American tax
dollars wasted on a man's lap.
Give us the plans now.
I need to know
that if I hand over the plans,
no harm will come to my wife.
Oh, my God.
Who the hell are you?
Who is this guy?!
This is setup?
No! God, no!
He's no one!
That's a little hurtful.
He's just the
boyfriend
of some-some girl
that I went
to high school with!
I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna
grab some club soda
to take care of my stain.
So, Heather, uh, how do you
stay in such great shape?
Got obsessed with karate 'cause
my instructor's such a hottie.
I'm a black belt now.
I clued in you didn't want
to talk about
your dad's situation
in front of your BF.
Does Chuck not know?
Uh, do you mind if I take over?
Oh, no.
It's my first day.
- Go check on Chuck.
- If you promise
not to filet her
before I get back.
- I can't promise anything.
- Okay.
Took a knife skills course
at the culinary academy.
Is that to further
your yogurt career,
or are you
angling towards
something bigger?
Say, carving station at Lawry's.
So, what you know?
I don't know anything.
I just came in to do
my little boy business.
Turn on hand dryer,
so no one hear him scream.
Hear who scream? Me scream?
You?
All right.
Gonna pull the van around
so we can stow these guys.
Be right back.
Oh.
How?
How did you do that?
Uh...
Uh, you know,
it's a self-defense thing
I took at the Y.
It was pretty comprehensive.
Are you nuts?
These guys are killers!
Bullies are like bears,
you know?
They're more afraid of you
than you are of them.
Or is that bees?
Actually,
it is bee.
Anyway, when you're dealing
with the Russian mob...
How, how did you know
they're connected to the mob?
Wait a minute.
I know exactly who you are.
Dude!
You're the man!
I'm hardly the man.
So who do you work for?
Is it the FBI?
CIA? NSA?
I, you know, I can't
discuss the particulars.
Okay.
I get it, I get it.
But just tell me, does-does
Jenny know who you really are?
Jenny knows nothing.
Of course not.
But anyway, I-I just
want to thank you so much
for saving my life.
Can't you just
tell me your name, Agent...?
Carmichael.
Special Agent
Charles Carmichael.
This is not a negotiation.
Okay, Ratner,
here's how this is
gonna go down.
Wait.
You're our waiter.
From the
restaurant.
Man, we really screwed you
on the tip.
You want into
witness protection,
you're gonna have
to scratch our back, too.
What do you mean?
Those two goons from last night,
they don't report back
to their boss, he's gonna
want a follow-up meet.
We're gonna cover that drop.
He contact
you yet?
I'm sorry, but I
prefer to deal only
with Special
Agent Carmichael.
The man saved my life
last night.
Is that right,
Special Agent Carmichael?
Uh...
It's funny...
You should really see me
scale buildings with
suction cups, 'cause I'm...
I'm very good at that.
I only dabble in the violence.
So...
Modesty doesn't suit you,
Mad Dog.
Mad Dog?
Why... Why do they
call him that?
Listen, I got to know
where your next meet's at, okay?
And I'll ask you real politely.
My partner here, he's a maniac.
It's...
It's fine when
it's to protect you,
but you don't want to be
on the receiving end of Mad Dog.
That's how I got this.
Huh?
I parked in his spot once.
This scar
reminds me every day-
don't mess with Mad Dog.
Now, I'm gonna ask you...
Let me ask you
one more time.
Where's the meet?
Look, I-I don't know, okay?
He texts me.
That's it, that's all I know.
He's all yours,
Mad Dog.
No, no! I...
Wait a minute.
This, this is him,
right now. He's-he's-he's...
He's texting me right
now! This is him!
Okay, he wants to meet tonight.
But-but that doesn't
work for me.
I can't meet tonight.
Tonight's my reunion,
and my wife has
really been looking
forward to this- she
wants to be reunion queen.
I couldn't disappoint her.
Stop talking!
You'll meet him there.
I... I-I don't know about this.
No one's gonna
mess with you, man.
I got your back.
Okay.
Okay, I'll do it.
No!
This can't be right!
No! No! No! No!
No! How did
this happen?!
No!
Hey, Chuck, what's up, buddy?
What are you doing here?
- I thought it's your day off.
- Yeah.
I had to swing by the mall to
pick something up for Sarah.
It's a long story.
What's going on with Lester?
What is happening?!
Is this broken?!
Are you broken?!
He's been at it for,
like, 15 minutes.
Hey.
What's going on?
Everything okay?
Chuck.
Chuck, thank God you're here.
You-you'll know what to do.
Look, so the new
Friendly Negotiations
sales strategy
worked brilliantly.
Right? We moved
the largest volume
of big-ticket merchandise
in four years.
But no matter how many times
I crunch the numbers,
we're still out 2,700 bucks.
Well, you forgot
to carry the one,
so actually it's 3,700.
What?! Oh,
my God!
I'm sorry I let you down, sir.
All right, come on.
Pull yourself
together here, man.
All right, everybody, listen up.
We are up excrement creek
without a paddle.
Okay? So we're just
looking for a few ideas
to make a lot of cash
by tonight. Any ideas?
My mom knows a dude
who will torch the place.
Our troubles will
go up in flames.
Yeah.
While I'm impressed by
the outside-of-the-box nature
of Jeff's pitch,
I'm thinking
maybe
a simpler solution.
Remember when we were
in high school
and we were hard
up for cash,
so when your
parents were out
of town, we'd host
a big kegger,
invite everybody
and charge by the head.
That's great, Chuck,
that's perfect.
- That's what we're gonna do.
- Yes!
No, no, no, I was... that...
I... that was a good idea
if we were 16.
Invite people from the mall.
And I can call
my best friend, Beer,
see if he can make it
on such short notice.
This could actually work,
this could actually work.
Great, good, glad I'll
be 100 miles away.
LET GO!
Hey, Jenny.
You must be getting
pretty lonely
with your dad locked up.
Call me if you ever need a man
around the house.
What?
Brought you a present.
Well, it's not
my birthday.
Oh, one down,
364 and a quarter
possibilities to go.
Just open the box, hmm?
Why do I need
a new dress for?
I know you're gonna see
this as a glass half-empty,
but I think it's a
real opportunity...
- Spill it!
- We have to go to your reunion.
Look, I know that you don't like
talking about your past,
much less revisiting it,
but the reunion is where
the drop's going down.
Look, I'm sorry.
It's just...
High school...
It was a tough time
for me, okay?
Tell me about it.
I- I-I get that.
Trying to figure out
who you are
and what you're gonna do
with the rest of your life
while constantly distracted
with raging hormones.
- I...
- It was more than that for me.
Hey... it'll be okay.
Trust me.
Besides, everybody
remembers high school
way worse than it was.
YOU LOOK GREAT
Welcome Cougar,
class of '98!
Hi.
Jennifer Burton?
Burton?
Ooh, here.
Thanks.
Wait. You're Jenny Burton?
I am if it says I am
OH, MY GOD.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
No one's gonna mess
with you, Sarah, okay?
I got your back.
Wow!
Oh.
It's not that bad.
- It's not that bad.
- Mm-hmm.
WELCOME BACK
COUGARS CLASS OF 1998!
Thank you.
Remember, the only difference
between high school
and a high school reunion is
that you don't get suspended
for being drunk.
Want to dance?
Fortunately for you,
I was at the top
of my game in '98.
Oh, a little bit of that.
Come that, oh, and then...
and then mirror that,
you know,
just kind of...
What? What is it? You okay?
So, my buddies and I
checked out the room
and picked the
best-looking girl here.
Decided to come
introduce myself
to the woman I'll be
waking up with tomorrow.
Dick Duffy.
And I'm Chuck,
Jenny's boyfriend, so...
Jenny? Wait. Jenny Burton?
Damn!
Ten years has been
very sweet to you.
Thank you.
Ten years is a hell
of a long time,
especially to someone living
in an eight by ten cell.
How is your dad?
PAROLED
LAS VENTURAS PRISON 4 YEARS: GRAND THEFT AUTO
Nachos!
Nachos! I
smell nachos!
That's gonna
hit the spot.
Let's get some
nachos. Bye, Dick.
I think that's him,
that's the guy.
- What guy?
- Duffy. I just flashed on Duffy.
What'd you do?
Attend Bad Guy High?
What are you talking about?
Well, Duffy has some kind of
connection to the Russian mob.
I'm pretty sure he's the
guy that Ratner is supposed
to connect with to hand
off the super-bomber plans.
Makes sense.
He's always been a jerk.
Okay, you go catch Ratner up,
have him set up the meet.
I'll tip off the DJ.
Why? Why the DJ?
CUSTOMER SERVICE
Dude, look at this.
We're in a sweet spot.
People are loving this.
I can't believe
this is actually working.
Hey! Hey!
Take off your shoes!
Tell them
to wipe their feet, right?
Keep it... Will you please
keep it down?
Keep the fingers
off the merchandise
over there, please.
Please. Please.
We got to be considerate
of the neighbors, okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
This the way you people treat
your own homes?!
My bosses at Langley have
informed me that that's the guy
who's been texting you.
Our target is Dick Duffy?
Of course!
The guy who terrorizes
me in high school
is now going
to terrorize the entire world
with my super-bomber.
You're gonna be just fine.
You have my personal guarantee.
Uh, excuse me, Dick?
I believe
I'm supposed
to see you
about a certain transaction.
Ratner.
You're the last guy I thought
I'd be having
this conversation with.
All right, fine.
Meet me outside
in five minutes.
Welcome class of '98!
Go Cougars.
Never should have
stolen the
bomber plans.
I should have gone
right to you guys.
But they threatened my wife.
I wasn't
thinking straight.
You see,
I'm just a guy who likes math,
you know, and
somehow I got
a beautiful girl like that
to fall in love with me.
I have to pinch
myself sometimes.
It's like
I'm dreaming.
Ah, forget it, Agent Carmichael.
I mean,
how can I expect a cool guy
like you to understand?
You know what, Mark?
Sometimes the nerd
gets the girl.
In the middle of something?
Got time for you.
Where's your boyfriend at?
Oh, don't worry
about him.
Can't believe
you're that same Jenny
from high school.
You've changed so much.
Well, I'm still the same girl
on the inside.
Bet you miss your daddy.
He's been gone so long.
But you know, baby,
you can always call me daddy.
Ooh!
That's all right.
I like my ladies rough.
Great.
Now we know he's a perv,
don't know if he's the perp.
Yeah, sorry.
I'm just working out
some childhood issues.
Knockoff watches,
bootleg DVDs.
He came out here
to sell Ratner a dime bag.
Guy's small time.
So if Duffy isn't
our guy, then who is?
My husband spilled everything
to the Feds.
That's him and his handler.
I overheard them talking.
He's some
CIA bad ass named Carmichael.
Kill 'em both.
Give him to me.
Find your own
freakin' fish!
- GIVE ME THAT!- YOU'RE A FOOL!
Norman!
That's it!
Party's over! Get out!
Right now!
I mean, was I born
to be a lawman? No.
I'd say it's more
of a calling.
I got a bit
of the shine.
GANG ACTIVITY
FORGERY
Oh, no.
What's oh, no?
Slight wrinkle in the plan,
got to improvise.
Move!
Welcome!
James Buchanan High,
Class of '98!
Go Cougars!
Uh...
Uh, for those of you
who remember me,
I clearly need no introduction,
and for those
of you who don't,
I'm not up here
to talk about myself anyway.
No. I'm here to talk
to you about some people
that will cause
you to flash,
flash back,
that is.
So, maybe with a...
with a few hints
and a little bit of luck,
we can find two
special Cougars,
and throw some
love on them.
Oh, how about... how about
- this guy, huh?
- Michael Adler.
Drooled his way
through Spanish class?
Se habla espanol?
I know you
do, Michael.
And, uh, who, uh...
who else do we have?
Hey, she is a part of this.
You go. I got these two.
Oh! Oh! How about, uh...
How about this guy
here? Come on, folks.
I know you know
him. Chippy!
Our one and only Chippy Sternin!
Remember, all-star
pole-vaulter, who was
unfortunately sidelined
- with a horrible case of impetigo?
- Come on, let's go.
I was rooting for you,
buddy. I thought you were
gonna go all-state,
but you know what?
It wasn't
in the cards.
Come on,
love on those guys really.
Just throw some arms
around them.
Heather?
Who's drunk?
You're drunk.
All right,
fantastic.
Heather,
why'd you do it?
Revenge of the
Cheerleaders.
We marry the geeks
because they're the ones
with the future.
But my husband wasn't
ambitious enough.
And they were offering
a lot of money.
Who do you work for?
I can help you.
I'm self-employed.
Your name has been at
the top of my list
of 'People who need
good ass-kicking. '
Get in the locker now,
Ratner.
You have three seconds
to tell me
where the plans are.
One...
two...
Agent Carmichael, help!
GREATEST HITS '98
Before I go here's a classic
from 1998.
Help!
Let me out!
Hello?
You should've been
suspicious of me right off.
I mean, why would
a girl like me
ever fall in love
with a dorky nerd like him?
You'd be surprised.
Thanks a lot,
Mad Dog.
Always count
on you to be
in the right place
at the right time.
Wh-wha...
I knew you wouldn't let me down,
Agent Carmichael.
Glad I'm not the one
who has to tell Ratner
about his wife's
involvement in all this.
That's why love
is for suckers.
Yeah.
Hey, you seen Sarah
anywhere?
Sucker.
Now, I got to ask.
How'd you wind up working
for the Feds?
I mean, if you had told me
in high school
that Jenny Burton wanted
to grow up to be an agent,
I would've said, "Dream,
jailbird's daughter,
dream. "
Guess you didn't
follow in daddy's
footsteps after all.
Go Cougars.
And the queen
of the class
of 1998's ten-year reunion is...
Jennifer Burton!
Jenny?
Where are you?
There you are!
Come on up here, Jenny.
See you at the
20th, Jenny!
Don't worry.
We'll fix this.
It'll-It'll
be all good.
It'll be all good.
Come on, guys,
we're almost there.
Big Mike's gonna be here
any minute. Let's go!
Listen up,
listen up, listen up.
Um, first of all,
I just
want to acknowledge
that
I know that I'm not
the easiest man
to work for, but I want to thank
you for all your hard work.
And mean it this time.
I mean, guys,
what we've accomplished here
is incredible.
And each and every one of you
is a big bright,
shining star.
Oh, mother crapper,
the fish!
Glue's still a little wet,
but we had no choice, dude.
Morgan.
You did all this for me
when I haven't always been
very kind to you?
May I ask you why?
I don't know, man.
I thought, you know, if I
was there for you selflessly,
that you would see that people
are essentially kind at heart.
You know, and maybe you
wouldn't walk around
so afraid in this world.
Dude, are
you crying?
Come on, I'm just
doing my job.
Oh, Mike's coming.
Work you've done here
is outstanding.
Everyone's on time,
store is tidy.
Even smells like a
pine-scented forest.
Nice touch, Patel.
Will you look
at these sales totals?
With the kind of brisk
business you've done here
in my absence,
I should go away more often.
Sir,
if I might, um,
the truth is that the,
the pressure of management,
it's, it's
just too much.
I would really,
uh, appreciate it
if I could just resume
my former position.
- You sure, son?
- Yes.
Yes, thank you.
What the hell?
Norman!
Isn't that supposed
to be a raw steak?
Not on a Buy More salary,
thank you very much.
I did, however,
scrape together enough cash
to get you a cooked one as well.
Medium rare with...
- Extra pickles?
- extra pickles.
Come on, who do you think
you're dealing with here?
Well, I never doubted you,
Special Agent
Charles Carmichael.
So I guess the big secret
about you
is that you used to be just
a typical high school student.
Wish I knew what happened
to change that.
IN CASE OF EMERGENCY
LOVE YOU, DADDY
Nice toss.
Who are you?
I'm the man who put
your father in prison.
The question is: Who are you?
In San Diego, you
go by Jenny Burton.
In Wisconsin,
it's Katie O'Connell.
In Cleveland, it's
Rebecca Franko.
Funny thing is when I looked
at your birth certificate...
I get your point.
What do you want?
Your father scammed some
pretty dangerous people.
I saved his life by
putting him in jail.
Well, don't expect
a thank-you note.
I can save your life, too.
No, not that way.
Your dad trained
you pretty well.
The CIA can do even better.
You like names so much, hmm?
What do you think
about Sarah Walker?
Sarah Walker,
hello.
Okay, fine.
I'll answer one question
about my past.
You've earned that much.
Hmm.
No, thanks.
I don't need to know more,
not about who you were,
'cause as much as you don't
think so, I know who you are.
A girl I'd like to share
a cheeseburger with.
Should I get a knife?
I'll get
- a knife.
- That won't be necessary.
That's awesome
and a little disturbing.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
A LITTLE BIT MESSY.
YOU WANT A BIG HALF OR...