January 22, 1980
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
- Two bucks.
- Here you go.
Thanks.
Buck 29.
I only have a dollar.
- Is this for school?
- Yeah.
All right, then.
Education's important.
You don't wanna end up like
those mutts on the corner.
Get outta here.
- And be careful.
- Thanks, mister.
Boss!
Takeout's getting cold.
Vera's wolfing down the last of
the sweet and sour. / Okay.
The Sixers traded Allen Iverson.
Uh-huh.
Boss...
- food's here.
- Oh, thanks, Lil.
I'm not hungry.
You got something on a cold one?
No, I just come down to take a look at
that case every once in a while.
Any reason?
Tender age.
The kid was eight.
Your job?
No...No!
No!
My little boy!
Calm down, please ,sir.
- Any good leads?
- Oh, plenty. None panned out.
Three black teenagers were main suspects.
We nearly had a race riot
in the neighborhood when the kid died.
You wanna take a look at it?
You got something new on it?
No. You get fresh eyes.
Maybe you'll see something I missed.
Any reason you're looking back now?
Today?
What am I, one of your suspects?
Well, you're avoiding my questions like one?
All right.
I can take a hint.
Be mysterious.
Cold Case 1x12
Glued
영어대본/싱크
강정아(florcita@nate.com)
한글번역
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
캐서린 모리스(릴리 러쉬 役)
대니 피노(스카티 발렌스 役)
존 핀(존 스틸만 役)
제레미 래치포드(닉 베라 役)
톰 배리(윌 제프리스 役)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2004/01/18
Tim Barnes was hit once in the face
below the right eye,
presumably knocked unconscious.
- He died of hypothermia.
- No prints, no witnesses.
The lead suspect
was a 16-year-old glue-sniffer
named Latrell Richmond.
Juvenile record of assault and burglary.
He and his pals hung out
at a corner by the store
where Tim Barnes bought that notebook.
You interview him?
That night.
So after the boy goes into the store?
I saw him leave.
Headed north on Grover.
What did you do after you saw the boy
walking north on Grover?
Nothing. Chilled.
You didn't follow him,
maybe try and rob him?
You deaf, Still-man?
I gotta repeat everything?
Anyone see you chillin'
on the corner, Latrell?
Other than your two friends?
No, it was... it was cold out.
- Nobody was out.
- What about Mr. Murphy, the store clerk?
- He see you chillin'?
- How do I know?
I stayed away from that white boy.
Cracker hates the black man,
just like the Philly PD.
We released him into
his mother's custody.
We were gonna box him in the morning,
- but he'd disappeard by then.
- How about his two friends?
They were polygraphed.
Both passed.
One is dead now, and the other's
serving time, won't talk to cops.
- Latrell's mom around?
- Yeah, she and his two sisters always
claimed they had no
idea where he went.
Let's fan out.
I'll go to the parents.
You go to the store clerk.
The clerk was the
last to see Tim alive?
Yep.
Maybe Jeffries and Vera
can pay Latrell's family a visit.
Good.
Tim loved delivering the mail
with his dad in the summer.
Your other two?
Uh, that's Tina in California.
She's a vet now, lives in Modesto.
And that's Brian, he's my youngest.
He's a law student of Syracus.
Oh, Greg, honey.
Uh, this is Detective Rush.
She's here about Tim.
What about him? / I'd like to talk to you
about the night he was killed.
Lieutenant Stillman sent me.
- He's lieutenant now, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
He was a nice man.
I told her it was okay.
I can handle it.
All right.
You wanna know what happened
that night, I'll tell you.
Once.
Hey, mom, can I go to the store
to buy a notebook for math?
- Ask your father.
- I got a dollar. I'll pay for it.
I said ask your father.
- Dad, that hurt.
- Hey, dad,
can I go to the store to buy a notebook
for math class?  / Stop it! Stop it!
Tina, your hair's gotta be washed.
Dad. / No, it doesn't.
- Dad.
- What?
Can I go to the store
to buy a notebook?
- Ask your mother.
- But she said to ask you.
Are we done, Daddy?
Stop squirming.
Forget you.
Tina, stop squirming.
You have kids...
Detective?
Because you don't know
the meaning of exhausion
until you've had a colicky newborn
on top of two others.
We were outgunned,
weren't we, honey?
Three against two.
How much time passed
before you noticed Tim was missing?
Um... two...
two and a half hours.
That's how nuts we were.
- Then what'd you do?
- We called Tim's friends.
Um, checked around the block,
and pretty soon we got scared,
so we called the cops.
By the time they found him...
Tim was frozen to death.
If we would have just
noticed him missing earlier...
It's okay, sweetie.
Like I said, once is all
I'm gonna tell that story.
Hey, hey! Hey!
Watch that.
Wilma Richmond?
Detectives Vera, Jeffries.
My daughters told me you called them.
You ain't gonna get nothing outta me
you didn't get outta my girls.
Think maybe we can
come in, Ms. Wilma?
- Yeah, we are, uh, sitting ducks out here.
- And it's cold.
Don't bother the kids none.
Besides, you got blubber on you.
We'll only be a minute.
So your daughters say
they haven't seen Latrell
since the night he disappeard in 1980.
- Ditto.
- No phone calls, letters?
What did I just say?
Besides, if I knew
where Latrell was,
which I don't,
you think I'd tell you?
Don't hear me wrong?
I feel bad for that family,
but they're not the only ones
lost a boy that night.
I lost my son the same
as they lost theirs.
So what happened that night,
after you brought Latrell home
from Homicide?
I don't like to think
about that night.
- We can understand that.
- Oh, yeah?
You lost a boy, Detective?
No, ma'am. / Then why are you
talking about understanding?
Trell was my eldest,
the man of the house,
but he was still just a boy.
We'll get us a lawyer, Trell.
You ain't gotta run.
We can't afford no lawyer.
Where are you gonna go?
Don't know, but if I stay here,
the police'll beat my ass till I confess,
pin this murder on me.
You know they will.
- You got any money?
- No.
Here.
- I'm not cleaning you out, Mom.
- Take it.
16 years old.
Can you imagine how scared he was?
Your grandkids?
From my daughters.
Thank God I at least have them.
Now if you don't mind,
why don't you go harass some
other innocent black people?
Sean Murphy.
Call me Murph-- everyone does.
You're a long way from clerking
at the five-and-dime, Murph.
That's what a little hard work can do.
So...
this is about Tim Barnes?
I understand you were the last
person to see him alive.
Aside from whoever killed him.
He bought some from your store?
A black-and-white composition book.
Was Tim a kid you knew from
the neighborhood?
He came into the store occasionally,
never had enough money.
I'd let him slide.
Felt sorry for him.
Why is that?
There were these black
kids in the area.
I think they were picking on him.
They do that a lot?
They were always hanging
around the corner, harassing people.
Mutts had the lazy gene,
if you know what I mean.
You see Tim with them mutts that night?
You bet I did.
They ever bother you?
No, they knew better.
You know this guy?
Yeah.
Yeah, he was the ringleader of those kids.
- Laquanda or something.
- Latrell.
You didn't actually see him or any of
his pals hurt the boy though, did you?
If I would have seen something,
I would have intervened.
I would have kick those...
African-American young
gentlemen's asses.
The Barnes speak highly of you.
How are they doing?
Getting by, I guess.
That kind of wound doesn't heal.
I used to call them a lot.
I stopped when I didn't have
anything new to tell them.
- You buying baby furniture?
- No, it's my daughter.
- She's pregnant.
- How far along?
A couple of months.
I just found out.
Anything from Latrell's family?
Mother and sisters are
sticking to their stories.
You think he could be dead?
I doubt it. Latrell
was a survivor of sorts.
So is that the new direction?
Hearing your daughter's pregnant?
It got me thinking
about this case, yeah,
and feeling guilty.
About what? / I was working the
Barnes job when my daughter was born.
Yeah, I missed her birth completely.
My wife, uh, wasn't pleased.
I lost my marriage over a case
I couldn't even solve.
Well, no wonder you
don't want back on it.
The sad part is, I do, though.
I want this thing solved.
I want it put to rest.
I get it.
No, you don't,
but you will one day.
Hopefully before I did.
Murphy's a piece of work;
into genetics racial superiority.
He thinks Latrell's the doer?
ID'ed him off his picture
in a second flat.
We got something.
Latrell's two sisters, Lisa and Leslie.
They got three kids apiece.
But according to Wilma Richmond,
she has seven grandkids.
Yeah, so who's lucky number seven?
Thinking maybe he's Latrell's?
We're gonna find out.
We're on the street, boss.
Us, too.
- Going to the crime scene.
- Good.
Ain't too often we got the Assigned
available to go with us. / Uh-huh
Come on, boss.
Be a big help.
I'll get my coat.
Used to be a working
class neighborhood...
half black, half white.
A lot of racial tension.
This is where Tim died.
Except he was lying in snow, not slush.
That coffee shop there
was a five-and-dime
where Tim Barnes bought his notebook.
Where Murphy worked.
In this corner right here,
this is where Latrell and
his pals were sniffing glue.
Even the church is getting a facelift.
The Barnes were Catholics, right?
Yeah, Tim was in the boys' choir.
- You talk to the priest?
- Yeah. Father Declan.
He was in the church that night,
but he didn't see or hear anything.
There wasn't a pedophilia scandal
back in 1980, was there?
No. Just pedophilia.
Oh, what, the guy's a priest,
so automatically he's a pedophile?
No, but don't we gotta look at it?
Well, he was close to the family,
both the parents and the kids.
Diocese won't disclose the priest's
whereabouts without a court order.
You got a relationship
with ADA Kite, right?
What do you mean, a relationship?
I mean, maybe you can give him a call.
He could help us, uh,
cut through the red tape.
Yeah, I... could call him.
Did a search of Latrell's
mother's phone records.
Other than her daughters,
one other name comes up consistently.
It's Candace Smith.
Who's that? / 36-year-old nurse
with a 14-year-old boy.
Wilma Richmond had a picture
of her kid in her apartment.
- Looks to be about 14.
- The seventh grandkid?
Latrell's, maybe.
With Candace.
Wilma told you to talk to me?
We're here about her son, Latrell.
Latrell?
Well, that's a name I
haven't heard in a long time.
Um...
this is a picture of him.
That there was Latrell.
A couple of names back, that is.
When I married him, he was
going by Julius Smith.
Your boy sure looks like him.
Don't remind me.
You wouldn't happen to know
where Julius is, would you?
Michael,
wanna give us some privacy?
Like I never heard you
badmouthing Julius before.
Go.
Julius Smith is a low-rent,
two-timing,
piss-poor excuse of a man.
Kicked his worthless butt
out the door six years ago.
He doesn't call,
- pay child support?
- Child support?
The day he left,
he cleaned me and Michael out.
Took his own son's GameBoy.
- He an addict?
- Addict, dealer.
Last I heard, he was hustling
out of the Badlands.
But what did he do now?
You know what? Don't tell me.
I don't want to know.
You find Julius Latrell--
whatever the hell his name is,
tell him his son's a straight-A student.
He's grown up to be a real man,
not like his lying ass.
Yes, ma'am, we most definitely will.
I went to law school with Sherman Markey,
one of the diocese's attorneys.
He spared us the rigmarole.
Your Father Declan's in a retirement home
for priests put out to pasture.
"Sacred Heart Retirement Home."
Thanks, Kite.
This priest, he a man-boy-love type?
I hope not,
but either way, I'll find out.
See ya.
See ya?
What do you want, a thank-you note?
We ever gonna talk about
that night on the street?
Talk about that night...
Hmm. Maybe when this case is over.
But then you'll be on another case.
That's true.
I tell you what.
You're the workaholic.
Call me at home.
I don't care what time.
Okay.
Maybe.
Tonight wouldn't be too soon.
- Father Declan?
- Yeah?
Valens, Rush, homicide.
Mind putting it on pause for a minute?
What can I do for you?
You remember a boy named Tim Barnes?
Of course.
Tragedy.
He was in the boys' choir at your church.
And on your baseball team...
when you were coaching.
Are you accusing me of
something, Detective?
You were transferred three
months after his murder.
At my request.
- I'm not a pedophile.
- So, why'd you decide to leave?
My white parishioners blamed the blacks.
I cautioned them against
leaping to conclusions.
My position was not popular.
You don't think the black kids
on the corner did it?
It's not for me to say.
In the case file it says you went to
the Barnes house the day of the murder.
Yes, Greg Barnes
asked me to check on Nicole.
She was having a hard time coping.
Needed...
cheering up.
Tina!
I don't know, Father,
I-I have these dreams.
What kind of dreams?
Bad ones.
You're tired.
Tired doesn't cover the half of it.
It's just... three's too many.
Tina, don't do that again!
See what I mean?
- Mom!
- Not a moment's peace.
- Tim hit me.
- Did you hit your sister?
Did you hit her?
Yeah, did you hit your sister?
- She-she made me!
- No, buts, Timothy.
I've had it up to here!
What do I have to do?
What do I have to do, huh?
- What do I have to do?
- Nicole, Nicole.
What?
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you ever tell
that to Detective Stillman?
Nicole had suffered enough.
Last thing she needed was cops
breathing down her neck.
You ever see Nicole hit Timmy?
She was high-strung, emotional.
But did you ever see her hit the boy?
Did you talk to Nicole after Tim died?
Confession is a sacrament.
Protected by both church and state law.
How about her husband Greg?
- Did he come talk to you?
- I couldn't say.
Couldn't or wouldn't?
Someone confessed to the murder,
didn't they?
That's why you left the parish.
You couldn't stand knowing one of
your parishioners got away with it.
I wouldn't say, regardless.
Even if that person
killed an 8-year-old boy?
Even if.
Father Declan knows something.
You think Tim's killer confessed to him?
We already know he was counseling
Nicole Barnes.
And it turns out she was hospitalized
twice for attempted suicides since 1980.
Her son was murdered, Lil.
It'd drive any parent over the edge.
According to Declan, she was over
the edge before Tim was killed.
You must have looked at her.
She said she never left
the house that night.
Her husband and neighbors backed her up.
I got two words for you,
boss; Andrea Yates.
From what Declan says, Nicole fits
the postpartum psychosis bill to a "T".
I'll give you this--in 1980,
that wasn't exactly on our radar.
I'm gonna talk her husband.
Don't go to her until you have to.
District cops and BD
teams in the Badlands
know of a Julius Smith, aka
Latrell Richmond, in the area.
Gave us an idea
of what block he's hustling out of.
You show his picture around?
Door slams everywhere.
Well, we gotta flush Latrell out.
Time for "No drugs today"?
Oh, I think so.
What's that?
You'll see.
Ms. Town and Country
doesn't know the pharmacy's closed.
I'll give her the heads up.
No drugs today, ma'am.
You're like a Swiss watch, Greg--
on your route just where
your boss said you'd be.
What do you want?
To talk about the night of the murder.
I've already told you,
once is all you get.
- Except you left out a couple of details.
- Like?
Like you asking Father Declan to look
in on Nicole the day of the murder.
Leave Nicole out of it.
Are you still in contact
with Father Declan?
We stopped going to
church after Tim died.
You bring Tim out on the route sometimes?
How do you know that?
Picture on the mantle,
him wearing your postal service hat,
carrying your bag.
He loved to come along...
carry the bag.
Yeah?
He was a great kid.
Were Tim and his mom close?
She loved him, same as I did.
I don't doubt that,
but sometimes people...
mothers...
they get so overwhelmed,
they do things they regret.
Well, Nicole coped the best she could.
Then why are you afraid to tell me
what happened that night?
I don't know what happened.
It was chaos, as usual...
Tim.
Timmy.
Honey.
Nicole.
Nicole!
Where the hell have you been?
- It's freezing out there.
- I don't feel it.
- I don't feel a thing.
- What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Where's Tim?
I can't find him.
What do you mean, you can't find him?
Tim!
Tim?
- Timmy!
- I'm gonna go look outside.
Greg...
What?
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
Three's too many.
Stay here.
Did you ask Nicole
what she was doing outside?
No.
And she never said.
24 years, you don't discuss it?
My wife is a good woman.
She raised the two other kids just right.
Now, if she did something awful to
Timmy that night, it wasn't her.
Do you understand?
It wasn't her.
I'm going to need to talk to your wife.
Not without me, you're not.
This ain't your corner,
and this ain't the beach, fools.
Why you acting like it is?
We're just taking in the sights,
ma'am, enjoying the city.
We gotta make a living same as you.
That's what we're counting on.
How long you gonna perpetuate
this injustice?
However long as it takes
to locate who we're looking for.
Maybe I can be of some assistance.
Maybe then you can vamoose
the hell off of my block.
We're looking for Julius Smith.
Julius?
- He ain't worth your time.
- Know where we can find him?
Can't rat out a brother,
even if he is a punk-ass.
Suit yourself.
You got any mustard?
Mustard? Hell.
No-good, mustard-eating mother...
Now we're rolling.
Yeah, she'll get Julius' name
all over the village, and quick.
It's my fault, Nicole.
I never should've opened my mouth.
No, it's okay, honey.
You're the one who's never
wanted to talk about this.
I've come to terms with what I'd done.
What was that, Nicole?
I went outside...
# God only knows #
# God makes his plan #
# The information's unavailable #
# To the mortal man #
# We work our jobs #
# Collect our pay #
# Believe we're gliding down the highway #
# When in fact we're slip slidin' away #
# Slip slidin' away #
# You know the nearer your destination #
I prayed with all my heart and soul.
For what?
For God to take away my burdens...
and He did.
He took away Timmy.
Didn't He?
Is that why you stopped
going to church, Nicole?
'Cause you made that paryer?
It's why I tried to kill myself, too.
Why would anyone wanna live in a world
where God would answer your
paryers by killing your son?
There she is.
Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- You didn't call me.
Um...
You know how it is.
Looks like I'm too
late to buy you dinner.
- I talked to that priest.
- Guess it'll have to be drinks.
- What, now?
- Yeah.
You mind? / I didn't take you
for a fast-food type, Kite.
You got me all wrong, Rush.
Let me drop these warrants
off at Fugitives, and, uh, we'll go.
You know what we need?
We need some marshmallows.
Marshmallows? Hell,
we need a bigger fire.
I'm freezing my nuts off.
Check it out.
Yo, Detectives.
Yo, man?
- You're looking for Julius, right?
- That's right.
- Got a cell?
- Number's up top.
I'll see what I can do.
You do that.
Won't be long now.
Should I, uh, go into
the high school years?
You like talking about
yourself, don't you?
Well, someone has gotta
talk about something.
- I talk plenty.
- About work. Nothing good.
What do you want, secrets?
Yeah.
Oh... you letting me in?
Come on, come on,
show me where you live.
- You like cats?
- Sure. Yeah.
Nice place.
Thanks.
Oh, dear God.
I thought you liked cats.
Cats, not... mutants.
This is Olivia,
- Uh-huh.
- and this is...
Tripod.
And you were doing so well.
W-What are you doing?
I wanna see it down.
Oh, I-I don't know about that.
Another time, okay?
Why not now?
Because you're...
because you're scaring the cats.
I think you got that
reversed, but, uh, okay.
It's a start... at least.
To what?
The adventure.
See ya.
Got the call an hour ago.
Julius is inside, probably asleep.
I'm ready.
Police!
Everybody down!
All right, police! Everybody down!
Everybody down! Now! Down!
We're upstairs!
Hey, where you going?
Come over here!
Come on, hands up!
Julius Smith. Where is he?
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
- What do you got here?
- What you doing, man?
What's that, huh?
Julius Smith.
Where is he?
Come on, lady. Those are my rocks.
Come on, please.
Julius Smith, where is he?
In the bag, over there.
Julius Smith.
Latrell?
We gotta bust a cap here,
see if he moves...
Show me your hands.
Let me see your hands!
Time's done a real number on you,
hasn't it, Latrell?
Latrell?
I don't know any Latrell.
Ah, man...
you're still around!
Where'd all your hair
disappear to, Stillman?
Same place as your teeth, Latrell.
Give us a minute, guys.
Why'd you do it, Latrell?
Why'd you kill Tim Barnes?
I didn't kill nobody.
I didn't believe you then,
and I don't believe you now.
You ruined my life,
you know that, Stillman?
The parents of that kid,
the brother and sister of that kid,
their lives were ruined.
This case took a toll on a lot of people.
- 'Cept you.
- No.
Me, too, Latrell.
That boy's death really
messed with your head,
- didn't it, Still-man?
- That boy's name was...
Tim Barnes.
You don't think I know that?
You don't think that boy's
death bothered me none?
Maybe there's a detail or two type
factoid I failed to mention way back when.
Come here, man.
Hey, you hear...?
I said come here.
Come, come here.
Where you think you goin',
little man, huh?
- Nowhere.
- Nowhere?
The store. / Yeah, you're damn
right you're goin' to the store.
- You know why?
- Leave me alone.
You gonna buy us some glue,
you hear me, Potsie?
I only have a dollar.
Well, that's your problem, okay?
'Cause you go in that cracker's
store and not bring us our glue,
you're gonna wish your
little ass was never born.
You understand?
Good.
Hey, Potsie...
don't be bringing us none of
that Elmer's glue, neither.
Model glue, you hear me?
Why the hell didn't you tell me that?
C'mon, Still-man.
Like I'm gonna tell the police
I threatened to whoop a white boy's ass
the same night that white boy gets dead?
If you didn't do it,
and you haven't said
anything yet that tells me
you didn't, then who did?
If you got any ideas, Latrell,
now is the time.
That night, when I was leaving my ma's.
I seen that cracker, Murphy,
knockin' on the church door.
One of them priests come out of the, uh...
What do you call them places
where the priests live?
- Rectory.
- Right. Rectum-ry.
Dude was wearing some funcky-ass
Phillies pajamas.
- Did Murphy go back inside with him?
- No. It got me thinking.
"Why's Murphy in need of
spiritual-type counseling?"
Think about it, Still-man.
Now, that cracker, Murphy,
he got the-the opportunity
and the motive to kill that boy.
Well, I'll give you opportunity,
Latrell, but motive?
I got it all figured out.
You kill a white boy, right?
Blame it on the black man!
What happens?
Cops come in, crime go down.
Crime go down, the real
estate prices go up.
Now, I ask you --
who stood to benefit?
The man buying up all the
real estate, am I right?
And who that?
Sean Crackerjack Murphy, that's who.
That is one hell of a theory, Latrell.
It ain't a theory.
That's a hypothesis, Stillman.
Well, now that we got motive
all squared away...
- Crazy theory.
- Hypothesis.
But Murphy going to the
priest is pretty interesting.
Yeah, in the middle of the night,
just hours after Tim Barnes died.
Someone confessed to Father Declan, Boss.
But why would Murphy kill that kid?
Ask Father Declan.
Oh, Declan hasn't broken his vow
of silence in 24 years.
He ain't gonna break it now.
Maybe he doesn't need to break it.
Maybe we just need to make
Murphy think he's broken it.
I appreciate your coming down, Father.
And I apologize for giving you
a hard time the other day.
- Don't mention it.
- Oh, here.
So... tell me your idea.
Ah, what I was thinking was this...
a baseball league for cops.
The problem is,
I don't know where to begin.
And you, you've got experience
starting up a league, right?
- Oh, that was a long time ago.
- Well, I could really use some pointers.
Okay, gimme that paper here.
That Latrell.
Ha! Must have been smokin' way too
much crack, coming up with that theory.
I know
pretty far-fetched, except you did get
rich off real estate, didn't you?
Where is he?
I-I can't wait to I.D. his worthless ass.
Where's the lineup?
Where's Latrell?
We gotta have a conversation first.
All right.
You were the detective
on that kid's case.
And you were the kind store owner
who let Tim slide
when he only had a dollar
for that notebook.
That's right.
Have a seat.
I never guessed it would be you
sitting in here.
We're exhuming Tim's body, Murph.
In 1980 we didn't have DNA testing,
but it's a whole new ball game in 2004.
You don't mind, do you?
I came here to identify
that boy's killer,
Latrell Richmond.
When's that gonna happen?
Did you see Detective Valens
out there, Murph,
taking down Father Declan's statement?
He shed a lot of light on this job.
Told us how you knocked on
the church door that night.
How he opened it in his pajamas,
let you in to confess to Tim's murder.
Well, a priest can't talk about
what he hears in confession.
That's true.
Except Declan's retired.
And bitter.
No allegiance to the church anymore,
not after all the scandals.
You... you hate little kids,
is that it, Murph?
I don't hate little kids.
Just black kids.
Tim Barnes was white, remember?
But he was a thief.
He stole glue from you
for those black kids.
That's an ungrateful mutt for you.
He betrayed you, huh?
Not just me.
Us.
Guys who work an honest day
for an honest wage.
White guys.
Thanks, mister.
Hey! Hey!
You little mutt!
- You think you can steal from me?
- They made me.
Don't lie to me, mutt.
# Genesis의 "Follow You Follow Me" #
# Stay with me, #
# My love I hope you'll always be #
# Right here by my side
if ever I needed you #
# Oh my love #
# In your arms, #
# I feel so safe and so secure #
# Everyday is such a perfect day to spend #
# Alone with you #
# I will follow you will you follow me #
# All the days and nights
that we know will be #
# I will stay with you
will you stay with me #
# Just one single tear
in each passing year #
# With the dark, #
# I see so very clearly now #
# All my fears are drifting
by me so slowly now #
# Fading away #
# I can say #
# The night is long but you are there #
# Close at hand I'm better for
the smile you give #
# And while I live #
# I will follow you will you follow me #
# All the days and nights
that we know will be #
# I will stay with you will you stay with me #
# Just one single tear in each passing
year there will be #
번역수정
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
한글교정
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)