이 이야기는 허구이며
특정 인물과 사건을 묘사하지 않습니다
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
February 3, 1990
Bless, us, oh, Load, for these thy
gifts which we are about receive
through thy bounty, through
Chirst our Load, Amen.
Amen.
Did you buy film, Mitchell?
Yeah.
We'll want lots of pictures of
Ryan tonight. / Okay, Mom.
Did you see your brother in his suit?
Yeah, he looks so
handsome. / Shut up.
Are you taking me to Cindy's?
I assume you're taking Ryan?
And no one misses
Church in the morning.
# Well I guess it would be nice #
# If I could touch your body #
# I know not everybody #
# Has got a body like you #
# But I've got to think twice #
# Before I give my heart away #
# And I know all the games you play #
# Because I play them too #
# Oh but I need some time
off from that emotion #
# Time to pick my heart up off the floor #
# And when that love comes down #
# Without devotion #
# Well it takes a strong man baby  #
Mitchell.
Mitchell? Mitchell?
Mitchell?
She ask for Homicide?
She can't ask for nothing.
She's loony tunes.
Carrying around an orbit of
a guy that died in 1990.
Covering my ass....
I called you.
Why's she locked up?
She kept wandering away.
Come on, Silvan,
get her out of there.
Son's on the way.
She had his number in her pocket.
Hi, Ma'am.
So many cuts.
So....so many cuts.
You want to come out?
Poor... Poor Mitch....
- Poor Mitch.... Mitch...
- Who's Mitch?
Couldn't have a church funeral...
not with all those cuts.
- Nuttier than a fruitcake.
- Mitch was a good man.
Was Mitch your husband?
"Mitchell Bayes served as
organist and musical director
of St. Anthony's Episcopal
church in Roxborough..."
Here's the son.
Mom, you can't do this.
You can't leave the house.
I don't think anyone's
pressing charges,
but she disturbed the peace
over at Holy Field Cemetery.
I'm sorry, I'll keep a better eye out.
Come on.
That where your dad was buried?
Yeah.
It's okay. It's okay.
She was talking about him.
He was murdered?
13 years ago.
She's been going back there a lot lately.
Doctor says it's something about
older memories becoming more present.
It's Alzheimer's?
Might wanna get her
one of those bracelets.
I ordered one.
She was carrying these.
We ever get the guy?
No.
Come on, Mom.
Come on. Let's go.
It's okay. It's okay.
Cold Case
1x04 Churchgoing People
영어대본/싱크
강정아(florcita@nate.com)
한글번역
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
캐서린 모리스(릴리 러쉬 役)
저스틴 챔버스(크리스 라싱 役)
존 핀(존 스틸만 役)
제레미 래치포드(닉 베라 役)
톰 배리(윌 제프리스 役)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2003/10/19
What's an '82 job doing next to a '96?
Civillian workers going the extra mile.
So how'd this guy die?
Stabbed by a hooker was the theory.
Here it is. Bayes, '90.
Why are we looking at this?
The lady was so distressed.
I just wondered why
we didn't bring the job in.
Mitch Bayes, 49.
Stabbed 14 times.
Wallet was gone.
Presumed robbery-homicide.
Never found a weapon?
No, they never even
named a good suspect.
Bump in the night.
Let's take this upstairs.
So is this a regular thing
now? Working cold jobs?
I am. You can stay
on the line if you want.
I guess cold cases aren't less
important than new ones.
They're more important.
They're been waiting longer.
Any limits on how far back we can look?
No limits.
There's some problems
with this job, boss.
Unsolved is always a problem, Lil.
The ME reports and the
body chart don't match.
Plus the inventory of
the clothes in the van.
Pants, underwear, shirt,
shoes... but no socks.
Uh-huh.
That was February.
You don't go anywhere
in February without socks.
Maybe they were inventoried wrong?
Whatever happened,
this case was a rush job.
The assigned chalked it up
to a solicitation gone bad.
Pretty much left it at that.
This is a nice lady, boss.
And her memory's going fast. If
we're ever going to look at this again...
We should do it now.
- Who's the assigned?
- Gil Sherman.
This was a typical job
during the crack era.
Guy comes 'round looking
for some company,
ends up robbed and killed by the girl.
Why'd you think it was a hooker?
Ever been to Kensington
Avenue, darling?
That's hookerland.
Yeah, I grew up in Kensington.
So what was he doing there,
seeing the sights?
You don't have this back wound
marked on your bodychart.
So I missed it.
You ever miss a wound?
No.
What did forensics show you?
Forensics were screwed. Rained
like a son of a bitch that night.
Whole scene got soaked.
He was in the back of a van.
They should have had some
evidence to work with.
Partial prints on vials.
Inconclusive.
So there were no suspects at all?
Plenty of suspects.
Whores, dealers, homeless.
Nothing stuck.
So that was it. End of case?
Look, Rush... these murders
were a dime a dozen that year.
crackheads thought nothing
of icing a guy for 12 bucks.
Next night the same job all over again.
You remember.
Yeah.
I felt for this family though.
They were decent people.
I had to tell 'em on a Sunday morning....
We found him in his vehicle
just off of Kensington Avenue.
I don't understand why he'd be there.
There's a lot of activity in that area.
What kind of activity?
Drugs, prostitution.
Like that.
Mitch wouldn't be
there. / I'm sorry.
No, Mitch didn't use
drugs, or prostitues.
We are churchgoing people.
I understand.
He didn't use.... prostitutes.
Bayes was a hypocrite church type.
Whoring Saturday night,
asking forgiveness on Sunday.
Son's meeting us here?
Maybe he's already here.
Yeah, I'm not sure
where they went exactly.
No, I...
I'm not sure.
I..Yes.
Okay.
I'll... I'll tell them.
When they.
Okay, I'll make sure
I tell them. / Hello.
They're home now...
Hi, Charlotte.
T-Tina.
No, no, Lily.
Remeber we talked about Mitch?
"Mitchell Bayes served as
organist and musical director
at St. Anthony's Episcopal
church in Roxborough..."
Oh. You're here.
Did Mom let you in?
The door was open, Ryan.
Was she trying to leave?
No, she was just talking to herself.
She has good days and bad days.
Can't have a church funeral
for Mitch... / Okay.
Just can't.
Why is she talking about Dad?
I brought him up.
We're looking at his case again, Ryan.
I'll do what I can to help.
I was only 16, you know.
Do you know if your dad
had any enemies?
Maybe someone
from work, or church?
No, he worked at Drexel Insurance.
I think it was pretty mundane.
At church all he had was friends.
Were you surprised to hear he
was found on Kensington Avenue?
We were all shocked by that.
Including your Mom?
I think it was the humiliation of her life.
Could we try to talk to
her about that night?
Yeah.
It'll be tricky. She kind
of goes in and out.
Mom. Mom.
We're gonna talk about dad, okay?
About the night he died.
Okay...Mitch...
He died, Mitch died...
Remember we had dinner as a family?
And I was going to a school formal,
and I was worried
because I couldn't dance.
I'll teach you.
You remember that?
Anyone can dance...
Cheers.
Okay, now let me show
you how it's dance.
Come on. Come on.
Aw, loosen up, sweetie..
I can't. I don't move right.
Sure, you do.
Come on.
Come on. Here.
My best gal.
Thanks.
Go easy on him, Charlotte.
He's got a real date tonight.
Started out as a nice night.
Who was the phone call from?
I don't remember a phone call.
Your mom does.
Huh?
Maybe she's adding
that detail in her mind.
Embellishing, you know?
To be honest, I'm still learning
about what's happening to her.
Ryan, could we get
your sister's address?
Yeah.
Diabetes don't scare you enough,
you got to add somking
to your health problem?
Thanks, Lil.
You know what? I don't
hear that enough at home.
I got that.
You're Tina, right?
Who are you?
Detective Rush and Lassing, Homicide.
We wanna talk about your dad.
No, thanks.
We know he dropped you
at a friend's house that night.
I'm not talking to any
cops. / How come?
You guys dicided a long
time ago how my dad died.
Why you got to bring it up again?
We just want to hear
about that night.
What your dad said to you?
You mean, like, did he say,
"Bye, darling, I'm going
to see my hooker"?
You think that's where he went?
I never thought that.
Tina, we're looking for answers here.
You can't give us five minutes?
Your mom and brother helped us.
They'd like you to do the same.
I haven't talked to my mom
or brother in eight years.
So I could really care
less what they'd like.
He was parked here.
Found at 5:00 A.M. by a homeless
guy looking for someplace to sleep.
So you're calling this a crime scene?
This is where it happened.
Rush, that was 13 years ago.
We ain't got much to work
with, Lil. / It's what we got.
You're standing next to the
best scene man I know,
but I don't think there's
blood in that stone.
Take a picture.
Gotta go find the girls that Sherman
talked about Mitch Bayes.
Hey, girls.
You know this guy?
Naw.
Uh-uh.
Sure, you don't.
probably playing hopscotch in 1990.
Any girls out here with some age on 'em?
Delores, Rhona, Rhono, Mary?
Delores....
She's, like, 33.
That is old.
You know where we can find her?
Works the alley.
She only do oral now.
'Cause of HIV.
Thanks.
She's got HIV or she
doesn't want to get it?
I don't need to know.
Delores?
Yeah,Yeah. That's me.
Remember this guy, Delores?
Mitch Bayes?
Yeah. Yeah, that guy died down
there behind the Dumpster.
Is he a trick of yours?
No, I've never seen him
before. Nobody had.
Know where I can find
a Rhona or Mary?
Rhona moved back to Delaware,
to her Mom's where her kids are at.
Mary got the AIDS.
She died, like, a year ago.
Yeah.
That looks kind of funny, you know?
Funny how?
I never seen a guy take all
his clothes off for a girl
and leave 'em in the
corner all tidy like that?
Right.
Thanks, Delores.
Take care of yourself.
She's right.
The scene's off.
There are a lot of props:
the crack vials, the magazines.
It's all wrong.
Mitch Bayes didn't hang out here.
We gotta redeem this guy.
Henry Walsh, his name's on
one of these porn rags
that was found in the van.
He's not in your file.
Do you know who he is?
Great, Sherman. Got to run.
A simple yes or no
don't work for Sherman.
I take it he didn't auto-track Walsh.
Probably too busy will
all the crack going on.
- You guys again?
- You were right, Tina.
About what?
Your dad didn't go with
a hooker that night.
How do you know?
We think someone drove him
to that ally after they killed him.
- That cop told us...
- That cop was wrong.
I knew it.
I knew my dad was too good for that.
You were close, huh?
Yeah.
We're looking for the truth here, Tina.
Can you help us and talk to us?
About what?
Start with the night he died.
Was there a phone call?
Nice families don't talk
about these things.
Tina, what things?
What was the phone call?
It was for him.
Do you know who it was?
I had an idea.
I know where you're going now.
I'm going home.
No, you're not.
What are you talking about?
Don't go.
Call her and say no.
T-Tina!
Go on in the house. I can
see Cindy's waiting for you.
You're always talking about
what's a sin and all that.
This is a sin, dad,
what you're doing with Judy.
You get out of this car.
That was our last conversation.
Who was Judy?
I don't know.
I just heard him talking
on the phone to her.
After he died, I thought
maybe it was a prostitute that....
Do you think your mom
knew about Judy?
I wouldn't know that.
Maybe you should go
with us to see your mom.
Ask her about this woman?
Why don't you ask her?
Your probably would have a better chance
of getting through with her condition.
What condition?
Your brother says it's Alzheimer's.
You're probably going to have
to help the conversation along.
Don't worry.
The door's open again.
Mom?
Oh, God...Mom.
It's Tina.
Ba-ba.
Mom?
We'll give you a minute, Tina.
All these locks...
what's that about?
I wish you would comb your hair.
She knows me now.
Can we talk to her?
Mom, we want to talk about Judy.
Judy...
Yeah.
Judy and Dad.
Judy...
I never,
never cared for Judy.
I never cared for Judy.
Judy.
Who was she, Charlotte?
How did you know her?
Judy Enright.
I never cared for Judy Enright.
Charlotte, it's okay.
It's okay.
What's going on here?
Never cared for Judy...
What are you doing here?
I just... I thought I'd come...
What?
I don't know.
We asked her to come.
Well, I'm asking you to leave.
They believed me about dad, Ryan.
Good for you.
Congratulations.
I really do want to help you,
but I'm not coming back here.
She always, always has the solos.
She always...
She always has the solos.
You shouldn't have come here.
- Strangers upset her.
- We thought with Tina....
- You thought wrong.
- The most talented singer...
She was talking to us about Judy.
That name mean anything to you?
No. Look, you should know my
sister has emotional problems.
She's been hospitalized a few times
and sometimes she says things
that aren't necessarily true.
You should know your front
door was open again, Ryan.
Tina says your dad was
close to this woman.
And I told you that she
has mental problems.
Excuse me.
Come in.
Something going on
with this family, boss.
The brother and sister
hate each other.
She says they've been oil and
water ever since dad died..
He says it's because she's crazy.
Plus that door upstairs.
Do you, uh, trust this Tina?
She seems more sad than crazy.
She was hospitalized
twice for depression,
but that doesn't make her a liar.
So, follow her leads,
see where it takes you.
Where do you find Judy Enlight?
She works at St. Anthony's
Church in Roxborough.
You better wash up.
Poor Mitch.
It was such a disgrace....
how he ended up.
The flesh is weak.
Yes, it is.
How well did you know Mitch?
Well, the congregation
here is very tightknit.
Plus, him on the organ
and you singing solos...
Did you see Mitch the night he died?
Unless we had a rehearsal,
I don't see how...
Judy, I have phone records
that show me two calls
were made from your home
to the Bayes' home that night.
Well, I suppose you already know, then.
I was weak, too.
So did you meet Mitch
the night he died?
Just for a few minutes.
Hi, why don't you park?
I can't do it anymore.
What?
Tina knows.
I can't my daughter
being ashamed of me.
Mitch, come on, honey.
We'll talk about it.
I gotta stop.
She's my daughter.
And that's the last
I saw of Mitch Bayes.
Are you sure you didn't
follow him, Judy,
in your anger at him,
for breaking it off like that?
No.
But you called Mitch again later.
There were two calls from
your house that night, Judy.
I didn't call again.
Could your husband have called him?
He'd have no rason, too.
Unless he suspected you two.
So did Lassing embarrass you in church?
No, he behaved. And we
met Mitch's girlfriend.
Oh, yeah?
She's a suspect?
Her alibi's good, but there
was a jealous husband.
Vera and Jeffries are
checking him out.
Mitch's clothes from
the van... no socks.
Is this criminalist screwing up,
or were they never
there in the first place?
You might want to ask
your pal Sherman over there.
People steal stuff off the
dead bodies all the time.
People steal Timberlands,
leather jackets.
They don't steal a guy's
socks and nothing else.
Fine. You know best, apparently.
Sherman, it's a simple question.
Were the socks at the scene or not?
No.
Are you sure?
I'm pretty sure.
You're known as a
good detective, Sherman.
They say you're the best in Fugitives.
Is that what they say?
So what was going on in 1999 that
you were doing work like a bum?
Nothing that ain't fixed now.
1988 to mid '94....
I was a drunk.
I mean bombed full-time.
So probably I did some damage,
being sloppy.
Just.... wasn't in my head.
Uh-huh.
You know that, uh, name you
wanted followed up, Henry Walsh?
The guy whose porn rags
were found in the van?
Did you auto-track him yet?
Uh, not yet.
Good. 'Cause I did.
Figured I'd save you some time.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Let's see, he had a carpet
business in Germantown.
He died three years ago,
but I got an address
on the son, Tom Walsh,
if that'll help.
It would.
I don't know who my dad knew or didn't.
Pretty strange how his porn rags
ended up in a van with a dead man.
What am I supposed to do about that?
How about giving it more
than 30 seconds of thought?
Bayes... I knew a Ryan
Bayes in high school.
There you go, Tom.
Were you good friends?
I guess.
We played a lot of Dungeons
and Dragons together.
Just nerds, you know.
Nerds who looked
at dad's porn together?
I probably took some
magazines there sometimes.
You guys ever take
it to another level,
like, uh, going to hookers?
Do we really got to go into this?
I've heard so much worse, Tom.
I guess we cruised for
prostitute once in a while,
just look at them. We'd be terrified
if they actually talked to us.
Where'd you do that cruising?
Kensington Avenue.
You see, Tom,
that's helpful to me.
Embarrasing to you,
but helpful to me.
Ring, ring.
I'll get it, Mom. / Ringing.
- Now is not a good time.
- We had to talk, Ryan.
Not now. / It's very important.
Mom, go back to the living room.
Someone's here.
- Someone's here.
- Did you hear me?
- Go back to the living room.
- Tea, tea, tea.
Ryan, hey, let's you
and me sit down.
Come on. You need a minute of
peace. Las will sit with your mom.
Come on, take a break.
Isn't there someone
that can help you out?
A girlfriend?
I don't have time for that.
We guess your mom's kind
of your girlfriend, huh?
She takes a lot of my time,
if that's what you mean.
Yeah.
I take care of my mom, too.
She sick in a different
kind of way, but, uh,
it makes me half crazy sometimes.
Yeah.
Doesn't feel natural.
It's role reversal.
Yeah, I mean, Mom's
supposed to take care of you.
That's what you're
used to. / Yeah.
Did she take good care of you?
Yeah, sure.
She let you meet girls?
Or did she keep you in
so you had to look elsewhere
for those interests?
I'm not sure I know
what you're talking about.
I guess I mean these.
Those aren't mine.
Technically they belong
to your friend Tom Walsh.
Do you remember him?
Uh-uh.
No? He's the guy you used to
cruise Kensington Avenue with.
I don't wanna talk about this anymore.
Thing is, I need explanations
for all these lies.
Because it looks bad that you lied
about the phone call from
Judy Enright that night.
And that you lied to me just now
about these periodicals here,
Ryan. / I want you to leave.
And it really looks bad that you were
so familiar with the strip
where your dad was dumped.
I got questions that need
answers here, Ryan.
And without good answers,
you're my number-one suspect.
My mom and I are not
talking to you anymore.
You speak for your mom?
Yeah, I do.
And you know what?
We want you to drop my dad's case.
When I'm so close to
the truth? Not a chance.
Well, that was one hot trail
you set us down, Rush.
You met Enright?
You call that guy a suspect?
He's a 90-pound invalid.
He's been in a wheelchair
since the Great Flood.
No chance he stabbed
anybody in the last century.
Okay, but was he our
second called that night?
Called Mitch to give him
a piece of his mind
Talked to the boy instead. / Ryan.
Yeah, I mean, he probably
traumatized that kid.
Must have told him 40 times
what a cheating sinner
his old man was.
Gives Mama's boy his motive.
Tina...
thanks for coming.
Did you find out anything?
Yeah.
Listen, Tina....
We think we can put Ryan
at the murder scene.
Ryan?
Yeah.
This is how you help me...
"Your dad wasn't scumbag after all,
but your brother's a murderer?"
I'm sorry.
We used to be really close,
me and my brother.
Do you think you could
help us one more time?
Can you do it for your dad?
A...a dance.
We really have to go
to church tomorrow.
There was a...sleep...
sleep... sleepover....
and a dance,
and that.... that's where
the kid's were going...
Kids were going...
sleepover...
That-that was a big... dance...
I know that part, Charolette.
I'm talking about later.
I-I-I... I danced,
I danced with Ryan.
After the dancing, much later.
Did Ryan fight with Mitch?
Poor Mitch.
Poor, poor, poor, poor Mitch.
After the dancing, did Ryan
do something to him?
Mitch...Mitch..
- Charolette.
- Mitch, Mitch base...
Mitch took-took you...
Mitch took you..
Mitch took you..to..
you s... your sleepover... Mitch...
He took me to the sleepover?
Mitch took you,
Mitch took you...
Tin-Tina?
Tina... / It's okay to tell me, Mom.
What did Ryan do?
Mom.. What happened?
Clothes...
Clothes? Dad's clothes?
Ge-Get thos.... get those...
get tho... get those...
Get that!
Put it in! put it in!
Yes, put the clothes... I'll
I'll fo...
I'll follow..
I'll follow.
Wait!
Get that! Get that!
Get that!
Get that over there.
over there!
Get that over there!
Get those vials!
Yes!
Yes, hurry!
Put the...put them in?
Yes.
Yes! Hurry!
Hurry!
Okay, Charlotte.
Okay.
You've totally disrupetd my family.
No, that was you, Ryan.
You and your mom, 13 years ago.
We heard all about you staging the scene.
When you weren't there to charperone,
your mom gave us details.
You took advantage of
a sick, old woman?
But you forgot the socks.
Nice touch with the crack vials,
though... real respectful to dad.
I respected my dad.
Really? / I respected
my mom, too.
What was I supposed to do?
You trying to blame Mom?
Mom who treated you
like you walked on water?
I never asked fot that.
I didn't want to be her pet.
She chose me.
I couldn't shake her.
Like you can't shake her now.
You dreamed of being an adult, right?
- Finally escaping her?
- But then Mom got sick.
And now you're trapped again.
You have no idea
how much she needs.
I know, Ryan.
That's why you leave
the front door open.
Maybe she'll wander away for good,
and then you'll be free.
I love my mom.
But you're angry at her
for what she made you do:
commiting murder in her name.
I didn't do that.
Come on, Ryan, you're
a classic mama's boy.
What better way to protect your mom
than to kill the guy
who's done her wrong?
My mom didn't need
protecting from anyone.
What's that supposed to mean?
You only know her
as this feeble woman
who gets confused and scared,
and you probably feel bad for her.
But you didn't see her in her prime...
when she terrorized us.
We weren't supposed to talk about it.
Nice family keeping up appearances.
She would bitch me
and Tina out all the time.
When it got really bad...
when she was good
and drunk and crazy...
she would attack my dad.
Hit him?
He never hit her back.
He would just take it.
and get away as soon as possible.
Is that why he had all those
locks on his bedroom door?
He couldn't sleep if he
didn't lock himself in at night.
That's how scared he was of her.
And still he stood up
for me that night.
Knowing what she could do to him.
Why are you home, Ryan?
Why aren't you at the dance?
Mom didn't want me to go.
We had an interesting call tonight.
He had a date, Charlotte.
Well, apparently,
you both had dates.
All right, get your jacket. I'll
take you to the dance myself.
No, he's staying with me.
Look, he's 16 years old, Charlotte.
He doesn't want to sit home on
a Saturday night with his mother.
Yes, he does!
Yes, he does.
Unlike you, who would rather
be sneaking around with Judy.
Don't do this in front of Ryan.
Ryan? Ryan took the call!
This between you and me,
and I'm going to take
him over to the dance
and when I come back,
we can talk about it.
He's staying with me!
He loves me.
Don't you, Ryan?
I do.
But I want to go to the dance.
What?
The both of you teaming up against me?
- Ryan, get your jacket now.
- Wha... Ryan....
I'm not going to talk to you
when you're like this, Charlott.
Do you understand that?
Now I'm going to go upstairs and
I'm going to get some dry clothes.
Mitchell... Mitchell!
Ryan!
Mi...
Ryan...
- Mitchell!
- Mom,
- Mitchell! No!
- mom....
No!
Judy Enright is cheap Christmas trash!
She's a disgrace and you're a
disgrace to good churchgoing people!
Do not shut me out!
Don't ....you...
Don't you shut me out! / Mom!
Do not shut me out!
You will not disgrace me!
Don't you shut me out!
No!
Ryan...
Get the van.
# Madonna의 "Live To Tell" #
# I have a tale to tell #
# Sometimes it gets
so hard to hide it well #
# I was not ready for the fall #
# Too blind to see
the writing on the wall #
# A man can tell a thousand lies #
# I've learned my lesson well #
# Hope I live to tell #
# The secret I have
learned, 'till then #
# It will burn inside of me #
# The truth is never far behind #
# You kept it hidden well #
# If I live to tell #
# The secret I knew then #
# Will I ever have the chance again #
번역수정
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
한글교정
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)