이 이야기는 허구이며
특정 인물과 사건을 묘사하지 않습니다
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
June 8, 1997
What do you say, Dorothy,
should I double down?
You're showing a four,
the book says no, but hey...
you're hot.
Me or the cards?
Both.
Good luck.
# And teach the world
to sing in perfect harmony #
to snuff the fires and the liars #
# Hey I know it's just a song #
# but it's spice for the recipe #
# This is a love attack .... #
Nice playing!
# It's just like any fad
it retracts before impact #
# And just like fashion.... #
Nice flirting with you, Dorothy.
You should never quit
after a win.
I got a feeling my luck's
running out.
# So don't delay act #
# now supplies are running out #
# Allow if you're still alive
six to eight years to arrive #
# And if you follow
there may be a tomorrow #
# But if the offer is shun #
# you might as well be
walkin' on the sun #
You waste your money
on the daily numbers?
- Every morning.
- Five bucks down the drain.
I don't got dependents.
I can afford it.
- So if you won big, you'd retire?
- Nah. I'd stay doing what I do.
I'd just dress sharper...
if that's possible...
- and brag a lot more.
- If that's possible.
Lil, you want to take a look at this?
What is it?
Regional broadcast
from Delaware State Police.
They just got a murder similar to
a cold job in Jersey.
Young white male,
walked into the woods,
shot once in the chest.
Both were hitchhikers.
- Motive?
- Straight robbery.
Bullet in both cases was .38 caliber.
"Requesting information on
any like murders,
solved or unsolved, in the region."
What, they think they got
a serial murder?
- Sounds like it.
- Nice. I'll check the H-records.
We had a job like that.
Yeah, a kid hitchhiking.
Five, six years ago.
Danny Saltzman's job.
Saltzman. Right.
What do you remember about it?
It was in the Summer.
And just like you said,
in the forest, hitchhiker, .38 slug.
Remember his name?
I should remember.
Saltzy brayed on and on about that kid.
There wasn't much on it,
some footprints, fiber.
Yeah, he just turned 20,
uh... "Gone good."
Saltzman was always saying.
"Crummy kid gone good", over and over.
He was a good-looking kid.
Saltzman had his picture taped up
on the wall.
Damn, this name thing's gonna bug me.
You ever establish who the kid
caught a ride with?
Nah, case went cold fast.
Dean... I think his name was Dean.
No, it wasn't Dean.
- Darren... Darren something.
- No.
Matt.
- What?
- Mills. Matt Mills.
Right. That's it.
Yeah. Almost had it.
Cold Case 1x10
The Hitchhiker
영어대본/싱크
강정아(florcita@nate.com)
한글번역
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
캐서린 모리스(릴리 러쉬 役)
대니 피노(스카티 발렌스 役)
존 핀(존 스틸만 役)
제레미 래치포드(닉 베라 役)
톰 배리(윌 제프리스 役)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2003/12/21
Matt Mills, 20,
shot in the woods off the Expressway.
The 3,000 bucks he'd just won
in Atlantic City, gone.
Like the other two jobs.
I talked to Jersey and Delaware,
both are thinking it's the same doer.
Serial killer.
Our guy Matt could've been his first.
Well, Matt's killed in '97.
Jersey's body turns up fall of 2000.
And Delaware's just four weeks ago.
A three-year cooling off period.
I say we go right now.
To Delaware.
No need.
Delaware's coming here.
Don't get too excited, Scotty.
A serial job don't get you
hopped up just a little, boss?
What else do we know
about the victims, Lil?
All young guys, 18 to 20.
All three were headed home
from Atlantic City
after winning a few thousand
in the casinos.
So the doer hangs around the tables,
stalks the winners,
catches up to them
on the lonely road home.
These kids are leaving
with thousands of bucks.
Why are they hitchhiking?
File says Matt missed his bus back.
I could win ten grand over there,
I still ain't paying a cabbie
300 bucks to drive me home.
Now, you put it that way,
I guess my tumb's out too.
Besides the robbery and the .38,
we got a size ten print that
lines up with other murders.
Plus the gray carpet fiber
on the body.
Delaware and Jersey
have a list of seven suspects
that could've done both jobs.
Add in this murder,
maybe we narrow it down even more.
Vera and Jeffries can check
the list, see if anyone
had ties to Philly in '97.
Hmm. / What?
When Matt was 17,
he got locked up by
my Sergeant at West Detectives.
For what?
Him and his cousin robbed
a food mart. Got probation.
I'll put a call in,
see if he remembers Matt.
Good.
Better get to the family, Lil.
Let them know what's going on.
Hello.
What's your name?
Katie.
- I'm Detective Rush.
- Detective Valens.
Are your parents home?
Is it about Matt?
How'd you know?
Whenever it's cops,
it's about Matt.
So Matt was in Atlantic City
visiting his cousin
Blaine that weekend?
Matt hadn't seen Blaine
for a long time,
he wanted to go whoop it up with him.
Yeah, he'd earned it.
How so?
He was working for a brokerage house.
An entry level position,
but a good start.
He'd gotten into computers,
that investment world.
It was impressive.
During the days,
he was hustling at his jobs,
nights he was over at Drexel
taking classes.
Folks he worked for liked him,
but Matt knew he needed his B.A.
Sounds like your son really stepped up.
After that trouble he
and Blaine got into.
A footnote in our file mentions
the food mart robbery.
It wasn't a footnote to us.
Matt had some... very bad years.
First, he was stealing
money off my dresser,
then breaking into the neighbor's house.
I'm glad he robbed that store.
He became a different
person after that.
Scared straight.
No.
That didn't straighten him out.
He straightened himself out.
There's a difference.
That kid...
He had what it takes.
He had it.
Well, the next three years,
Matt was the boy we'd always
dreamed we'd have.
And what about Blaine?
Blaine's still over in Atlantic City.
You the guys from Philly?
Blaine Robbins.
Detectives Rush and Valens.
Hey.
Gotta admit, um...
I'm not that glad to see you guys.
Dragging up Matty's ghost
has me feeling kind of funky.
- Don't you want his murder solved?
- Definitely.
Look, he missed his bus.
I told him stay, but
he had to be at work.
I would've given him a
ride myself, but no wheels.
Well, you remember anyone watching Matt
that night, haning around him?
Well, I wasn't with him at the time,
but Matt is a... was....
a real approachable guy.
Let's talk about that robbery
you and Matt did.
Those were our bad years.
We were kids.
Kids who needed a thousand bucks.
A thousand bucks for what?
Start a vending machine business.
What, like a Coke machine?
Candy bars.
There was a machine for sale
for $1,000.
And the idea was,
after we stocked it,
Matt and I could clear $300
a week!
Young guys, thinking big.
Yeah... Yeah.
Anything else about that night?
No, I...
I was kind of hammered.
Been celerbrating all night.
Celebrating what?
Matty had become a real entrepreneur.
This rockin' investment opportunity
had just come our way...
So this Click Twice
stock is a sure thing?
For us to get in on an IPO,
the broker would be doing us
a major favor.
And that would get us in
on the ground floor,
right where you wanna be.
The stock'll shoot right up,
that's why everyone wants in.
But then it'll re-set,
find its real value.
But, by that time,
you and me have already cashed out.
Millionaires by age 25.
We would've made out like bandits.
But...
without Matty, the deal...
went up in smoke.
How's our list doing?
Getting shorter.
Two guys were in jail in '97,
three others have good,
substantiated whereabouts
at the time of Matt's murder.
So that leaves two.
One.
Oh. Meet Sam Royal,
Delaware State Police.
- How's it going?
- Okay.
Down to one, huh? / Yeah.
My suspect number
two was in a hospital
in Bridgeport having dialysis
the night Matt was killed.
So who's that leave?
Henry Floyd.
Truck dirver with a three-page sheet.
He's a convicted thief,
con artist, attempted rapist...
- overall menace to society.
- Sounds like you know him pretty good.
Yeah. I interviewed him.
He's got ice water in his veins.
And a size ten shoe.
Guns?
Got three registered hand guns,
including a .38 Smith and Wesson.
Oh, and, uh... Mac
withdrawls puts Floyd
in the AC casinos the night
before each of the murders.
Gas receipts also put him
near the crime scenes.
I'm liking Floyd more and more.
Oh, when I asked him about these kids,
the cocky S.O.B. smiles at me
and tells me
he never picks up hitchhikers.
What was cocky about that?
I never mentioned hitchhikers.
I wanna meet this guy.
I got copies of his logs,
he's due back tomorrow.
Where's he stay in Philly?
Uh, he's got ties
to a woman out in Bristol.
- What's the tie?
- Girlfriend.
Name's Janice Burns.
Yep...
I'm the girlfriend.
- That always sounds so silly.
- Why is that?
I look like a girly-girl to you,
Hot Stuff?
Besides, um... I wouldn't exactly...
consider what we got
a traditional situation.
What do you have?
Henry comes here for one thing.
Two, if he decides to stay
and eat up all my food.
That doesn't sound like
you get much out of this.
Why you let him in?
Because if I don't,
he'll get his tool box
and he'll take the door off the hinges.
He's done it before.
Who knew you'd be better off
leaving your door unlocked.
Janice, you never called
the police, filed charges?
- Nope.
- Why not?
I know what he'd do to me.
Look, I made my bed.
The only reason I met Henry
was I was at the truck stops
looking for dates.
And now that animal's been
in my life for ten years.
I knew what I was doing was risky.
So, tomorrow is just another day?
What's tomorrow?
Henry's coming to town.
I didn't know that.
He hasn't called you?
Like I said, I leave the door open.
Damn it.
Ah, don't worry about it.
Janice, you say Henry's been trampling
in and out of here the last ten years?
That's right.
And how long have you had this gray carpet?
Hey, lab going to do a rush job
on that fiber?
We'll have the results
by the end of the day.
You check on Floyd?
On schedule. Should arrive
at Muncy's Meats by noon.
It'll take him at least another
40 minutes to get out to Janice's.
- We'll go early and wait for him.
- Royal's already on his way over.
He's got it bad for this guy?
Got a few hours.
Wanna take a ride, see my old Sergeant.
He called back.
He remembers the arrest?
Just says he's in the office.
We should swing by.
Scotty Valens.
How's Homicide treating you?
Ain't all bad.
How's things here?
Good and quiet with you gone.
Manny, this is
my new partner, Lilly Rush.
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
Here's that DC number on that
arrest I was talking about.
Two kids robbing a food mart, right?
Yeah.
Let me grab the 49...
Cousins.
One of the kids, Matt Mills,
ended up dead.
Matt was younger of the two.
Him mom said getting locked up
scared Matt pretty good.
I don't know if it was so much
about being locked up
as it was that Russian
reading him the riot act.
The Russian is the store owner?
Yeah. Ivan Medvedenko.
Made a scene out here
you wouldn't forget too easy.
so I took the phone, dialed 911.
I should've ran after them.
No, calling was the right thing.
That is one, right there.
You!
You stole from me!
Shame on you.
Your dirty hands.
Lazy, American boy.
Calm down, Ivan.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
Too late.
Too late for what?
Change.
You'll always be spoiled.
Die!
Just, die.
A boy like you no one will miss.
Johnny, take this man downstairs.
Russian tells Matt to die.
Anything behind those words?
First detectives on that kid's
murder came asking the same,
but Medvedenko had no record.
Wonder if Matt and Blaine
ever want back to his store.
If they were dumb enough to do that,
then I'd say all bets were off.
Sorry.
Rush.
- Working with a girl, huh.
- Yeah.
She a political case?
Nah, she came from North.
Did real good there.
Floyd just got to town.
Gotta go. Thanks, Manny.
Henry Floyd?
Yeah.
Philadelphia Police.
Sit down, Henry.
Get you some coffee?
Sure you can't offer me more
than that, sweet tits?
Oh... you and me are gonna
some problems, Henry.
It's okay, Scotty.
You wanna do me, huh?
I'm not sure yet.
Twirl around once.
Scotty, give me and Henry
some private time.
You've been naughty, Henry.
Three murders along your truck route.
So?
We've been charting where you've been
and what you've done,
and not just us.
Jersey and Delaware cops are
on your ass, too.
Am I under arrest?
No.
You're free to go.
Want to?
No, I'm enjoying myself.
We have copies of your trucking logs,
credit card receipts,
day-to-day map of your whereabouts.
Dolly, none of that means
nothing and you know it.
Actually, one good piece of
physical evidence
can mean everything.
And we have fibers, Floyd.
from Janice's carpet.
Oh, you've seen Janice?
So you know what an upgrade you'd be.
Three murder trials in three states.
Anyway you look at it,
you'll get the needle.
Matt Mills.
You ended his life for $3,000.
- You ever think on that?
- I don't get your meaning.
Well, what's the lowest you'd
end someone's life for?
2,000, 1,000...
a Swiss Army Knife?
Dolly, you and me...
we don't see the world the same way.
Oh, you're a Philosopher.
So that gives you the right
to take someone's life away?
You're putting words in my mouth.
I didn't kill him, didn't kill anyone.
Then take a polygraph for me.
Okay.
Did you murder Matt Mills?
No.
Did you kill Chuck Praska?
Chuck get iced in Jersey or Delaware?
Yes or no answers, Floyd.
Roger that.
Did you murder Chuck Praska?
No.
Did you murder Brian Fritz?
The next question
I want you to answer incorrectly.
The purpose is to intentionally
make the chart spike.
Is this card the ace of spades?
Yes.
He never spiked.
not even when he lied about the card.
He beat the polygraph.
But good.
You know, you never should have
gone to see Janice.
Now s perfectly good ten-year
relationship will have to end.
You gonna kill her, too, Henry?
Like those three kids?
You're putting words
in my mouth again.
What?
What are you looking at?
A dead man.
And get those feet off my table.
The ball on Floyd's left
boot is severely worn down,
probably from pressing down
on the clutch when he's in his rig.
First time around,
criminalistics looked at
the brand, size, and tread.
Maybe they never looked at
the ball of the foot.
So let's pull the molds from evidence,
re-submit them to the lab.
You wanna that Jersey know?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- See you.
Yeah.
Lot of wear and tear
on Floyd's left hoof.
If the plaster molds
match, we got him.
Good. 'Cause the fiber match
didn't happen.
- Crap.
- Inconclusive.
But I got something else.
Yeah, what?
Manny called back.
He ran that store owner
through the computer again.
Starting '99, he does have a sheet.
For what?
Arrested for assaulting one of
his customers.
Then five months ago...
chased a shoplifter with a revolver.
Fired six shots.
What kind of revolver?
.38 Special.
Just like the one that killed Matt.
Better go have a conversation.
Philadelphia Homicide.
We wanna ask you some question.
I haven't done anything.
We're investigating the murder
of a young man you had history with.
Recognize him?
You know who that boy is, don't you?
He robbed me.
Him and the other.
Held you at gunpoint, right?
Like animals.
Thanks.
Hey.
What are you doing there?
Sorry, pops.
Hey!
Get away.
If you don't get away,
I'll call the police.
Get away, I said!
Hey!
Thief!
- Don't move!
- Thief!
Don't move! Don't move!
Matty, hurry!
Don't move!
You shouldn't have chased me out.
Why you gotta make things complicated?
Matty, hurry!
Let's go!
They never saw Pejia,
my son,
and for that... I am thankful.
But you must've held a grudge.
What's your meaning?
Those boys got arrested
but only got probation.
- Did that get you mad, Ivan?
- They should've gone to jail.
And since they didn't, maybe you
decided to do something about it.
Aah, three years later?
You remember how many years later
Matt got killed?
You heard that kid got murdered, huh?
Yeah. Everyone talked about it.
You recall where you
were the day he died?
- Here. Working, like always.
- Can you prove it?
I leave people alone.
I've never hurt anyone.
Oh, you leave people alone
outside of when you shoot your gun
off at them, is that it?
I don't have a gun.
Medvedenko, we're cops.
We know about you firing shots
at the shoplifter.
The neighbors told police
you had a .38 Special.
No gun was found. Go on, check.
That's 'cause you got rid of it.
Please, leave my store.
You wanna tell us about
the gun, otherwise
you look suspicious, Ivan.
I sold it.
To who? / Back to whom
I bought if from Mr. Joey.
Mr. Joey?
You saying Joey's, his last name?
I don't know.
He just has hot guns.
At his pawn store.
You'll never find it.
I wanna find Mr.Joey.
Follow that gun.
- Molds came back.
- The ball on the left foot?
Worn down.
Perfect match...
for Jersey and Delaware.
What about our job?
So, Floyd didn't kill Matt.
But it absolutely puts him away
for the other two hitchhiker jobs,
and, uh, honest,
I can't thank you enough.
Yeah.
Anytime.
Floyd'll go down to holding
until Jersey can get here.
You can fight over him down there.
Thanks, Philly.
I couldn't have done it without you.
So, you just solved two murders.
- That's pretty decent.
- We didn't solve our murder.
Matt's our job.
Lil...
Matt's sister.
Hi, Katie.
Hi. Is it okay I'm here?
- Sure. Your parents with you?
- No. I got the address off your card.
Uh, I'm gonna go find Mr. Joey.
What can I do for you?
I wanted to know about Matty.
'Cause no one tells me,
and... I mean, I miss him, too.
What do you wanna know?
Do you know who killed him?
Not yet.
Blaine said a serial killer.
You're close to Blaine, huh?
He tells me things,
not like my parents.
Well, your parents probably
just wanna keep you young,
Katie, as long as possible.
Matt treated me like a grown-up.
Blaine's just like him.
Real nice,
really, really smart.
Smart, huh? / He knows how
to do all kinds of stuff.
He can fly a plane.
- Blaine's a pilot?
- He has his license.
And later this year,
he's starting a restaurant.
Really.
Well, a nightclub kind of place.
I got some seed money
saved up to invest.
Sounds like you got business
in your blood, Katie.
Like Matty did.
He called me that night.
Matt did?
Before he died.
I'm coming home tomorrow, okay?
You made a lot of money?
Yup.
So you'll buy me something?
- I already did.
- What?
Sand dollars.
What else did you do there?
I ran into somebody I knew.
Sort of got into a fight with him.
It brought up some bad feelings.
Matty?
Yeah?
Besides the sand dollars,
could you bring taffy, too?
Sure. Taffy, too.
I was only ten.
I didn't think about what he said.
I understand.
But now I'm thinking that maybe
it mattered that he ran into someone.
It might.
Thanks for telling me now.
He first came by after
them two kids robbed him.
Said he had to have a gun.
You gave him the .38.
Then all was quiet for, like, years
till he ran wild on that shoplifter.
After that craziness, he came back,
wanting to move that gun real quick.
I need to get that gun, Jeoy.
Where is it now?
I only had it another week.
It went back out hot?
Nah. I'm riding on the boulevard,
minding my own business.
These bozos on patrol pulled me over.
I wonder why.
The bastard said I ran a light.
Next thing you know,
they're confiscating
that .38 out of my glove box,
and I'm on my way back to court.
What did the Judge say?
Ordered that gun destroyed.
Wasn't such a loss.
I might've had a body on it anyway.
How well you know this Ivan Medvedenko?
Well enough to stay out of his way.
What's his deal?
When he first came to the neighborhood,
he was actually kind of nice.
Had this idea America was gonna
treat him and his kid right.
Didn't work out that way?
He hated all them lowlifes
hanging around,
homeless trying to get
free stuff from him.
When he came asking for that gun,
talking about lazy
kids needing a lesson,
he had some... glint in his eye.
Kind of scared me.
- Morning.
- Hi.
Over losing Floyd?
- All about Medvedenko now.
- What changed?
I've been trying to connect Medvedenko
to Atlantic City the weekend
Matt was killed.
And?
Guess who won a Center City Bank
sweepstakes, June of '97?
- Medvedenko.
- His wife.
Prize was a free gambling
junket in Atlantic City,
trip for two.
Medvedenko said he was working.
- Guess he wasn't working.
- Oh, it's gonna be a good day for us.
Bad one for Medvedenko.
You lied to me, Ivan.
I had to.
I knew you'd bring me in.
That you'd suspect me.
Those are some good instincts.
I'm innocent.
When did you come to this country, Ivan?
1973.
'60s and '70s were some
dark times in Russia.
Walk lightly.
Very lightly.
Must have felt good to finally
get to America.
Since I was a boy, it was my dream...
to work...
make your own life.
What a gift.
Then one day, two
good-for-nothing boys,
who didn't think much of that
gift, came and robbed you.
I didn't kill that boy.
Take a seat.
Don't lie to me.
You were in Atlantic City,
so was Matt Mills.
Okay.
- Yes.
- Yes, what?
Yes, I saw him in Atlantic City.
I saw him, did not kill him!
Remember me?
I-I-I don't want any trouble.
You don't want trouble?
I didn't want trouble either.
My son, Pejia.
You don't remember him.
But he was there when you robbed me.
He saw!
Sir, I regret what we did,
an-and I heard what you said to me.
I tell Pejia if he works hard,
he can be anything he wants.
But he says, "Dad,
why work hard when people
can just take your money?"
You did that.
Sir...
all I can do is say I'm sorry.
Please...
Did you shake his hands?
No.
Because sorry wasn't good enough.
And who would miss this kid anyway?
What?
If he died, who would
miss a boy like him?
Remember saying that?
No.
There he goes,
lying to me again.
You already lied to me about the gun.
You lied about leaving people alone.
Lied about your whereabouts
the day of the murder.
I mean, who do you think
you're lying to, Ivan?
I'm the police.
You got that?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
Because you wanna see your son again,
I'd better start hearing some I believe.
Please.
You're going away, Medvedenko.
I'll disappear?
What?
You'll make me disappear?
- Or Pejia?
- Hey, you're damn right.
You wanna keep lying, Medvedenko?
Poof! Now start talking about
how you killed Matt Mills.
- I have to see my son again.
- Tell me about the .38 you got from Joey.
How you took Matt in your car
and marched that kid into the woods
but don't you lie!
I hate a liar!
Yes.
Yes, what?
I did it.
I killed him.
You want me to feel sorry for you?
You murdered a kid.
- I'll write what you want.
- I write, you talk.
It's got to be first person.
The other one deserved death.
- What other one? Blaine?
- He put the gun to my head.
He was there that night, too, Ivan.
You could've had a twofer.
I saw him outside the casino,
but he drove away before
I could say anything.
He went.
Yeah.
I'll notify Matt's family, his cousin...
I don't know, Scotty.
Don't know what?
Blaine told us he would've given
Matt a ride home,
but he didn't have wheels.
But Medvedenko said he saw
Blaine driving away in a car.
So, Medvedenko's lying.
Maybe, but you should check it out.
We did. DMV shows Blaine
didn't own a car in '97.
But AutoTrack just gave me
a secondary address
on Blaine for all of '97.
A magazine subscription
was sent to his workplace.
What workplace?
Roll-The-Dice Rentals.
A rent-a-car company.
Would have given Blaine
access to a car.
Medvedenko just confessed.
I mean, why would he go
if he didn't do it?
Because you got him wetting his pants.
You figured out where he lives,
and you went there.
Ain't that our job?
Scotty, you ask a guy like that
if he wants to see his kid
again, maybe he thinks KGB.
Maybe he thinks you're saying
you're gonna kill his kid.
Make him disappear.
That was a good interview.
Let's make sure of that.
We got a lot of power in that room.
No good deed goes unpunished, I guess.
It's one more trip to Atlantic City.
We can afford that, can't we?
Before we put away father of
an 11-year-old forever?
That's gonna be one fun
ride, I'll tell you that.
We can't get a car for another hour.
Okay. / It's pretty pathethic.
The department don't get
enough cars to go around.
You're just now noticing
our crap resources?
Don't take a tone.
I was just about to say that to you.
Just hung up with
the Atlantic City Flying Club.
Blaine shelled out $3,000
in October '97.
Exact amount stolen off of Matt.
Four months after he died.
Case was cold by then.
We know Blaine didn't
have a lot of cash flow.
$3,000 all at once is significant.
Yeah, but do you kill your buddy
just so you can take flying lessons?
This wasn't for recreation.
He was gonna start a business.
Another business?
The plan was to buy a Cessna
and go into aerial advertising.
Like one of them planes with the
banner flying over Eagle games?
Yeah, for "Ted's TV and Stereo",
whatever.
So, what happened?
The $3,000 got him through
instruction, not to his license.
- Blaine never became a pilot.
- Another brainstorm down the drain.
But he didn't kill Matt for the money.
What's his motive?
They hadn't seen each other in a while.
Maybe they grew apart.
We know Matt changed.
Blaine's looking like the
mope he's always been.
Could rub a guy the wrong way if your
prodigy grows up different than you did.
Especially if that kid looked up
to you the way Katie does now.
Let's go see about that car.
If Blaine took a car out that day,
I don't have the paperwork.
What about mileage that's not
accounted for?  You track that?
Give me a second.
Of course, all this tells me
is if a car went out on
such and such a day,
- not who drive it.
- Understood.
Okay, here's something.
One vehicle does show
some missing miles.
89 miles on a Honda Accord.
About the round-trip distance
between here and the crime scene.
Sure glad I fired that kid.
Why did you fire Blaine?
One morning he showed up with a gun.
I saw it in his duffel bag.
What'd you do about it?
I took the gun,
I turned it into the cops.
You're a tough guy to find, Blaine.
I've been upstairs.
Got on a bit of a streak this morning.
The house comped me a room.
Come on, number two.
Come on, two horse.
Even a permanent address,
I couldn't find one.
I don't got one right now.
- Where were you living last?
- With some chick. It's a long story.
Been there.
Yeah. Drink?
Em..Thanks.
Uh, what you're having.
Come on.
Come on, two, two, two, two...
Damn it!
We talked to your cousin Katie
the other day, Blaine.
Yeah? I love that kid.
Smart, you know?
Funny, she said that about you.
Yeah?
Told me about the nightclub, bar
restaurant thing, you're getting started.
Sounds like a hot move.
Could' been big,
but some backers just dropped out.
Deal fell through.
Same old, same old, right?
What?
You just seem to run into that a lot.
You know, this restaurant deal,
and that airplane venture before that.
Candy bar machine.
Why you taking shots?
Those aren't shots.
Part of me feels for you, Blaine.
When a someone's bad at
what they want to be good at,
that's not easy to deal with.
We know about Roll-the-Dice
Rentals, Blaine.
How you took the car out that day.
There's no record of that.
There's a record of the mileage.
Probably didn't think
it through that far, huh?
Didn't cover your tracks
with that gun too good, either.
Bringing it to work.
Now A.C. police have it inventoried.
And spending Matt's three
grand at the flying school...
Kind of a half-baked
plan, huh, Blaine?
Kind of a familiar theme for you.
I'm good at business.
Matt was the one working for
a brokerage house,
making connections.
I taught Matt.
A 20-year-old with enough
moxie to get in on an IPO.
You said you were happy
about that, but maybe it hurt.
Matt being the guy who was
the one making things happen.
I made that happen!
The IPO was my idea.
The whole damn things.
Millionaires by age 25.
Salud.
Blaine, put the drink down.
What?
In theory, everything you're
saying is great.
Now let's talk specifics.
Yeah, yeah, let's talk.
Who are the principals behind this?
These McSorley Brothers.
It's their dot com.
And who's underwriting?
Uh...
I don't know.
Well, you'd want to find that out.
Look, Ronnie Mack says
we got to jump on this.
Blaine, IPO's are all based on hype.
You can't just go on what
this pit boss buddy of
yours is telling you.
When I get back to the office
I'll see what an analyst thinks.
Ship's gonna sail.
We gotta pull the trigger on
this day after next.
Then why we having this conversation?
You said we needed 15 grand to get in.
Where are we gonna get 15 grand?
A casino.
A casino?
I've been casing this place.
Here we go.
What are you doing?
Cover that.
They got an open cage here.
We're in and out in 40 seconds.
Are you crazy?
Watch how you're talking to me.
Blaine, you gotta wake up.
Always with the pipe dream.
- It's getting stupid.
- Blah, blah, blah.
Forget you, pal.
I'm doing this one myself.
I'm not gonna let you.
You're not gonna let me?
I'll walk over to the cage right now.
Tip'em off.
Listen, he don't wanna go along?
Fine.
But saying he's gonna stop me?
For my own good?
That runt used to wear
my hand-me-downs!
Now he's gonna big-man me like that?
No.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Come on. Get in.
Don't you stop. I swear, Matty,
I blow your head off.
All right. All right.
Go to that tree.
Okay.
Turn around.
Listen, Blaine, you're gonna rob me?
Take the three grand from the tables.
You can have it.
Shut the hell up.
I'm talking now.
You've known me longer than anybody.
Why did you look at me like that?
Like what?
You're still doing it.
Put your head down.
I don't wanna see your face.
Do it!
Nothing's changed, Matty!
Suddenly, you're looking at me like
you don't know what the hell I'm doing?
All I need is a break.
One break and I'm on my way.
You've always known that
since we were kids.
You were the only one.
- Blaine...
- Shut up!
There's nothing for you to say.
I wanna see it...
in your eyes.
Matty, I need one thing to go my way.
And no one's gonna tell me different.
Now you look up at me,
and you show me you still know that.
Just one break...
# Blessid Union Of Souls의 "I Believe" #
# Violence is spread worldwide
and there are families on the street #
# And we sell drugs to children now
oh why can't we just see #
# That all we do is eliminate our future
with the things we do today #
# Money is our incentive now
so that makes it okay #
# Walk blindly to the light
and reach out for his hand #
# Don't ask any questions
and don't try to understand #
# Open up your mind
and then open up your heart #
# And you will see that you and me
aren't very far apart #
# Cause I believe that love is the answer #
# I believe that love will find the way #
# I believe that love is the answer #
번역수정
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
한글교정
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)