LOOK... I WOKE UP,
I WENT TO WORK.
IT WAS A REGULAR DAY.
AND THEN I ENDED UP
IN THERE...
WITH ALL OF THESE PEOPLE.
MOST OF US DIDN'T KNOW
EACH OTHER AT ALL.
BUT AFTER
WHAT WE WENT THROUGH...
I DON'T KNOW.
www.1000fr.com present
sync:FRM@summerbai
DRKATES IS A TOP SURGEON.
HE'S IN GOOD HANDS...
REALLY GOOD HANDS.
HE'S STABLE.
OH! OH, THANK GOD.
STUD.
I HAVE A TREMENDOUS URGE
TO KISS YOU RIGHT NOW.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
NOT A PROBLEM.
(woman) THANK YOU, LIZZIE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE WOULD'VE
GOTTEN THROUGH ALL THIS
WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
WHY DON'T YOU HEAD UP
TO THE THIRD FLOOR?
I'LL GET YOU IN TO SEE NADER
AS SOON AS I CAN.
OKAY.
YOU ALWAYS GET THE HUGS.
I NEVER GET THE HUGS.
YOU'VE USUALLY GOT
A SCALPEL IN YOUR HAND.
BESIDES, YOU DON'T REALLY
WANT THE HUGS.
NO, BUT I'D LIKE
TO BE ASKED.
(laughs) I NEED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
I'M IN TROUBLE.
MAYBE. I'LL TELL YOU
OVER LUNCH.
SO FONTANA'S FREAKING OUT.
HE'S SURE THIS IS GONNA BE
HIS OWN PERSONAL "CRYING GAME,"
AND SHE REACHES
INTO HER HOT PANTS,
WHIPS OUT A .45.
GUY'S GOT A GUN IN HIS FACE,
AND THIS JACKASS IS RELIEVED.
(man) CAVANAUGH.
THANKS, SEAN.
NICKO, A WORD.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN GOING
TO YOUR G.A. MEETINGS.
THE DEPARTMENT MANDATED SIX.
I DID MY SIX.
SO YOU'RE CURED.
COME ON, PETE.
THIS GROUP THING
IS NOT FOR ME.
BUT I HAVEN'T LAID A BET
IN THREE MONTHS.
HAVEN'T EVEN BOUGHT
A LOTTO TICKET.
ALL I'M SAYING IS, WITH YOUR
HISTORY, YOU DON'T HAVE--
LEAVE MY FATHER OUT OF THIS.
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOUR FATHER.
I'M JUST LOOKING OUT
FOR YOU, NICK.
WELL, I'M THE GUY WITH
THE MOST COLLARS LAST YEAR.
IF YOU'RE REALLY
LOOKIN' OUT FOR ME,
SHOULDN'T WE BE TALKIN' ABOUT
THE PROMOTION I WAS PROMISED?
WE WERE READY
TO GIVE YOU THAT PROMOTION
UNTIL YOU BLEW IT WITH
YOUR LITTLE GAMBLING MISHAP.
I'M NOT THE ONE WHO KEEPS
SHOOTING YOU
IN THE FOOT HERE, NICK.
YOU DO A PRETTY GOOD JOB
OF THAT YOURSELF.
OKAY. I'M GONNA GO
DEPOSIT MY PAYCHECK...
IN MY SAVINGS ACCOUNT.
I HAVE NO SYMPATHY.
I MEAN, NONE.
SHE KNEW THAT HEROIN WAS PUTTING
THOSE DIAMONDS ON HER FINGERS,
AND NOW SHE'S SCARED?
PLEASE.
I TOLD HER THAT IF
SHE DOESN'T TESTIFY,
I'M GONNA RING HER UP FOR 10
TO 15 ON CONSPIRACY CHARGES.
I THOUGHT WE SAID
NO SHOPTALK TODAY.
SORRY.
CAN'T HELP IT, I GUESS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO HELP IT.
YOU KNOW, IT MIGHT DO YOU SOME
GOOD TO REALLY BE WHERE YOU ARE.
THAT SOUNDS A LOT LIKE SOMETHING
YOU MIGHT SAY TO SOMEONE
YOU'RE IN A RELATIONSHIP WITH.
I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I CAN'T HELP IT.
OLD HABIT.
COME ON.
NO ISSUES, NO EXPECTATIONS--
IT'S BETTER LIKE THIS,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
(cell phone rings)
LEAVE IT.
(ring)
HELLO.
(woman) Kathryn.
MOTHER...
I'M AT THE BANK.
SOMEONE HAS STOLEN MY CAMEO PIN
FROM MY SAFETY DEPOSIT BOX.
WELL, DID YOU TALK
TO THE MANAGER?
YES, YES,
I TALKED TO HIM.
HE KEEPS TELLING ME
HOW GOOD THE SECURITY IS.
I TOLD HIM MDAUGHTER IS
AN ASSISTANT DISTRICT ATTORNEY.
I DON'T THINK
HE BELIEVES ME.
I THINK YOU OUGHT
TO COME DOWN HERE.
MOTHER, I'M IN COURT.
I CAN'T JUST DROP EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW THAT PIN
WAS THE LAST THING
THAT YOUR FATHER GAVE ME
before he died,
but if you're too busy--
FINE, FINE, FINE.
I WILL BE THERE
IN A FEW MINUTES.
JUST TRY AND BE CALM.
I AM CALM.
MALCOLM.
EXCUSE ME JUST A MOMENT,
MA'AM.
YES, YOU'RE EXCUSED.
REMEMBER, THE FIRST THING
THAT HAPPENS
IS I DISARM
THE SECURITY GUARD.
THEN YOU GO
FOR THE DRAWER MONEY,
I HIT THE VAULT DOWNSTAIRS
HEY...
I'M NO AMATEUR.
YEAH, ALL I'M SAYING
IS WE GOTTA BE PRECISE.
THANK YOU, SHEILA.
HI, I'M MALCOLM JONES.
I'M THE BRANCH MANAGER.
OH, THE MANAGER...
(laughs) WOW.
UH, I DON'T THINK
I REALLY NEED THE--
THE BIG GUNS HERE.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T GET YOUR NAME.
EGAN FOOTE,
WITH AN "E"--
NOT AT THE BEGINNING
OF THE "EGAN,"
BUT AT THE END
OF THE "FOOTE."
OKAY, HOW CAN I HELP YOU,
MR. FOOTE?
WELL, I WAS
SIMPLY CONSIDERING...
A LOAN FOR A BOAT--
A BOAT LOAN.chuckles)
AND I WAS JUST TELLING
SHEILA HERE--
BYE, SHEILA.
I HOPE I DIDN'T--
OH, NO, NO, NOT AT ALL.
SHE'S JUST GOT PLANS
FOR THE LONG WEEKEND.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
SO IS IT A QUESTION
OF THE INTEREST RATE?
BECAUSE WE'RE
VERY COMPETITIVE.
IT'S MY WIFE.
SHE WOULDN'T LIKE IT.
WOULDN'T EVEN LIKE
THAT I'M HERE,
BUT I JUST THOUGHT--
I THOUGHT A BOAT
MIGHT HELP ME.
I WENT SAILING ONCE
AS A KID.
IT FELT FREE.
WELL, UM...
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD GO HOME
AND DISCUSS IT WITH YOUR WIFE.
HEY, SHE JUST MIGHT
UNDERSTAND.
CAN I USE
YOUR RESTROOM, PLEASE?
SURE, ABSOLUTELY.
UM, TOM...
WOULD YOU PLEASE ESCORT
MISTER, UH, FOOTE
TO THE RESTROOM?
THIS IS GONNA CHANGE
EVERYTHING FOR US.
YEAH.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
GIVE ME $200 ON THE YANKS
IN THE NIGHTCAP
AND $500 ON THE DODGERS
TO COVER.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, THANKS.
(singsongy voice)
EVA, YOUR BOYFRIEND'S HERE.
HAS HE EVEN
ASKED YOU OUT YET?
WHAT THE HELL
IS HE WAITING FOR?
YOU SMELL LIKE TEQUILA
AND MENTHOLS.
LIKE DAD, ACTUALLY.
THAT COLOGNE...
IT'S CALLED "AXION,"
WITH AN "X."
ALL THE COLLEGE BOYS
ARE WEARING IT THESE DAYS.
YOU ONLY GOT ME THIS JOB
SO YOUOULD TORTURE ME
ON A DAILY BASIS.
YOU ONLY TOOK THIS JOB SO YOU
CAN KEEP TABS ON ME.
COME ON. IT'S ALMOST 3:00.
LET'S DO THIS THING.
I TOLD YOU,
WE GOTTA WAIT FOR THE TELLERS
TO LEAVE FOR THEIR WEEKEND.
WHY IS THAT?
FEWER TELLERS, FEWER FINGERS
LOOKING FOR ALARM BUTTONS.
FINE, FINE, FINE,
FINE, FINE, FINE, FINE.
SITTING TIGHT.
(bell dings)
(Eva) THERE YOU GO.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD?
(bell dings)
HI.
UH, I GOT MY DEPOSIT.
YEAH.
UH, YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
COME IN HERE TO DO THIS.
YOU COULD USE
THE A.T.M. OUTSIDE.
OH.
YEAH.
IT'S PERFECTLY SAFE.
I MEAN, THERE'S CAMERAS
WATCHING THE WHOLE TIME.
I PREFER EYES
THAT LOOK BACK AT ME.
I HEARD THAT ABOUTOU.
REALLY? WHO YOU BEEN
TALKING TO?
I'VE GOT MY FLIES
ON THE WALL.
(Kathryn) MOTHER, PLEASE.
I AM TELLING YOU, SOMEBODY
HAS BEEN INSIDE MY BOX.
MA'AM, MA'AM, I REALLY
UNDERSTAND YOUR CONCERN,
BUT I CAN ASSURE YOU,
NO ONE HAS BEEN INSIDE
YOUR BOX.
DID YOU COME ALL THE WAY
DOWN HERE TO PATRONIZE ME?
NO, MOTHER. I'M SORRY.
I--
AND I'M NOT FILLING OUT
ANY FORMS.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
PARDON ME.
HONEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU OKAY?
I REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO YOU, DADDY.
OKAY, ALL RI--
OKAY, SO TRISH AND MAGGIE
INVITED ME
TO GO SEE HOOBASTANK TONIGHT,
AND JARED WAS GONNA DRIVE--
TOTALLY DESIGNATED,
NO ALCOHOL--
BUT HIS CAR DIED,
AND SO NOW THEY'RE GONNA
GIVE MY TICKET AWAY TO SOMEONE
WHO CAN PROVIDE TRANSPORTATION.
YOU WANNA BORROW THE CAR?
JARED'S 18
AND SUCH A RESPONSIBLE DRIVER.
HONEY, LOOK...
I NEED TO WRAP
SOME THINGS UP.
GO DOWN TO COFFEE GROUNDS
AND GET SOMETHING, OKAY?
I'LL BE THERE IN 15 MINUTES.
GREAT, SO YOU'RE
GONNA BLOW ME OFF, TOO.
HONEY, TEN MINUTES, OKAY?
EXCUSE ME, MALCOLM,
HEY, I'VE GOT THIS PROB--
OH, HI, FELICIA.
I'VE GOT THIS PROBLEM
WITH AN ACCOUNTS PAYABLE
AND A COUPLE THINGS I NEED YOU
TO SIGN BEFORE I CAN GO.
(knock on door)
IS ANYBODY IN THERE?
I'LL BE RIGHT OUT.
SORRY.
(sirens wailing)
(siren beeps)
LIZZIE, LIZZIE...
JEREMY, STOP ASKING.
COME ON.
THE SUSPENSE IS KILLING ME.
YOU HAVE TO BE PATIENT,
IMPATIENT BOY.
OH, LOOK AT THIS.
I HAVE MONEY.
LET'S JUST GO.
YOU'RE NOT BUYING ME LUNCH,
NOT ON YOUR SALARY.
(Jeremy) WHAT?
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
SURE.
(bell dings)
SO, UM...
I WAS WONDERING,
MAYBE WE SHOULD HAVE--
SHE'D LOVE TO.
HOW ABOUT TONIGHT?
WILL S BE COMING
WITH US?
NO.
WHO IS SHE?
MY SISTER FRANNY.
THERE'S A COP HERE.
OH, I THINK
WE CAN HANDLE HIM.
NOT WITH
THE SECURITY GUARD, TOO.
WE SHOULD WAIT.
I KNOW, BUT IT WOULD BE
SO MUCH FASTER
IF PEOPLE
HAD THEIR CARDS OUT.
WHAT DO THEY THINK,
IT'S A CANDY MACHINE?
THEN THEY GET UP FRONT
AND THEY REALIZE,
OH, I NEED MONEY.
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING HERE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, ALREADY.
LET'S JUST GO INSIDE.
I DON'T LIKE IT. WE SHOULD
COME BACK ANOTHER TIME.
THERE IS NO OTHER TIME.
NOW.
I'LL TAKE THE SECURITY GUARD.
YOU TAKE THE COP.
HAVE A GOOD ONE.
YOU, TOO.
OKAY.
THANK YOU.
OH, I'M SORRY.
THE BANK'S CLOSED.
eremy) OH, COME ON.
WE JUST NEED THE A.T.M.
NO, WE'RE CLOSED. OH!
AAH!
FREEZE!
(Lizzie) AAH!
(whimpers)
(Eva) OH, NO.
DON'T DO IT.
(Jeremy) JUST BE STILL.
DON'T TRY TO BE
A HERO, MAN.
THIS WILL ALL BE OVER
IN FIVE MINUTES.
THE NIGHTMARE BEGAN
52 HOURS AGO
WHEN TWO GUNMEN...
ONE HOSTAGE WAS RELEASED
IN THE FIRST FEW HOURS
OF THE STANDOFF.
THE CONDITIONS OF THE NINE
REMAINING HOSTAGES--UNKNOWN.
JUST OVER AN HOUR AGO,
TWO GUNSHOTS WERE HEARD.
(woman) ANOTHER,
THE SECURITY GUARD,
WAS KILLED INSIDE.
(woman) ...AND EMPLOYEES
HAVE BEEN TAKEN HOSTAGE,
THOUGH THE NAMES OF THE HOSTAGES
HAVE NOT OFFICIALLY...
(men yelling indistinctly)
(explosion booms)
(man) DON'T MOVE, DON'T MOVE!
(man) HANDS WHERE
WE CAN SEE 'EM!
GUN!
(woman) EGAN, NO!
(man) GET DOWN!
GET DOWN!
(gunshots)
I'VE GOT ONE DOWN!
DON'T SHOOT! I'M UNARMED!
DON'T SHOOT!
DON'T SHOOT HIM!
DON'T HURT HIM!
(man) KEEP YOUR HANDS
WHERE I CAN SEE 'EM!
DON'T HURT HIM!
AAH!
I'M THE COP! I'M THE COP!
WHERE WERE YOU HIT,
DETECTIVE?
NO, IT'S NOT MY BLOOD.
A WOMAN HAS BEEN SHOT.
SHE'S BACK THERE.
GET HER OUTTA HERE!GO!
PLEASE, HELP HER. PLEASE!
STAY WITH ME, EVA. EVA.
PLEASE HELP MY SISTER!
HEY, GET OFF ME!
I'M A DOCTOR.
EVA. EVA, STAY WITH ME.
EVIE, EVIE, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
WHERE ARE
THE DAMN PARAMEDICS?
(sirens wail)
THE KEY IS ON THE PSYCHO
U SHOT.
(sirens wail)
WHAT THE HELL?
(man) THERE'S ANOTHER ONE
OVER HERE.
(crowd cheering)
(man) WE NEED TO KEEP
THAT AREA CLEAR.
(sirens wail and whoop)
(cheering)
(helicopter speeds past)
LIZZIE!
LIZZIE. LIZZIE, IT'S OKAY. IT'S
OKAY. LOOK AT ME. I GOT YOU.
I'VE BEEN TREATING HER
FOR THE LAST HOUR AND A HALF.
I'VE GOTTA GO WITH HER.
I'M RIGHT HERE, EVIE.
I LOVE YOU, EVIE.
SHE'S ALLERGIC TO PENICILLIN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE.
HOW ARE WE DOIN'
ON THOSE KEYS, FELLAS?
BRINGING 'EM IN NOW,
DETECTIVE.
(man) RENZO, THOMAS,
SECURE THIS GUY!
(Felicia) DADDY! DADDY!
(man) Can anyone
identify this man?
IT'S OKAY!
HE'S THE BANK MANAGER.
DADDY,
WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE?
GET HER OUTTA HERE.
BUT DON'T TAKE HER ANYWHERE
WITHOUT THIS MAN.
THIS IS HER FATHER. IT'S OKAY,
HONEY. IT'S OKAY, HONEY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT OUT.
MALCOLM. MALCOLM!
YOU DID GOOD. IT'S OVER.
LET GO.
(siren wails)
(man) ALL THE WAY
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
WHERE'S THE NEGOTIATOR?
OH, DAMN IT! NICK,
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
HER DOCTOR AND HER SISTER
ARE GOIN' WITH HER
IN THIS AMBULANCE.
(man) WE'LL BE
RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
LET'S GO, AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
COME ON.
DISTRICT ATTORNEY ED NIELSON.
THIS WOMAN WORKS FOR ME.
YOU'VE GOT ONE MINUTE, SIR.
JEEZ, KAT.
HOW IS MY MOTHER?
I TOOK HER TO MY PLACE.
WILL YOU BRING HER
TO MY APARTMENT?
YOU GOT IT. IT'S DONE.
WE'RE GONNA NAIL
THESE BASTARDS.
THEY'RE NEVER GONNA SEE
THE LIGHT OF DAY AGAIN.
(man) MOVE IT, LUC.
NO ONE WAS SUPPOSED
TO GET HURT.
I SWEAR TO GOD, NO ONE
WAS SUPPOSED TO GET HURT.
(man) GET HIM IN THERE.
MR. FOOTE?
MR. FOOTE,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
MR. FOOTE?
AM I DEAD?
NO, YOU JUST
HIT YOUR HEAD.
(police radio chatter)
(man) 10-David reporting code 4.
The bank is clear.
Code 4.
HOW'S EVERYONE ELSE?
WHERE'S EVERYONE ELSE?
(sirens wail)
FRANNY'S WITH EVA, RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHY ARE THEY DOIN' THIS,
TAKING US LIKE THIS?
BECAUSE TO THEM,
WE'RE ALL SUSPECTS.
(man) WE KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH A TERRIBLE ORDEAL,
AND WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
OUTTA HERE AS SOON AS WE CAN.
BUT WE NEED TO TALK TO YOU NOW,
WHILE IT'S ALL
STILL FRESH IN YOUR MINDS.
BULLET WENT THROUGH THE CHEST.
HEART RATE'S IN THE 130s.
I PUT IN A CHEST TUBE
TO EVACUATE THE PNEUMOTHORAX.
WHAT DID YOU USE?
A PEN. IT'S ALL WE HAD.
SHE'S LOST A LOT OF BLOOD.
I DON'T KNOW IF SHE HAS
AN AORTA TEAR.
I GOT IT FROM HERE.
O.R. ONE. LET'S MOVE. MOVE!
SHE'S ALLERGIC TO PENICILLIN!
DID I SAY THAT?
(man) We've got the perp
Randall Reese
coming to you right now.
(man) Make sure he stays secured
to that gurney at all times.
(mouths words)
(man) DO YOU RECOGNIZE
ANY OF THESE MEN?
THAT'S HIM. RANDALL REESE.
OH!
FELICIA?
WERE YOU AFRAID
FOR YOUR LIFE? MS. MILLER?
WE ALL WERE. RANDALL KILLED
THE SECURITY GUARD.
WE KNEW
WHAT HE WAS CAPABLE OF.
LOOK, I'VE I.D.'ed THESE GUYS
THREE TIMES.
NO MATTER WHAT COMBINATION
YOU SHOW ME,
THIS IS STILL RANDALL REESE
AND THIS IS STILL LUCAS DALTON.
NOW I WANT MY UPDATE
ON EVA RIOS.
WHAT IS TAKING THEM
SO DAMN LONG IN THERE?
(man) DR. KATES,
I'VE GOT MORE QUESTIONS.
YOU COMIN'?
an) YOU BROUGHT A GUN
INTO THE BANK ALSO?
I WAS GONNA KILL MYSELF.
NOT HERE. LATER.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
THE L.A. RIVER BASIN,
YOU KNOW, WHERE THEY HAD
THAT DRAG RACE FROM "GREASE."
(man) AND LUCAS DALTON,
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
LUCAS IS MILITARY?
HIM. HE'S...
HE'S FAMILIAR, BUT...
I CAN'T PLACE IT.
I CAN'T.
DADDY,
I DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
(man) AND YOUR HAIR, MS. HALE,
WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN?
SAME TIME AS THIS.
IT WAS A TWO-FER.
MAY I SEE THOSE PENS,
PLEASE? THANK YOU.
WHO DID THAT TO YOU?
WAS IT REESE OR DALTON?
STICK WITH ME, OKAY?
AND THIS WILL BE OVER SOON.
HEY, I DO THIS FOR A LIVING.
I'M FINE.
DEPUTY DIRECTOR
ROGER MARSHALL, FBI.
I HAD THE PLAN TO END
THIS THING YESTERDAY.
YOU GUYS BLEW IT.
YOU CHOKED.
IT WAS A RISKY PLAN AT BEST,
AND THEN IT BECAME UNTENABLE.
AND THE NEXT TE YOU WANT
TO TAKE A SWING AT SOMEONE,
IT SHOULD BE ME.
I WAS THE ONE THAT MADE
THAT CALL.
IT WAS A BAD CALL.
OR MAYBE YOU AND KATHRYN HALE
WOULD'VE BEEN KILLED.
BUT WE'LL NEVER KNOW, RIGHT?
DID DETECTIVE CAVANAUGH MAKE
ANY EFFORT TO STOP THEM?
CHAINED TO A POLE, I'D SAY HE
DID EVERYTHING HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
HE CERTAINLY WAS MORE PERSUASIVE
THAN YOU PEOPLE.
DID HE TRY TO PERSUADE
LUCAS DALTON
TO STOP RANDALL REESE?
THE ONLY WAY TO STOP
RANDALL REESE WAS TO KILL HIM,
AND LUCAS COULDN'T DO THAT.
WHY IS THAT?
RANDALL IS LUCAS'
OLDER BROTHER.
I WANNA FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPED TO EVA RIOS.
YOU HAVEN'T ASKED
ABOUT YOUR BROTHER.
IS HE DEAD?
HAVEN'T HEARD. HIS CHANCES
AREN'T GOOD, THOUGH.
HE DIES, YOU KNOW
IT'S ALL ON YOU.
THAT'S FINE.
IT'S ALL ON ME.
SO IT WAYOUR PLAN?
YEAH.
AND NO ONE ELSE
WAS INVOLVED?
I'M NOT SAYIN' ANOTHER WORD
TILL I GET MY LAWYER.
I'D LIKE MY PHONE CALL, PLEASE,
AND THE NUMBER TO THE HOSPITAL.
I'LL GET YOU WORD ON
YOUR BROTHER WHEN IT COMES.
I WANT TO FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED TO EVA RIOS.
(monitor beeping)
(medical team
speaking indistinctly)
(woman) HEY, EGAN!
(man) PRETTY GOOD STUFF,
EGAN.
YOU'RE A HERO, EGAN.
HOW'S IT FEEL?
HERO?
HOW'S IT FEEL
TO BE A HERO?
HERO?
MR. FOOTE,
A STATEMENT, PLEASE.
IT--IT'S EGAN FOOTE,
WITH AN "E."
HOW'S IT FEEL?
HOW DID YOU DO IT, SIR?
(Marshall)
PRETTY HARROWING EXPERIENCE.
I'VE SEEN YOUR FILE.
YOUR FATHER WAS A COP.
GOT HIMSELF
AND HIS PARTNER KILLED
BECAUSE HE WAS ON THE SAUCE.
NOW YOU--GAMBLING PROBLEM--
COST YOUR DEPARTMENT
A HUGE COLLAR.
WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
WELL, CLEARLY, YOU'RE NOT HAPPY
ABOUT SOME OF OUR DECISIONS.
YOU GO PUBLIC WITH THAT, WE'LL
GO RIGHT AT YOUR CREDIBILITY.
WE'LL EVEN DRAG YOUR EX-WIFE OUT
OF THE WOODWORK IF WE HAVE TO.
I'M DONE HERE.
WE STILL NEED
TO GET YOUR STATEMENT.
I JUST FEEL LIKE THERE ARE
MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
I SHOULD BE DOING.
I SHOULD BE AT THE HOSPITAL
WITH FRANNY.
I'M SURE THERE ARE OTHER
SOCIAL WORKERS ON HAND THERE.
BUT I'M HER FRIEND.
I THOUGHT YOU ONLY KNEW
JEREMY KATES.
LOOK... I WOKE UP,
I WENT TO WORK,
IT WAS A REGULAR DAY.
AND THEN I ENDED UP
IN THERE WITH...
ALL OF THESE PEOPLE.
MOST OF US DIDN'T KNOW
EACH OTHER AT ALL.
BUT AFTER
WHAT WE WENT THROUGH...
FOR THE REST
OF OUR LIVES, I--
I DON'T KNOW.
NOW CAN I PLEASE GO?
HEY.
HI.
ANY WORD YET?
NOT YET.
HOW IS SHE?
WE DON'T KNOW.
(door clicks)
WHAT?
(sobs)
I'M--
I'M SO SORRY, FRANNY.
(crying)
WHAT? WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
OH, MY GOD.
(crying)
FRANNY, YOU'RE HERE.
RICKY'S BEEN ASKING
FOR HIS MOM.
I DIDN'T--I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
TO TELL HIM. WHERE IS SHE?
CAN I HAVE
THE SPARE KEYS, PLEASE?
(keys jingling)
EVA'S DEAD.
UM...
SHE DIED.
IS RICKY OKAY
FOR THE NIGHT?
YEAH, OF COURSE.
THANK YOU.
MA, I CAN'T HEAR YOU
WHEN YOU AND DAD TALK
AT THE SAME TIME.
I PROMISE
WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
YES, LIZZIE'S HERE WITH ME.
SHE'S STAYING HERE TONIGHT.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
(telephone beeps)
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN SEE THEM TOMORROW.
IT'S NO PRESSURE.
(sighs) WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE A VEGETARIAN.
I WANTED BACON.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT IT?
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
IN THERE.
A LOT OF THINGS HAPPENED
IT WAS A MOMT, LIZZIE.
A MOMENT.
DOES IT
HAVE TO MEAN EVERYTHING?
(man) POLICE ARE NOW
JUST RELEASING THE NAMES
OF THE NINE HOSTAGES...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I HATE THIS SHIRT.
(laughs)
I ALWAYS HAVE.
YOU'RE THROWING IT AWAY?
ALL OF THAT STUFF
IN THE GARBAGE?
NO, NO, NO. I'LL BRING 'EM
TO GOODWILL IN THE MORNING.
I WANT NEW DUDS, MARY.
DUDS?
YEAH! WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
WE WENT SHOPPING?
EGAN, YOU'RE BEING CRAZY.
NO, I'M NOT.
I FEEL GOOD. I FEEL GREAT.
I HATE THIS SHIRT.
AND KNOW THAT.
THAT'S PHENOMENAL.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME...
THAT YOU BOUGHT A PAIR
OF NEW SHOES, HUH?
I WANT YOU
TO HAVE ANYTHING--
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
WHAT--WHY WOULD YOU
DO THAT, EGAN,
RISK YOUR LIFE FOR PEOPLE
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW?
WHAT ABOUT ME?
WHAT WOULD I...
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO PROVE?
(man) * DANCING WHERE
THE STARS GO BLUE *
* DANCING WHERE
THE EVENING FEEL *
* DANCING IN
MY WOODEN SHOES *
I'D LIKE TO FILE A REQUEST.
MY MOTHER...
I DON'T WANT HER
VISITING ME HERE.
* DANCING OUT
ON SEVENTH STREET *
YOU HAVE TONS OF MESSAGES
FROM YOUR FRIENDS AT SCHOOL.
EVERYONE WAS WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
EVERYONE IS HAPPY TO KNOW
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
MOM, I AM NOT ALL RIGHT.
THERE ARE TWO FULL DAYS
OF MY LIFE
THAT I DON'T REMEMBER.
YOU'RE HOME.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT'S ALL RIGHT, MOM.
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE
JUST TRYING TO HELP.
LOOK, I'M TIRED.
I'M GONNA TRY
AND GET SOME SLEEP.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH,
MY BABY.
* THE STARS GO BLUE *
EVA WAS CRASHING HERE UNTIL
SHE GOT BACK ON HER FEET.
WHERE'S HER EX?
PRISON.
SHE WAS JUST STARTING
TO GET HER LIFE
BACK TOGETHER AGAIN.
SHE WAS REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT YOU.
SHE WOULDN'T EVEN
HAVE BEEN THERE
IF I HADN'T GOTTEN HER
THE JOB.
I WOULDN'T TAKE THAT
ON YOURSELF.
WHY NOT?
COME ON.
WELL, THANKS FOR
BRINGING ME HOME.
WHY DON'T YOU GET
SOME SEP?
I'M GONNA BE OUT HERE
IF YOU NEED ME.
OKAY.
YOU JUST TRY TO GET
SOME SLEEP, TOO.
* WHEN THE STARS GO BLUE *
(Malcolm) IT'S GOOD
THEY HAVEN'T SHOWN HER FACE.
I TALKED TO THE FBI,
YOU KNOW, TOLD 'EM
TO PUT SOME PRESSURE
ON SOME PEOPLE...
TELL THE PRESS
TO JUST CONSIDER THE FACT
THAT SHE'S JUST A CHILD.
SHE SHOULDN'T BE EXPOSED.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
I TOOK CARE OF THAT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER
IN THERE?
NAOMI... (sighs)
HONEY, WE WERE TRAPPED
FOR TWO DAYS.
SHE--SHE WAS SCARED.
YES, BUT WHAT HAPPENED,
MALCOLM?
(Felicia) DADDY,
WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WASN'T WITH HER
THE WHOLE TIME.
(cell phone rings)
(ring)
(cell phone beeps)
HELLO.
Hi, it's Kathryn...
Hale.
GOT YOUR NUMBER
FROM THE STATION.
I MADE IT SOUND OFFICIAL.
I-I HOPE IT'S OKAY I'M CALLING.
NO, IT'S FINE. UM...
AM I--AM I WAKING SOMEONE?
NO, I'M AT FRANNY'S.
GOOD.
THAT'S--THAT'S GOOD.
How is she?
SLEEPING RIGHT NOW.
HOW'S YOUR MOTHER?
(chuckles) SHE'S--
SHS FINE.
COULDN'T STOP TALKING ABOUT
YOUR HEROICS ALL NIGHT,
the way you got her
out of there.
You saved her life
as far as she's concerned...
AS--AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
NICK, EVERYTHING WOULD'VE
GONE DOWN A LOT WORSE
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN THERE.
KATHRYN, WHO ARE YOU
TALKING TO?
OH, JUST, UM, JUST GIVE ME--
GIVE ME A SECOND.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU NEED TO GO.
YEAH.
YOU TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
YOU, TOO.
HEY, THERE.
HEY.
YOU LOOK VERY PRETTY.
OH, THANK YOU.
I LIKE YOUR SUIT.
(chuckles) IT'S NEW.
SHOULD WE...
PLEASE.
***
(car door closes)
(woman) NICE OF
YOUR FATHER TO COME.
OH, HE COULDN'T GET OFF WORK,
COULDN'T FIND A FLIGHT.
WHATEVER.
A MAN HAS TO DO
WHAT HE SHOULD DO.
(Jeremy)
THIS IS A GREAT HOUSE.
WOW. YOU REALLY DIDN'T
HAVE TO BRING ANYTHING.
UH, JEWS BRING FOOD.
IT'S--IT'S WHAT WE DO.
IT HELPS STUFF DOWN
OUR FEELINGS.
WELL, YOU CAN PUT THAT
RIGHT OVER THERE.
OKAY.
EGAN, HOW ARE YOU?
HI. WELL, YOUR EYE
SEEMS  BE HEALING.
YEAH, YEAH.
HOW'S YOUR HEAD?
FINE. GOOD AS NEW.
THAT WAS QUITE SOMETHING
YOU DID BACK THERE, EGAN,
AT THE END.
AH... JUST INSTINCT.
(salsa music playing)
YOU SEEM... BETTER.
I'VE GOT A SECOND CHANCE
AT LIFE.
WE ALL DO, DON'T WE?
(music continues)
OH, THAT SOUNDED TERRIBLE.
I, UH--IDIOT.
EGAN, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
IDIOT, IDIOT, IDIOT.
NO BLURTING.
I DIDN'T MEAN--OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HI.
HEY.
I LEFT YOU A MESSAGE YESTERDAY
TO SEE IF YOU WANTED A RIDE.
YEAH, RRY.
I HAVEN'T HAD A SECOND.
MY CASELOAD DOUBLED
AT THE HOSPITAL
WHILE I WAS GONE.
OH, YOU'RE BACK
AT WORK ALREADY?
SINCE TUESDAY.
OH.
SO...
HOW ARE YOU?
I-I'VE GOTTA BRING
THIS PLATE TO FELICIA.
WE ALL COULDA DONE THINGS
DIFFERENTLY IN THERE.
(music continues)
NACHO?
(mouths word)
HEY.
IT'S GOOD
TO SEE EVERYONE.
I'M PREGNANT.
WHAT?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU KNOWN?
A WEEK.
YOU NE--
YOU NEVER SAID ANYTHING,
I MEAN, THE WHOLE TIME
THAT WE WERE IN THE BANK.
I DIDN'T
WANT ANYONE TO KNOW.
OH, IT'S, UM...
IT'S NOT JEREMY'S?
NO, IT--IT IS.
AND I WAS GONNA
TELL HIM...
(chuckles) THAT DAY.
(sighs) BUT...
NOW I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF I WANT HIM TO KNOW.
YOU KNOW?
WELL...
IT WON'T COME FROM ME.
(music continues)
THANKS.
YOU KNOW I WON'T BE ABLE
TO TAKE CARE OF RICKY...
I KNOW.
NOT NOW, NOT LIKE THIS.
IT IS UP TO YOU NOW.
I KNOW.
TIME TO GROW UP.
GRANDMA, I KNOW!
(music continues)
(chuckles)
SO I HEARD YOU PUNCHED OUT
THE NEGOTIATOR THE OTHER NIGHT.
PUNCHED, YEAH.
OUT, NO. UNFORTUNATELY.
YOU GETTING A HARD TIME
ABOUT IT
NOT YET.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU SAID IN YOUR STATEMENT,
BUT IF YOU WANT
TO MAKE AN ISSUE
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
ON THE OUTSIDE,
I'LL BACK YOU UP.
EXCUSE M MR. JONES.
DEPUTY D.A. ED NIELSON.
THAT'S NOT GONNA BE
SO SIMPLE FOR YOU.
I WORK WITH KATHRYN.
SIMPLE'S OVERRATED.
ARE YOU NICK?
YEAH, YOU MUST BE RICKY.
ARE YOU THE COP?
YEP.
THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU SAVE
MY MOM?
HEY, RICKY, I FOUND
THE DVD. LET'S GO WATCH IT.
(music continues)
(footsteps approach)
(Jeremy) YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
(music continues)
I'M REALLY SORRY
I COULDN'T DO MORE.
LOOK, SHE WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN ALIVE
AS LONG AS SHE WAS
IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU.
CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE LEFT ME.
AND I FEEL SO ALONE.
I KNOW.
(man singing ballad
in Spanish)
PLEASE.
HI, MALCOLM.
IT'S SO GOOD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
HEY, SHEILA.
IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK.
WE'RE SEEING POTENTIAL
NEW RECRUITS TODAY,
IS THAT RIGHT?
(Sheila) STARTING AT 2:00.
GREAT.
(man) HEY, DALTON.
YOUR BROTHER'S
OUT OF HIS COMA.
TOO BAD HE'S GONNA MAKE IT.
THERE IS NO OTHER TIME.
NOW.
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS, DETECTIVE.
THIS IS GONNA BE
REAL HELPFUL.
HEY, PETE.
WHEN'S MY HEARING?
IT'S BEEN OVER A WEEK.
I WAS JUST WONDERING WHEN
I WAS GONNA BE REINSTATED.
LET'S GO INSIDE.
YOU'RE SCAPEGOATING ME,
AREN'T YOU?
NICK, YOU'RE NOT
BEING SCAPE--
NO, IT'S JUST PERFECT.
LIKE FATHER, LIKE SON, RIGHT?
IT'S A GREAT STORY.
YOU'RE NOT HAVING A HEARING
BECAUSE WE DECIDED
YOU DON'T NEED A HEARING.
YOU'RE GONNA BE REINSTATED
RIGHT AWAY.
YOU'RE BEING GIVEN
THE MEDAL OF DISTINCTION.
AND YOU'RE GONNA GET
YOUR PROMOTION.
WHAT'S THE CATCH?
KEEP YOUR OPINIONS
TO YOURSELF.
AND IF I DON'T?
THIS IS A BIG CHANCE
FOR YOU, NICK,
TO GET RID
OF SOME OLD GHOSTS.
(Beth Orton's "Thinking
About Tomorrow" playing)
* TIRED,
BUT I AIN'T SLEEPIN' *
* THINKIN' ABOUT
SOME SAD AAIR *
* AND WHY
I SHOULD BE LEAVING *
THERE ARE PLACES
THAT DO THAT, YOU KNOW,
FOR YOU.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
I HEARD WE JUST LOST
CARLA BARRETT.
WELL, SHE DIDN'T BELIEVE
THAT WE COULD PROTECT HER.
WELL, I THOUGHT
OUR STANCE ON HER
WAS SHE KNEW
WHAT SHE WAS GETTING INTO--
THE DIAMONDS, THE FURS.
I'M NOT GONNA FORCE HER
TO TESTIFY
IF SHE DOESN'T FEEL SAFE.
WELL, I WISH YOU WOULD'VE
RUN IT BY ME BEFORE...
YOU WANT SOME HELP
WITH THE BACK?
NO, THANKS. I GOT IT.
(woman)
WHEN I FIRST GOT DIAGNOSED,
EVERYONE RUSHED TO MY SIDE.
YOU GET PHONE CALLS,
FLOWERS AND SUPPORT.
RIGHT?
AND IT'S THIS
REALLY AMAZING EXPERIENCE--
SO MUCH LOVE.
AND THEN AS SOON AS I STARTED
TO GET BETTER,
EVERYONE WENT BACK
TO THEIR LIVES.
AND I FELT LIKE...
LIKE A LOT OF THAT LOVE
WENT WITH THEM,
LIKE THE LOVE FORGOT ME.
I GUESS THAT'S WHY
I COME HERE
TO SEE YOU PEOPLE
EVERY WEEK,
'CAUSE I DON'T
WANNA BE FORGOTTEN.
AND I DON'T WANT TO FORGET.
EGAN, WELCOME BACK.
HEY, THERE'S RAMBO.
(woman) HEY...
THE CONQUERING HERO
RETURNS.
* SO LONG... *
WAY TO GO, EGAN.
* WILL IT
EVER HAPPEN AGAIN? *
* YOU KNOW THAT I'VE
BEEN WAITING FOR YOU *
* I'VE BEEN CREATING
FOR YOU *
* SO LONG *
* YOU KNOW THE LIGHT
AIN'T FADING FROM YOU *
* NOTHING COULD SAVE ME
FROM YOU *
* SO LONG *
I HEARD YOU WERE BACK.
YEAH. (clears throat)
YEAH, I'VE GOTTA BE
IN SURGERY.
WELL, I WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT EGAN AND I ORGANIZED
A GET-TOGETHER TONIGHT
FOR EVERYONE.
WHAT FOR, GROUP THERAPY?
NO, IT'S...
WE'RE GOING TO MEET
AT JIM'S COUNTER
SO WE CAN SEE EACH OTHER.
YOU KNOW, WE SHOULDN'T
LOSE CONTACT.
* THESE HABITS ARE
SO HARD TO BREAK *
* AND THEY'RE... *
JUST COME IF YOU WANT TO.
* EASY *
* YEAH *
* SO LONG *
* BYE, MY FRIEND *
HEY.
YOU'RE EARLY. (chuckles)
I MEAN, I'M EARLY,
BUT YOU'RE REALLY EARLY.
YEAH, I ALREADY ATE.
OH, NOT A PROBLEM.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE,
THIS MEETING.
I MEAN...
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU, NICK.
* SO LONG *
* YOU KNOW THE LIGHT
AIN'T FADING FROM YOU *
*OTHING COULD SAVE
ME FROM YOU *
* SO LONG *
(Egan) IT'S A LITTLE BIT
OF EVERYTHING ON THE MENU,
PRETTY MUCH.
SO YOU GET--IT'S THE WHOLE--
(Lizzie) OKAY, OKAY.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
HEY.
HI.
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
(Kathryn)
HOW'S EVERYTHING GOING?
HI.
(Malcolm) HEY,
HOW'S YOUR MOTHER?
OH, SHE'S GOOD. THANK YOU.
HERE, TAKE MY MENU.
I KNOW EVERYTHING.
OKAY, THANKS.
YOU GUYS HAVE ORDERE
(Egan) NO, NOT YET.
I LIKE YOUR HAIR THAT WAY.
THAT ABSTRACT THING WAS KINDA
CONFUSING PEOPLE AT WORK.
THEY'RE USED TO ME BEING
VERY CUT-AND-DRY.
IS THAT SO?
ED WANTS ME TO TAKE
A COUPLE OF DAYS OFF.
HE THINKS I'M GOING SOFT.
WE CAN'T HAVE THAT,
NOW CAN WE?
(woman) OKAY, SIR?
OH, UH, NEW SHIRT.
YES, I KNOW.
TAG.
(laughs)
THANK YOU.
(glass shattering)
OH, MY GOD.
(laughs)
I'M SORRY.
DID YOU SEE... EGAN?
HE ALMOST JUMPED UP
AND BODY BLOCKED THE WAITRESS.
(Malcolm)
DON'T ENCOURAGE HIM.
(Franny) JEREMY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HI. YOU CAME.
YEAH.
ARE YOU UNK?
MAYBE.
(Jeremy) I'M SORRY
I HAVEN'T CALLED YOU.
I HAVEN'T
CALLED YOU EITHER.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY TALK,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
ABOUT WHAT?
COME ON, I'M STARVED.
IF MY WIFE KNEW I WAS
EATING FRENCH FRIES...
LOOK WHO I RAN INTO
OUTSIDE.
HEY!
(Franny laughs)
(Egan) HI.
HEY.
SO I WAS AT HAPPY HOUR,
WITH MY FRIENDS...
AND THEY WANTED TO COME
AND MEET YOU GUYS,
BUT I TOLD 'EM
IT WAS A PRIVATE PARTY--
HOSTAGES ONLY.
OH, THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
VERY FUNNY.
YOU WERE GOING
TO TELL ME SOMETHING.
HMM?
BEFORE WE WENT INTO
THE BANK.
OH, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WOW, EVERYBODY CAME.
(Egan) ALMOST.
OH, WAIT,
WHERE'S FELICIA?
SHE HAD SOME PARTY TO GO TO,
WHICH I WAS GLAD ABOUT.
BUT SHE SAID TO SAY HELLO
TO EVERYBODY,
SO HELLO FROM FELICIA.
TELL HER WE SAID HI.
(Egan) MAYBE SHE'LL, UM,
SHE'LL JOIN US NEXT TIME.
***
(door lock buzzes)
(buzz)
HI.