It was an ordinary day...
It's almost 3:00.
Let's do this thing.
There were nine of us...
Most of us strangers.
We all ended up in the bank.
All for different reasons.
- And then in an instant...
- Now.
- Our lives changed.
- Aah !
This will all be over in five minutes.
52 hours later
...we came out of there
no longer strangers,
bonded forever
by what we went through.
What happened in there ?
Only we know for now.
Previously on The Nine...
Get down ! Get down !
Don't shoot ! I'm unarmed !
- I'm the cop ! I'm the cop !
- Please help her. please !
- Stay with me, Eva.
- This is her father.
What is happening ?
It's okay, honey. He'll be right out.
We're gonna nail these bastards.
They're never gonna see
the light of day again.
No one was supposed to get hurt.
Where's the negotiator ?
Well, clearly, you're not happy
about some of our decisions.
You go public with that,
we'll go right at your credibility.
- Do you want to talk about it ?
- About what ?
About what happened in there.
Daddy, I don't remember anything.
What happened to her in there ?
Eva's dead. She died.
Look, she wouldn't have been alive
as long as she was if it wasn't for you.
I'm in trouble.
Maybe.
- You were going to tell me something.
- I'm pregnant.
You never said anything, I mean,
the whole time that we were in the bank.
Nick, everything would've
gone down a lot worse
if you hadn't have been there.
If you want to make an issue
about what happened on the outside,
- I'll back you up.
- That's not gonna be so simple for you.
- How's it feel to be a hero ?
- A hero ?
Why would you do that, Egan ?
Risk your life for people
you don't even know ?
Egan and I organized
a get together tonight.
You know, we shouldn't lose contact.
Everybody came.
Hey, where's Felicia ?
Hi.
This will all be over in five minutes.
Your gun...
Hour 1 - 3:06 PM
On the floor, slowly.
Nobody gets hurt here.
Everybody, hands up !
That means you, now !
Kick it over.
Get over here now.
Come on !
You two pretty little ladies,
outta there !
And do not even think
about touching those alarm buttons.
You ! Away from the door.
We can't. It's locked.
Come on. Let's go, gorgeous.
You...
Lift up his pant legs.
It's okay.
We're gonna be okay.
- Move it, lady !
- Okay, okay.
- Come on !
- Okay, okay. I'm... I'm moving.
Over there.
You two, over there.
Let's go. Let's go !
Higher.
That was my only gun.
He's clean.
All right, get up.
You're making a big mistake here,
robbing a bank
- with a cop inside.
- Oh, yeah ?
- Don't.
- If you get out of here right now,
you've barely even committed a felony.
- Stop, stop.
- Shut up. Shut up !
Just do what he says.
Well, I appreciate your concern, ma'am,
but we got the cameras covered.
As far as a felony...
How's that, huh ?
I need your cell phones.
Dump 'em on the floor, all of you.
Where's your phone ?
What the hell is that ?
I don't know.
You don't know why your sleeve is blue ?
Hey ! Come on. You don't have to do that.
Look, he just went to the bathroom.
Maybe it got wet in there.
It's all right, Mr. Foote. Just,
try to explain whatever... went on.
I... I dropped my wedding ring
in the toilet.
How the hell did you do that ?
I was gonna flush it and
I changed my mind.
All right, let's get on with this.
- Who's in charge here ?
- I am.
Take me to the vault.
I just have to get my keys.
- Now !
- They're in my desk.
All right !
Everybody else down on the floor
on your stomachs.
- This will be over in five minutes.
- Okay.
Are you all right ?
Follow me.
11 days later.
Hi.
You're not that surprised to see me.
Nothing would surprise me
at this point.
So you're okay that I'm here ?
Not like I get a lot of visitors.
It's a pretty big story, you know ?
All of this.
Not exactly what I had in mind.
So I guess there's gonna
be a trial, huh ?
A big one, looks like.
Do you have a good lawyer ?
We'll see.
I hear they're keeping your brother
at the same hospital
where Jeremy and Lizzie work. I guess...
that it was the closest one to the bank.
Why are you here ?
I've been thinking about it, you know ?
Everything that...
happened in there, and...
Yeah, well, try not to think too much.
Just get back to your life.
Forget about me.
- But please, I just...
- Forget about me, Felicia.
And don't come back here.
No. No, Lucas.
The Bloc Team presents to you
The Nine - Episode 2 - Heroes Welcome
Well, it was a great idea,
getting together.
And a great place.
- My fries were kinda cold.
- Yeah, yeah.
So, uh, same time next week ?
- Oh, sure.
- Sure.
Yeah.
- All right.
- Come on. Let's go, kiddo.
Oh, I'm telling you, I'm fine.
I had, like, two margaritas
three hours ago.
- Young lady, I am driving you home.
Understood ?
- Fine.
Good night, everybody.
- Good night.
Night.
- You haven't told him yet ?
- No.
I hate to break it to you,
but you're not gonna be able
to hide it much longer.
Walk you to your car ?
Sure.
Night, everybody.
- Night.
You still have some stuff
at my place.
Yeah, my guitar.
Yeah, a few t-shirts, tennis racket...
Your first edition unbearable
lightness of being.
You want me to bring it in
to work for you ?
Did you come here with Franny ?
Did I... ? No.
No.
We bumped into each other out front.
It's okay if you did.
I thought it was good
that she wasn't alone.
No, we didn't.
Okay.
So are we done ?
I need some time to think
about a lot of things.
Two years...
Two years, and we just flush it
down the drain with barely
a conversation.
I just said I need
some time to think.
Right.
Well, you know where to find me.
Yeah.
Safe drive.
So the department wants
to make you their mascot.
I prefer "poster boy".
It makes sense... Pin a medal on you
and put you out front.
The department gets some good P.R.
It certainly helps take the stink
off of how they handled things
And keeps my mouth shut.
I know it's kinda slimy,
the way they're dealing
with things, but...
You do deserve a medal,
or a promotion or,
whatever else you might
want from them.
Two people are dead.
One of 'em was shot with my gun.
There was nothing that
you could've done about Eva.
I should go.
Uh, get some sleep.
Everybody say yeah !
- Say yeah !
- Good morning, Los Angeles,
and welcome to "The L.A. morning show".
And a fantastic morning it is, isn't it ?
It's great out,
and we've got a great lineup,
starting with
the unlikely hero from
last week's fidelity
republic bank hostage standoff.
Please welcome a very
brave man : Egan Foote.
- So, Egan...
- Yes.
- Egan.
- That's me.
The moment that we've
all been waiting for.
You've been trapped in
the bank for over two days,
the S.W.A.T. team comes
busting in, and you...
you manage to take down
your brutal captor
- Randall Reese.
- That's right.
How did you do that ?
Well, carpe diem, Josh.
The day was there, and I seized it.
And you almost took a bullet
from S.W.A.T. in the process.
Uh, uh, lucky, I guess.
I came out of it with a...
slight concussion
and a new lease on life.
Ricky, breakfast is ready.
Now come to the table.
Let's... let's go back a minute
to how the whole thing began,
because we understand that
a 9-1-1 call came
from with inside the bank.
Uh, well, it began with
two men wanting to rob the bank.
Right, but the standoff,
that happened because 9-1-1 was called
and then the police showed up.
Yeah, that's right.
And then all hell broke
loose from there.
- Please help my sister !
- Hey, get off me !
- Ricky, come on.
- Yeah, essentially.
So if you were in
a situation like that again...
- Uh, heaven forbid...
- Have sharon draw up
a motion in limine to keep
the mother's statement out.
Here's the cummins' complaint.
Make sure that it's filed today.
Thank you.
'cause, you know, there's
a lot of speculation
about how the police
and the FBI may have
- mismanaged the situation.
- Do you want me to draft...
Hang on a second.
You're someone who saw
everything that went on inside.
What's your position on that ?
Well, I'm no expert on police procedure,
but as far as I can tell, um...
Well, let's just say,
it seemed like they could've
handled it a lot differently.
Better, I mean.
And what about the cop
who was inside with you ?
Nick Cavanaugh was, uh,
a hero in there.
Without him, I don't know how
we would've gotten through it.
- Sounds like you two are close.
- We all are now.
Come on !
Nobody gets hurt here.
So you all right ?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Well, last night must have
been a good warm-up for you.
The party, you know,
seeing all your friends.
Oh, yeah. I guess.
Listen, honey, if you can't handle it,
you just say the word, I'll take you home.
No, dad, seriously, I gotta
do this sooner or later.
All right ?
That's my girl.
All right, I love you, sweetheart.
- You be good now.
- See you later.
Morning.
Frank Waters, 43,
severe cardiomyopathy.
He's been on a pump
for two months waiting
for a transplant.
U.N.O.S. found a match
yesterday in San Diego.
The transplant should take
about ten hours, so...
His wife is going to need
some hand-holding today.
Where's Frank now ?
I.C.U.
Have you... been up there yet ?
I mean, since Randall's been up there.
No. You ?
No.
Hey, Tessa.
This is our social
worker Lizzie Miller.
How's he doing ?
Um, okay.
He's a... a bit scared,
I think.
Well, that... that's to be expected.
Uh, let me talk to you...
what has to happen now, okay ?
Lizzie.
Lizzie, you coming ?
But that is the thing
about facing your fears.
Seriously.
Well, it's been great having
you here on the show, Egan.
Thank you so much. And before...
you get back to your life,
we understand that there's one
more thing you'd like to say
to our audience at home.
Yes, uh, thank you.
Well, um....
Well, you see, there was, um...
There was one of us...
Her name was Eva Rios...
And she didn't make it
out of there. She was killed.
And she left behind a little boy... Ricky.
He's 6 years old.
His father's in prison.
His aunt Franny...
She was in there with us, too...
Now she's gotta raise him on her own.
They don't have very much money.
And, uh, Eva didn't work at
the bank long enough to
have any pension or
life insurance money or anything, so...
I'm asking those of you
at home who may have an extra
$5 or $10 to please
call this number and,
um, make a donation.
Hey, Mark.
You get a hit on that plate
I asked you to run ?
Just came in.
It's a federal plate.
Bureau, actually.
What's this about ?
You've come to a decision I hope.
Not quite.
You got any idea why the FBI
might be tailing me ?
I imagine they want
to pressure you,
otherwise, you never
would've made them.
Pressure me ?
Everybody wants you to step up, Nick.
Take one for the team.
The FBI can't exactly put
their negotiator out front
for the photo-ops.
They'll settle for you.
So what's next, bugging my phone,
burning a cross on my lawn, what ?
- No, just an extra request.
- What's that ?
The department would like
to set up something for you
at city hall.
The commissioner will be there,
someone from the FBI,
the D.A.'s office.
You'll get your medal
and your promotion...
And you'll also say a few words
about how proud you are
of the job everybody did.
P.R. department typed up
something for you.
You can tweak it a bit,
but you get the gist.
So this isn't just about me
keeping my trap shut.
I gotta be your mouthpiece now.
This is an easy choice, Nick.
You're right.
I quit.
So guess what I came up with.
An expert witness for
the McManus hearing ?
- Close.
- Hmm.
A hearsay exception
for the holloway trial ?
Not holloway.
Hollywood, as in bowl,
as in garden box for Elvis Costello.
Tonight ?
Backstage passes.
You're good.
- I've been told.
- Kathryn.
I have Nick Cavanaugh on the phone.
- We got to prep for Petrocelli.
- All right, I'll be right there.
- Line two.
- Thank you.
- Hey, there.
- I quit my job.
What happened ?
A fed tailed me to
the diner last night.
I spotted him after you left.
The feds ?
They're trying to bully me.
They want me to get out
in front of the cameras
and say that everything
they did was all right.
So you quit ?
What are you gonna do now ?
Go after them.
- The cops ? The feds ?
- Everybody.
Are you still there ?
Yeah, yeah. I'm just, um...
I'm just taking it in.
Somebody has got
to pay for what happened.
Lucas and randall will pay.
Isn't that enough ?
Is that enough for you ?
Look, I...
I know what I said
at the funeral. It's just, um...
I'm trying to move forward.
Well, things happened
in that bank that involve you.
If I talk to the press,
to whoever, they're
gonna come to you.
I just want to know
what I'm up against.
Am I alone in this ?
Fine. I get it.
Time to move on.
Nick.
Can you tell me your name ?
My name's Tom.
You know you're not
supposed to be in here.
I know. I...
How's Frank doing ?
Okay considering he's about
to undergo a heart transplant.
I just wanted to say that I'm sorry
I freaked out this morning,
- left you alone with them.
- It's fine.
You know, I'm not as bad
with the patients as you think.
I wish Randall was dead.
You just gotta put your head
down and do your thing.
They're waiting for me.
Thank you so much for coming in.
We'll let you know one way
or the other next week.
Excuse me, Malcolm.
Yes.
I have Tom's last check here.
Should I just send it
to his home or...
Um, no, his wife wants us
to deposit that directly.
Thank you.
Franny.
What are you doing out here ?
Uh, I came by...
I wanted to thank you
for organizing the fund with Egan.
I wanted to come inside, but...
I can't.
I thought I would try, you know ?
But...
I can't.
Well, you don't have to rush.
There'll always be
a job for you here.
No. Actually, I don't...
I don't think I'll ever
be able to go in there.
Okay. well, I'll, um,
I'll write you a reference,
and I'll make whatever
calls you need.
Oh, uh, I never finished processing
that mortgage application
for the Malones.
It's still in my drawer.
It's under the P.O. forms.
I really wanted to do that,
you know ?
I... I really appreciate
you giving me a chance.
You always gave me a chance.
You always deserved it.
Well, thanks.
Listen, I'll tell you what,
Why don't I go inside
and I'll get your things,
okay ?
Eva, no !
What ?
Monica Turner from the Times.
Okay, thanks.
Monica.
Kathyrn, how's it going ?
Good, fine. Just getting back
into the swing of things.
What's up ?
Well, I'm not sure if there's
a conflict of interest here,
but just wanted
to feel it out with you.
Go ahead.
I got a tip about Nick Cavanaugh.
Yeah ?
Apparently, the bank teller
Eva Rios was shot with his gun.
And I'm also hearing
he was a problem in there...
Butting heads with the negotiator,
impeding the police
in his own department
and the FBI.
Is there any truth to that ?
Where are you getting
this information from ?
You know I can't tell you that.
Is someone on the department
leaking it to you ?
Is it true ?
Let me call you back,
and don't do anything
until you hear from me.
Okay.
Cavanaugh.
I'm with you.
So how's Randall doing ?
The doctors say he'll be
out of I.C.U. tomorrow.
They're calling him Rasputin
- down at the D.A.'s office.
- Funny.
Well, they can
joke all they want.
We need him to live.
Why is that ?
Well, if he dies, the prosecution
will try to pin everything on you.
Which doesn't go so much
with my plan to pin everything on him.
I told you the
robbery was my idea.
And we will deal with the
robbery as a distinct issue.
I'm trying to get you off
on the felony murder charges.
- You do want that, right ?
- Obviously.
Well, we're gonna need
to put some hostages on the stand.
Will any of them
testify on your behalf ?
I don't know.
What about the Jones girl ?
- Felicia is it ?
- What about her ?
I heard she visited
you last night.
Juries love sweet,
teenage faces.
You stay away from her.
- Lucas...
- No, I mean it.
I know you think
I'm gonna be your O.J.,
but you go anywhere near her,
I'll fire you and go back
with the public defender.
Got it ?
I'm not just talking about making
it easier for the customer.
I'm talking about making it
more fulfilling for us.
Corporate will never
go for it, Egan.
What do you mean,
"Corporate will never go for it ?"
How do you know
until we've tried ?
I don't remember calling
a staff meeting.
No, I... I was just, uh...
pitching...
Some of my new
ideas to everybody.
Really ? And what are those ?
Really ? Well, all right,
for starters, um...
A paper-free, internet-based system
that tracks insurance
claims in real time.
Paper-free ?
Yeah, now we'd have some
cash outlay for computer
hardware up front,
but it would pay for itself
in increased efficiency,
not to mention save us from...
from drowning in
pointless triplicate forms.
Don't leave out the most
important part, Egan.
Yes, good. Thank you. Yeah.
It would keep sick people
from having to haggle
for their money all day
when they should be worried
about their treatment.
Well...
I think it's a great idea, Egan,
except for one small problem.
Okay, what's that ?
The inefficiency,
as you call it,
is how we make our profit.
Without it, you're out of a job,
which you'll all be anyway
if you don't get back to work.
And, Egan...
Yeah.
You got any more appearances
I should know about ?
Because I need you here on time.
He's just a jerk.
It's fine.
Just an idea.
Hey !
It's taco Tuesday
at the cafeteria.
You down ?
I'll be there in a minute.
Saline.
I need suction.
Okay.
That does it for the atrial walls,
superior and inferior vena cavaes
and the pulmonary artery.
We'll fix the aorta,
prep the paddles
and get this baby humming.
Let me have a 4-0 prolene.
I said a 4-0, Terry.
This is an aortic anastomosis,
not your stitch-and-bitch group.
Guess some people never change.
And this plan of yours,
this is at what point in the standoff ?
About halfway through it.
After reese had killed
the security guard
and it was clear that
negotiations were going nowhere.
I just want to make clear
that Nick offehimself
as a sole hostage.
He had Reese and Dalton
convinced that they were
gonna make it out of there.
- This plan would've worked.
- Right.
Now about the security guard,
is it true that you had
an opportunity to get him out,
- but that your mother was released ?
- Now that was protocol, Monica.
The man was wounded.
He was conscious and alert.
Dalton wouldn't have
allowed it anyway.
By the way, the real question is...
Why negotiations broke down
so badly that Nick
had to be the one to deal with it on the inside.
Hello, Monica.
Good to see you.
Deputee District Attorney.
Nick.
Kathryn, can I borrow you
for a second ?
Yeah, sure. Excuse me.
- What are you doing here ?
- Walls have ears, Kat.
The question is
what are you doing here ?
- Helping a friend.
- Helping him do what ?
Make our case against
Dalton and Reese more difficult
by casting the cops as bad guys ?
Saying that the cops
on the outside screwed up
shouldn't hurt your case
if you do your job right.
But I appreciate your concern
for your career.
Well, it might do you some good
to think about your own.
Look, if you side with him,
you will alienate everyone
in the L.A.P.D and the FBI,
not to mention quite
a few people in your own office.
And you can certainly kiss
any political aspirations
you have good-bye.
That'll be gone.
They were gonna throw
him to the wolves.
I didn't have a choice.
Look, I know what
you went through together.
No, I don't think you do.
Kat, hey,
I understand you feel you owe
him in some way, okay ?
But do you even have any
idea what you are getting into
with this guy, who he is ?
Is there something we should
all be talking about ?
- Nick...
- No, no.
It's all right, Kathryn.
We may as well get everything out
in the open here, right, Nick ?
I'm all ears.
I was just wondering
if you bothered telling her
about your past.
What about it ?
Well, maybe about
your gambling problem,
The one that blew a huge
case for your department
and put other cops at risk.
The one that landed you
on probation
and got you his close
to getting tossed out on your ass.
Now you think Monica Turner
doesn't know about that ?
Isn't gonna lead with that
in a story like this ?
I think she's gonna lead
with what's relevant.
My past has nonothing
to do with anything.
Well, I think that's a little naive.
You do what you gotta do.
But I'd appreciate it if you'd
let me know either way.
Gambling problem ?
I've got an ex-wife, too.
She's not gonna say
nice things about me.
Next time you want me
to go out on a limb with you,
you better be straight with me.
I'm sorry.
Where were we ?
Are you still interviewing
for a new teller ?
Tellers now.
Franny quit.
Oh, well.
I never thought she'd go back.
Well, anyway, I haven't
found anyone yet
to replace them.
You know, the therapist said
it might be helpful
if you go in there
with Felicia at some point.
It might be good for you, too.
You know, to talk to somebody.
Or you could talk to me.
I know I can.
Do you ?
Felicia.
What ?
You don't want
to be here, do you ?
Mm, you're good.
You know, I feel like people
don't even believe me.
Believe you ?
That I lost my memory.
Like who ?
I don't know, people at school,
my mom sometimes.
Well, why wouldn't
people believe you ?
Maybe they think I'm trying
to get attention or something.
Are you ?
So you don't believe me either ?
That's just great.
Felicia, I didn't say...
I mean, what the hell
do you think I been
coming here every day for ?
Is there anyone else
you can talk to,
Any of the other hostages ?
I've tried a little, but...
But what ?
Nobody wants to deal with me.
Everybody just wants
the whole thing to go away.
Okay.
Lookin' good, folks.
Lookin' good.
I'm just gonna
give him one last...
I got a bleeder.
What's the B.P., Mike ?
Uh, 80 and falling. 70.
It's the aorta.
Everything else is holding.
Oh, stay with me now, Frank.
- Save her ! Oh, my god !
- 70. 65.
There she is.
I've got it under control.
I got you Franck, I got you.
Stop the music, please.
Can you tell me your name ?
- My name's Tom.
- Okay, Tom.
I had my doubts about
Dr. Kates, you know,
for him to operate
so soon after...
But, um, Frank was adamant.
Dr. Kates would never have
performed surgery
if he wasn't ready.
Yeah, that's what Frank said.
He, uh, has so much
faith in people.
There were some minor complications,
but he's looking good now.
He's stable.
Thank you !
Thank you.
I didn't know what
I was gonna do.
How I was gonna raise Chloe if...
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
You have five minutes.
I heard you and Kathryn Hale
talked to a reporter today.
So ?
That was a big mistake.
We'll see.
What are you trying
to prove here ?
Is this about the girl, what ?
Her name is Eva.
Look, mistakes were made.
We all regret them.
But there's plenty of
blame to go around,
including some for you.
I never said any different.
So you want to be
a crusader now,
With no job, no paycheck ?
You got a habit
to support, my friend.
Is that what
you called me here for ?
You may not care
about your own ass,
but how about your friends ?
Your buddy Egan Foote...
He carried an unregistered,
concealed weapon into the bank.
That's a felony.
What are you doin', Pete ?
And then, of course, there's
Eva's sister Franny.
I bet you didn't know
she had an ounce of pot
and ten hits of ecstasy
in her purse that day.
Yeah.
We found it after
we took the bank.
We've been overlooking it,
considering the circumstances.
But if we decide
to press charges,
she could lose custody
of that kid.
We just haven't had the heart
to do that so far.
It's too late.
We already talked to the Times.
The story can be killed.
All you have to do is call
the reporter and recant.
There are bigger forces
at work here than me.
Take your medal.
Take your promotion.
Get on with your life.
...adding a T-9 report
to all arthroscopic biopsies.
We'll bill another $2 per claim.
But the T-9 doesn't add
information. It's pointless.
Not to our shareholders, it's not.
But we're profiting
from other people's pain.
Well... yeah.
If you don't like it,
go join the peace corps.
Now I've had enough of all of
this second-guessing today.
You're an employee.
Your job is to hear what
the company has to say
and keep your mouth shut.
You don't have the right
to talk to her like that.
Excuse me ?
You don't have the right
to talk to anyone like that.
Really ? I didn't realize you were
suddenly in charge here, Foote.
You're just afraid, Brian.
It's okay.
Bullies are always afraid.
You never listen to our ideas
because you're threatened by us.
You don't stand up to corporate
because you're scared of them.
Don't you ever
just want to let go,
take charge of this place,
take charge of your life,
for Pete's sake, huh ?
Go for the gusto, Brian.
Do something impetuous.
You're fired, Egan.
How's that for impetuous ?
Now go be a hero
somewhere else.
Ricky, I told you
not to do that !
Why not ?
Because we agreed,
if I let you stay home from
school today that you'd behave.
Ricky !
Huh. You don't have to keep
checking up on me, you know ?
I was in the neighborhood.
I'm just trying
to organize a bit.
Yeah, sure.
How's it goin' there, Ricky ?
Pretty cool car. Is that... Whoa !
Ricky !
Sorry. I... I didn't know
what to do there.
It's okay. He's just being a brat.
I'll be right back. Hold on.
You've reached the home
of Franny Rios...
Eva Rios and...
Come on, Ricky.
Don't be shy.
Ricky Rios.
Leave a message and have
a beautiful day. Thanks.
Franny, it's me.
I want to see
how Ricky's doing.
If you're there, pick up.
You know, I'm the kid's father.
I deserve to know
what's going on there.
I guess I'll call you tomorrow.
You've reached the home
of Franny Rios...
Eva Rios and...
Come on, Ricky.
Don't be shy.
Ricky Rios.
Leave a message and have
a beautiful day. Thanks.
Oh, go, go, go, go, go.
Eva's ex called.
He, uh, left a message
on the machine.
Oh, okay.
Is everything okay with him ?
Yeah, I think he's trying
to get custody of Ricky back.
Do you have a lawyer ?
No. I was...
I was actually thinking
of calling Kathryn.
I thought maybe she could help.
I'm sure she would.
Are you hungry ?
Can I make you
something to eat ?
Sure.
Okay.
Where are we, Mike ?
He's in asystole. We intubated,
but I have no pressure.
Gave him two rounds of EPI, no response.
We've got tamponade.
14-gauge needle on a 60.
Come on, Frank !
Help her, please !
Let's get him to the O.R.
There's no time.
He's been down for 15 minutes.
Then we're gonna open him here.
Prep and give me the wire cutters.
- Dr. Kates, he's gone.
- Give me the cutters !
Okay. here we go now, Frank.
Come on !
Come on, Frank !
We've done everything we could.
Call it.
Time of death... 2:48 p.m.
Hey, Dalton.
you got a visitor.
- Who is it ?
- Felicia Jones.
He says he can't see you.
What ?
Why not ?
I'm not a concierge, miss.
Why did you do that ?
Why ? !
Why did you do that ? Why ? !
No ! No ! Please !
I'd say congratulations...
I wish you wouldn't.
You're not gonna tell me
what turned this ?
No.
I guess we go back
to our lives now.
I guess so.
We've got a little
surprise here.
Hey, buddy.
Congratulations.
Oh, Ms. Hale, we didn't realize
you were gonna be here.
It would be great
to get a shot with you.
Actually, I...
I have to be back in court.
It'll just take a minute.
No, thanks.
I... I really have to go.
The two heroes.
Transcript Made By Raceman
Subtitles Made By The Bloc Team
Synchronised By Tagne
For www.forom.com