Précédemment...
What's a rich boy like you
doing this stuff for anyway?
I need cash, OK?
I'm Ella Simms.
Junior publicist.
All my life all I wanted
was to be a doctor.
- I'm concerned about your finances.
- I can work it out.
I didn't peg you as someone
who wanted to pursue
this line of work
on a regular basis.
I can't believe that girl
had to be the one to find her.
- She's lived here 30 seconds?
- There's a hostess that just quit at Coal.
- I could put in a good word for you.
- You'd do that?
Who's this?
I'm the girl you kicked out of here
yesterday. Is the job still available?
We're getting married.
I'm only about to have a sit-down with a
guy whose films are over a billion dollars.
I'm Kendra, his development exec. I have a
lot of say in how we develop the scripts.
I just want you to tell me that you and Riley
have not crossed the line of friendship.
She kissed me,
not the other way around.
She kissed you?
So there's nothing going on
between you two?
You are the only guy
I want to be with.
- I was scared I missed you.
- What happened to your plans?
Just decided
it was an opportunity
I couldn't pass up.
You did not just say
The Killing was a better
film than Reservoir Dogs.
Reservoir Dogs is so
much more polished.
Dogs totally ripped off Kubrick.
Most of Tarantino's so-called
masterpieces
are overrated knockoffs.
Yes, he appropriates.
From like, everybody.
What makes him a genius
is how he puts those
pieces together.
I love how one of the most
original voices
I've heard recently is defending
one of the most unoriginal.
But enough about Tarantino.
I want to know more
about Jonah Miller.
From the beginning.
The Jonah Miller story...
just starts out a little slow,
but then it has a few good twists.
* Did you hear me?
* Hello *
* Hello, hello,
don't disturb me * 86...
* I don't think you heard me,
so I gotta... *
And here she is again
returning home from yet
another late night
looking absolutely fabulous.
What are you doing here?
I thought you had a client dinner.
Client cancelled.
Anyway,
I need all the deets
on who you're getting dolled up for,
so spill.
Who's the lucky guy?
Believe me, there is no lucky guy.
Just a lot of unlucky first dates.
You are being strangely secretive.
Are you?
Or perhaps a married
doctor?
No married man.
Doctor or otherwise.
Drop it.
You know, Lor, gossip may be
my bread and butter at work,
but off duty,
I can actually keep a secret.
I've been through the same thing
that you're dealing with,
at least once.
I appreciate that.
But my life's just
not tabloid material.
And he is running faster than
I've ever seen the guy run,
and there's this totally
insane saliva-dripping Doberman
right on his heels.
I'm in the car, yelling,
"Travis, just drop
the chicken, man!"
Oh, my God.
Please tell me he made it.
Inches.
Doggie birthday parties,
never again.
That is where I draw the line.
That is hilarious.
And really sad.
Yeah. I guess it's that combination
that makes Living in Reverse
so heartfelt, too.
I have to say,
it is so refreshing
to meet a Hollywood executive
who gets my vision.
I just said
"gets my vision" out loud.
Like, without any irony.
On a scale
of one to total tool,
where do I fall?
Well, the scale I'm looking at
rates you in pretty high at funny,
honest...
charming...
... sexy.
Actually...
I'm engaged.
You're engaged?
Why didn't you tell me?
I would've never...
I know. I-I should've.
I just... I got so wrapped up
in the moment.
The moment? We've been
here for an hour.
Look, Jonah, don't break
your poor fiancée's heart.
If you're not ready to take
the plunge, tell her now.
Oh, no, I'm ready
to take the plunge.
Then why did you kiss me?
Check.
Dark_Chii, Just-In, Luoleilina, P$iKo^^,
SirHill et WoLF971 présentent...
Oh, my God, Auggie,
that smells amazing.
Why are you still here? We're closed.
You hungry?
I...
could definitely eat.
My dinner was cherries and olives.
That looks so beautiful.
Well, forget how it looks.
Close your eyes.
Come on, close your eyes.
You don't trust me?
You're the chef.
Too much going on?
- Maybe I should dial back some of the thyme.
- It was delicious. The flavors,
they're so layered.
Is that saffron?
Someone is developing a palate.
Mason, the owner, is coming tomorrow
to weigh in on the winter menu.
- If I could get a dish on it...
- Hostess, then bartender.
Don't tell me: you're
the next Julia Child?
Marcello, you have to try this
dish Auggie invented.
- It's unreal.
- What is it?
Seared scallops
with oven-roasted tomato couscous
and a saffron beurre blanc.
Auggie, what were you thinking?
The saffron will bring out
the iodine taste
of the scallops.
That's why I used caramelized shallots,
for sweetness,
and fresh thyme to punctuate.
I'd have used a little less thyme.
Chef, I-I know
you're looking for dishes
for the new menu...
Your point?
I was wondering,
if I make the adjustment,
- maybe it could be a contender?
- Not quite ready for prime time.
But didn't spit it out for a change.
- I loved it.
- I'd order it.
Not at this restaurant you won't.
Want to get high?
I want to do whatever
you want to do.
You go first.
This where all the cool
kids come to hang out
and impress the ladies
with their skunk bud?
What skunk bud?
Come on, David.
Do you think I really give
a crap about the joint?
I'm investigating a homicide.
Look, we've been through this.
- I told you everything I know.
- I'm not so sure.
I didn't kill Sydney.
But your alibi's tied to someone
who was an accessory in her death.
The night of the murder,
Ella Simms hired a private investigator
to break into Sydney Andrews'
apartment.
Theory is, things turned bad.
Now, you admit that you weren't
with Ella that night,
and we can arrest her
for obstruction of justice.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
But trust me, Ella didn't have
anything to do
with the murder.
Protecting your friends...
that's honorable.
It's also going to get you
in a lot of trouble.
Aiding and abetting kind of trouble.
If El killed Syd, do you really
think that I'd protect her?
I hate the person that did this.
Syd and I, we had a connection.
A real connection.
The kind where doors slam
and neighbors file noise complaints.
So, not every relationship's
picture-perfect.
She was there for me.
I want to make you proud,
then I-I just...
I screwed up.
I can't help it, Mom.
I just... I miss you so much.
Here.
I'm okay.
Your mom?
I had friends
whose parents had died,
and I felt bad,
but I never really got it
until... until I joined
that messed up club.
- Are your parents buried here?
- My father.
I don't think you ever get over it.
You just have to try
to deal however you can.
But...
the last thing you need
is advice from a stranger.
No, it's okay.
Everyone else says
that time makes things better.
You're the only one with
the guts to tell it like it is.
My name is Sydney.
David.
Do you want to get some breakfast?
Just tell me you and Ella were never
together the night of the murder.
That'd be a lie.
What else is a lie?
You live like a rock star
without a single deposit from
a trust fund or your old man.
You don't cooperate with me,
I'm gonna eventually find out
how you can afford
this life of leisure.
Where were you last night?
Didn't you get my text?
Said I'd be back late.
I did, and I tried waiting up.
Did you get my
message about Anton V?
I got it on my way home.
I replied.
An emoticon?
It's hardly an
enthusiastic response.
Last night when you
left, you were upset
about Auggie.
I-I didn't want to go
to bed without talking.
Must have been some
walk you went on.
Where'd you go?
Just, you know, kind
of wandered over
to Sunset for a drink.
Next time, please wake me
up when you get home, okay?
You've got to be kidding me. What?
Travis just blew off
the wedding today.
He said he broke his wrist
playing Wii.
Is that even possible?
Yeah, anything's possible with Travis.
I don't believe this.
There's no way I'm going
to get this footage
they want today on my own.
I happen to know a girl
who used to assist her
boyfriend back in college.
From what I remember,
she was pretty good at it.
Thank you, Riles,
but I'll be... I'll be fine.
Senior year.
The chancellor's inauguration.
Was that not the funniest day ever?
Hilarious.
Practically every frame of B
camera was wobbling exactly in time
with your giggling. Come on, when is the
last time we spent a whole day together?
No, I'm on my way now.
Get him a private room.
A private floor, if possible.
Ella, Defcon five.
Let's move now.
I haven't seen you this stressed
since Allegra Abrams flashed
the entire press corps opening night
of Sundance. Jessie Roberts OD'd.
Apparently, he thought oxy
would help bring him down
from an all-night coke-fest. Please
tell me we're not headed to ID the body.
No, he's stable for now.
Just get a team together.
We can't have the public knowing
how many drugs are fueling
their favorite all-American smile.
Choppers are buzzing
ULA as we speak.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Jessie's at ULA?
Let me handle this.
Ella, if we don't spin this exactly
right, we're gonna lose him as a client.
Caleb, my bestie, slash,
roommate works at ULA.
I'll have this thing buried
before the nurses bring Jessie
his Jell-O cup.
The owner's here.
He just valet'd his car.
Thanks for the heads-up.
It's great to see you.
Knew I was coming,
so I didn't eat breakfast.
Mason, let's taste the winter menu.
Think a global
bazaar of flavors.
Lots of small plates.
Smaller plates mean smaller profits.
I want high-ticket entrees.
That's funny you should say that.
One came to me last night
in a flash of inspiration.
- Scallops.
- Got it. Sear them.
We'll pair them with
an oven-roasted tomato couscous.
How about a sauce, Chef?
Saffron beurre blanc.
Caramelize some shallots,
and throw in a some fresh thyme
to balance it out.
My mouth is watering.
By the time we're back from
choosing a bottle from the cellar,
it'll be ready, right, Auggie?
Yes, Chef.
Can't wait to taste it.
That one sounds like a real winner.
Did that just really happen?
That's like cooking plagiarism.
You can't let him get away with that.
I don't have a choice.
It's my job to make
Marcello look good.
There's a chain of command
in the kitchen, and if I ever want
to get promoted, I got to obey it.
From here, it looks like
your chain is being yanked.
Look at this place.
It's so beautiful.
The flowers are so amazing.
Amazing.
Can you believe that this is
going to be us soon?
No, I really can't.
What is it?
You barely said a word in the car.
I was just, you know,
going over shots in my head.
These weddings are tricky.
We drove past three
comic book stores,
and you didn't even joke
about wanting to stop.
I know when something's up.
We should probably set up
these tripods.
Let's talk about it.
Otherwise, let's try
to make today fun, okay?
I mean, there's no reason
why it can't be.
You know, you're right.
Let's try to have fun.
Good.
You set up the mama tripod.
I get the big daddy one.
Where do you want me?
Oh, my gosh, right here. Kidding.
Hi, champ.
Is this the part
where you yell at me?
Later. But first,
how are you?
I'm fine.
I don't even know what happened.
- I swear, I just did, like, two lines.
- And ended up in the hospital?
Jessie, you're out of control.
It was nothing.
It was just some bad blow.
You keep telling yourself that,
but I am not going to let your
legacy be a True Hollywood Story
- of "Oops, I Did It and Died."
- Does everyone know?
Does... does my mom know?
The rumors are starting to swirl.
Nothing that's not beyond repair.
Do you have any allergies?
I-I don't know.
Penicillin.
Perfect.
I am going to lock you in here.
No texting, no tweeting,
no phone calls, okay?
I'm gonna need my video games.
Fine.
But more importantly,
no more putting any
of that crap up your nose.
Otherwise, you're going to have
to power lunch with River Phoenix.
Who's River Phoenix?
God, kill me now.
I got a page. W...
How is my favorite doctor?
- You paged me?
- I did. Come on, let's go chat.
Listen, Lauren,
I need a little favor.
Mm-hmm.
Jessie Roberts is one
of our biggest clients, okay?
He is Zac Efron
and the Jonas Brothers wrapped
into one squeaky clean,
heartthrobby package.
Squeaky clean?
That kid had so many
chemicals in his system,
it's a miracle he woke up.
Which is exactly why
we are in crisis mode,
and exactly why you could
help us save the day again.
- What can I do?
- I just need you
to create new admissions documents
saying that Jessie had an
allergic reaction to penicillin.
Jessie does have the allergy, if anyone
checks, it'll be completely legit.
- It'll be completely unethical.
- And a felony.
I just need to buy a little time
until another scandal breaks out,
and then Jessie can move
forward with his life.
And I swear,
I will personally escort him in to
Promises as soon as he gets out of here.
Come here.
Do you hear yourself
right now, Ella?
I am busting my ass at med school
so that one day I can take an oath
that says, "First do no harm."
So, who's harmed?
The patient, the hospital,
the doctor, the truth.
You want more?
This could work in everyone's favor,
including you.
What do you mean?
How?
WPK can make a donation
to the hospital.
Jessie could come by once a month,
visit the children's floors.
What if I offered you
a financial incentive?
Say, a couple thousand dollars?
What did our friendly
neighborhood nurse have to say?
She won't budge.
And you tried everything?
Opened with altruism,
preyed upon her soft spot
for sick kids,
and then, trumped it all
with a generous financial plan.
Clearly, I don't know my
friend as well as I thought.
Well, how much did you throw at her?
A few grand.
If you're gonna try and buy somebody
off, you don't do it with chump change.
We're gonna charge this
to Jessie's account.
Go back, do a little multiplication.
Fifty.
Thousand?
That is a week of walking around
money for Jessie.
We don't have time
for negotiation games.
I'm not sure that there's
a deal to be made.
There is always a deal to be made.
Get it done.
We need to talk.
David, whatever it is, I don't
have time for it, all right?
I'm in the middle
of a major spin cycle
for a major client.
Detective Rodriguez cornered me
in the courtyard last night.
I always thought
he had a crush on you.
He thinks that you had
something to do with the murder.
And he wants me to admit
that our alibi's a sham,
and if I don't, he's gonna find
a reason to throw me in jail.
He can't do that.
I mean, he doesn't have proof
that we weren't together.
He did tell me a funny story
about you meeting with a P.I.
the night that Sydney was murdered,
hiring him to break into her place.
You weren't with a married client
that night, were you?
Why did you lie to me, El?
I know you didn't kill her.
Yeah, I didn't kill her,
but that P.I. I hired--
he was a hothead, David.
If Syd found him
in her apartment, he easily
could have killed her,
and if he did, well,
that would make yours truly
an accessory to murder.
He didn't kill her, Ella.
How do you know?
I just know.
Last time I checked,
you're not a psychic.
So, why don't you tell me
what's going on, David?
I blacked out that night.
You know how I get
when I'm that drunk.
Landing in bed with
some double-bagger...
After you told me that Syd
was sleeping with my dad...
I was so mad at her, El.
I know, I know.
You hate the pretentious idiots
who go to art openings,
but... I'm dragging you to this one.
And when we come back,
I will make it worth your while.
Why, Syd?
David, let go of my arm.
Why did you have to use me?
What are you talking about?
You were sleeping with my father!
He calls it off, so you
come after me to make him jealous?
I loved you.
At the cemetery,
you knew exactly who I was.
And your father... I bet
he's alive and well, isn't he?
You'll say and do
anything to get what you want.
You're nothing but a pathetic whore.
And you are a spoiled brat.
David. Do you really think
that you could have done it?
Honestly, El?
I don't know.
50 bucks says the band inside plays
"Celebration" within the first 3 songs.
All right. I'll take that bet.
Double or nothing.
The other two songs will be
"Hot Hot Hot"
and "Unchained Melody."
All right. You're on.
I guess we should start thinking
about bands for our wedding.
Bands?
Bands are way too unpredictable,
and then they take breaks,
and you have to feed them.
DJ all the way.
What are you talking about?
Bands are so much more fun to dance to.
Maybe after the
45-minute sound check.
Would you...
maybe consider having a band
because it's what I want?
Now you want me to start considering
the other person's feelings?
Dangerous precedent.
What is that supposed to mean?
You don't think
I consider your feelings?
- Videographers.
- Get ready.
And be sure you get close-ups
of the vows.
They'll always want to remember
how in love they were
on their wedding day.
Hey, Lauren.
Yo, woman.
You would make, like,
the best porn doctor ever.
Fancy.
I like it.
Oh, my God.
My God.
What are you doing?
I was just going to ask you
the same thing, pretty woman.
The late nights.
The amazing wardrobe.
The mystery men.
How did I not
figure this out sooner?
Figure what out?
My dad sent me that money
for school.
Who's your dad, Tony Soprano?
This is a brick of cold cash.
He won it playing poker.
He's been playing
every Wednesday night,
ever since I was a kid.
Lor, it's the middle
of the afternoon,
and you're dressed
like a million bucks.
Which better be in the ballpark
of what you're charging.
I was at a luncheon, okay?
An interns special honors lunch.
And I resent you interrogating me
like I'm some kind of...
Prostitute?
You're right. I'm sorry.
Having said that,
if you help my client,
maybe I can relieve you
from some of your intern luncheons.
You're not seriously still trying to get
me to change Jessie's hospital records?
I'm confused.
You refuse to screw the system
just a little bit,
but you have no problem at all
screwing...
Seriously, stop.
We're offering you
$50,000.
No more having
to get money from Daddy.
You can pay for school yourself.
My career comes first.
Thought you of all people
would understand that.
I vow to always be honest with you.
To never keep a secret from you.
'Cause sharing my life means
sharing everything with you,
the good and the bad.
And knowing that whatever
we come up against,
and no matter what we go through,
how tough things get,
we'll handle it... together.
That was so sweet.
I was actually tearing up
during the vows.
Yeah, I saw that.
I kissed someone last night.
What?
Her name's Kendra.
She works for Andrew Misher.
Oh, God.
I had the same exact reaction
when I found out you kissed Auggie.
But the difference between
us is, you carried on
like nothing ever happened,
and I feel like absolute crap.
I can explain the Auggie thing.
Now you want to explain it.
That blows my mind, since you've
been going out of your way
to keep it from me for...
how many weeks?
You have no idea how much I wanted to
come out and tell you. But you didn't!
And, meanwhile, I had to tell you,
because it's just been
eating at me all day.
The Auggie thing...
it was meaningless.
It was a stupid mistake.
It wasn't worth telling you,
and then fighting about,
and then...
Finding out how awful it feels
to rip someone's heart out?
If I could take it back,
Jonah, I would.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what else to say.
There's nothing else to say.
I've got a reception to shoot.
Where is it?
It was right here.
Oh, no, it's gone.
Someone killed
this porterhouse twice.
I said medium rare.
I'm on it.
Everything okay?
You... you seem
a little stressed out.
Yeah, I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
I was wondering if I could
talk to you for a minute.
Do you mind, Violet?
No, not at all.
What's going on?
Why did you tell Jonah we kissed?
Riley, I'm so sorry about that.
The way he was talking,
it sounded like you already told him.
I completely screwed up.
Yeah, so did I.
By getting drunk that night.
Obviously, if I were sober,
that would have never happened, ever.
It was a one time thing.
We just... we got caught up
in the moment.
There was no moment, Auggie.
That's what I'm trying to say.
It will never happen again.
I know.
Because...
I don't think we should
hang out anymore.
It's ruining my relationship.
What, so no coffee, no jogging,
no doing what friends do?
I'm getting married...
to Jonah.
I love him, and it bothers him
when we hang out.
I'm sorry.
It's the way it has to be.
You know I care about you, Auggie.
Please tell me you understand.
It makes complete sense.
I totally get it.
Finally.
Let me see the documents.
I got the Smoking Gun on standby.
Plan "B."
You ready? It's good.
What the hell are you talking about?
What happened to plan "A"?
Where are the medical records?
Turns out my friend's a lot
more stubborn than I thought.
I am as shocked as you are.
You said you live with this rse.
Dig up everything you can find.
Malpractice suits,
test scores, what...
I have a better idea.
We let the story out...
exactly how it is.
The truth.
I'm sorry.
Did you get your hands
on Jessie's stash
and ingest all of it?
Look, paying off hospitals,
pretending like none of this ever
happened... we'd only be enabling him.
Is this a plan "B"
or an intervention?
Both.
Look, this kid's life has
to come before his career,
and if we bury it,
it's only a matter of time
before he ends up back in this
hospital getting his stomach pumped.
Plus, you and I both know
that there is a solid chance
that some tabloid has
a hospital worker on payroll.
At least this way
we control the story.
Exactly.
And if Jessie is spoon-fed
a healthy dose
of public humiliation
and goes through rehab,
not only will he be healthy,
but the baby-faced tweenybopper
turns into a leading man.
It's risky... but inspired.
I'm gonna go make some phone calls.
Oh, and Caleb, for the
record, my friend...
she's not a nurse. She's going
to be one of the finest doctors
this hospital has ever had on staff.
Deglaze, don't torch the place.
It's under control, Chef.
I don't taste the thyme.
Great, I'll just put it back
to the way I originally had it.
I don't need attitude.
And from now on, when you're on shift,
no ducking out to whisper sweet nothings
to your exotic girlfriend.
She's just a friend.
Come on.
I saw the way you two were staring
into each other's eyes,
which was fine because...
I couldn't stop staring at her ass.
Don't talk about her like
she's a piece of meat.
She's not a piece of meat.
She's sweet like dessert.
You up for sharing?
Just stay back, stay back.
Oh, my God, Auggie! Stop!
Get off of me! Get off of me!
Calm down, calm down.
Look, I'm not exactly the
best company right now.
You left your knives
at the restaurant.
I knew you'd want them.
Thanks.
Who needs Coal?
You are way too good for that place.
And Marcello... he had it coming.
That guy is a total dick.
I just lost control
like I was out of my body.
I couldn't stop.
You don't need to hear this.
I'm your friend.
You can tell me anything.
Whatever you need.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have.
Yes, you should.
Look what was just turned in.
Construction worker
found it at a site in Van Nuys.
Blade size is consistent
with Sydney Andrews' wounds.
Get it to the lab.
Put a rush on it.
I'm so sorry, Syd.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, tomorrow's great.
I look forward to it, okay.
I'll be there.
So I was just at Coal.
Telling Auggie that we can't
hang out with each other anymore.
I didn't tell you to do that.
I wouldn't tell you to do that.
I know; I wanted to.
We come first.
Was that another job?
It was...
Kendra, actually.
You're seeing her tomorrow?
To work on my pitch.
You know, for Andrew Misher.
I just told one of my closest friends that
I'm going to have nothing to do with him.
I didn't ask you to do that.
I wanted
to show you how much
you matter to me,
and you are in here making plans
with some girl you kissed.
This is my career.
I'm not going to stop working
with a development executive
just because you and I
are having trouble.
You're obviously not going to
feel guilty about it either.
This is the only producer
who cares about my film
in this town.
I can't afford
to just walk away from that.
My relationship with Kendra... from now
on, it's... it's strictly professional.
Now, if you just want to maybe...
I don't know... trust me, fine,
but if not, I don't...
I don't know what to say.
What is happening to us?
I feel like we are
on two trains heading
in two completely
opposite directions.
And it's bigger than
Auggie or Kendra.
I feel like...
ever since I asked you to marry me,
things have just been...
off.
We have our issues; everyone does.
Relationships aren't always
easy, but come on, it's us.
Jonah, I am willing to
do something about it.
Are you?
I want to save us.
I hate fighting with you.
Fighting with you sucks.
Whatever this... this place
that we're in right now,
it sucks.
If I could just...
if I could erase
everything that's happened over
the last couple days, I would.
I can't.
So where do we go from here?
Lor, it's rare I say
these words, but...
I'm sorry.
Walking into ULA,
trying to buy your signature,
I don't know what I was thinking,
but I'm sorry
for even thinking it and...
I-I'm even more sorry for assuming
that you might go along with it.
I promise I will never ask you
to compromise
your doctor's ethics again.
Unless it involves
a future prescription pad.
I saw Jessie's story break
on the news.
Yeah, genius, right?
A few Psas, he'll be
the next Robert Downey Jr.
But... you were right.
The best thing for him
was to come clean.
So I hope you're not sharing
your ridiculous theories
about me with the whole world.
No, I didn't say a word
about my ridiculous theories,
and I won't bring them up again...
to anyone, including you.
But if you're ready
to talk about it, I'm here,
and if you're never ready
to talk about it,
I will still be here.
There's nothing to talk about.
Understood.
Now, can we go watch
some movies?
How about a Julia Roberts marathon?
Okay, you make one more Pretty
Woman joke, I will kill you.
Hey, I was going to say
Steel Magnolias.
Closest I come to that crying
thing you people sometimes do.