Previously...
She moves in, and Sydney's dead.
Okay, the girl's a little weird,
but that doesn't
make her a murderer.
There's a hostess
that just quit at Coal.
If I can put in
a good word for you...
We're getting married, guys.
All my life all I wanted
was to be a doctor.
I went on this fancy dinner with
this guy. He offered me $5,000
to have sex with him.
I'm Ella Simms, junior publicist.
Jonah, you are
a hugely-talented filmmaker.
What's a rich boy like
you doing this stuff for?
Look, I need cash, okay?
David, what happened?
I borrowed a buddy
of mine's bike, spun it out.
Your injuries are completely
inconsistent with your story.
Anton V wants you to
model for his new line.
Ella has a thing for you. - You think
Ella's trying to come between us
when you and Auggie are, like...?
Friends?
Oh, God.
You can come to me with anything.
We're not gonna make it
if we just keep secrets
from each other.
No more secrets.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Amazing. Oh, this is wonderful.
I love it.
It's heaven.
Oh, it's gorgeous.
Work it. That's it.
Do I look tired?
I got, like,
an hour of sleep last night.
No. What, pre-photo shoot jitters?
Your smile could melt
the polar ice caps.
Okay? That lens is
gonna love you today.
Well, it doesn't make me feel
any less guilty for telling
my students
that their teacher
has a case of the sniffles.
So what? You go a couple
of days without a gold star.
Not the end of the world.
A little white lie not gonna hurt you,
especially
if we're getting ten grand
for you to pose in a pair of jeans.
Oh, my God, isn't your huge
meeting at Paramount today?
Why am I the only one
having an anxiety attack?
I guess I'm just good
at hiding my nerves.
I mean,
I'm only about to have a sit-down
with a guy whose films have
grossed over a billion dollars.
Do you realize, if Andrew Misher
turns Living in Reverse into a feature,
this could be huge for me.
Nothing would make me happier.
But for the record,
I don't need to see your
name in the opening credits
to know that I am
marrying the perfect guy.
We wouldn't even be daydreaming
about any opening credits
if you hadn't talked
me up to that agent.
What are you doing?
They're back.
- The sparrows?
- Yeah. See the eggs?
You know what that means?
That you win the bet.
And that I have
the honor of bringing you
- lattes for the next week.
- Lucky me.
What are you guys looking at?
Oh, nothing. We were just, uh...
we had a bet whether or not
these sparrows would be back.
Oh, how sweet.
Shouldn't you be in
a classroom right now?
Actually, I'm taking the day off.
I'm sort of working this
shoot for Anton V jeans.
Well, like, as a photo assistant?
Like as a model.
No way.
A model?
Guess I'm just used to you in
a ponytail and running shorts.
Well, that's sort of
why they hired me.
The campaign is "Real
People Wear Real Denim."
Anton saw me at one
of Jonah's jobs, and,
I don't know,
wanted to photograph me.
I don't blame him.
I don't know.
All those people
staring at you.
Sounds totally stressful.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I better go. The shoot
is way out in Malibu.
Well, you're going to do great.
So...
I hate to be the neighbor who is,
like, always
asking for a cup of sugar,
but I just got this new furniture,
and it's in, like, 200 pieces.
Yeah, I could probably
help you out with that.
Thank you so much.
I seriously didn't know
what I was going to
do if you said no.
Yeah, I, uh... I think
I should be free after work,
so, I guess I could
stop by after that.
Perfect.
Okay.
Riley? Miss Richmond?
- You better have a tardy slip.
- You're here?
WPK wanted me to hold your
hand through your first shoot,
but so far, I've only had to
make excuses for the late model.
There was an accident on PCH.
- Where's Anton?
- Driving in from downtown.
No wonder he's running late.
Next time, just leave a
couple hours earlier, okay?
This is a big deal, Riley.
You could have missed a lot more
than just the Pledge of Allegiance.
Remember, you look good,
I look good.
Now, come on, let's go.
Look at you.
No scars, no bruising.
- Looks like you're gonna live, after all.
- Thanks to you, I'm a new man.
Just no more fistfights, all right?
- Doctor's orders.
- Can't make any promises.
Might want to tend to this one.
These people.
God. I've told them,
like, ten times there's
been some mistake.
They keep sending me
these stupid notices.
The bold-faced "Past Due" on that
envelope looks pretty serious.
It's nothing to be
embarrassed about.
It's not like you're
the first person
who's ever fallen behind
on a tuition payment.
Right. This is from the guy
who's never worried
about a bill in his life. Nice.
How much do you need?
It's fine.
They've given me till the end
of semester to pay in full,
and I've already made a lot
of headway, so it's-it's fine.
How much?
$20,000.
Let me loan it to you.
What?!
- There's no way.
- Straight up.
No interest.
There's got to be some benefit
in knowing a kid with
a trust fund, right?
That's a really generous offer,
but even with a trust fund,
you can afford to spare
that kind of money?
When they're gonna kick the best doctor
I've ever had out of med school, I can.
But money and friends...
That can get complicated. I don't...
I'll make sure it doesn't.
Sleep on it.
So Anton is obsessed
with this photographer.
Another one of his genius ideas.
He started using her six months ago
after he saw her shots of the
starving children in Africa.
Pretty much he would go to
the edge of the world for her.
And that is basically
where we are now.
I didn't realize there would
be so many people here.
Keep the butterflies to yourself.
Try not to think about the fact
that everybody out here is here
braving the elements
because of you.
Come on.
Gorgeous hair, sparkling eyes.
You must be my model.
Riley Richmond, meet Jo Reynolds.
Oh, my God.
You're Jo Reynolds?
The photojournalist.
The fashion photographer.
What do you say we shoot this thing?
Dark_Chii, edouardn, Just-In,
Luoleilina, SirHill et WoLF971
All right, schoolteacher,
let's start with some test shots.
I have to admit,
it's a little intimidating
posing for you.
Chin up.
Actually, I studied your "Snapshots
from Darfur" project at NYU.
- It was really powerful.
- Turn to the left.
Yeah, Darfur
was mind-blowing and heartbreaking.
Have you ever been to Africa?
I wish.
Started teaching right
after graduation, so,
not a lot of time for travel.
Well, isn't
that what summers are for?
There's a whole world
outside of that classroom of yours.
My fiance and I have
a few bills to pay off
before we can even think about
traveling around the world.
Fiance? Aren't you a little young
to commit for the rest of your life?
I'm just going to
change a lens. Take five.
This is never gonna work.
She's a total amateur.
That's why Anton hired her...
A real girl for real denim.
Oh, come on.
Models are like jeans. You just have
to break them in a little bit.
I see this all the time
with the new girls.
You know, she's just
afraid to lose her inhibitions.
I need hot, I need sexy.
How am I doing?
Is everything okay?
You're doing great. I'm just
gonna shake it up a bit,
look for a different look, so, um,
keep the jeans, and lose the top.
There you go.
Parking's straight ahead.
Well, sure, Johnny, take your time,
but I got to be honest with you.
Leo's people are all
over me for this role,
so let us know soon, huh?
All right. Hey, take care, Johnny.
You must be the Jonah Miller.
Living in Reverse. I'm Andy.
That wasn't...
was that Johnny Depp on the phone?
Welcome to the dream, my friend.
We got a lot to discuss.
I am a huge fan of your films.
When I heard
that you watched my short, I was...
I thought they were going to have
to peel me up off the floor.
Good. 'Cause I got to tell you,
I loved it.
I completely identified
with that character.
It's like everything
is finally going right,
and then bang!
- It all turns upside down.
- Exactly.
So, here's what I think.
Love the title.
Okay. Love the characters.
Not so in love with
the story in reverse.
I mean, that's...
it's kind of the point,
'cause it's called
Living In Reverse.
Yeah, but who wants to pay ten bucks
to see a movie backwards?
Right.
Trust me on this one.
All right, let's go, hot stuff.
Jo's locked and loaded.
Ella, you have to stop this.
I am not taking my shirt off.
Riley, sweetheart,
this is a jeans ad.
A little skin is par for the course.
Does Anton know about this?
He's still on the road, but I just spoke
to him, and he loves the take.
Okay?
Jo knows what she's doing.
What happens when my parents Google my
name and they see this on the Internet?
You're an adult, Riley.
How many people do you know
that can throw on a pair of jeans
and get paid ten grand?
Which... not to mention... is, like,
50 wilderness scout
videos in Jonah dollars.
Maybe I'm just not cut out for this.
Come on, Riley, you're beautiful.
And not just denim ad beautiful,
either.
You're one of those girls
who can't walk into a room
without everyone falling
in love with them.
It's disgusting, actually.
Thanks...
I guess.
And the camera is the same way.
You know, you'll walk out there,
it'll fall madly in love with you,
everyone will gush and...
it'll be great.
To be totally honest,
you were the last person
I wanted by my side for this.
But I'm actually glad you're here.
Good.
Now, will you get
your butt out there
and try to enjoy
being a diva for once?
Please, can you?
Think bitch.
Attitude, attitude.
Shake it off. Breathe.
Work the ladies, work the
ladies, work the ladies.
Let's go.
Man, if they ever found out
I was selling these treasure maps...
Yeah, mum's the word.
Where are the security codes?
- You're doing the world a favor.
- By increasing the crime rate?
By letting these rich bastards know
they can't lie and cheat their way
into these million- dollar homes.
Hey, this home up on Alpine...
they launder drug money.
They're getting what they deserve.
So, we make the lead a woman.
I'm telling you, Cameron Diaz
is going to flip for this thing.
We tell the story in
chronological order,
lose all the black and white stuff.
How's that sound?
Andrew Misher's office...
it sounds very different.
Great. Listen, I got to head out,
but I love
what we're orbiting here.
Can't wait for your new take.
We'll talk soon, kid.
Andrew Misher's office...
I know that look.
You think you're giving
Andrew Misher Sling Blade,
and he pitches you back
the next Freddy Krueger.
Oh, no, it wasn't so bad.
Right.
I'm Kendra, his development exec.
Sorry I missed your meeting. I had a
five-minute notes call with Michael Bay
that turned into two
hours of arguing.
Geez.
Miller, I know. I'm the one
Charlie Kitsis called
to get you in the door.
The door that's about
to hit me on the way out?
It just turns out
that Andrew and I are on...
completely separate
pages with all this.
Andrew's never on anyone's page.
But the good news is,
I actually have
a lot of say in how
we develop the scripts.
Let me guess.
Mine needs a 3-D alien invasion
followed with... an apocalypse?
Actually, I wouldn't change a thing.
I want to turn Living in Reverse
into a feature film.
And if you're not busy now, I'd love
to discuss what we can do
to make that happen...
on your terms.
Are you punking me?
Is it, like...
Seriously?
So, what's taking her
so long?
Okay, so here's the deal.
Riley's chest has
seen the light of day
about as often
as the latest Usher album.
She's been with...
three guys her entire life,
and her idea of a good time
is hanging out at Whole Foods
trying to convince you
to save the whales.
So, if you want her
to feel comfortable,
you're going to have to appeal
to her sensibilities.
Comfortable is the last thing
I want her to feel.
All right. You ready?
You good to lose the shirt?
"Good" is stretching it.
Come on, sweetie.
Riley, this is a jeans ad, you know.
All the models are topless,
and I don't come up with this stuff,
so just relax...
deep breath.
It'll be beautiful.
Here we go.
There we go. Don't be afraid
to show that body of yours.
No more fake smiles.
We tried that already.
Come on, this is a campaign
about raw emotion.
You're a real woman
with real feelings.
Let it all out.
What do you think
I'm trying to do?
I don't know.
You're still hiding it. Come on.
These are the jeans
that the teacher puts on
after the bell rings.
She's new at this, remember?
Go easy on her.
I want you to show
me the side of you
that wants to unchain herself
from the classroom,
from the fiance
that's stopping you
from being the person
you really want to be.
I am the person I want to be.
Come on.
Nobody really wants
to teach public school
and marry some guy
who can't even pay the bills!
Come on.
You're just afraid of the unknown.
All right, that's it.
You know what? That guy
is someone I love, and that
classroom is my passion.
Even on the hardest days,
at least I know I'm
following my heart.
That's a lot more
than I can say about you.
Sweetheart,
why don't we go for a walk
and unwind a little bit?
Somebody get her a benzo, ASAP.
Forget it, I quit.
You have a minute?
Now is not actually a good time.
You okay?
Just on my way to
a business meeting.
So, um...
David, if your offer still stands,
I... I'd actually like to
take you up on that loan.
We can organize a payment plan.
Money's yours. Just give me
a couple of days to make it happen.
Thank you... so much.
No worries.
Studying to be an architect?
That?
No, it's just some property
I'm thinking about acquiring.
Really?
Beverly Hills mansion.
I knew you had money, but...
I'm just looking for now.
Putting my feelers out there
for some investment opportunities.
Since when has flipping
multi-million dollar real estate
been a hobby of yours?
Since... forever.
Is something wrong, David?
You in trouble?
'Cause if you are, you can tell me.
Nobody's in any trouble.
Now, uh...
do you mind?
I got to get ready.
Okay. So...
that little paper thingy you signed?
Yeah, that was a contract.
You can't leave.
I didn't sign off
on being humiliated.
If this is what being a model
is about, it's not for me.
Okay, look. Anton is on his way,
and if you're not here,
then I get an ass-whipping,
and it turns into a PR nightmare.
That is all you care about,
isn't it?
Furthering your career.
Hey, I meant what I said
in there, okay?
It's your choice
if you don't want to
believe in yourself.
Since when does believing in myself
require me to abandon all self-respect?
Do you think Jonah's self-respect
soars through the roof
every time he shoots
a Dora the Explorer-
themed birthday bash?
No! It's called compromise, Riley.
You know what, just stop.
I don't trust you.
I have never trusted you,
and I am not having
this conversation with you.
Well, have fun
having it with your fiancs, then,
when you tell him you blew it today.
I mean, really?
Giving up on ten grand
because of a little ego bruise?
Kind of says a lot about the way
things work at home, doesn't it?
You heading out?
Yeah. That killer lunch rush.
Just hoping my legs will hold
till I get to the bus stop.
I can take you home if you want.
On your motorcycle?
Only if you appreciate that a Triumph
is so much more than a motorcycle.
Auggie, I... I don't want
to take your helmet.
Are you kidding me?
You think I'd ever let
anything happen to you?
Come on. Let's go.
I loved how you played with shadows.
Well, that whole last sequence,
that was lit
by one super-long string
of Christmas lights.
What? Yeah.
It wasn't going to work, I didn't think,
'cause the Santa bulbs
kept getting in the way,
but it actually...
it, uh, turned out really cool.
Well, look, Jonah,
you're obviously passionate
about your vision,
and as the voice in Andrew's ear,
I want to make sure he knows
exactly what that vision is.
Thank you so much. I mean,
this movie is pretty much my life.
Movies in general are my life.
Hooked the moment I saw
Chitty Chitty Bang
Bang at the Ritz Five.
Wait. What?
The Ritz Five in Philly?
You've been there?
Kendra, that's where I'm from.
- What?
- I'm from Philly.
The Ritz Five is one of my favorite
movie theaters of all time.
- Me, too.
- I've had life-altering experiences
in those hallowed walls.
Oh, my...
Taxi Driver...
And Rang Bull.
The Scorsese festival. The best...
- I go every year at Christmas.
- Me, too.
I ca...
This... I can't deal with this.
Like, we've probably
been standing in line
ordering popcorn together.
I think I would have remembered you.
Yeah, I definitely think
I would have remembered you.
You know, I'm having
drinks tonight at Katsuya
with the VP of Paramount.
We'll probably be done by 10:00.
You want to join me after?
Uh, meet you after your drinks?
To work on our pitch.
T... to work on the pitch.
Sounds good, sounds...
yeah, sounds great.
I'll save you a seat at the bar.
What are you doing?
You don't want to buy this house.
My real estate agent stood me up.
I'm actually just on my way out.
Yeah, so what's with
the black gloves?
Lauren, this isn't a good time.
Right.
First you get beaten up,
then the blueprints.
The bag... David, what's going on?
You're completely overreacting.
Then show me what's in there.
This is ridiculous.
Excuse me.
Lauren, get in the car.
We got to get out of here.
Now.
Guess there's no love lost
between you and the speed limit.
I peeked back a few times
to make sure you were
still holding on.
All that adrenaline tired me out.
How about a margarita before
we tackle the furniture?
Virgin, obviously.
Sure, why not?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, hey, what's up?
Nothing, I just...
I totally tanked the shoot,
and now I have to
break the news to Jonah
that that extra money we were
counting on doesn't exist.
Hey, it was just one shoot.
Yeah, exactly, one shoot.
Do you know how many video jobs
Jonah's had to sweat through
just so we can make rent?
Do you want to come
over for a minute?
I'll make some tea.
You can shed some of that stress.
No, looks like you're in the
middle of something. I'm okay.
No, no, it's, it's totally fine.
Come over, please.
Is Riley okay?
Yeah, she's just...
she's just had a rough day.
Um, do you mind if
I help you out tomorrow?
No, of course not.
Riley obviously needs
you more than I do.
Thanks, Violet.
Ella said
the photographer was trying
to strip away my inhibitions.
I don't know.
Sounds like she took you
for a rough ride out there.
I moved where she wanted,
I looked where she wanted,
I did everything she said.
I mean...
Auggie, I even took my shirt off.
How'd that go?
How do you think?
I'm a schoolteacher pretending to be
some sort of supermodel.
Yeah, well, you're allowed to want
more than one thing in life, Riley.
Jonah is going to hate me
for giving up that money.
Riley,
I don't know if you know this,
but it's kind of
impossible to hate you.
He'll understand.
I just had to get out of there.
She just kept
pushing me to be this reckless,
carefree
kind of person who just throws
caution to the wind.
It's like she was trying to make
me question my choices in life.
You don't think I'm too young
to get married, do you?
I don't think I'm the
right guy to answer that.
You know, um, instead of drinks,
like, if you just want to meet
at your office another day,
my schedule is super loose.
Eh, don't worry about it.
Drinks go on the company card.
You got to love a studio gig.
You've seen Autumn Falls, right?
Three times.
My ex-boyfriend
wrote and directed it.
Kevin Carlyle is your ex-boyfriend?
Andrew plucked him out of
obscurity and made him huge.
You kind of remind me of him.
Thank you.
Look, I got to be honest with you,
Kendra.
I don't know if I can come tonight.
How come?
It's just I...
well, I,
I kind of have some plans already.
So, you know...
All right, well, if
you happen to free up,
You know where I'll be.
Caleb, Muffin, I would hardly
call the shoot a disaster.
Look, I'm sure Jo got
some amazing shots.
Of course I'll work it out.
I always do.
That girl was a waste of my time.
So Riley's no Elle Macpherson.
Not like you did her any favors,
constantly reminding her of that.
With amateurs, it's my job
to ruffle their feathers.
Without that little push,
she couldn't even
get off the ground.
Right, and you're the
professional, supposedly.
Maybe you shouldn't
have pushed her so hard.
It's what I do.
Until she's able to tap
into who she really is,
she should stick to the ABC's instead
of selling out for a pair of jeans
and a few thousand bucks.
Selling out?
I'm sorry,
weren't you the one who traded in
the refugee camps for a
12-page spread in Vogue?
Maybe Riley wasn't the only one
posing out there today.
Isn't this bird's nest,
like, the coolest thing ever?
If it wasn't
dive-bombing our doorway.
What were you doing out
here... gauging the pH levels?
No, I was just taking a break.
I've been trying to put
some furniture together.
Right.
I would lend you a hand with that,
but, uh, I have a date with Riley
when she gets back
from her photo shoot.
I think Riley's back already.
No, I'm pretty sure she's not.
She was going to call
me on her way home.
Well, then, maybe your phone's
messed up. She came home
about a half hour ago.
She's probably still at Auggie's.
Sh... she went to Auggie's?
He was supposed to help me
assemble my furniture,
but then she came home
and she was super upset,
so he invited her over.
Wait... did something
happen at the shoot?
No clue.
You know how the two of them are...
like everything's
their little secret.
I should let you
get back to your life.
I promise I won't drag you
into any more of my meltdowns.
Riley, we all have our moments.
We wouldn't be human if we didn't.
Oh, hey, buddy.
Come on in.
I heard you had a big meeting
with a producer today.
How was your meeting?
Please tell me we have
a reason to celebrate.
Yeah, yeah, it went, uh, went great.
That's awesome.
I am so glad you're home.
I'm starving
and in desperate need
of a champagne buzz.
Oh, I guess that means
your shoot went well?
I will tell you all about
it when we get home.
I want to borrow
a bike pump from Auggie.
Meet you back at the ranch?
I'll go dig out those veggie burgers
that have been hiding
in the freezer.
Perfect.
Thanks for the tea,
Anytime.
What's going on here?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the hours on end
you spend behind closed
doors with my fiancée.
Riley's shoot didn't go as planned.
She just wanted to talk about it.
And look who was more than happy
to throw a strong
shoulder in her direction.
You were in a meeting, she
didn't want to bother you.
Seriously,
that's all that happened.
Right. So, you're still playing
the "we're just friends" card?
I'm not playing any card, Jonah.
We are just friends.
Really?
Because I saw security footage
of you guys sitting out
in the courtyard acting
like way more
than friendly.
You mean the day after Sydney died?
I was barely holding it together.
Riley was the one person
who would talk to me.
I'm sure it was
the sound of her voice
you found so incredibly consoling.
You're way off base.
I just want you to tell me
that you and Riley have not
crossed the line of friendship.
You know, she always jokes
that you're paranoid.
She's not really joking, is she?
Look, Riley and I have already
talked about what happened,
I think maybe it's
time that you fess up.
She kissed me,
not the other way around.
She kissed you?
Wha...
Look, I'm talking about...
She kissed you?
It's not what you think.
She was drunk.
She loves you.
Trust me.
So, what should we toast?
To your bright future
as a filmmaker?
Or my terribly short
career as a model?
Okay, you are either really
thirsty or really upset.
Why did you go to Auggie?
Jonah, you were having
the biggest meeting of your career.
I didn't want to burden you
with my modeling woes.
Right, well,
you could have texted me.
I guess it was just...
just easier to go to
Auggie's open door.
What?
This isn't about Auggie,
it's about me,
completely blowing it today.
Ten grand.
Gone.
I mean, I... I showed up,
and... I couldn't follow through.
I really wanted
to do this for you,
Jonah, and I couldn't.
I let you down.
No, you didn't.
You didn't let me down.
At least not because
you ran out on some...
some photo shoot.
I don't care about the money.
You get that, right?
All I care about
is knowing that you're
telling me the truth.
So there's nothing going
on between you two?
Are you... are you
seriously still worried
about Auggie and me?
Nothing has ever happened
between you guys?
Your ring is on
my finger.
You are the only guy
I want to be with.
You want the truth, that's it.
Right.
You sound entirely convinced.
I just gotta get
some air.
Whatever you need to do.
What, are you stalking me now?
David, this is serious.
That must've been thousands
of dollars worth of diamonds.
Not really your problem, is it?
Is it the thrill?
Do you get off on doing this to people?
I see.
First you're my doctor,
now you're my shrink.
David, if you think you need
to go out and take what's not yours,
there's obviously something
missing in your life.
What would you know about that, huh?
That's right.
Miss prim and proper.
The ambitious doctor
who's got it all figured out.
You wouldn't have any
idea what it's like
to have to bend
the rules just to get by.
You don't think there are times
when I feel powerless?
When I just want
to close my eyes and pretend
that I was somebody else?
You know what?
It doesn't mean I go out
and victimize people.
They're not victims.
The people that I target...
white-collar criminals.
Scum of the Earth.
Just like my father.
What does this have to do
with Dr. Mancini?
My dad's not
the miracle worker that you
and your med school buddies
put on a pedestal, I'm sorry.
Well, you know what, David?
No father's perfect.
He never had an interest in
being my father, Laur.
You know, the idea of a... of
trust fund is almost laughable
considering he's done
everything in his power
to forget I even exist.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry he let you down.
You didn't deserve it.
But stealing?
Come on, David,
that's not how to get back at him.
Maybe you're right.
But it does allow to loan money
to my friends, doesn't it?
David, do you think I want
anything to do with your money
now that I know where
it comes from, huh?
So, where's your moral
compass pointing to now?
Police?
My old man?
I'm going to do you
the biggest favor of your life.
I'm going to keep it between us.
And in return,
you're never going to steal again.
Go ahead.
Answer it.
Still need a hand?
I wasn't expecting you to show up.
Yeah, sorry I had to bail earlier.
It's cool. Building
this thing has actually
been kind of therapeutic.
Really? 'Cause that's exactly
what I'm looking for right now.
Are you okay?
Yeah, just my sponsor'not
answering his phone.
I'll be fine. I just
think putting
my hands to work would...
help clear my mind.
Great.
So...
what are we making?
My new bed.
Your new bed.
Let's do this.
All right.
Oh, these...
It's your favorite photographer.
I couldn't
believe when I looked your address.
I used to live in
this very building.
Are you serious?
Right over there.
A lot of memories in this place.
A lot of them I'd rather forget.
I noticed someone still
rides a motorcycle.
Is that your fiance's?
Someone else, actually.
Listen, I came by to tell you
that you kind of hit
a nerve with me today,
when you told me to go to hell.
Look, you were just doing your job.
I was totally out of my element...
No, but you were right.
I told you to set yourself free,
and maybe it's time
I take my own advice.
Does that mean you're thinking
about going back to Darfur?
Actually, I was thinking
of heading south for a bit,
to bring some media attention to
the food shortage
in Latin America.
Well, you're obvious
the right woman for the job.
You have a gift of exposing
things in your photos
that most people are afraid
to look at in real life.
It comes with a big pay cut.
Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
you kind of got through to me, too.
Maybe I have closed myself off.
Maybe I need to be
a little more open-minded.
You know, when I was your age,
I was engaged.
After I left him,
that's when my real life kicked in.
How did you know it was
the right thing to do?
I didn't.
I almost forgot.
Listen,
don't worry about how today ended.
Anton, he saw that last photo.
He said he's never seen such
raw emotion in his whole life.
Congratulations.
You are the new face
of Anton V. Jeans.
You're kidding me.
Oh, my God.
Good luck, Riley.
You showed.
I was scared missed you.
What happened to your plans?
Just decided
it was an opportunity
I couldn't pass up.
Can I buy you a drink?
Sure.