Previoulsy...
Hi, I'm Ella Sims,
junior publicist.
You are a hugely talented filmmaker.
We're getting married, guys.
You called your dad?
Get in the car!
Look at you. Paddock watch, the Prada.
You're getting your money somewhere.
If you need to go out
and take what's not yours,
there's something
missing in your life.
- I'm concerned about finances.
- I work it out.
You're gonna be going to a party
tonight. The client's gonna love you.
There's a hostess
that just quit at Coal.
I could put in a good word for you.
Oh, my God, Sydney!
- Did you know her pretty well?
- I met her 4 years ago.
She was the one who convinced
me I could be a real chef.
Who needs Coal?
You are way too good for that place.
I kissed someone last night.
I had the same exact reaction when
I found out you kissed Auggie.
So, where do we go from here?
You're...
incredible.
Thank you, so are you.
What's the rush?
You booked two hours.
Now I gotta go.
But I want you to stay.
Thousand dollars if
you stay till sunrise.
I'm all yours.
You're sure they're not
gonna be home all day, right?
We've done this before,
and we've had no problems, right?
You have nothing to worry about.
I'll see you soon, bye.
Dad stick you with
the graveyard shift again?
Part of the joy of med school.
What about you? Where
are you off to so early?
Oh, Hugo's.
Waffles and eggs.
Long night of
making people feel better?
Endless night, actually.
Let me see, we had two
car accidents, gunshot wound,
and a kidney failure
all in one shift.
You look exhausted.
- Are you okay?
- I'm still standing.
Yeah, for now.
Dr. Mancini's got us coming in
for rounds in two hours.
So I have like 90 minutes
uninterrupted sleep ahead of me.
Take care of yourself.
Did we forget to set this clock back
or are you, like,
an hour late to class?
I have teachers' conferences today.
I don't have to go in early.
Oh, right, forgot.
You gonna work on your
treatment for Kendra?
Yeah, probably.
Where are we, Jonah?
I have no idea.
We're supposed to be engaged
and we're kissing other people?
God, I wish none
of this had ever happened.
Too bad in real life
there's no "undo" command.
I was thinking,
I should maybe take a road trip.
Like hike Joshua Tree or something.
I was gonna say the opposite,
that we go together somewhere.
What was that?
Police! Get inside!
Now, now!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
LAPD! Go! Go! Go!
Get in there!
Watch them!
Do either of you happen to know
where Auggie Kirkpatrick might be?
- Why?
- We found the murder weapon.
- What does that have to do with Auggie?
- It was a knife with his blood on it.
Mr. Kirkpatrick's wanted for murder.
Balibal,Dark_Chii
Just-In, Luoleilina
Ps!Ko^^, SirHill
WoLF971
What would a boy do
without his balls?
Whatever you have planned
for the rest of the day, cancel it.
Do I get a why?
I got a heads-up
from corporate in New York
and they wanna a
video conference at noon.
They want a full rundown on how I'm
making the L.A. office more profitable.
And you want me to be your wingman?
- Talk you up to the New York brass?
- Done and done.
I've never needed a wingman.
What I need for you to do is
take over the lunch meeting
I was supposed to have
with Franz Keppler.
You do know who he is, right?
The German wunderkind who makes
indecipherable indie movies
that I would rather pluck
my eyes out than sit through.
I wouldn't open with that.
Franz is white-hot right
now that he's about to start rolling
on the Bruckheimer blockbuster.
I need you to convince him
that he needs WPK.
A couple of problems.
I know nothing about his movies,
I speak zero German
and lederhosen is not my style.
New York's gonna ask me what
gets I have lined up.
I'm gonna tell them I'm about to
bring Franz Keppler into the WPK fold.
Don't make your boss a liar.
All right, no need to get
your jock strap in a knot.
I'm on it.
Are you sure you know where it is?
I got it written down.
1:00, right?
But where is the place again?
Pasadena Tile
on Colorado.
I wanna kiss you good-bye, Mommy.
Sorry, Miss Vanessa, he's so fast.
You want a kiss, you got it, pal!
I want Mommy.
Oh, come here.
Be a good boy today, okay?
We'll be back later.
Thanks.
Come right back.
Hola, Leticia.
- ¿Como estas?
- I do not feel good about this.
It's fine. I'll have him
back in a of couple hours.
There's my little munchkin!
Ready for an adventure
with your big brother?
- I can get in so much trouble for this.
- But you won't.
Because no one has to find out.
All right, you ready? Let's hit it, pal.
- Where are we going?
- It's a surprise.
Come on.
I may not be CSI,
but when your blood ends up
on the murder weapon
along with the victim's blood...
you're usually guilty.
It doesn't prove anything.
What other proof do you need?
It's Auggie.
He'd never murder someone.
Are you forgetting about
the night he told
you about stabbing
a guy in a bar fight?
That was self-defense.
And look, obviously you're
not exactly Mr. Objective when
it comes to judging him.
I wouldn't put you anywhere
near that jury box.
I'm just stating facts here, Riley.
One being that right after
they found that knife,
our good friend Auggie seemed to
very conveniently disappear.
He goes on surfing trips
all the time, you know that.
How do you know he's surfing?
I saw him loading his board
and his bag into his van.
He could just
have been going to the beach.
How do you know he's on a trip?
Did he tell you
he was going somewhere?
If you know where he is,
you have to tell the police.
Why? So they can arrest him and
convict him of a crime he didn't commit?
It happens all the time.
They also convict people
for aiding and abetting
a fugitive.
We all know you have this
uncanny ability
to see the very best in people,
but is that really worth
going to prison for?!
You have no idea he's even innocent.
Yes, I do.
I know Auggie.
Oh, really? You know Auggie?
I get that you're
friends and you talk.
But think about it. Honestly.
How well do you really
know that guy?
- I gotta go.
- Where?
Ella's having some kind
of emergency.
Of course she is.
You better hurry.
This might actually turn out to be
a blessing in disguise.
I was talking about
spending some time apart.
Why not start today?
There's one rule that
we cannot break, no matter what.
It's that we cannot leave this place
until we have gone on
every single ride.
- You got it?
- Got it!
Good.
Why can't we do this every day?
That's a little complicated, bud.
Auf Wiedersehen, Mr. Miller.
That kind of means "good-bye."
What's this whole emergency?
So there's this German
guy that I'm trying to woo...
and I know you know all
about German cinema.
This doesn't sound remotely
like an emergency.
The real emergency's happening
at our building right now.
What happened?
The cops raided Auggie's
apartment this morning.
They found the murder weapon
with Auggie's blood on it.
What?
Oh, my God.
It's terrible.
Is Auggie in jail?
He's doing what every
innocent person does.
Disappear into the ether.
Course the only person who thinks
Auggie's actually innocent is Riley.
Little disagreement
between the two lovebirds?
I'm getting a little tired of her
obsession with him, that's all.
I don't blame you.
But there is nothing you can do
except help your neighbor who's
not a murderer... me.
So, wait.
Who's this Aryan mystery man?
Franz Keppler.
We're having lunch
with him at Coal in 45 minutes.
He just won the Palme d'Or.
He totally revitalized
European cinema.
If this is a joke,
it's cruel by even your standards.
There's no joke.
There's just one teeny-weeny catch.
You're not the filmmaker,
you are Jonah Miller
the new publicist at WPK.
I don't know a thing
about publicity.
You don't have to. You talk his movies,
I'll talk publicity.
We'll be fine.
It'll be fabulous.
Mr. Walters here presented
with mitral valve prolapse
of the anterior leaflet.
What were the possible
complications?
Endocarditis
makes the surgery more difficult.
And...?
And, um...
Anyone.
The patient might have
extensive calcium deposits
on the valve leaflets,
which ups the surgery risk factors.
That's it. Very good.
All right, that's all.
I'll see you all tomorrow.
Dr. Levy to Oncology.
Just a minute, Miss Yung.
- Have you been studying?
- Of course.
When I chose you,
you said you could handle the grind.
- I can handle the grind.
- Really?
Because there's a long list
of students
who'd give their right arm
for your spot.
Don't blow it.
Oh, my God.
Good times, huh?
- What the hell are you doing here?
- I need one more little favor.
Our agreement is very clear.
I send you your weekly payments,
and you stay the hell away
from me and my family.
But I had to come see you in person.
You won't return my phone calls.
You know what? This sick little
game of yours is starting to piss me off.
I'm supporting another child.
Don't think I'm not appreciative.
Your money has been so helpful.
I just bought some awesome
new furniture.
So let me guess,
you need more money.
Right?
I need a lawyer.
I have a court case coming up.
What for?
The cops came after me for some
little thing I did up in Oregon.
And now, they're saying
I, like, resisted arrest.
It doesn't even matter.
But I figure,
you're this big-time doctor,
you probably have tons
of important patients,
including lawyers.
You expect me to find
a lawyer for you?
The person who's blackmailing me?
Go to hell.
Actually, it's your marriage
that goes to hell
once I send your wife our little
video.
People like you,
they don't get away with this
kind of behavior.
It comes back to haunt you.
You would know.
My court date's
December 11'th.
Your choice, Doctor.
Either get me a lawyer,
or I get you divorced.
Enjoy your lunch!
There's our Bavarian buddy.
My gosh, I can't believe I'm about
to have lunch with Franz Keppler.
Control the drool, and remember,
you're a publicist, not a fan boy.
I know.
Franz?
Oh, hello.
Caleb didn't tell me how
beautiful the publicist would be.
He is a man of few words.
Anyway, this is my associate,
Jonah Miller,
who also happens to be one
of your biggest fans.
It's true. Das Lied is one of my
favorite thrillers, like, of all time.
Thank you. Come, let...
you know, let's sit.
Yeah, with Das Lied I was,
trying to make a movie
that was visually striking,
mesmerizing.
Kind of like your eyes.
Danke schön.
So, congratulations
on the Bruckheimer movie.
No doubt that it is going to be a hit,
but we need to make sure that
you are getting the accolades
that you deserve.
It's not just a Matt Damon movie.
This is a film by Franz Keppler.
You're confident.
It's what I do.
I like that.
Ella is an amazing publicist.
- Thank you.
- She's the best.
And one of the most inventive
filmmakers of his generation
deserves the best.
Uh, but, Franz,
your use of shadows...
it makes Fritz Lang
look like an amateur.
You're too kind, Jonah.
Which must make you
the naughty one.
You nailed it, Franz.
Ella is naughty.
Why do you think I proposed to her?
Couldn't let her get away.
Like I would ever stray from you.
I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
You were a couple.
- I thought you were colleagues.
- We just try to keep a low profile.
You know, keep it professional.
But in reality,
he cannot keep his hands off of me.
I don't blame him.
Okay, boys, let's relax our trousers
and get down to business.
Like the juggernaut, otherwise
known as Franz Keppler's career.
Cheers.
Vive la Franz!
Unbelievable, huh?
Murder?
Auggie?
I know.
He would never do
something like this.
I guess the police are coming up
empty in their investigation, so...
They're trying to pin it on Auggie?
They're desperate.
And stupid.
Listen, Violet, I wanted to talk
to you about Auggie.
What about him?
You guys work together.
Has he been...
I don't know, acting strange lately?
He's been Auggie.
I mean, yeah, he got in that fight
with Marcello, but
Auggie had no choice.
What fight with Marcello?
Last night.
Auggie finally got fed up
with Marcello taking credit
for his recipes,
and he taught him a lesson.
Is Marcello okay?
Broken nose, couple of broken ribs.
Auggie may have lost his job,
but Marcello got what he deserved.
I took care of Auggie
last night, though.
Auggie and I have become...
intimate.
Look over there!
How about getting one of those?
Yeah one of those.
The blue one.
That was so fun!
We were way up there, huh?
I think I saw my house.
I think I saw the North Pole.
And Santa Claus was shoveling
his driveway.
He only comes in winter.
What?
Can you win me a prize?
I'll win you a prize.
You got it. Come on, pal.
Wait, one second, Noah.
Leticia, what's up?
They're not home, are they?
Okay, good.
No, we're fine.
Get down from there, pal.
We'll be home in, like, an hour.
And the good news is you won't
have to feed him for a week.
He's eaten his weight in corndogs.
You okay, buddy?
You're gonna be okay.
We're here, buddy.
We're gonna get some help, all right?
I'm looking for Lauren Yung.
She's a med student,
part of Dr. Mancini's team.
- ER's this way.
- All right, buddy.
When you called you left out the
part about how this happened.
It doesn't matter.
He said that his arm hurts real bad.
Okay, just relax.
Pulled some strings, we can
get him in straight away.
- We can take it from here.
- Wait over there.
Unless you're a guardian,
it's not really policy.
- I'm not leaving him...
- It's okay.
Check his vitals, get me a chem 20,
do an A.P. and a lateral, left arm.
He also threw up in the car ride over.
It's probably all the junk he ate.
- Could also be a concussion.
- What?
- I didn't see him hit his head.
- I'm going to take care of him.
Add a CT scan.
My dad doesn't know
that I took Noah.
He's about to.
They're calling him as we speak.
Maybe you shouldn't have
anything to do with this.
If you want to step out
and have another doctor come in...
The child needs medical care.
I'm giving it to him.
Auggie, it's me.
I just want you to know
I'm totally here for you,
and I know it's only been 24 hours
since we last saw each other, but...
I miss you.
Call me.
Nice furniture.
Love what I've done with the place.
- Did you find me a lawyer?
- Oh, didn't need to.
I checked out the
details of your hearing,
and it turns out I know the judge
that's scheduled to preside over it.
- What does that get me?
- I actually met Judge Davis
the day I did a quadruple
bypass on Mrs. Davis.
Needless to say, the good
judge was extremely grateful.
That's perfect.
Eh, that depends.
See, Judge Davis has
the utmost trust in me,
and I'm your character witness,
- either way.
- What do you mean?
That I can tell him
that the Violet Foster I know is
a poor, disinherited orphan
and should have
the justice system smile upon her.
- Thank you.
- Or...
I can tell him that Violet is
a sick and twisted menace to
society that should be locked up.
Your move.
Fine.
And now we're done.
Your days of milking
me for money are over.
Now, if even
one single frame of that video
shows up anywhere, I call
Judge Davis
and he throws your devious
little ass in jail.
Who says doctors don't make
house calls anymore?
So tell me,
how did you guys meet?
At my apartment building, actually.
Well, he had a
girlfriend at the time,
but as soon as I saw
that adorable smile,
I just knew.
You know what? I'm thinking of
doing a romantic comedy,
and looking at you two,
I have found my inspiration.
Did you hear that?
- I did.
- It's nice to meet you.
And Ella, my dear...
- Franz, oh, very sweet.
- Very nice to meet you.
I'm going to put some serious
thought into working with WPK.
Jonah, hang on to her tight, yeah?
She is worth keeping.
Auf Wiedersehen, Franz.
Call me at the office tomorrow.
Ja, ja.
Always knew you were destined
to win an Oscar someday,
but I never thought
it would be for acting.
Bravo.
I had to come up
with a way to stop Franz
from slipping you the wiener
schnitzel before salad was served.
I was talking about pretending
to be a publicist.
Jonah, hi, it's me, Ella.
You actually think some horny
director would ever faze me?
I deal with guys like that
all the time in my sleep.
I think that you put
your arm around me
and pretended to be my beau because
secretly it's what you wanted
- since the day that we met.
- You are drunk.
Aren't you?
Funny thing is,
is that you and I as a couple...
completely natural.
Franz totally bought it.
After drinking an entire vat of wine,
I think he'd buy anything we sold him.
Jonah, come on.
Give us a little bit of credit.
You and I at that lunch
were completely compatible.
More than I can say about
some real couples I know.
And by that, you mean me and Riley?
It's pretty obvious that the two
of you have been having problems
since the day
you asked her to marry you.
It's not exactly my definition
of compatibility.
Maybe it's time
that you explore
some other options,
the operative word
being "explore."
Okay, uh, what's that
supposed to mean?
Well, Hotel Andaz is
right down the street.
I can...
cancel the rest
of my meetings, you can clear
the rest of your day,
and you can finally experience
what you've been missing...
all this time.
Oh, Jonah, come on.
You can't tell me that you haven't
at least fantasized about the idea.
I'm engaged.
Remember that minor little detail?
What does "engaged" even mean...
giving your college
sweetheart a ring
because you're insecure
about your career
and you're hoping that she'll
bring you some sense of security?
Is that why you think
I proposed to Riley?
Absolutely.
Jonah, you guys are nothing alike.
Okay, look, we might be going
through some growing pains right now,
but it's nothing that's not normal
for any couple planning a wedding.
Nothing about you is normal,
and everything about her
is painfully normal.
- El, you are so out of line right now.
- Am I?
You...
are this brilliant,
passionate, creative type who seeks
adventure and, and,
an-and excitement,
and Riley is this mellow,
laid-back schoolteacher
whose idea of a fun night
i-is grading spelling tests.
Okay, look... say whatever you
want about me, I don't care.
Don't you ever bad-mouth Riley.
If you have a problem
with the fact that I'm in love with her,
then it's just that... it's your problem.
The only reason
I am even out here all day
alone with you is because
Riley trusts me, and I trust Riley.
That's the reason she's the
person I'm meant to be with,
the only person I'm
meant to be with.
To: AugKirk Hey, U there?
AugKirk Yeah. What's up.
To: AugKirk What u doing in Mexico?
AugKirk Struggling.
Riles17 Struggling with...?
AugKirk I've ruined my life.
To: AugKirk What did you do?
AugKirk I'd rather not say.
Don't worry, he'll be
good as new in no time.
I can keep an eye on him if you
want to go to the commissary.
The coffee's semi-toxic,
but it's caffeinated.
No, I'm good.
Oh, my God, Noah.
It's okay.
Mommy and Daddy are here now.
Sweetie...
- How you doing, buddy?
- Mommy?
Can I... is it all right
to hold him?
He really shouldn't be moved.
He's got a,
a hairline fracture to the ulna
and a mild concussion.
You are never to come near
Noah again, is that clear?
If you ever pull something
this reckless again,
so help me God,
I will press charges.
The last thing I ever wanted
was for him to get hurt.
What were you thinking?
I wasn't. I just wanted
to spend time with him.
I wanted to be a brother.
Okay? I screwed up.
I love him.
You have an odd way of showing it.
Good work, Yung.
I'm in here.
You okay?
No, not really.
Who are you calling?
No one.
Yet.
It's Auggie, huh?
You're calling to warn him?
I IM'd him.
I meant it when I said that I wasn't going
to have anything to do with Auggie, but...
He's your friend.
I get it.
You believe in him,
so I believe in you.
If you don't think he did it,
I don't think he did, either.
I trust you, Riley,
because, in the same exact situation,
I'd want you to trust me.
The Ims Auggie sent me back...
they were kind of scary.
Maybe I don't know him
as well as I thought.
Maybe he did hurt Sydney.
But, if he did do it,
and he ends up hurting someone
else because I kept my mouth shut,
I couldn't live with myself.
At the end of the day,
you were right.
It's not up to me to decide
whether or not he's innocent.
Whatever you decide to do...
I'm here for you.
Detective Rodriguez, please.
Ah, Simms, there you are.
Oh, God.
You brought me in here
to talk football?
Franz Keppler just called.
He's coming to WPK.
Not only did he love your pitch, but
he especially loved your... boyfriend?
Invite me to one
of your slumber parties...
we'll have a pint
and share boyfriend stories.
He said his name was Jonah.
That wouldn't happen
to be Jonah Miller,
the director of the Anton V EPK
- and the Boomkat video savior, would it?
- The one and only.
I'm impressed, Simms.
He's absolutely adorable.
Yeah, he is, but, um...
But nothing.
He's brilliant, he's charming.
He's a very talented director.
You know something?
You've actually got good taste
in men.
I have very good taste
in everything, Caleb,
but the truth is,
is that Jonah is engaged.
You're a bad girl, aren't you?
I'm not a home wrecker,
and Jonah is not my boyfriend.
Okay? He's just a friend
who was protecting me
from Franz's groping.
He's a hot-blooded,
heterosexual male.
Engaged or not, if he's pretending to
be your boyfriend, then he wants to be.
Oh, well, then, that's his problem.
Because Jonah Miller
is so not my type.
Please.
Sorry. Did I get your book wet?
That's okay.
I've dropped my fair share
of books in the deep end.
That's what hair dryers are for.
You know, I was thinking.
Making rent every
month is turning out
to be harder than I thought.
And you're a med student, so money's
got to be tight for you, too, right?
That's putting it mildly.
I was wondering if you and Ella
would be interested
in having a new roommate.
I don't take up too much space,
and I promise I don't
talk in my sleep.
We would have so much fun together.
You know, Violet,
I'd love to, but, um,
I-I don't think Ella's going to be
too psyched about sharing the
bathroom with one more person.
Yeah, I get it.
I figured it wouldn't hurt to ask.
One shot of tequila.
Or 12.
I take it you've had about
as good a day as me.
Oh, no, I've had worse.
Especially since the police finally
figured out who murdered Sydney.
What?
Who did it?
Have you two been trapped
in a vault all day?
The police were here this morning
raiding Auggie's apartment.
The murder weapon
had Auggie's blood all over it.
They're searching for him
as we speak.
Oh, my God.
That is so messed up.
I'm as broken up
about it as you are.
Did you guys hear about Auggie?
We're, like, in shock.
Oh, I bet.
I mean, Riley, you know Auggie
better than all of us.
All those morning jogs together.
Who knew that you
were running with the devil?
He's not the devil.
Right...
Look, I'm, um...
I'm sorry about earlier today.
I have no idea what got into me,
except for three bottles
of Pinot Grigio.
That much wine, and I go
straight for shock value.
Well, don't worry about it.
I won't.
I'm going to go chase my buzz.
Can I have a word with you, David?
Sure.
If you're here for David Beatdown
Part Two, can we get on with it?
Actually, uh... no.
No, I'm not here for that.
I stand by what I said
at the hospital.
What you did was reckless.
- You cost Leticia her job.
- It's not Leticia's fault.
Most importantly,
you put Noah's life in danger.
You don't think that I feel
terrible about that?
Do you think that I wanted
to hurt him?
He's my little brother.
I just want to say that,
well, I appreciate...
that you wanted
to spend time with Noah.
Anyway...
I just wanted to say thank you
for, you know, today.
It's pretty obvious you're
going to be an amazing doctor.
Just doing my job.
I've known a lot
of docs in my day, and...
most of them didn't care
nearly half as much as you do.
I think you're the one who cares.
You know?
Seeing you with Noah
like that today...
I didn't think you could be
that devoted to someone.
Pretty easy to be devoted
to a kid like Noah.
It's the other
million things in my life...
that's a different story.
You know, David, um...
you're obviously smart.
Obviously.
Seriously.
All you have to do, David,
is decide what you want to do
with your life and apply yourself.
Just make sure that, whatever it is,
it's legal.
You should know that that little
hobby of mine, it's over.
Good.
I'm glad.
'Cause it was going to be really
awkward calling the cops on my neighbor.
Do you want to know why it's over?
Why?
'Cause I don't want you to ever
look at me the way you did
when you caught me
coming out of that house.
Ever.
I want you to look at me the way
you're looking at me now.
Are you okay?
Did I cross a line?
No, it's... it... it's not you.
Then, what is it?
I just can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, so am I.
www.forom.com