www.seriessub.com - www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriestele.net - www.arcadya.net
Truthworteam Arcadya Global Team
A&M!
You played great today.
I was doing what I'm good at.
You know what else
I'm really good at?
Showtime, baby.
Get out the door.
Get out, man.
Hair of the dog?
Dude, that chick last night
was all over you,
and she was 5 kinds of hot.
You don't got to tell me.
Excuse me, Mr. McNeil?
- Can I have your autograph?
- Sure.
You should stay in school...
don't do drugs, recycle
and all that jazz.
Was she freaky?
She's freaky, uh?
Was she a little bit freaky?
Not in front of the kid, man.
Start with you. I told you.
- She's lot or little freaky?
- Man, she was a little bit freaky.
- You better stop...
- I'm sorry. C. McNeil?
I'm sorry for you.
Maybe you can tell me your name too,
darlin'.
My name is Detective Ferro,
and you're under arrest
for contributing
to the delinquency of a minor.
What?
For what?
Some people call it statutory rape.
Please stand up, sir.
What's going on?
Lie to Me
2x02 - Truth or Consequences
- Thanks a lot!
- That's good, you work for me.
You both need to see
my monkey sex tape.
Sounds like fun.
It's the most
interesting research I've done.
The female Bonobo,
she'll entice a mate
and sometimes attack
with no provocation whatsoever.
I'm familiar with the phenomenon.
We'll talk.
Chimpanzee sex later.
IRS case now.
Right, we're gonna go see the kook
waiting for us at his compound.
- Don't call him a kook.
- What do I call the leader of a cult?
The IRS thinks he's a tax fraud.
And even cults have rights.
Statutory rape.
The former hang 'em high prosecutor
isn't above defending the wicked
when the price is right.
My client had no idea
Susan Reed was underage.
She was on a college campus.
She had a fake ID.
She was drinking,
looks to be at least 20.
She goes to school
with our daughter.
Emily knows the girl, but
they don't travel in similar circles.
How does she feel
about you representing this guy?
- She understands my position.
- Which is?
If Cabe were white, these charges
wouldn't even have been brought.
Susan Reed came home late, intoxicated.
Her father went ballistic.
She broke down
and told him where she was.
- In a black man's bed.
- That's right.
Before Mr. Reed had even
hung up the phone with the cops,
my client was as good as indicted.
I don't know.
Underage girls and...
sex, it's really...
It's just not my cup of tea, love.
Hewlett County, Virginia
is twice as likely
to bring criminal charges
against blacks as it is whites.
And the A.D.A., Jay Putt,
I went to law school with him,
He's a pompous ass who isn't beyond
overcharging just based on race.
That is why Cabe McNeil is
facing trumped-up sex charges.
And he diddled a 16-year-old girl.
Let's not forget that little tidbit.
These charges cost him his future.
What do you want?
Sex charge
is a strict liability crime.
But if I can prove
that Cabe truly believed
that Susan was of age,
then I can use that
to mitigate the charges.
You really want to defend this guy,
or you're just taking this personally
because of the black and white leaves
on your family tree?
Both.
At least you're being honest.
But I'm not gonna blindly help
this guy.
Anything I find out, I'm gonna...
disclose to both you
and the prosecution.
Of course.
What happened to my client?
Cons here,
someone's in for kid-touching.
They don't ask for details.
- Did they let you see a doctor?
- I'm fine. Just want to go home.
First, I need you
to talk with Dr. Lightman.
What do you wanna know?
The truth.
Give us a minute?
My baby.
Who is that in there?
That's Cal Lightman,
and this is his associate
Ria Torres.
They're experts in deception
and witness veracity.
They wanna help me help Cabe.
How old are you?
22.
How do you feel
about being locked up?
I was scared.
Tell me you enjoyed it.
- What?
- Convince me that...
being locked up was nothing.
It was breeze.
Jail was nothing.
I didn't sweat it.
What the hell is he doing?
He's trying to get a baseline
for when Cabe is telling the truth.
Cabe always tells the truth.
Did they give you any medication
for your injuries?
2 painkillers.
You like having sex
with little girls?
What?
Driver's permits, pigtails...
That kind of thing turns you on?
I thought she was in college.
That's enough.
I'm telling you
that I have the right to see my son.
- Calm down.
- Just let me... I am calm!
If I'm gonna help
a statutory rapist walk,
I'm gonna be damn sure
he's telling the truth, right?
I just want to make sure
my son...
is OK.
You OK, Cabe?
I'm OK.
I'm right out here.
We're getting you bailed out.
So you weren't sure she was legal.
I assumed she was.
High school girls
crash the parties a lot.
And you seek'em out?
That's not my thing.
Ask anyone.
I don't hang with the chicks
from Parker High and Lynbrook.
I didn't know she was from Lynbrook.
I thought she was my age.
How often
do girls from Lynbrook Academy
party at Virginia A&M?
Every weekend.
But Susan was talking about econ classes
she was taking, like she went there.
I swear.
The tells I normally pick up on,
painkillers might be masking them,
His facial injuries are restricting
movement, and the swelling...
- I don't know if he's lying...
- Cabe McNeil?
She's a kid.
Why would you do that to her?
She's a child.
My child.
You know what that makes you?
That makes you a rapist.
That's what that makes you.
Mr. Reed, I know...
I consider your pain sincere.
Our daughters go to the same school.
If someone came after my Emily,
I'd be as angry
and upset as you are.
You have no idea how this feels.
That's true.
But I can see it in your face.
Go home.
Don't make it worse for yourself.
Go home to your daughter.
- Who are you?
- Just a bystander.
I don't have a dog in this fight.
Don't just stand there.
Get your son out of here.
Just go home, Mr. Reed.
Just go home, sir.
That was interesting.
- Hi.
- Jamie Cowley.
- Dr. Gillian Foster.
- This is Eli Loker.
- Hi.
Hello.
Here's a copy of the court order
allowing us to visit your compound
and conduct our research.
It gives us 3 days to observe and
interview the members of your church,
and we will come and go
as quietly as we can.
How many disciples
live on your compound?
I share the property
with about 150 other believers.
The IRS has had difficulty
determining an exact number.
The children born into your group
don't get social security numbers.
They don't need one to know God.
- And God, would that be you?
- The Supreme Court is very clear.
The IRS cannot judge
any church's religious tenets.
Only whether your followers' beliefs
are sincere and genuine.
That's where we come in.
You have over 30 houses
on your compound
registered as individual churches.
God is everywhere.
30 churches,
that means 30 different tax exemptions.
The IRS calls it fraud.
Only if they can prove that...
any of my followers
aren't true believers.
You seem pretty confident
that they all are.
Take a look around.
Keep an open mind.
- You might find yourself moved.
- Come on, I'll show you.
Other than you, I've only seen
two other men your age here.
Those are Chris and Ken.
They helped found the church.
When our boys turn 16,
we encourage them to explore the world,
though they're always
welcome to return and...
the women tend to stay.
They care for us
and vice versa.
I'm curious.
How many of these children are yours?
Spiritually,
they're all my children.
Biologically,
Twelve.
And in your...
materials,
you claim that you're a prophet,
that God is gonna teach, through you,
how to live a fulfilled life.
That's right.
So...
It's pretty intense, uh?
How exactly
do you communicate with God?
How does anyone?
Through prayer,
sometimes by looking
into a child's eyes.
I can see that you need convincing.
Why don't you stop by my sermon,
see for yourself?
You have to excuse me.
I have a realization class to teach,
but feel free to talk to anyone.
We're happy to cooperate.
We're not here to judge, remember?
How can I not judge someone
who creates their own harem
and tosses out the competition
when they hit puberty?
Judge him?
How can I copy him?
It's weird, I know,
but it's a free country,
and if the earth mamas wanna split,
there is no gate.
No one's getting hurt.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Is Susan the kind of girl
who'd make up a story like this?
I don't know her very well.
What kind of things do you hear goes on
at these frat parties, then?
I've never been to one,
so I couldn't tell you.
You wouldn't be
dodging my questions?
No, I'm not dodging your questions.
So, the girls
who go to these parties,
do they lie about their age,
- or are they on about it?
- I told you, I've never been to one.
But...
But what?
No, you tell me.
I've been to A&M a couple of times,
but just like, bars, you know?
Excuse me?
It's not a big deal.
Where is mom?
She'll be home in a minute.
She drives like a quaker.
Just... I'd never go to a frat party.
Those things get crazy.
What, as opposed to a pub?
Not a pub, dad, a bar.
A college bar.
And one with bouncers
and a million other people.
It's totally different
from a frat party.
And I don't even go to drink.
I just want to listen to the music.
Really?
Really.
So how'd you get in, then?
What?
- What's in the drawer?
- Nothing.
- What's in the drawer, darling?
- Nothing!
- Excuse me!
Dad, please.
That's private.
- Dad, stop!
- Excuse me.
That's private, dad.
That's such a violation.
Your mom's a lawyer, sue me.
Come on.
You have no right to do this.
Dad, I'm serious.
Come on!
What these, Emily?
Or, should I say...
Kami Schwartz?
Everyone my age has fake Ids.
And your social calendar demands two,
does it?
Dad, that's just a jewelry box.
What'd I miss?
I hope, for your sake,
these are just tic-tacs.
You're using birth control pills?
Do you realize there's consequences
for your actions?
There's consequences to...
going to frat parties
and hanging out with older boys.
- There's consequences to having these.
- To not having those, too.
You just read me.
You swore you would never
do that, and you just did.
Don't go through my things,
ever again.
Well, that went well.
Don't be mad at her.
I'm not mad at her.
I'm mad at you for not telling me.
She thinks she can't talk to you
about that.
Why?
Because when you read her,
she feels like you're judging her.
I'm not judging her!
That's rubbish.
I'm not judging her.
Did you know that some of her friends
are already having sex?
Which ones?
Why, so you can forbid her
from seeing them?
Come on. You know
what we were like when we first met.
Look, Cal, I know in your work
you uncover all kinds of terrible things
that people do every day, but you can't
put all of those fears onto Emily.
And look. She's not on the pill yet,
and I hope it stays that way,
but I think it's best that she have them
for when she is ready.
Bloody hell.
24 years old.
Are you attracted to her?
Sure.
19.
What does she do for you?
Pretty hot.
18.
16 years old?
Find her attractive?
15 years old?
OK. When I showed him the photograph
of the 24-year-old in the brown panties,
he subconsciously licked his lip,
and his pupils dilated.
These are all signs of arousal.
Now, this is his response
when I showed him
the 16-year-old, the 15-year-old,
and asked him if he was attracted.
He said "No."
You lied, Cabe.
- My son is a good boy.
- That's right.
He knows he's not supposed
to be attracted to a 15-year-old girl
'cause society tells him it's wrong.
But I mean, look at her.
Ample breasts,
slim waist,
- ass that won't quit.
- Cal.
All physical attributes
that a heterosexual male
is biologically wired to desire.
There's nothing wrong
in wanting her,
especially since
she's 22 years of age.
I lied, sorry.
Now, for the good news.
When I asked Cabe
if he had ever knowingly
had sex with an underage girl,
he said no.
And he was telling the truth.
Out in the world,
7-year-olds can get
carpal tunnel
from texting and playing
video games all day long.
And our children
grow their own food,
make crafts, become self sufficient.
Hear his word choice?
"Out in the world?"
He defines his followers' universe.
He compares himself to buddha
and other biblical figures.
- You got a point.
- No, but his point is irrelevant.
He's using details
with special context,
like underneath
that huge oak tree and
behind the work shop.
It's contextual embedding,
a sign he's telling the truth.
So he really believes he's a prophet.
His religious beliefs are legit.
Well, to him and them.
But see that?
Not her.
- Why the rush to see us?
- So you and your expert can sign these.
- For what?
- Clearance from the state
and federal government
for you to watch child pornography.
Your client secretly taped
his sex romp with Susan Reed,
and then he put it online
for everyone to see.
That's enticing a minor and making
and distributing child porn.
What was a simple misdemeanor
is now 3 felonies.
Hey, I hear the moaning stopped.
You stopped banging.
Let us in.
The forensic team traced the source to
the wireless router in the frat house.
Susan Reed also swears she
told Cabe how old she was.
Cabe may have fooled you. I was thinking
he was a good kid in a bad spot.
He is a good kid.
Your case is falling apart, so let me
send this kid where he belongs.
Why, because he's black and he slept
with a white girl, he belongs in jail?
No, because she was 16,
and he put it online.
- This has anything...
- Jay, don't play victim.
Come on. I know your track record,
and how you treat black defendants.
I know how you treated me in law school.
I had one white, one black parent,
and I was the only Brown student there.
You never looked down your nose at me.
I'll see you at the grand jury.
- Why'd you made the film?
- I didn't.
But you know who made the film!
And you put it online anyway?
I didn't make any film.
This is the first time...
- You knew she was 16.
- No!
Yeah, she told you that she was 16,
and you brought her home anyway.
She never said she was 16!
Dr. Lightman?
Can you come into the lab, please?
What?
Look at this.
You knew she was 16.
Yeah. She told you
that she was 16,
and you brought her home anyway.
She never said she was 16.
You see what I see?
A tired man.
A guy who's losing control
over his emotions.
This case involves a girl Emily's age
who goes to her school.
Maybe you should let me talk to him.
Maybe you should remember
who's name's on the door.
- What?
- She might be right.
Says the woman who's bringing up
personal gripes from law school.
You didn't even let him answer. How
can you tell if he's telling the truth?
- If you don't even allow for a read?
- He is telling the truth.
He doesn't know anything
about the film,
unless you saw
some signs of aggression
I missed during my particularly
unprofessional session.
He's being honest.
Are we done here?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Come on.
- Where?
- Back to school.
Hell no.
Hey, I'm sorry, old man,
but Shady Acres is down the street.
I used to run this place
back in the day.
Look, see? Look. Class of '85.
- Blue and gold, proud and bold.
- You were Theta house?
Yeah, hang on!
There you go. That's me right there.
That's you?
- Damn.
- Yeah. Father time's a bitch.
Enjoy the party, brother.
- Keg's in the kitchen, right?
- In the kitchen.
I used to strip.
So this is college.
Guess I didn't miss much.
What did you find out?
Most of these guys
just talk a big game.
Once you mention anything about
aggression or voyeurism, they pull back.
Actually, I don't think
any one of these guys
could throw a decent hump at me.
You drunk?
Did you see anyone who, you know,
might be inclined to film
and distribute a sex act?
3 guys showed signs of arousal
when voyeuristic topics came up.
Round them up.
All right.
The simplicity of our lives,
the simplicity
of Jamie's teachings, it's all
- very...
- Simple?
Jamie's belief that he's a prophet that
can lead his people to a better life,
Do you share that belief, Catherine?
Of course.
Isn't that sweet?
Did you make this?
What does it say?
They can't read?
Jamie's homeschooling stresses
ethics over standard academics.
They can't read,
and from what I can tell,
they spend all day making crafts
for Jamie to sell?
Do you think that's healthy?
Not why we're here.
We'll take care
of our children our way.
And yours your way.
Men fathering children year-round,
kids not getting educated.
Yeah, like a quarter
of the U.S. population.
This doesn't bother you?
These children are not being cared for.
There are people out there
who'd want them, who'd love them.
We're here to find tax fraud.
No more, no less.
And no, wacky religions,
they don't bother me,
because they're no wackier
than the mainstream ones.
Do you really believe that
there's a man in the clouds
who will solve your problems
if you make a wish to him?
So being a scientist means
I can't believe in God?
Well, last I checked,
talking to invisible people
is usually diagnosed as schizophrenia.
Look at her son.
His body language is very open,
his arms behind his back,
- standing off to the side.
- Waiting where we have to pass.
I didn't catch your name before.
- I'm Zack.
- I'm Gillian.
Is there something
that you want to tell us, Zack?
My mom doesn't believe
in any of this.
Not in Jamie, his church,
none of it.
Then why does she stay here?
If she tries to go,
Jamie will take us from her.
- This would be my room.
- I see.
So, what's the plans?
No plan.
You ready to party, boys?
Take a hike, dude.
Which one of you made the sex film?
Who was it?
There's our man.
You two, hop it.
Your name?
Wayne.
Wayne what?
Wayne Harkey.
Hello.
Where's the sex film?
You made...
a film with an underage girl.
If I have to ask you again, I'm going
to cuff you. You understand me?
I didn't know what to do.
Or you couldn't stop watching it.
I didn't know
she was in high school,
and I did not make that film.
I found it.
I just... I posted it online
as a joke to punk Cabe.
Real funny.
Look, I came up here for some beers,
and it was sitting on the desk.
I found it, all right?
The sex stuff was already on it.
I posted it, and I just...
I went outside for a brew.
I believe you.
Go on. Sod off.
What?
Give me the camera.
I want to know how a video of you ended
up on a camera with a sex film on it
that I found at a fraternity house.
Look at me. Look at me.
Now, I found it at a fraternity house
that you told me
- you never went to.
- I didn't go there.
How did you end up on this camera?
It was outside school after a basketball
game, not at some college party.
See, I don't know what to believe
anymore. I really don't.
You've got fake IDs,
and birth control pills.
What else are you keeping from me?
Look. Look at the date.
That was before the party,
which I wasn't even at.
Who are the girls on the video?
That's Dori and Kate.
They're seniors
that I hang out
with once in a while.
And that's Kate's camera.
They're really cool, and there are only
a couple of juniors that they'll even
talk to.
- Let alone bring along to frat parties.
- I've never gone with them.
Yet?
Do you believe that
Jamie Cowley's a prophet?
I was 19 and a user when I met him.
Jamie was handsome, and...
he cleaned me up.
He'll keep my kids.
And I cannot lose my babies.
I hate to bring up the obvious.
We have to report her to the IRS.
She clearly doesn't
believe in the church.
Her home is registered
as a place of worship.
Only because Cowley makes her.
That's irrelevant.
We just report the facts.
Ok. Fact,
we tell the government,
she's arrested for tax fraud,
she'll lose her children.
I'm not about to serve her up
when I can deliver Cowley instead.
I'm not going to lie to the federal
government about our findings.
I'm going to tell
them exactly what's going on there.
Laws are being violated.
We need to get those kids out of there.
So you're suggesting another waco.
You just bust down the door.
Women and children who
are just too scared to leave?
Well, they're not just going to
go in there and round them up.
We were hired to pursue
the tax fraud angle.
- Let's do our job.
- Except Cowley believes his delusions.
They won't be able to prosecute. All
we'll get is maybe a few scared women.
Then that's all we'll get.
Which one of you's Kate?
And you are?
The man who found your camera.
Where did you get that?
Where did you leave it?
It's mine. Just give it back.
After you've answered a few questions.
Whatever, stranger danger.
Give me back my camera, or I'll call the cops.
Go ahead.
Tell them all about
filming your friend Susan while
she was in bed with Cabe.
Which one of you recorded it?
Neither of us. Susan did it.
Susan did it.
At least that's the truth.
I told you we should have never brought
her along. She was being such a baby
- about the whole thing.
- What whole thing?
It's a lot more comfortable
talking to us than is the cops.
A bunch of us made a pact
not to have our first time
with a college guy
when we were in college.
High school boys are tools.
You go to A&M to have sex
with college boys.
And we picked a few juniors
we thought were cool enough to hang.
Susan was, totally petrified,
so I gave her my camera.
For proof.
You made her record it?
We made a pact. We needed proof.
After the deed,
she totally wigged out.
She ran out of the room
and left it there.
You feel bad about any of this?
It's just sex.
Now, give up the camera.
It cost my dad, like, $400.
You tell him it's held by
county in evidence.
In fact, the cops, they'll be by later
today, and they'll tell him themselves.
My daughter's Emily Lightman.
You two stay away from her.
- Whatever.
- You stay away from her.
Mr. Reed.
You defend that boy.
You work with his lawyer.
You have the nerve
to come to my home?
I know it's hard for you.
I don't want to make it any harder.
You know what's been hard?
Let me tell you what's hard.
My wife dying 11 months ago
because the insurance carrier said
the treatment she needs
is experimental.
My plant shutting down so some
guy in Paraguay can have my job,
my baby girl on the internet
because some animal filmed ...
I promise you, it's not my intention
to bring you any more pain.
Right, Susan?
I spoke to Kate and Dori.
I think you need to talk to your dad.
I think he deserves the truth.
There's stuff I haven't told you.
Hey, you guys.
Is your mom home?
Catherine...
Hello, Ms. Foster, Mr. Loker.
I called the IRS today.
They assured me that you
wouldn't overstep your bounds,
that they'd hate to see
my civil rights violated.
But I'm sure
that's not your intention.
Of course not.
I can see that you have a
fondness for children, Gillian,
but I sense that you have none
of your own.
Perhaps the animosity I feel
from you is misdirected at me.
My seed flourishes...
Buddy.
While yours, doesn't.
I can help you.
You and I can pray together.
Many of the female members
couldn't conceive in the outside world,
but when they came here, we prayed,
and they conceived.
Your problem isn't biological.
It's spiritual.
I don't need you to help me pray.
Today's the last day
of your court order.
Gather your things. You're
no longer welcome here.
He must have looked you
up online or something.
It's a cold read.
It's a carnival trick.
I've taken all the facts of
this case into consideration.
And I've decided to drop all
charges against Cabe McNeil.
What?
The extenuating
circumstances of this case are such
He violated my daughter.
She's a kid.
He's a 22-year-old man.
He had a reasonable belief
that she was of age.
It was filmed!
It's out in the world forever!
The only one who
gets punished is my daughter?
- Come on!
- Mr. Reed. it was a tough decision.
This is the way
the system always works.
You're the prosecutor. Do your job!
The system has to make someone pay.
My job gives me
prosecutorial discretion,
and I am using it here.
Your daughter went to the party
with intent of having sex.
She lied about her age.
- She filmed it.
- She's the victim!
In this case,
Cabe McNeil is a victim, too.
Come on, Susan.
Excuse me.
Jay, I don't know what to say.
How about "I'm sorry"?
Could you please get my
daughter's jacket now? Now?
I'm not a bigot, Zoe.
I filed the charges
because I follow the law.
And the only reason I had a
problem with you in school was
you made law review, and I didn't.
Jay, I am sorry.
Good job on the case.
Next time,
I'm knocking you in the dirt.
Mr. Reed. Hold on a minute.
Hold on a sec.
I think I know what
you're going to do.
I'm fine now.
Your hand says otherwise.
Don't go off to Cabe.
It will just make
matters worse for yourself.
Think about your daughter.
She's all I'm thinking about.
- I thought you were done.
- We just have a couple more questions.
Actually, just one more question.
Are you ready to leave?
What's going on?
You need to leave here
before Jamie sees us.
No, actually...
I want you to leave.
What is that?
It's a safehouse. It's a licensed
non-profit for battered women.
They'll take you and your children and
find you a place to stay,
- they will never reveal your location.
- Are you out of your mind?
He'll find me. He'll bring me back
and make me a prisoner.
You already are a prisoner.
You're helping her kidnap the man's children.
- That is not the way to do this.
- The van's leaving in 30 seconds.
Come on. It's your last chance.
I'm going with or without you,
and I'm taking them with me.
Come on, guys.
Thank you.
Go around.
Come on, guys. Around the car, ok?
Catherine, what are you doing?
Those are my children, Catherine!
Don't... Catherine, stay here!
That was a big mistake.
You aided and abeted the escape
of the only possible person
we could have prosecuted.
I have no idea where the van came from,
and I had nothing to do
with Catherine's departure.
Mr. Cowley tells a different story.
Mr. Cowley believes he's
a prophet sent from God.
He's delusional.
You don't play games with the IRS.
Mr. Loker,
you've been very quiet.
you have anything to add?
What Foster said is accurate.
You tell Lightman he's going to have
an auditor with a microscope
up his british keister
for as long as I have a job.
Why did you do that?
You got to have faith in something.
I'm putting mine in you.
Thank you.
Doesn't mean what you did was right.
Dc. Foster to the lab,please.
I'll be right there.
Thanks. I appreciate that.
Reynolds called in a favor.
He's got a cop watching Cabe.
What's going on?
I need fresh eyes on this.
I think that the dad is going
- to take a run at Cabe.
- Do you really think he'd go that far?
He doesn't want blame his daughter,
He's directing all
of his anger at Cabe.
People have trouble accepting when
females are the sexual aggressors.
It's like the Bonobo chimp...
Not now, Loker.
Not now.
Play it again.
You're the prosecutor. Do your job!
Just play it again. Play it again.
No, let it play.
Make someone pay.
Listen to his words.
The system is at fault.
"The system has to make someone pay."
- Oh, hell.
- What?
Call the police.
He's not going after Cabe.
Someone has to pay.
Did you see his face?
Yeah.
He's at peace.
Come in.
How you doing, love?
I'm just thinking about Susan.
She doesn't have a mom,
and now, her dad's in prison.
What's going to happen to her?
I don't know, love. I don't know.
She was just excited
that the older girls liked her.
I was excited that they liked me.
Now, a man's dead, and...
Susan doesn't have any family.
How did all of this get so messed up?
See, this is what I mean
about consequences, love.
Can't predict them.
And when it comes to you,
that's what scares me the most...
The unknown.
I'm sorry.
It's all good.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Be good.