Hi, it's Marla.
I changed my mind.
I can't do this right now.
You're here?
At the club?
I can't meet you.
I have to get back to my daughter.
Mom?
Mom.
Mom! Where are you?
You don't trust me.
It's such a control thing.
Admit it.
You're reluctant
to leave me in charge.
- Rubbish.
- Then why haven't you gone yet?
What?
Why are you trying to get rid of me?
You haven't had a vacation
in 6 years, Cal. Come on.
- You are trying to miss your flight.
- I'm not.
I am not.
I am trying to find
the Anderson file.
I've got it, all right?
I can take care of it.
Stop stalling.
Where are you going?
Honestly, Cal.
The cab is outside waiting for you.
Grab your jacket and let's go.
You deserve this.
- Emily's waiting for you.
- Don't push me.
Come on, let's go.
Here.
Give me your cell phone,
you don't need to check in.
It's just gonna stress you out.
No kicking and screaming?
I have absolute faith in you.
And my staff.
Here I go, then.
Have a good time.
Are you really working?
We've only been here 2 days.
You really need to learn
how to relax, dad.
People who can't relax die younger.
I learned that in health class.
Don't worry about me, love.
- What are you looking at, anyway?
- Nothing.
You're spying on the office?
I'm my own boss.
That's a 24/7 job.
When I'm a stressed-out workaholic,
I'll have you to thank.
When did you become
such a know-it-all?
We had an agreement
that if I behave maturely,
you'd treat me like an adult.
As an adult, I'm telling you to relax
and stop it
with the creepy snooping.
If you don't,
I'll just go pick up boys by the pool.
All right, deal.
- I'll have one of those too, thanks.
- Make it a virgin.
Dr. Cal Lightman?
My name's Lou Nemeroff.
I'm with the american embassy.
There's an urgent matter
that we need your help with.
An american woman, Marla Seeger,
disappeared 2 days ago
from the Oceano Hotel.
It's just down the beach.
She was last seen at the hotel bar.
This is local news footage.
This is the bartender who last saw her.
He says that she was drunk,
coming on to several men, and that
she eventually left with one of them.
The local police,
they aren't doing anything.
They believe
that she left voluntarily.
She's a really good mom.
I just want to find her.
Mom, if you're watching this,
please come back.
And that's her 12-year-old daughter.
Oh, my god, that's so sad.
What's the D.O.S. doing about this?
Their official policy is to leave it
in the hands of local authorities.
So nothing.
They're doing nothing.
Which makes me wonder
why you're here.
Your boss doesn't know
about this little field trip of yours.
I can't ignore what's
going on in Mexico.
Which is?
More than 200 americans have gone
missing in the last few years,
mostly collateral damage
from the drug cartels,
but unless it's some pretty blond teen,
nobody even wants to talk about it.
All I need to know
is if somebody on this video
is trying to hide something.
The detective in charge of the case
and the bartender.
Dr. Lightman,
can you help us find Marla Seeger?
- Dad.
- What?
Come on.
Some people at the hotel,
they said that they saw your mom crying.
Why was she sad?
I don't know.
Everyone's saying she was a bad mother,
but she always took good care of me.
I'll bet she did.
You think you can find her?
Absolutely.
He's definitely gonna find your mom.
I don't know.
I don't know, love.
You ever think that
grownups are full of crap?
Lots of times.
Usually,
it's 'cause we've made a mistake,
done something wrong,
but we don't want to talk about it,
we don't want to admit it.
Which makes us hypocrites.
I think you've got a secret.
And you're too scared
to talk about it.
Mom always picks awful boyfriends,
so I signed her up
for an online dating service.
This is a guy you found for her?
He said he traveled a lot
and I told him we're coming here.
What did he say?
He said he'd meet me.
I wasn't aware of this.
J-Rod25.
My mom was supposed
to have dinner with him last night.
What if he did something to my mom?
We rushed over here right away.
Did we hear right?
3 patients have been infected
by tainted blood?
The first patient died this morning
at Cottage Hospital,
and the second is in critical condition
at St. Mary's.
This is Gary Spar,
the third patient to receive
a blood transfusion during surgery.
It should have been a routine operation,
but he never woke up.
I need you to seal off that O. R.
And gather and test everything.
So 3 different patients
at 3 different hospitals?
It's no longer a coincidence.
We shut down
the D. C. Central blood bank.
Go help Pat rule out
any other possible contaminants.
We're in a real quandary.
We need to protect people,
but if there's no blood available
for trauma cases and other emergencies,
patients may die anyway.
Do you have any idea
what's in the blood?
Worst case scenario,
it's a biological or a chemical agent.
The FBI has been alerted
in case this is bioterrorism.
I know. I'm on my way
to the hospital CEO, right now.
- What can we do to help?
- The people who have access
to those blood units
all claim no involvement
or knowledge.
I need to know who we can trust.
- Should we get Lightman back here?
- I can take care of this.
- Hey.
- Hey. What have you got?
The tainted blood units all came from
the overnight shift at the blood banks.
There were 2 techs on duty.
We're taking them down
to the Lightman Group for questioning.
Dr. Cho, I haven't forgotten about you.
As soon as I have a minute, we'll talk.
That little boy
has sickle cell anemia.
If he doesn't have a blood transfusion
in the next 24 hours,
he could have a stroke.
What if we get the blood
from elsewhere?
There's a real shortage, we're working
on it, but it's gonna take time
we don't have.
Jack, thank God you're here.
Do you know Dr. Foster?
Gillian, lovely surprise.
- What are you doing here?
- The CDC contacted the Rader firm
to help assist you
since Dr. Lightman isn't here.
Where is Cal?
- He's on vacation.
- And hell didn't freeze over?
Now it's a shame he's gone. I was hoping
he and I could bury the hatchet.
- Is there a problem?
- Lightman and I are...
friendly rivals, so to speak.
It won't be a problem.
Will it?
Not at all.
The 2 techs from the blood bank
are here.
So tell me,
what's the deal with Lightman and Rader?
What,
they don't get along or something?
Cal...
despises him.
He thinks all he cares about
is money and publicity.
For once I'm with Lightman on this.
Something tells me
not to trust that guy.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You're the detective
in charge of the Seeger case?
I'm Emily Lightman.
This is Dr. Cal Lightman.
He's a deception expert
- and he works along with the police...
- In the United States.
- This is Mexico.
- No, I knew that.
I knew it.
I saw some news footage,
and I think that the bartender
at Marla Seeger's hotel
is giving false information
about her disappearance.
Dr. Lightman, there is no case here.
We spoke to several
resort employees.
They said she seemed unstable,
more than likely a drug user.
Based on what?
We found several used
needles in her hotel room.
She probably found
a fellow drug user, left with him.
She will be back
when the drugs run out.
I still think you should have another go
at the bartender.
And I think that you and your daughter
should have a very lovely time here.
No, what about the guy
that Tyler said her mom was gonna meet?
- You spoke to Tyler?
- Yeah.
There're many people here who'd not like
you have shown interest in this matter.
Do you understand me?
I'm gonna give you one piece of advice.
Stay out of this.
Mojito, por favor.
And a margarita.
A coke.
Coke for the señorita.
Enjoying your vacation, señor?
Yeah, well, no. I was
until that woman turned up missing.
What's her name again?
- Marla Seeger.
- That's it!
You're the guy on the TV, right?
You saw her that night?
What do you think happened to her?
She was dancing
with many different men.
- She's looking for a good time.
- She left with one of them.
They were sleeping on the beach
or getting high.
What did he look like,
the guy she left with?
Don't let this trouble
get in your head, señor.
Everything is fine.
You're an awful liar,
Miguel.
Now you're terrified.
What is it?
You work for the police?
I'm so sorry, we are closing this bar
while we restock.
Is there a problem?
If you're here on vacation,
please tell us whatever we can do
to make your stay more enjoyable.
If, however,
you're here conducting an investigation,
you're not welcome here.
Torres, it's me.
I need you down here.
Wait, that's for why?
It's a woman's gone missing.
I'll tell you all when you get down.
Just bring something pretty to wear.
Dude, you're gonna find her.
For you,
I will move heaven and earth.
Lightman just called. He needs me
to fly down to Zulia right now.
- He's on a case?
- A woman's missing.
I gotta go.
He's on vacation!
Just give me one sec.
So, how is it working for Cal?
- Been so long, I can't remember.
- I work with Cal.
- I'm an equity partner, you know.
- Good for you.
That means Cal's been working
on his control issues.
- Jack...
- I meant that as a compliment. Really.
He's my mentor. I have nothing
but respect and admiration for the man.
Obviously,
he doesn't feel the same about me.
Cal says he taught you just enough
to be dangerous.
He's the better scientist, no doubt.
I'm not going to apologize
for having ambition
and a better business sense.
If we're gonna work together,
I have some ground rules.
First, I'm the boss around here.
Second, don't try using me
to get back at Cal.
So long as you...
admit that there's just
the tiniest moment happening right now.
Will you admit that?
Romeo and Juliet,
you want to get this show on the road?
People could be dying right now.
You can leave.
Thank you for coming.
Agt. Reynolds, could you escort him out
and bring Ms. Bynes
- to a more private room?
- Sure. Will you come with me, please?
People hiding something never want
to draw attention to themselves.
That was awesome.
The old routine's a little rusty,
but she still works.
I meant what I said
about the ground rules.
And I meant what I said.
Shall we go find out
what Ms. Bynes's hiding?
Nice work.
It was a regular night
at the blood bank. Nothing unusual.
Your boss was about to fire you
for being late too often.
You knew.
Was this retaliation?
She's breathing faster.
Foster's getting somewhere.
You have no idea how good she is.
Lightman doesn't know.
He's a hard time seeing
the true potential of his employees.
What was that?
Little flash of anger
at the infallible Cal Lightman?
You run this entire lab.
But I'll bet Lightman's never showed you
an ounce of appreciation.
So,
you and Lightman...
you had a falling-out,
what, over a case?
Water under the bridge now.
I never knew my own worth
until I got out from under Cal's shadow.
Someday, you'll do that same.
It's been hard for me.
My husband left us.
I'm alone with the kids.
- Voice pitch is higher.
- What's that look there? Shame?
I just went through a divorce
myself.
I can barely get out of bed.
I can't think straight,
I can't do my job right...
people are dying.
You feel guilty,
but you're gonna feel worse
if you keep secrets
and another person dies.
On my last shift, I didn't run
the full testing protocol on the blood.
You have to test on any blood
for different diseases.
I left early. My daughter needed me.
There are so many other safeguards.
I didn't think...
I just...
- I think we have our culprit.
- No, we don't.
Someone else just died
after a transfusion at Euclid Park.
And this patient banked his own blood.
Central blood bank isn't responsible.
You're setting me up on a blind date
with a potential murderer?
Why? He's not your type?
I'll keep an eye on you.
You'll be fine.
- What are the police doing?
- Nothing.
So, we're doing this on our own.
You pulled me off a really big case.
The cdc brought in the Rader firm...
Jack Rader?
He's at the office working with Foster.
What's the problem?
Not sure.
Get in.
Want to see the sights?
My daughter said she saw you.
Who you with?
You with the hotel?
Police?
Drug cartel?
Who's that guy?
He's with the police or drug cartel.
Dont go anywhere.
- How did you find me here?
- I bribed a waitress at the hotel.
The wrong part of town to visit.
You think I should call the cops,
then?
You scared of being seen with me
by the police, are you?
The police told us to say the lady
was looking for a good time,
- that it was her own fault.
- Why?
Zulia depends on tourists.
Something bad happens,
you all disappear, the town dies.
After the lady from Miami
disappeared,
we were told
not to talk to anyone about...
What lady from Miami?
Do you want me to call the cops,
or...
she came here 4 months ago.
She was found dead.
The police kept it out of the news.
We should get out of here.
I'm gonna tell the cabby we're ready.
Did you...
really see Marla Seeger at the bar?
I saw her with one man.
I'm not sure
if she left with him or not.
Was it this guy?
That's him.
I'm positive.
Now go.
Cab's gone.
What?
The cab, it's gone.
Hold that.
I'll give...
200 dollars
to the person
that gives us a ride back
to our hotel.
Where's your car?
We're lucky they didn't kill us
and dump our bodies in a ditch.
That wasn't luck.
The driver was happy
to make some honest money for a change.
You read that?
Speaking of big and flashy...
I need you to find out
what Rader's up to.
- You want me to spy for you?
- No, I don't want you to spy for me.
I just want you to poke about a bit.
I'll do my own spying.
All right. It's just my opinion, but
I think that might be a little overkill.
Your opinion? I don't need your opinion.
I didn't ask for it.
Just do it. All right?
Wait here.
That's my daughter!
- That's my daughter.
- She started talking to me.
You're having a conversation
with my teenage daughter!
She started talking to me.
What?
All right. I'm leaving.
Dad, that was the guy
that Tyler's been emailing.
I know it was, and you shouldn't
have been talking to him. Bloody hell!
- You never said I shouldn't talk to him.
- What am I supposed to do?
Tell you not to do every
potentially life-threatening thing?
- I figured if I kept him talking...
- This is the last thing I need, Emily.
You know, I've got a con man
back in my office!
And I've got you
behaving like Nancy bloody Drew!
I was just trying to help.
Where are you going?
Don't.
I'm lola.
Jerry conway.
Please.
Thank you.
You're a very confident woman, Lola.
I mean that
in the most flattering way.
Then color me flattered.
So, how long you been a masseuse?
Just a couple of years.
Really?
No, seriously. The last guy I dated
was a complete nut job.
- I've been there.
- Really?
Tell me about your last psycho,
I'll tell you about mine.
Least interesting story
does a body shot.
You're on.
I met this weird chick,
Marla, a couple nights ago.
The hospitals trade blood with each
other, but Euclid Park's not at fault.
I've been here 10 years. Yager's been
here 9. We've never had a problem.
We're not the source
of the tainted blood.
How can you be sure?
I can't imagine how.
There's been no change in procedure.
Dr. Foster, here's the blue file
that you needed.
Sorry for the delay.
The blue file?
Thank you.
Do you know what this is, Mr. Dunst?
This is a file all about you.
Background check,
interviews with coworkers,
family, friends.
My team compiled it.
You know, we can scour this
to discover what you're hiding,
but why don't you save us the time?
Tomkins, the new driver
in the lab, is a felon.
He told Yager he left the conviction
off his job application.
And I should have
reported it, but...
Maybe you should talk to him.
He's married, goes online to meet women
while he's on business trips.
He's a schmuck, but he had nothing to do
with Marla's disappearance.
- Are you sure?
- Positive. They met.
She left after like a minute.
He says that she was crying
and talking to some couple in the lobby.
He seems truthful.
I can't believe you told him
I like role-playing and dirty limericks.
Don't knock it
until you've tried it.
Hang on.
You following me?
You have a lovely friend
and daughter.
Is that a threat? 'cause you really
shouldn't be confusing on that.
Not at all, Dr. Lightman.
You sent someone to follow me,
and they threatened my daughter.
I didn't hire him.
Some people here do.
So do the drug cartels.
I warned you not to get involved.
All right. 4 months ago,
another woman went missing,
just like Marla Seeger,
but this one turned up dead.
OK, listen. I insist
that you stop interfering. OK?
The night Marla Seeger disappeared,
she met a man named Jerry Conway.
Then she met a couple outside the bar.
Did you know that?
There is no case here.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a young
woman who killed her own mother.
I think you should talk to this boy.
He's using his anger
to hide something.
She's protecting him,
so just talk to the boy.
How many of your people
are involved in this cover-up?
There is no cover-up.
You may not be a part of it,
but you know one exists, don't you?
The couple that met Marla Seeger
say that she seemed unstable.
You talked to them?
Well, who are they?
Dan and Stacy Felder.
But it's a dead end.
You know, there is a case here.
Actually, there's 2.
But you already knew that, didn't you?
You lucky you survive
to this accident.
Why did you fail to mention your
criminal history on your application?
I was 19 when i stole that car.
If I say I'm a felon,
who's gonna hire me?
They should have done
a background check.
You've been in health care
for a while.
- Do you enjoy it?
- It's very rewarding.
I missed my calling.
I should have been a paramedic.
I mean, the action, the glory...
I mean, this...
- That's real life-and-death stuff.
- It's not too late.
I'm too old.
I don't know how we get
to where we're going.
Are we even aware of our choices?
- What, are they just chatting?
- We're just getting a baseline now.
You know, let me ask you something.
Was your "aha" moment
when you stole that car?
I don't understand the question.
You stole that car and got into
an accident with a 23-year-old kid.
The police found you
cradling his mangled body.
Did you get into health care
because you realized
you could be around blood and
guts and death all the time?
That you wouldn't have to cause
an accident to get sexually stimulated?
Sicko alert.
Pupils dilated. He's aroused.
From talking about blood and guts?
Yeah. They've sussed that out.
What did you put in the blood
at Euclid Park hospital?
- Nothing.
- You want people to suffer and die.
I swear I had nothing to do
with the tainted blood.
I never did anything at Euclid Park.
Speech pattern's back to baseline.
He's probably telling the truth.
So, we're back to square one,
again.
- Why are you being so hard on yourself?
- People are dying,
I can't stop thinking
about that boy with sickle cell,
and I have nothing for the CDC.
If Cal were here,
he would have solved this by now.
I should have just made him come back.
We can do this, OK?
Excuse me.
You can't come in here. Jack.
McKenzie!
How did you get in here?
I'm a reporter who talked her way
into Attica once, remember?
Scheduled surgeries are being canceled
all over DC with no explanation.
Something's going on at the CDC.
And when a little bird told me you were
partnering with the Lightman Group,
my reporter antenna went off.
You have uncanny timing.
Let me fill you in.
Can we do it on camera?
Yeah. Thank you very much.
I'll tell him. All right. Thanks.
So, a woman named
Ramona Posner came here
alone from Miami about 4 months ago.
Ten days after she disappeared,
she was found dead in an alley downtown.
State department and local police
ruled it an accident.
Well, a cynic
might call it a pattern.
By the way, Rader seems to be making
quite an impression at the office.
- Is he, now?
- According to loker,
Foster seems a bit gaga over him.
Lovely.
- God.
- What?
- Is that jealousy?
- No.
Where are you going?
I left my hat out by the pool. Don't
worry, I won't do anything childish.
Why don't you take your extraordinary
powers of observation
down to the pool and use them
to keep an eye on Emily?
You're jealous.
Marla came up to us in the lobby.
She said, "I hope you
experience the great joy I have",
and then she left.
It was bizarre.
You work with the police, right?
Didn't they tell you this already?
But I wanted to hear this
from you two.
Mrs Felder, do you have any idea
why she would approach you like that?
Not true.
We're gonna be late for the airport.
- No, I'll hold that.
- No, I'll get it. I'll get it.
You know, you're never
gonna get that through customs.
Why not?
Because I'm gonna call them. I'm gonna
tell them you got a suspicious package.
That's the kind of pain in the ass
I can be if I don't get the truth.
It was just a hunch.
There's a fertility center here
that matches egg donors with couples.
We're from Canada and it's illegal
to purchase eggs there.
The donors stay anonymous, but they
can choose who they want to donate to.
These are our frozen embryos.
So you thought that Marla Seeger
was your egg donor.
For a moment. But then
we realized that it couldn't be her.
She was nothing like the person
the broker described to us.
You find my mom?
Not yet.
That's lovely.
Welcome to the age when they need you
but think they're smarter than you.
She always was.
All right, I've got one for you.
Marla Seeger was a waitress
in a diner, right?
Ramona Posner was a teacher's aide.
How do two women like that
afford fabulous trips to Zulia?
How?
Marla Seeger came here
as an egg donor.
She was giving herself
hormone injections.
Right. And the needles
that the cops found.
Hence the mood swings.
- Can I help you?
- Cal Lightman?
Yeah, he's here.
Just the man I wanted to see.
You need to call in some
of those embassy resources.
Can't.
Someone from the police department
called my boss. I've been reassigned.
And threatened.
Our egg donors have high IQs,
are from stable backgrounds.
They don't have drug, alcohol,
or mental health problems,
and many of them are star athletes.
How specific can we be
in how the donors look?
I have a couple here,
they're seeking someone at least 5'9",
blond, blue-eyed, athletic,
and an Ivy League school.
We found a match yesterday.
It's only 50,000.
In the states,
it would be double that.
We're in here.
How do you harvest the eggs, then?
Our reproductive endocrinologist,
Dr. Alvarez,
he's responsible for everything.
- How much do you pay the donors?
- The fee is generous.
Plus they get a free trip to Zulia.
But no one does it for the money.
They just want to help
the right couples have a child.
- That's wonderful, that's wonderful.
- Yeah, it's great.
We actually are looking for a donor
with blue eyes and light-brown hair.
And 5'6".
I think I can arrange that.
Thought you were gonna say that.
Dr. Alvarez, these are the Garrs.
Pleased to meet you.
May I talk to you, please?
Can it wait?
No, no. We've gotta
shove off anyway.
- We gotta go.
- We've got to think.
Yes. I mean, it's a big decision.
I've got a question for you,
Dr. Alvarez.
We've been told
that my wife's infertility
is due to an estrogen imbalance
caused by the coriolis effect.
Is that possible?
That could very well be true.
Did you see Wynn when I described Marla?
Flared nostrils, quick breath?
- He's in this.
- There's no way all those donors
- fit the criteria he described.
- Wait. See, they don't have to.
They find donors like Marla Seeger
who are desperate for money.
They insist the donors
remain anonymous.
Wynn can give the buyers
any description he wants.
- It's a con.
- Yeah, absolutely it's a con.
Isn't the coriolis effect
something about the earth's rotation?
- Exactly.
- Alvarez agreed with your theory.
That's because Alvarez is not a doctor.
He's a fake.
I'm in charge of blood orders here,
and Yager coordinates trades.
For the other hospitals in DC.
So why did I have to reinterview
these two guys?
Because we've got nothing else.
He's exhibiting extreme control.
He could still be hiding something.
No, voice pitch is steady.
Dunst isn't lying.
But why does Yager
keep looking behind him?
And why is he anxious?
What'd I miss?
- What happened to the reporter?
- I took care of her.
That could mean so many things.
- So the story won't be on the news?
- That's what you wanted, right?
Did Cal brainwash you
into thinking I'm kind of
media whore without scruples?
Come on, tell me you got something,
'cause the tox screen's all negative.
And the CDC is getting
all kind of calls from reporters.
I can charm one reporter, I can't
control the entire fourth estate.
We had the 5-car pile-up
on the beltway...
Wait.
Something's different.
I had to change the battery,
so we took a little break.
But they're both more relaxed now,
and Yager's not looking behind him.
Go back to before the break.
He was looking at that.
They got rid of it.
Why didn't they want us to see it?
- What can we do for you?
- We need to take a look around.
How often do you give blood?
Every 6 weeks or so. I have a rare
blood type. What are you looking for?
- Found it.
- That's sensitive equipment.
What's it for?
Processing patient fluid samples.
Could you be any more vague?
It's positive for narcotics.
So you've been running
a drug lab down here.
Where's Marla Seeger?
- I don't know who that is.
- Not true.
You're the couple
from the office today, no?
Your partner Wynn sold you out,
made a deal with the police.
He said the scam was your idea.
He never said that.
Dr. Alvarez is responsible
for everything.
- A lie.
- I can assure you
it's perfectly true.
What happened to her?
She was one of our egg donors.
She wasn't doing well
on the hormone treatments.
She wanted to get the procedure
over with. Then she changed her mind.
Wynn brought her in anyway.
This is all his doing.
What happened to Marla?
I started the egg extraction,
but there were complications and
I punctured something.
She started to bleed.
So where is she?
Wynn has an apartment.
She's dying.
One more day,
we would have lost her.
Listen, how did you know
that I wasn't part of the coverup?
When I accused you,
you showed genuine anger, not guilt.
About that man you sent
to threaten my daughter.
That wasn't me, that was my boss.
You sure this man
was part of the cartels?
If I was you, I'd keep him
away from the evidence locker.
I'll keep an eye on my boss, too.
Rader and Foster busted a drug lab.
He's saying she's brilliant and has...
All right, keep it to yourself.
Lou from the embassy
asked me to stay...
Lou from the embassy?
That's nice.
He asked me to stay few more days.
I said yeah, is that all right?
And here I was thinking
we were happily married.
The two techs were making
designer fentanyl in the hospital lab.
They were using the blood
as a means of transport.
Liquid fentanyl was
injected into the blood bags,
which would then be delivered to all the
heroin processing centers in the city.
A lab within a lab.
Pretty ingenious.
Problem was, the new guy Tomkins
picked up the wrong bags one day.
And the fentanyl never triggered any
alarms in the patient tox screen because
it's a common anesthetic
used for surgery.
Sorry I'm late.
They filled you in?
I guess we'll reopen
the central blood bank
and track down all the units
that left Euclid Park hospital.
Thanks to you.
You should both know that I taped
an interview with McKenzie Dodd.
Should be airing in about an hour.
How could you do that?
The CDC hasn't had
the press conference.
I forgot.
You love the spotlight.
I promised an exlcusive
to buy us time.
This was all about getting back at Cal
and the Lightman Hroup, wasn't it?
You know me too well.
- It was fun.
- Bye, Jack.
Here's my card.
In case you plan on making
a life change.
Thanks, man.
Well, it's been a very tense time,
but the threat has been eliminated.
Dr. Cho credits you with helping
a little boy with sickle cell anemia.
I knew he was slick, but, man...
Could I just say that I owe a debt
of gratitude to Dr. Gillian Foster,
who really cracked this case.
This potential health disaster
wouldn't have been averted without her.
Mommy!
So you're saying that
you can just treat me like a child
whenever you want to.
No, I'm not.
I'm saying that on occasion,
it's my right as a parent
to be suspicious and overprotective.
Then on occasion,
I reserve the right
to throw tantrums
and spend all your money.
Deal.
Now, if you're done forcing me to work,
can i have my holiday back, please?
How do you learn to live longer?
Well, there's meditation and yoga,
but for you,
I'd definitely say do both.
Yoga's that thing you do in a lounge
chair with a mai-tai in your hand?
Yeah, it is.
"Don't hate me too much
because I'm filled with admiration."
Give it to me.
So who sent the flowers, then?
Because you know I'm the jealous type.
Welcome home, Cal.
Rumor has it you never even left town,
but that can't be true
because you look like a different man.
I feel like a different man.
You know, a vacation is a
wonderful thing, 6 days of nothing.
Well, i heard you were working
on a case.
Well, it barely qualifies as a case.
I feel so relaxed that...
I don't even care
that Rader was here.
Then Torres told you.
He sent you the flowers, then?
Have you checked them for aphids?
No, no, I don't care.
- Did he see any of my research?
- I kept him out of your library.
- And is everyone still here?
- He didn't poach anyone.
And did he break
into the office supply closet?
He definitely didn't do that.
Except one thing,
the sprinkler system
was acting up a little bit.
That's odd.
What exactly happened
between you and Rader?
I'd tell you,
but you'd think I was lying.
My card. Just in case
you're thinking of making a life change.