Joe, what's your 20?
Almost done with rounds.
Just checking the carousel.
You need some backup?
I'm falling asleep here.
No. But could you leave
a cupful of coffee in the pot?
Anyone back here?
This is private property.
I'm gonna give you 5 seconds
to come on out.
Funny, Don.
I'm a man of simple pleasures,
and that was one of them.
What are you doing back here?
Switching out a timing belt.
Thought I saw someone
messing around.
Nah, it was just me.
It wasn't you.
- Turn it off.
- What?
Turn it off!
What?
Ed?
- Go ahead.
- You need to send that backup.
I see checkmate in 5.
What do you see?
I see it in 3.
- We've missed you out here.
- Thank you.
Thanks. I, uh, I had
to take a little break.
How come?
I used to play with
a co-worker friend of mine.
He's probably the best mind
I ever went up against.
One day, he just decided that
he didn't want to play anymore.
So you gave up, too?
Just the opposite.
I attempted to play
through every permutation
of moves on a chessboard.
- That's an infinite number of games.
- It's not infinite. It's just...
it's exponentially large.
You couldn't have played
through them all.
There's an average
of 40 moves per chess game,
and I'll tell you something the more
I played, the more I realized that
every single match,
every single chess game,
is really just a simple variation
on the exact same theme.
You know?
It's aggressive opening, patient
mid-game, inevitable checkmate,
and I realized why my friend quit.
He was tired of repeating
the exsame patterns
and expecting a different outcome.
So you have a lifetime
of chess strategy in your head
- and you're just sitting on it.
- I still use it.
I just, uh...
I apply it differently.
I have to go.
It was good seeing you.
Rita Stuart, 25,
second victim in Atlantic City.
Pretty public spot for a dump site.
You know, technically, I think it
would qualify more as a disposal site.
You don't leave a body on a
merry-go-round out of convenience.
He took some time with her
appearance, didn't he?
Her nails were polished, her hair
was cut, clothes were brand-new.
Wants her to look her best when found.
That's a lot of remorse.
- Who is victim number one?
- Stacia Jackson, 29.
- She was found at a local playground.
- A change in victimology.
What's the connection
between these women?
There is none. Rita was married,
Stacia was single.
Rita worked at a diner,
Stacia was a corporate lawyer.
According to their credit cards, they
never came within 10 miles of each other.
Both women were taken 2 months ago?
Yeah. They lived such
completely different lives,
the police didn't tie their
abduction together until now.
Was there any evidence
of sexual assault?
There was no evidence
of violence of any kind.
So how did they die?
Rita had a stroke,
Stacia had a brain hemorrhage.
Look at this, the unsub gave
them a battery of drugs...
Atracurium, Doxacurium.
These are neural inhibitors.
They block signals from
the brain to the muscles.
He put them in medical comas
for 2 months.
Actually, they weren't in a coma.
You'd need phenobarbital
to keep them unconscious,
and they didn't have that.
So, wait a minute. These victims were
paralyzed but they were still conscious?
They could open their eyes, hear,
probably even feel stimulation.
Physical immobility
but mental awareness.
This unsub wants total
domination over them.
And he turns their bodies
into prisons to do it.
Mildred Lisette Norman wrote,
"Anything you cannot relinquish
"when it has outlived
its usefulness,
"possesses you,
"and in this materialistic age,
a great many of us are
possessed by our possessions."
Keeping women in a conscious
paralysis reads as sadism.
Definitely dehumanizing,
reducing them to objects.
But there's nothing else about this
profile that takes us down that path.
These women were found
in excellent condition.
There was no evidence of bed sores,
they were well fed through an I.V.
His access to I.V.S and drugs...
he almost certainly
has medical training.
Are we sure this is a he?
The care this unsub
shows these victims,
although they are dehumanized,
- the profile says female.
- What about the postmortem posing?
That's a lot of dead weight
for a woman to carry.
These women are petite.
They're under 100 pounds.
All right, if we reconsider the gender
of the profile, what changes?
Nothing.
If anything, it fits better.
Men kill to fulfill a sexual
compulsion. Women don't.
You see this in angel of mercy killers,
like Genene Jones and Amy Archer.
They didn't care about race
or hair color. It's men that do.
Damn straight.
Men do.
Well, hello, red.
Look at you. Guys.
What did you find
out about the clothing
the unsub's dressing the victims in?
At first only that both
garments were made from chiffon,
but with the wonder twin powers
of the Atlantic City police
and my impeccable eye for fashion,
we have also determined that these
garments fit ridiculously well.
They're super flattering to each
victim's exact measurements,
kind of exactly like the unsub
whipped them up herself.
Maybe that's what
connects the victims.
How so?
Maybe she isn't just
killing petite women
because they're easier
to abduct and pose
but because of a physical type.
She wants a body type.
Sewing clothes for a specific size
of woman.
Please tell me she is not killing these
women because she needs human models.
I mean, there's gotta
be more to it than that.
There probably is.
But at least we have
a start on the victimology.
Prentiss and Morgan, I want you
to interview the victims' families.
Talk to them
about lifestyle choices.
Any body image issues
these women may have had.
Reid, go to Rita Stuart's autopsy,
see if the drugs point to any specific
medical training the unsub might have had.
Dave and I will go
to the disposal site.
Sir.
I want you to check missing persons
reports for the last 2 months.
See if any abductions
match what we know.
We need to find out if the unsub's
already taken another victim.
- Agent Jareau?
- Detective Marty Cotrone.
Hi. These are ssas
Morgan and Prentiss.
- Were you able to contact the families?
- They're already here.
Did they bring the pictures
we asked for?
Yeah.
They were pretty confused by that.
And to be honest, so am I.
Agent Morgan, I don't understand.
How does what my daughter
looked like have to do
with the monster who killed her?
We think the unsub is
looking for a physical type.
Fit but petite.
This is her.
This is my wife.
Did Rita work out, stay in shape?
Sure.
I guess.
She went to the gym
at least 3 times a week.
Stacia took pride in every
aspect of her appearance.
- In what way?
- You know, her clothes.
It was her clothes.
She loved to shop.
It looks like she has kind
of a bohemian streak going on.
Yeah.
What were her favorite
places to shop?
High-end boutiques.
- Expensive ones?
- Certainly.
- And dressed to fit.
- She was tiny.
Everything had to be taken in
so she'd look...
Her best.
Would you mind writing down
some of her favorite places to go?
So these are mostly
consignment and thrift shops?
That's really all we could afford.
Did she ever have
these clothes altered?
Tailored to fit her better?
I never really paid attention.
Would she ever...
have worn something like that?
Would she ever wear
anything like that?
No.
Dave!
- Can you hear that?
- Yeah.
She's posing her victims in a place
that represents innocence
and childhood.
Most serial killers don't have
a particularly happy childhood.
My guess is she wants them to have
the fun she never got to have.
Let's think about how she's
doing this practically.
How's she getting them
from her car to the carousel?
She's moving a body
in the middle of the night.
She needs to make conditions
as favorable as possible.
So she'd need a vehicle
that afforded her privacy...
a van or an SUV.
That's still a lot of ground
to cover once she parks.
Even if these women are light,
she risks getting caught
carrying a corpse.
If she has a medical background,
what if she used a wheelchair,
something that would help
her move them quickly?
And if she has a wheelchair,
that means her van has a lift,
which would be helpful
to unload a body.
Which also means she has
a handicap placard.
Which would give her
the closest place to park.
I'll have Garcia pull all vehicles
with handicap registrations.
Thanks, Dave.
Once I have the knees bent,
I can get leverage under her.
Normally, an assistant helps me.
But I can do it
by myself if I need to.
I'm assuming the unsub would
have this training, too.
Let me ask you this is there
anything specific about it?
No, any caregiver out
there can do this...
Docs, nurses, orderlies.
Where do you think she's getting
the drugs that she's using?
Do you think she could be manipulating
a doctor or a pharmacist, maybe?
He'd be criminally
negligent if she was.
But it is possible.
I mean, doctors order things
through residents,
nurses forge signatures,
prescriptions fall through cracks.
That's a lot of drugs
and a lot of cracks.
She keeps these women
paralyzed for 2 months.
Your report said both of them
had hair extensions clipped in.
Yes, to hide the fact that clumps
of their real hair had fallen out.
But if they were fed through I.V.S,
that wasn't from malnutrition, right?
You see this a lot
in bedridden patients.
Loss of motor function.
Especially in a young woman like this.
Of course.
Psychic shock.
Yeah, the mental effects
take a physical toll.
One last question in
your professional opinion,
do you think the hair extensions were
clipped on before or after death?
Before.
And you seem pretty
certain of that?
You know the old wives' tale
about your hair and nails
growing after death.
What's really happening
is that dehydration
is shrinking your skin,
pulling it back.
Based on where
she put these extensions,
they were definitely still alive.
Now, we know this unsub is
stuck in a rich fantasy, right?
An incredibly detailed delusion.
We don't know what the delusion is,
but we know that it involves
remaking these women,
and it begins the moment
she has them drugged.
So she has them paralyzed
and she can do whatever she wants,
- why is she killing them?
- Well, I don't think she means to.
The brain is a machine
designed to respond to stimuli.
If you keep the brain awake
but the body immobile,
it breaks down, loses its hair.
After 2 months,
it eventually strokes out.
So death isn't this unsub's goal,
it's an unfortunate side effect.
Exactly.
What'd you find out?
Both Rita Stuart and Stacia Jackson
were clothes hounds,
but because they were petite women,
they had a lot of their stuff altered.
Could be how our unsub
is finding her victims.
She gets her hands
on their measurements.
But we already exhausted tailors,
alteration shops. There's no overlap.
The tailors might send specialty
items out to third parties.
Dig deep into extended
employment records
and see who they might
be subcontracting to.
Garcia needs to talk to us.
Go ahead, Garcia.
Hello, my pretties. I have
finished my missing persons sweep.
I've got nothing on the medical vehicle,
but 2 new matches on the clothes
make the woman front.
Cindy Admundson. she was abducted
outside a thrift store,
and maxine wynan was last
seen at the hillridge mall.
That sounds like our girl.
Any surveillance footage at the mall?
No. It was an outside parking lot.
So sorry.
The new abductees
what's their physical type?
They look pretty tiny to me.
I'm gonna send you pictures.
Also, if it pleases the court,
I would like to direct
your attention to exhibit "a,"
the calendar map.
What about it?
Both of these new victims
were abducted one week ago,
exactly one day before
the bodies of Rita Stuart
and Stacia Jackson, respectively,
turned up.
She doesn't let a body go
until she has a replacement.
Thank you so much.
Excuse me.
Do you need some help?
the ramp's broken.
You want me to call a tow truck?
I just need to get
the chair in the van,
and then I can go home.
Well, we could load it.
You think?
Sure.
We'll put it in the back?
Go on in.
You pull, I'll lift.
Ok.
one, two
three
Do we need to lock the wheels
or anything like that?
You're so pretty.
Victim is mary newsome.
Abducted 2 months ago.
She was found on this bench
first thing this morning.
Ok, well, it looks like her style.
It's chiffon, and it's sewn to fit.
If she's disposed of this body, it
means she's recently taken a new victim.
We'll call hotch, we'll comb through missing
persons reports from the last 48 hours.
I'll pulling them.
Thank you.
What?
These aren't hair extensions.
Maybe her hair was too brittle.
Maybe.
I don't know.
You know what?
This is a wig.
Kanekalon, I think.
What's that?
Synthetic hair.
There's nothing special about it.
It's used in wigs all over the world.
But look at this.
Are those stitches?
On her scalp.
She sewed this in.
Yeah. Wallace.
I got it. Thank you.
Hey, I think we found who
was taken last night.
Her name is Bethany Wallace.
Her husband says she never came
home from the dry cleaners
where she stopped off
to pick up some clothes.
Anybody at the cleaners see anything?
The employees were busy locking up.
But they did mention
that they do farm out work
to tailors who work from home.
Good. We can match records based
on who worked on Bethany's clothes.
We just got the pictures of
the 2 recent abductions from Garcia.
Line up the photos of the new victims
next to the bodies they replaced.
That might help us with the timeline.
You guys see this?
Yeah. She's matching up
the victims physically one to one.
She's a collector.
We're ready to give the profile.
The unsub we're looking for is a woman.
She's a collector.
It's a psychopathology
similar to hoarding.
So when we say collector,
we're not talking about
stamps or baseball cards.
It's not what your kids, or even you,
might pursue as a normal hobby.
This is an attachment to objects
that's become obsessive,
by someone who is antisocial
and extremely introverted.
These people attach a part of
themselves to their collection.
If you try to separate them from it
or take it away from them,
they will react violently,
even psychotically.
They've suffered damage
to their prefrontal cortex.
That's the part of the brain
that regulates
basic freudian fantasy/reality.
They can still function, like drive a
car, go to work, even do their taxes
In fact, she excels
at goal-oriented jobs,
like the precision of sewing.
Or the details of abduction.
But they've lost their ability
to categorize the difference
between living and dead,
uh, belonging and loss.
That has been irreparably destroyed.
So, what's she collecting, women?
Actually,
we think she's collecting dolls.
Technically, replacing them.
We believe that
she lost the originals
sometime within the last 3 months,
and this is what served
as her stress room.
She searched for a replacement,
and when she couldn't find them,
she started abducting
the closest possible surrogate.
Women of different ethnicities
but of similar physicality.
The drug-induced parasis
is part of the fantasy.
She puts her victims in a position
where they can't talk back
so she can fetishize them
like the objects she's lost.
Look.
I respect your analysis,
but this woman kidnapped 6 women
and killed 3 of them.
And you're telling us
this is about dolls?
This unsub stitched a wig onto
the scalp of her latest victim.
It's a technique used
to attach hair to porcelain dolls.
And keep in mind,
collectors and serial killers
do share certain traits.
A lot of serial killerstake tro,
attaching the same significance
to them that this collector
does to objects.
But this unsub's
intent isn't violence.
She needs this collection
to be complete
so sheaneel in control of her life,
probably to overcome some
trauma she experienced.
She really only feels that control
when the collection is complete,
which is why she's repeating an
abduction pattern with living victims.
If she loses a doll, or in this case,
if she loses a woman
who represents a doll,
she has to replace it.
This woman works alone.
We know she has medical training.
Look for nurse's aides or orderlies
who we fired for a lack
of social grace
she can't fake a bedside manner.
We believe she's currently working
as a tailor or a seamstress,
and we're following those leads now.
But do let us know
if you notice any overlap
in your suspect pools.
Thank you.
Of course I remember Ms. Jackson.
We were all sad to hear
what happened.
Do you ever farm
out tailoring jobs,
someone who might have done this?
No.
To be perfectly honest,
we wouldn't even sell
something so dated.
Let me take a look.
Where did you get this?
Why?
Did you see something?
Look at this lockstitch.
It's a handkerchief pattern.
You see this on
silk-sewn handkerchiefs.
And it's all done by hand.
So this is her signature?
This is unique to her.
I couldn't do it,
not even with a machine.
If there someplace that specializes
in handcrafted sewing like this?
I'll tell you this much, though.
She's been at it a long time.
This woman...
is an artist.
Hotch, this is Bethany Wallace's sband karl.
We brought him in for questioning.
Do you know where my wife is?
We're searching for her, sir.
No. You have to find her
in the next 24 hours.
Bethany is a diabetic.
Look, agent Prentiss said
that the woman who took her
has medical training.
So... Bethany could have a chance?
What?
She keeps her victims
in a drug-induced state.
They can't communicate.
These...
These drugs, will they...
we don't know.
But we're doing everything we can.
Everyone, this is Sally.
Be nice to her.
So, doctor, if a diabetic were given
this battery of drugs
to keep her paralyzed,
what would the reaction be?
Diabetics metabolize everything
they consume differently...
Food, drinks, drugs.
It all gets broken
down to blood sugar
at varying rates.
Most likely, this patient seized up
minutes after she was medicated.
So she's already dead.
Probably.
Although...
there is another possibility.
Bethany's condition could
break down the drugs
faster than the other victims.
She could regain control of her body?
Every hour that she doesn't
turn up is a reason for hope.
We're still running out of time.
If the drugs don't kill Bethany,
she's not gonna last
long without insulin.
Look, collectors are good,
honest people.
Just because you enjoy dolls doesn't
make you a freak or a pedophile.
We appreciate that, sir, but the
woman that we're looking for
has lost her ability
to control her obsession.
She's killed 3 women trying
to recreate a type of doll
she had as a child.
Describe the line to me.
Well, there's a pattern to the victims.
They're in their 20s,
and they're petite.
Most doll lines revolve
around infants.
Is she dressing them like babies?
No, she's not.
Their wardrobe consists
of chiffon dresses,
worn by one blond woman,
a redhead, and a black woman.
The dresses...
is she sewing them herself?
How did you know that?
It's the valois line.
Local company,
back in the late eighties.
Probably when our
unsub was prepubescent.
They promoted feminism
and multiculturalism.
Strong, independent girls
from different backgrounds
who could still be friends.
Reid.
Birth certificate to fill out.
A form to describe their lives.
And a kit to sew your own clothes.
JJ said she's been at it for a while.
She's probably been sewing
since she was a little kid.
Wait a minute. Sir,
what's this contest that they held?
That was to see who could come up
with the most imaginative doll.
Sew a dress.
Write an essay to describe her.
If you won the contest, you'd have
your doll featured in next year's line.
I assume that didn't
end well, did it?
No, it did not.
It's a classic tool
child psychologists use.
Tell me a story with these dolls.
When the company got essays
with thinly-veiled references
To physical or sexual abuse,
they turned the entry forms
and the dolls over to the police.
The publicity killed the line.
You said the company was local, right?
They might still have
the clothes in evidence.
How are the essays going?
Makes for some pretty depressing reading.
Prentiss is having a good time.
These dolls are all like
little time capsules,
only the eighties fashion
wasn't so kind to them.
I'm surprised how many little girls
knew how to make shoulder pads.
How's it going on your end?
I got a list of vendors
the victims went to...
tailors, seamstresses, that sort of thing.
Hey, JJ, you said something
about a handkerchief hem, right?
That's exactly like what
she sews for her victims.
What's the name on the entry?
Samantha Malcolm.
She's on my list.
Wait a minute, guys. I have her
essay around here somewhere.
Right here.
"sally doesn't like the
room with the lightning."
That can't be good.
Ok, guys, I just got Samantha
Malcolm's medical records, and...
Oh, my god, she was doomed.
Like emily bronte doomed,
like shakespeare doomed,
like red-shirted ensign
in "Star Trek" doomed.
What happened to her?
Oh, uh sorry, uh,
well, for the first 10 years, nothing,
and then she started a battery
of electroshock treatments.
At 10?
Who subjects a child to ect?
That would be her father,
Dr. Arthur Malcolm.
He runs an inpatient
mental health facility
for troubled young
people called new lives.
At first, the essay that
Samantha wrote raised some flags,
but her father explained
that the therapy
was to deal with the
recent death of her mother.
After that, he started her
on a serious regimen
of anti-psychotic drugs,
which he weaned her off
of a few years ago.
It explains her familiarity
with medication.
Where is she now?
Uh, her father declared
her incompetent,
so he's still the legal guardian.
Everything is in his name.
And all of her records list
new lives as her residence.
She couldn't keep victims
in an inpatient facility.
She needs privacy.
Garcia, what about real estate
holdings in her father's name?
Just his own.
But new lives has
a bunch of outpatient and
halfway houses all over town.
JJ, where does she work?
I have her placed at 3
different shops around town.
All right, let's split up and
cover the shops and the facility.
I want to go to new lives.
Whether or not she's there,
I want to talk to the father.
There are literally hundreds of
therapies to help kids through loss.
Electroshock is not one of them.
Take Rossi.
Be nice to each other.
See you later.
We're leaving.
Phone...
No... No.
I am very confused, gentlemen.
What does this have
to do with Samantha?
We need to talk to her.
Is she here?
No, she's at work.
Does she live here,
or did you move her into
one of your halfway houses?
As a matter of fact,
she is in one of my houses.
Well, we'll need the address.
And I'll need to know what this is about.
She might be tied
to a series of abductions.
That's not possible.
It's not my daughter.
Is Samantha on her own
at this house?
There are no other patients, right?
She thought that was best,
and I agreed.
Yeah, but let's face it...
You're happy that she's out
of your hair.
I beg your pardon?
Because if you had been
visiting her recently, doctor,
you would know what she's been doing.
Samantha has always been troubled.
3 women are dead because of her.
She's not capable of that.
Are you certain?
I mean, the effects of electroshock,
especially at that age, are permanent.
But maybe you knew that.
My wife died when Samantha was 10,
and she never recovered.
I tried everything.
Child psychiatry, pet therapy,
nothing helped.
She was cutting herself.
She was in pain.
That's the end of this meeting.
Where's your daughter, doctor?
And, agent Rossi, if you try
to talk to her,
a mentally ill woman, without
her knowing what she's doing...
Do you know about
the women she's keeping?
And have no medical
or legal counsel present,
you'll have no case.
Do you understand me? None.
We'll keep the police here in case
Samantha drops in for a visit.
Let's go, Reid.
Hey, a really fast question.
Why are these toys here?
I use them in my therapy.
No, I understand that,
but why are they way up on this shelf,
away from where any kids
can actually reach them?
They're reminders of
patients that I've helped.
Let me ask you something.
What was the name of the girl
you helped with this one?
Jenny Larson.
And this one?
What was the name of the girl
you helped with this one?
Abigail Moore.
How about this one?
Linda Krauss.
These girls are what, they're like
9- -9 or 12 years old, I'm assuming?
My ph.D. is on the effect of trauma
on prepubescent girls.
I do not appreciate
what you're implying.
Oh, I'm not implying anything.
I'm making an inference.
An inference is an educated guess.
And based on that,
I form a hypothesis.
For instance, my hypothesis here
is that after you raped your daughter,
you submitted her to electroshock
treatment to make sure she stayed quiet.
This is outrageous.
And then, out of guilt, you bought her toys,
more specifically,
you bought her a line of dolls.
Because that's what serial
molesters do. They give gifts.
So you continued the pattern
with your other patients,
and once they left your care,
you added their toys
to your collection.
I'm sorry, you can't back
up your story, doctor.
This is why I love my job, doctor.
Because my lab, it's a jury of your peers.
My tests will be Jenny Larson,
Abigail Moore,
and Linda Krauss.
The D.A. will put them on the stand,
and I'm going to personally
bring these dolls in,
and we're going to watch how they react.
Or you could tell us where your daughter is
and we'll tell the d.A. You cooperated.
But once we walk out this door,
that deal comes off the table.
2529 Adams Street.
You'll tell them, right?
That I cooperated.
You want to knowow I figured you out?
Those toys.
You take care of them.
These ones you treasured.
But you know what?
The collection's not complete.
Where are they?
She's coming back.
I have to put it back in.
No, please.
- Please, don't.
- I'm sorry.
Don't leave me.
Let us go.
I can't.
Samantha?
Hi.
Uh, my name's Spencer.
I'm with the FBI.
I know what your father did to you,
and I want you to know
that he can never,
ever hurt you again.
He never touched me.
He's a good father.
He loves me.
I know that he probably forced
you to say those things,
and he punished you if you got it wrong,
sent you to the room with the lightning.
Yeah.
The dolls that your father
gave you after he hurt you,
what would happen to them?
He kept them in his office
with the other toys.
That's where he let you play with them?
But when I moved out,
I had to take my friends with me.
I couldn't leave them behind.
Of course.
And so you went you get them.
What... what did you find?
Yeah.
He gave them to another girl, didn't he?
Do you want them back?
He said I couldn't.
He said they were gone for good.
He lied. He's been lying
to you for a long time.
Do you want to see them?
Can I?
Yeah. Yeah,
do you want to play with them?
Clear.
We need medical here.
Hold on.
Hold on one second.
Hey, Samantha?
Listen.
You need to go with these men,
but your friends can go with you, ok?
They won't take...
they won't take them away?
I promise no one will
ever take them away again.
Well done, agent Reid.
Thanks.
Checkmate in 12.
No way.
Let me show you.
Isaac Asimov wrote,
"In life, unlike chess,
the game continuesafter che"